Going on, you know, a lot of happy birthdays. Appreciate that. Thanks for the birthday wishes.
33. It's good to be 33. I'm not almost 40. You know what I mean? So today I've got a few things
to talk about. Let's go over some things. I might sound a little different. That's okay.
I have changed setups. You're not going to believe where I am right now. I could tell you where I am
but you wouldn't believe me, but I don't have the camera set up to prove what's going on.
I am lying on the ground right now. Isn't that interesting? I got like a beanbag chair.
I'm like lying on the ground. I've got a set. I'm like lying down and playing today.
This is gonna be awesome. This is gonna be so cool. I can't wait. Is he zonked? No,
I am absolutely sober, but I'm going into full relaxation mode today. Can you show us? I'll
probably set a camera up here and then I don't know if this is permanent. So this could be
pretty temporary, but I, you know, I just felt like today I'm like, you know what?
I want to like lie down and just, well, I'm not lying on my back. Let's be really honest and clear
here. I'm sitting up, but I'm sitting in like a beanbag chair. It's a, it's not a beanbag chair.
I keep making that up, but I am reclined. He's in a hospital bed. I have really retired. Yeah.
I'm screaming from the, you know, retirement home. Don't fall asleep. No, if anything,
this is going to be, I feel like this is going to be better to stream from. I can just sit back now.
All right. Let's, let's do real talk for a second. I actually have a lot of trouble,
which I've been realizing lately, the last like, I want to say two or three years.
I know it has a lot to do with the chest and back problem, but sitting up,
does anybody else hate sitting up in a chair? Sitting straight up with like my arms up is,
it causes a lot of pain in, especially nowadays. So I was like, you know what? I'm going to try it.
I'm going to try just lying down, like sitting down, sitting back, reclining.
This is a trial run. Let's see how it goes. Yeah. It's going to be back. You can play CS2. I don't
think so. It's way better. Well, if you're sitting up, you want your posture to be good,
but if you're leaning back a little and put my knees up, I bet you in an hour, I talk about how
much I hate this. I'm going to be leaning back like this with, and I'm just going to be like,
I hate this. All right. Give me one second. Let me, I just want to grab a drink. Be right back.
Okay. I got my drink. So is this game any good? I saw this game being played. It looked really fun.
Is it fun? It looks good. What are you drinking? Something really weird.
It's a sun-kissed berry lemonade. We're going full recline streamer mode now. It's all right.
It's pretty good. Going complete food mode. All right. So what, let's go. All right. So what,
what's the best character? Who should I play as? Do they have stats or is it just, they're just
characters? What about Resident Evil 4 DLC? Oh yeah. A hundred percent. Maybe not, not today.
Do the otter? I just burped wicked loud. I really am retired. Did that come through the mic?
That was like, do otter? They're all really cute. They are. I'm going to go. No, no, no.
Ooh, ooh. Maybe royalty-free Garfield. Should I be royalty-free Garfield or all right. We're
going to go with Lloyd. Do I have this stuff? No, I don't. All right. Well, we'll go Lloyd.
So now we just do quick match, right? Is that how this works? You should do dark Lloyd. I can do
dark Lloyd. Oh, I don't have enough money. Okay. Well, let's go do the tutorial. All right. Time
to play. Do you dye your hair still? It's completely natural. Okay. Left and right.
Move on to the next room when you're ready. Let's go. You see that wee thingy that just
popped out? It's pretty sloppy. That is the stamina bar. You need stamina to run,
attack, climb, or carry things around. Okay, there's the stamina bar. Better keep good
track of it at all times. I'm like choking myself. A little run up lets you jump further.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait. Okay. So run up. Wait, what did I miss? Easy. All right.
You can grab everything in the game. Pick up the green cube thing.
Oh, I like lying down and screaming. This is awesome. I'm starting a new trend. Yes,
yes. Just like that. Calling it right now. Now, put the cube thing onto the metal pressure
sensor to unlock the door. Chop, chop. Right here. Easy. This is maximum chill. That's right.
Did I not get it? You didn't invent lying down, but I invented lying down and screaming at the
same time. No, I didn't. Okay. All right. All right. What do I do? Hold X to charge
and then release. That didn't really work. What do you think invented means?
You are the first person to do something. You invented it and then you patented it. See,
the problem is I didn't patent this yet. That's what I need to do. Close enough. Yeah.
See that punching bag? Time to learn a couple of moves. Yeah, well, there's a punch in the game.
A couple of jabs for a start. It automatically just got a full letter grid. Quite a sizable
hedge you've got there, don't you? Headbutt. B. Where's Lloyd? This is the tutorial. I don't
think Lloyd is in the tutorial. Sorry. Forgot to mention, you can get knocked out by your own
attacks from time to time. I won't forget again. It'll be a 10 if there are cars in this game. If
there are cars in the game, it's a 10.0. While running? Press X while running. Oh, you mean like
this? I feel like this is like a toddler having a tantrum. Those are tantrum arms. Okay. Jump.
Wait. I missed. Oh my God. I'm bad at this. All right. Turn this way and do it.
Just me, or is there a nice lollipop in the presentation box? Lollipop? Let's break it out.
Give me it. Give me this thing. To pick up, wait to align your hands with the handle.
All right. Now we... I'm going to like this a lot, I think. All right. How do I use it?
To correctly pick the weapon up. Correctly. Like this? This is like this. Okay. Oh, and you can't
let go of the grab button. Hit the punching bag with the lollipop. Oh, I'm going to bash somebody's
head in with this thing. That's what you're supposed to do, right? I'm going full violence
mode and I don't even know if that's what the goal of the game. Double press it. Okay. Hold Y
while grabbing the net. Okay. Hold Y. Oh, we have to grab it. Right. Okay. I don't do anything else
because it's... Oh, it's automatic. Okay. Let's go. Dodge roll. Are there iframes in this game?
Because that would be really funny if there were. Okay. Well, I missed. No. Okay. No. All right.
Wait. That was good. Clap for me. Clap. Beat the crocodile. Oh my God. All right. So...
Throw him off. What the fuck? I win.
That was not too bad at all. Next room. All right. Cool. Whenever you're ready.
I got one star. That's pretty good. Except it's not. Why would you want... You're going to give
me stars in a tutorial? All right. Quick match. Let's go. I don't have any friends.
How come I'm... Where's my... Where's the other character? Am I the dog? Don't ever do that slurp
again. Well, now I'm going to do it because you just said not to. Three, two, one.
Okay. Choose the map you want to play. How about this one? Does it matter? Don't get carried away
by water and stay alive. Oh. Why are you really goofy today? I think that's just who I am, man.
That's the worst sound of the year. No, not even close. No way. Oh, here we go. All right. I want
to be... I want to be somebody that nobody else is though. Oh, I have streamer mode on. Is that
a good thing? Probably. I'll be the duck. So it's all about just beat the shit out of each other.
I think that's a great title for a game. Don't you think that's a huge grabber for a title?
Beat the shit out of each other. Oh my god. I wasn't even looking. Am I already dead? All right.
I'm ready. Okay. That was bad. That was very bad. I'm all right. Am I all right? Get back up here.
How do I climb? What? Oh, this is all wear on teams. All right. Enough with that. Give me these.
Give me the nunchucks. Oh, now you're in trouble. I'm gonna come. I'm gonna come over here and...
What is wrong with me? What is wrong with my character? Get over here. Get back. Get back. Get back.
I didn't let go of items? All right. Get rid of them. Shit. We can do it. We can do it. We're fine.
We're fine. We're fine. We're fine. We're fine. Everything's fine. Everything's fine. What is this?
Headbutt. Headbutt, right? Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. We have to climb.
Get off of me. All right. Now, I'll get a step on his fingers when he gets up here.
Oh, shit. That's bad. No. Wait. I'm all right. I'm all right. Everything's fine. I'm still alive.
Oh my god. It's... I'm still holding on. Am I still alive? We won. We did it. All right. We're good.
Smash somebody with a frying pan. This is not how you pick that up. Yeah. Get out of here. Get away
from me. All right. I have... I have the fry... Oh my god. Get up. Get up. Whoa. Okay. I need to...
Okay. Should you grab them when they're still alive? Oh, wait. Oh my god. I have an opportunity right now.
Didn't work. Oh my god. I'm gonna crush him. He's gonna get squished like the juicer. Whatever this
thing is. He's in like the meat grinder. Oh god. Hold on. Wait. Wait. Wait. Oh, I'm unconscious right now.
Do not hit me with that, please. All right. We're good. Get up. Pick him up with both hands. Yes. I got it.
All right. Just hold on. Hold on. I'm gonna hold on for... I'm absolutely gonna hold on.
Who is throwing stuff at my head? We're all wedged into this hole. How did we all get in? No.
No. No. Grab it. He's holding my head under the water. That's illegal. You can't do that.
That's illegal. Oh, boy. There's no more boat. Oh. All right. I get it now. Let's go. Oh, shit. My
headphones fell out. Sorry. They're not paying attention. Should you always go for like running
kicks or what? Baseball bat. Give it to me. No. What am I doing? Just get up there now.
Shouldn't I climb to the very top right now? You piece of shit. Don't get eliminated immediately,
really. What just happened to me? What was that? What just happened? Oh. I only had three. I had
two. Did I spend all my coins? All right. Wait. Wait. Wait. I'm gonna throw a coin at this guy.
Oh, I just missed. Oh, they're in trouble now. All right. Okay. Here we go. Ready?
That's not where I just aimed. Why did it go all the way up here? My crosshair was right here.
Garfield's on your team. Oh, whoops. Here we go. Nice. Very, very nice. Ah, shit. Garfield's got it.
Don't let him take you in there. Right in the face. I don't want to throw this. I'm afraid I'll hurt
him. Dude, that was like a snipe, bro. Nevermind. Damn it. I'm so bad at this. Take the shot. That
was really close though, you have to admit. Where are they? All right. Did we win? All right. No.
All right. Let's go. Okay. Okay. I'm ready. Ready. Garfield, we're gonna get this right now.
Check this out. I got a gun now. Pick it up with both hands. Start whacking people.
Get over here. All right. At least I scared him. I almost just walked into the fucking like,
hold on. Oh, how do I pick them up? How do you pick people up? How do you pick people? How do
I let go of the bat? Isn't it right? Oh, it's double tap right trigger. That's why I was just
tapping right trigger. Just get up. I'm going up right now. Forget about anything else. Yeah. This
is all that matters. It's just whoever's at the highest point. So who cares? I'm just gonna stand
at the very top of this thing. Why would you do anything else? Just hold on right here. Don't move.
Oh, you idiot. No, no, no, no, no. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on tight. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold
on. Hold on. Oh, that's bad. I'm good. All right. Just me and you. Ooh, somebody missed big time.
And no, please get a shot. Beautiful. Unbelievable shot. All right. Just hold,
hold right here. All right. Am I safe? Yeah, there we go. All right. That's a win. We're good.
All right. This is it. This is, this is for all the marbles right here. Do not put me into the
fucking juice machine. I'll put you in there though. Let's go. Oh, it's a rocket comes out.
I thought it was the thing that opens and just crushes whoever's in there. Oh, it does both.
Okay. That's whatever. Ooh. See you later. Get over here. Why would a submarine have that? I
don't know. It's a goofy cartoon game. As long as I, I'm doing the same strat I did last time.
Seriously. Why is he going so slow? He's so, why did I do that? No, don't even think about it.
What did you just threw it to me? And I pick, I, I, what? I caught it. Put it down. Why did I pick,
I caught it out of the air. I didn't mean to do that. I think it just ran into the pole. Oh my
God. What am I doing? Why did I do that? Honestly, if as long as blue doesn't win, that was bad.
Oh, that's not good. It's very bad. Well, as long as blue doesn't win, we're good. All right. I
gotta help. Hey, we did it. Nice. Is that, that's worth, is that worth something? Nice job,
Garfield. You did it. I don't know why. I just, I don't know. That, that character, that character
had a punchable face. That character had a punchable face. That just went right. By the way,
what is up with that? Have you guys ever noticed that like, oh, that, oh yeah, that guy has a
wicked punchable face. Why is like your first impression of somebody to physically assault
them? What, what's up with that? Oh, it took a picture. I see. Your face is punchable.
But you know what I mean? Like, oh yeah, yeah. That guy's got a wicked punchable face.
You're already like having a fantasy of beating this person up. You don't even know who this
person is. You just said it though. I was setting up the joke. I was going to bring that up like
two weeks ago. All right. What's up? What's the fun one? Winter is, oh, well I guess we don't
even have a choice. Is anybody, is people saying play with other people? Is that, I know this is
like a multiplayer game and everything, but I kind of just wanted to try it. I don't know how
long I'm going to play this game for. So I don't, I mean, I know I might be here for playing this
game for like an hour or two or three, but I don't know if I want to be like, Hey everybody,
let's do it. And then like 20 minutes later, I'm like, yeah, I'm kind of done. All right. This is
really fun though. I like it. All right. So we just have to stay alive. Wait, wait. Oh, it's not
stay alive. It's okay. I was being it. Okay. It's not stay alive. It's, I didn't pay attention at
all. All right. So you have to score a goal in a circle. Sorry. All right. I get it now. It's
the first time I've played it. Okay. I'm going to go. Don't wait. You'll never be the first person
that runs for the dodge ball. All right. That's fine. What is, what goal is ours? Because that's
incredibly embarrassing if I don't do it the right way. What goal is ours? What team am I on?
What team am I on? Blue team. All right. Good. Oh, right. It's right up over our heads.
Okay. So we want to score on that goal in front of us. I'm really upset that Garfield's not there.
Oh, it's okay. Yeah. The whole time that it was explaining, I was looking over here,
talking about the punchable face thing. I wasn't even looking. I'm scoring a goal. Get off me.
How long did you stay down for? All right. I'm good. Oh, I got it. I got it. I got the ball. I
got the ball. I got the ball. I got the ball. I got the ball. I got the ball. I got the ball.
Shit. I tried to drop kick. I like the gorilla. The gorilla's cool. You can move the camera. Oh,
shit. Right stick, I guess. I just tried to do the same thing and I got hit. Really? We just
got annihilated. Is it actually five to nothing? What is happening right now? I'm going, I'm jumping
in and drop kicking immediately. I'm going to do the same thing they just did to me.
I pressed B instead of A. Let go of me. How do you get somebody to let go of you?
Okay. How do I stop this guy from doing this? Somebody help. Good. Good. Good. Good.
Clear shot. Clear shot. Yes. We got one goal. They disconnected. Did they? Do not. Oh my god,
how? All right. That one needs a little more practice. This gorilla scored, I think,
all of their goals. No, I want to be right in the middle. What the hell? Is he biting me? He's
biting me. Did you see Destiny 2's DLC? No. All right. All right. Let's go. Do you like frosty
flakes? Yeah. Frosted flakes, but it was too long of a name, so I had to get rid of the E and D.
The name was too long. What about sorcery? We'll go back to sorcery probably in this coming week,
next week maybe. All right. I want to do beat up bridge 100%. That looks like the absolute best
one. Stay on the bridge and stay alive. You got it. I think the problem was I wanted to be the
goose and I was playing as the duck. I think that was, I think that was the mistake. Your
shout out for frozen red grapes literally changed my life. Thank you. Honest to God. I'm glad to
hear that. I'm seeing a lot of sames right now. I'm seeing a lot of sames. That's great.
They hurt my teeth. All right. Let me, let me give you a little bit of a tip. You, this is
very important. A lot of people that do frozen grapes, they fuck the whole thing up. So listen
closely. Okay. The grapes, they need to be in the freezer for at least a whole day. This takes a
whole day. It takes like six plus hours to get, they need to be frozen solid, frozen solid.
Take them out. And then once they're out, you, I lost. Um, that was okay. Uh, anyways. So what
were we talking about? Okay. Frozen grapes. Did I actually just lose? Okay. So put them in the
freezer for at least six to eight hours. If you've frozen solid, when you take them out of the
freezer, don't just eat them right away. I know it's like, Oh, here they are frozen grapes. Let
them sit out for 15 to 20 minutes, maybe like 10 minutes. They'll be a little bit softer,
but still frozen and chewy on the inside. I, it is the greatest snack ever invented.
I invented it. I just want to make sure that we all can attribute it to me. Did I miss with the
bomb? Yeah. You invented it. Uh, also somebody said frozen blueberries. And I said, Oh, intriguing.
I had them. They're wonderful. Why the fuck did I just do that? Okay. Yeah. I will reiterate this
one more time. Regular grapes. They're not as good to me. And the thought of eating a handful
of grapes is like, Hmm, that's okay. I cannot get enough of these frozen grapes. I can't get enough
of them. I have, let me tell you something. I've been to the grocery store three different times
to get another big container of grapes. The last time before this, that I got a container of grapes,
I didn't even eat half of them. I don't think. And it's like, Oh shit. I don't like doing that.
Right. So you buy like the smaller container to make sure I'm buying the big ass container
and I'm freezing them all. And I'm eating the whole fucking thing. Not in one sitting,
obviously, but I can do some head butts. Wait, that's not a bad idea. Get away from the bomb.
He's trying to like put it in my mouth. Why there's so many of these.
Holy shit. I just did it. And I was unconscious when it happened. Cool. We did it again. No,
get off me. Thank you so much. You just saved my life. Not good. Oh my God. Why? I just went
flying. It'll hit somebody, whatever. I'm just dumped my entire drink on me. Yeah. Frozen
blueberries are awesome, but frozen grapes. Oh my goodness. It just changes everything.
Speaking of somebody that actually finds it kind of difficult to put fruits into his diet. I can
do vegetables, right? But there's something about a fruit, like eating an orange or an apple or,
yeah, I'm going to eat a bunch of melon today. That kind of just doesn't happen. This thing is
vertical. Bananas are great. I like to blend bananas in a smoothie, but if you're having
trouble getting fruits in your diet, is it no jokes around? It's a great way to do it.
Damn it. You should talk about tuna fish again. Okay. So what about the Silent Hill 2 remake?
Is it out? Remember, you're not even playing the game. I was playing. Watch this. I just,
he tripped on it. You should try eating a cold orange in the shower. I've had a can of Coke in
the shower and that was kind of cool. It's been a very long time. I've had a freezing cold,
like a really ice cold can of Coke. There's something about it. I don't know. I don't
recommend you do this, but I remember just slurping it down and I didn't even care if
it got all over me. I didn't even care. It was like, oh yeah, I'm going to slam this.
I want to pick up the right way. No, you know, I didn't pick it up the right way.
Why didn't I do that? How come he didn't use his other hand? Yep. Okay. See ya.
Oh, the tables have turned. Give me the gun. Gun. It's like woke me up.
Put that down. That's one. Holy shit. We did it. That's another win. That's a,
that's a W right there. You can call it a cleanup job if you want, but that was still,
hold on. I just spilt this shit. I'm an idiot. Did I a little bit? Whatever. I'm in the picture. I
don't care. Play this with Vinny. Thank you so much. She's rescuing me. Yeah, I got it. It's
good. It's just in my, it's just on my hand. I got to get used to that. I got, I'm a, I'm a,
I'm a reclined streamer now. Gator Valley. Do this one. Show us the setup. Uh, I didn't really
have time to put the webcam in, but you'll see it. And you're all going to think I'm
out of my fucking mind, but it's all right. Cause I'm comfortable here. And who cares people? Uh,
yeah. My stream set up. I've got all these like lights and I've got like a green screen and I've
got like stuff. I have like that Reddit shelf, right? Like, Oh, I'm going to put stuff on it.
I'm everything's on the ground right now. I'm literally on the ground and I kind of like it
here. I kind of like it just sitting here against like with a beanbag chair. That's not a beanbag
chair. I don't think I don't, I don't even care. It's fun. I like it. Uh, I'm going to stay with
the goose. There's nothing quite like being on the floor streamer. Yeah. And God damn it. I wasn't
even looking. All right. I think we're teams, right? Yeah. It's like a candy factory. Oh,
we eat the candy, bro. Get off me. Oh, wait, are we taking the, I didn't pay any attention.
Are we taking the candy back to our base? And in one sentence, what's the goal?
Steal the candy. Okay. I'm just going to be the muscle.
Ooh, that was a big one. All right. Get it, get it, get it, get it, get it, get it, get it, get it.
I am clobbering this dude. Oh my God. I killed him. You can kill people. All right. It's only
us here. We should be fine. Are we winning? Shit. I'm I'm I helped quite a bit. Actually.
I, that was, I helped quite a bit. Where am I? Damn it. I got an egg coin. Cool. The rabbits
are holding hands. Are they kind of remarkable? They actually could go up there is gambling.
Ooh, really? Okay. Don't tell them about that. Well, it's too late. I already did. Oh man,
this one looks kind of crazy. Frozen grapes are great, but if you hold on, let me see what you
said. Combine them with whipped cream. Hold on. I need to know that strat. It looks like somebody
has a frozen grape strategy. Have you tried carbonating them in a whipped cream dispenser?
Huh? Carbonated grapes? I don't, I don't even know what that means, but it sounds kind of
intriguing. You mean like you mash them up and whip them up with a, and then you put them in
like heavy cream and put them in a dispenser? That actually sounds kind of cool. You can do
that with like any kind of fruit, right? All right. I got to pay attention. That was,
I hope that was not a teammate. I don't, it might've been. Ooh, get out of here. Get out of
here. No. Oh, I freaked out. Oh, that was a victory right there. I freaked out. We still won.
Oh, I didn't. Oh, that hurt a lot. What if I just stay on the ground? Will anyone come get me? Um,
who has the electricity? Don't ever give me a weapon. I'm going to stand over here. Oh,
is there a taunt button? I hope there is. Oh, what is going on? Get off me. There's tasers.
Can I have some? Pick him up. Pick him up. Oh my God. You have to be fucking kidding me.
I'm trying to grab him and he just holds on with one hand. Like he's,
has a fucking little kid's wagon behind him. A whole wagon? Like those little kid wagons that
you drag. All right, let's stay back here together. Oh, okay. I'm not very good at this.
I went for a super move and it didn't do anything. Oh man. Oh man. I just wanted to
punch that guy in the face so bad. There was so much power in that punch. If it hit anybody,
it would have gotten annihilated. It's getting intense though. Ooh, big kick.
I mean, we got a 10 out of 10 cameraman here and saw the whole thing. This is a formal request for
you to play Baldur's Gate. Holly and I have actually been playing it off screen. Not a
whole lot though. Where am I? Just barely got into it. Oh, hold on. Actually, let me go see
the other stuff. I can do, I have money now, right? I have like coins or something. Okay,
level up. I got 1500 cookies and a bacon avatar. Okay, cool. So where are these eggs?
How do you like it so far? It's really, really, really cool. I like that it's kind of, you just
can sort of go wherever you want really. There's that, you know, there's a ton of
main mission storyline stuff, but you can kind of just walk in a direction and just kind of
do whatever you want. Okay. Surprise eggs. How many do I have? One? Okay. I can do one egg.
Let's go. Is it worth doing it like this? Or I think this, no, that's end game currency.
All right. What do we get? Character. I'm playing a, a gnome sorcerer focusing on lightning. Pink
hammer. Ooh, okay. That's right. Laughing my ass off. That's you. Of course it's always sorcery.
Well, sorcery is one of my favorite games of all time. I'm going to compare it to sorcery. No,
I don't want to do this one again. This one was too hard. Can you review the game immediately?
That might take a long time. I have a feeling that's going to take a little bit.
I feel like I've seen the amount of the game that amounts to the first preview at the movie
theater. Well, you're gonna have to give me a little bit. Oh my God. Hell yeah. Did you win
any F-Zero games? Holly and I have been obsessed with F-Zero 99. I've come in third place overall
one time. I took a screenshot to prove it just in case anyone didn't believe it. There's a lie.
Well, it's no, it isn't. It's for real. But realistically at this point I can get into the
top, like top 15, top 20. Very, very much consistently. Pretty much every time.
I like this character a lot. Whoa, whoa, whoa. You're way stronger. Why?
Let me up. Pull me up. Pull me up. Come on. Up, up, up, up. Pull us up. Pull us up, dude. Come on. Pull us up.
Pull us up, dude. Please pull us up. I was trying to let him go, but okay. It's all right. Can I get in the
cockpit? What the hell was that? Dude, he hit me in the hands and I shot the gun straight in the air.
Yes. Wait. Yes. Do not get eliminated first. Come on. Thank you, whoever did that. Thank you.
Actually, thank you very much. I'm a hammerhead. I should be hitting people with the head.
Get out of here. Oh, I'm on your team. I'm, hey, what are you doing? Why did you do that?
Why? He just saw red. He just saw red. He didn't even know. I don't think he even knew.
All right. We're kind of just fucking this guy up. That was revenge. Did I shoot him before? No.
Revenge? Why are you saying? Wait, really? Oh, no. That's not good. All right. I deserved it.
That's very, dude, I'm getting carried so hard. You tased him. But all right. But here's the thing.
I didn't mean to. He meant to punch me in the face and throw me off the ship.
The person just rolled off. That's a cool skin or whatever it is. What kind of animal is that?
I want to see. All right. As long as blue doesn't win, we're good. Ori and the Blind Forest. Oh,
okay. That's cool. I want to pick these up. How do you pick up the things on the ground?
What are you doing? I made one mistake and you're going to eliminate me twice?
What the hell? I tased you once and you're going to throw me off the ship two times?
Come on, man. Bro is holding a grudge. Yeah. Well, I still, I want you to win because I get the win
too. Oh, he hates you. He does. He hates me. I'm going to stay away from him. I'm going to,
I can stay on the other side of the map because he sees the hammerhead and he's like,
I'm going to kill that guy. Good backflip. Give me, give me. Oops. Sorry. That was kind of loud.
No, no, no, no. Get away. Get away. Get away. Get away. See ya. All right. I got,
I got to clutch this up right now. What are you doing? Oh my God. I freaked out. What I,
I didn't. Okay. Let me explain. Let me explain. Everyone listened for one second. I thought the
ship was two or three. I thought it was longer. No, I want to get up there and get my picture
taken. You're so bad. I thought the ship was a little bit longer. I was, that guy freaked me
out. I thought he was coming to get me. We still win. That's all right. It's a win. He looked like
a mole rat. Why did you move? I don't know. What famous animal would you add to this game? An
armadillo? It might even be in the game already. Oh, what is this one? Carry candies back. Oh,
okay. Carry candies back to base to earn points. I'm going just straight up defense. Octopus.
Octopus will be cool. Squid. Octopus. Is there a whale? Is there like a lobster or crab or
something? That'd be a great addition. Play Counter-Strike 2 in your off time. It's a great
game. It's really fun. I remember playing the original Counter-Strike 1.6. I was terrible at
it, but I played it. I tried CSGO. There's a video on my YouTube channel where I talk about
like, oh yeah, man, going to be playing a lot of CSGO. I think I played it one time and never played
it ever again. And I think there's a video of me playing it. And it's like, oh yeah, like it's a
big deal. And I just, I just, it just wasn't for me at all. People are, people are too good at that
game. Where's our base? Where do we turn this in? Oh, right here. You can't fall down that, can you?
I'm going to start just transferring. Give me that. All right. Deposit those and we'll win.
Did I help? Am I dead? Dead? Am I dead? Dead? I'm here. I'm good. Nice job. Duck. All right.
We're doing all right. No shit. I'm sorry. Make sure you bring them all back. Come on,
we got to work together. Get with that shit. Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Just take it back. Take it back. Good, good, good, good, good, good, good. Go, go, go, go,
up, up, up, up, up. We got it. We got it. We got it. Where are you going? Where are you going?
Where are they going with that? I just stomped all over that guy's face.
Don't let him drop it. Don't let him. Close this shit. No, don't open it again. Close it. Did I
close it or did I open it? Give me this. Give me this. I'm going to drop you into the fucking
freezer. Damn it. We can hear you mashing buttons. You can hear me like gripping the controller.
Shit. This game is fun. I like it. Don't eat the controller. It's going to hurt to poop.
What about Dark and Darker? Um, not in the immediate future. What about football? What
is it? Stay away from the poison cloud and stay alive. Uh, I get it. Browser games? We'll do
browser games the next time I stream. Or maybe I'll play the Resident Evil DLC. That sounds fun
too. Resident Evil 4? I also have to finish Sorcery. He's just going to play Binding of Isaac
for four hours. Waste. All right. Stay out of the poison. I have a new strategy. It's called just
stay on the ground. It's playing dead. Nobody pays attention really. This is where I get up and
throw you. I'm going to throw you in. Oh, nevermind. God damn it. How do I get out of here? Oh shit.
All right. I had a choice. I knew that was going to blow up in half a second. I was trying to
throw it at somebody. Just, you got to try. You have to go for it. Otherwise I would have blown
right back. Yeah, but why? Okay. I was climbing up here and there were three bombs here. I climbed
up here. Boom. Blinking red. At some point you have to just go for it. Your teammate is so good.
Yeah. They're so good. In fact, that I'm on the menu too. As long as we win, I'll take the three
eggs. Whatever. Oh, I think we actually, no he's dead. Oh, it gets closer. Oh, he shot him in the
head. What the fuck? That guy, he's done that to me twice. Thank you so much. Damn it. I want those
nunchucks. Why is this guy glowing? I don't know how to fix this. How do I fix this? Oh, okay.
Give me. Hold it the right way. Oh shit. Sorry. I'm sorry. I did not mean to hit you in the head
with that, but it just happened. Second, I get a melee weapon. It's over for everybody. I'm trying
to plant this on somebody. Damn it. Hold it the right way. No. Oh, come on. Fuck. Dude, Miku has
been waiting for birthday wishes for you from a month. I said, happy birthday, Miku. You just
weren't here. I said it. Yes, I did. Oh my God. This guy's going to kill me. You can't see who
did that, right? This person has no idea I did that. I should save the coins. Do they carry over?
I imagine probably so. I'm going right for the boomerang. I need to get away from everybody.
Damn it. Watch out, please. You hit, hit. I have to get away from the guy with the frying pan.
That was a risky move, but you know what? Fuck it. I'm in the face of the fucking cinder block.
Who is dude? What? Watch out. Uh, we need some, we need some more teamwork.
Just give it to me. Don't. This is such a bad place to be. Why am I still on the ground?
I screamed a lot today. They call me. Okay. Get the brick. Did I not? I didn't. How did I not
hit you with the brick? I dropped on his head. I got him. He's not getting up for a long time.
Oh, thank goodness. We're all hurt. This guy just won't leave me alone. No. What? Wait,
what just happened? Oh, the gas was everywhere. Come on. We got to get in the picture together.
Right when the picture gets taken. Can't wait for Hylics 2. How long is Hylics 2?
Because I know Hylics 1 was four, five hours? Three, four? It's like five to 10. There's a
lot of game modes. What is wind tunnel? Eh, we'll do this one. Beat the hockey into opponent's
gate to earn points. Beat the hockey into opponent's gate. Trevor, can you do another
sponsored stream? Oh, all right. Okay. I mean, that's a request. That's a request. Somebody
just requested one. One guy, one guy moment. You know what I mean? Nobody said. Nobody said
you make me sick. Oh, settle down. Industry plant. All right. So we have to score goals.
Oh, it's this thing. It's a huge puck. We're not going to score on our own goal, right?
It's a whole, there's a whole team of gorillas. Oh, no, it's not.
Dude, I want to, I want to watch this version of hockey. Oh, I'm on your team. Give me this thing.
I got it. I got it. I'm just going to play defense. He's just holding his arm out and
has his palm on the top of my head and I am swinging while he holds me back. We just get a
goal. Okay, let's go. All right. We got to be aggressive now. Aggressive, aggressive, aggressive.
Good, good, good, good, good, good. One more. There it is. Nice job. That was the most tired
let's go ever. Let's go. This thing probably pushes it pretty far, right? I'm going to play
goalie. I actually think that's a smart use of my time right now. All right, get it out of here.
Yeah, this is offsides. You're going to get a fucking red card. Where am I? Yeah, try getting
it by me. Oh shit. Don't please. Okay. And the goalie is coming out of his goal and he's going
all the way down. We've never seen anything like this before in giant puck ice hockey.
I helped. Defense. Let me handle this. Had my shield. Oh, deflected. Parried. Oh, parried again.
Come on. You're just, I mean, you're getting parried. You guys got it. Stay forward. Face forward.
Get out of here. Oh my god. That, my head spun 360 degrees. Oh, that's sad. Look at where I was.
This game is fun. All right. You want to fight? I'll give you a fight. I blocked it with my body
and my face and my head and my brain and the concussion that I now have. I don't know. It
looks so good. I just got up from a concussion, dude. Really? Unsportsmanlike conduct. Got it.
They're dinosaurs. That's cool. If you come over here, I am going to make your life a living hell.
Nice. Tell the Oreo puke story. Okay. When I was
college, what did I just do? There's a puck. This is my chance. It's my chance. No, we can do it.
Come on. Stay in the back a little. If it flies back here, I'm going to be ready to get it.
Everybody just stay on the goal. I just have to body block. Oh, this is so embarrassing.
This is really embarrassing. It's like I took an extra five seconds to know I was still playing
the game. Oh my God. Get out of here. Oh shit. Oh shit. You stood there like a kid in the little
league. Yeah. Come on. It's right there. We won. Wasn't it a tie? Oh no, we did win.
I just want to get in front of this guy and ruin the picture. Your character looks like you.
I don't think. What do you mean? Explain. Explain. He does. Explain. It's the eyes.
You guys think my eyes are that far apart? My eyes are not that far apart. Your eyes are close
together. I think my eyes are very normal distance. We should compare. Looks like we struck
a nerve. I don't care. I don't like, I don't fucking care at all. It's just annoying. I don't
give a shit. I don't care. I don't give a fuck about that. I don't know. It's annoying to me.
I don't care though. What are you talking about? I think I'm good right here. Nice try. No,
no, you're not going to get me off it. I'll pull it this way. I don't care as long as I'm behind
the wind. Dude, everybody just stop grabbing at it. Oh, I'm going to fuck this up so bad.
Oh, actually not bad. Oh, well, sacrifice yourself. Blue team wins, right? You need to
do a bunch of wind compensation there. Is somebody else alive? No. Dude, I'm on your team.
Get up. We've got to pull, all right, we have to pull a lever. Somebody, we're all going to go,
we're all going to die. That's what I want. I want chaos. Hit him instead. Oh fuck. All right,
that's really strong. Yeah, go the long way. Everybody comes over to me. You're getting shot.
Oh fuck. I need to live too. Oh shit. No. Oh shit. It's two v one. This is not good. Oh,
oh, I got him. Can you not climb this? What's going on here? Why are you not doing this?
Climb up this. Why can't I? Why couldn't I climb? He had to go around. It was convex. Oh shit.
Stick out by my guys up there. Take somebody off from red because they're going to sacrifice
themselves. This is very, very low. Is he going to get blown off? What's going on with this guy?
Trying to get the head butt in. All right, the goal is to stay all the way to the left.
Everyone's going to just, as we need stuff up now, hold on. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't
let go. I'm holding the thing down. At least the wind's not here. Fine, fine, fine. Take that one.
I don't care. We can all have one. Let me know. This is how we survive. What the fuck? I was
what? What was that? Well, I got annihilated. What was that all about? No, don't. No, don't. Please.
I got it. Don't worry. All right. Good luck. All right. Lower profile. And him. Oh man,
that was pretty good. That's fine, I don't care. Just stuff over here. Oh, don't ever jump here.
Ever. Oh my. God damn it. Bring back grandpa. Hey, it's me. Grandpa. Okay, bye. Hey, oh,
Grant, you just missed him. You didn't even get a crown. I got a crown my first game,
and the second game, and the third game. Are you playing against bots? No, it's a streamer
zone. I just saw it was a thing I could click, and I said, if they have it, something to enable,
there's a reason why they want you to enable it. That's my philosophy on the whole thing.
Oh, everybody loves this one. These are bots. I need to get some new skins. You should roll for
10 skins. You have to get a high enough MMR to matchmake. Oh, is that for real? I kind of feel
like I've been talking shit this whole time. Nice try. Oh, double tap. Oh, triple. No, you don't.
It's just 2v2. We got it. Come on, duck. You just pushed me off. You dope. You dope. You jumped off.
Well, I jumped, but then he gave me the extra momentum to fly off. I would have landed perfectly
fine. I'm perfectly safe. Okay, come on. Does this thing hurt, or is it just bounce? Yeah,
I think it's just a bouncer. Swing at him. Why am I not swinging it anymore?
Oh, that's my friend. Sorry. No. Oh, shit. That hurt. I'm using an inflatable toy.
Good start. I tried to save him. Don't even think about it. Was that a hat? Oh, it's a banana.
Get that bomb away from me. Oh my god. I have the weapon, and I'm scared. No, give me back. Give
me the weapon back. Yeah. I'm just not capable of doing that advanced technique, and I just tried.
I went for the advanced technique. It was just immediately run, jump, kick, and it was a problem.
Why is Yoshi driving? I don't know. Yoshi, you can do it. I know you can. You have super power.
Don't do the dive jump. It's bad. Not a good idea right now. Good. Finish it off. Finish it.
Good finish. Nice work. God damn it. Don't shoot me. Okay, I'm good. Get away from me.
Oh, he's got me with the plunger. No, I'm plunged right now.
Where is it? What the fuck was that? What was I doing? The fact that he was pulling his arms
behind his back trying to... Oh, that was cartoonish. That was fucking wedged.
Jeez. Okay, as long as green doesn't win, we're good. I don't even know who... I don't know who won.
They both fell off at the same time. That was fun. All right, now I'm gonna get some skins.
I'm like whispering a secret to him. Where'd they get... That's a pumpkin head. That's kind of cool.
All right, let me go back and do some... Let's see. 1,500 cookies and some money. I got 200 bucks.
All right, what can I do? This one's 22,000. 12,000. This is what people are spending their
money on, I guess. Okay, yeah, that's cool. I like blue. Should I do it with money? Why not, right?
And I got blue. I wanted blue and now I have blue blue. Nice. Do I need to have blue to do blue blue?
You should roll for 10. Do you have to buy the money? No, okay. Let's do it. I'm gonna do one
more and then I'm gonna go take a quick break and come back and do this one. You get money on level
ups, yeah. Is he tired already? No, I'm lounging. Show the beanbag chair. Uh, you will see it
eventually. This is the one that we have not seen. You should wear a giant yellow raincoat on stream.
Intriguing. Cool. All right, Lulu. And get a big yellow hat and adopt a monkey. What did the man
in the yellow hat do for a living? What did he do? He's an archaeologist. He was a researcher.
He was a zookeeper. I was like, what a fit that is. A long brimmed yellow hat and just a yellow
jacket, yellow pants. That is an awesome look. Then you showed up to work and your boss was in the
the man, the curious George dad fit. He'd be like, holy shit, I really hate to do this. I'm really
sorry. What just happened? What just happened to my head? What did he just do? Did I just hit my
head on his head? What just happened? Yes, come on. Oh, I would say I deserved it, but it's a free
for, no it's not. What hit me? The gorilla is popular. Look at this. I kind of want the gorilla
now. I feel like my gaming skill would increase by at least 25% if I was the gorilla. Got him on
the backswing. Oh, my team, I'm on green. Okay. Hi, I want you to win. You can do it. Did I help?
I'm not sure. You can do it. Let them fight each other. Ooh, big punch. Almost got it. Watch out
behind you though. I'm not in a discord with anybody, but they can't hear me. Seems to lose, right?
Did we win? Okay, good. I want to stick this on somebody. Come here. Got you. Okay, let go. Shit.
Okay, come here. I threw him far too. Good. I punched him in the face. In your arms. Nice work.
Come on, get up. Dude, you overshoot it every time. Fuck you. Oh, that's bad. Actually kind of good. Come
on. Shoot. All right, two gorillas. One with a nunchuck. Who wins? He just knocked himself out
with a nunchuck. That'd be so funny if he lost. Pretty even. You're AFK. I'm going to help you here.
See? I didn't kill you. You're AFK. Remember that for when you try to get me. How is it going through
the gap between their two heads? That's what I want to know. Oh, don't even think about it. Shit.
The poor cat is over there, still lying down. I need to rescue the cat. I'm rescuing the cat.
I think it's too late. Oh, come on. The cat. The cat's going down. Cat's going down.
Iceberg melting. Oh, I feel bad. That was my fault. I'm going to get up first and we're going to win.
Get. Come on. What? Oh, give me a break. I was grabbing onto the ledge and then my left arm
grabbed onto his head and then pushed his head down. I just saw blood and I just had to just
continue. No. Why didn't you climb up? Whatever. Oh, this is going to be fun. Oh, I was going to
try to have like 10 plungers in his head. I'm staying. No. I want to stay over here with the cat.
Oh, shit. This is big for me. No. Excuse me. Get me the fuck away from that. Wait. You idiot.
The two red team is still here. All right. I'm going to hang out for a second.
Get away from me. I don't know what to do. Oh, conductivity. I forgot about conductivity.
Sorry, I'm still alive. Run. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Why are you having so much trouble
getting up? Come on, dude. Get up. Do it. Get up. Why is he not getting up? Why is he not getting
up? Did I win? No stamina. Oh, I think we still won. All right. One more. This might be a win
right here. I just knocked somebody out with my body weight. Jesus. What happened? What happened?
Get out of here. Come on. Who wants to fuck around? Who wants to fuck around? Get that thing
away from me. This is it. This is a win right here. If I get it, if I get it. I got it. I got
it. I got it. This is a win. This is a guaranteed win. I thought everybody was dead. I thought
everybody was dead, but they were just on a different part of the map. That dude's probably
pissed. That's the first time that person's got that power up and they get hit with a coin.
Uh, okay. We're still in it as long as, uh, yeah, there's no green. Unfortunately,
yellow can win. That's fine. Good. Blue winning here would be huge. So we're going to try to
put our thumb on the scale here. Nice job. You're green. Yeah. I don't want yellow to win.
Okay. Oh, blue had one win too. Shit. All right. This is, this is it. This is the one here. Let
me try as hard as I can. One, two, three, go. Yup. Wow. Oh, please tell me I eliminated five
people. We don't want blue to win. Blue or yellow has to lose. Where's my teammate? Do I have a
teammate? No, I need that pen. Oh my God. It hit me right in the face. It hit me right in the face.
That's so frustrating. You can do it. I know you can get up there. I'll be careful though.
But, but, but, but get off me. Get off me. What did I just do? No, I had an opportunity,
but I missed it. Holy shit. Whoever did that, you just saved everything. Shit. No, right to him.
Don't. Oh my God. Why is he so super powered? Why does this guy have super powers? How do you get,
how do you get the super power? You have to eat a biscuit or a drink. Oh,
damn it. Did I even have a teammate? I feel like I didn't have a teammate that whole time.
There's a whole gorillas. You killed him with the bomb. Oh, that seems to be a theme.
Where's my teammate? What happened? Oh, you killed him in the first five seconds. Oh, right.
Makes sense. Right. Sure. He was AFK the whole time. I think we did pretty good for AFK teammate.
Can we bully Jerma? No, but you lighten up a little bit. Bullies you. Stop. It's not his
birthday anymore. We don't have to be nice to him. It's my birthday month. Hey, if Grimace gets to do
that, I do too. You gotta follow the same rules. Where's your weird milkshake? All right. This is
a goofy one. Is it lit? Oh, that's not good. Saved by the bomb. What do I do with it? There was no
way to put it. All right. Good job, blue team. No, it's my bomb. Oh, I got him. I got him. He
bailed on the bomb and it was the mistake. He bailed on the bomb. What the fuck? I'm all right.
I got a hand on the, uh, on it. Oh, this is one of those laughing games. You know what I mean?
I kind of threw pretty hard right there. I'm not gonna lie. That was really dumb.
I threw completely. I actually just, I just threw. Where's my teammate? Oh, there you go. Well,
we'll get him next time. Right in the head. Oh, you're gonna get kicked from the clan for that
one. That's so rough when it does that. I get so impatient here because I just want to throw
rocks at him. I don't want to. The bomb is awesome, but anybody's game. Ouch. That was a
really good throw too. Oh, unfortunate. That was a great throw. Perfect placement. All right. Let
me see if I can drop bomb. Got it. I just threw it right there. Decent placement. Lots of damage
on blue. We don't want blue to win. No. Oh, that's too bad. That's if you can get this thing,
it's game over. No, I need to buy the handle. No, no, nobody can use it. Shit. Come on.
Your teammate's AFK, is he? Not like it really matters that much. You have five feet of space
next to you. People just ramming into each other anyways. Floating dead in the river right now.
Nobody's won yet. We're doing all right. That, I didn't even see that. Am I the only one that
died from that? I'm the only person that died. Okay. Well, blue, I got it. This has got to be
a good bomb here. Right there. Perfect. Oh, that's going to be great. Watch this.
Oh, I thought they were going to get launched over to it. Blue cannot win. Come on, cat. You got it.
Nice throw. There we go. Don't be. Okay. You guys can do that all you want. Whoa. Wow.
What happened to that guy? Hey, we did it. He hit himself. Oh, okay. Wait, I got to drink that,
right? I plunged him. Watch out for that bomb. It's going to eliminate every single person.
This is going to be awesome. Nobody wants to pick it up. Dude, really? Really? Everyone's like
running around the bomb. No, I would have picked it up. I would have been the first person to pick
it up. Oh, red one. I need to win another one. Oh, game's addicting. Damn it. Okay. One more.
And then I'm going to actually go to the bathroom. Get blue death feigning beetles?
No, we want them. We just want to be in a position where we can take care of them.
It's all like the traveling, lots of stuff going on. I would say probably like in the,
in the new year, we'll probably get them. I want to make sure we can really,
like truly pay attention to them. Everything. Oh, what is this? I've never seen this one.
Oh, let's play the new one. They're very easy to take care of. That's what we have heard. Hey,
they love grapes, right? I love grapes. It was just meant to be. Did you get a pet lobster?
That's cool. I love fish. I love aquatic life. I love marine life, but I don't, taking care of
aquatic life. There's a lot of maintenance, like cleaning the tank and making sure that the
levels are good, right? Like you can't just like, oh, there's my lobster. I mean, I've heard it's
very fulfilling and it's really cool to have like a bunch of fish in a fish tank or lobsters or
crabs or whatever people do. I'm going to score my first goal ever. Hey, why are you so mean to me?
That's the inside of that. How are you that good to be able to do that? Also the play is probably
just a standstill while everybody just runs into each other. There you go. Nice. Are you excited
for the FNAF movie? Yeah, I'll watch that one on times four speed instead of times six speed.
So yeah, I mean, I'm very, I'm going to tell him very excited for it. What's Saw X? Yeah, I don't,
I want to see Saw X, but I don't want to go to the theater to see Saw X. Although they're making
this one a big deal. This one's a big deal. And we all know how much of a fan I am of the
Saw movies. Although I can't say I remember what happened between five and 10. Oh my God. I, wow.
I jumped in the air and he hit me right in the chin. Come on, come on. Go, go, go, go, go. It's
right there. Stop him from doing this. How did we not stop him from doing that? Marathon them.
I still do want to do that thing I talked about. It might just, it might just be a video. I think
it's funnier as a video. Yeah. So watch along. Wait, did I, wait, wait, wait, wait. What's
happened? I forgot what, I forgot what team I was on. Am I going, is this correct? Is this bad?
That got everybody. That wiped out the whole crew. Oh my. This has been a big talking stream,
more than a gaming stream. It can be both. But a game like this is pretty much just kind of goofy
and fun to sit here and play it. Pulling his hair. Oh shit. I forgot I was going to go. All
right. One more. How's the mystery video? Well, there are two videos that I want to do. The one
I was just talking about. And then this one, the mystery one. I'm only making the mystery video
for me. It's not for anybody else. So when you see this, just, it was not, I didn't make it for
anybody else, but it could get 10 views and I wouldn't even care. Everyone wants to play them.
I'm bad at these ones. I don't like these ones. Okay. I won't watch it. That's all right. It
actually is fine because the video is not going to be any good. This video is going to overstay its
welcome in the first 30 seconds. And it's going to be like a seven minute video or more. It could
be longer. I don't know. I am actually going to play goalie this time. All right. Good, good,
good. Go. Nice. Somebody else is playing goalie. Watch this. I'm going to go fuck this guy up.
Yeah. I'm talking to you. What the fuck? I see. I'm distracting him. This is bad for him.
All right. All right. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. All right. All right. I'm done.
I'm a good spot right here. Give me a spot right now. Watch this. I got a line right to the goal.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Here we go. Three, two, one. Dude, get it out of here.
Okay. We're good. What'd you say? Get over there. Oh, I get credit for that one. I do.
I get credit for that one. Perfect bounce. I like that little guy. He's funny. The shark. Yeah.
I'm going to be the last one to get up. I would have been there, but I was so late to get up. Hey,
good night, Jerma. You should have played fall guys instead. I don't want to play fall guys.
I want to play party animals. I'm getting in the goal. This is dangerous. Imagine seeing a goalie
come out and do that. The other team scores on their goal. Oh, he's not on the goal. He's not
on the goal. Uh-oh. Not on the goal. Hey, hey, hey, bro, bro. Get your head in the game.
Who else wasn't in the goal? Yeah, but I belly to belly suplex that guy. It's worth something.
That cat's eyes. Holy shit. That cat. That cat like hot boxed his room for an hour. All right.
I'll be right back. Just going to get another, get some water. Use the bathroom. Back in two
minutes. Three minutes. I am back. I want to do something. Check this out. Ready? Turn the game
down. Have you guys ever done this before? The brainstorm or green needle viral video? Somebody
have. Yeah. Yeah. No, no, no. It's really, it's weird. Okay. So there's this toy that when you
press a button on it, it plays an audio file and the audio file that it plays, it goes brainstorm,
brainstorm, but you can make your brain. You can make you, you can make yourself hear something
else. Let's do the experiment. It's been like five years. Hey, I just found it. So whatever.
I'm 40 and I'm retired. Okay. We find things a little later. I want to do it, uh, brainstorm
because sometimes it'll say both at the same time and it's freaky. All right, here we go. Ready?
What do you hear? Do you hear brainstorm or do you hear green needle? Brainstorm.
Brainstorm. Right? Brainstorm. Okay. Green needle. Green needle. Green needle. Brainstorm.
Who the fuck is hearing green needle? It's going to happen. You know, that image of,
I think it's like a spinning ballerina that if you watch it long enough, it spins the other
way. It's like that. Just give it a second. Green needle. Buzzfeed Andy. Green needle.
Isn't that cool? Isn't that interesting? Isn't that cool? I heard radio static. Huh? Getting
real 78 year old grandmothers showing something on the computer vibes. Do Yanny and, oh yeah,
this one too. Let's try this one. All right. What do you hear on this one? What do you hear?
Mary. Laurel. Mary. Laurel. Mary. Mary. It's hard for me to get it to do the other one.
Mary. Mary. Cause it goes like,
I can't get it to say, I can't get it to say Yanny.
Mary. Yanny. No, I can't get it to do Yanny now. Mary. Mary. Shit. Mary. It's Laurel only.
Mary. Say, say. Mary. Yanny. Mary. Shit. Mary. Mary. Okay. So the parts, the, the kind of the,
the like the vibrato of the, the voice, it's like, it goes like Yanny. Yanny. But I can't get
him to do it now. Mary. Mary. Shit. Mary. Mary. Mary. Damn it. Mary. Mary. Yeah. Sometimes it
goes Laurel. Yanny. Yanny. Mary. I can't get him to do it now. All right. What do you, uh,
there's a couple more interesting ones too. Mary. I can't get them to do it. Mary. I'm
gonna try it one more time. Yanny. Say it. Mary. Mary. Mary. There's a couple more cool ones.
Let's try this one. All right. Do you hear this one? This one tripped me up big time. Do you hear
a burp or a fart? Which one? It's, it's hard for me to find, to decipher it. What do you guys hear?
What'd you hear? See, I can't get it to burp now. No, still. What are you guys hearing? You hear
both? Let me try it one more time. So I'm saying if you slow them down, you can hear different
things. Really? Hey, I, uh, like I'm, I'm hearing Laurel. That's interesting. I hear brainstorm
minus 3 million. Well, unfortunately you can't take that many points away. There's only a hundred
points. So I still get an F. You could have said you minus 50 points and I still get an F. Dude,
you're embarrassing me. All right, let's keep playing this one. Yanny. Yanny. Yanny. Okay.
If you take what I just did and mess with it, can you make it say Laurel? That's what I'm,
that's my question. Is it going to haunt me in my sleep? Um, just like,
like a couple of blueberries. It'd be all right. All righty. Let's do it. Did I get any new stuff?
Did I get any new things? Refreshes in three days. Oh, is it a burp or a fart? It's so funny.
Kind of with the cat. I'm buying the cat. Uh, hold on. I need to, this is, we're not,
we're not going anywhere. Somebody said this sounds like the DVD menu for the mask.
And we need, is it available to see if that's the, hold on a second. Oh, we, we stall a lot here.
Sorry. I'm curious. The mask DVD menu. It's right. It is here. All right. So this is the,
this is the mask DVD menu song. Okay. He's like spinning around. Okay. This is not even close.
Wait, they were thinking Austin powers. Oh, were they thinking Austin powers?
Oh, we have to, we have to ban that guy. Yeah. You gotta get, you gotta ban for at
least a couple of days. I mean, I stream like once a week now, but like, you know,
you're banned for a day. Austin. Yeah. This is just, this is kind of scary.
Austin powers DVD menu. Okay. I mean, not, I mean, not really. This is wrong too. What
does it sound like? No, not, not really. Well, wait a minute. Hold on. Wait. Unban that person.
Unban that person. And I'll tell you why this is the mask, the animated series intro.
This is what they thought of.
Wow.
Okay. Hold on.
Yeah. I tried to save you. It's, it's the same genre of music. There's two or three of the same
instruments. What about, hold on. No, I can't. I'm sorry. I can't save you, but you know,
what's cool though. I, it could be, it really could be, this could be the mask DVD menu.
You could have convinced everybody. In fact, I, it should be all right. What's going on? Oh,
I'm in an activity. Change outfit. Ah, wait. Surprise egg. Do I have enough? No. All right.
Let's play. Olive garden music. I remember that. That was great. That was a really fun night.
Jackbox. It could be jackbox. All right. I want to play this one. No, no one wants to play the
safe back to base to earn points. All right, let's go. So to grab onto it. Have you ever
done a jackbox stream? Oh yeah. Lots of times. Lots of times. Oh, let's see if my mouse is
moving. Okay. It's been a very long time. I think the reason why I don't do jackbox streams anymore
is because, uh, all the answers. Oh, okay. Everybody. So what do you think is the answer?
Is it German? Nine, eight, five. Jerma sucks. Jerma pooped his pants or Jerma sucks.
Which one of those is it? I was just like, well, these are all kind of the same answer.
Aren't they somehow? Who am I holding onto? I'm sorry. I apologize. Can I apologize?
I apologize to that person. Hey. All right. I've, I've had you in chokehold. I don't know who has
who here. He's stuffing me into a locker. I can't get out of here. What the hell?
Get off me. Just start bite, bite his neck. Bite him. Not right here. Shit. Yeah. Got him.
Let's make this way easier for us. Uh, I have, I don't know what, how this one works. This thing
floats around and we have to like put it over here. We got it. All right. Press the button.
I think we got it. Yeah, we do. There we go. We need to get the actual thing. Oh,
everyone's holding onto it. All right. Where we need to bring it. Where? I don't really know
what's happening, but we're having fun. We just got it again. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got
it. I got it. I got it right there. Right there. No. Knock it up. The first victory in an hour
and a half. That was a really bad picture. It's beautiful. Is it? It's September 27th already.
I blinked and we went from May to September. Icebreaker is a lot of fun. It's probably one
of the best maps. Retirement does too. I'm very active. I have 0.99. I wanna do that. When's the
update? Isn't there a big update coming really soon? Because I'll definitely play it when the
update comes out. Somewhere in October, right? Yes, I did try to punch my teammate and yes,
I'm sorry about it. Okay, okay, okay. You heard me. I went Super Saiyan. Am I actually gonna fall
down here at Super Saiyan? I'm gonna ruin this for everybody. This is gonna be great. Let's do this.
That should count for a win for me. I should get points for that. I should get every point for that
one. Oh, that was great. I'm so sorry, but you definitely lost. Why are we all on one of them?
There's more than one. Oh boy, that's not good.
Come on, what the hell? It's like he did that for dramatic effect. All right, let's see.
Yeah, see you later. I'm gonna put it right in the middle. Oh, that's bad for you. That whatever
the pig guy. The wind actually helped. You're terrible at this game. I know you are, but what
am I? The pig is on my team. For some reason, I always just think I'm on green team. Just to
be green. It's like, yeah, green versus red. I'm always on green team. That bunny is pissed
because of what I did last. You can hear the button pressing. Somebody turn it on. I got you.
Don't let go. I'm still here. I'll stay over here. Fuck all of you. Hey, hey, you're weighing
it down. He's weighing it down. He just weighed it down. He sat on top of the N64 cartridge and
just went right in. All right, I gotta make something happen here. I'm just like hitting
nothing. Oh, fuck. Oh, there's another one. Get up. Try to get away from the bomb. Headbutt with
that glorious head of yours. I'm gonna wait for the win. Actually, you know what? Oh, never mind.
Yellow team is the team to beat. Oh, he's gonna slurp down there. Yep. Oh, he didn't even know.
He didn't even know. I have to hold on to my friend. Oh, shit. Big move right there. Okay,
we win. We win. We win. We win. We win. We win. We win. No! I just hit him in the head with that.
I'm so sorry. Are you still alive? You can do it, man. I know you can. You can do it.
Where is he? Where is he? Where was he that whole time? My control is in my lap right now.
Whatever. Good luck, everybody. Oh, that's not good for the person. No, that's my friend,
but I gave him a bomb and he's gonna utilize it. Nice throw. All right, I have confidence in the
dog. You got this. Nice job. Stay alive. I'm gonna wait for a bomb. My team is green.
Unless they're... I might wait for the last one. Nah, let's do it now. You're okay.
Jess gets his head electrocuted. That's not cool. That's not cool. He's gone. See, to me,
you pick the bomb up when it's 2v2 and you just run at the other guy. You drop it and turn around
last second jump. Oh, you're both going down. You gotta get something up. Oh, I don't... Who was it?
Okay, good. Is the game fun? Yeah. Oh, yeah. It's really fun. Oh, this cat. Can I pull the cat
through? Okay. Big moves. Big moves. Got two of us here. Clawing under his head. No, we're all
going. Oh, and that one guy that's stuck right there. That's so annoying. Oh, we should have
spread out. That was my fault. I should have went the other way. That's the best one of the whole
night. It's a really good one. How do I add it? I want it. It's a great one. Do you think there'll
ever be one of these where everyone just behaves? Just stands in line? I'd like to see that. Do you
do your own laundry or do you have a butler? I have six butlers. One for the left arm,
one for the right arm, one for my head through, and one to feed me while I'm doing it. The other
two tie my shoes. And then the other one reads me the daily briefing of the day that I need to hear.
Number seven brushes my teeth. Number eight has already... I don't know. Number eight can just do
whatever he wants. They asked you if you did your own laundry. Oh, uh, yes. Screw that. I'm going
over here. Why fight when you can guarantee you'll be in the top four if you just smoker?
Oh my god. That was not... I just laid this person out so hard. It's like off the top rope. Excuse
me. Why did we both just do that? That was very odd. I'm not coming up here yet. You can stay up
there and taunt all you want. Look at these clowns over here. Okay, good. Very good. That's exactly
what I was wanting to see. I'm just gonna hold on. I'm just gonna hold on to this pole. Am I
still holding on to it? Somebody saved my life. This is like... I had quite a few cocktails. I'm
just gonna lie in here. I am the king of the mountain. I think I won. I did, right? Yeah.
They've been in the water for way longer than I have. Okay, I was gonna say, geez. Oh, it worked.
It worked, but I got hurt. I think I'm gonna be all right. I... I'm gonna be all right. I'm all right.
I can do it. I'm going for another win. All right, who wants to fuck around? That was a big mistake.
It's all right. It's all right. It's all right. Fine. I'll... It's all right. I still have my teammate here, right?
Pretty sure the teammate... Yeah, teammate's still there, right? Oh, too bad. You can grab right here.
Shit. Well, it looks like it's the... the tower bolt. Let go. Really? That's dirty. That was really dirty.
Dirty. Really dirty. All right, you're playing dirty. That's fine. That's all right. Got my sights on you now.
You're gonna play dirty? Okay. All right. That's fine. You're gonna play dirty? I need to have a chance to get off.
Uh, I'm dead. Um, that guy just... All right. Well, now... Now you're dead. My buddy's up there now.
Hey, wait. You want a coin right to the head? Oh, I may have made a mistake. I am bad.
It's okay, though. It's okay. As long as you don't win. Oh, man. I gotta aim much lower than that.
Okay, I gotta hit this. This is make or break. I have to hit this. Who's in first? Who's in first?
Oh, would you look at that?
That's not my stamina though, duckhead. Don't do that. Really?
Say hi to fucking Satan for me. Oh, the rocket went off. Easy. Look at him. That is... That is like
rabid. What? How does he hit me like that? There's no way. I still got my buddy over here. Are you good?
Hey, I'm not going up there. That's a stupid idea. Let's... Hey, hang out down here. Yeah,
let him do that. No room up there. I... I'm gonna uninstall the game. I'm so fucking bad.
I tried to hit it. It's okay. I'm still here. And I'm still a fine... I'm still... No, I'm not. It's
over. Oh my god. I feel so bad. Use me. Use... Just use me. Use me. Use me as a raft. Use me...
Use me as a raft. Use me as a raft. Use me as a raft. Oh, whatever. Oh. Oh, I punched him right in
the nose like it couldn't have been cleaner. Right in the face. Yeah. Yeah. This guy. Yeah.
Get in that racket. I'm gonna smash your head over there. Get out of here. We both need to
have weapons and we got this in the clear. Oh god. No. He's just beating the shit out of my face.
Don't ever suspect anything. Oh, my head's underwater. No. Oh, shit. It depends on who has
the most... How do I... Okay, just... I'm just gonna just explode. Just float. Float. Float. Float.
Float. Float. I'm just gonna float. I'm gonna conserve all my energy. Why'd I die? Oh, I
couldn't turn around fast enough. That's a good one. That's a good one. To throw them off the
submarine. I threw that guy off the submarine three or four times. It's a shame corner. Yeah.
Late night stream. Uh, kind of, yeah. I was around like eight. I was around like about 430. I
probably will do more later streams like late night. I know EU does not want to hear that but
I don't want to start too, too late but around this time is alright. I'm between like four and
seven, four and six Pacific. How long is the Resident Evil 4 DLC? It's football? Oh, this is
so... Can we pass it? You have to get a touchdown? This is so cool. Alright, I probably should be
playing baseball. I wonder if that didn't connect. I got it. Good. What? I got it. I have it. I have
the ball. I have the ball. There we go. About five to six hours. Okay. Oh, this is free.
How have you got so much faster than me? Good, good, good, good, good, good throw, good throw.
Oh. Oh, no stamina. No. Good hit. Yo. Oh, it's not. Wow. Huh? What just happened?
They better not. They won't do it. Do goals not work anymore? You have to be holding the ball.
Shoot. I got it. Dang it. Patriots fan. Alright, the same... The Yoshi character just takes it
every time. That Yoshi character just picks it up and runs every... Okay, I'm not going anywhere.
This Gumby character. Put it in there. Is his name Prickle? Yeah. Uh-huh. Let me get through
my defense. Where's, where's, where's... Pass it. Alright, somebody just touch it. Give me this ball.
No, no, no, no. Oh, he's gonna run away with it. Okay, that's a good attempt. Nice try. Your
teammate knocks you out like six times. Yeah, this is the way it is. It's fine. Alright, good, good, good.
Don't let it roll down. Nice. Okay, we're in the game. Chad is helping somebody with their math
homework. I would don't... I do not... I would not take math homework advice from Chad. You're gonna end up...
You're gonna end up like on a different continent. Alright, we're back in this. If you throw it, I'll
get it. I just want to get it down. My Gummy. Did I hit the shark out of 15 people? How did I hit him
right in the forehead? You're still in it. You get that ball down here and I'm gonna run away with it.
Somebody just toss it down here and I got it. Get it down here. You can do it. That's their MVP
right there. I want to get in the picture. I'm always lying down in the pictures. The F-Zero
update came out right now. I feel like that's a lie. It's true. I was trying so hard doing the
practice game. I want to do this. Please, somebody vote for this. No one's doing it. Everybody
picks the soccer or football ones. It looks like trivia. Is it some kind of trivia? I want to see
it. Alright, we need a new hit here. How is Otto? Otto's doing good. He needs to get his teeth
cleaned for that. He needs a dental appointment. The game's a little loud. It is kind of loud.
You're right. Oh, I hit the wrong person. You're quiet too. That might be... I'm leaning back
quite a bit. That's probably why. This new setup, I'll make sure I... I got to get it a little bit
more. The word I'm looking for is complete. I'm getting rolled. This is not good. Who even has...
Oh, you have the ball. Alright. Okay. Okay. Okay. Good. Nice. Wait, did you score on our own goal?
Wait, I'm confused. What just happened? You're red.
You're not very good at this. I'm staying all the way back because they just keep barreling
through everybody and just... Okay, I'm staying back here. Yeah, I know this bullshit. I know
this bullshit tactic. Get out of here. I tried. What back brace were you using for your VR streams?
Um, I kind of flip-flopped between just an abdominal band that I would wear.
Kind of on the upper part of my abdomen. I don't remember the brand though. I think it was just
like an abdominal band. Not tight. Just kind of there. Are you making shit up? Nope. Uh, the VR
streams, I have like a jet pack on on some of them. I used to wear a brace for my chest. It was
like a intercostal pain chest piece. It was okay, but it became pretty clear that it was putting a
little too much pressure on my body and wearing something like that for three, four, five, six,
seven hours sometimes was like, uh, this, I should not be doing this. No, no, I'm, I'm quitting. I'm
rage quitting. I don't want to play soccer again. How are you doing now? It's still there. Eh,
it's all right. Pick a map from the main menu. Maybe stretch before. Yeah. So not to get into
it again for the millionth time, but I just realistically have to go just, just do hernia
surgery. I think that's really what it is. And I, I said that like a year or two ago and I just
never did it, but that might not even be the problem. The last doctor I went to that I had a,
an upper endoscopy, they were like, yeah, you have a idle hernia, but it really shouldn't be
causing those problems. Like, oh, oh shit. And then you kind of start convincing yourself. No,
it has to be that. No, it has to be. It's not, it's nothing else. Get in there. But I'm good.
I'm good. I would tell you if I wasn't, I was pretty transparent about it a few years ago,
just managing it. And then maybe I'll just go in and get surgery done to see if it does anything.
It was officially costochondritis, but I don't know. I don't know if I agree with that. I don't
know. Yeah. I don't want to play. I want to hit people with shovels. I don't want to play soccer.
This has 100% less shovel gameplay. Would it be you're just old baby? I mean, that would be kind
of weird because this started and it's been a while. It's been a long time now. I remember
telling doctors being like, oh yeah, it's been going on for like two or three years now. And
that was 2019, 2020. Right. It's weird how you kind of just get used to something and then just
try to not let it dominate your entire life. And don't get me wrong. I am fine. Like this is not
like debilitating at all. It's just there. It can get a little rough sometimes if I'm,
if I said a certain way or I kind of stand up for too long or sit for too long.
Just had hernia surgery three weeks ago. I hope it fixes whatever is going on with you. No,
don't do it. This dude eats goat cheese. Definitely. I do. I like the bear that right
to the left. I love that. I want one of those. I wish there was a dance. Oh no. You had to eat a
whole frozen stick of butter in 30 minutes. How would you do it? Uh, I wouldn't, but if I had to,
if I had to probably just melt it down and drink it. That seems the least awful way.
What's the stipulation here? Do I have to eat it whole or can I put it in something? But I just
have a wicked gross fettuccine Alfredo that has like a ton of butter in it. Fettuccine Alfredo
already has a stick of butter in it. So I'll just eat some fettuccine Alfredo. I think I've
solved your conundrum. I feel like I'm not doing anything, but I also feel like I'm doing a lot.
Just by being a presence back here. See, we won. I did not play. Prove you can make
fettuccine Alfredo. I don't need, I don't know how to make fettuccine Alfredo. I don't know,
butter, shredded cheese, flour, uh, water. I don't even know what's in fettuccine Alfredo.
I know it's like cream, cream, butter, salt, garlic, a little bit of au jus. You know what I
had? Oh man. So my mother made this for me. If you didn't know, I was visiting with my mother
all the way around. And my mother made, it's great to see her by the way. It's been a while.
She tries to make the trip every year or two, but it was wonderful. She taught me how to make
a poached egg because I've tried a million times and I can't do it. But a poached egg on a piece
of toast, jammy in the middle, forget about it. That's the worst egg. Oh no, no. You just haven't
had it made right. Trust me. I've had poached eggs that were just disgusting boogers. I get it. But
a good poached egg, I think is probably the best kind of egg, but they're just so annoying to make.
It's really easy to mess them up. All right, we're going gorilla. Take a piece of toast
or two, two pieces of toast, butter the toast. Nice and buttery. Drop that egg, that poached egg
right on top and just start carving it out with a fork and knife and eating it like steak. So,
so good. I'm putting these in the right side, right? This is not the wrong way, is it?
Yeah, I've heard, uh, my mother talked about the, uh, vinegar, the, I can't say the word,
the vinegar trick. Yeah, poached eggs get really stringy, but if you add vinegar to the water
just a tiny bit, it makes it so it doesn't get so stringy. I'm trying, trying to get him up here.
He's faking his accent. What? What accent? He's faking his accent? What am I doing?
What am I doing? I, I'm not aware of it, whatever it is. What did I do? What did I say?
Am I faking it? I don't know. I don't, I'm not even aware of the word. He just got exposed. I
don't even know what you mean. What word did I say? Mother. Oh, but that's just how you say it.
He just went down. Oh, are you referring to what I just said? Forget about it.
Yeah, that was a little weird. I agree. Oh, look at that pig. You do feel more powerful when you're
the gorilla. Confirmed. Where are you taking it? Get it through the door. Get that pig.
I gotta get this pig. Oh my goodness. Oh my god, I ruined everything. Whoa, we are moving with this
now. Holy shit. We're on point. Pull it. Here we go. Nice. We moved. We went so quick. Oh,
I almost had 11 cookies. That pig was a bat. Oh, a watching bacon and cookies. 12,000. I don't
really want this stuff though. This one's kind of cool. Yeah, I'll get this one. You're not saying
it in the right voice. Yeah, true. Cookies. There you go. Oh, did you mean the Mario version?
Cookies. Well, you got both. I've already dunked your cookie in milk. I've never seen this one.
I thought that said butthole lab. Uh, stay away from the black hole and stay alive. So you take
the cookie if it's an Oreo or if it's a chocolate chip, doesn't matter. You just dunk it halfway.
Count to 10. Take it out. Tap, tap. Bite. Yeah, that's a 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10. Pull it
out. I want it soft, but I don't want it to be mushy. How incompetent do you think we are? No,
that's not what I said. Somebody asked how I dip my cookies in milk. I didn't say every single
person needs to do it like this or you're stupid, but you are if you don't. One omega lull in a sea
of D faces. Hey, hey, hey, hey, you and me get it. Hey, you and me get it. You know what I mean?
This is a cool skin. I like it. All right, don't go in the black hole. Am I doing it right? I think
I just broke my neck. Is he all right? Uh-oh. I think I might be wedged in this. Don't tell him.
I think I just automatically won the game. I think I'm stuck in here. Am I? Something is wedged here
and I can't really figure it out. Oh, I was stuck in the, no, maybe I wasn't. That was weird. I
couldn't move. Oh, that's what just happened. Everybody's a gorilla. Oh, that was an amazing
shot. It's midair. I mean, strategy is obviously grab the cane. They feel about just straight up
milk. Sometimes people treat me like I'm the devil for drinking milk. You do whatever you want. You
you should do eat. You should you should care about whatever you want to care about. Like
things you like. Somebody says it's gross that you drink, uh, you drank, um, like almond milk
or something or regular milk or oat milk. Okay. Every time I talk about the milk that I like,
it's almost like I like almond milk. Well, almond milk is bad. Oh, regular milk. Regular milk is
bad too. Oh, what about, um, oat milk? Oat milk sucks. It's bad. It's really bad. Everything's bad.
Uh, uh, rice, milk, soy milk. I just want my coffee to taste a little creamier. I've somehow
made it all the way. Oh, milk is good, but it depends on the brand. Yeah. I like oat milk right
now. I think oatmeal tastes the best out of all of them. I was just missed and went over. That
would have been so funny. Where's the chain? It's over here, isn't it? That's bad. I didn't even get
anything. I got this guy though. All right. We're good. No, that's my friend. It's just a cat and
three gorillas. Why do I feel like they're on the same team even though they're not? No, get away.
It's mine. Fine. He just knocked me out. You better hold onto me. You'd better hold onto me
this whole time. Dude, you killed us both. I love matcha. I just wanted to call him a freak. Matcha
is great too. Ooh. Well, we have to even the odds. Is that going to hit him? It skimmed right over
his head. How long have we gone without talking about milk? Don't you guys feel like it's sometimes
it's like once every two weeks, bro. You just absolute. You know what? Yeah. There you go.
There you go. Yep. I'm going to hit somebody right in the head. What team am I on? Okay. I'm on yellow.
Well, you stream once every two weeks, so yeah. We just talk about milk every single time I'm live.
So you say, oh, milk, but almond milk. I'm going to be such a bastard here. All right. I want to
avoid hitting you. Oh, that's going to be so sad. Is it going to get anybody? No. Stop engaging in
the conversation. I like that conversation. It's fun, but also to something to keep in mind.
How many people here? It's very possible that there's like 11,000, like 10,000 very much.
Oh shit. I just clicked back into the window and threw the bomb into the trash.
All right. So if this 10,000 people here, it's very possible that this 10,000 people
is a different 10,000 people next time. And the time after that, it could be like another
10,000 different people. Everyone's not all here at the same exact time at the same exact stream.
So if we talk about, uh, oat milk, we might be talking to a completely different group of people.
I still got it. It's okay. Oh, what? No, give it to me. Aha. That's a win right there. At least
it should be. Pick them up already. Why did that explode? Okay. Are you high? No, I'm just chilling
man. Hey, I've done that a million times before. I know how it feels. Dude, don't. You're doing it
on purpose. Of course they are. How would it be on accident? You're just dropping people left and
right. This. Why am I, am I holding it? He's holding it with one hand. Why? Put both hands
on it, please. Oh, you're getting dunked. Hey, we did it. On the ground again. Milk and Pepsi.
I drank the, the pilk on stream. Weird, but it was okay. I would never drink it again, but
I wouldn't spit it out. I love pilk. Hashtag pilk fan. If we have an opportunity, please vote for
that one. One person voted for that. One person voted for it and we're going there. Two of us
voted on the right one. Everybody wants to play sports. I just want to beat people up with shovels.
I need to read this because I, I don't even know what it is. Oh no, I don't. Okay, never mind. What just hit me?
Oh, it was the puck. All right. And there it is. No, there's a cow. I love that. I want that.
That's the best skin in the whole game. It's just so perfect. Big fat orange cat is cool too.
God, that was a good block. That was good. Damn it. I wasn't, if I was lined up right there,
it was just a little to the left. Okay. Oh, it's perfect. Somebody to get it. It's right there.
Look. Set me up. Set me up. Damn it. I think I'm going to get an opportunity right. Get it out of
the corner. Ouch. Do not. Wow. I thought that went in. Is it in? This is a pretty good game so far.
Sorry. Sorry. Not sorry. Racist. Do something about racist. Mean Geno. I'm trying. I had it first.
Macho Man is a voice that if you can do it, you can sometimes do it for like three seconds and
then it just turns into something else. Yeah. Let me tell you. Let me tell you. Let me. Macho Man.
Randy Savage. I'm trying to do a voice. Don't punch me. Cream of the crop. They'll just never
be another Macho Man. Randy Savage. There's a lot of those guys that just, they'll never be another
one ever again. Ever. All right. I want to get lined up. This cow is a good goalie. We got to
get that shield away from you. Right now. A lot of you might not know this, but you know the way
that I talk sometimes where I talk like this. Emphasizing a lot of the W's. That's Mean Gene
Oakland. Mean Gene Oakland was a huge, huge influence on like voice stuff. He had this
incredibly particular way of talking. He was a master at it. You just did it in your own goal?
Oh, sorry. Oops. I'll make up for it right now. Get up. What? Oh, I thought we got a goal because
he put the shield in his own goal. That's weird. Set me up. Set me up. Set me up. Set me up. Set
me up. I'll be goalie. That's fine. I keep getting clocked by this thing every time. That's a
beautiful setup. Oh yes. There we go. I haven't seen him contribute in any way. You must have
just came to the stream because I'm the one that got the first goal and it was a beautiful shot.
Like this. Good tie. Oh no, we won. He was the team's clown. Yeah, I have to entertain everybody.
The goal. I finally got my face in a picture. No more sports. More shovel. Yeah, that's what I'm
saying. You always feel the compulsive need to entertain everybody. I think that just comes
with not being able to sit still. So talking a lot is a way to expel a lot of energy.
Which I usually have a lot of. Maybe not so much anymore, but I still do. 10 years ago, 15 years ago,
I was just a ball of just energy that had to constantly be doing something or talking or
moving. I've definitely mellowed out a lot in the last five years, I'd say. Without a doubt.
You're a mellow yellow. Do I? Wait a minute. That's soda, right? It's a drink. Just block them all.
That's a great strategy. Make it so they can't get over here.
I don't have stamina. How are we holding hands backwards behind? That was very strange.
God damn it. Is Mountain Dew for boring people? I didn't even mean to do that and I hit my own
teammate. No, I didn't. OK, I'm on green this time. Mellow yellow is boring? I feel like that's the
opposite because wouldn't Mountain Dew be the default and that's just the one to get because
it's Mountain Dew because it's everywhere and it's the popular one? Mellow yellow to me is no,
we don't got Mountain Dew. We got mellow yellow. It's like, whoa, interesting. You've got,
I haven't seen that in a while. That's like having squirt in your fridge. It's like,
oh shit, you've got, you've got squirt? I would have thought it would have been a Sprite.
Oh, whatever. I don't care. I don't even care. I don't care. Oh shit.
Oh, that was very embarrassing, but it's OK. I just forgot to hold right trigger to grab onto
the ledge and just hit my teeth off the ledge. Squirt is a good soda. One of the best. Not
messing around this time. Wow, nice. Ooh, tiger skin. There are a lot more models in this game
than I thought there were going to be. Highlord Tyrion Fordring needs you, champion. The Lich
King must be stopped. Yeah, I also can sit in Dalaran for 60 minutes a day and hear that
two or three times. One shot, one shot, one shot to get up. Please get up. One shot. You're going
to get us both killed. You're going to get us both killed. Who's your favorite Dragonball Z
character? Who's the one that goes like this? Boo. That's right. That's the one. I'm alive,
right? I'm holding it. Not Mr. Satan. No, it's not Boo. I don't give a shit about Boo
at all. I just thought it'd be funny to do that for five seconds. It's Mr. Satan. It's not Mr.
Satan. I just like that voice. So I say it's my favorite character, but it's actually Beerus.
Fuck that guy. It's Goku. You know what I mean? And that's how you tell everybody
your top four favorite DBZ character. He's on the wiki looking at them all.
In the beginning of the stream, I told you I was lying down. I don't have Wikipedia over here.
I'm lying in one of those beanbag chair, upright chair things on the ground. I don't
got Wikipedia. You lost viewers for that? Oh, they weren't strong enough. I thought
you were going to punch me, but you didn't. So I'm not going to punch you. Look at that tiger.
That's so sad. That's so sad. He made it? What? I just knocked myself out?
I was trying to. Okay. I did not know that could happen.
You got styled on. I did. You're right. We still got a shot. Oh, now you're all in trouble.
That was my friend, but it's okay. It's not here yet. Please lift that up. Don't leave me hanging.
Keep it up. Thank you. Oh, we got a 2v1 scenario, don't we? No. Did I die?
I'm dead. I didn't even know that was possible. That alligator is so fucked up right now.
Stop. Somebody has to pull the lever. I'll do it. What's this? Is this a helmet?
My buddy's still here. Oh, shit. Don't. What? It broke. It broke. Why am I getting the three
stooges shit happening to me all the time? All right. That's not a bad photo. Preferred
brand vacuum cleaner. A stick vacuum. I don't have to plug it in. I'm a mover. I'm like a
cellar spider when I vacuum. I'm just up all over the place. I'll start in the corner in one room.
I'll just walk to the other room and just go in the other room. In the bedroom. One, two, three.
Just walk across the fucking hall. Just go across to the other room. In the bathroom. Just zooming
around with a stick vacuum. Because when you don't have a stick vacuum, you end up having
you're tethered to the plug. Vacuum a whole room with a plug in the wall and all of a sudden it's
like, yeah, I got to unplug this. Pick this up. It's kind of heavy. I got a bag. I got to move to
another room. Where's an outlet? Am I going to have the problem where I vacuum too far where
the outlet can't reach and there's just one strip that is just never done because I just don't care
about the vacuum can't go that far? Stick vacuum. Add coal into the furnace to speed up your train.
Okay. Bro, what's the brand? We don't want to rant. Um, I had a Dyson stick vacuum,
but I broke it. I have it. A Dyson is like, it's like a Cadillac. I just, I, I don't want to get
another one. Cause what if I break that one? And they're very expensive. One of my friends came
over one time and they thought I had one of those standing hand sanitizers in the corner of the
room. Like they were like, why do you have a big hand sanitizer? I was like, that's not what that
is. Cause it does kind of look like one. It looks like a big standing hand sanitizer. He was like,
I was going to go over and put my hand underneath it. I thought you were a weirdo for a second,
but it's a vacuum. What train am I putting this? I never played this one before. Holy
shit. Drop it. That was a big one too. Let's go put them in the furnace. Oh, that was a bad idea.
Damn it. All right. They're ahead of us. Forget about that guy. He's just going to troll us.
Okay. What does this do? Is it the gas? I didn't know if you had to heat it up.
Why would you break? Oh, but why? Oh, I get it. I was saying, why is there a lever on? I get it.
I get it. I get it. All right. We're going to, we'll be fine. Oh my God. You are shit face.
Just get it in. I'm so sad. I'm an anchor right now. Misjudge the jump just a little.
Steal this too. Oh, give me the shovel. We're winning. I was such an annoying distraction.
We won. My head. Fuck you. We did it. Oops. Yeah. They're not halfway there. We've
been by a mile. I got it. Yes. I want that one. I got it. I did not think I was going to be playing
this for almost five hours, but it's really fun. How do you feel about boiled peanuts?
I don't know if I've ever had them. I don't really know. I ate them. What are they in?
You just eat them by themselves. I don't think I've ever had it before. So do you take the
peanuts out of the shells or is it in the shells? And then you take them out in the shells. Okay.
You know what? You take them out. How long do you boil them in the shells for in water?
They're so good. Seven hours. You do it for a couple of what you boil them for hours.
I kind of am interested in this though. So not you just talking about like on the stovetop.
I feel like that would be kind of crazy. Rock pot will do it. Yeah. On low heat. Let me take
care of this guy. This person just had a bunch of groceries in their hands. That was so sad.
This is one of those games where you just giggle. Wait, you mean I can smash somebody's head with
this? We got to go. You got it. We got to shove it in. Just kick it in. Kick it. Punch it. How
do you do emotes? There we go. That was weird. It was like I was trying to press left stick,
right stick. That was so lucky that we got this immediate spawn. If the team is AFK. Oh,
that's sad. All right. Good job. You didn't have to go in too. We can let them get one gumdrop.
Right? We can't just take them all. We got the perfect placement on this too. This is the way
to do it. And they were AFK. Oh, I just won a quick match without being knocked out. I don't
know where I am. Oh, I got money. Let's open up one of those surprise eggs. 200. So if I
1080, I feel like that's going to take a while. Yeah. I want one now. It's green. What is it?
Is that like epic or something? Cute. Pink sparky. Uncommon. Dark ancient underbite.
Don't I already have this? I want to see those ones. What were those? Dark ooga. Okay. But could
you beat Goku though? Yes. I 100%. I 100% could beat Goku at rock, paper, scissors. Maybe spend
five grand on skins. No. Can you even use real money? You can. All right. I got some cool stuff.
What'd I get? I got a melon hat. How do I change outfit? Oh, there we go. Melon hat or do that one.
I mean, maybe I get a little, like a little bit of the in-game currency, but I'm going to spend
$5,000. That's too much. How did we fuck that up? How did we screw that up? I was going to say that
was three knuckleheads. Yeah. I think the game's definitely worth it. Especially if you have a
group of friends. This is one of those ultimate party games and the varieties there. I thought
this was going to be four maps or so. I was completely wrong. And yeah, it's on. I thought
that was one of my teammates pissed that I kept trying to grab the ball. Can somebody get it in
there? It's on Game Pass. That's right. Ace Attorney is coming to Game Pass. You have no excuse now.
Okay. True. That's true. Trying to run away with it here. Don't tease me like that. I'll play. I'm
definitely not going to play the whole series. I'm not going to do all of them. I'll try one or two
cases because I don't know how much I like those games. Genuinely. I've never played one. I have
downloaded them on four separate devices over the course of 10 years, but I haven't played it.
I know. It's weird. I've gotten it on iPad, on Steam, on what was the like, like a PS4.
I've just, I buy it every single console generation with the intent that I'm going to play it.
And I just don't. They're not great stream games. Yeah. But I mean, I got a new philosophy anyways,
right? Doesn't everything doesn't have to be, oh, it's going to be really high energy and
tons of interaction. And maybe it's just fun to do one day just to hang out and play it.
A lot of reading out loud. Well, I do sorcery. Sorcery is fun.
Kind of the same thing, right? Yeah. I've said a thousand year door. That's the one where Luigi
goes. I'll give it a try. That was a great walk down there by player 244. I'll tell you what I'm
the most excited for besides Elden Rings DLC. WarioWare. They're going back to the basics
on WarioWare. That is, I'm going to play the absolute hell out of that game. I'm going,
I'm going to try to 100% that game. I hope it's good. You can swear, you know, right?
Yeah. But my mother was just here and I'm kind of used to being a little more, a little more tame.
All right, everybody, if you're in the game right now, dude, oh, we're doing icebreaker.
I want to, what is that one? But you're almost 40. It doesn't matter how, if you're 30, 40, 50,
nobody wants to be like, oh, fuck this. Fuck you. And fuck that and fucking whatever.
It's my mother. You're going to come on. My mom cusses a lot. Yeah. My mother swears too a lot.
My mother and father both swear. It was never like weird, but I tone it down. You tone it down
a little bit. You don't want to, you just don't want to overdo it in front of ma and dad. My mom
is here. How come you're not playing this? I'm sure your mother would think this was fun. I'm
sure your mother would love this game. Why you guys should play it. Family friendly streamer.
Stay tuned. Coming up next. We got, can't think of anything funny. Just imagine I was pretending
to be a like G rated person. Okay. So how do we feel about that? I somehow got the W on that one.
And I don't know how. You're watching the Disney channel. Oh, that's also a dinosaur.
Ooh. Oh, that shut the whole crowd up. I just slipped on the banana field. All right. We're
good. Sorry, mom. They were Yoshis before. Yeah, that's true. They can stay Yoshis. My shovel.
I did not hit my head on the shovel. Right. We can all agree on that. Shit. Oh, that's not good.
That's bad. Not good. I'm going to die. I'm so greedy. I want it so bad. And now I'm dead.
Now I think I'm dead. I'm so sorry. I forgot you were on my team. Get me away from the edge.
Damn it. Oh, that's so sad. That's very sad. I couldn't get him with the, I still have a
teammate in here, right? Not anymore. Too slippery. Is this a bit? Uh, no, it's just when the changing
teams like one round, you're on green one game. You're on blue one. You're on red. Oh my God.
That was a great shot. Oh, I hit him. I had this exact same idea and we both missed. You leave him,
but leave him alone. Leave him alone. This is my friend. That was a dangerous move, but it was
worth it. Oh, I took his head off. Just jumped over it. Let go of the shovel and get up, bro.
What are you doing? I couldn't drop the shovel. I couldn't drop the shovel.
It was just still in my hands. Oh, I got you. I got you. I got you. You got it. I know you got
this. Roman, Roman, Roman. That's teamwork right there. You can do it. No, it was a good try.
Nice try. Anybody's game. I, I, I have no defense on that. I don't have a defense on what just
happened. Dude, you're going to kill yourself too. You're going to die down here too. It's not worth
it. You, you, it's not worth it. Trust me. Just get up there. See, forget about the bat. No,
you okay? Don't get on this. I'm dead. I was just way too far away. I wouldn't have made it.
Is my buddy still here? No. He doesn't see it. You're a bad teammate. I accidentally hit him.
I protected him at least two or three times, but it was the one time that I hit him in the head
with the shovel. You guys are going to keep going back to a lot of stuff. All right. Deny yellow at
all costs. That was the plan. Get up, get up, get up, get up, get up. All right. Dunk him. As long
as I don't go in the water, I don't care. Shit. That's bad. Oh, thank God. I just can't catch a
break. Get me up. Oh, what? How am I still here? Time for you to go for a fucking swim.
Oh shit. Shovel versus pan. Oh shit. Oh, I thought I had an extra half second. No,
he got me with the very, very end of it. It was like the tip of the top of it. He had the length.
Yeah. I was always going to be hard. He had a full foot on me and what he could be able to swing
with. I made it in the picture. All right. Last one. Last one. And then I am going to go eat some
dinner and I'm going to go chill. What's the other game I said I wanted to play? Oh,
Resident Evil 4 DLC. Uh, we got to close it on a typhoon. It's the best one. F 0 99 and the DLC
for Resident Evil 4. He's addicted to the funny animal game. Oh, it's great. It's great. Let me
think of some good. Let me look at the calendar. Maybe Sunday, Sunday or Monday. All right. I got
to go out big. So my best games were with the cat. When are you going to stream? Uh, either Sunday
or Monday or this week? Likely Monday. Monday makes the most sense for me. Schedule wise.
It's going to be annoying over here. No, you don't understand. It's the boat. That's the problem.
It's the boat. That's the problem. We need to fight the boat. You guys don't get it. They want
us to fucking kill each other and then they'll get all the snacks. Oh God. Watch out. I'm just
climbing up. If there's ever a game that I wish the floss was in, it's this one because I would
just do it right here. Welcome. What the hell was that? I don't think a bird shit on me. Oh,
I don't think any of us are going to get out of here. Yeah, there's, there's no getting up.
Okay. Now there is, this is a victory for sure. Come on, come on. I had more health than you did.
I had more health than you. Didn't I? Oh, but cracked out right now. Hey, what's up? You piece
of shit. Oh, that's my friend. So fucking sorry. I'm so sorry. He's AFK. Whatever. It doesn't matter.
It's not like he was playing anyways. Oh boy. I might be in trouble. I don't think I have enough
stamina to get up all the way. Oh, it's going to be close. Okay. You dummy. Oh no, my friend. Oh,
stay up back into the cockpit again. I was going to spam the head butt button and see what happens.
He was just left, right, left, right, left, right, left, right, left, right, left, right to my face
and killed me. Come on, man. Yeah, that was all wind up in the face. Right hand,
elbow up, back, left hand in the face. Repeat 10 times. I was not going to get up from that.
I'm going off the stop rope. Oh, the rocket came out. I just got rocked. Come on. It's right there.
Grab it. It's right here. Put somebody in the missile silo. I got somebody in the very beginning
of the stream. Dammit. Well, let's see if I can blow somebody up. Is my teammate still here?
Oh no, they're AFK now. Good placement. Yes. Holy shit. That was diabolical, dude.
You already had the wind. You froze him and then just kicked his dead, lifeless body into the
water. That was terrible. What are you looking at? Whoops. I'm going to get him right in the head.
No. Fuck. How much higher? Of course. We want yellow to win, but looks a little hairy right now.
Oh, maybe. Okay. We need a crown too. Yeah. Let's get this. Let's get this party going.
I'm underneath this and I can't get up. What the fuck? Am I underneath the boat?
Oh, that rocket's coming out. Blast him. This is going to be so scary for this guy.
Nice try. Fuck that. You thought you could get rid of me? Not yet. That's not fair. They shouldn't
be able to throw things from the stands. You shouldn't be able to throw things from the
stands. That's just not... That's very dangerous. I just hit with the ground. Oh, all right. I went
for the punch. Is there a reason why I was just electrocuted for a hundred million years?
Why me? Why me? Anybody else? Leave me alone. Somebody help me. Oh,
now the tables have turned. Looks like you're in a little bit of a pickle, aren't you?
Be careful down there. Oh, you're alive I see. Hello, Captain. I thought I was friendly.
I was not. It always happens like this. And then someone's going to drop a brick on my head and
they're going to throw me overboard. This gorilla... Yeah, see? Somebody stop him. Stop him.
Gorilla, help me. It's 2v2 with one on each team. 2v2. That's fine. I'll just climb to the top.
Ow. Let go. I should have won that. This didn't have enough health. Watch out. Why am I not
swinging it? Damn it. You want to put me in the fucking juice machine, huh? You want to put me
in the juicer? I think you're gonna put me in the fucking meat grinder, don't you? Well, now we're
both dead. I hope you're happy. I gotta go. Oh my god. That was the strongest headbutt I have ever
seen. That was... I just got sent to outer space. You can definitely get there. Are you kidding me?
Sitting there. I'm holding Y and right trigger and this won't do it. I have to try. Too much lasagna?
That was a crazy headbutt. Is it green? It wasn't blue. All right, one more. I want to do one more.
Actually, one more. I mean it. I just went out really badly. Rude. Rude. Still looked the coolest
though. There's some pretty cool cats here. This game seems rage-inducing. You would think so,
but everything is so goofily presented that you can't be. Please play as Melon Dog. I don't think
I can. Don't pull the brake this time. Yeah, I'll try. I'll be Melon Dog. Should I actually
try winning this time? It's not about winning. It's about... Whoa. Is that a moose? That's cool.
What an insane animal a moose is. Sometimes you forget just how unbelievably massive a moose
really is. They're like elephants. They're gigantic. They're such a majestic... Are those antlers too?
What? Was it the sign? Did I get hit in the face by the sign?
Oh. All right. I'm gonna go fuck with the other team. It's just like looking into the abyss.
I have... I just... I need to go over here. All right. Well, they let me help them. Let's see.
Stop. I'm on your team. Holy shit. It's a mess over here. I want to play too. Actually, you know,
while that's happening, let's load this shit up. Forget about this. All right. Forget about the
moose. Just put the coal in. He's doing it on purpose to mess with us. It's such a great strategy
because it's just like I have to get this moose. He's just... We have to kill him. And then you
can just get distracted the whole time. All right. Somebody kill the moose. No. No. Get me out of the
fire. Whoa. Easy. I think we can still do it. Okay. I've had just about enough of this. Get out of
here. Hey. Okay. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go.
I think we're going to lose. It wasn't my fault though. I just jumped off the edge like five
times accidentally and then accidentally killed the teammate and a little bros running around
here with a tennis racket right now. He's no regard for anything. He's just hitting every...
It doesn't matter who it... He doesn't care what letters or colors or... He's just hitting
everybody it doesn't matter who it is this this gator needs to be stopped immediately he still
has it somebody stop him stop this fucking gator you're watching too much tiktok i don't have i
don't have tiktok guys i'm not even signed into youtube i watch youtube shorts until i fuck up
my entire algorithm to to the point where it's just just wacky wacko shit and then i have to
clear all my search history and all my fucking browser history on it so i reset the algorithm
again and then it gets all fucked up again in like 20 minutes yeah and it's even worse when
you reset the algorithm it's even worse for like 10 minutes 20 minutes 30 minutes and then you go
through one of these youtube shorts it's just like oh shit this was like a fucking goofy one
and i could have just skipped it but i was on it from the whole time i watched the whole thing
so now i fucked up the algorithm again one too many roll the glass down the stairs videos and
it's just like oh i want to see what happens and it's like oh shit ah damn it now i gotta go clear
the watch history again and i watch him every time i watch him the whole way through i don't watch
very much youtube shorts though i feel like they literally burn a hole in your brain i i i seriously
all right now that was supposed to be the last one oh wait and i want to do a sports one they're
fun wait is this football or soccer yeah no i i gotta go i want to eat something it's been a
little while since i've had some food is it bad is it bm if i leave now that's all bots anyways
you get um if you leave it's bm you have to play okay fine let's make this quick all right we got
we have the advantage here i'm not gonna let otter take the ball from us are we get it downfield
how did i not grab it what am i doing why would he oh my stamina bar is low and somehow i managed
to get out with that they were just pulling me in two different directions that was good
all right get it downfield down down down down no okay good it's all right i'm gonna rip his head
that's a lot of people all holding the ball like help me get that shit out of here now this is
interesting um i don't think the ball is technically on the ground or i don't know
where it is all right if we actually score after that that's gonna be awesome come on we can do it
that's so clutch if we do get it bunny oh so clutch get it in there you didn't think i was
ready for that you didn't think i was ready to catch you didn't think i was ready to catch that
is that what you thought did you think that oh no get it funny right there come on get it in there
that's a huge that's a huge deal that's one for the history books for sure how come that didn't
count before i think because the ball was on top of so many people that it technically was like out
of bounds that's my best guess oh they're pissed off now all right yeah they are not happy about
that stay back here right through his head no we can't just let him run away with it like this
yeah yep yep yep yep yeah let's go but one more two more uh that's gonna be a goal all right well
the game now and that is big so is this if i stop you big run it in yeah nice i like this one way
more than the soccer one or the hockey one all right we're all here we're all here just let
let somebody let somebody grab it everybody wants to be the hero of the game i'm running the stamina
somebody grab it we could win it right here there you go wow the juke that was unbelievable
he went a little too far over his head i just he knows he's coming wow that was well played
on both of them that was a great play for both of them it just one of them did it a little better
oh no stamina good exactly what you should have done yeah oh yes it's all right good good good
good grab it grab it shit they're gonna tie it up no they're not okay three what four to two
four three just a little bit chance oh we should be all right do not let him run away with it like
that together oh that's it nice so i was about to score right here anyways all right went out on a
win that's good all right everybody i will see you guys on probably monday but did i get any money
because if i got money then no monday probably around like four or five pacific this game is
really good this is a great just kind of hang out and play a game it's a great kind of party game i
would imagine but yeah see you guys soon see you in four or five days monday is what four or five
days from now how's it going that was fun uh gonna have some pretty interesting things uh to talk
about very soon a couple of fun things uh grotto beach tts is very very close very close i'd expect
you'll see a lot more on that very very soon and that's just going to kind of live as long as people
want to play it and then there's something else fun i'm going to be doing something it'd be
interesting i got to figure out a lot of stuff here in the next like three months we're going
to do sorcery on monday uh i want to do the resident evil 4 dlc so we'll do that that if
that takes three or four hours maybe but that's the plan for monday i hope you start making youtube
shorts i want to do a youtube short where i just have a podcast microphone in front of me it's like
a podcast room and i'm just talking to somebody who also has like a podcast mic in front of them
as if this is like episode 400 i find that to be kind of funny just upload a shitload of them
i've seen people do that that's funny i don't have very i really don't have any plans for youtube
shorts maybe i remember talking to stir about how interesting the concept was and he's talked
about it a lot too but a youtube short for me i would want it to be i there's two kind of schools
of thought it's like highlight interesting things that happen on a stream but also or that's
something that's happened in a video but also a completely just original 30 second short video
then i feel like you go kind of down the rabbit hole with that and i don't know exactly how much
time i want to put into something like youtube shorts not really much time at all if i'm honest
turn this off yeah thanks for hanging out thanks for watching i didn't i think a couple of raids
came in looks like i missed them i'll get in a more comfortable setup though this is step one of
three stages to be able to kind of not be sitting so upright when i stream and i feel pretty good i
feel okay usually after about six hours i kind of start to lock up a little and feel like but
i felt pretty good today so are you laying down well i'm not that was a joke i'm sitting up but
i'm just sitting back into a more comfortable kind of pillowy chair and it is on the ground
i have stuff underneath me too on the ground it's comfortable i like it yeah i'll see you guys on
monday i'll be around like let's just say five pacific that makes sense do another kind of later
night stream i'll have face cam on next time because i mean it's a horror game all right see
you guys soon take care call your mother you know you know the drill all you have to do why not
go on both call your siblings call your friends all right take care