I'm just gonna stick this medigun up your ass and we're gonna kill everybody. That sounds fine. I'll grab
the righteous bison
Oh, you can juggle I didn't know you could juggle Jerma. I learned how to the other day when I was bored waiting for my
Anal exam. Oh, really? How'd that go? They put the juggled in my butt. What's a juggle? Oh
Right. We were just talking about juggling
I
Don't know that it's a noun but I mean
The juggle is it time? Is it time here? Is it time? Yeah, not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet
Not yet. Use it. Yeah, I needed it for that ng because screw ng's watch up on a scope
No one here now. Yeah. Oh backstab. Watch out turn around turn around. I was
Could have gone better. It was like a whole nest up there a second ago
Could have sworn at least yeah
Things. Hey, that's all that matters shot a guy killed an engineer
That's top priority mini century engineer. That is like not priority number one
That sounds smash, you know, we're gonna go around the round the back
It's right for that spy too, cuz he's like always killing me because I'm Jerma
I got a double kill at the crit rocket. Like I was standing there just like waiting to see who would hit and I got
Me killed
Yeah
That was very very crazy looking on my screen. It looks like you just disconnected from the game
Are you dead? No, I'm alive. I made it out
he's
Connach I feel like I've done nothing. Oh
Bye. I was like, are you ready? You ready Jerma? No, not yet. There's no one here. Oh
Let me heal this guy
Boy, oh boy. I'm gonna die. I had to run. Okay. I'm coming with you. Where you be? I'm on the cart
I'm just trying to get some help. Oh, I forgot I had them
What keeps happening to you, I don't know but at least I'm doing it spectacularly
I mean if you're gonna die make a scene of it and
We need like a bug we'd like six snipers standing in the same spot for you to get like a quadruple to the kill
Oh
Oh, he jumped down going for it. Oh you oh, he took so much damage. Let's back up. We can't be here
This is scary gonna get on that cat. Oh
No, they're kind of like camping them. Maybe we can stay here kind of where's the red team?
I don't know. Where the hell is the other team? What's going on? Oh, I got this reload the bison and here it goes
Use it going up. Oh
That was pretty oh back step. That's okay. I think we we are winners. I'm gonna go scalp
I'm gonna go scale just a run on the cot just sprint on it. Oh, yeah
I got him pretty good here at spawn. This is how we do it
Top frag again, I'll play the Solomon
Soldier is a spy. The heavy is a spy. The heavy is a sniper. What?
Good job
Should have played harder. What did he just like shoot him in the friggin door?
There was like a hundred of them at the gate like how they always placed them there
Yeah, I was like I was like standing where the train tracks are like I would do like behind the cart
Oh, I think that some of them got blown back by an explosion
Okay
Makes sense
There we go. Pray. I love your rock anybody in there
I'm you I'm also birding to death somebody in there somebody in there. I just heard like I heard the ding
I heard the ding. What's the ding it goes dings? Which class did oh the ding?
I heard a ding. Oh a lot of stuff going on up here
I love all that guy just thought this was an actual built dispenser. I've done that so many times before
I keep thinking that like I'm not used to that yet. I've seen the sentries do that
What way dispensers are newer you think they would fix that you think they wouldn't fix like the invisible players
You think they would fix a lot of things like heavies hands disappearing valve. What the heck man
Hey, come up left with me. We got to be one again. Come over here. I'm right over here. Yeah, is it good?
Hey, let's go adventure
There's way for this to open wait. Just wait here. Just just crouch in the corner with me
We're gonna have a good time. Don't shoot hold your fight. Okay. Oh
Mini century don't think so. I think we're winning. I'm damn looks like it. We have the heavy
No, don't you think about it? Don't you think about it?
I am in desperate need of a medic big time or this health back. Thank many century. Where are you where?
There's a mini century in that gray gravel Co building and I'm afraid to go over and do anything about it
Oh, it's gone. Hey, I could smell you scout right behind you. Just keep walking forward. Oh
Sentry
Whoa, you didn't top left top left. Oh, I'm up there. Oh, there's a lot of people up there. I'm up there
That's cool. Oh my god, there's a video. We did it. He got 50 points for just standing on the car
Wow, well, he really did he really got 30 above everyone else just for I'm gonna stand on the cart