Hey, I want to grab my phone. Give me one second. All right, phone downstairs. Let me just make a
tweet and I'll be with you shortly. Good afternoon. Continuing our stream journey from yesterday. I
said I was going to play max action, maximum action today, right now. Does anyone actually
believe that Jerm is a real person? Anywho, I'm going to turn it on. This game is an action game.
Of course it is. No, no, it's a reading game. This is a second grade reading, teaching second graders
how to read. Imagine naming your game maximum action and it's just a reading game. I should,
I'm going to do that. I should do that. Where's Terraria? You're going to have to ask Mr. Star
that question because Terraria, his computer was broken last time I talked to him and he was like,
my PSU. I think I got that right. Power supply. I don't know. Maybe this weekend. We'll see what
he's doing. But hope you're having a good day. Let's get started. I have the game up. Now I
don't know how much content is in this game. I think there's probably like less than an hour or
two of content. So from here, we are going to play probably rollercoaster tycoon two. Michael
action movie. Wait, it's a movie. Michael action maximum productions. I don't know. That's just a
placeholder. Okay. How about, uh, just call me Mike. Movie studio name. How about, uh, does this,
I don't think this even matters. We don't care about this paid promotion. I've, I've, I don't
do those paid promotion. Uh, this is not, I'm just, that's a good, that's a good title.
It's like half-life characters. All right. I guess, well, you know, it's gotta be like the,
the German colors, right? This is gloves. Outer body. Let's go. There we go. Hello, body. Glove.
No, we need more blue. Change of glasses too. All right. It looks all right. Tutorial. All
scenes are a work in progress. Maybe missing assets, textures, or gameplay elements and not
representative of final product. Well, this game is about, it's kind of like a combination of what
I'm told is there's like Max Payne, John Wick and hotline Miami. It looked at, it was a recommendation.
Looked interesting. I felt this, I felt like I wanted to play it. All right. How are you, how
we doing? Welcome to maximum action. Press escape to pause and adjust options. Okay. Press mouse three
to kick. Press mouse zero to punch. Mouse one to punch. Mouse three to kick. Okay. Well, that's fun.
Okay. FOV 90 or next game. I think it already is.
Oh shit. It's not. You got me. How would you know that? How would you possibly know that? No,
this is no way.
Press R to reload. Press E to pick up weapons. Okay. Now what? What do I do? Press zero
to do what? Oh, I do that. Where is it not loaded? Okay. He's jumping. Press G to drop weapons.
You know, you could throw shit. Okay. Let me, I got to rewind that. Just put that at the other mouse.
That's good. Right there. Okay. Good. It's empty. All right. So now what do I go?
That's kind of fun. What is the TV that tells me what to do? Oh,
let's go. Hold left shift to slow down time. That's pretty cool. All right. Press left shift to enter
action time. Hold. Okay. So that's the same thing. Time moves as you shoot. Hold down
to slow down time. Okay. And then press it to do action time. That's what I just did.
Time moves when you shoot. That's not happening. Yes. The binding. Why is the binding the same?
Come on. Action time. Left shift. I think that's just, I think that's just what it is.
Yeah. Okay. Just, you just, I just tapped it. Yeah.
Gain action time through movement, sprinting, diving, and sliding.
I just headbutt that thing. All right.
All right. That's fun. Hold C while moving to slide. Nice. Press space while moving to dive.
All right. Press mouse three in the air to kick boost off of things.
Hold on. Damn. That's cool. All right. Press X to use the grenade launcher.
Okay. X to use grenade launcher. There it is. Throwing weapons, diving and kicking can break
glass. Good. Press use to continue. I feel like this is going to be really, really fun.
Okay. I don't know if that's supposed to happen. All right. Get the henchmen.
All right. What do I want to use? This one and this one. I don't have that many hands.
Let's go. All right. I got it. Great job. I did it. I got all the henchmen. All right. Let's go.
So let's just do the intro. Is there like, I don't think there's a story in this game.
All right. I'm ready. Do you have to go fast? Punch here. All right. First aid. Hold mouse
four to pick up props. Wait. No. Shit. I wanted to pick that up. Mouse four. No. That's kick.
Stop that. Okay. I got it. Can I pick the bed up? Wait. Bucket. Frash. Okay. Dive. Hold mouse
four to pick up props. Yeah. I know. I have to be quiet. Action recording system. When you walk
through the door ahead, the game will begin to record your action. Your goal is to create the
most action-packed take and receive the highest action score possible. You can rewatch your scene
once you have completed the section. Good luck. All right. Wait. I didn't go through the door yet.
Wait. Oh. Am I dead? What? Should I? Can I watch my movie? Where's my movie? Scene select. Other
modes. Other modes? Endless mode. All of us are a work in progress. Scene select. Do I have to
beat it before I can see it? I have to win to get the movie. All right. Fucking. That's easy. Let's
go. This is loud. Okay. Let's go. I gotta get good to get the movie. All right. We'll start with the
TV. All right. I just Dragon Ball Z'd that guy. He ain't getting up. Here we go. Action. All right.
And close it. Oops. Bounce. Holy shit. That's too many. I need a gun. Oh boy. Try to keep going.
Exit. What the fuck? I didn't have any bullets left. Okay. I'm getting it. I'm understanding it.
And those are not infinite bullets. No. Stop. Get up. Why am I falling down? Let's go. Which way should I go?
Is that a baseball bat? Give me that gun. Give me. No. Give me the gun. Gun. Gun. Gun. Where's he?
This thing's empty. Stop. Give me the gun. How close do I have to be to get the gun?
Free bolts. I get it. Let's see it. Let's see if it was any good.
I keep fucking proning. Oh, I switched to press V. What's happening over there?
I did it. Let's go. Continue. I'm understanding how this is played.
Too quiet? Too quiet? What does this say? Is this mouse sensitivity? All right. I'm ready.
Scene select. Scene one. Action. No. Go back in. I had to kick this guy out the window.
I got it. You guys wanted it loud, huh? Wait. What's this? No. This way. That's gonna be good.
That's gonna be a good scene. No. I didn't want to do that. I thought it exploded. Shit. I was too
insane. Oh, God. I got destroyed. One action movie. It's a Call of Duty camper. Shit. Is he dead?
Got it. Let's go. Oh, you can go over 100 health. That's good to know.
Slide. I thought I threw that and caught it in midair. Who? Excuse me. All right. Slide. Action. Slide.
They're dead. Okay. Never mind. Let's go. Get out there. All right. Do I have bullets?
Which way do I go? Where do I go? Where do I go? Where do I go? Over here. What? Is there a boss?
Oh, God. I think it's a boss. I can't pick that up. Ow. That's so loud in my ears. Slide. Away from
the fight. I turned the sensitivity too high. I get it. Here we go. It's too loud. All right.
Let's watch the movie. All right. Even there. I'm lost. The actor doesn't even know where to go.
Uh, come on. Chaz, you really fucked it up. You missed your marks like five times.
Oh, that was so stupid. I dove on my own grenade. Here we go. Switch. This is
when I'm trying to figure out how to switch weapons. Good job, Chaz. Oh, health. It's so loud.
I have to turn it off.
That's, that's, that's something. It sure is. Coming up next is, uh, the streets. The streets
available? Yeah. I'm going to try to do something actual cool. Okay. Actually cool. I'm going to do
the, there's going to be stealth movie so far. Not bad. Nevermind. I can still do it. I think.
All right. Movie's still going. I need health. No. Whoops. Where's the gun? I lost my stealth gun.
Out of bullets. What's that? God damn it. Give it to me. I need health. Oh my God. I'm almost dead.
Oh, fuck. All right. This movie's too long. Oh, what happened? Oh my God. That guy blew up.
Good. I just pressed the button. I kind of want to do that one again. Just run and press the button.
Good shot of the wall. Oh, I double stopped that guy. I think I can get it. I can think,
I think I can slow mo run through the whole level and just jump and touch the thing.
How am I going backwards? Was that my voice? Didn't I go like, oh yeah. I screamed there,
didn't I? I'm going to try that again. I think I can do it. Ready? I just have to believe.
Jump off the wall. Jump off the wall. No. All right. Still worked. Stuck.
Somebody up top here, right? They're still chasing me. Oh, shit. Just touch the button. I did it.
Okay, good. Let's see how that one turned out. I really didn't want to shoot anyone.
Did I jump on top of the bullet? Okay. What are these edits? This is the kind of edit where
this is a flashback sequence. This is not even happening in real time. This is just,
I'm having a vision flashback sequence. What the fuck is going on? That didn't happen.
He shot me that many times. Remember that. You can die in the recording. All right. Restaurant.
Thank you PJFS for the five community subs and Chris Bach for the five community subs as well.
Here we go. Hold on. Let me see if I can be like a Mario. Oh, fuck. I'm in trouble.
Give it. Nothing in here. Oh, shit. Give me the chair. Chair. Anything. Something. Shit.
No. They're spawning it. Give me the health. Get the health, please. I jumped over it.
Fuck. Give me the shotgun. Give me the shotgun. Okay. I have two health. I gotta do this right.
Just throw a grenade out there. What? That wasn't a headshot? All right. Here we go. Damn.
Press P. Sandbox. All right. Let's go. Okay. Why did you tell me I could do that?
Let me beat the levels first. Oh, that was so loud in my ears. Get me over here. Oh,
just throw a grenade. No, don't throw it. Win your trajectory. All right. Let me relax for a second.
What the fuck was that? Was it a grenade that he throw? I didn't know they could throw grenades.
I can do that shit too. I got it. That's going to be a good scene. All right. I got 86 health.
Here we go. This is it. Where did they go? What? Why are they not there? I just blew up the fucking
health. Oh, my God. Give me a break. Get in there. Where's the guy with the laser? There's a guy
with the laser. Laser. Where's the guy with the laser? Why? That just hurt. All right. I made it.
Watch this funny thing at the end. No. I wanted to watch the... I can just do better this time.
No, I did it again. Damn it. Okay. I'm fine. What? He can shoot through walls. All right. I got to...
This is the big scene at the end here. Big finish. How do I want to... Grenade off the wall.
Got it. Let's watch the movie. Did I just drop the gun? Oh, I dropped the gun. I'll pick up another
one. Press V. V. Why do you want this angle? This angle sucks. You can't see anything.
It's just this guy. There's nothing here. What an intense action movie this is. All right, guys.
No, it's not free cam. I can't move around. How do you move around? I'm stuck here. Arrow keys?
No, it's not the arrow keys. I didn't even do anything.
Number pad? No, it's not the number pad. Press P. All right. We'll do... Let me go through each
level first. All right. Jungle. I'm going to make this one worth watching. Ready? 30 bullets in
each one. Get down. Catch it. Catch it. I think I just... Did I shoot myself? I think I just
shot myself in the back of the head. What just blew up behind me? Who's shooting this?
Okay. I need health. Health is over here. Oh, my God. Okay. Don't... I don't want to... I can't
fuck this up. I got to... Does this have any more? Look, this has 60 rounds. Why does this have so...
Look at all this. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Where do I go from here? Health? Whoa. Somebody else is firing. Do a rocket jump. No. I'll die
instantly. I got to jump up and hit this guy. I just snuck it over. Just barely snuck it over.
Okay. Hold on. Fuck. Oh, shit. He's here. Exit. I did it. Oh, he has a rocket launcher. Get rid
of his rocket launcher first. All right. I got it. Minimal action. Can I time it? Can I shoot one
in the air? Is this going to come back down? I don't think so. Like five hands. You had the
worst rocket jump of all the TF2 YouTubers. I don't... All right. Who cares? Where am I?
Oh, my God. Why are there rocket launchers over here? You're rubbing your butt on the ground like
a dog. Look at this hesitation. Because I know I would blow myself up in a second with this thing.
Complete fear. What? Oh, yeah. Wait, did I hit a guy from across the map?
I think I hit a guy direct across the map. Did that happen? Hold on a minute. Let's take a look
at that again. I love this. I love this stupid action movie movie. It's so janky. This is the
third game you've played in a row where you're making a movie. Well, I mean, I went fishing
yesterday. I didn't know that this had this. I thought it was just an action game. This makes
it so much more interesting for me. All right. Pay attention here. So I jump. I think I... Do I
shoot somebody accidentally? Oh, no. Okay. I was aiming for that guy, I guess. It was a different
cut last time. The audio is breaking. Maximum coward is what somebody said. Okay. This is fun.
All right. Let's go back to the room. Get this saloon. All right. Now I'm going to do a cowboy
movie here. Single action. Why is that guy still standing up? Get this fucking door out of here.
What? Was he shooting me on the ground? Double kick that guy. Who's next?
Give me that one. Good catch. Fourth arm. Wait. Hold on a second. That'll be a really long gun.
Okay. Wait. Wait. Time out. Time out. Time out. Time out. Time out. Time out. Okay. Time out. All
right. Oh shit. That was loud. I need to get rid of this. Get... No. Get rid of this. That's not
Maximum coward. It's called I need to have... Get rid of one of these. Oh shit. No. Get rid of this.
Somebody has their arms behind me. Like whose line is it anyways?
I'm not a coward. I just don't want to die here. Okay. Here we go.
I'm just slowly falling down the stairs. All right. I got lots of ammo in this thing.
What the fuck? How many times do you have to shoot a guy in the fucking face? Oh my god. I shot
that guy like four times. I shot that guy like three times in the face. What's with the doors?
That's impossible. Oh fuck. This one's hard. Oh shit. Do I have a gun? That guy's got a gun.
That guy has a gun. That's who shot me last time. No. Don't. If I can hit once, I'm dead.
Dead. Oh my god. Throw a grenade up there. No. Please. Are they dead? All right. Get me up there.
Okay. Go. No. Am I... I'm not even staying. I'm about to just... I can't do it. Jesus. Here we go.
The camera doesn't know where it wants to be. You can see how... You can see how upset I was
right here. Like I have to do this again. I was really, really trying right here.
The hell am I... I didn't do that. I did not do that. That was added in. Damn it. Oh shit. I'm gonna
run. Got him. I wish it captured the voice too. You can just hear me. What was going on here?
Oh, the guy had a gun, right? Camera. Yeah, I had two HP.
Why did I let... What? Why did I drop the gun? I didn't let go of the gun?
What am I doing? Waving at them? That guy just landed on his head. I am so confused. I am
telepathically beating these people up with my fists. Okay. This makes no sense. Yeah, this is
my favorite scene in the movie. Stop looking down. You know you're having a real problem when
you're looking straight at your feet. This time more with feeling. Oh yeah, I'm trying to jump
off the walls now, I think. Nope. Just trying to get leverage from the bar. Oh yeah, this is
crouch jump. Crouch jump. Crouch jump wasn't doing it either. That was a great movie. Yes, fantastic.
Uh, arctic. I'm gonna try to get only headshots. Oh, that's a grenade. It's an enough a grenade.
Okay, we're good. He walked over to it. Oh my god. I mean, that was very clearly...
That was a headshot. It was. I mean, health. Is it health back here? Something blew up.
Oh, fuck. That is ultimate panic. Is that it? I think that's it. Oh, no. Yeah, I don't like how
quiet this is. I can hit once I'm dead. Health? Anywhere? I'm almost out of ammo. I think this
ammo... this health right there. Is he dead? Yes. Got it. Oh shit. I want the one with the ammo.
What's in there? Double health. Oh yeah. Do I have to go down? Did I open it? Can I just get down there
from here? I think this is the action shot where I jump all the way down. Got it. Bingo. That's gonna
be a good one. That was a first try scenario. What is this? Oh, I thought... right, I was... oh,
headshots only, I remember. That was so violent. I love when you dive backwards. You just stick
your legs up. That's... that's all a dive is, is you just fold your legs back. Did I die? That's
like a... oh, you got me. No, he's still alive. Just trying to make it look interesting.
I had two HP this whole time. I wonder if that door doesn't open. Give me this. No, that one
doesn't open either. I guess we're gonna go this way. You can just feel the internal monologue.
Why would the camera be in the ground pointing up? You'd think you'd just want like have a static.
Oh, that guy got a few shots. Not a whole lot.
I just took one right in the throat. That was like right into my... right into my jugular.
I need to play dubstep. See, this is the point. I remember right here.
This is the point where everyone was screaming blind.
Blind. Blind. Blind. Turn around. Turn around. You are so dumb. You missed it. Blind. Wait,
no. What is it? Over here. Oh, sorry. Can you hear the sound? Those little...
audios compressing into itself. What are you showing me? Oh, I'm trying to... yeah, right.
I was trying to jump over. Now that was a good shot. I wish they stayed on it.
That's not what happened. I landed with such explosive ferocity. That's the end of that one.
All right, we have rooftop. I think that's the last one until I'm gonna just do...
I'm gonna make my... I'm gonna just go into the editor and like mess around.
Rooftop. Okay, at least it worked. Where's this gun? Where's this guy's gun? Did I get him? I
don't... I don't even know if I got him. Where are the guns? All right, did... do not drop it.
Is this guy still... Okay, they don't have any guns. I'll take that. Don't go too far.
No, don't, don't, don't, don't. That was really easy. That was really easy. Yeah!
Now where do I go? I'm just not gonna snipe this guy from really far away. Watch this.
Yeah! Adam Sandler. That's not Adam Sandler. All right, exit up there. Yeah, it is, isn't it?
Wait, no. Is that... where do I go? That way? That's where I came from. Ramp. What do I mean?
Was it ramp? Ramp? Under there. What do you mean under there? Go under there. What do you mean
under? Over here? All right, ramp. Found the ramp. Don't fall off this shit. Oh my god! Okay, I'm
fine. I didn't... I didn't think there was a gap. I just screamed really loud because this is a good
run. Up. Um, okay, there's a... lead the target. I just fucking missed. That wasn't even where I
was aiming. Am I lying down? I'm lying on my back. Why can I not hit this thing? Oh my...
Yeah! I still... how did I still get that? There's no way. Oh, I can't hit this. Nice.
Double. Print it. Really? Oh fuck, I have no... oh, I don't want to do this too far...
too much in front of my own face. No, he's getting too close. What do I do? What? Did I explode too
fast? Okay. Oh shit. Get it again. Get it again. Get it again. Get it again. Get it again. Get it
again. Get it again. Get it again. I can do it twice. I can do it twice. It's gonna be the end
of the movie right here. The end of the movie. Final scene of the movie. Here it is. I can get it.
I can get it. I can get it. I can get it. I can get it. Get out of here. I did it. It's over. That
was a six minute movie. Here we go. Let's take a look. I was trying to jump off the other side.
This is so fucking bad.
I got him. Okay, good. Am I gonna try the other modes? Oh, absolutely.
This is where I'm searching for the gun, but I can't find it.
Acid base? I can't stop this right now. I'm afraid to. I feel like if I hit escape or
something, it'll ruin everything. Play it from your phone. I can do that. Here we go.
It didn't even show it. This didn't happen. This didn't fucking happen. Why is the helicopter
still there? I'm so confused right now. Just landing and taking off. I'm picking the lid up.
That looks cool though. It does. This thing's not gonna go in to the glass that I jumped through,
right? This looks way, way worse than what I thought it was looking like when I was playing.
Now, wait a minute. This is where it happens. There's two more helicopters that come up.
Right? What is happening? I did not hit that. I did not do that.
What is going on? There's two helicopters chasing me. Why am I aiming down at the glass behind me?
Don't I fire this? Why have I not fired the rocket launcher one time? I clearly didn't
shoot it like five times. What am I firing at? I do not aim at the helicopter. Is this somebody
else's replay? I want to watch this from the first person perspective. You know what I mean?
We need to see a clear indicator of what happened. Can I fast forward? I can't. This is great. This
is the only, hold on. This is the only camera that's in this room. I can't move this anywhere else.
All right. All right. We don't have to see it again. So let's see. Other modes. All levels are
work in progress. Dojo. Canyon. Where? So there's more. Restaurant. Garage. Tutorial. Rooftops.
All right. So lobby. Dojo. Canyon. Is it endless mode? Does this have a film? This is video tape?
Oh, I died. Okay. I think I can just place enemies places, right? Yeah, this is just like a sandbox.
All right. Well, hold on. Props. Items. No. Weapons. Characters. Where did the
rocket come from? Characters. Suit guy. Can I give them something to fit in health?
The game spawns. Go right. Does it? Spawn health all over me. Go right. Oh, what do you mean go
right? Down here? I don't think I can go down there. North left. That's not even real.
No, I think this is like a little sandbox level. Nothing over here.
No. Okay. Let me do one thing. Items. First aid.
What's the max health? I mean, I think 1100 is pretty good. 1500. Whatever. Okay. Now characters.
I don't have any weapons. No clip? Thank you. Oh, fuck. I'm dead. All right. Is there anything
else that I could do? Just like the scene. Let me look at the scene creator. Create scene. Oh,
Jeremy. Okay. What do I want to name for your scene? Test. Let's just test it out.
Mouse three to rotate objects. Start recordings. Maximum action editor. Floor clone. Mouse two,
delete. Move object down. X to undo. Mouse one to move objects. Okay. Editor menu. Floor five by
five. Okay. What else can I get in here? Objects. Can I do a
snow guy? Where's the helicopter? I don't even see the crossbow. Really? That would have been
fun to use. All right. Space, move object up. Place objects. Yeah. You can pick them up and
put them down. All right. Well, I mean, that's cool if I wanted to. Why am I moving? That'd be
fun. I don't think I want to really sit here and learn it though. So I think that's it for
what about what's weapon room? Ah, now this is what I'm talking about. Okay. So you can test
it with a crossbow. I want to use the crossbow. Is it not here? Am I stupid? I think I might be
stupid. Wait. No. Damn it. Endless mode. Act one. What? What do you mean? What? Endless arena.
Armory. Endless. Why? This is a weird menu. Endless arena?
Press to begin endless mode. You will not be able to leave. This is too bright. I thought this was
a gun on the wall. This hurts my head. I need to, I want to go somewhere else. I can't, I can't look
at this. Other modes. Dusk. Everyone was saying do dusk. Let's go AK. Okay. 30 is 60. Crossbow.
Nice. Finally. It's got a red dot. You got it. It's going to use the crossbow. Press to begin
endless mode. All right. Let's go. Explain to me what is going on right now. Uh, those are my
arrows. I'm confused. All right. I can't, I can't. Let's try this again. All right. Let's go. Current
wave. Here it comes. How's that not hitting you? Oh, fuck. It did hit you. Get in the house. All
right. Wave two. I gotta, that's just stay in the house. You did, I did a better job than you.
Shit. I'm gonna die. Okay. Damn it. Well, that's cool. I wish it recorded this. Yeah. All right.
Any other modes? Endless mode. The cutting room floor. What does that mean? Endless mode. The
cutting room floor. I'm not quite sure what this does. This is a weird view. I think it just
records the whole thing. Oh, fuck. I'm out of ammo. Didn't say what it was. All right. Well,
this is another level. It's like a different area. Oh, get out of the way. Oh, you're playing old
levels that are, okay. These are not official levels anymore. Okay. I get you. So these are,
this is like the first pass of that, uh, this rooftop level. That's all right. That's cool,
though. You can still play them. All right. I'm going to pee my pants. I drank a large coffee.
Why do I always say that? Because it's, it's true. I would pee my pants if I wasn't smart.
Where's the exit? Somewhere over here. Where am I going? Am I missing something?
The TV. Look at the TV. They give you a lot of those. All right. We'll move on. What did
I say in the very beginning of the stream? That there was probably less than a couple
hours of content so far. Yeah. That's really fun though. It is. It's fun. I love when games add
a little something interesting without that movie mode. I think the movie mode makes it
huge. And if they continue to develop this and add more stuff and add more camera controls,
and I think it'll be really, really fun. Old. Yeah. Okay. All right. So what we're going to do
now, I'm going to go pee. I'm going to come back and I'm going to play a little bit of
Rollercoaster Tycoon 2. That's the plan. But no, that was fun. That was absolutely like fun,
funny, and worth playing. So I'll be right back. We'll change games. See you guys in a minute.