Okay, here I am. And I have done some audio tweaking. Here I am right here. How does the audio sound? Do we sound a little smooth? Do we sound a little a little better? How do we sound? Let's give it a little bit of a yell test. Let's give a scream test here. I think that's a good idea. So if I were to make a weird noise, if I were to go, that doesn't get fucked up, right? I sound way better.
Hey, how about this one? I'm gonna I'm gonna make a loud sound. Well, actually, no, I'm not gonna do that yet. I don't do that yet. You sound like classic German. Oh, classic German. Do you want to know why you think I sound like classic German? Because there's no compressor, there's no noise gate, and there's no noise suppression. This is just Mike out of the fucking box. Okay, it's just right out of the box. No, no more filter Andy. Okay,
you're a little on the quiet side. Yeah, I probably can turn it up a little bit more. I'm kind of afraid to though. There's no more noise gate. So you're gonna be able to hear my fucking air, you're gonna be able to hear my weird burps and farts and shit, you're gonna be able to hear everything. Turn it up by like 10%. Should I turn it up by about 10%? What do you think? I need a unanimous decision. Can we get a vote in chat, please? Should I turn the microphone up by like 10%? You definitely heard that I just like gulped three times. I'm so used to be able to hook
That's gonna be bad. I am. You definitely heard that too. You definitely heard that. I'm so used to you guys not hearing any of these sounds for the last like four fucking straight years. Just mute when I breathe in. Huh? What do you think microphone up to? Alright, the unanimous. Alright, you tell me microphone. The microphone is going up by 10%. Tell me if this is good. You ready? Okay, here we go. Mike's going up by 10%. I just did it. Just did a 10 did about 10%. Do we need more?
Is that good? I just did about 10%. How's that? Are we okay? Good. Good. Let's let's do some testing. I need you guys to listen because I it's hard to do it myself because I speech jam myself. Listen. Ready?
How's that? Is that loud? Is that getting cut off? Is it is it peeking but it's pulling it back? How is it? How does it sound? Is it okay? Does that is that like bad to listen to? Because there's screams
but you know, nobody wants to hear a real loud ass scream, right? I can hear the bacteria forming in your mouth. Okay, so it sounds okay. Turn the compression on. I am not turning the compression on. I'm going to get you know what it is. Here's the problem. I am going to get a hardware compressor. I'm going to get a hardware compressor. I've been using software compression for four or five years. A hardware compressor. I have to get one. They're a huge pain in the ass. But fucking whatever.
But do I but do I really even give a shit though? Like honestly, do ask me do I really give a shit to buy a hardware compressor into like a fucking amp and then put that into a fucking? I don't know. Does it matter? Is this fine? Okay, software compressors are better. All right, well then whatever I don't care. I've never been like an audio person, right? You could try a limiter filter in OBS. That's what I had on before, unfortunately, and it just kind of like was
deleting the sounds. All right, it's okay. Let's go. I'll tell you what we're going to do today. I'll tell you the plan. We got some stuff going on. Eat 40 sausages on stream. No, I'm not going to do that. There's no difference between a hardware and a software compressor. Oh, your volume keeps fluctuating. Well, that's because I'm sitting back in the chair and then I kind of go like this and I lean in for a second. And it sounds kind of like one of those microphones where I'm going to tell you all about something. I move the mic the microphone. I'm not going to be the volumes are gonna be like going.
Oh, I'm going to be sitting still. Dude, back the fuck up. I'm backing up. I'm backed up right now. You should play ring fit. Now that will require me to get up and move around. All right, you guys ready? First thing we're going to do. We're going to do who wants to be a millionaire. Weirdly enough, all these games are on Switch. Honestly, trying to find these game show games is such a huge pain in the ass. They only are in
C noses slot machines or on Xbox Live Arcade from 2010. They are they're all on like the random consoles though. Like this is on Switch. Yeah, or they're it's so I don't get it. Like deal or no deal. Deal or no deal is like only on like MSN's web page for the this was like one of the most popular fucking TV shows of all time. Right? Why? Why? Why is there only like two places that are like random
old flash players that you can play this? Where do I get deal or no deal an actual developed video game? Well, I guess it's I mean, literally, it's open 100 cases and look at it. And I guess you don't really need to spend that much time on it. It's on the DS. Yeah, but that's what I'm saying. It's on the fucking Nintendo DS. Why would this not be on every console? Deal or no deal was really dumb. Well, I have it. Okay. The DS has it. And guess what you can't. Whatever. Game
show popularity. Wait, what'd you say? Game show popularity must be dying out for the newer generations. I guess that makes sense. I can understand that. Yeah, that makes some sense. Alright, well, we're gonna play who wants to be a millionaire. I'm ready. You guys ready? Let's go ahead and do it. And let's go. What's up? New camera spot to I no longer getting blocked by any any shadows or anything. I'm just sitting here. I'm here. Here I am. Super much better lighting to I took this very, very seriously. I took this dead seriously. That's to zoom
in. It's not this is you're not zoomed in. You're getting even closer to the northern lion shot. I mean, this is an ideal place for a microphone and a fucking webcam. Okay, you guys ready? I'm gonna play deal or no deal. I don't really need audio for this. Do I care? All right, let's go. These are all the categories. I know how to play millionaire. I understand how to play the game millionaire. It's fine. Oh, by the way, how cute up of the sounds.
Oh, the sounds good. Let me do a test because it's capturing this through a capture card is weird. Ready? Like, one, two, three. Ready? So I'm gonna say we're not six. Oh, hey, good thing. Hey, look at that. Wheel of Fortune is coming up soon. Because I just fucking started downloading it like 40 minutes ago. That's why I spent so long getting here. Because this was taking a long time to download all these because I had this all on PC. But I realized, wow, none of these
fucking games are on PC unless you go to some weird website. Oh, okay. So let me go plug in my Xbox from fucking 2011. Let me go get my Xbox 360 and plug it in and go to Xbox Arcade. No, these are on switch. So let me go get them all on switch and then start the stream fucking 40 minutes late. You're stalling. Yeah. There's no game sound. Yes, there is. You can hear it right now. Okay, so that we're gonna do a test here. Ready? But but does that sound fine? It's quiet. You guys do you guys really want to Okay, let me let me just do it.
Let me just tell you what this music is gonna be like, it's gonna go. Who cares? It's the same fucking sound that you've heard for like 20 years. Is it delayed? Are you wearing a prosthetic nose? Oh, fuck. I just like scratched my nose. What the shut up. All right, let's go. I'm gonna be okay. My nails are too long. I need time. I need extra time before I need extra time before stream. All right, let's play as
this is what doesn't even matter. All right, we're gonna play we're gonna play as Ruben. Okay, thank you. Good thing you can hear the claps. Right, everybody. Good thing I can hear the claps. Turn it up. I you know what I was told to turn it up. I hope this is love. Because everyone's told you. Oh, yeah, this is the thing you all needed to hear so loudly.
Yeah, okay. All right, let's go. I don't care. So if you don't know how to play this new question, everyone knows how to play who wants to be a millionaire. I don't have to describe it. But what common name is the harmonica also known? I don't know. The mouth organ, the mouth organ. I'm going to choose B. Why would it be anything else? You sure?
Perfection. Your new question is ready. Good luck. In a game of poker dice, a throw resulting in three of a kind in one pair is called what poker dice? What do you mean poker dice? That's just a full house. But why would you just say poker poker dice? What the fuck is poker dice? Okay, let's roll. I know you is the right answer. Why don't you say poker?
Kaching. Okay, we're driving up the jackpot that they have to talk. I don't they don't have to write can I turn it off for this new question? In physics, what color comes next in the visible light spectrum after red, orange, yellow, green, blue and indigo?
I'm not gonna cheat. I'm not if I promise I'm not cheating. You can tell if I'm cheating because I moved my shit around, right? Chat used to be over here. Chat is now over here. And my stream settings and preview stuff is over here. Okay, well, no, no, actually, that's a good right there. You're both like, right?
So if I'm looking over here, if I go like this, I'm looking at you guys. What's the question? What did the Lumiere brothers invent? I'm lost. Not electricity photography. I don't know. Photography or cinema. Whatever.
Unfortunately, it all ends here for you. This is not the right. Yeah, if I if you see me do this, I'm looking over a chat. This is me. Okay, I'm gonna give you this the spectrum here of looking and when I am not looking at the actual game, looking at the game, looking at the game, looking at the game, looking at the game, looking at the game, looking at the game, looking at the looking at the chat is right here.
You understand looking at the chat is right here. I'll give you this side. Ready? Looking at the game. Nothing's over here. Doesn't matter. That's just a warm up. Who cares? Nobody can beat this game anyways, because they give some random ass trivia that nobody knows after after the thousand dollar threshold. All the questions are just random shit that you would have to look up in a book. Is that copium? I don't think it is. Why is my hair so big today? Because I put hairspray in it. All right, let's go. Here we go. I gotta get to it.
At least 1000. At least 1000. Let's go. Which of these is a national holiday in the USA held on the fourth Thursday in November? Okay, for a second. There's like freaking me out. Ready for this new question. Okay, what everyday object is a ball cock most likely to be found? Is in a bad bit? A ball cock? What the fuck is a what is a ball cock? Definitely not. Definitely not teapot. Not a telephone. It's probably toilet.
Let's go with B. Yeah. Okay, we're driving up the toaster. It's in a toaster. Our team of editors. Okay, what describes a period with very little rainfall? That would be a drought. Let's go for C. Let's save some time. You know, they have all this dialogue, but I would wish they would just read the questions. Yes. I wish I could just have TTS do it, right? Like I just I don't want to read this. I want to hear it. Here's a new question.
For you. State of Wyoming is in which time zone? Oh shit. Is that Pacific? Or is it mountain? That's not central. It's mountain. This might be a trick question, though. I think it's mountain. It's mountain. No, it has to be. There's no way it is. Okay, if it's not mountain time, then I'm I again, there's no way.
Let's go for a whole new question.
Ah, that'd be the Cardinals.
The St. Louis bishops.
Bless you. Listen, I told you there's no noise gate anymore. You're gonna hit fucking everything.
In weight measurement, what does 14 pounds equal? I don't know. It's not a peck. No, a stone, a score.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen, you heard it. We need a little help here. If you would pick up those keypads and
Okay, it's a stone. A stone is way less than 14 fucking pounds.
A stone. A stone. A stone is maybe one pound.
A stone.
That's all me. Perfection. That's a rock.
But you know what I mean, though? It's a stone. It's a whatever. But you shouldn't stop there.
Here is a new question. By what name are the musicians Tom
Rollins and Ed Simons collectively known as?
Chemical Mothers. The Chemical Mothers.
They're the Chemical Brothers. They're not the Chemical Fathers.
The Chemical Mothers.
All right. 4,000. Let's get to 16.
Are you ready to face the traps of this next question?
Good luck to you.
Mount Olympus is the highest peak in which country?
That's Zeus, right? Greece.
There's too much. Okay, B. Let's roll.
Of course.
Yeah, of course I know that one. Yeah.
All right. 8 grand. Let's go.
You will be asked a new question now.
That's the voice actor from One Punch Man, season one.
What's his name? Not the main character.
What's his name? Complete the title of the Noel Cowher Play private investigator?
I don't know. I'm going to phone a friend on this one.
Let's phone a friend.
By our friends. You choose to call one and we will have them.
Okay. Definitely like Paul, father would probably know this, right?
Oh, uncle. I think uncle would know.
Good evening, Mark. This is who wants to be a millionaire.
Good evening. It's a pleasure to have you on the phone.
How do they do this?
Be the helping hand for a very delicate question.
We're counting on you.
Well, as far as my knowledge goes, I would say B.
But honestly, my memory can fail me.
Private lives.
All right. We'll listen to the uncle.
Let's go with B.
It's probably fucking wrong.
Are you absolute?
Uncle pulls through. All right. Uncle pulls through.
Where are we at right now?
Will you be able to answer this new question as well?
At the first modern Olympic Games in Athens,
the victors were given a crown of what leaves olive, orange, laurel or bay leaves.
Olive, olive leaves.
I don't know. I'm going to do 50 50.
Okay. If it's olive, if olive is there.
All right. It's olive.
Do olives have leaves?
You had to make a choice.
32,000. We're good.
I'm not cheating. I fucking promise you concentrate.
Here's a new question for you.
What was Kubla Khan's relationship to Genghis Khan?
Oh my goodness. I have no idea.
I want to say son or grandson, son or grandson.
I, I still have lifelines.
This is way too kind of, I don't know.
This is too vague for me. Like father, brother, son, grandson.
It could be literally any of these.
Um, what this one is, what's this one?
I think, oh, this is a new question, right?
Let's switch the question right now.
Hoping that the new one will bring you.
It could be any one of these, honest to God.
I just don't know.
The game is off to a good start, but you shouldn't stop there.
How do you say court in Spanish?
Oh, why do we only have 10 seconds?
Uh, Dorado.
Okay, let's roll.
We're choosing A.
That's the only one that sounds like it.
Mosaic.
Juzgado.
That's the wrong answer.
Sorry.
Yes, but the questions were also too hard.
They're true.
What do I leave with?
32,000.
That's not bad.
Chat was wrong again.
I don't, I don't know Spanish.
32k.
Yeah.
Oh, the voice actor.
Um, the one that's like master.
What, what's that character's name?
Genos.
Yeah.
I think, okay.
I think this is the Genos voice actor from the one punch man dub.
I, I, I hear it.
I can, I can like, I can hear it.
What a great show, by the way.
See what season one, season one.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves here.
Season one.
All right.
Let's, let's play with a different character.
How about, um, how about Massimo?
I never even seen season two, by the way.
I have no idea how it is.
I just, I'm just jumping on the bandwagon with everybody that said they don't like it.
I've never seen it.
Okay, let's go.
If a comedian is very funny, where would the audience be said to be rolling
in the aisle, down your way, over the top, up the wall?
I don't, who fucking even says this anymore?
Rolling in the aisles, right?
No, this is wrong.
If the audience is laughing, where would they be laughing?
They're laughing their ass off.
What would the audience be laughing off of their body?
These questions are from like 50 years ago.
When someone is not as fierce as they sound, what is said to be worse than their bite?
Their bark.
Massimo chooses Dean.
That's one.
Final answer.
You're so old.
No swearing on TV.
Are we sure?
Listen, hold on.
I believe it to the end.
I did a good job.
Your new question is ready.
Good luck.
Are you sure it's not Jess?
A hit by Gladys Knight and the Pips was titled Midnight Train to Georgia.
No, but that one's the right answer.
I'm gonna say B.
So this is your final answer?
Yes.
It's not.
The VA is too young.
Okay, well done.
You've got it.
That was the right answer.
I can't believe it.
This game is too loud.
I had to turn it down.
This new question.
How come everybody's British?
I don't know.
In theory.
The four C's of diamond quality are color, cut, carrot, and quality.
Carbon.
Clarity.
It's definitely clarity.
It's clarity.
Has to be, right?
There was a cost?
No, it's clarity.
I'm not looking.
I know everyone's freaking out.
It's definitely color, cut, carrot, clarity.
My gut says that it's C.
Okay, C.
Yes.
You are right.
Kimorbin.
A meticulous, well-executed job.
I'm gonna watch that movie to see what the fuck everyone's talking about.
What are you all talking about?
Is the movie, is the movie, is it a bad movie?
Does the movie suck?
Is it a bad film?
I don't get it.
Which of these is gravy usually served?
Gravy boat.
I'm going to choose D.
Kimorbin.
I will answer.
You sure?
That will be.
I fucking can't.
All right, let's go.
Now this is where the questions get harder.
I don't want to use any lifelines until 32,000.
Eric Cartman is a character on which animated TV series?
King of the Hill.
Let's go for...
So that was easier than the $100 one.
Seriously.
How would I know Eric Cartman?
Who's currently like alive right now?
You know what I mean?
Churchill Downs racetrack is in which US state?
This is exactly what I was talking about.
The question before this, before $1,000.
What TV show is Eric Cartman on?
Now this very specific racetrack in the country.
Where is it?
I don't...
Who would even know this?
I don't know.
Oh, I kind of have to do this.
You decided to appeal to the audience.
Kentucky.
I was going to say, and I would say probably not in New York.
Let's go for C.
But like I would have literally been throwing a coin in the air.
It's famous.
That was the right answer.
Obviously not as famous as Eric Cartman, apparently.
Alicante is on which Spanish coast?
Do you hear these people?
Why are they all talking?
Coastal...
Coastal Rock!
I would say B, obviously.
Got it.
A meticulous, well-executed job.
Good.
I would have had...
Oh my God.
I'm all skinned.
Which of these is not a state of the United States?
New England.
What?
That's not a...
That's a region.
Well done.
Got it.
A brilliantly executed success.
Okay, $16k.
Here we go.
$32k.
Still have plenty of lifelines.
Will you be able to answer this new question as well?
The Smithsonian is an institution of national museums in which city?
Washington, D.C.
Thank you.
And I would say B, obviously.
Easy.
$32k.
We got lifelines.
Somebody just like sneezed.
This new question is now waiting for you to be answered with flying colors.
What is the meaning of the Latin word thesaurus?
Probably comparison, right?
A thesaurus.
Comparison.
It has to be.
Otherwise, what's the point of calling it a thesaurus?
What's the point of calling it that?
There is no.
There's no reason to call it a thesaurus unless it means that.
But it could be a trick question.
And I don't know what the actual answer could be.
A treasure?
Give me a new question.
What was it?
You used to use your switch lifeline.
Was it D?
You were careful.
Well done.
It was D?
It was treasure.
Okay, I would have gotten it wrong.
So would have like a bunch of you apparently because you said collection and you were wrong.
The game is getting tougher now with this brand new question.
Pointillism is a painting technique chiefly associated with which artist?
I mean, well, this is not a this is Monet is the artist, right?
This is not a person, is it?
Picasso?
Pointillism.
I think it's Picasso.
It's Picasso.
I have a good hunch that it's C.
Final answer?
You sure?
I mean, it starts with a P.
I don't know if I was if somebody were to talk about a technique that I was doing,
it would be like you're like Germanism or something or whatever.
If I made a technique up, it would be called like I don't think I'm ever going to get a million
dollars here.
These questions are too hard.
That was as easy to be as the Eric Cartman question.
Really?
Why can I want to unlock the Harry Potter questions?
I'll get all those right.
Like, can I just do Harry Potter and Star Wars?
Can I just do Harry Potter, Star Wars and fucking and like Star Trek?
Okay, I got to at least get to half a million.
That's the hair.
What phrase forced a forcefully persuading me to do something I'm reluctant about?
It's the twist my arm.
Yeah.
I would say A.
Yeah, twist my arm.
That is correct.
Well, that was a really close call.
Good luck to you for this new question.
Which of these words means delight or great merriment?
Flea, brie, knee, or glee?
It would be glee.
I'm not sure.
Sometimes you have to take a chance.
You don't know what glee is?
Is that your final?
That will be my final answer.
You have given just own it.
You got it.
Trust yourself and your acquaintances for this new question.
I swear to God that's Genos.
It has to be.
If I'm wrong, then I'm wrong completely.
But I keep hearing it.
In which of these sports is a checkered flag normally used?
That'd be auto racing.
But you are and we're still going forward.
300 bucks.
Are you ready for this new question?
Little Rock is the capital of what state?
Not Alaska.
It's not Alabama.
It is Arkansas.
I'm going to choose D.
You're literally speed running.
You have to speed run these first five questions.
Children can answer these correct.
Okay, here we go.
New question coming up.
Good luck to you.
Camp David is the country retreat of which public fantasy president of the United States?
These are easy.
Like it's after a thousand is where they bring out the random questions that nobody will know.
Here's a new question.
Okay, here we are.
A popular children's novel by Cressida Cowell is titled How to Train Your Dragon.
I only know that because of the movie.
I haven't even seen that movie, by the way.
These are easy.
How to Train Your Monkey.
Disney Pixar presents How to Train Your Monkey.
How to Train Your...
The great red spot is a feature of which planet?
No, but I'm sure that I have the right answer.
I think it's Mercury.
No, Jupiter.
Jupiter has a big fucking spot on it.
Jupiter has a big spot on it.
Final answer.
No slacking off.
All right, I got all my lifelines.
I've known all these answers.
Concentrate.
Here's a new question for you.
The Normans who invaded and conquered England in 1066 spoke which language?
The Normans.
Norwegian?
The Normans?
Danish?
Norwegian?
I don't know.
I would say...
I'm going to say Norwegian.
If it was Norwegian or Danish.
I'm going to say Danish.
I don't know.
I have to do it.
What the fuck?
German?
They're not going to screw me over here, are they?
What the fuck are you talking about?
They all got it wrong.
You walk away with your guaranteed cash prize.
Good for you.
That was 40 and 49 percent.
So you mean to tell me that 89 percent of the entire audience didn't know?
What?
That never happens.
Jerma, where is Normandy?
I don't know.
For some reason I was thinking like 5...
Like a thousand years ago or something.
Like 5,000 years ago.
Like the Normans.
I don't know if I figured that they were...
Some other...
I don't know.
NA education.
I have not been sitting in a...
Okay.
All you young kids out there can...
Okay, I get it.
Oh, dude.
You went to high school.
You went to like college.
I went to high school.
I went to like college.
Dude, you probably have been in a classroom.
Honestly, there are people probably in this chat right now where their entire life has gone by.
And I have not been in a classroom.
Do you know what I mean?
I haven't been in a classroom in like 17 or 18 years.
It's been that long.
It's only been like probably two years for you.
It might have been like maybe four or five years since you've been in a classroom.
I haven't been in a classroom fucking 20 years.
So it's shocking that I know some of these.
It just speaks to my incredible intelligence that I can get these correct.
Some of these.
A portion of them.
A small portion of them.
I turned 41 this year.
So please, I haven't been in a classroom in like fucking 25 years.
And yeah, excuse me.
Somebody just said it.
I've said this before, too.
Memorization does not equal retention.
I'm sorry.
It's not real retention of knowledge.
Memorizing something for like one week to just get it on.
Okay, that's what it is.
It's not knowledge retention.
You know what knowledge retention is?
What are you talking about?
This guy was a teacher.
I was never a teacher.
I was a quiet.
Which of these is type of narrow-legged trousers?
What?
Hose pipe?
Drain pipe?
I would say C.
Final answer.
Narrow-legged trousers for the first question?
And you're still going forward.
No slacking off.
It's time to move on to a new question.
What would you normally find a set of in a golf bag?
Irons.
Oh, it is irons.
It actually is irons.
It's irons.
I don't know why I was thinking like a bunch of heavy iron scrap.
It is irons.
I thought they were going to say clubs, not irons.
The North American bison is commonly known by which name?
Oh, I know this.
No, but I'm sure that I have the right answer.
I believe in my gut and I'm choosing B.
So you weren't a teacher.
That's an answer.
I can guess.
It's time to move on.
I was a substitute teacher for like a tiny portion of my life.
Which musical group is famous for wearing theatrical makeup?
Kiss.
I'm going to choose D.
You lied about it.
No, I swear to God.
I was dumb thing to lie about.
What a stupid fucking thing to lie about.
I can't think of a dumber thing to lie about where, you know, I was a substitute teacher before.
Why would you lie about that?
What do you gain?
What do you gain from that?
Am I looking at you?
Because it's like too bright to see.
All right.
What is the indefinite article in the phrase?
A happy new year.
I have no fucking idea.
Indefinite would be happy, right?
Because you could be sad.
And it's like, that's not completely definite.
You could be unhappy.
Or is that the constant?
No, it's no, it could be a different year.
I don't fucking know.
Don't say, bro.
Okay.
Really?
Let me drop some knowledge on you guys right now.
I'm sorry.
But and currently, this is I don't need to know much.
I don't like know much about this.
I don't know much about this.
I don't know much about this or this.
But damn, man.
Superheroes, TV series, Star Wars, Harry Potter, Disney.
I want to flip these questions.
And I'll tell you, if I tweeted right now,
if I tweeted a scientific equation right now,
I'd get fucking 200 likes.
If I tweeted a reaction to the latest Star Wars fucking trailer,
I'd get a hundred thousand likes.
You understand?
We got to make this cool again.
We got to make these things cool.
Otherwise, I'm just going to tweet about fucking Captain America
and talk about Captain America.
And everyone's going to think I'm the smartest person in the room.
Somebody said, dude, not one person thinks like that.
I fucking bet you anything.
I bet you anything.
If I were to tweet, I would tweet a math problem.
And people would be like, this is dumb.
But if I tweeted a picture of just I'm talking a math problem,
an interesting math problem.
If I tweeted a picture of me going like this
to like a picture of Captain America with a shield on,
it would have, people would say like, oh, base this.
Oh, yeah.
I love that.
All right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, nerve wracking.
I'm going to bet on B.
I bet you anything.
Math isn't funny.
A tennis match is set into sets.
You need to prove this.
You seem to be convinced, but no, I'm not going to tweet about Morbius.
It's so funny because somebody was like, dude,
science is cool.
Like people, you know, we just need to get off Twitter.
Is that like where this is going?
Is that where this is going in motor racing?
What name is given to the position at the front of the grid?
I don't know.
I just, I don't know.
What is it?
I think it's, this is the only one I think.
Tweet E equals MC squared.
No, this is how I fix it.
It's going to be Captain America with a shield.
And he's like got like, like lightning coming out of his eyes
and he's holding it up like this and he's like taking,
he's blocking like a punch from fucking, I don't know, Morbius.
And on the shield is like a complex math problem.
That's how I can win this.
The minute you walked in the joint, big dipper, big spender, big spender.
I would say big spender.
I'm going to bet on B.
You had to make a choice.
That's the one.
Big bopper.
No slacking off.
Morbius does your homework.
Which of these is also known as the Aurora Borealis on the Northern Lights.
I know that I'm completely.
I would say, Oh my God.
It's beautiful.
You know what?
You reach that threshold.
Not El Nino.
This new question shouldn't give you a hard time in theory.
Anything described as gustatory refers to which of the senses gasp, like gastric,
like gut, like gusto taste, probably.
Gustatory.
Gust.
Wait, smell.
It's like a gust of wind.
I think it's smell.
Gust.
I actually, I don't, I do not know.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen, you heard it.
Taste.
Going to choose D.
That's what we were looking for.
What is gustatory?
Perfectly executed.
Awesome.
It's from gusto.
I would think like a gust, you know, like smelling something.
How many equinoxes are there in a calendar year?
Oh, the equinox.
It's the, the equinox.
Equinox.
The equinox.
Two.
Make sure to get ready for the equinox.
Get ready for the equinox.
I don't know.
Is there one every season?
I'm going to say this.
I think there's one every season.
What do you mean?
What am I doing?
Okay.
I could have done better, but hey.
Let me tell you, I was going to say two.
Listen, listen, listen.
It's the solstice.
I know.
But listen, it's summer and winter.
But what happened was I went like this and my eye caught the chat and I saw four a dozen
times and I was like, fuck, I accidentally cheated and I got it wrong.
And then you made me second guess.
I was going to do two.
You saw me hovering over it.
Give me Star Wars.
I'll get every, how much, $4,000?
How many neurons do I have?
I have to like win games.
You don't have enough neurons.
I need to get a high score right now.
This is the one.
Actually try.
All right.
I'm going to fucking try as hard as I can.
Let's go.
Speed around the first question.
What name is given to the men who drafted the original U.S. Constitution?
The Founding Fathers.
I'm sure that it's B.
Okay.
We have faith.
That's what we were looking for.
Your new question is ready.
Someone who drastically alters his opinion of something that is
something is said to have a change of what?
Change of socks.
I'm choosing B.
I had a real change of socks the other day.
Okay.
What is the capital of California?
Oh shit.
I actually don't know.
You said it was Sacramento.
The other one's Florida.
Which fictional character is the boy who wouldn't grow up?
Peter Pan.
Right?
It's Peter Pan, right?
I'm sure that it's B.
It's Peter Pan.
Okay.
You.
We have faith.
This new question.
Trust me.
I'm a grown up.
Theory.
Which of these was a notorious outlaw of the American Wild West?
Yeah.
I feel like a kid.
I believe in my gut and I'm choosing B.
Who is Dick Turpin?
This money is safe.
Dick Turpin.
That famous outlaw.
It's time to move on to a new question.
American author Zane Grey was known for writing what type of novels?
I don't know.
I have no idea.
You know how many books there are?
Zane Grey.
I don't.
There's no way I would know this.
I read A Song of Ice and Fire and then cried when 10 years went by and we didn't get another one.
So that's it.
I don't do any of the reading.
Maybe you count the back of cereal boxes and food just to read random shit that's on the back.
Do you count like reading the toothpaste?
Like just the back of the toothpaste?
Just because you just need to.
Oh my fucking god.
Give me a break.
It's I don't know.
I'm just gonna have to go with this one.
I have no doubt.
Is that?
That's the one.
Well, that was a really close call.
Phew.
In which sport?
That was weirdly quiet.
In which sport did the USA's dream team compete in the 1992 Barcelona Olympics?
Is it hockey or basketball?
I think it was basketball.
Which one is it?
It's basketball.
I think it's basketball.
It's definitely it's basketball.
I know it's basketball.
The dream team, right?
Let's go.
Yeah, it's basketball.
Hockey, they won.
It was a different Olympics.
Different team.
Perfect.
We're making.
You will be asked a new question now.
A vehicle with an S international plate comes from which European country?
It could be any of them.
It could be it could be literally any of these.
How would I know?
I'm not from a European country.
And I don't.
How would I know?
Why would I know this?
I need a new question.
Using the switch, you decide to be wise.
Which is it?
Was it Sweden?
It was Sweden.
I would have probably said Sweden, but it could have been easily one of the other ones.
Very easily.
All right, come on.
Concentrate.
Here's a new question for you.
Beta vulgaris is the Latin name of which plant often used in salads?
All right, which were these are in a salad?
Beets is definitely arugula.
Vulgaris, arugula.
There's a U and L and a G in that.
It's definitely it has to be.
It's arugula.
It has to be.
It literally has three or four of the same letters.
This is the wrong answer.
No regrets, really.
I did my best.
Beta doesn't mean, but beta is like Latin for of or the.
What is beta?
I don't know.
Beta means like, I don't know.
Does that mean beat in Latin?
You're telling me beta means beat in Latin.
It's just a B, man.
Vulgaris means common.
Beta means beginning.
Why would you know that?
Nobody knows that.
Nobody fucking knows that.
Oh, beta vulgaris is the scientific Latin name for beets.
I just eat them.
I'm sorry, guys.
I don't eat beets in my salad and then go look up everything about a beet
and like where it came from and what you call it in every other language.
I just eat it.
It's a beet and it tastes good.
OK, here we go.
What city is the home of Major League Baseball's Yankees?
That would be the New York Yankees.
Well, I'm going to try A.
Yeah, get you in the hot seat and see how you do.
This new question shouldn't give you a hard time.
Which king had two of his wives executed?
When I saw which king, the first thing that came to my mind was Burger King.
And then I read the rest of the sentence and I was like, no, never mind.
I actually don't fucking know.
I think it was Henry.
I think it was, yeah, it was Henry.
Henry the, it was Henry the fucking seven.
Well, a choice has to be made.
So we're going to say D.
That's the one.
It was Henry.
One more answer.
Aha.
That's fucked up lore.
Here is you a new question.
Which of these is the title of a 2011 hit single by Lady Gaga?
It's, it's, it's born this way.
I believe it's D. I'm choosing A.
Lady, what are you talking about?
I believe it's D, but I'll pick A.
Trust yourself and your acquaintances for this new question.
Complete the title of a 2002 film.
My big fat Greek wedding.
But didn't they make a couple of movies?
My big fat Greek boyfriend?
No, my big, there was two or three movies, wasn't there?
Is this a trick question?
A seems quite appropriate to me.
Okay. No, they, they did a couple of them, didn't they?
Our grid is still pretty resourceful.
You see, you're ready for this new question.
According to the title of a 1988 film comedy, earth girls are what?
That would be, that'd be earth.
That'd be easy.
I'm saying B.
Yes, B.
Why do you talk in third person?
Do I?
No, I don't.
Why did I know that?
Trust yourself and your acquaintances for this new question.
Look up who is in that movie and ask me why I would know the answer to that question very quickly.
Look up who stars in that movie and then ask me why I would know that.
Go ahead.
What is the name of Miami's NBA team?
I'm choosing B.
And now to the most important question of all.
That's a name so I can get behind.
Exactly.
Hey, that question almost drove me crazy.
Yeah, Jim Carrey.
You will be asked a new question now.
The U.S. city of Minneapolis stands on which river?
Uh-oh.
Oh, God.
Um, I know I'm right there with you.
Um, Ohio, Missouri?
I don't know.
This could be like a weird trick question here.
I'm saying B.
Yes, B.
That makes sense.
It doesn't.
Oh, no.
You were so close.
Well, the old nanny goat is up to her old tricks.
I don't know because I read it in chat.
You're guaranteed cash prize.
You played a good game.
Good try.
This is hard.
You know why?
Okay, listen.
I know there's some trivia buffs here, but listen to me.
Everybody has a handful of categories that they know everything about.
And then they kind of don't know shit about any of the categories in life.
You know what I'm saying?
I know a shitload about very specific things.
So trying to know everything about every category is impossible.
That's why these shows make money.
That's why nobody ever wins.
That's why like 15 people have ever won this goddamn show.
You could know a little bit about everything,
but you never know everything about everything.
You got to know a few about one topic, three topics.
There are probably some people that have really big history buffs,
but the second a science question comes up, you're just like, I don't have any idea.
But you could literally name me precise dates of when very important things happened.
I would get, I would probably, honest to God,
I would probably get a hundred percent of these correct.
I would probably get a lot of these correct too.
But once you start talking about lifestyle or literature,
oh boy, I have absolutely no idea.
I could, I know a lot about food.
I don't cook it.
I don't make it, but I eat it.
And I know a lot about it and I know what I like.
I'd probably get most of these, that probably wrong actually.
I would probably get a lot of these right.
Entertainment, turn them off.
That's kind of cheating though, isn't it?
I have 560 points.
Oh my God.
You definitely heard that.
How do I get, I need a thousand points to unlock food.
I'm not playing on easy.
Put on emote only.
Yeah, fine.
Put it on, put on emote only right now to prove that I'm like, that I can't cheat.
Do it.
Let's go.
When something is quartered, it is divided into how many pieces?
15.
Boom.
What are you said to do to the roof when you make a lot of noise?
Paint the roof, raise the roof, retile the roof.
Everybody, we're going to retile the roof.
No, don't click it.
Don't click it.
How do I hit B?
No, that's not my, no, it's not.
No, it's not.
Don't, I didn't hit it twice.
I didn't hit it twice.
I didn't, why did it say final answer?
Oh my fucking God.
Damn it, dude.
I'm so glad that you guys can't talk right now.
Okay.
Which of these is a popular garden flower?
Carnation.
Let's go for this new eliminatory question.
In which game might a caddy carry your clubs?
That would be golf.
I'm choosing B.
Stop bat-chesting me.
Offers you a new question.
What type of knife was named after a U.S. frontiersman who fought and died at the Alamo?
What type of knife?
Bowie knife.
B, I think.
It's D.
That is the right answer.
Oh, but no, you don't really need to scare me like that, okay?
And let's go for a whole new question.
Death Valley, the lowest point in North America, is in which U.S. state?
I know, I know where that is.
And I'm saying B.
Yes, B.
That's in California.
Boom.
Let's go for this new eliminatory question.
What is the main unit of currency in Canada?
That would be the, uh, Canadian.
It's the Canadian dollar.
What is it called though?
It's just the Canadian dollar.
It's Canadian dollars.
It's just a dollar.
It's a Canadian dollar.
It's not called anything else.
The Canadian dollar.
It's a Canadian dollar.
That's a Canadian dollar.
It's not called a fronk, a pound, a mark.
It's a dollar.
Trick question bullshit.
Present day celebrated on the third Monday of which month?
February.
Okay, I got my lifelines.
I'm ready.
We're at 2000.
That question almost drove me crazy.
You will be asked a new question now.
In the context of CMYK color printing, what does the C stand for?
Cyan?
Cyan.
Yes.
I'm choosing B.
I'm at, what are we at?
4K?
Will you be able to answer this new question as well?
Which comedian hosted his first Academy Awards ceremony in 2001?
Fuck.
Oh my God.
I don't know.
It's probably, it's not, it's not Steve Martin.
Is it Chris Rock or Billy Crystal?
It's Chris Rock or Billy Crystal.
But I don't think it's Billy Crystal.
I think it's Chris Rock.
I think, I really do think it's Chris Rock.
What the fuck?
Steve Martin, what are you talking about?
Steve Martin was wildly popular from like 1970, 1980 all the way, what?
No way.
I had all my fucking lifelines.
I had all my lifelines.
Keep emote only mode on.
I don't want to hear them.
Oh my God.
I fucking can't do anything.
I need extra lives.
That's the problem.
And every game show when you get a question wrong, you don't lose.
And okay, I know how to make who wants to be a millionaire better.
Every time you get a question wrong, the maximum money pool of every question goes down by like 20%.
So instead of who wants to be a millionaire, it'd be like, okay, who wants to be a millionaire?
If you get the question wrong, the number one question becomes $750,000.
If you get like 10 questions wrong, you go all the way, you get like fucking 50 bucks.
That'd be more fun.
All right.
Which category of plants are Christmas trees placed in?
An evergreen.
The nine time Wimbledon ladies singles champion is Martina who?
I don't know.
I don't, I don't know.
I truly don't know.
I don't know.
I don't fucking, I don't know.
I don't watch fucking television.
Unless it was, unless it's Star Wars, superheroes or Disney or manga.
I don't, I don't watch sports.
I don't watch TV.
I've these are the ones that like, I would get right.
Except for this one.
Give me this.
I want the, why do these have to be so expensive?
4,000 bucks.
Oh my God, I've been doing this for an hour.
I have to get to at least half a million.
Which phrase refers to charging prices that seem far too high?
That would be daylight robbery.
Which former Soviet state shares its name with the US state?
Georgia.
In geometry, which of these is a type of angle?
Obtuse.
Awkward.
A stubborn angle.
Stop bad chesting.
What are you doing?
I want the mods.
For every bad chest that the person does, we're going to reduce their,
we're going to make this slow mode.
We're going to make this slow mode five seconds bigger.
Just like my, who wants to be a millionaire fix.
Which of these is an American cocktail?
I have to reread it from the beginning.
Uh, I don't, I, uh, I don't know.
Tom Collins?
I've thought about it a lot and I'm going to say C.
That's an answer I can get behind.
So let's move on to a whole new question.
They blocked it.
Oh my God, they blocked it.
I can say every opinion I've ever had about Spider-Man.
Okay.
Guys, you know who I'm going to be for Halloween this year?
Spider-Man.
I love Spider-Man.
He's my favorite Marvel character.
I'm going to be Spider-Man this year.
What was the surname of the first father and son to hold the office of the U.S. president?
John Adams and then John Adams and then John Quincy Adams.
You resident sleeper.
Good luck to you for this.
Wake him up.
Which is the chemical formula for carbon dioxide?
That would be CO2.
And the best answer is C, no doubt.
Oh, speaking of sleep, can I pause it?
Okay.
Speaking of sleep, you got to answer me this.
You can, you can leave it on emote only mode.
They don't need to respond.
Why, when somebody is sleeping, have we made them sound?
We give them certain sound effects like cartoon sound effects that don't make any sense.
For instance, like I understand like the...
Right?
Because okay, people snore.
But why in the name of fucking God did it sometimes?
Why?
What's what is...
What is that?
What does that sound supposed to even be?
That doesn't make any sense.
Why did we start putting like...
On snoring and sleeping?
I don't get it.
There's no logical explanation.
That's not a sound anyone's ever made.
I know you can't answer it, but just ponder it for a little while.
Because the three stooges did it.
Yeah, but why?
How did anybody go like, oh, let me watch this person.
This person's like asleep right now.
Let's let's...
They're snoring.
Okay, this is what they're doing.
Uh-huh.
No, that doesn't make any sense.
Where did it even...
Where did it come from?
Why is it...
I'm sorry, I'm getting a little worked up.
I'm getting a little worked up.
Which of these major sporting events takes place annually at the Churchill Downs?
I don't fucking know.
Wait, it's the Kentucky Derby.
This place is in Kentucky.
That scared the shit out of me.
The resident sleep ring.
I gotta wake him up a little.
Okay.
In which year did the Pilgrim Fathers sail for the Americas?
In...
When sail for the Americas.
In 1600 and something to Columbus was a made-up guy, right?
When in 1400 and 1600 and in 1600 and in 1600 and...
I don't know.
I've no these...
Look at this timeline.
There's no fuck...
Who would ever know this?
Okay, guys.
This is an important question.
If you would pick up those keypads and enter...
In 1640.
1630.
I don't know.
These were so long ago.
Nobody would know this.
You know what my...
The audience doesn't know it either.
You should have listened to that voice.
In 1620, Columbus...
Oh my, I played really badly.
Nice shot.
Respect for playing the game.
It was really fun playing with you.
Great player.
All right.
You know, I didn't really pay that much attention in school.
I mean, let's be honest.
You know, I used to...
It was so bad.
Like, I would just kind of want to sleep in a lot of class.
This may be some of you guys can relate to this.
You really should like really take school seriously.
You can, right?
But I remember holding a pencil and I got really good at this.
I was holding a pencil in my hand like this with my head on the desk.
And I could...
I could...
I would go like this.
My hand would be moving, but I would just be sleeping.
I would be going like this with my hand like this with a pencil in my hand.
It's like so fucking obvious that you are asleep.
I don't know why I thought that.
I thought I was being so clever.
Like this dude hasn't moved and he's just holding a pencil straight in the air
and his head is on his desk.
You're not fooling anybody.
Why would you think you would be fooling anybody?
And like teachers would come over and there'd be nothing written down.
And then you kind of...
It would be like, oh, I'm just start like moving the pencil around.
Oh, you didn't write anything until I came over and realized you were sleeping.
I try to be really creative about trying to sleep.
Go back to 30 minutes slow mode.
That's fucked up.
Okay, which Puerto Rican singer sings Despacito?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
I'm taking a wild guess.
I don't know.
I have no idea.
I have absolutely no idea.
I don't know.
I don't know any of those people were.
I don't have any idea, guys.
I really don't know.
That's a hundred dollar question.
What do I do all day?
I don't listen to music.
I don't watch TV.
I don't read any books.
What do I do?
I'm having this horrible realization.
Don't read.
Don't watch TV.
Don't listen to music.
Don't watch movies.
Don't read books.
What do I do?
Hey, I make my own TV.
See you July 14th for the baseball show.
All the residents sleepers.
But honest to God, I just I don't like pay attention.
I don't know anything.
I'm trying to think of like what general knowledge questions I really do know.
Food.
All right.
Block residents sleeper too.
Don't let them be.
They can't do that either.
Which of these is a fried potato dish often eaten for breakfast?
Oh, excuse me.
That would be hash browns.
I know food.
Thought about it a lot and I'm going to sleep.
Just own it.
You got it.
It's time.
Traditionally, how many wonders of the ancient world are there?
Seven wonders.
And too bad if I'm wrong.
Get rid of baby rage too.
I don't want them.
They can't do that either.
Trust yourself and your acquaintances for this new question.
Who has a giant peach?
James.
And I'm saying B.
Yes, B.
Question almost drove me crazy.
Get rid of the salty mode.
Get rid of the not like this emote.
Get rid of everything.
Which name is which name is the rhyming slang for T?
What?
What the fuck are you talking about?
I don't have what the rhyming slang for T.
Rosie Lee T.
Did anybody actually know what that was?
Get rid of every emo besides pogchamp.
That's a good idea.
Move on to a whole new question.
Chiao is a greeting in which language?
That would be Italian.
I'm choosing B.
Sid Charisse is best known of which of the following?
I don't know.
Guess what?
I don't watch movies.
I don't watch dancing.
I don't watch plays and I don't read.
How would I ever get this right?
Why would I ever get this correct?
I don't know.
A fucking poet?
And the best answer is C.
No doubt.
All right.
Let him free.
Let him make every all emotes.
Everything's fine again.
Let him let him out.
I can't.
It's hard.
They can't speak yet.
Which of these is a common term for serialized television dramas?
It's a soap opera.
Not a shampoo opera.
Not a sponge opera.
And not a swiffer sweeper opera.
I'm too stressed out.
I have to copy.
Seems quite appropriate to me.
I think we all agree.
What is the present perfect tense's third person singular of the word?
What?
What is the present perfect tense's third person singular of the verb to eat?
This is fucking horseshit.
Had eaten?
Has eaten?
I don't fucking know.
What a dumb question.
What a stupid question.
But here's a new question for you.
The tree species Salix Babylonica is better known as the weeping what?
That would be the weeping willow.
Voice has to be made.
I'm going to say D.
You know what my next question is, right?
You figured it out perfectly.
Nice answer.
Let's go for this new eliminatory question.
Which of these states does not share a border with Utah?
Doesn't have a border with Utah.
Okay.
Uh-oh.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oregon.
What?
What are you?
Oregon.
In total, how many days are there in the month in which America celebrate Independence Day?
So how many days are in July?
I think it's 31.
Well, a choice has to be made.
It's July.
Yeah, there's 31 days.
I'm going to say D.
All right.
Thousand bucks.
All lifelines.
Don't fuck around.
I got to get to at least half a million.
Let's go.
Let's go for a whole new question.
I just said that.
A collection of different songs performed as a continuous piece is known as a what?
Uh, a mixtape.
A mix.
A medley.
I don't know.
A medley?
No, a medley is a really long song.
That's background music for sitcoms and stuff.
An assortment?
An assortment of songs played in a row, all right?
It's assortment.
It's definitely, it's assortment.
It's an assortment.
If I get this wrong, I swear to God.
It's a fucking medley.
Hesitation.
You should have listened to that voice.
That's the wrong answer.
I think I just thought medley was
I can't do fucking trivia.
I thought medley was a long just background song.
Like just a long song, not like a bunch of songs.
Fish and chips.
The waltz and the tango are both dances.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Hurry the fuck up.
Here's a new question for you.
Which of these men is known for saying I shall return?
Gandalf.
Gandalf doesn't say that.
I'll be back.
And I'm saying B.
Yes, B.
Oh no.
What do you mean?
What?
Well, the old nanny goat is up to her own.
What are you talking about?
Oh no.
I'm so sorry.
I shall return?
It's great to meet you.
I thought they were saying,
I thought that was just a dumb way for them to make the question harder.
What actor says like, oh, I shall return.
I will be back.
Give me a fucking...
These questions are stupid.
I thought that was a dumb cheeky way to make it be like,
hey, yo, who says I shall return?
Of course it's Arnold Schwarzenegger.
That's fucking nuts.
I'm sorry.
You know what I'm figuring out right now?
I would be the muscle.
I'm not the brains, right?
I'm the muscle.
You might not think it, but it's B.
I'm coming to terms with this.
I'm figuring this out right now.
If someone you have just been talking about suddenly appears,
you might say, talk of the devil.
Speak of the devil.
I'm choosing B.
I'm serious.
You know that's what we were looking for.
That's right.
Hey, that question almost drove me crazy.
This new question shouldn't give you a hard time.
In which month do Americans celebrate Independence Day?
I'm too sure, Sam.
July.
I thought say C.
Let's go for a whole new question.
I thought it was a movie question.
With which brand of the arts is Vincent van Gogh painting?
According to the title of a 1986 Matthew Broderick film,
which of these did Ferris Bueller have?
A night out.
It's a day off.
Ferris Bueller's Month Abroad sounds like the straight to DVD sequel.
It's this.
You seem to be convinced.
But is this your final answer?
That's what we were looking for.
That's right.
Our team of editors offers you a new question.
Ebony is a what type of substance?
I think it's what if it was metal, I was gonna freak.
I was like, I was freaking out for a second.
I think we all agree that we can move on to this.
A windfall is unexpected.
What windfall?
A windfall.
If I came down with a windfall.
Oh, what a windfall.
Probably illness.
That's not good luck.
A windfall.
Man, I had the biggest windfall last night.
I had fucking extra hot sauce.
I had a big ass windfall.
I think it's an illness.
A seems quite appropriate to me.
Oh, yeah, sir.
I played really badly.
You are leaving with your guaranteed cash prize.
You played a good game.
Good try.
Windfall.
I don't know.
I'm thinking of like a fucking hurricane.
I'm not...
Son of a gun.
I think it's, you know, it's Margaret.
Margaret's...
It's Margaret.
We're gonna...
Okay, we're gonna go with Pablo.
Margaret was...
You know what's crazy?
Theory.
If I had...
Oh, I'm gonna...
If I could make a save point in life, haha, and go on
who wants to be a millionaire and like keep going to the save point,
I would never win.
I would be stuck here for a very long fucking time.
If I was able to restart and do this over and over again,
I would never win.
Which of these is an informal name of...
For the little finger.
The pinky.
I would get bored doing this and be like,
well, I'm not gonna win a million dollars
even if I could go back in time a thousand times.
Who would you be most likely to consult if your teeth hurt?
The butcher.
A private detective.
Hey, my teeth hurt.
Can you figure it out?
Al Roker?
Trust yourself and your acquaintances for this new question.
Wow.
What's the question?
Which word refers specifically to the removal of wool from a sheep?
Shearing.
I would say B.
I have no doubt.
So this is your final answer?
That'll be my final answer.
Okay.
Well done.
Which word links the sound of laughter and the sound of bells?
What?
Like, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Is that a sound like, that's more of, that's like a...
What?
Like ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
What the fuck are you talking about?
A crash of laughter?
I don't know.
That's the audience.
Quick.
Okay, audience.
Fingers on your keypads.
Let's help our contestant.
All vote now.
A boom, laughing, laughing boom.
Appeal?
Did I get it?
Okay.
C.
That's an answer.
I can get behind.
What links laughter and bells?
Appeal?
One more right answer.
A peel of laughter.
Ah, goodness, what talent.
I have no idea what that means.
Trust yourself and your acquaintances for this new question.
In total, how many letter Ds are there in the names of days in the week?
Um, how many Ds?
Wednesday.
Wed.
Two on Wednesday.
Monday has one.
Tuesday has one.
Thursday has one.
Friday has 1, Saturday has 1, Sunday has... is 8.
C is the right answer. I would stake my life on it.
You've reached that threshold, the money is in.
Yeah.
Here's a new question for you.
How is 0.125 expressed as a fraction? I don't... I don't care.
It's called Use a Measuring Cup. There's no reason to know this.
1... 8th? It's 1 8th, right?
It's 1 8th.
Use a fucking measuring cup.
At the pace you're going, you're going to make short work of this new question.
Which U.S. city is served by LaGuardia Airport? LaGuardia.
It's New York, right? LaGuardia Airport in New York, right?
It's not Los Angeles. It's not Chicago.
Dallas... it's not... it's New York, it's LaGuardia.
New York, LaGuardia.
It's C, right? Okay, C.
I got all my lifelines. No, I don't. I used one.
The questions follow each other and are not alike.
Which explorer originally... I'm trying to fucking read. Shut up.
Which explorer originally named the Hawaiian Islands the Sandwich Islands?
Magellan or Vespucci? Vespucci.
No, I don't... Magellan? I think it was Magellan.
It's Magellan. It's Magellan. Magellan did that.
Did Magellan do it? Yes, Magellan did it. I think so.
I'm just going with it. I think it's either Magellan or Vespucci.
God, it's Cook. Who the fuck is Cook?
The Cook named the islands the Sandwich Islands.
That seems like such a meme that they made up for the video game.
The Cook named the Sandwich Island?
That's a made-up question joke from Who Wants to be a Millionaire developers.
Oh, God. I'm never going to get to fucking even 100,000.
I got to move on at some point. We got to play Wheel of Fortune and
Family Feud and Deal or No Deal. I'm not going to get to the million.
So let's just be really upfront about it. Cook. Hey, what do we name the islands?
How about Sandwiches? There's no way.
That doesn't even make any...
Which of these phrases describes a restless or fidgety person?
I don't know why. I just read this as bats in his ass.
That would be fucking crazy. Ants in his pants.
Oh, that person's really visiting.
He was the... Wait, his name was James... Wait a minute.
His name was James Cook. He was the captain of the ship.
He wasn't the cook of the ship. Thank God we're on emote only.
According to the proverb, it's impossible to make what out of a sow's ear.
It's impossible to make a silk purse out of a sow's ear.
It's impossible to make a leather wallet out of a sow's ear.
It's impossible to make a linen sack out of a sow's ear.
Leather wallet out of a sow's ear. I don't know.
B? Silk purse? That's not possible. Make a silk purse out of a sow's ear.
I don't know. That makes sense. Yeah.
That is the right answer. Trust yourself and your acquaintances for this new question.
What were the names of the Catholic kings in Spain?
I have... I don't know. I don't know.
Can we start giving like nicknames to people?
Like Henry... Henry the Eighth.
No, no, no. Call him like Henry the Bloated or something.
Then people will remember. I have... I don't know.
Fernando? Oh, shit. That's right.
Which of these words means the formal resignation of a king or queen?
A resignation. Oh, god damn it.
I think it's... it's not absolution. It's aberration, I think.
Or is that adding? Is that adding a king and a queen?
I think that's it. I think it's aberration.
I'm going to...
Oh, people are laughing at me. Is that wrong?
I don't fucking know, man.
I noticed your hesitation. You should have listened to that voice.
It's... it's... it's a...
Oh, well.
Memorizing what a king and queen's resignation is is not a sign of intelligence, okay?
You know what is a sign of intelligence?
Being able to get the exact perfect fucking frame
for when somebody swings an axe at you,
when to move out of the way so you don't get hit by it.
That's real intelligence. That's... that's intelligence.
Which I've got a lot of.
Which of these musical instruments is normally played by blowing air through it?
Trombone?
C is the right answer.
I would stake my life on it.
You're just raving me of questions.
That's the answer I can get.
Yeah, okay. Like... okay.
Like the brain surgeon that's doing brain surgery.
Doctor, what's the thing that when a king and queen end up stepping down,
what's that called?
I don't fucking care.
It doesn't matter.
In days gone by, which of these might have you found under the bed?
Chamber pot.
I'm going to pick A, the star of the family, when I go...
Here's a new question for you.
Of which city was Rudolph Giuliani the mayor?
That's in New York.
B for me.
That is correct.
Baby rage.
It's time to move on to a new question.
What president was assassinated in the Ford Theater?
Abraham Lincoln?
Let's go with A. One more right answer.
Your new question is ready.
A 2008 top 10 single for Rihanna was titled Don't Stop the Boogie.
Don't Stop the Rhythm.
Don't Stop the Beat.
Or Don't Stop the Music.
Don't Stop the Music?
Don't Stop the Music.
It's Don't Stop the Music.
What was the nickname of General Schwarzkopf,
U.S. Commander in the Gulf War?
But I don't know.
Schutten, Newton, Schouten, Schumann,
Stormen, Norman, or Screamen, Stephen.
These all sound like nicknames Twitch chat is going to give me
when I'm doing something.
Oh, he's Screamen, Stephen.
Oh, Schouten, Schumann.
I don't know.
Like if I yelled for a prolonged period,
somebody in chat would call me Screamen, Stephen.
Stormen, Norman.
I would say D, obviously.
Is that your final?
I'm wearing a prosthetic nose.
That one's hitting me hard right now.
That's like hitting me right now.
Forgot about that.
The game is off to a good start, but you shouldn't stop there.
Here is a new question.
Shakespeare's King Lear is the father of Regan, Cordelia, and who?
Shakespeare's King Lear.
I don't know.
Who would know Shakespeare?
Sister.
I think sister.
Or maybe.
No, maybe not.
I don't know.
I'm going to say sister.
Good evening.
What?
What happened?
I pressed the wrong.
I pressed it.
What is that?
It didn't say anything.
I hung up on her.
D?
Okay.
Gondril?
It's D, I think.
Actually, I'm sure of it.
You had to make it.
Nice.
All right.
You got it.
He is still in good shape.
Your memory is terrible because we just called somebody and that person gave us the answer.
So that's not that's not what you're talking about.
Now that you've released the pressure, here's a new question.
Which US state is nicknamed the volunteer state?
Vermont, New Hampshire, Tennessee, Wyoming.
It's not New Hampshire and it's not Tennessee.
Give me a new question.
I don't want this.
Let's switch the question right now.
I don't know.
Concentrate.
Here's a new question for you.
Which of these is the name for the catkins of the hazel tree?
I don't know a new Dark Souls area.
DLC for Elden Ring.
Catkins of the hazel tree.
I don't fucking know.
A sheep's ears?
See, no doubt.
A lamb's tail.
Oh, of course.
Listen to that voice.
Of course, it's a lamb's tail.
Oh, well, didn't see that coming.
All right, one more.
One more and then I'm moving on to Wheel of Fortune.
The last one.
One more, I promise.
This is Wheel of Fortune.
Nobody wins a million.
I could Google all these answers too.
By what name is golfer Eldrick Woods better known?
All right, you can take off emote only.
To show that my memory is still in good shape.
So let's move on to a whole new question.
In motor racing, what does a checkered flag signal?
The end of the race.
Oil on the track.
I'm choosing D.
That's the one.
See, experienced contestants.
I think we all agree that we can move on to this new question.
Which of these is a style of brick laying?
English Bond, Welsh Union, Scottish Fuse.
I mean, these don't...
English Bond, Scottish Fuse, Irish Jo...
Yeah, these...
Okay, these all to me.
I'm gonna say Scottish Fuse.
All these to me sound like when you go to the weed store.
And they name all their joints and their weeds different weird things.
I don't know anything about brick laying, guys.
One more.
I have to get past a thousand one more time.
Play on easy.
No, I don't know.
All the naysayers right now, I want you to check out how good I do at the next one.
I want you to see how good I am at Family Feud and other ones.
Something dull or ordinary is I'll describe by which of these phrases.
Run of the mill.
Please, next game.
Wait!
Trust yourself and your acquaintances for this new question.
Which of these is the name of a U.S. state?
South Georgia.
I wonder.
In which of these gambling games is a small ball typically a vital piece of equipment?
Poker, craps, blackjack, roulette, a roulette.
Come on, Pablo.
Think.
It's D, I think.
This is easy mode.
Up until a thousand dollars it is.
You know, of course.
Okay, now what?
This new question shouldn't give you a hard time.
Cookie Monster is a regular part of which children's TV show?
Teletubbies.
It's Sesame Street.
Daniel Tiger's Neighborhood.
Or Adventure Time.
Imagine if Cookie Monster was on Adventure Time.
I'm gonna try B.
Is Adventure Time a children's TV show?
Complete this proverb.
Love my, love me, love my cat.
Love me, love my cat.
Love me, love my work.
Love me, love my dog.
Love me, love my heart.
I don't know.
Love me, love my cat.
I have no idea, guys.
Love me, love my heart.
That makes the most sense.
But why would...
I don't know, though.
It's impossible.
I don't know.
It could be any one of these.
Big one here.
Pick up those keypads and enter your votes now.
Love me, love my dog.
C is the right answer.
I would stake my life on it.
I would have said heart or work or something.
Or maybe I would have said probably cat.
Love me, love my dog.
I guess.
You ready for this new question?
The capital of the state of Washington
shares its name with which ancient site?
What is Washington's capital?
It's, um...
Washington state.
Shit.
What is Washington's capital?
I know this.
What is the state of Washington's capital city?
Anchorage, Alaska.
Washington state.
It's not Seattle.
See...
We are never better served than by our friends.
You choose to call one.
We'll have them on the phone right now.
Was it loud?
That was loud?
Well, I told you we did a test of audio.
We did an audio test.
Screaming Steven.
Add it again.
We did a scream test, didn't we?
And that was bad?
Okay, I'm gonna call.
Who would know this?
I think Theo would know this.
Screaming Steven.
You're live on Who Wants to Be a Millionaire.
Oh, good evening.
Very good.
I'm in good company.
But now we need your help.
Well, especially me in this instance.
Listen up, Theo.
Because I'm really drawing a blank here.
Well, that's great since I know the answer.
Olympia.
Is it Olympus, Washington?
No!
I tried to click it fast!
You had to make a choice.
Is that your final answer?
No, it's not!
That's mine.
No, it isn't!
I had zero seconds left on the clock.
I had to go fast and I went...
It was already there.
One more.
That one doesn't fucking count, dude.
Like, seriously.
Like, this is bullshit.
This is actually bullshit.
There was zero seconds on the clock.
You understand?
I had to freak out.
I'm not playing on easy.
Last one, I promise.
Then we're gonna move to Family Feud or whatever it is.
Dumbass Andy.
You're so bad at this.
Trivia is not my thing, okay?
Trivia is not my thing.
What was the name given to a group of newborn kittens?
It's a litter of rubbish.
A garbage of kittens?
I have no doubt.
There's a new question for you.
Which words follow tug, life, and row to give three other terms?
What does that mean?
What?
Like tugboat, lifeboat, rowboat.
Dogboat, doglife, dogrow?
Dog, tug, doglife, dogboat, tugboat.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Shedboat, shedlife, shedrow.
Road, tug, roadlife.
He's gotta be faking this.
No, I'm just fucking...
I'm just like fucking...
I don't know, I can't even...
What is the square root of 625?
I actually have no fucking idea.
I actually don't know.
I don't know the square root of 625.
I have no idea.
I don't know what that means.
I just know like the power of two is over it.
I don't know.
I looked at chat.
This game sucks.
I didn't press that.
I did not press that.
I don't want that to be final answer.
Thank you.
Okay.
Which of these is the act or ceremony of crowning a monarch?
Oh, it's called an appendix.
It's a coronation.
C is the right answer.
I would stake my life on it.
Good luck to you for this new question.
The Nationality was the author of the novel The Three Musketeers.
This is so specific though.
I don't know anything about The Three Musketeers besides it's my favorite candy.
I don't know anything else about it.
Swiss?
I'm gonna say either Swiss or Spanish.
No, it's Spanish.
It's Spanish.
It is.
Fucking God.
NA education.
Yeah.
Book smarts.
Oh no, I'm not book smart.
What do I do?
What did I do about this?
Give me liberty or give me a high five.
The house is...
The witch's house was made out of gingerbread.
C is the right answer.
I would stake my life on it.
You make it.
Come on, Pablo.
The seat of the U.S. government is in which city?
We have to find the right answer.
Let's go with A.
That is out.
Which of these words describes an egg which has gone bad?
Adled, paddled, rattled, saddled, addled.
And I don't know, but I would just say it's a rotten fucking egg.
Why would you ever say anything else?
It's a rotten egg.
It's gone bad.
The egg has gone bad.
Just say the egg has gone bad.
It's worth a good prize.
Good good look at it.
Oh, that egg is addled.
Just say the egg's bad.
The egg's bad.
The word QPI relates to which type of children's toy?
I mean, I just cheated.
I don't care.
I won't cheat for this one, I promise.
It's time to move on to a new question.
The third novel in a trilogy by E.L. James is called 50 Shades of Grey.
50 Shades dirtier.
50 Shades naughtier.
50 Shades feared.
50 Shades freed.
This was a trilogy?
50 Shades was a trilogy.
50 Shades dirtier?
I'm gonna say probably like 50 Shades naughtier.
Because that's 50 Shades dirtier would sound weird.
50 Shades naughtier.
I didn't know this was a trilogy.
50 Shades freed?
Playing with you.
Great player.
Why do so many of you guys know that?
You're never gonna make it past a thousand.
I made it past a thousand an hour ago.
All right, this is actually the last one.
No fucking help.
Turn the chat off.
I don't even care.
I'm gonna try as hard as I can.
I'm gonna go deep into the fucking brain here
and I'm gonna get every answer most of them correct.
Actual final one.
Don't care.
I'm not looking over here.
Emote only.
Make it emote only.
I'm just focusing.
I'm gonna try as hard as I can.
I'm gonna pretend like no one else is here.
50 Shades freed.
Let's go for a whole new question.
Action film especially.
That's Cliffhanger.
I would say B.
I have no doubt.
It's not a book and it's an old movie.
I know the answer.
You got it.
Poker, what name is given to a hand?
10 Jack Queen King Ace.
The same suit.
That's a royal flush.
I would say D, obviously.
I'm not looking over here.
That just goes.
And let's go for a whole new question.
In the fairy tale,
which trio built houses of straw sticks and bricks?
That would be the three,
not the three Billy Goats.
The three, the little pigs.
C is the right answer.
I would stake my life on it.
This new question shouldn't give you a hard time.
Where did the Wright brothers make their first powered flight?
Kitty Moth, Kitty Cove, Kitty Hawk, Kitty Cat.
God, Kitty Cove.
All the rest of these sound weird.
Kitty Cove.
Not Kitty Cat.
Not Kitty Hawk.
It's Kitty Cove.
I'm going to try B.
I fucking hate this.
I don't know if fucking trivia.
Who cares?
Does it really matter?
Does that actually matter that I don't know?
You know what would probably help?
Instead of auto playing ASMR eating videos
and log cutting videos,
maybe I should just keep autoplay on like fucking American history
and like European history and shit.
That's probably the problem is.
Maybe I should have like documentaries playing
rather than like people eating snacks loud
playing in my head all night.
Actually, last one, I promise everybody,
I actually promise is to find no matter what happens.
I'd have to get past fucking a thousand bucks.
Come on.
I just keep second guessing myself.
I swear to God, this is it.
This is embarrassing for me.
It's embarrassing.
I'd rather be naked on stream than do this
because I would rather be naked on camera.
Look at how embarrassing this is.
I'm sitting here doing trivia like questions in front of you guys.
This is hard.
This is like kind of embarrassing and hard for me.
Okay, which of these is a process
that might result in the removal?
It's impeachment.
Well, I'm going to try B.
Okay, this is the last one.
Ready?
What was the nickname of the American showman?
William Frederick Cody.
Bumblebee Brian?
No, it's isn't that what?
Wait, no, that's not right.
That's right.
I think, yeah, okay.
Let's go for this new eliminatory question.
Which of these is traditionally baked in America?
Apple pie.
Shoofly pie?
See, that's the right answer.
I would stake my life on it.
Begone bug cake.
It's time to...
Excluding jokers, how many playing cards
are there in each suit of a standard pack?
Exclude the joker.
How many?
There is four of each suit.
Four, eight, twelve, sixteen.
Wait, I'm misreading the question.
What?
Four, eight, twelve, sixteen.
How many suits are there?
Twelve?
No, I'm reading the question fucking wrong.
I'm reading the question wrong.
I've read the question wrong.
So much pressure and too much fucking bullshit.
Too much it made in my head.
There are four cards of each suit.
There's four?
It's sixteen.
I'm reading the question wrong.
What the fuck were they asking me?
There's a jack of...
I gotta get this fucking music out of my head.
All right.
I guarantee I'm gonna get these questions right.
Guaranteed.
Turn the music off and I'll get it right.
No more fucking loud musical sound effects.
I can concentrate now.
I thought it was asking me how many suits...
Watch this.
Watch this without like blasting shit in my ears.
Here we go.
Which of these is the name of a mountain?
Easy.
That's the...
It's K2.
According to the title of a Strauss Waltz,
what color is the Danube?
Is it green?
But what the fuck is that?
What?
That's not even general knowledge.
This is not general.
That's very specific fucking knowledge.
That's very specific.
Fucking trivia.
Gives a shit.
Watch A.
Watch me in Wheel of Fortune.
Yeah.
I'll see you at Wheel of Fortune.
We all have things that we're good at
and like I don't fucking care about trivia questions.
Which of these is a large choice steak cut from the sirloin of beef?
The T-bone.
Which of these chemical elements is not a metal?
Tin.
Copper.
Helium.
Getting this wrong would...
I would be concerned.
I haven't spent...
I would say D.
Obviously.
That's a name.
Chill.
Let's go for this new eliminatory question.
What's the name for the hard skin at the base of the fingernail?
The cuticle.
It's an E-bone steak.
I'm choosing D.
You had to make a...
You make...
Let's go for a whole new question.
There's so many things to know.
There are a million things to know.
What day is celebrated each year in the U.S. on June 14th?
It's...
Flag Day?
Is it Flag Day?
It's C, right?
C.
It's Flag Day.
This new question shouldn't give you a hard time.
Which U.S. city is known as the Big Easy?
That would be...
I think that's New Orleans.
The Big Easy.
That's New Orleans.
I would say B.
I have no doubt.
We're good.
Which Ivy League university is located in Providence, Rhode Island?
Brown.
No.
Yale is Connecticut.
Shit.
It's Brown.
It has to...
Yeah.
Yale is Connecticut.
Columbia is...
Brown's in Providence.
Let's fucking go.
I'm gonna try B.
See, I know shit.
I just don't know specific other shit.
Are you ready to face the traps of this next question?
Good luck to you.
What shape is the room in the White House used as the American president's private office?
That's the Oval Office.
See, I know things.
Look, I just don't know every other thing.
If you dislocated a metacarpal,
which part of your body would be the most affected?
Your hand.
Metacarpal would be like up here.
That's your hand.
Wait, but that...
No, that's hand.
But could it be elbow?
I think it's hand.
That makes the most logical sense to me.
I don't need to use a lifeline for that.
It has to be metacarpal.
It has to be hand.
Look at this.
Without music or without sounds in my ear, I can do this.
Let's go.
This new question is now waiting for you to be answered with flying colors.
How many letters are there in a tetragrammaton?
A tetragrammaton.
Come on, Pablo.
Think.
You have to find the right answer.
I don't know.
It's now up to the audience to choose what they think is the right answer.
Good luck.
Four or 40.
I mean, tetra...
Tetra sounds like four, but like grammaton sounds like a lot.
Like a tetragrammaton.
That sounds like a big number.
But I'm going to go with the audience.
I can say D, obviously.
That's it.
I can get behind.
I hope you have recovered from your emotions because here is your new question.
The name of which of these colors means seawater?
Aquamarine or turquoise.
Aquamarine.
Tur...
To me, these are the same color in my head.
It's aquamarine.
Turquoise is a little more blue.
Aquamarine is more green.
But turquoise is seawater.
Turquoise is blue.
Aquamarine is kind of green.
I think it's turquoise.
I'm going with turquoise.
I'm going to click on turquoise right now.
And then three, two, one.
It's aquamarine.
32,000.
A regulation American golf ball usually has how many dimples?
No one would know this unless you cared deeply about golf.
I don't know.
This is such a stupid question.
This is not even a general knowledge question.
This is such a specific dumb question.
It's probably 136 or 230.
I don't know.
Three and 400 seem way too high.
I'm calling somebody.
I'm going to call a friend, somebody that plays golf.
Who would play golf?
Maybe me.
This guy plays golf.
This character plays golf.
Would Theo know this?
I need to hear what he says.
Good evening.
You're live on Who Wants to Be a Millionaire.
Oh, good evening.
Very good.
I'm in good company, but now we need your help.
Well, especially me in this instance.
Listen up, Theo.
Because I'm really drawing a blank here.
Well, that's great since I know the answer.
It's C.
You know, you actually know it.
That sounded pretty confident.
That was confidence.
Thank God.
All right.
We're good.
We're at like, we finally made it to like 64,000.
I got two lifelines.
Let's fucking go.
I'm ready.
We got to get to at least 200,000.
You ready to face the traps of this next question?
Good luck to you.
What type of creature was Sam,
the official mascot of the 1984 Los Angeles Olympics?
The eagle.
Sam the eagle?
Sam the alligator.
I think it's Sam the eagle.
It's Sam the eagle.
It is.
I am 90% positive of this.
Or alligator.
Okay.
Let's take away two in-
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Is it Sam the bear or Sam-
It's Sam the eagle.
Oh, I get more time if I do that.
Sam the eagle.
It is.
It's D, I think.
That's in my head.
Yeah, of course.
It's Sam the eagle.
God damn it.
I have one more lifeline.
Now let's go to the next question, if you don't mind.
What is the name of the evil money lender in Charles Dickens' bleak house?
I would never know this.
I need a new question.
I wouldn't-
You use this switch.
It's a tough choice.
Something else.
Good luck.
Why can't it give me something really dumbly specific that I know?
Will you be able to answer this new question as well?
In German mythology, what is a Nibelung?
A dwarf?
A giant?
A god?
A dwarf?
I would say giant.
Is it a giant?
I would click giant.
If it was going to be giant.
I'm doing giant, I think.
Fuck it, whatever.
I think it's giant.
It was a dwarf!
I had it right!
This is not the right answer.
Sorry.
Well, geezer messed up again.
That was a 220, 250,000.
I had it right.
All right, I'm moving on.
I'm playing a different game.
Trivia-
Whatever, I don't care about trivia.
Who cares?
I don't care about-
Oh no, I don't know trivia questions.
Who cares?
Okay, Will of Fortune or Family Feud?
Let's do Will of Fortune first.
That sounds better.
Can one of the mods switch to Will of Fortune?
And you can take it off, emote on emote.
They can't give me answers for this anyways, I don't think.
This is an Ubisoft game?
Interesting.
Okay, so how do I-
Will of Fortune, coming up.
Oh, you need to pee?
What is it doing?
What the fuck just happened?
Why can I-
It's 20 FPS.
There he is!
Sam the Eagle!
I know how to play Will of Fortune.
Okay, so I don't want to play online with people.
They're gonna make me look like shit.
One controller.
Classic.
I need to-
Let me get this in the swing of things first.
I need to get into the swing of things first.
Because what if I get this so fucking wrong?
I'll do online in a minute.
Why would you lock every hairstyle?
Every single hairstyle is locked?
Except for the default one?
There's only one pair of pants.
Okay.
I think that works.
Let me just familiarize myself with the game.
I need to familiarize myself with the game.
There's only two choices.
Ladies and gentlemen, are the stars of America's game.
Hello everyone, how are you?
Five FPS.
So many people here.
I hope you're all well.
This is very bright.
This is a very bright game.
I'll take that as a great.
I'm sure you're ready to get started.
It says here, well, it doesn't say much.
New free-to-play avatar.
Thank you for joining us today.
You're out yet?
Ready for the toss-up?
Okay, let's go.
The category on this one is-
Yeah, this is a switch version.
Food and drink.
Food and drink, okay.
So, Will of Fortune is you have to-
Salad.
Swaps, slop.
Sea scallops.
Fried sea scallops.
Seared, seared sea scallops.
Got it.
You know why I don't want to play online?
Because we're going to queue up with people
that are watching the stream,
and you're going to sit there for 45 seconds
and make me sit there and watch the whole thing.
That's why.
Someone's going to be a troll
and just run the fucking clock out
every single fucking time.
All right, let's go.
Ready for the toss-up.
The category on this one is-
What are you doing?
Renting a jet ski.
Reading a trivia guide.
Test to number one, go ahead.
Reading a-
Reading-
Why are these other people not doing anything?
Reading a trivia guide.
Reading a-
Reading a trivia guide
is a fucking encyclopedia, man.
Reading a trivia guide.
It's a travel guide.
You fucking moron.
Reading a travel guide.
They're all just standing here.
I got three grand.
Well, I think it's time to take our places.
The contestants are ready to start.
I think it's time to start this round.
The category is-
Looks like somebody else is doing his arms.
Doesn't look like somebody's doing like the funny joke
where somebody puts their arms behind their back
and then another person puts their arms through
and does the motions.
What do I do?
Oh, spin.
Free play.
Let's go.
It's a free play.
You have a free-
So take another spin.
What?
Okay.
Let's look for-
Are there any T's?
We have one T.
So that's not a the.
That's a fair bit of a-
Okay.
Let's get another spin here.
No bankrupt.
Oh, fucking shut up.
Why does that even exist?
I don't understand why that exists.
What's the point of that existing?
Get the fuck out of here.
Ouch.
The wedge is always a painful one.
You didn't have any money, so it doesn't matter.
Your turn.
Go ahead.
What is happening right now?
Okay.
All right.
G.
So what is this?
What are you doing?
Standing.
A million?
Oh, shit.
You just lost a million bucks.
Wow.
That-
Why would you get some-
What the fuck is happening?
We could have another one million dollar winner.
Fuck.
We have one-
He's won another million dollar?
You gotta be kidding me.
You won a million dollars?
How do we ever beat that?
You won a million dollars.
I would be a little bit more excited.
So wait, let me get this straight.
That lady won a million dollars no matter what.
You don't even have to win the game.
No.
She has to win.
All right.
What are you doing?
Sliding.
I don't know.
All right.
I'm gonna say-
Okay.
Climbing a big tower.
Climbing a sliding-
What the fuck?
It's either a million dollars or bankrupt every time.
That feels so awful.
Oh, that would-
That's so terrible.
That feels so terrible.
A million bankrupt.
Oh my god.
I feel bad.
Don't even do that.
All right.
Okay.
Flying a-
It's gotta-
It has to be flying, right?
Flying?
What?
What is this?
Playing?
A cue?
Why would you say cue?
Playing a big trumpet.
I don't know.
Playing-
Playing a-
Okay.
Playing-
Let's go again.
All right.
Do it again.
Playing a big concert.
Okay.
Playing-
What?
Are they all vowels?
P-L-A-Y?
I'm sorry.
There are none on the board.
What?
They're all vowels.
Planning a big wedding?
Six hundred.
Will we get any help on this?
What'd you just do?
It seems we're out of luck.
If you'd like to buy a vowel, we have one-
Planning a big-
A-
Eight hundred.
We have one V.
Planning a big-
I guess you're paying for dinner tonight.
What?
With a V?
We got the money.
We have one-
Invitation?
Six hundred.
What are you doing?
I'm planning a vaca-
A-
Planning a big adventure.
Planning a new adventure.
What the-
What are you talking about?
That's the most vague bullshit I've ever heard in my life.
Seven hundred.
Planning a new adventure.
That's-
You're not-
What do you-
What does that mean though?
What are you doing?
That's not the thing you're doing.
I guess you'll be paying for dinner tonight.
Hit bankrupt, please.
Hit bankrupt.
Bankrupt.
Bankrupt, motherfucker.
You're gonna land on bankrupt.
Planning a new adventure.
What are you doing?
Solve it right now.
If you think you know the answer, please go ahead.
That is incredible.
How did you come up with that?
I've landed on bankrupt three times.
As much as I enjoy standing here, I'm ready to get the show started.
Why do they still have zero?
Shall we go ahead and start the round?
The category is showbiz.
Why do they still have zero each?
Contestant number two.
Go ahead and take the first-
Wait, what's happening?
Why do they have zero dollars?
You're going on a cruise ship.
Do we have-
No, you're not.
No.
I'm sorry.
Okay, showbiz.
Six hundred.
Yes, we have success.
Showbiz.
Well, that is a healthy amount to add to your winnings tonight.
Gee.
I guess you'll be paying for dinner tonight.
Showbiz.
Something-
Somebody is singing.
Dancing.
Singing.
OC.
Rocking.
Rocking out.
Rocking a-
Get out of here.
Rocking.
Rocking the new-
Rocking out.
I'm going to say rocking out.
Or rocking the-
Can somebody else fucking play?
Can we get a turn?
Six hundred.
Don't seem to have any of those.
Okay.
I'm going to say-
Let's try it.
Let's try R.
Six fifty.
Okay.
Rock-
Rocking.
Yes, we have some R.
Okay.
Rocking the-
Rocking-
Rum-
Rocking the-
Wild.
Got it.
Rocking the red carpet.
Contestant number one.
Go ahead.
I didn't read that in chat.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
How do I delete?
Wait, what?
Yeah.
Rocking the-
What about Scooby-Doo?
Rocking the red carpet.
I win.
I'm speechless.
Did you just pull that out of thin air?
It's time for the prize round.
The winner will be getting a special prize on top of the cash.
The category is Showbiz.
Showbiz again.
Contestant number three.
Why don't you go ahead and take the first spin?
Well, I'm the only person who has any money.
This is weird.
Will we get any help on this?
Literally cheating.
Put it in emote only then.
That was a super spin.
Thirty five hundred bucks.
Let's go.
You've been baked with thirty five hundred dollars.
Uh, let's go with, um, any D's.
There are hyphens here.
What does the wild card do?
No, what does it do?
That's a free play.
S.
Okay, something something S.
I'd like to buy a vowel, please.
I'd like to buy E.
A lot of E's.
Let's see.
See.
Sheesh.
Um, I'll buy another vowel, please.
That's it.
Showbiz.
I don't know.
Ask something E.
E.
S.
T.
All right.
What is all the hyphening?
Let's use it.
I don't even know it does.
What does this do?
H.
Something the seashells.
All right.
Showbiz.
Something something to the shed.
I don't I don't know.
Eight hundred.
There any ends?
Scenes.
Behind the scenes.
Oh, no.
Behind the scenes documentary.
Oh, shit.
This is bad.
Behind the scenes.
Behind the scenes showcase.
Behind the scenes documentary.
Behind the scenes dialogue.
Behind the scenes credits.
Behind the scenes.
Behind the scenes camera.
Behind the scenes commentary.
Behind the scenes.
Behind the scenes show.
Behind the scenes outtakes.
Behind the scenes outtake.
It's an outtake, right?
By the scenes is outtake.
Oops.
Behind the scenes.
Out of behind the scenes.
I don't know, guys.
I don't fucking have any idea.
Behind the scenes.
What?
Land on bankrupt.
You fucking idiot.
Behind the scenes.
What else would it be?
No, don't solve it.
Yeah, let me solve it.
Behind the scenes.
Lose another turn.
I'm a fucking millionaire.
Why did I do that?
But what if there was an I down there?
Okay, I'm going to buy another vowel.
I'd like to buy.
Oh, please.
Okay.
Oh, behind the scenes.
Ootail.
What is that?
Behind the scenes.
Take.
What even fucking letters do I have?
Behind the scenes.
What?
What in the name of fucking God is this?
I'm going to freak out.
Behind the scenes.
Oh, take.
But you have to give me a break.
Oh, go.
This is real.
Did I win this?
Holy shit.
I'm going to Europe.
Four.
Gone for.
Good for.
Food for thought.
I need to turn the difficulty up.
Category is food and drink.
Food and drink, okay.
Scallops.
Scallop potatoes.
Wait, he just spun it.
What if he lands on bankrupt?
Fortunately, that's not what we need.
Unfortunately, there are none on the board.
This person just keeps doing Q.
Q is in 11 words in the dictionary.
Q is in like maybe 15 fucking total words in the dictionary.
Why do you keep saying Q?
I.
No, no, no, no, no.
What?
No, I don't want to solve.
Why would I solve?
I'm not ready to do that.
Okay.
L.
This is food and drink.
Would you like to solve?
You're going to solve it?
No.
Okay, um.
A.
Yes, we have some A's.
Ale.
Contestant number one.
Would you like to solve?
No.
No, we don't seem to have any of those.
Will we get any help on this?
C.
It seems we're out of luck.
Any Rs?
We have one R.
Good job.
Keep back going.
Contestant number one.
Your chance to solve.
I don't know.
We have one M.
M.
Ma.
Quite a bit of money now.
Contestant number two.
Your chance to.
Yes, we have some S's.
S.
Sliders.
Meatball sliders.
Don't get it.
It's mine.
Contestant number three.
Your chance to solve.
Meatball sliders.
Don't get it.
Yes, we have some E's.
I want a meatball sliders.
Contestant number one.
Your chance to solve.
Who eats a meatball slider?
That is incredible.
How did you come up with that?
Because it was one of the only things I could possibly do.
27,000 versus.
Wow.
I get a bonus round?
We're ready to start the bonus round.
I think.
How do you do this one?
Let's get over there.
Is P good?
Please follow me over here.
What is that?
Things.
Oh, great.
You know the letters R, S, T, L, N, and E.
Let's see what kind of help you can get.
Could we have three consonants and a vowel, please?
Jingle bells.
Let's go H.
I don't know.
M.
Bell B.
And give me an A.
Give me the A.
Wow, you made that look easy.
Only a limited time, so good luck.
And.
Where's my fucking answer?
Where's my shit?
Peel.
Pie.
Fearl.
Pearls.
Diamond pearls.
Something pearls.
Something pearl.
P-E-R-A.
Something diamond pearls.
I pass.
Window decals.
Whatever.
It's fine.
Oh, I unlocked new hair and shoes.
Should I get new clothes?
I just I keep leveling up.
Did I win by so much money that?
Okay, I want to go back.
Customization.
Nice.
Okay.
I have to pee.
I haven't peed in three hours.
Wait, what about should I do this set?
All right, should I try?
Should I see if I can play somebody online?
Nice redditor college professor.
All right, let me go pee.
I'll be right back.
Let me pee.
I'm gonna have to pee like once.
I'll be right back.
Somebody said, when is he going to learn how to spell?
Huh?
Spell, what do you mean?
How does how do you think pearls is spelled?
I'm on the I'm up against a clock.
All right, let's go.
Oops.
I don't think anybody plays this game, guys.
I don't know if we're going to be able to find anybody.
I don't know if anyone plays this.
Wait for me.
I don't know if it's going to work.
You're going to get sniped.
I don't I mean, I don't think people care that much to buy this and snipe me in this game.
People are probably buying it right now.
Well, we'll do another we'll do another one versus the AI.
Okay, we'll go ahead and do another one versus the AI.
Can I make it harder?
Just wait.
You're the first person to play this since 2008.
This game came out like probably a year ago.
How do I do it on hard?
Is there like a settings I can do?
Okay, options, settings.
No, of course not.
I think it's just the AI is going to lose every game.
You have to pick a mode.
Oh, it's difficulty after.
Classic.
Controller.
Now what customization?
I don't where is it?
Oh, all right, let's go.
Okay, there's a bunch of snipers that just got the game.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for joining us today.
Your outfit looks quite interesting.
You must have visited the customization menu.
It says here.
Well, it doesn't.
How are you doing today?
This is our $1,000.
I know how to play now.
All right, it's on hard thing.
Analytics.
Analysis.
You don't know this.
Effort and analysis.
Wait, what do you mean effort?
What?
Go ahead and solve expert analysis.
Oh, my God.
Seared seas gallop.
Let's start a toss up round for $2,000.
The category is food and drink.
Seared seas gallop.
Savory, turkey, turkey, turkey, turkey gravy, turkey, turkey beak,
turkey beaks, turkey beak, turkey beaks.
What is it?
Turkey, turkey, turkey, turkey beaks, turkey beak.
I think it's time to start this round.
The category is.
I forgot it was food and drink.
I thought whatever.
I've tested number three.
I didn't know what it was.
What the hell is that word?
What?
That word is huge.
That's a that's a word.
Look at how big that one is.
Wow.
Look at how long.
What is this word on the board?
What the fuck?
That's a word.
Oh, backwards.
Oh, try to keep positive thoughts now.
Got it.
Seven hundred.
Turkey.
Okay, there's a T.
Is this like a math thing?
It's going to be like a what was the thing?
The tetragoman, the tetradhomicon.
The tetradhomicon, what was it called?
It was like a tetragomicon.
It's going to be like a math thing.
The tetradhomicon.
Yes, we have some S's.
There's a phrase.
Could you pick up that sheet and sleep?
What?
Bankrupt.
Hundred.
Yes, we have some R.
That's a lot of money you won there.
What is it?
This game's fucking dumb.
It's just what this is not even possible.
As bankruptcy gets.
This is almost logically not possible to hit that.
I've hit it five times, six times.
I don't think it's possible to do that.
Yes, we have some L's.
Not bad.
You've got quite a bit of money now.
You'd like to buy a vowel.
Unfortunately, there are none on board.
No, there's no A's.
All right, it's.
I'm sorry.
Bankrupt.
Six hundred.
Wait, did we just get a let's go?
I'm sorry, there are.
It sounds like you're ready to solve.
Go ahead.
Simply.
Is it tubble or?
To.
Irresistible.
Is it irresistible?
No, it's not.
It's irresistible.
Tibble irresistible.
I got it.
Cheater.
Guess what?
You want to play online?
You want you guys saying everybody's cheater?
When I play online with the like 50 of you that bought this game 10 minutes ago.
You're in the chat.
No, you're okay.
You're just going to fucking get it right.
This round start a category.
You're just going to be sitting reading chat and get it right every time.
Online is not going to work.
Number one.
So take a spin.
Put it on emote only.
It's a good idea.
All right.
Around the house.
Give me that vacation.
All right.
How do you get half of a car?
Half of a car.
What do you get the other 50% of the car?
What?
Okay, let's go with B.
We have one.
Okay.
That's a fair bit of cash.
Around the house.
Boom.
What do you do?
Okay, like around the house.
You are doing chores or something.
Chores around the house.
Hanging out in the house.
Building.
B-U-I-L-D-I-N-G.
Bringing.
Yes, we have some R's.
I don't know.
Are you interested in taking a gamble on the mystery wedge?
Flip it.
Let's go.
Ouch.
Bankrupt is always a painful word.
Is that even possible to be on the back of that?
Is that actually possible to be on the back of that?
I feel like that's not supposed to be there.
Six-fifty.
We have one T.
A bag.
Okay, T.
We've got quite a bit of money now.
Bart.
Boom.
You hit big with $3,500.
Big.
Yes, we have some L's.
Boom.
Picked up some cash.
But what's not served?
You've certainly got the money.
We have one E.
Beat.
Bertolli.
Sure, you can buy a vowel.
We have some U's.
Bertolli.
Beautiful.
Buy a vowel.
Beautiful floor.
Beautiful flooring.
Beautiful hardwood flooring.
I got it.
Uh-oh, see you later.
Beautiful hardwood flooring.
Beautiful hardwood floor.
I got it.
If I play online, by the way, I have to shut up.
I can't say all these things out loud.
Beautiful hardwood flooring.
I'd like to solve it, please.
Actually, no, let's get some money.
I was gonna say that.
I'm just gonna quit the game.
Beautiful hardwood floor.
That's quite a bit of cash in your pocket now.
All right.
I'm gonna do this one more time.
Because I'm terrified of actually hitting banker
because I keep I'm glued to it.
All right, good.
600.
We have one.
Well, that is a healthy.
Very good.
One more.
Last one.
Good.
Yes, we have.
Beautiful hardwood flooring.
Okay, I'd like to solve it now.
Great job.
It sounds like you're ready to solve.
Go ahead.
Beautiful hardwood floors.
Thank you.
I'll take it.
I'm in the lead now.
A free prize?
This is a person.
Express 1000.
What's that mean?
900.
All right, person.
We have one.
W.
Well, that is a healthy amount to add to your winnings tonight.
It's one word.
If you'd like to buy a value.
Yes, we have some E's.
E.
Wait, is this a person's name?
I don't know.
I don't get what this is.
Testant number two.
Go ahead.
News.
Caster.
Oh, that's a person.
That's a job.
More of a that's not a person.
Safe.
I see it.
Maybe I should stick with.
That's enough.
But you might want to brush up on your French.
Oh, my God.
Because France is where you're going.
I lost.
It's time for a toss up round for $3,000.
Four, five, six, seven.
Category is phrase.
What?
Testant number three.
Go ahead.
What a day.
God damn it.
What the fuck, dude?
Let's go ahead and start the round.
The category is living thing.
What's that?
What's that mean?
Here goes one last spin.
Living thing.
Yes, we have some A's.
Aardvark.
Your chance to solve.
Anaconda.
Any ends.
Yes, we have some N's.
Wait, it could be living thing.
That could be that could be American.
Contestant number one.
A-M-E-A-M-E-R-I-C.
American.
I don't want to give it away.
But I don't know.
I'm not giving it away yet, though.
Yes, we have some E's.
Okay, it's American.
It's going to be some kind of.
Contestant number two.
Would you like to solve?
We have one.
American water.
American water buffalo.
It's American water buffalo.
American water.
I don't know.
Yes, we have some R's.
That's a fair question.
I don't know.
American water snake.
Contestant number one.
Would you like to solve?
American water crane.
No, American water.
I don't know.
American water.
We have one T.
I need another letter here.
Contestant number two.
Would you like to solve?
American water spaniel.
A water spaniel.
What is that?
To be honest, I wasn't sure how you were going to solve this.
That's what people tag their dog as
when the dog is in the pool or something.
Oh, look, we got an American water spaniel.
That's what?
That's what a real fucking animal.
American water spaniel.
She's not going to get it.
We'll throw R, S, T, L, M, and E.
Maybe it's the German dog house.
I was pretty sure you were going to get that one.
Just a few moments to solve so quickly.
Birthday party.
Oh, come on.
That's fucking easy.
That's actually easy.
Wow, you won the bonus round.
And the prize is, I think you'll be happy with this one.
Actually easy.
All right, are the strange snipers ready?
Strange snipers, are you ready?
Oops.
I have a feeling you are.
I'm not going to tell the stream snipers when I'm going to do it.
You know what I mean?
Isn't that a good idea?
Here we go.
I'm turning the sound off.
You guys ready?
Stream snipers, good luck.
I'm not going to tell you when I press it.
It's me and Joe Two.
Wait, only one of you is playing this?
Hold on.
Me, Joe Two.
I fucked up my camera.
Hold on.
Okay, me, Joe Two, and Moo Moo.
You guys ready?
What is it?
In the kitchen.
Salad, salad bowl?
A wooden salad bowl.
Wooden salad, wow, I'm better than them.
I'm sorry, I just screamed.
That was so loud.
I'm sorry.
Wooden, is it wooden or wooden?
Is it wooden or wooden?
Wooden or wooden?
Wooden, wooden, it's wooden, wooden, wooden.
Is it wooden or wooden?
Which one is it?
I think it's wooden.
Wooden, is it a wooden salad bowl?
Yep.
All right, get it in emote only.
I don't want them to see.
Hurry, quick.
On the map.
Nice job.
Nice work.
You did it.
Okay, event.
So let me spin.
Why can't I spin?
I can't do anything, Bob.
Whatever your name is, I can't do anything.
Is this me?
Oh, we're the same character.
We're literally the same character.
What was it?
The game is muted?
Game spin.
We're the same fucking character.
Thank God it didn't land on Banquo.
All right, shh, don't say anything.
I don't want them to know.
It's an event.
There are no S's?
What?
You're gonna be shitting me.
Okay, all right, all right, okay.
This is an event.
Something, something, don't say it out loud.
You're going too fast.
It's a free play.
You have a free play.
So take another spin.
If you'd like to, we have one A.
Um, no, you don't get the vacation.
You're gonna get the vacation.
Prize.
Uh-oh.
Banquo.
No.
Vowel.
If you'd like to buy a vowel.
Yes, we have some O's.
Um.
Yes, we have some I's.
I think I, do I know the answer?
I think I know the answer.
We have one.
It's, um, I mean, we can't, we're just kind of sitting there watching.
Contestant number three.
Go ahead.
I'm not gonna say it.
What do they, what, what, what?
Get it wrong?
Should I get it wrong?
Don't, no help.
No, wait, did you just pass it?
All right, my turn.
It's not even my fucking turn.
Contestant number one.
Go ahead and solve.
Free, wait, did you, you passed it to the other person so they could get points and not me.
This is, that is incredible.
But wait, hold on.
Wait, did you think you were passing it to me?
I know that's kind of confusing.
Are we all ready to start?
We're the same character.
Yes?
Well, let's get to our places.
Shall we go ahead?
I'm so confused.
What happened?
Contestant number two.
Why don't you go ahead and take the first spin?
All right, this is an event.
All right, let's get some, let's get some money on the board.
Huh?
There's no fucking B's.
You tried to drag the time out, but you just got screwed over.
I told you people were gonna do that.
I told you.
All right, Joe, what do you got?
We have one.
Try to wait till the last, the last possible second.
Okay, R, event, event, event.
What is it?
Ow, my neck.
Be careful.
Don't flip that over.
I would just take the thousand.
Be careful.
You don't want to flip it.
If you flip it, it's going to be bankruptcy.
Don't do it.
Careful.
Oh, I told you.
I tried to tell you.
I tried to warn you.
This is not Wheel of Fortune music.
This is Monopoly music.
Okay, this has got to be a C.
What the?
How is that not a C?
That seems impossible.
She's slacking the game out.
All right.
I can't, there's no word I could think of.
L.
An event.
It's too completely nondescript.
Okay.
Bankrupt.
Uh-oh.
Oh, and you didn't land on the car.
Didn't land on the car.
I don't know.
I don't think anybody is going to get this for a while.
Okay, so it's got to be an F somewhere then, right?
Give me some money.
Don't do it.
All right, I got a free flight.
I got this is huge.
With your free, this is massive.
Okay, I would like to buy a vowel for free.
If you'd like to buy a vowel.
I want.
Oh, something.
Don't say it.
As of by International Space Station.
I don't know.
Seven hundred.
What is the first letter?
Well, it looks like you won't be winning the one million dollars.
The one million is gone.
To go home with a lot of cash.
You've certainly got the money.
Yes, we have some fees.
What does this start with?
This is an event.
I have no idea.
It could be anything.
It could be actually literally anything.
Ouch.
Bankrupt is always a painful one.
Bankrupt.
Shit, I'm in a good position then.
Okay, give me don't give me don't bankrupt.
Okay, what the fuck is this?
Seven hundred.
W this W.
No, we don't seem to have any of those.
What?
Ernest?
Bankrupt again.
What is this fucking thing?
It's honestly I'm so confused.
Nobody else knows it.
Good.
If you'd like to guess, we have some eyes.
You think you know the answer.
Please go ahead.
Preliminary investigation.
This is not an event.
That's a preliminary investigation is an event.
That's so vague.
We have a prize round now.
The winner of this round will also be getting a free prize.
Are you all ready?
The category is person.
Okay, person.
Let's go.
Contestant number three.
You're up first.
So take a spin.
Person.
Don't land on bankrupt again.
That would be so sad.
In a hundred.
We have great job.
That's quite a bit of cash in your pocket now.
Wait, wasn't this a different person?
What happened to the other contestant?
What the fuck happened?
I'm going to spend all that at once now.
Who is where is this?
Where is there is there another contestant somewhere?
I'm so lost.
What happened?
I'm so confused.
When does that happen?
Yes, we have some tea.
Okay, this is a person.
Let's go.
Check this out.
I didn't want to do that.
No, I wasn't doing trusted psychic.
Okay, I was doing trusted physician.
But my psychic.
Yes, we have some ends.
That's a healthy amount.
Well, now they know it's trusted.
I was so confident.
It was trusted physician.
Congratulations.
Trusted magician.
Who else do you trust?
That's a person.
Lawyer, physician, trusted lawyer.
Flip it bankrupt.
What's going on?
Unfortunately, it looks like you won't be going home with that today.
What just happened?
Why did they?
Why?
What happened?
Why bankrupt?
All right, come on.
With the free play, you've got a second chance at this.
If you'd like to buy a vowel, you've got the cash.
Trusted.
Somebody that you trust.
I trust a.
No, it's not.
No, that's not what this is.
No way.
600.
Fortunately, there are none on the board.
I'm sorry.
Trusted.
I don't know.
600.
Trusted.
Fortunately, that's not what we need.
You got the car.
You got the other half of the car.
Holy shit.
We have one excited.
Trusted coupon.
I have 50.
We have one.
That's a lot of money you won there.
All right, solve it.
I know you might solve it.
You know, solve it.
Are you ready to solve?
Contestant number three.
Trusted companion.
I have a thousand dollars.
This is such bullshit.
We'll be in France.
Everybody goes.
Why is everybody going to France?
Toss up round for three thousand.
It is.
I isolated.
Isolated.
Isolated island.
Number two.
All right.
I'm back in the game.
Let's get this round started.
Back in the game.
Category you doing?
Not this shit again.
I'll give the wheel one last spin.
So what if it lose a turn?
Does he just like slap himself in the face?
Yes, we have some ease.
Contestant number two.
Okay.
Want to solve?
No, I cannot solve.
Please.
This is a what are you doing?
Yes, we have some tease.
Okay.
Very clearly.
We know what that is.
Something the.
Great job.
That's quite a bit of cash.
Contestant number three.
Your chance to solve.
I I know it.
That's a lot of money you won there.
Contestant number one.
Would you like to solve?
Do you know?
You don't know, right?
Do you actually know?
Betting the.
Betting the what?
Do you actually know?
I don't think you actually know.
Betting the what?
Okay, we're good.
Will we get any help on?
I don't know it either.
I was just trying to freak the other contestants out.
So they thought I knew it.
Yes, we have some G.
Betting the.
Gigi.
Good good good.
The goo goo.
What the fuck is this?
Betting the goo goo.
Betting the what?
What word is this?
Betting the the giggle.
Betting the giggles.
Have you ever heard a human say that out loud?
I wasn't sure how you.
I've never heard a human say that before.
Oh, I'm going to be betting the giggles.
Lucky contestant.
Good luck.
See how you do.
Oh, a comma.
What's that mean?
Please follow me over here.
Phrase.
We can give you the letters.
R.S.T.L.N.
This is a phrase.
Come on, let's get it.
So let's see what shows up.
Would you please choose three consonants?
Come on, you can do it.
I was pretty sure you were going to get that one.
Okay, trash.
I hope you're ready because we only have a few moments to solve.
Traf rammer.
Traf roamer.
What's a phrase?
Cash.
I know it.
Uh-huh.
Crash.
Crash something.
Crash racing.
Crash.
Trash.
Ten seconds remaining.
Crap.
Clash.
Oh, you didn't get the bonus round, but you still came in first.
Wash rumors.
All right, I'll do.
I'll do this one one more time and then I'm going to move on to Family Feud.
Nice job, guys.
Nice playing.
Same deal.
I'm not going to tell you when I'm clicking it.
You'll never know.
It was getting the giggles, not betting the giggles.
Wait, what?
It was getting.
It wasn't betting.
I thought it was betting.
Betting the giggles.
It was getting the giggles.
Okay, I actually did not fucking know.
All right, here we go.
I think I just jumped into somebody else's game.
Did I just?
I meant somebody else's game.
Have you guys been playing with each other this whole time?
I'm in another person's game.
Round one.
Okay, I just jumped into another game.
Okay, well, it's there's an AI here.
I only had two seconds.
I got it.
I'll buy a vowel.
Sure, you can buy.
I'm looking for.
Is there an A, please?
I'm the stream sniper.
I'd like to spin, please.
Give me the cruise ship.
All right, I'm going to.
This is on the map.
This is any DS.
All right, you realize that these are little kids.
No, they are not because you want to know why they're not little kids.
Because I tried to find a game an hour ago and nobody was playing.
There was not a single person playing the game.
I waited 15 minutes for all of you to download it.
And now if you'd like to buy a vowel.
No, we don't seem to have any of those.
I tried to play this online like an hour ago.
And then I waited for all of you to download the game.
You realize that we are little kids.
No, you're not.
I have I got demographics.
I've got demographics.
Yes, we have some tea.
OK, something a little bit of stuff.
Yes, that tough.
Yes, some of them up.
Yes, that doesn't miss.
That that means that six fifty.
Yes, we have some.
Oh, twenty five hundred.
Nice, nice job.
Nice job.
You did a good job there.
So that tough.
I don't know.
I guess you'll be paying for dinner.
Is it X?
How could it be an X?
What is this again?
This is it.
Is this a six fifty is on the map.
Yes, we have some six sith.
I know contestant number one.
It's your chance.
I know what this is, but I don't I don't know the first part.
I know the second part is a good one.
As much as I enjoy.
It's a mystery.
Balls.
Go ahead and take the first spin.
I jumped into somebody else's game.
This sucks.
I want to do my own game.
OK, food and drink.
Fortunately, that's not what we need.
Lobster mac and cheese, ground pork, ground burgers, ground patties.
I got to stop talking.
They're going to hear six hundred.
Oh, please.
None on the board.
I'm sorry.
It's a free play.
You have a free.
You're going to do a concert.
You're going to buy a vowel for fruit.
OK, food or drink.
Don't get bankrupt.
Yes, we have some.
Banana.
I guess you'll be paying for dinner.
Yes, we have some.
Oh, shit.
Oh, come on.
Steam, steam, steam.
Contestant number three.
Go ahead and solve.
Steam steak fajitas.
Oh, my God.
Fucking damn it.
Hey, just wait till you wait.
Do you see me in Family Feud?
What do you see me in Family Feud?
Just wait, contestant number.
Take the first spin thousand.
OK, B, we get any help on this being this being everything.
Fifteen thousand.
How am I ever going to win this?
Yes, we have some tea.
This is also food and drink, right?
Is it food and drink?
It is.
Yeah.
Oh, all right.
That's good.
That's a good thing for me.
Contestant, it's your turn.
Seven hundred.
OK, food and drink.
Something and peanut butter and jelly sandwich.
Yes, we have some.
Risotto.
Something risotto seared, sauteed, sauteed something.
Yes, we have some.
Oh, my God.
My chest.
All right, here we go.
Yes, we have some beans.
OK.
All right.
I know it.
Don't solve it.
Get it wrong.
No, don't get it right.
This is my chance to come back here.
We have a bit of money now.
The expense that you're going to end up with a hundred thousand dollars.
This Express Bowl should have stop.
It's dumb.
Salted and dry roasted peanuts.
You spelt it wrong.
It's an I.
For one second, I think they may have been watching and they were like.
No, that's right.
You might want to brush up on your French because.
What?
You don't know what this is.
Organic.
Or again, I organic organized.
Yo, I know this person is going to have 50 million dollars by the end of this.
Organized pantry.
I am really surprised that nobody has written down ball sack and hit enter and then left the game.
You guys are really, really doing well.
I'm actually very surprised.
This is actually you guys are on your best behavior.
Characters.
We have one car.
Quite a bit of money now.
Test it.
Number one, your chance to solve.
I have zero dollars.
Romeo and Juliet and Romeo and Jules.
Nobody, nobody wrote.
Nobody paid 30 dollars to buy this.
Got into the game, wrote ball sack, quit and uninstalled it.
God damn it.
All right.
Is it time for a family feud?
You can take it off of.
Let's go over here now.
We need to see if they win.
Braids contested.
We will give you the typical letters R, S, T, L, N and E.
Is it Donald Duck?
All right.
What do you got?
You know, the drill here will need three consonants.
P, P, C, M.
What are we going to use for a vowel?
I was pretty sure you were going to get that one.
I don't know.
Time is short.
So get ready to solve.
Game.
Home away from home.
This person legit is good.
Yeah.
And you can add 50,000 50,000 dollars.
What?
All right.
It's family feud time.
That's fun.
Let's do family feud.
Do more.
Now it's family few time.
One more.
I'll go back and do one more.
Maybe after this we'll see.
It depends on how fun family feud is.
You're just going to get rolled again.
Can you do this one online?
Am I going to be able to connect?
I'll try.
Can you play family feud without a family?
I'm just doing it in the solo game.
Getting the giggles.
I know that was stupid of me, but whatever.
It's fine.
Don't worry.
This is loud.
Can we change the family?
This is family feud 2021.
It's whatever the one is on Switch.
Have I played this one?
I don't think I've played this one.
I played almost every single family feud.
That's ever released.
I don't think I played this.
No, no, I refuse.
You got to be fucking kidding me.
What if I don't want it?
I don't want an Ubisoft account.
I don't want to fucking do an Ubisoft.
It's like such a pain.
I don't it's too late.
It actually isn't too late.
I got away from it.
That's got to be the worst thing that they ever did.
Why do they care that much?
Let me I'm going off on a rant here.
To have this like annoying fucking locked up bullshit that you have to do.
Why do they care that much?
What is what?
What do you care that much for?
Just to like is it for just for data?
Just to collect data monetization.
You can do monetization in your game.
It's for data.
I hate that.
All right.
Well, let's let's let's do let's have I played this classic.
Okay.
In the authentic family feud experience.
Let me just let me get let me say what goes.
I've never played this one before.
That's just literally what I wear every day.
I don't have to do anymore.
Is that it?
Happy's family.
Okay.
I they have a streamer mode.
I have to connect an Ubisoft account.
Connect.
Relog in.
I just I just I refuse.
Wait, it's just me.
It actually is only me.
What is that?
What is there as a cat?
Who the fuck is Lucky McCoy?
Okay.
In a team of one.
This is fucking sad.
Here's who's standing in your way.
It's the Cooper family.
Oh, the Cooper family.
Why am I only one person?
Our family get out to answer your surveys.
Whoever scores the most points goes on to fast money
for the chance to win a lot of cash and a brand new car.
It's feud time.
Let's do this.
Why do I have no family here?
The person that asked the question.
Can you play this?
Can you play family feud without a family?
Get things rolling.
The answer is yes.
It's time for the face off.
One person from each family to join.
All right, let's go.
That run was really weird.
I'm going to need five answers to this question.
Okay.
I'm going to ask you a question
and you need to buzz in first to answer.
If you can find what's hiding behind the top slot.
You get to choose if your family plays the round
or gives it a pass.
100 people.
We ask them the following.
Name something you buy
that you hope you never have to use.
A toothbrush.
What you got?
I don't know.
What does that mean?
A, I don't know.
A coffin, a gun.
Yeah, I don't know.
A coffin.
A gun makes sense.
Maybe a coffin.
Our survey says.
Gun answer.
Are you going to play?
Or are you going to pass?
I do that.
I go.
I'm going to pass this because I don't know.
This is a big chance.
Let's make the most of it.
Have you got something for us?
What do you got?
Something that you don't ever, you don't want to use.
You sure about that?
Be up there.
Let's find out.
Fucking suppository.
Why does he say suppository?
That's going to put a dent in your game.
No, you want to use a suppository.
If it's medical, if it's medicated.
You want to, you need to use a suppository.
If it's prescribed, what are you talking about?
That's good.
Is it up there?
Pregnancy test.
Does this guy just say everything right?
We've got another strike on the board.
Okay, what else?
You got anything else?
I need to think of something to steal.
Name something you buy that you hope you never have to use.
That's what you think, huh?
Our survey says.
Like you shit your pants.
Spare underwear.
These are all such fucking dog shit answers.
Oh no, that's strike three.
That's such a fucking bad answer.
That's such a bad answer.
Okay, what do I never want to use besides that gun?
How about?
Give me an answer.
And if you're right, you get all the points.
Give me a wrong one and well, you know.
Something you buy that you don't ever want to use.
A knife.
No, you cook with that.
Bug spray.
Like roach killer.
Roach spray.
Bug, roach kill, bug spray.
A poison to kill bugs.
It's worth it.
I'm very curious about what these answers are because.
Holy shit, man.
Congratulations.
What?
What is it?
Let's tidy up the board and show those missing answers.
Number five.
What are you?
Jumper cables.
This is the fourth answer.
This mouth.
What's going on?
Insurance.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's see what's behind number three.
Casket.
Oh, it was casket.
I got what I got it.
Hiding behind slot number two.
Fire extinguisher.
Whatever.
Here's how the scores are shaping up so far.
What's going on with his voice?
His voice is changing pitch.
Here's how the scores as of are.
What the fuck was that?
Let's see what awaits us next.
Your family sucks.
I am the only family.
Let's go round two, round two, round two, round two.
It's time for the face off.
Who's going to join me up here?
I need someone from each family.
Okay, I'm ready.
I need five answers.
Get those feuding fingers ready.
Whoever buzzes in first gets a shot at the question.
We took a survey.
100 people.
Name an activity that your feet aren't on the ground to do.
Flying.
But wait, that's weird.
Flying, swimming.
But what's number one?
Swimming.
Oh, okay.
And what did our survey say?
That's got to be number one, right?
Swimming.
Number one.
Answer number one.
Pass or play?
I'm going to pass.
They'd rather pass than play?
Fine by me.
I don't want to play.
And now it's your guess.
Cycling.
Oh yeah, okay.
That's what you're going with?
Cycling and swimming are the only ones I can think of.
Cycling.
Correct answer.
Have you got some feud for thought?
Huh?
Swing.
We have an answer.
Um.
There aren't many answers left.
Is it there?
No.
Swing.
What?
Nice.
You put your feet on the ground to swing.
You have to sit in the swing, put your feet on the ground, and push.
Name an activity that your feet aren't on the ground to do.
That's your answer.
Our survey said...
Sailing.
Nope.
All right, I gotta think of some good ones.
Sorry.
You've earned yourself a strike.
It's up to you now.
Sleeping.
Oh, shit.
That's a good one.
We have a few answers left.
Have you found one of them?
That's a good one.
Sleeping.
Almost cleared the board.
There's only one answer remaining.
Skydiving.
Okay, sure.
Is that the last answer on the board?
Yeah, I would say driving a car.
You've cleared the board.
Getting ahead now.
Why did I pass?
So, where are we with the score?
Because I didn't think...
Whatever, I'm not gonna pass this next one.
I'll get this one.
One of our families hasn't gone on the board yet.
No, that's sad.
Let's go.
It's time for a face-off.
Can I have someone from each family join me, please?
It's a full board.
Eight answers are up there.
Interested in doubling your money?
Because now everything is worth twice as much.
In our survey, we asked 100 people,
name a U.S. soap opera.
I don't fucking know any.
That's not a soap opera?
That was...
That's not a soap opera.
Melrose Place is not a soap opera.
Can we get another question?
The number one answer is still up there.
Days of our lives.
Yep.
Said with confidence.
Do we have it?
I am going to pass this.
Because there's no way you're gonna get all these,
unless the computer...
That's on the board.
I don't know.
You wanna play?
No, I don't wanna play.
Force them to play.
I don't wanna play.
There's no...
There's so many up there, pass.
Okay, play passes over.
Pass, Patrick, passing Andy, that's fine.
There's no way they get all these.
I think you've got a great answer for us.
That didn't even fit on there.
Let's see if it's up there.
The young and the restless.
Somebody said he doesn't even wanna play the game.
He's not even playing the game.
But it works a lot of times.
One life to live.
Feeling lucky?
No, that's not a soap opera.
That's the name of my old Team Fortress 2 series.
One life to live.
All right, way to go, kiddo.
Name a U.S. soap opera.
Our survey said.
Knott's Landing.
At your first strike.
Two more and you're done.
I need number one, what is it?
I thought it was raining.
I thought it was actually raining.
So that's just the weird clapping sound.
All right, let's try it.
Could it be there?
Mash is not a soap opera.
That's tough.
What do you have for us?
Oh, Settle Down.
What's with this end zone celebrations?
Interesting answer.
Did anyone in the survey say this?
Dallas.
Double.
All right, all right, all right.
I need one.
Uh oh, two strikes.
Our other family better get ready.
Name a U.S. soap opera.
Sure thing.
Let's see if that's the correct answer.
The Bold and the Beautiful?
Guiding Light.
Bold and the Beautiful?
Oh, shut up.
You're still in the game.
Bold and the Beautiful.
All right, I'll get that one.
What will you go for?
As the world turns.
Okay, is that one of the ones we're still looking at?
Bold and the Beautiful is way more popular.
As the world turns.
Way more popular.
Thank you.
All right.
Bold and the Beautiful is probably...
Three strikes.
That's gonna do it for you.
Bold and the Beautiful.
There's an opportunity to steal here.
It's not Family Guy.
It's not a soap opera.
Stop it.
All we need is one answer
and this family can steal the round.
Okay.
Bold and the Beautiful.
If this answer is up there,
you take the points for this round.
All My Children?
I think it's Bold and the Beautiful.
I just have to get one.
Bold and Beautiful.
But is that the...
That's it, right?
Answer accepted.
Let's see if that's a good answer.
The Bold and the Beautiful.
You've cracked it.
I'm in the game.
Those points.
It's time to take a look at what we didn't find.
Time for five.
All My Children?
Passions.
Answer number three.
All My Children.
It would have been all right.
You would have had it.
Okay, here we go.
Let's take a look at the current scores.
I'm in the game still.
One more good round and I get it.
This game is shaping up to be a real thriller.
I gotta piss so bad.
I can't wait to see who comes out on top.
How am I so sad?
Are you ready for another face-off?
The game is close.
Why am I so depressed?
I need a contestant from each family, please.
Top five answers on the board there.
All right, this is actually important.
Let's go.
Triple points in play now.
You better make sure your answers count.
100 people gave us an answer to this question.
What would a pirate bring on a date?
Fast fingers, my friend.
Feeling confident?
Boat?
Boat.
Treasure.
A treasure.
You bring treasure.
Okie dokie.
Did any of our 100 people say it?
Treasure.
What?
That's not up there.
Can you do any better?
Let's find out.
What else would you bring?
What would a pirate bring on a date?
Treasure.
You would not bring us.
Ok.
Well, I don't know if I want to go on a date with that guy.
Bring a sword to the date.
Sword.
Excuse me?
Looks like you finally struck gold.
You're on the board.
You won the face-off.
What are you talking about?
Play or pass?
I said treasure because...
Let's hope someone in your family has the top answer.
Let's play.
Ok.
Let's watch again.
Watch Andy.
It's your go.
What do you think?
Here we go there.
Jolly Roger?
Serei said...
Jolly Roger.
If it's not on the board, you get a strike.
You're gonna bring the Jolly Roger.
Alright.
Let's hear it.
A parrot.
Yeah, ok.
Let's see where you're going with this.
I need to steal because I need...
This is important.
Is that answer good enough?
The parrot's not on there.
Parrot.
No, it's not.
Holy shit.
What's number one?
Gold?
Strike.
Get another strike and the other family will get a chance.
Ok then.
Let's check the board and see if it made it.
If it's not number one then I don't know what it is.
What is number one?
It has to be gold.
This game is not over yet.
Gold.
It's gold.
I got it.
Gold.
What would a pirate bring on a date?
Alcohol.
Yep.
You bring the ship to the date.
Let's see what the survey says.
You're going to bring the ship to the date.
Ship.
How would that work?
And how would that work?
Nice.
Feudal.
Yeah.
Let's go to the Applebee's.
I'm going to show up in my fucking sailing boat.
What do you...
What?
It's all up to you now.
No pressure.
But if you miss this...
Where are you...
How?
That's all she wrote.
No, it's going to be gold.
Will that be one of the missing answers?
Peg leg.
Gold.
It's going to be gold and I win.
And that's your third strike.
The other family has a chance.
Gold or alcohol?
Rum.
We just need one answer.
Would I bring my own booze into the restaurant though?
The round is yours.
I don't know.
Would I actually bring my own booze to the restaurant?
If it is, you've scored a steal.
If not, the points go straight over to the other side.
Gold or rum.
Which one's better?
It's going to be rum.
Nope, it's not.
What is it then?
Gold.
It's got to be gold, right?
Or eye patch.
No, peg.
Peg leg wasn't on there.
Why would eye patch be?
It's gold.
Okay, survey says gold.
That's not what we're looking for.
Fuck your whole family.
Congrats, this round is yours.
Now it's time to see what you missed.
Number four, show yourself.
Car, show me the third answer.
And now it's time for one last look at the scores.
And that's it.
Car.
You'd bring a car, baby.
Of course you would.
Because you'd be a guy dressed in a pirate costume.
You'd be a girl dressed in a pirate costume.
Why would a car?
Car and shit.
Let's make Sunday a fun day.
Come on, let's play Family Feud.
I'm not going anywhere.
Somebody said behind the scenes.
Lucky is here today.
Let's give a big, hey, haven't we met before?
To our returning family.
This guy's got me energy.
I'm feeding off of this guy.
With their eyes on first.
And defending their crown.
I feel like me and this guy would get along.
Here's a quick rundown on the rules.
I'll ask you a survey.
No, I don't fuck the Ubisoft club.
I want to play Family Feud on the Switch.
I don't want to go through a fucking hoop to get there.
I want to play the video game without any other extra fucking steps.
Let's play another game.
Without any extra steps.
There's extra steps everywhere.
Just want to join me up front.
I'm going to relax my blood pressure, right?
I don't want to go too long.
We've got five answers up for grabs.
I'm taking this.
I'm going fast money.
Let's go.
Be sure to buzz in when you've got an answer to the survey question.
If you're first to find the number one answer,
you get to decide if your family will play or pass the round.
We asked 100 people to give us an answer to this.
Name something a person opens every day.
Nice reflexes, Tex.
Yes.
Time to find out if it's up there.
Door.
We've got a right answer, but it's not at the top.
Jar.
Name something a person opens every day.
Yes.
Time to check the board.
What?
Mind.
You open your mind every day.
I'm going to play this.
No points.
You open a door.
You open a...
What do you open?
You open...
A jar.
You open a can.
You open a bag.
You open a bag every day.
You open a...
All right.
You open a bag.
Everybody opens a bag every day of some kind.
A potato chip bag.
A clothing bag.
Bag.
You open up a bag of some kind every day.
You don't.
Okay.
Strike one.
Two more and you're out.
Number one answer.
What do you open every single day?
What do you think?
Your phone?
Like you open up your phone.
Look at you.
Is that what is this supposed to...
You open your phone.
You open your...
Oh, more physical.
Right.
You open your eyes.
That's your mouth.
I want to see that answer.
Eyes.
Okay.
Really?
Mouth?
Excellent job.
Can. It's gonna be can.
Oh.
Are you ready?
I need an answer from you.
Okay. Open your mouth.
Open your phone.
You open your mouth.
You open your doors.
Mouth.
That's what you think, huh?
Did our survey agree?
Mouth.
That's a good one.
Nice work.
Time to search your mind for an answer.
What else?
Can.
There's no can.
Okay.
You open a...
You open the fridge.
It's worth a shot.
Is that one of the remaining answers?
Good answer.
Fridge.
So what is number one?
Look at that beautiful board.
Almost full.
What do you open every day?
That's not a...
Your mouth?
Your eyes?
Your...
Bridge.
A door.
Your...
A car?
But car would be door, wouldn't it?
I don't think that's accurate.
I already said pornhub.
You open your...
Mail?
I don't know if mail's gonna work.
I'll try it though.
And I guess I did read that.
Do you guys open mail every day?
Let's check the board.
I don't think...
That's not accurate.
What?
You open your mail every single day?
I don't think so, but I got it.
The points go to this family.
Which family is leading the way?
It wasn't email.
That was regular mail.
That's only the first round.
Let's keep moving.
Some of us have responsibilities.
What do you think I have responsibilities?
What are you gonna get in the mail that you need?
That you can't get on your fucking phone or on a website?
What responsibilities are you gonna do for the mail in 2022?
I'm very curious.
That you do every single day in the mail.
You know what I get in the mail?
A bunch of fucking advertisements that I have to shred.
I get advertisements.
All right.
Name something people put all over their bodies.
I don't know.
That's an image I don't need in my head, friend.
Let's see if you're right.
Who is doing this?
Honey.
Who puts honey all over their body?
Why would you do that?
Not in this survey.
Okay.
Lotion?
You put honey all over you.
I would say lotion.
Right?
That's what you're going with?
Do we have a right answer?
Lotion.
We've got a top answer.
I ain't playing this.
So what do you say?
I'm passing it.
Pass or play?
There's no way the AI's gonna get this.
You're up.
What you got for me?
Tattoo.
We have an answer.
Did our survey say it?
Tattoo.
Nope.
You failed to find an answer.
Water is a pretty good one.
Which means you get your first strike of the round.
Do you have an answer?
I am playing the game.
This is tactical strategy bullshit.
That's your answer.
They're not gonna get it.
The first person said honey, guys.
So it's up there.
Name something people put all over their bodies.
Got it.
All over your body?
Perfume.
No, no way.
No fucking way, dude.
No way.
You put perfume all over your entire body?
Moving along the feud, Jane.
Okay, sure.
Is it there?
Clothes.
All right.
Yeah.
There's only two answers left on the board.
Yeah?
Tattoo wasn't up there.
Piercings aren't gonna be either.
All right.
I gotta think, I gotta think, I gotta think.
Ouch.
What goes up here?
Oh no.
Oh god, I'm sorry.
Name something people put all over their bodies.
Say it with confidence.
All right.
What do we got?
What sunscreen?
Water?
Is that one of the ones we've got left?
Sponge.
Sunscreen.
Sunscreen is gonna be good.
Sunscreen, sunscreen, sunscreen, sunscreen, sunscreen.
It's time for the other team to have a crack at this.
Sunscreen.
Perfect.
To steal the points, all they've gotta do is find one right answer.
I don't know.
Water would be the only other one that I could think of that would be the real one.
That was really fast.
Water.
Sunscreen.
But water is so stupidly easy.
I feel like it has to be up there.
You're looking at huge neck veins.
This is not what that is.
Look.
I'm gonna say water.
Water.
Oh, come on.
That was such an easy answer too.
What was it?
Nobody does that.
Who puts powder all over their whole body?
Oil.
Nobody does that.
Oil all over your body?
Let's see how the scores look.
Powder all over your whole body?
One of our families is moving ahead.
Are you a gymnast?
But there's still time to catch up.
Who's putting powder all over their body?
Get your game faces on because it's time for the face-off.
Who wants to play?
Get over here.
I'm still winning.
I'm fine.
Yeah, baby powder.
I put baby powder on my balls.
Okay, yeah.
Going like this on your balls with powder, by the way, is not going like this.
Everywhere else.
It didn't say what do you put on your balls.
Something smells good.
Bacon.
Do you have an answer?
Feeling lucky?
Let's see it.
Bacon.
That's worth the most points.
What's it gonna be?
Play or pass?
This time around, they want to play.
Okay.
Food.
I think all food is included in that, right?
So you can't say any more foods.
What smells good?
Candle.
I mean, a candle makes sense to me.
A candle.
Got it.
Perfume.
Let's see if it's there.
Candle.
Candle smells great.
That's not up there.
So here is your first swipe.
Okay.
Perfume.
Nature.
Flowers.
Got another answer?
Yeah, I'll do flowers.
A flower smells good.
All right.
Let's try it.
Is it up there?
Let's hope so.
Here it is.
All right.
These next...
They're gonna be so specific.
That's almost 80% of every single answer.
Name something that smells good.
What is a specific thing that smells good?
If I say a drink, does that include...
I'll say perfume, but I think...
I don't know if it's gonna be up there.
Cologne, perfume, right?
That was the other one I wanted to do.
Interesting answer.
The survey says...
Perfume.
Cologne, perfume.
Okay, yep.
So then what's the other one?
You're doing great.
Soap?
This is so exciting.
Okay, what about soap?
One uncovered answer up there.
I think soap could be it, probably.
Coffee, but I think coffee is gonna be food.
Soap.
Soap smells good.
Sure thing.
Fresh cookies.
Have you found the missing answer?
Let's find out.
Somebody said fresh cookies.
Soap.
All right, all right.
Ouch.
That's your second strike.
Put on your thinking cap.
It's time for an answer.
Coffee.
I'm gonna say coffee.
Good.
Okay.
Our survey says...
Coffee.
So what is it?
That's three.
This round is getting thrown over to the other side.
They're gonna say something stupid.
If they could find just one answer...
Watch, somebody's gonna say dog shit.
This baby will steal the board.
Here's your chance.
You can do it.
Answer accepted.
To me, that's candle.
To me, if candle is not that, then that's annoying.
Air freshener.
Yeah, that's annoying.
I was gonna say candle and air freshener are both in the same category.
So what is it?
We've got just one answer you missed.
Want to see number three?
I sure do.
People.
Before we start another round, let's find out who's on top.
The lead just got bigger.
If somebody asked me, hey, what smells...
What do you think smells good?
Just give me like if the first thing comes to your head.
People.
Nowhere near as painful as it sounds, it's the face-off.
How would that be?
How would that possibly be the first thing that you say?
How would that possibly be the first thing?
I can't imagine a world where that is remotely physically possible.
We're on the hunt for six answers.
Bacon, perfume, flowers.
Stakes are getting higher because we're now tripling the points.
We got 100 people to answer the following question.
Name someone in your life who usually does more talking than listening.
You got in first.
It's definitely it's like it's like it's...
We're gonna do mother-in-law.
This is like the answer, right?
This is like the answer.
What?
That's that's the answer.
Oh, my mother-in-law.
Understood.
Our survey says...
Neighbor.
Your neighbor?
Who?
Not up there.
Good try.
Do you have an answer for us?
I don't.
Okay.
But should it do...
But I don't know.
I don't know.
The fucking dentist.
The dentist like keeps talking, right?
Here we go.
Dentist never shuts up.
Let's run with it.
Dentist.
Oh, so sorry.
We were going for number six.
We weren't going for number one.
Let's move on.
I was going for number...
Listen.
I was going for number six.
I wasn't going for number one.
That was my other answer.
And what did our survey say?
We're not gonna be like do this.
No.
What happens?
We need an answer.
Okay.
How about this?
Like it's gonna be...
It's gonna be wife, husband, right?
That's gonna be two at least.
Okay, then.
Let's take a look.
Okay, right.
Okay, there we go.
But I don't know what else this could be then.
Now here's the million dollar question.
Who does more?
I know, pass Andy.
But still, what should I...
Do you...
I don't know.
What am I gonna do?
You won last time.
And now you run a roll.
Let's play this thing.
Okay.
Who else talks a lot?
Dig deep and think of an answer.
Okay.
Who talks a lot but doesn't really listen?
They talk a lot.
Like mom, parent, a teacher or a...
But a teacher is talking and it should not be interrupted
because they're talking.
They're doing a lesson.
I'm gonna say like mom, right?
By the way, I love my mother.
And this is not my mother.
Mom, answer.
What do you think?
No, I said mother-in-law.
It's different.
Okay, I'm gonna say teacher but I feel like that's kind of...
What did our survey say?
A kid?
A little kid?
Yeah.
Teacher.
Who does a lot of talking?
It isn't there.
But doesn't really listen.
No, but I knew that wasn't gonna be wrong.
Lawyer.
A politician.
That's a good one.
What answer do you have for us this time?
Doctor.
Oh, boss.
That's a great one.
Yeah, boss, boss, boss.
Okay.
That's a good one.
Do we have it?
Boss.
Two strikes.
Okay, that's weird.
Our other family need to get ready to steal.
Oh.
Doctor would be the other one I would think of.
I would say doctor.
You can do it.
What do you think?
Or politician.
It's gotta be politician.
It has to be.
Ah, yes.
Let's see if it's up there.
Or doctor.
Politician.
How is that not up there?
What would be up there besides the doctor?
I did teach her already.
We could be about to witness a steal.
What else would it be?
A sibling?
One answer will do it.
And they can steal the round.
Dig deep.
Give me a correct answer.
And you snatch these points from the other team.
Yes.
It's not going to be up there.
Sibling.
No.
Eight motherfuckers.
You know the score.
I still win.
And we got ourselves a winner.
We're good.
Are you ready to see the rest of the answers?
I'm actually very curious about this.
I really am.
Myself.
Okay.
How about the fourth answer?
Best friend.
What was the third answer?
Kids.
This kids, yep.
Here's what the scores look like after that round.
I'm still in the lead.
I think I won.
Do I win?
There's one more round.
It ain't over yet.
We need one more round to settle things.
I do talk a lot.
I do.
The winning team needs to hit 300 points.
It's time to decide this game.
All right.
Let's do it.
Let's play Sudden Death.
Someone from each family.
Get up here and play.
So this is it.
We just want the number one answer.
For this survey, we're asking for the top answer only.
Points are tripled.
Whoever gets this answer wins the round.
We've got answers from 100 people for this question.
Okay.
Name something in the house.
People turn on while doing chores.
Music.
What's your answer?
Thank you for the victory.
I appreciate it.
Are you sure about that?
Our survey said music.
It's not TV because you can listen to music in every room.
The TV is only in one spot.
Sorry, Coopers, but somebody's got to come in second.
All right.
Let's do Fast Money.
Fast Money.
And then we're going to go Pee.
We're going to come back.
Dealer no deal to the screen.
Are you ready to play Fast Money?
Let's go.
All right, my lonesome lovely.
Since you didn't bring anyone with you,
you're going to have to answer these questions.
I have to answer them twice.
So I don't have to go hide.
I'm going to ask you five survey questions in a limited time.
Okay.
Then I'll ask you the same questions again.
If you can score 200 points altogether,
you'll win the jackpot.
Let's start the clock.
Name something people love to do outside in the summer.
Swim.
Tell me something that is purposely sold with a hole in the middle of it.
Donut.
What's fun?
Name a sport in which you might fall off something.
Pass, pass, pass.
Come back to it.
Tell me something you associate with Canada.
Maple syrup.
Fine.
Maple leaf is fine.
Name a creature whose gender you're never sure of.
Pretty much all of them.
A frog?
Name a sport in which you might fall off something.
I don't know.
What do you fall off of?
Like a snowboard or something?
Snowboarding.
I don't know.
Snowboard.
We're all out of questions.
Okay.
You could like fall off the snowboard, right?
We're going to go again.
The same exact questions.
You need to answer the questions again,
but this time make sure you say something you haven't said already.
Your time begins now.
Name something people love to do outside in the summer.
Tan.
Tell me something that is purposely sold with a hole in the middle of it.
Bagel.
Name a sport in which you might fall off something.
Maybe like gymnastics?
You could like maybe
because they go up on the little horse thing, right?
Cycling is better.
Tell me something you associate with Canada.
Hockey.
Name a creature whose gender you're never sure of.
Fish.
I don't know.
Birds.
Um birds is better.
Oh, I did fish.
Okay.
You can relax now.
We're done.
Let's see how well you did.
All right.
Let's see.
I'm very curious.
For starters, we asked name something people love to do outside in the summer.
And here's what you said.
These answers are looking good.
I think those are perfect.
Yep.
We found the most popular one.
And for the next question,
tell me something that is purposely sold with a hole in the middle of it.
That's a great question.
You said you should feel confident.
Donut and bagel.
Yeah, it's gotta be it.
The number one answer number one and number 100.
All right.
For the third question, we asked name a sport in which you might fall off something.
The answers to this one.
Those answers look good.
Don't they?
Both of those answers got some points.
Horseback riding.
Oh, that was our top answer.
Next, we wanted to know.
Tell me something you associate with Canada.
This has got to put me on the edge here.
What do you say?
That's going to put me over maple leaf and hockey.
Come on.
That's got to be over 200.
It is almost.
All right.
Great job.
Come on.
It's 200.
For our last question.
I got a piece so bad.
Name a creature whose gender you're never sure of.
The answers you gave.
You pull this off and get 200 points.
You'll win the jackpot.
I got it.
Is yours.
Well played, everyone.
This is lucky McCoy.
I can feel so bad.
I'll be right back.
We're going to come back with a deal or no deal and I'm turning the stream off.
All right.
Goodbye.
I'll be right back.
The audio is coming out of my screen and I don't know how I like I unplugged it or something.
Okay.
So this monitor has speakers in it.
Give me one second while I figure this out.
Where are you?
Okay.
Deal or no deal coming up.
Shut up.
Shut this thing up.
All right.
Get that off.
I got to change my.
Ow.
Get this back here.
It's good.
Okay.
Cool.
It is.
Okay.
Very nice.
I got to turn this down because this is inaccurate.
Okay.
Let me just do this real quick.
I don't know how loud this is going to be but it's probably going to be horrible.
So just be careful.
Turn that off.
Turn this filter off because I don't need to delay my camera anymore.
Okay.
Looks good.
Does that look good?
How you doing?
Nice to see you.
Now we got to put this on here.
Be careful.
This might be loud.
I'm just saying.
There's no audio at all.
I don't hear anything either.
Is there no audio?
I thought there was.
Okay.
Well, here we go.
That's not accurate.
Hey, there we go.
All right.
So if you don't let me move my camera, where can I go?
This is fine up here.
Oh, it's fine.
You know what's over here.
All right.
So deal or no deal, I have to pick a case.
After I pick a case, I go from here and I've got to hold that case until the end of the game.
Is there no game audio?
All right.
I'm going to pick number one.
Is there no audio?
Maybe there is no fucking audio.
Yeah, there's supposed to be.
Oh, there we go.
Did it work?
Can you hear it now?
All right.
That's my case and I have to pick six cases.
There we go.
Excellent.
Oh, okay.
I'm going to take four.
Why is it doing this?
Is it doing it for you too?
It's so horrible sounding.
Do you hear that?
Is that just for me?
It sounds like crunching, crackling audio.
I don't know why.
All right.
Twelve.
Nice one.
That's better.
It's still wicked loud.
Are you playing this on new ground?
Dude, this game only exists in two places.
This game is just slot machines or random fucking flash games.
This game does not exist anywhere else.
All right.
We're going with ten.
Five thousand.
That's not bad.
What do you guys think?
Chat's choice.
It's on the Wii six.
Oh, five dollars.
Nice pick.
Excellent pick.
Really good pick.
Let's go with two.
Seventy five.
That's another good one.
Wait, counter offer?
I got a counter offer for you.
Hey, how about you give me a fucking easy four hundred K and I'll leave.
All right.
Five.
Oh, come on.
Get out of here.
Eight.
Seven fifty still in play.
We're good.
By the way, who cares?
There's no stakes in this at all.
There are no stakes in what I'm doing.
So who cares?
It doesn't really matter.
Why am I pretending that there's stakes?
All right.
Thousand.
Seven.
We need.
It's the same offer.
No.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
Nine.
Shit.
Twenty two.
Nice one.
All right.
Not bad.
Oh, you guys have stakes.
That's kind of cool.
You guys get to have stakes.
That's pretty awesome.
Twenty.
Nice one.
Will I win two hundred fifty K or more?
Excellent.
Oh, all right.
Deal or no deal.
Fifty three K.
I mean, the dollar is still in play.
That's a no deal.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
Eleven.
Excellent.
Good.
Twenty one.
Excellent.
Good.
Twenty six.
Excellent.
Deal or no deal.
Ah, this could this could be a good one.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
If I get rid of that one and that twenty five, then this is this is a GG.
Thirteen.
Nice one.
I'm going to wait till you guys bet.
Okay.
Now it's sealed.
Oh, man.
Congratulations.
Or no deal.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
Twenty five.
Excellent.
Oh, boy.
Deal or no deal.
Okay.
So there is a one one in five chance that I have the seven fifty.
But there's also a one in five chance that I have the ten thousand as well.
You don't give me a chance to fucking think just hang the phone.
All right.
Eighteen.
Nice one.
Good deal or no no deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
If I get rid of the ten K, that's big.
Removing the ten K guarantees that the people that bet against me lose.
So we're going to go for it.
Fourteen.
Excellent.
Oh, deal or no deal.
Oh, very brave.
Time for the next.
There's a one in three chance that this is over a hundred thousand.
No deal.
Very brave.
Time for the next round.
I'm keeping my case.
Oh, fuck off.
Why is it broken?
Do you hear how fucking loud this is for me?
All right.
Again, let's do it again.
Do it again.
Will I win more than two hundred and fifty dollars in deal or no deal?
I'm going to wait because I don't want to.
I want you guys to be able to put your bets in before I do anything.
This the game's not a virus, dude.
It's on it's on MSN.
It's on MSN.com.
It's not a fucking virus.
Okay.
But get your bets in because we're going to close it.
Well, I can pick the case I want, right?
Okay.
The case I'm going to take is twenty, twenty.
You should do stuff with the debt.
I don't even know what the debt is at right now.
That joke like sailed over me from like the last two years.
All right.
How are we looking?
We good?
Can I start picking cases?
My grandfather uses MSN.
Yeah, I know.
All right.
Lock it in.
Good luck to whoever's betting their channel points.
And here we.
All right.
Good start.
Let's give it a one this time because I picked it last time.
Very good picks.
Very, very good picks.
Twenty six.
Not very good, but all right.
Nineteen.
Oh, my God.
I owe like a hundred and fifty community subs from like fucking two months ago.
Oops.
Oh, that's bad.
That's really bad.
Come on, dude.
Oh, there's so much at stake.
That was probably really loud.
I'm really sorry.
Was it loud?
That was probably incredibly loud.
Deal or no deal?
Was that really loud?
I'm really sorry.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
Three.
Excellent.
There's still a chance.
There is.
Just got to get rid of a lot of these low numbers and that's it.
Get rid of the one cent.
Does anybody else think that this show should have started at a thousand?
Because if you're on a game show and you leave with a check for one cent,
that kind of feels so rotten.
That's just so evil.
I think it should start at a thousand and go one, two, three, four, five.
Then like ten, twelve, fifteen.
You know what I mean?
Starting it at one cent.
That feels fucking evil.
Or yeah, or start at twenty five.
Very brave.
Time for the next round.
That's the point of the game.
Yeah, but it's still, I mean, a one cent.
Nice one.
That's not a nice one.
That's bad because I need to get rid of these small numbers.
I need to get one dollar.
Excellent.
Good.
I'll take a crisp twenty five dollar bill right now.
Oh no, you took a crisp twenty five.
That means a twenty and a five.
Okay.
Excellent.
Good.
All the doubters, I think you might be in some trouble.
Nice one.
Deal or no.
Very brave.
Time for the next round.
Oh, it's over.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, everybody.
Nice one.
It might not be over.
If I have the three hundred K, then it's fine.
Nice one.
All right.
Hold on.
Deal or no.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
It's all right.
The three hundred K is in play still.
Nice one.
This is still possible.
Or no.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
Nice one.
All right.
Deal.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
Nice one.
Okay.
Deal or no.
It's going to be three hundred K or one cent.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
Nice one.
Oh my God.
Deal or no deal.
I mean, you almost kind of have to take this.
Very brave.
Time for the next round.
Nice one.
All right.
Okay.
Deal or no deal.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
This is it.
It's either in my case or it's not.
And if it's in my case, then the believers win.
I'm sorry.
I had faith.
I believed in my case.
I'm sorry, guys.
I'm sorry.
Let's do it again.
Let's do this one more time.
And then I'm probably going to go.
All right.
I'm going to pick.
Let's go with two.
All right.
Get your bets in if you want to bet.
Will I get over 250k?
Which is actually that's a hard bet.
It's way more probable that I will get under 200k.
That's a risk.
Where's the gamble?
It's going on right now.
You got about 15 more seconds.
Why do I feel like you've done this exact stream before?
I played a lot of the game show stuff.
Yeah.
Some of the other versions.
This like 15 versions of all these games.
I don't think have I done millionaire?
I've done an old version of millionaire.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's fine.
This is fun.
Just chilling playing these.
I'm just stupid.
Some of them are.
It's fun.
I come back to these game shows times then.
There's no gamble.
Yes, there is.
It says predict right now with channel points.
I can see it.
You played this exact one before.
There's no betting.
Oh, how come it says predict with channel points?
Oh, how do I do it?
Slash predict prediction.
Okay.
So slash prediction.
Start a prediction.
Okay.
Will I win 250,000 or more?
Yes or no.
And the submission panel is two minutes.
Like that.
Did I do it?
Does it, did that work?
Okay, cool.
I got it.
Two minutes is too long.
I think I can just, I can shorten it.
So what, do I have to press a button?
I can end it early.
Oh, do I hit the predict button?
You guys are going all in?
Oh, be careful.
Okay.
You ready?
I'm going for it in 10 seconds.
Here we go.
I'm going in.
Predict.
Did it work?
Did I do it?
All right.
Here we go.
No.
All right.
We got to wait like 25 seconds.
Don't let us down.
This is the last one we're doing anyways.
This is it.
If you want to bet, this is the last time I'm doing this.
And then I'm going to bed.
What time is it?
It's way too early to go to bed.
30 seconds.
If you want to bet, this is the final one.
Swap at the end.
I will make that decision at the end if I get there.
All right.
This is it.
Good luck.
Three, two, one.
Here we go.
Good start.
Not great.
26.
That's all right.
As long as these three stay, we're fine.
12.
What the fuck?
Oh, very brave.
All right.
Four.
What the fuck, dude?
Come on.
This is getting bad.
Statistically, these should stay for a while though.
Statistically speaking.
Good.
18.
It's okay.
Deal or no deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
10.
Good.
Give her the one cent.
Eight.
Good.
All right.
This is starting to shape up a little bit.
Nine.
Okay.
This offer is getting bigger.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
Uh-oh.
The million's still there.
Million's still there.
Nobody freak out.
Okay.
Good.
15.
Very good.
No deal.
Very brave.
Time for the next round.
You ready?
20.
Excellent.
That's all right.
As long as we get rid of 10,
then it's possible that I can take a deal that's over 250,000.
Ow.
The next round.
Okay.
We're almost at 200k.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Get rid of the 10.
Get rid of the 10 and I win.
Oh, okay.
236.
250.
It's not 250.
What if I counter offer?
I did it.
I got over.
I got 250,000.
I just got 250,000 dollars.
I just won.
There it is.
That's cheating.
How is that cheating?
It's a gameplay mechanic.
That's a built-in gameplay mechanic.
Ow, my ears.
I guess I'll...
Okay.
You want it again?
That counts.
That's a part of the game.
You knew that was part of the game.
Rip to the all-ins.
Well, guess what?
We're doing it one more time.
I'm getting another chance.
You get another chance.
It just said, will he get over 250,000?
It didn't say how I was going to get to 250,000.
Oh, I have to pay you out.
How do I do that?
How do I pay?
Mods?
Mods, how do I pay?
All right, let's do one more.
This is it.
I'm going to pick my case.
I'm going to pick 10.
This is the final one of the night.
After this, I'm literally leaving.
I'm turning the stream off.
Thank you for the raid, by the way, Prezzo.
Appreciate it.
Thanks, everybody.
Welcome.
What's going on?
Good to see you.
POG, POG, POG, POG, POG.
What are you guys saying?
What is it?
200, yeah, 250K again.
I feel like that's a good enough risk
because tons of people are betting against that.
But I mean, statistically speaking,
it's hard to get over 250, but yes,
that's the gamble you're willing to take.
That's the risk you're taking.
Put your camera over your case.
That's a very weird request, but okay.
Why is this such a big deal?
All right, let's close it up in 10 seconds.
I picked 10.
Why is that so funny?
It's not.
Why is this funny?
Why is it so?
It's not even funny.
It's not funny.
Why is this funny?
Pretend like you're the case when you get opened.
Why is this not funny?
I'm just on 10.
All right, let's go.
I'm ready to pick the first case.
There's a little pixel to your left.
I'll fix it.
All right, you ready?
Here I go.
Bets are locked.
Three, two, one.
Good.
Go to that one, man.
Nice.
I told you.
Go try that one.
I would say try that one.
Okay.
14 sounds like it's going to pay out.
You guys can't even see the number.
Two.
This is a big one.
You guys can't see the numbers.
This is stupid.
I'm literally moving.
Okay, seven.
What was it?
It's 300k.
Get me the fuck out of here.
That was funny for five seconds.
No deal.
Time for the next round.
Nice one.
All right, not bad.
Excellent.
50k.
Okay, that's not great, but whatever.
Three.
10k.
Four.
Put it over the lady's face.
No deal.
That was 500k.
Fuck.
Very brave.
Time for the next round.
Five.
Oh, bad.
Very bad.
That's a million.
Oh, you guys are in trouble now.
Actually in trouble.
750 still in it.
Nice one.
Okay.
Excellent.
That's good.
Good numbers to come up with.
How about 11?
Excellent.
Deal or no deal.
That's pretty good.
Very brave.
Time for the next round.
21.
Nice one.
One cent gone.
20.
Get rid of the dollar.
Excellent.
Okay, getting interesting.
22.
Excellent.
Deal or no deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
26.
No, 25.
Nice one.
23.
Oh, shit.
Deal or no deal.
We're getting there.
It's getting close.
Time for the next round.
Excellent.
Uh oh.
Deal or no deal.
That's 168.
I need a 250 deal.
Oh, very brave.
Time for the next round.
Nice one.
Oh, shit.
Deal or no deal.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Okay.
Time for the next round.
It's a 50-50 chance that pretty much I win or lose.
Whatever.
Get rid of the 50.
Excellent.
Oh, this could be it.
That's it.
Or no deal.
But do I take the deal?
This is on, this is up to me.
I, this is up to me.
Do I take the 750 in the potential?
I didn't have a chance to do anything.
What?
What's going on?
What just happened?
Why do they do that?
Why do they, I don't know why they do that.
That's fucking annoying.
I couldn't even think about it for less than 10 seconds.
But that's like kind of fucking bullshit, don't you think?
No deal.
$50.
Always pick the other case, right?
I just screwed over everybody.
We'll do it again.
One more time and I'm going to speed run it.
You already experienced the timer.
I have the memory of a fucking goldfish, man.
All right, I have no more money.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think it was going to kick me out.
But I wasn't sure if I was going to take it.
But I was going for big bucks, not little.
You should have taken the deal.
I was thinking about it, but I didn't.
All right.
This is the last one.
I'm going to speed run it.
If you want to bet, bet.
Yeah, time to bet.
You get 10 seconds.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
And that's a zero.
And close it.
I'm picking number one again.
You ready?
Let's go.
Nice one.
Good.
Low numbers.
Oh, boy.
Excellent.
Not bad.
Low numbers.
Good.
That's a high number.
Low numbers.
Oh, very brave.
Time for the next round.
Nice one.
750 still there.
Low number.
Low numbers.
Good.
Excellent.
That's not a low number.
That's a medium number, and I don't like to see that.
Excellent.
There are so many of these.
Deal or no deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
Excellent.
100k.
That's a big number.
Low numbers only.
I don't know what to say.
Sorry.
It's still possible.
Excellent.
Okay.
Low number.
Nice one.
Good.
Deal.
No deal.
Oh, very brave.
Time for the next round.
It's not looking good.
Nice one.
Is it still possible?
Of course it is, but is it probable?
Not really.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
Nice one.
It goes one cent.
Excellent.
All right.
Deal.
Oh, very brave.
Time for the next round.
Excellent.
Okay.
Deal.
205.
We're almost there.
No deal.
That's the spirit.
Time for the next round.
Nice one.
Deal or no deal.
I'm going to take it.
I take the deal.
I win.
I would have kept my case, by the way,
just to make sure you understand.
I would have kept my case to the end.
I was going to keep my case.
Which means I would have won anyways.
So all the people that are freaking out
right now in the chat room,
I'm sorry to tell you,
but I would have won anyways.
I was going to keep my case.
I wasn't going to swap it.
All right.
That's it.
I'll see you guys later.
Thanks for watching.
As always, have a great rest of your evening.
It's always fun.
The next time you will see me will be,
let's say Wednesday.
Wednesday the 1st.
I'm going to keep it at 3 p.m.
Then I'm going to tell you why.
I usually start streaming at 4 o'clock Pacific.
But when I say I'm going to stream at 4 o'clock,
I always show up at like 4 30.
And I'm actually ready to stream at 4 30, 4 15.
So if I say I'm going to stream at 3,
that means that I have to be here
and I'll turn the stream on at like 3 30.
Right.
So that makes sense to make it that way.
I don't know what we're going to do,
but I know I have a lot of options.
I got a lot of things on my steam list
that I want to play.
I don't know my voice.
My voice has been getting just junk
after like four or five hours.
I don't know why.
What is this?
No, this is like my like Firefox web page.
You see like the hotels.com.
You want to go to hotels.com?
Cover your body in honey.
You need to show your YouTube history.
I'm not showing my YouTube history.
Solve the riddle.
Can you solve Albert Einstein's famous?
Okay.
Let's see if I can do it.
Why am I so stretched?
What's the famous house riddle?
Let's find out.
Why am I so stretched?
Okay.
All right.
And these.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let's see.
The Englishman lives in the house with red walls.
The Swede keeps dogs.
The Dane drinks tea.
The house with green walls
is just to the left of the house with white.
I don't care.
Like you do it.
I don't want to do it.
Thanks for watching.
I thought it was going to be a simple thing.
It's like a 15 step riddle.
I'm not doing it.
Thanks for watching.
See you guys Wednesday at three o'clock Pacific ish.
Got a lot of shit to play.
You know, in pre stream, we'll do a poll.
Thanks for the subs.
There were actually.
Let me see.
Yeah, I don't like to talk about like resubs or new subs or whatever,
but I do appreciate it.
Thanks guys.
Maybe we'll see you again.
I feel like I'm going to have a lot of stuff to talk about really soon.
So there should be some really interesting things we can go over.
I'll have some green screen updates for you this week coming up.
I will also have some grotto beast updates for you this coming week.
Give you some more info on that project.
July 14th that is still set in stone for the baseball stream.
So there's some things to talk about.
Should be cool.
Oh, that's a POG.
That's a POG.
But yeah, thanks for the subs, everybody.
Good night.
Goodbye.
Have a wonderful day or wonderful night.
Also, happy Memorial Day.
That's currently right now, Eastern time, right?
Take care of yourselves.
Stay safe.
Call your mother.
See you guys later.