It's just it's just showing us the scenery. Yeah, why is it? It's just okay. Here we go. Oh god
It's so loud. Why is it so loud? I know why did it like real out and no you're wicked loud again
You are so loud. I guess I'm ready
Let me try and change my volume again
This is the loudest game ever. Oh my god. I'm driving. Are you driving? I'm in the common your car. Are you behind me? Yeah
What's going on?
Let's go
We're taking the secret highway route
But everything is so loud
You are so loud
You are so loud right now
I'm sorry
Your microphone is so fucked
Hey look at this car
Look at this
You can't control this
What is the objective?
I'm passing out
I'm passing out dude
Hold on a second
Oh my god
Do we get out?
No don't get out
I can't I got out
No I'm driving
We win
We're the team player both of us got the team player away
What the fuck is this game?
Hold on I'm not ready
I'm not ready I need to fix this audio
My mic says it's back down to like 20
Options
Audio, jeez
Bring the mast of all down
I'm driving
Watch out there's guys behind us
How do I drive this car
Drives like a piece of shit
Yeah it does a little bit
Why do you get arrows pointing?
Why do I get the GPS?
I'm getting out
This is the hardest I've laughed in a long time
Oh my god
I'm just watching some guy drive his car
This is the best thing ever
How's this guy doing? He looks like he's well in the life
He's just like looking at me just beeping
What just happened?
He had a blue light expression
I'm just getting out
It has to be VIP
He's alive
VIP's alive
That makes no sense
Come here Jerma
What's with his foot?
He's squashed in there
Oh my god
Watch out
This game
I can't take it anymore I gotta get out of here
Wait what the hell what's your name in here Jerma
You stole his car
Like five people just
Gunned him down like surrounded him
And just started firing
Alright I'm driving I'm going fast
I got the need for speed
Get out of the car
There's two of the same guy holding their feet on the car
On the dash I'm stuck in this
Get me the
Behind you
There's two of the same guy with the feet
On the dash
Same guy
I seriously am passing out
You see the spoiler on the back of that car
I'm too busy blacking out
It just threw us into this game
Seriously we were at the ready screen
It got wicked loud
That was just too much
Too much stimulation
Of the brain