All right, let's go.
Okay. All right. Welcome to.
Welcome, everybody.
Welcome to filter myth. A tale of dragons and danger.
And guess what? I'm like five minutes early.
It said somewhere around 12 to one.
Let's go. Here we are.
Hi, everybody.
How do you got a character in mind?
Do we have like a whole race selection?
I don't know.
We're going to make our character.
Your character is important.
We can either randomize our characters,
but I think it might be better if we make them.
I think that's fun.
Oh, I got to tweet this too.
Okay. We got a couple options here.
We have the age of old tricks.
I think we should do that.
That's like the standard campaign.
Let's go with that.
Sounds good.
How do you spell this?
Wilder.
Is it not on the top left of your screen right now?
Yeah, dude, I'm looking down at my phone and I'm like,
how do you spell it?
Oh, there it is.
Okay. Wilder myth sounds fun.
Okay, let's go.
Okay. Right.
So you guys should, you guys see the screen right now?
Yes.
Okay. So we're going to allocate one, two, three.
You guys are now in control of your characters.
So you want to, you can click them
and you can start customizing.
Oh, okay.
So the top left.
I clicked randomize once and I'm happy.
Okay. So the top left, you can scroll along
and you can kind of like auto people.
And then you've got like the bottom left is the most important
and this is probably why you don't want to randomize stuff
is because you need to customize your like aspects.
His name is Alunga and it looks like me.
Like I'm done.
I don't even have a chat.
Okay. You don't want to customize
like any aspect of his personality.
You happy with him?
Oh, okay. There's a whole, there's a huge thing here.
Okay.
Yeah. So the bit you're going to, you can,
if you want to write a backstory, you can.
That normally the randomly generated ones are pretty funny.
Okay.
And then the biggest thing is you go to history
and you can pick like three traits.
So you can pick like, you know, potential library and brash.
So this is pretty detailed then.
Yeah. And like picking all this stuff will determine
like it will determine like your character interactions,
how he behaves, what might happen to him,
the decisions he'll make all that stuff.
Is there, where does your class come in?
Like that comes in later.
So essentially this is a RPG DND AI roguelike
that we're going to be playing and it's in the same realm.
Yeah.
I just turned my stream on and I haven't been talking so.
Yeah. Relationship simulator.
Okay.
So there will be combat.
It'll be kind of like tactics based.
If you've played like a Final Fantasy tactics or game like that,
it's like, it'll be like a top down, like hex board.
And then the combat's pretty fun.
But between the combat will be long periods of story
and what we'll do is we'll voice our own characters
and the AI will generate our dialogue and our.
Really?
And what happens.
Yeah.
Why have I never heard of this game?
That sounds, that sounds, this sounds amazing.
It's such a charming game, but like not many people have heard.
Okay.
Yeah. I kind of forgot about it.
I'm like a youth.
Yeah.
Currently locked in.
So if right now we've got Starr is the hunter
and Gemma is the mystic.
Wait, where am I?
I am the warrior.
See where it says at the top, future warrior, hunter and mystic.
Where do you change that?
If you don't want to be a hunter.
I don't know if you can change it.
I'm cool with being the mage.
That's cool with me.
If you want to be the warrior though so we can swap.
Oh, no, I think it just gives you one of each
and then we can assign them.
Is there a hair, a hair color?
Normally we can pick them, but this is like the base campaign.
So it's kind of like.
Oh, okay.
So this is a tutorial too.
So we like locked in.
All right.
I think, I think that's wait.
Should I have a beard or something?
All right.
That's good.
No, that's good.
I did my history.
What did you guys do for your history?
Can you write it?
Yeah, you can if you want.
Oh, no, I was talking about the like the three drop downs.
Yeah, I'm going to do destiny, shame, but also.
I did dreamer, clown and nostalgic.
That yeah, that sounds like you.
I thought you said streamer.
Streamer.
Oh, shit.
All right.
I think so is the names are here.
Yeah, I'm excited.
This is going to be fun.
Is there any other customizations?
We should.
Jesus, are there any other customers?
The way they said that, like, oh my goodness.
Are there any other customizations that we can do?
I think you get more if we.
This is like just the first campaign to kind of show you the ropes.
Oh, we can do hair color and everything like that.
Yeah, you can do hair color and all that kind of stuff.
The main thing is the three the three aspects in history is like important.
And then if you got to customize, you've got like size, color,
head and face and then your name.
Man, if you could do character creator before you were born,
how long would you spend in it?
Days.
That sounds like weird.
Wait, would you just hit the randomize button?
No, I just named my character Smushman, but it was just like, I don't know.
I already have that character name.
Nine months.
Yeah, you got nine months of character creation.
Yeah, that's true.
What if like you had nine months and then like you were one day
from the nine month limit and you accidentally hit like randomize
and everything, all your hard work was just like undone, like bam.
Oh, I forgot to save.
Oh, that's not good.
I'm just going to get born like that name in dogwood details.
OK, all right.
Well, this is just a trial run we're doing, right?
Yeah. Yeah, let's go.
No, this is literally who you will be for the rest of your life.
OK, let's go.
Welcome to Wildermyth.
OK, so the best way to do this is like one person will kind of be in control of
when we go to the next slide.
OK.
If either of you want to be that guy or you just want me to do it and then
kind of read along.
I'm not ready for that responsibility.
I think somebody should be like the bookkeeper.
I'll be the guy.
If you guys click read along with leader, that checkbox,
then it will bring you with me.
Perfect.
Oh, we have our own little mouses.
Yeah.
So did you see the change page?
Yep.
OK, there's room in it for another story.
It's cold.
I'm stuck here.
Oh, this is you.
Oh, OK.
So you got to read it.
I am.
I'm trying to think of what I do for a voice for this person.
OK, like get in character.
Deep breath.
Have a feel for yourself.
Figure out what you want to sound like.
The audio.
How do I turn the audio down?
All right.
That's one thing he doesn't know.
Anything.
Should it be like a...
OK.
Just make it you.
Just be you.
Anything to prove I lived, I guess.
Not that.
Not that I'm giving up.
Someone will come.
Maybe my friends.
It's still you.
Oh, I thought this was the narrator.
But all right.
This is how I'd started here in my yandering country.
Something in the woods is very strange.
I don't have any lines.
A line?
Concerned only with the depth and echo of his own thoughts,
a young man named Inan takes the seasonal road to the town of Thunderost.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
His whole character introduction is...
There's something going on in the woods.
Yeah.
OK.
There's a timeless problem.
The stone in the shoe.
When should one bend and remove it?
When is it finally time?
Where's that threshold between discomfort and laziness?
I could write a treatise, probably.
Breeze is light that day.
Birds are timid.
In fact, the whole world is taking a breath, ready to leap in the sea.
I'm there already, huh?
Here's the hard part.
Getting a longus out of bed.
Or worse, if I have to dislodge him from a book or smoke.
Fluttering flames roost among the far-off rooftops.
Inan hurries towards town, thinking of a longus,
a young man whom he's known since boyhood.
OK, so now I can choose...
Wait, you have to choose this?
Yeah.
I can choose to increase my rivalry, my friendship, or some romance.
Let's do friendship.
If we've known each other all our lives, I doubt we'd be rivals.
He must have tried to cook breakfast again.
There we go.
A longus!
You all right?
I'll get you out and just make a little noise.
OK.
Wait, what?
So it looks like my introduction is a burning village,
and I'm going to be in a solo combat situation looking for a longus.
So who is a longus?
Is that you, Ster?
That's me.
That's Ster.
So the game has decided that we are childhood friends, just randomly.
OK.
So now you can kind of get a feel for, like, the combat.
This is kind of the combat map, and it's all time-based,
and we all act at the same time, and then the enemies act at the same time.
Oh, so it should go pretty quick.
So this is a longus' house?
Yeah, look.
His house is still standing, at least.
A longus!
Fire right here.
You're not sleeping, are you?
What's going on here?
This is me, a longus.
He doesn't know.
Why is no one?
Hey, do you not smell the...
I smell the smoke.
Get inside.
Yeah, my bow.
The blaze is secondary.
It's doom's detail.
A herd of these hideous, afflicted-looking beasts.
Garoo!
They stampeded in.
I managed to trap one behind the house.
Small victory.
Staying in here is not really an option.
Right, so.
Here, I've got some tools around.
You're stronger than I am.
You can swing something pretty good.
I bet we can at least drive it off.
Okay, do I grab the pitchfork, the pickaxe, or the frying pan?
I'm going pickaxe here.
If it breaks stars, it'll break bones.
It can be killed, right?
If we're steady and methodical, we can manage it.
Steady and methodical beating of an animal.
Let's get it done.
I hope it just cuts to me and I've been eaten.
Our first enemy is a roe.
It looks like it's just a deer.
And we're going out the back of the house.
So that's the end of my turn.
I'm out of actions.
You should be in control of your character right now.
Okay, I will get behind you.
Okay.
With my bow.
I'm going to open the door and head out.
Enemy revealed.
Bow card.
That's my turn.
You have a shot?
Nope.
Your come out is going to be really interesting, because you're a wizard.
What you can do is you can like basically like you click on it.
Why did he go in the house?
Get out of my house.
Wait, what?
I'm going to strike it.
Oh, it's over there.
Where am I?
Holy shit.
You're so strong.
To get the AI has written out of our story already.
Okay, I leveled up so I can choose one of these three abilities.
That seems cool.
You're leveling up and you're in your room like, oh, I live near the forest.
Yeah, I looked out my window.
That's my whole story arc.
You leveled up as well?
With my level.
Everyone's saying you guys gave me the unplugged controller.
You're playing, dude.
Trust me, you're playing.
Oh, it's not my turn.
Okay.
Did you see that thing?
What could have wrought such a change?
Why did it go in my house?
The creature's death is quiet.
It seems to slip from life in a few stunned and hazy blinks.
Spend a piece of the day getting the flames under control.
The damage isn't as bad as it could have been.
Townsfolk emerge from hiding to fight fires and clear debris.
Some full of curiosity.
Others visibly haunted by what they've seen.
Geez.
We should go.
Thomas is alone.
Unless you think, I mean, I'm not sure who's safer suddenly.
Who the hell is Thomas?
It's like that kid that just sits in his window.
This is you, man.
I changed the line.
Oh, okay.
Oh, he did a little bit of improv.
Let's start one out.
Thomas will be waiting for us.
What happened today could be happening everywhere, couldn't it?
Something about that tower is just stuck in my mind.
It's like when you get an apple skin in your teeth.
Oh, some of these.
It unchecked the read-along with leader, I think.
Okay.
Are you caught up?
I know the sensation you describe.
Huh?
Yeah.
Anyway, I just think we said we'd meet him, so we should.
The towers and the hills.
You've been there?
Yeah, once.
Actually looking at the tracks, they come and they go.
That direction.
Oh, no.
And on and along us follow the pounded path of the monstrous feet,
hoping for the best and dreading every other possibility.
Okay, this is your choice here.
How do you tell who's choosing?
Your character is front and center, so it's related to you.
If you have a rivalry with Thomas, a friendship, or maybe a romance.
A romance.
Okay.
A worthless while passes between them, but the quiet only heightens their worry.
You've always been a little fond of him, I thought.
Of Thomas.
What have I?
You've noticed.
Is that true?
I do find he's grown on me.
Always kind of looking for an angle, a way to get ahead.
He's not mean.
There's just kind of this unapologetic self-interest with him.
That makes me laugh.
And plus, it seems like no matter where he goes, we tend to have adventures.
All right.
Okay.
So now our next mission is to find Thomas at the tower.
It's kind of explained to us that the way we do this is we're going to scout the next area.
And then it takes some travel time.
And then sometimes we can be intercepted on the way,
but most of the time we'll just travel there.
And then we reveal and trigger the next kind of chapter.
He's not there.
He said he'd be here on time.
Previous night.
Eh?
The tower where Thomas had arranged to meet Inanna and along us
is a place he often used to escape to as a boy.
He knows its rooms and floors so well.
He could survive being chased through them.
And now I wait, I suppose.
The dust gets deep as rain puddles in here.
Alive is alive until that beast breaks through.
You're a rare beast.
Folks would pay to see you.
I'd pay not to.
The tower is an heirloom of an earlier people.
The locals have lost the legend of it.
The emptiness is deep and fragrant.
The odor of 10,000 rains soaked into the stone.
But as the old will tell you,
precious things go overlooked in a ruin.
But lodges amid the bones of failure
is often the dream that drove it.
What's this over here?
That book.
Why have I never?
Easy there.
I guess you're wondering why I'm talking to myself,
beast.
I'm also wondering too.
Thomas bends down.
Don't, it's me doing that.
The books, I was gasping as the audience.
The book's heavier than its slender spine suggests.
It's the game.
It's gone meta.
Look at this.
It's full of strange stories.
It's you.
No, no, no.
You can, you want to narrate this.
Go on.
Go ahead.
Oh, I thought I was reading it.
But no, I, yeah.
Anyone can narrate.
All right.
It's full of strange stories.
The folklore of folk long forgotten.
Candlelight leaping strikes no significant bell.
It's the weird story of a child watching candlelight
against the ceiling and wishing himself through it
to a far realm without grownups.
Wait, why, how old am I?
What?
Why am I reading this book?
Why do I have this?
Maybe you just, maybe you're an adult
and you just want to go where there's no other grownups.
Gift of the Inscriptor proposes an unlikely legend
that one spider-limbed woman crafted all written language.
She trapped ants between vellum and pressed them so long
and relentlessly that they became letters.
Mama Thunder Roast's horn spins the yarn of a mother
who drank so much and laughed so freely
that she grew a beautiful spiral horn.
Her children were very proud.
Huh?
I did that.
This book.
What's happening with this?
There's room in it for another story.
I'm stuck here.
But all right, this is how I'd start it.
Here in my yondering country.
Thomas writes, words are ready.
Omens have formed in the fabric of everything
and he's beginning to recognize them now.
Okay.
Some are just misgivings.
They've crept through his body
like the sourceless aches one wakes with.
Others are more substantial.
Now they seem lightning plain, a promise of thunder.
Somebody just called me a theater kid and it made me mad.
Hold on.
Time that person up for five minutes.
From the wild black woods where birds once belled,
a hateful silence churns.
Pain lights Thomas's head.
What?
Oh, I'm fired.
I made it.
He lowers his bleary eyes.
His story lies before him in luminous script.
Empty pages have sprouted behind it.
Why do I feel powerful?
Okay. What do you do?
I pull out a spoon.
Open wide, beast.
I'm getting out of here.
All right.
So this is a, you're fighting a rager.
This is going to be a solo combat for you.
Okay.
It charges without seeing.
And you've got actions.
I believe you can still cast spells as a wizard with a spoon.
Oh, that's right.
I'm a wizard.
Okay.
Where is this beast?
So you have to see him for him to appear.
I don't know.
Oh wait, attack scenery?
Yeah. So what you want to, so what you can do as a wizard
is you can basically imbue a piece of scenery with a spell
and then the following turn,
you can throw the thing you imbued at the beast.
So if you imbued a table or a fireplace,
you could throw a flame at the beast on the next turn.
Oh, okay.
So I could.
So you can see how there's like a link
that's attaching you to that scenery now.
Yep.
So you could probably spend your second action moving,
try and get, get eyes on this beast.
Yeah, there you go.
Here it is.
Okay. Now I'm gonna.
Yeah, grab it.
Okay. Wait, I'm throwing the fireplace?
You're going to be throwing the flames.
Oh, fireplace.
I can't reach.
All right. I'm just going to move.
I mean, this time you can just, you can move
or you can just end turn and you can let him approach.
Yeah. I'm going to get up here.
All right. There you are.
All right. Now let's, let's discuss that.
I'm wondering if.
Yeah, I have no idea.
Oh, okay. So it has to be within these tiles.
Yeah.
So I think I could just, how do I get over to the beast?
I think it's trying to get you to throw the bookcase at it
or something.
Can you, you can't target it.
Can you through the rubble?
I don't think so.
Maybe it's just end turn.
Well, yeah, maybe in turn and see how he approaches.
All right. He's trying to break through.
Yeah. Can you imbue the,
maybe you can imbue the rubble in front of you.
I think I just, can I burn this?
I just stole the fire.
Possibly.
Let me see if I can burn it.
Okay. Fire, steel fire.
Oh, maybe if you infuse something on his side,
like the bookshelf.
I can't target anything across this.
Should I start breaking shit?
Yeah. Just start breaking shit.
He's going out the door. I think.
All right. Hold on.
Break the rubble behind you maybe,
or infuse it and then throw it.
What does withdraw?
Stop. Okay. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
I'm going to stop using this and let's, ah, here we go.
All right. I'm going to use the paper's table back here.
There it is.
Oh, good idea.
Then splinter blast him with it.
Yeah. Splinter blast. There you go.
All right. I get it. Let's go.
Oh, nice. Okay.
The same deal.
Down again. Same deal. Infuse something nearby.
Candles. And I'm going to,
oh, let's just light the room up.
Okay. I guess I'm done.
I guess I've lit the fire.
That's cozy.
Okay. Now if I can blow up,
I'm going to blow up the bookcase.
There we go. All right. See you later.
Look at that. Nice.
Okay. And Thomas, I think Thomas is going to level up.
There we go.
Ooh.
You can choose from these three abilities.
And so read through them,
see which one kind of you like the look of.
Elementalist, ignite or open mind.
Thomas can interfuse with one additional target.
That means you can link two targets at once.
Instead of just like the bookshelf,
you could do a bookshelf and a table.
I don't know.
Elementalist, what that kind of does
is it improves the things you interact with.
So if you interact with fire, it won't burn out.
If you interact with wood,
you get something called splinter salvo,
which is like a better version of what you just did.
I think, I think open mind.
I like having, I want to infuse with more stuff.
Cool. All right.
Ooh. And I got a, you got a amulet there,
a strap of golden links.
Everyone knows who's winning.
When you show up wearing this, it gives you bonus damage.
So you can just click your empty slot
and you can equip that.
Oh, nice. All right. Cool.
0.7 bonus damage.
This is pretty neat. I like this.
This is fun.
More monsters roam the battle halls
and rattle the rotting furniture.
But Thomas moves quietly, sensing his way in the dark.
Oh, you're already dressed like a wizard.
Daylight lands on his wrist.
Cool wind soothes his tired eyes.
I'm still allowed to live?
He closes the tower door gently to make no noise.
That was the mystic's art that I did.
Right, tower?
Where'd I get it from?
Could it have just happened?
Is it just one of those things?
Things a man's born with
that might blossom in his life when he needs them.
Well, I might not deserve it,
but you never turn down a turkey.
So they say.
I'm sorry.
That guy calling you a theater kid
is still Red Freak in my head.
Well, who never turns?
What if we never turn down a turkey?
You don't.
I bet this is you, Stan.
Thomas.
I should plumb the depths of this power,
but safely, I suppose, and out of sight.
I don't want anyone to know that I'm a magician.
Thomas.
You're okay.
You look like it.
Hey, Thomas, something happened.
And along us, you're here and you're safe.
Good.
Oh, sorry.
And you, too.
Is it how do I pronounce it?
Inon.
Inon and I only barely made it.
Yeah, see that smoke on the horizon?
That's from the town.
Yeah, that's thunder roast.
It burned?
Things are different than they were.
Are they?
Yeah.
Well, I don't know if you've ever seen something quite like this.
A monster.
Sure, we have.
Yeah, we slay monsters.
Oh, good.
I'm glad you're okay.
Well, I do magic.
Yeah, I know.
We're childhood friends, apparently.
And our party has been formed.
So we've discovered a new site.
So you can see in the region of the Arnie Vigil,
you can see that sword banner.
And that means that there is a battle to be had.
Ooh, a battle.
Yeah, so let's do it.
I do magic.
Is there any information that might be pertinent?
Someone else narrate for a bit.
A perfect understanding isn't likely to emerge.
What these beasts are, where they came from,
and what drove them to attack the town of thunder roast.
But letting them nest here feels like the wrong idea.
By the way, sorry, I thought that said chatter in the lower left, not clatter.
So I was doing like, sorry, that's my bad.
Do we fan out, get aggressive, or maximize our defense?
Stay tight?
Sure, well.
Okay, so either Ster can choose Icarus as a suggestion,
or Jemma can choose Stoicism.
What? What?
Like, I mean, one is him and one is me.
This is one of the things where we just kind of decide as a group.
It's like, how do we want to approach this combat?
I guess we discuss.
Back in my house, it was pretty simple.
It ran in, and we hit it one time.
Or let them come to us.
I just came out of there.
If we're methodical, patient, we can fan them off at least.
No, he overpowered you.
I know what's best here.
Our modifier, we all get plus two damage.
Okay.
We have raccoons and roe as our foe cards.
All right, I guess I'm the tank, I think.
So I'll approach the door.
Okay, I'm going to.
Oh, we can move on our own move at the same time.
Yeah.
All right, I'll just stay in the back.
I'm going to I'm going to get a fuse ready here on the tree.
Just in case I'm going to imagine they're going to be lured out potentially.
Courage, Thomas.
Courage.
We must move forward.
But not me first.
And on.
I mean, I'm not I'm very squishy, so I'm not going to get in there.
Once you've used up your two action points, you want to just end time.
Oh, there it is.
You almost killed him in one hit.
I had sentinel, which is like an inception.
I will rush the raccoon.
Okay.
I guess.
I'm going to.
I'm coming in.
I'm just going to come in.
That's a good thing we got, Thomas.
All right.
That was good support.
Great work, everybody.
There's a little tutorial fight that we did.
Great, everyone.
Okay, we found Hunter's armor.
Armored two, warding one.
Town watchers who are good with a bow and who can't get anything fancy
have long traded to each other the secrets of Graybark.
This is an upgrade for along us.
Okay.
The misshapen creature folds its bones and dimes in a nice little neat pile.
Blue fluids darken the dust.
A sick.
Fascinating.
Grim.
The color in their veins.
What does it mean?
A sickness, probably.
Today is put reality in a spiral.
Yeah.
Day day drops, day rises.
Dusk is sweet.
The sunrise sweeter.
It's not long before they've cleaned the old tower up a bit.
There's still a thousand questions in this place.
Excites.
Even the oldest books say very little of what we've seen.
Monsters come from myths.
But where do myths come from?
I suppose we'll learn.
They're real now.
Let's not wait to be overrun.
We're a company of heroes now.
We'll walk the land.
We'll fight.
People need us.
We'll give ourselves a name and make sure it's one they'll sing.
Sounds like you've thought about this.
Name of the bands for cunts.
We name our company.
So my character suggestion is the Queer Crown.
Walkers of the Queer Crown.
Ster's suggestion is the Bats of the Fabulous Four.
And Jerma's suggestion is the Family of the Golden Romance.
Okay.
The family of the...
These are all our fault.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't think we're allowed to enter our own name.
I think we have to pick from our three.
Oh, the Bats of the Fabulous Four.
I think that's my favorite.
I like that because there's three of us.
Yeah, because there's not four people.
Let's do that.
After that, the three of them are inseparable.
Rumors are rampant.
Heroes are needed.
This world will be flooded in sorrows.
But its defenders are joined by a fire that night.
Here follow the tales of the Bats of the Fabulous Four.
Be remembered.
That's us.
Anime outro.
The game has crashed.
Please send your logs.
Oh, no.
What?
Yeah, my game crashed.
That's an interesting prompt.
Wait.
No, I'm still here.
Oh, you're here.
You're good.
Am I?
Hold on.
I think I'm seeing a card of a raccoon on the screen.
Oh, yep.
I can see it.
We're good.
Yeah, we're good.
The way the combat system works is the longer our campaign goes,
we'll add more monster cards to the debt list of calamities.
And what that means is these monsters will...
There'll be new monsters.
They'll get tougher.
We'll encounter new things.
And so the longer we survive, the more the calamities of the world will grow.
Really?
Okay.
Right now, all we have is feral raccoons.
So we're the problem?
Yes.
So we have some choices here.
We have some land around us.
We have cloudy birch wilds.
We have gruff demon woods.
We have the demon wilds.
We have the humboldton beaches.
Two of these require us to build a bridge to reach.
The other two, we can just kind of walk there and kind of scout the area.
So where would you guys like to go?
What kind of sings to you?
Okay.
We got the humble demon, the demon wilds.
Yeah.
Rough demon.
Wild demons.
Yeah.
Wild demons going on.
The cloudy birch wild seems like the least demon-y place.
What do you guys think?
I think cloudy birch would be the safe play.
It sounds nice.
Yeah, it sounds nice.
What's wrong with my background?
What's wrong with my walls?
What do you mean?
It's like holding it.
You've been punching it again.
Yeah, you want a green screen?
No, no.
I think it's because you're seeing light come through the window.
Wait, did that say 23 days?
Yeah.
So the time is passing in real time.
You can see at the top, year one, spring, day 10, 11, 12, etc.
We killed a raccoon and we're like, we're adventurers now.
30 days.
Let's go.
So we've revealed the cloudy birch wilds and it looks like
there is a battle here to be had.
Okay, assault moose landing stone.
I have to be honest.
I'm glad it's you cooking tonight along us.
My feet are so tired that my hands are starting to feel it.
Don't get too excited.
It got excited.
So we'll hit moose landing stone tomorrow morning.
But that detour added more time than we thought it would
and our food is running a little low.
How low?
I've got onions and some more onions.
I still thought it was jerky.
I figured we'd need that tomorrow.
What?
Onions aren't a meal, they're an ingredient.
Okay, so we can either bet on me catching a fish 30% chance
or along us changing my mind and cooking an excellent onion
meal, which is a 51% chance to succeed.
Thomas, you settle this.
Should I cook or should he go fish?
Yeah, I think that's a good way to do it.
The person not involved gets a pick.
I think that what we should really do is I'd like to see if you can change his mind.
I feel like onions could actually be a meal if you put them into an onion soup
and make a broth and make it salty and put a little bit of cheese on it.
Let's do it.
A good onion soup can hold its own against any other meal.
Low and slow.
That's the key.
How slow?
Start thinking of stories now.
The version they tell in Cloudy Birch's Wilds differs in one key way, you see,
because of the agricultural significance of the later.
And as I was astounded, there it was in the original document.
Document?
Even later than that.
So how much longer do you think?
They're not doing what I wanted them to do.
I'm not sure if it's salvageable at this point.
Sorry about the onion mush.
What did you even do?
No, it's good.
It's OK.
You're right.
It's disgusting.
But thanks for trying.
You shall soon come to learn the tragic extent of my failings.
All right.
We had a terrible onion soup and then we got attacked by enemies.
Oh, shit.
All right.
They're in here.
Yeah, most likely.
I remember when we did this a month ago.
Different times.
I'm pretty sure same tower.
Quite not.
Where are they?
There's three monsters in here.
They're going to be in the back rooms, probably.
Looks like Thomas go off on his own.
I'm opening this door.
Nothing in here.
Oh, God.
What?
Oh, shit.
I just started blasting.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
Can I blast through the wall?
Probably.
Oh, God.
Oh, shit.
Oh, oh, it hurts.
Oh, watch out.
Watch out.
I'm going to throw a fireball.
One eye goes dark like a candle prematurely snuffed.
And then fights the sensation that he's swimming.
Fights to stay on his feet.
So I can choose to just die.
Dealing 12 damage to the enemies.
Or I can choose to fight on.
But I will get minus 15 accuracy for the rest of the campaign.
That's rough.
Two of us get through life unscathed.
Now's no time to give up.
I've lost an eye.
And then feels his way back to safety.
There's so much that he has to live for.
So much ahead of him.
If he can make it through today.
An eye patch might add a dash of mystique to my look.
I literally lost an eye.
Can you imagine saying that while getting attacked?
Your eye pops out.
Oh, an eye patch might add mystique.
And your stomach hurts from gross onion mush.
You guys are going to have to deal with this.
Now I'm gone.
All right.
I think let me tell you something along us.
I'm going to torch this room.
I just want to make sure you understand.
My eyes just went flame, right?
And everyone's like, oh, my God.
He's going to use his powers finally.
It's been like 45 minutes into the movie.
And everyone knows I'm going to hear it comes.
Here comes the powers.
OK, so he's going to infuse that clothing rack
and throw a t-shirt at the deer.
So wait, do we do I have to hit done?
No, this is a fresh turn.
You've got two actions.
Why are you dead?
He fucking says I came out three enemies and my eye came out.
But you're on the screen anymore.
I don't think you want to move up on that.
Yeah, Thomas, Thomas, do not run up there.
I'm not going to but you have no armor.
All right.
You see the you see the mannequins up here on the right?
Yeah, those have been infused.
What we're going to do is we're going to pull them back
and then I'm going to back and you're talking character, boy.
OK, flame eyes.
Stand back along us.
I'll handle this.
You step back, pull them through.
I'm pulling, I'm pulling and your turn when you're ready, though.
OK, push through aggressively.
Step back.
No, OK, flair.
They're blinded.
Uh, they will miss their next attack.
You might want to line of sight the raccoon, though, like get away.
You might be right.
So you are you're ranged.
Oh, sorry.
Can you use that bow?
My special ability, thunder shot.
Got him.
That's a good thing that that all that books and clothes was there.
OK.
What do I want to do here?
Constriction power.
You blocked it.
Can you still move, pal?
Maybe you get outside slow and methodical, like you used to say.
I can't move.
I just tried.
I did my I did.
I used my power.
Nice shot.
I've got plenty of cover here.
I'm still infused.
Oh, should we go hide in this room?
We should probably hide in the other room.
Oh, you're going in.
OK, I'm going to come in with you.
My secret ability, silk step.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What?
How does this work?
Hold on.
I'm reading my special duty.
Oh, check this out.
Can you kill it?
Good block.
I can't believe he's blocked twice and I'm the tank and I just lost an eye.
I'm confused.
So except supposed to make me hidden.
But then it also told me to move.
I don't know how the ability is worth.
Great job, Thomas.
Let's find that.
I let you have an eye patch.
Look.
Oh, you do have an eye patch.
That's funny.
OK, we got the lizard beam spear.
I think I will replace my pickaxe with that.
Sure, you can handle a spear with one eye.
It's kind of a precise weapon.
Oh, I get to name the item.
So that's five damage, right?
That definitely should go to you.
And then we have a ring.
Warding, which is plus eight zero point warding.
That's magic magic armor.
The way gear works is if you hover over the empty slot for everyone,
it will tell you the warding will go up from two point one to two point nine.
So every value of one is like an upgrade.
It says it absorbs magic damage in on.
You should take it.
You're mine.
You're tanking.
Yeah, I'll grab it.
Yeah, my way through hell, my friend.
And the thought of you trekking back in this state is unacceptable.
I'm going to make you some onion soup.
Blue.
Good.
You're still here.
All right.
Who wants to play Luke?
This is a new cat.
Wait, is this a new character?
I just introducing us to an MPC.
OK.
Hello.
And on this is Luke.
She's headed back out of here.
And I've arranged a slight detour for her to give you a lift back to town.
It's just an eye, mate.
Arranged.
You mean you bombardo is some arsenal of reasons.
They were extremely solid reasons.
Huh.
What?
Just feels weird getting special treatment.
Then think of it as balancing the scales a bit.
You were in front of death's door not that long ago.
It's time to enjoy the good fortune where you can find it.
Take care as long as you need.
I mean, you're sending me away.
I've been sent away.
So in our first fight, I died, lost an eye,
and now you're sending me away to like a home.
What is happening to you?
You're just getting a nice tree tops passing by the bump in that ox smell.
What?
Enemies improve their strategy.
OK.
So they've added the deer are now corrupted and they leave trails of corruption when they move.
Oh, no.
OK.
So I am.
You're legit gone.
Yeah, I am maimed and it will take me some time to heal.
So you guys are going to have to travel ahead of me.
Oh, no.
Next place.
Wait, we're turning back to thunder roast on a wagon.
Why are we going the other way?
Why are you back with you?
Why did we send you back?
Because I mean, I'm wounded.
I lost an eye, guys.
Well, we could go back with you.
No, it's you chose not to.
That's OK.
Painted by the amber by painted amber by the fading light,
a formation of stone catches a long as his eye.
You think something's up there?
You never know what you'll find until you look upon the hill summit.
Nothing.
Turns out your eyesight is shit.
The decent view, at least.
Look, you can see the salt road.
Oh, far in the distance.
I think that's our friend going back to town.
What's happening?
A thrumming.
What's that?
It grows louder, a rumbling.
Well, and louder until the stone underfoot shatters and shakes.
It grows louder, even more.
Very loud.
Oh, it's so loud.
OK.
The mighty growl, calamorous, was thundering.
And that resolves.
OK.
That was weird.
That was close.
Oh, hold me.
Maybe we shouldn't have took all those drugs 20 minutes ago.
Probably a bad idea.
Corruption.
A voice.
I.
The voice of a carnivore cunning and crooning,
warning them to run, promising to give chase.
The one you have hunted so long.
In my dreams at night, I would think of this animal.
Through cups and riddles.
That doesn't sound right.
You have hunted so long for me and for a brotherhood that should be yours.
Wait, can I go back?
Do you see your face, Thomas?
Yeah.
I like know what's going on.
You're tripping.
I'm like, do you know my name?
Her name.
It was the gift I gave to your ancestors.
Thomas is still tripping.
They walked my myth over Greenfield and Fallow to the curves and corners of being they walked.
Do you know my name?
Uh, how would I?
A blessing heard through ancient service, an oath written in the steps and trails
and sealed with a name.
You need only to know it.
I'll ask you once more.
We don't know your name.
Do you know my name?
Lot I, yes.
I hope that's right.
It's like reading a fairy tale from your childhood only to realize how disturbing it is.
The Longest doesn't like knowing the name, but he's sure it's right.
Sorry.
Yes, I am lock chaos, your wolf God.
And now you may take my oath, abandon your humanity, my boy, and be blessed as wolf kind.
Oh, yes.
I always knew that I was different somehow.
A furry perhaps.
It feels like coming home, taking oath along us.
No, I'm going home along us, kneels and beneath him a green light pools.
Dandelions rise yellow out of the sparse wind scraped dirt.
They grow old and white, throw their seeds and then wilt to nothing.
The God rock he kneels upon hums.
It cracks somewhere inside.
A geode of understanding splits and catches light beneath the earth and behind his eyes.
Mildly.
Somebody like took a picture of you to flash on in like a bar late at night.
We're going to get the anamorphs transition along us.
Plus forward time and age.
You have human arms.
You just have a wolf.
You have a wolf head.
That's it, man.
When when I next see you, I'm going to be very confused.
Oh, no.
Okay.
So what we can do is you can head back to moose landing and you can secure it.
And that will give us like a source of income.
Are we able to station here earn resources?
Yeah.
So we can you want to build a station in Pinewood?
That's a good.
I'm running around chasing squirrels.
What does Thomas do?
Okay.
Oh, no, I this is going to and you chose this fate.
So you have to stick with it.
Wait, do I have a laboring?
God damn it.
You have to you have to go all out.
But you know, you could do the wolf from every major RPG.
And that's just like this talk.
Just like this with a little bit of a little, you know, you don't really care that much.
Labor intensive, but practical in the long run.
I don't know how I got this accent.
Should we lend a hand?
I'm going Batman.
Cowlings of sleeping top have been dreaming of building a new threshery or lumber yard.
The wild folk want to restore the woodland altar.
Okay, so we can spend one of our legacy points, which we get, we got a bunch for each campaign.
We can have a build a threshery, which will provide us with wooden fabric or a lumber wood.
The lumber yard will provide us to wood and a primal altar will give us hides and spell threads.
And all this stuff can be used at the end of each chapter to craft new gear for us.
Hmm.
I mean, I'm going to vote for the, uh, for the spell threads because I mean,
if you saw on the land, the previous battle, my, uh, my flames were very, very effective.
Three damage each at least.
Okay. Well, it's going to take 25 days to complete.
Get to work.
25 days?
I'm healing all the while.
Oh, okay. Good.
Inan has returned.
Okay. So while you guys are doing that, I will go to moon's landing and meet you there.
Moose landing.
Okay.
There are studies must be comprehensive and meticulous.
I'm up to it.
If no one else is.
I'm so glad I'm not the wolf character and you are.
We can invest, we can investigate thoroughly to find a new item.
We can prioritize speed for like crafting stuff.
I think we find an item here.
Yeah, I agree.
Okay. Let's do an item.
So this is my job.
I will head there and find an item while you guys build that place.
Cool.
Uh, alter dedicated longhorn alter now produces hides and spell threads.
So you guys can probably come and meet me if you want.
Yeah. Do we have to do anything else with, with this or is this just stays here?
No, it's, it's all done.
Yeah. That'll, that'll be, that's good.
All right, let's head over there.
Okay. So now we just want to stay here and see this through.
I think we see this through.
If it's going to be adjacent to our altar over there, right?
Yeah. I think we should make sure it's secured.
Someone paused.
Uh, infants infestations increase the strength of the source threat.
Can ambush groups of two or one heroes.
It's dangerous out there.
Don't travel alone or split the party at every opportunity.
Hmm. Okay.
We're going to take the source out.
All right.
A thorough delving through the mysterious mysteries of the moose laying stone has
proven rewarding.
Which strikes me how much this is defined to know.
I can't believe I haven't reacted to your wolf head.
Yeah.
Moose landing stone will return to the hands of the common folk.
And while they tend it, this site will provide resources at the end of each chapter.
When will he notice me?
Do we want, uh, hides ingots or spell threads?
I say ingots like a bit of steel.
I think it's useful for everybody.
I think that's a good idea.
Okay. Oh, we get, we actually just get all three.
Oh, we get it all. Cool.
All right.
Who's still reading?
Oh, there we go.
Okay.
We unlocked a sash, um, which is a plus six stunt chance.
Stunt.
That's like a crit.
Is it sounds like, yeah, it feels, I don't know, but I know you grow over it.
It doesn't even make sense.
Then percentage chance that attacks will inflict additional damage and stunt effects.
Oh, I think that's probably a wizard thing.
It's crit.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
It's creating.
Is it spell crit or is it just regular attacks?
So I would assume not spells unless everything's an attack, but I don't.
Oh, really?
Attacks.
I don't know.
I think spells are an attack.
Yeah.
People saying ranger or mage would be a good choice.
So either of you guys, let's, let's give it to long.
That's cause he doesn't have anything yet.
I don't think.
Ooh.
I mean, I did become a wolf.
That is a thing.
Yeah.
You should be the ranged crit guy.
But Thomas already has a, yeah.
We got you the silk threads.
All right.
We're splitting it up.
We're even.
Okay.
So now I think we head for the demon wilds, right?
It's time.
I'm like really, really, really far.
Yeah.
Cause I'm noticing we have a countdown timer at the top until things get awful.
So, you know, it's a long journey, but you know, worth it to save the world and such.
Okay.
Yeah, I guess.
Oh no.
So the calamity has grown.
We now get Gorgons, Watchmen, Bogmores and Draven get extra help.
Okay.
So what do we have?
So these are our legacy points.
Yeah.
I think it's like, I think it's like some kind of abrasion on the camera.
Stop some of the things like, like, I don't want to read Gorgon.
Whatever it is like, like a glare on the lens.
Maybe calamity and spend one.
I'll get it figured out.
Or we can just let them all through and see what happens.
I don't, I don't want bow guys to be healthy guys.
Yeah, I like that.
I think we can handle the rest.
Although I did get blinded by a deer and I've never been the same.
I can't believe you lost an eye.
I know.
Well, I think I'd rather lose an eye than just have a wolf head.
That's all I wanted.
Okay.
The demon walls have been revealed and we have, we have an assault on Swine Side Copes.
We're attacking.
All right.
Would you like to be narrated now?
Yeah, sure.
I'll narrate a little bit.
The sun's fallen and the silver fog floats from the trees where shadows pool.
You can see it.
Wait, go back.
I didn't even notice it at first.
What happened?
My little dog is on the left.
Oh, you're just sitting there.
Along us.
Can you slow down?
And I won't want to lose you.
You're gonna have to keep me on a leash.
I thought that's what it actually said.
Said Mr. Nixon.
You're gonna have to keep me on a leash.
The quiet forms of fence around them.
Impenetrable.
The whirling air almost utterly opaque.
Inan!
You trust me, don't you?
Let's get to the trees.
At least those are solid.
They halt just inside the shelter of the pines.
Dark air clinging wet.
The trunks they press to dampen their palms.
Being lost with you isn't so bad.
I'm the one who's lost.
You guys are together.
And then suddenly, and then something vast moves beside them.
Slow, achingly slow.
It passes too enormous to be seen.
Impossibly silent.
What?
It's a tree.
It's just a regular tree.
Some kind of beast.
What's that Pokemon?
Why are we?
Who took this other picture?
Tradaru.
It's all AI generated.
That's the crazy thing.
Wait, so hold on.
Yeah, it's like, oh, look at this.
But look at this too.
This is a different, like, this is.
They're trying to like really emphasize this really weird silhouette.
Night's fallen.
The fog wanders away.
Clinging to the felty outline of that gargantuan shadow.
Oh, let's find Inan.
Maybe he saw it too.
Maybe he saw it better.
So, as long as it's choice will probably put you guys in a two-man combat.
Thomas's choice will find me first.
Okay.
I know you're beyond intrigued, but let's find Inan first.
Bad night to be chasing moon beams.
Oh, I'm the theater kid.
I'm the theater kid.
You are howling every chance you're grunting and growling.
I have told you this before.
The more I do this.
There's another word for that, Jeremy.
It's not theater kid.
During the audition at the school play, you went down on all fours.
And we're running around on the stage for the wolf character.
And nobody else did that.
Honestly, you want to know it's really cringe?
Not giving it your all.
That's true.
They meet in the open.
Crickets crackle again.
Finding the rhythm.
Somewhere, an owl pipes his blue notes.
We're here.
Apparently, Inan was also able to glimpse the shadowy giant as it passed.
Didn't see more than a black suggestion of its form.
I don't see a lot these days.
Then, as they're about to decide whether to set up camp or search for huge tracks by starlight,
the disturbance shakes the tree line.
Okay, we all get plus one temporary hit points.
You'll need it.
We're probably going to need it.
Okay, we have bogmores, rages, raccoons, and rose.
Heaving its overgrown body in mucusy plops, its grasping mouth drips and stinks.
And that fire spirit, we got to catch it.
It says it won't be here for long.
If we catch the fire spirit, it will actually give us like a legendary item.
Oh, I'm up.
I'm up here.
I'm going to send them just in case something comes, but we definitely Thomas is still using
a wooden spoon, even though we're in the second year of our journey.
So we probably need to get him something.
Why wouldn't I have just picked up a rock?
It would have been better.
Oh, okay.
Go for it, Thomas.
All right.
How do I think I don't know if we have to kill it.
There you go.
Caught you.
Do I get to make a wish now?
Okay.
So you can get a tier one fire wand or a legacy point.
I mean, the wand is definitely got to be it.
Yeah, for sure.
Fire damage definitely replaced the spoon.
Yeah.
Replace the soup spoon that you've been carrying.
Nice.
Cool.
And fire now has a stunt effect of damaging up to three nearby enemies.
Replacing gear is permanent.
That's the stunt effect.
Nice.
All right.
Cool.
So now I'm kind of out of the combat zone, though.
So it's okay.
I'm not going to push.
We're just going to let them come to us.
Good shot.
Oh, shit.
That's big.
Whatever that is.
Oh, not again.
Oh, no.
Is this on like masochist difficulty?
I'm going to see if I can blow the tree up.
Is it going to hurt you?
I don't think so.
I don't think you can friendly fire.
See if I can pop both these.
I actually can hurt you.
Can I hit them both from here?
There we go.
They blocked it.
I'm dead.
No.
I'll save you.
Oh, no, you're good.
We lived.
No.
Oh, gosh.
That thing is huge.
This thing is terrifying.
I think we're all dead, by the way.
We need your magic, Stamble, than ever.
I can try and finish off this guy.
I think I can.
I can pin this person here, I think.
If I do this.
Oh, the Bogmaw?
I can try it.
Wait, am I moving him?
If you pin him, he loses his movement next turn.
That's good.
This plant sends out tendrils that grab and draw in an enemy,
dealing damage and pinning them.
I'm going to try it.
I could run away after the fact.
Yeah.
See if it works.
Oh, you hit him.
And you killed them.
Whoa.
All in a day's work, is what I'm saying.
I get a swift action free wolf bite,
but I think I can't use it because I'm holding a bow.
I think you can't use it because you're not in melee range.
No, I was trying to do it to the deer when it was next to me.
Okay.
Oh, oh, it's okay.
It's only cardinal.
This raccoon is just going to keep shooting.
Maybe I run off to him.
I feel like that's probably less dangerous.
You ran off to it.
You want to try and finish it?
Then I start a blast.
Oh, that's actually helpful.
Nice.
All right, we're okay.
This is corruption.
I wonder if I can reach from here.
Wait, that took two actions.
I was going to go nuts.
Yeah, you moved really far.
Okay.
Well, I wanted to eat it.
All right.
What if I do this?
Hopefully this doesn't hurt you guys.
What?
Oh, no, he dodged.
There we go.
All right.
That was that was big.
That worked.
I did not think we were going to make it out of that.
That was good.
All right.
We got a talisman of power ancient charm to hang around your waist.
I think you should take this because you're going to be always up in front
and you're going to always take hits.
So you should be dealing damage at the front.
Maybe we should save something.
Like I should wear like more tanky stuff.
We should give you guys the damage.
Give it to me.
That puts a long us up to one bonus damage.
So he would do one extra damage.
I need one second.
Can you guys hear me?
Yeah.
Yeah, we can hear you.
Okay.
Oh, I think I like kicked my Wi-Fi or my router out.
You're you're like breaking up a little bit.
Wait, do you actually physically kicked it with your feet?
Okay, let's just freeze it.
You want to take like a should we take like a two minute break or something like him?
Yeah, we take a two second break.
Yeah, maybe like two minutes.
Yeah, I'll make some coffee.
Cool.
I want to take a little break whilst the sorts of stuff now.
You enjoying it?
No, this is great.
This is I so for people that have no idea what's going on.
You can grab your coffee because I want to explain a little more detail.
Go for it.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Yeah, I think I kicked like the power cable halfway out.
Really?
Modem.
So my internet was like half out.
It was weird.
But yeah, we'll be back in two minutes.
Cool.
So just before I go BRB, we're just going to take a quick two minute break.
But for those of you that don't know what's going on,
if you were like what the hell is going on,
we kind of jumped right into it because I was a little late.
This is all AI generated.
So this whole game is a procedurally generated RPG AI D&D like.
Not everything is AI and procedure generated.
I know.
Yeah, but a lot of stuff is.
It's sort of just like a procedurally generated RPG.
Not everything.
It's not AI.
Well, I keep saying that it's stupid.
That's the wrong thing.
But you know what I mean?
It's just like random stuff that they plug in.
RPG D&D or ADHD.
But yeah, if you're curious as to like why is all this stuff so weird,
it's because it's just generating it.
And my camera, I have no idea why that was happening.
I think it honestly was because the way the light was bouncing off the wall.
I don't know.
I'll have to figure that out.
It seems to be gone now.
But this is really fun.
This is funny.
I'm going to take two quick seconds.
I'll be right back.
Yeah.
Hello.
I'm back.
Hey, welcome back.
I'm ready.
We're all ready.
I think we're good to go.
Yeah, we're good to go.
I was thinking this game is so good if you like want to try D&D,
but you don't have a friend who's a DM because the game is the DM.
Yeah.
So can you correct me when we were on break?
I was talking about it.
Is there is it AI?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's all like every no adventure will be the same.
It's like procedurally generated.
There's like certain campaigns, but they have like not every campaign
is going to have a wolf head and I'm not going to lose an eye.
Right.
It's all AI.
I believe like to an extent that there are like events that happen,
like the wolf head, but it is still like phrased differently, I assume.
The scenarios are written, but like what happens is kind of like
all thrown into an AI and then like thrown at you.
So it's just like a like a jumbler essentially.
That's interesting.
That's cool.
Yeah.
So like certain stories, so you can see at the top this this particular
like encounter we found ourselves in is called silver and shadows
and it tells you who the writer is.
So someone wrote this story.
Oh, oh, all right.
But the AI kind of like puts everything in a timeline
and then like, you know, throws the events at us and that kind of stuff.
That's cool.
All right.
I'm you guys ready to go?
Yes, let's do it.
The fight has brought them back under the bows of the wood.
I think it's quiet.
I hate a night battle.
Keep knocking into pronounced bows.
Can you stop, please?
Keep knocking into trees.
It's too late.
They make a broad search for sign of the giant's passing,
but are forced to camp precious hours from sunrise having found nothing.
Still, the story does quite well in taverns.
And those who saw it dream of a colossal being,
all shadowy gray, silver, fog, and overwhelming giant.
They dream of seeing it again one day.
They dream for years and years.
I'm in the corner like, yeah, I'm above all this human stuff now.
All right, three legacy points.
Is this implying that we spent years just hanging out?
Yes.
This might be a time skip.
We just got a three year time skip?
We needed a break.
Hold on.
Did we just spend three years telling everybody how cool we are for fighting in the woods?
I think it's more like it's telling us it's the narrator saying
that this will happen for years to come.
Like people will tell the stories for years to come.
We're still in our second year of our adventure,
but he's kind of like saying people will talk about their deeds for years to come.
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay. Cool. Cool. Cool.
Okay. So we can go to the Hallenwilds or the night top.
You know, this is year two.
So it was a time skip.
Yeah. So we can, if you mouse over the Hallenwild seems to be infested with Gorgons.
They may ambush our group.
And the other one is Draven, which may ambush our group.
If we check our card deck again, our calamities by pressing B
or clicking the one in the top right, we can see that the Gorgons are kind of stacked.
They are.
And the Draven look kind of weak by comparison.
So it might be worth...
Oh yeah. And we avoided the one Draven once.
Let's Draven.
Yeah. So let's go Draven.
Cause I think that's like the safer bet.
Good idea.
Cause we are very injured right now, actually.
What?
And you'll see that we're healing over time as we travel.
Wait, wait, two years passed and we're hurt?
No, it was the narrator.
It was confusing, but it was the narrator saying that
people would be talking about our stories for years to come.
But the top says year two, day 20.
That's yeah, that's our entire journey so far has been two years.
Randomly generated.
Yeah. It's, you know, I'm angrily traveling.
Okay. Well, Assault Viv Mia shop is our thing.
I'm low health, but I think we can do it.
We can also choose if you see at the bottom right,
you can see that we don't just have an assault choice.
We have a patrol choice, which will send our party to clear
the infestation on the tile and reduce the strength of the enemy.
So we can spend some time just like kind of scouting.
How, how certain are we going to lose this?
It's, it, it's strength four.
If we clear it, it'll become a strength three.
Okay.
We like patrol.
See if we can do it.
Yeah, there we go.
Okay. So now it's a strength three, which is more doable and I healed up.
Perfect.
So this is perfect.
Oh, a little nervous.
Telling myself it's all birds and mice out there.
You click.
Of course I'm tense.
Moments before a battle, I get all squeezed up inside.
I'm good.
That's it.
Yeah. What?
We gained temporary damage of potency because you, you, uh, yeah.
Apparently my incredible simple overconfidence.
Yeah. Through the power of like toxic masculinity,
you put up a front that you had to deal with this.
Hey, I appreciate that.
Yep. I'm good.
Yup. I'm good.
Me too.
Yep. Same.
Okay. So this is a small area and dots.
Okay.
I think I'm, I'm, I'm kind of scared.
I'm going to stay back.
That scarecrow is blocking the path.
Open fire.
Oh, oh my God.
Nice.
Strong.
Okay. I'm going to, yeah, I'll jump here and then I'm going to sentinel.
If they get too close.
I'm going to infuse the wagon.
If they walk near the way.
Actually, let me see if I can do it now.
I can.
All right. I'm going to do a, I'm going to do a blast.
That's huge.
Oh, let me do this again.
Um, actually I was going to move.
I'm going to get a better spot.
I have never heard of a player like being a werewolf and using a bow.
Who has that like fantasy?
I mean, into a wolf and just pick up a bow.
Imagine a situation where you can identify an enemy location via your sense of smell.
So even in like pitch darkness, you're an excellent ranger.
Yeah. I don't believe all the dogs are good at smelling stuff.
My dog is an idiot.
Like there's no way it's smelling stuff that I can't smell.
Okay. But you're not a dog.
You're a wolf, man.
Yeah. You're a, you're a, well, you're a wolf.
Um, wolf head.
I'm not buying it.
Okay.
It's propaganda.
Gemma, how are you liking the wizard?
It's fun.
I like the, you kind of have to tap into scenery and then blow up scenery.
I don't know if I'm, I don't think I have like a regular attack.
Maybe I'm not close enough.
No, I think this is it.
Yeah.
Yeah. I have a strike.
Yeah. I forgot that you do like insane fire damage because you're warm.
Yeah. I think it's crazy.
I need to start doing that more often instead of blow up.
Oh, I leveled in and dogwood is now a blood horn warrior.
Ooh.
I can interrupt.
I can upgrade my central move.
I can go untouchable.
When Inon gets a kill, the next attack against him within one turn will miss.
That seems really good.
That does seem great.
Um, yeah, I really like that.
I, because I keep getting my ass beat.
Ooh.
A fang axe, tier one axe plus one damage to drawmen.
It does bonus damage to drawmen forged by long dead roamers of the wild lands.
So we can either give this to one of you guys just so you have like an alternative weapon
or I can just take it for when we fight drawmen.
Is this better than what you have?
Uh, it's, I think it's about this.
It's the same as what I have, but it has more shred and stunt damage,
but I also have an empty weapon slot so I can like carry both.
Hmm.
Um, but you don't have like a melee weapon per se.
So if you want like something, just in case something's in your face or you don't have any,
uh, scenery to play, to pull from, we can do that too.
Um, I, I think it's just go to, uh, can I, do I do very much melee damage?
Um, I think the damage is dependent on the weapon itself.
So it says five damage on the weapon and I think like damage is just like,
if you get plus damage gear, it would apply to everything you do.
I mean, if I'll take it and put it in my other slot.
Yeah.
If, uh, if it's not better than what you have.
No, it's, it's the same as what I have.
All right.
Yeah, that's good.
Yeah, cool.
Cool.
And then we get the phone shadow pauldrons, which gives five dodge.
You should dodge.
Let's see.
I do not want to see another eye come out.
Uh, everyone's saying Austin.
Yep.
It didn't.
Austin, did you announce it?
Are these tanky though?
I feel like they might be a ranger thing.
Just take them.
And then if you get a tanky thing, just we can trade it later, right?
Gonna be, gonna be, gonna be flying in a, uh, in a plane simulation with Austin
in a couple of days.
It's gonna be wild.
Go check the Twitter.
I'll retweet that too.
What a minute.
If only he dodged.
We came out losing very little.
Some ripped scuffs and notches, but mostly clean.
That's a worthy day's work.
I don't know how I get.
I don't trust simple success as irrational as them.
Jesus Christ.
You think of all the stuff that's out there.
Evil.
Yeah.
Or just hungry.
Could come rampaging into our midst and take one of us away.
Makes me frustrated.
How fragile we all still are.
Someone asked if he was Scooby-Doo.
Yeah, I was gonna say you're getting into like, like, like, no, like ape territory.
Like, I think he's just, just general beast.
Yeah.
General beast.
Okay.
I was like, I was a person before.
I don't know what it is to be a wolf.
You are quite close to just, yeah.
I'm more a man than I am wolf.
Okay.
So the Draven got stronger.
They learned from their defeat.
Oh, but that's okay.
That's their first card.
So it's not a big deal.
Do we want to secure the, the, the shop or do we want to press on?
Does that mean we can buy stuff?
It means we can get an item like we got last time.
Ooh, secure.
We're greedy.
Yeah, I say secure.
Let's find an item then.
I'm in the mood for some scaring and discovering.
We can set this place right as we go, can't we?
Investigate thoroughly.
Okay.
Nice job.
All right.
Secure complete.
You look so happy.
Study the world and you'll never finish discovering wonders.
Looks like you guys are playing fetch.
Yeah, it does.
Somebody want to take a narrator?
So we've unlocked.
No, I think you're doing a great job.
Okay.
So a thorough delving through the mysteries of Viv Mia shop has proven rewarding.
Viv Mia shop will return to the hands of the common folk.
While they tend to the site will provide resources at the end of each chapter.
You've got two leaves and one of those.
Click done and we should get a weapon.
There we go.
Warding is star slate necklace and warding is absorbing magic damage.
Somebody rather you for being up front, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd go for it.
Okay.
So if you guys look in the top left of the screen,
you'll see that along us is currently glowing and he has an icon.
So that means that he has a side quest that we can pursue.
I mean, let's do it.
If we click that side quest.
How long has it been?
Haven't I wait.
I forgot how you like change the reader.
Oh, yeah.
Just is it just when I press next, I like took it.
Yeah.
So we had to check the box.
We're just reading along with you now.
Haven't cracked a book in ages.
How long since I've felt inspired?
See a more man.
Well, you're turning into like Arthur Morgan.
I've been through a lot along us.
Why you vote here?
You won't suppose to find my note until tomorrow.
Here.
I thought I was being nice, letting you rest.
Yeah.
No, you are.
I just wanted some time.
I don't know what it is really.
Mind if I keep you company?
I'm sure you can come.
Okay.
Just let me get my travel things.
You have any idea where we're off to?
I don't know.
Where are we going?
I left you a note and I didn't really think beyond that.
We have options.
I need to spark my mind somehow.
I need to become inspired.
And that case isn't the bar a good place to start.
No, it's beyond the horizon.
Face.
He gives it number two.
Like, what?
I didn't think of that.
What are you doing?
I chose the bar.
I didn't think of that.
That was clever.
Yeah.
I love how your side quest is let's go get a drink for like a half hour.
I've just been running around in the woods.
I can click it again.
It's the same.
Did we just complete it?
Okay.
I think you didn't.
I think.
Oh, I think you have to.
You got to select one.
Yeah.
I did select.
I think the selecting that one is making it because I'm choosing number two.
Maybe the bar is like it's just ending your adventure.
It's suspending the side quest because it's like you're not actually leaving on a journey.
You're just going to the bar.
Oh, let's choose.
Yeah.
Okay.
I guess somehow throughout this, I was just third wheeling behind you guys carrying like
the wagon or something.
That's so funny.
I'm here.
I know we're big time.
Wow.
Look at this journey.
Oh, my God.
We're going so far.
We're going back to the altar where I transformed.
This is like a seven month journey.
Yeah.
You guys are my best friends.
Oh, no.
Things got really bad in our absence as well.
We have so many points.
Let's just like just.
I think I want to can't.
Yeah.
You want to just cancel a little bit.
We're not fighting anything.
Pass everything.
Nothing happened.
No clammies.
We're fine.
Why are we going all the way over here?
So what do you think of Brighton?
You're blind.
Is that what this place is called?
They say the brave who come here shall learn themselves the deepest truth.
Well, one thing I've learned is to mistrust your vacation ideas.
We traveled a year out here.
They didn't have the budget for me in this side story.
Yeah.
How come you're not here?
I'm just carrying the bags.
What are we doing?
I'm trying to stay upbeat about this, but.
The day dies.
Sun falls away.
And in the night, they build a fire.
Why do we even?
Why do we do this?
Just keep going.
There must be a reason.
I don't know what I expected to find.
I think I'm mostly looking for a feeling.
Is that really something you can search for?
Remember when we did this?
Everything was new.
Each path we took and every labor we put ourselves to.
I'm bored.
You know, it's really boring walking for a year and.
To find to build a fire in the woods.
And not fighting anything, not doing any adventures.
We just we just go like on a walk across the whole country.
You know, what's even more boring than that is doing the same thing.
But neither of you spoke to me for a year.
I just yeah, we didn't even ask.
You just came.
Tell me of sorrow this rose that you kept.
By the bed in which last your pole is about slapped.
Why am I singing this?
That's a theater kid.
That song.
She woke full of laughter and brightly she gazed
at the curve of her mouth and a kiss she appraised.
All right, I'm going to count you guys in.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
She sang over the hills.
It instantly voice jammered me.
Take your headphones out.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Sir, sir, take out your headphones.
Okay.
Ready?
Three, two, one.
She sang over the hills.
Peaks are shy, but sure dawn.
And sure as the sunrise I'll someday be gone.
But recall me my love.
And our joy may live on.
And you do and you do and you do you.
That's a howl at the end.
There has to be a howl at the end.
And then we fused as one.
The old love song is one he's sung a hundred times by a fire,
a hundred times with a friend.
And still tonight it feels new.
Strange song always broke my heart when we sing it together.
Forming a deeper bond of love.
I we might be.
I suppose we each thought of each other
and what it would be like to have to go on alone.
Is the relationship more akin to like a human and a pet dog?
Or is it like?
I don't know.
We'll find out.
A noise rises in the darkness.
Not an echo of them,
but the resonant call of something else.
Did our voices awake the neighbors?
Well, there's been some run ins out here.
Stick by the fire.
Maybe it's nothing.
If we're being hunted,
I say we turn the snares on our enemy.
Okay. Well, so my choice here is to let you guys stay by the fire
with the guy with the fire wand.
Ooh, that's a sure bet.
Or roll the dice on a Lugas hunting prey.
I'm going to stay by the fire for you guys.
Oh, I want to sing and I want to kill and I want to fuck.
They stand back to back at the rim of the fire light.
A foe emerges.
Oh shit.
These look scary.
Like, yeah.
They're like necrobots.
Yeah, they're like necrobots.
So wait, you have you're here.
So I think these side stories normally involve two characters,
but the whole pie comes along.
Oh, and early on he said he loved you.
So you would have been like the guy.
All right.
I'm fusing this.
Yeah, I don't know.
I think they're going to actually one over there.
I think they all gather over there.
It is this one on each side.
Okay, I'm going to I'm going to just pin this person over here
so they don't move.
You guys can deal with that.
Demolished.
Good work.
I'll get in front of you.
I can just hurt it.
Nice.
Somebody still have an action?
Yeah, hold on.
No, it won't let me.
Let me see.
I'm waiting for the walls of your room to fall down,
revealing you're in front of a live studio audience.
Nice work.
Oh, my level.
Yeah.
Piercing shots.
My range attacks have to pierce.
Does that mean it goes through, buddies?
Passive a bard.
A lungus reduces the cost of recruit job.
We've never done that ever.
Yeah, I don't know what that is.
One speed.
You can upgrade howl.
Howl.
I'm a wolf.
Look at that.
Warrior's armor.
Yeah, I'll link mail.
That looks pretty sick.
It's not even my adventure.
I'll take the loot.
To my eyes, it's all clear.
Same here, nothing moving.
Well, that was sudden.
Seems like we'll survive another night.
You know, I'm glad we came out.
But let us be on the road at dawn.
Yeah.
When you sang and when I sang with you,
I considered that word I tend to think of all the time.
It's raising.
It's like a well.
This well inside you will always fill and empty.
It's fine.
But I want to live for the lasting things like love and old well-worn songs.
In the morning, they will simply start home.
So if we walk all the way back, I will lose it.
Just for clarity's sake, we could have done this.
Anywhere, like a year ago.
We could have just walked in.
Yeah, but along us convinced us to walk for a year to the birthplace.
Oh, he leveled up from doing his side quests.
He's going to live 10 extra years and he now gets another move.
I'm a blue-born hunter now.
I can throw a trap.
Every time I kill an enemy, I can enter the gray plane.
That's stealth.
30 dodge.
30 dodge sounds like a lot.
It does.
Yeah, and you already have the plus dodge stuff.
Oh, and you can reroll these with lupi.
Yeah.
I feel like I'm not supposed to waste that.
How much LP do we all have?
It says at the eight at the top, right?
So we share this as a group.
Yeah.
Okay.
Did anything reroll?
It gave me the same dodge again.
Oh, okay.
For a second, I thought nothing changed.
And wind walk.
Wind walk is like Misty Step.
Like you'll be able to teleport somewhere, I think.
Thornbanging.
Okay.
Because that bite was doing a lot of damage.
I think we can go to the Hallenwalds from here and just walk.
It's only 20 days.
Wait, weren't we at the Hallenwalds, though?
No, this is fine.
Okay.
Wow, we really did lose six months and 33 days on that journey.
I can't believe we walked from just here all the way to here.
I would like to apologize.
Or us to sing a song.
Okay, Hallenwalds has been revealed.
See, this is a big world.
Wait.
Okay, so we can't actually...
This is the last place.
It says assault the Lithgram engine.
We must achieve our other objectives first.
So we must clear all the hostiles in the land.
So we have to go to the other three places.
Everywhere is in part...
Oh, no.
Oh, the only place we haven't been is Humble Demon Beaches,
which is all...
It's going to be a year.
It's going to be so far.
Let's patrol this place and get rid of the thorns,
and then we will leave.
Well, at least you leveled up a couple of times.
I tricked my party into taking me on a walk.
Okay.
A very long walk.
How far is this trip?
Okay, are we carving a pass all the way there?
It's a commitment, but I think it'll bring us goodwill.
Goodwill can buy you a lot in times of need.
Okay, I guess let's get started
and try and carve our way to the place we haven't been.
Let's get started.
Okay, 78 days it will take.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my goodness.
We have to walk all the way.
We lost nearly two years from your inspiration journey.
I love this.
We spent more time finding inspiration for you
than we have on the rest of our quest.
Thank you.
You're good friends.
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
Okay, so this is our first incursion.
So Gorgons and Greatnumber move to attack our lands.
Your enemies will travel from tile to tile,
attacking and destroying all the sites.
And so they are repelled.
Okay, so what's going to happen is
you can see their progress here.
They're going to come from that land
through Arnie Vigil and then Thunderost.
So should we just set up shop in Arnie Village?
Yeah, that's the best.
Probably the best idea is to set up shop in Arnie
and then intercept them.
Or we can just keep building this bridge
and then like follow them.
Wrap around.
I'm down for whatever.
Yeah, I think we can intercept them, right?
That's probably safe.
Yeah, that's secure.
Okay, do you want to find an item while we're securing?
I think we should work faster
with the whole incursion situation.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, that's good.
Yeah, let's just take everyone off of this.
Yeah.
And go.
Yeah, because they might just be on their way over here now.
Yeah, see how it's filling up with...
Okay, do we want to cancel all these?
No, I think we can handle these.
I think we're all right.
We don't want to waste all of our points.
Yeah, we're strong.
Oh, no.
Whatever this is, what's this?
Gorgons?
Gorgons is terrifying.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
What counter is this?
Oh, it's a raging Gorgon.
Okay, okay.
So we're dead.
Everything's...
No, everything's fine.
We've got this.
We're going to crush this.
We've been killing everything.
Arnyvigil has been cleaned and put in good order,
with time left for a few days of comfort.
Arnyvigil will return to the hands of the common folk
while they tend it.
The site will provide resources at the end of each chapter.
Tides, ingots, spell threads.
Good.
They were carved in the past.
I think it's...
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I don't know how...
Are we building a bridge so the enemy can use that bridge?
We're not doing that, are we?
Yeah, I think we are.
Why are we helping them?
It's fine.
What else are we going to do, I guess?
They can't get over here.
We're helping them get over here.
Well, they're...
Yeah, they're beasts.
Maybe they'll swim.
We don't know.
Okay.
So now we have to stop what we're doing.
All heroes on this tile will fight.
It looks like we have four farmers helping us.
What?
The Gorgons have come.
Silence falls, emerging in their tortured shapes.
The beasts only breathe and blink their oozing eyes.
How should the defenders respond?
Along us, I...
Okay.
Charge into battle and fight them.
Use our knowledge of the land and harry their approach
or stay here until the last moment and fight with cunning.
I mean, my vote's going to be on that.
I'd...
We'll just jump out and surprise them
and then we'll get the jump on them.
Use any excuse to play hide and seek.
Yeah, he loves hide and seek, dude.
Is it?
Concealed amid their surroundings,
they elude the frustrated eyes of their enemy.
Choosing the moment to strike is up to them.
Wait for it.
Okay, we all begin in stealth and we have flanking attacks.
Nice.
Oh my god.
There are so many enemies.
So I think we are actually going to be controlling the farmers too, I think.
There's one up there.
Are there any in this room or no?
No, no, no.
We...
I think they were going to be coming from the top of the screen.
Oh, no, they're not.
There's some below us too.
Oh, shit.
Where?
Oh, yeah, they're out down there.
All right.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna make my way over there.
Oh, god.
Okay.
There's a huge guy over here.
Oh, there's a lot...
Oh, wait, where?
On the right.
Is he down by me?
Oh, yeah, I see him.
You want me to move to intercept?
We should probably prioritize this guy
because I think there's enough...
We have barricades, right?
Sacrifice as many villagers as you can.
Wait, are you throwing the villages at the...
Oh, fuck!
I didn't mean to do that.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I thought I was...
All right, all right.
We're okay.
I didn't realize I had all control of these people.
We just can send them anywhere, really.
We have control.
Yeah, use them to block the barricades.
Just have...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
File the bodies.
Oh, no.
Oh, my god.
Wait, what?
They just jumped over?
I intercepted him.
Nice.
Uh-oh.
Okay.
They come from inside the houses.
Oh, my god.
There's so many.
Uh, okay.
I...
I'm going to infuse the cart.
I'm going to try to do some damage over here.
I'm going to double infuse it.
No, I'm not.
See if I can hurt these guys over here.
Shit, it's not far enough.
Oh, there we go.
That didn't hurt that much.
Wait, which one did you hit?
Oh, back over there.
I'm going to move, except the big guy, I think.
Okay.
Uh, blocked.
Uh-oh.
He's going to eat you.
Bring this guy down here.
Yeah.
Good shot.
Oh, no.
No, kidding.
He's going to die.
There are a lot of people down here.
There's four enemies down here.
How many are up top?
There's two?
One?
There's one left.
Thomas got grabbed.
Oh, what do I do?
Can you run or are you rooted?
I don't think...
Am I not?
I don't know.
I don't...
I can't get over there.
Can I go in the door?
Can you...
Yeah.
Open the door and then run through.
All right.
I'm out of here.
I'm not fucking with that.
Oh, zoinks.
Yeah.
You guys do have like a Shaggy and Scooby vibe going on.
Shit.
Why did I shoot?
Oh, my God.
I'm an idiot.
Here we go.
All right.
I feel a little bit safer.
Okay.
Hard to tell who hasn't done things.
That's right.
It would just...
If someone hasn't acted,
it would just jump to them once you've like had the turn.
I think it's...
Their portrait is not...
It's just kind of lit up.
Yeah.
Let's get Katie to safety.
Is that right?
Oh, no.
Uh-oh.
Lost Staya.
Don't think we're...
Oh, no.
That's bad.
Okay.
Can you throw that whole barricade at them or something?
I can't select the barricade.
Let me see if I can just...
Let me walk back over here.
Okay.
I can...
All right.
I'm going to try to throw the barricade like you said.
Uh...
Blast.
What does this do?
All right.
I can do this.
This is going to hurt a lot.
Oh, nice.
Although I did get rid of the barricade.
I feel like that's bad.
Don't know if that's a good idea or not.
We turned our defense into offense.
Oh, my God.
There's a giant furnace.
I'm going to put her in front of you so you don't die.
Yeah, I need to move towards this fire
because I want to pull up next turn.
Wait.
Nice.
Oh, he was untouchable because I killed him.
Cool.
Uh-oh.
My blindness.
I can't select this.
Shit.
Sorry.
Ooh.
I love how the mage just kind of breaks objects in the world
and throws it at people.
Actually, that was...
We did a pretty good job.
Yeah, that was really good.
Thomas.
Level up.
Thomas has grown stronger.
OK.
I like this one.
Naturalist compulsion.
Oh, yeah.
You can move an enemy.
I like that.
I think that's very useful.
Cool.
All right.
So we quelled the invasion.
Now we're just going to finish building the bridge.
Let's finish building that bridge.
Yep.
I can't believe that's what we actually were doing.
Build the bridge for the enemy.
Yeah.
Year five.
OK.
So that's a...
It's a strength full or we can patrol and get it down.
I feel like we could maybe handle a strength full though.
I think so.
I think we're gods among men.
We're in year five at this point
because Alongus took us on a two-year round trip.
Sorry.
We learned a lot.
We...
Yeah, we did.
Got some stuff.
All right.
You finally get to be in the game.
So that's good.
Yeah.
Look.
I'm there.
Uh, you want me to keep going?
You were...
I was...
I'm chewing.
A ridge of limestone wraps the edge of Ghost Ring.
Find a way from this direction and you'd have the high ground.
You'd have surprise.
I don't know.
Looks impossible.
Possibly.
But limestone is a rock full of surprises.
After a few dead ends and false hopes.
I like that little snake.
Finally, a promising channel in the stone stretches out in the right direction.
Probably carved by an ancient stream.
See, limestone is a note worthy that when repeatedly exposed to water.
What?
Seems sturdy enough.
I think you just got trapped.
You got lost in a thought there and we just kind of just didn't even think to interject.
Yeah, his wolfy ramblings.
You doing okay back there?
It's kind of tight here, isn't it?
Not all of us are made of wet noodles and silk.
Some of us got...
Warrior shoulders.
Hey, perfect.
Here we are.
Couldn't ask for a better spot to emerge.
Just one last squeeze and it's a straight shot to Ghost Ring.
I mean, I could ask for a slightly better spot to emerge.
Maybe one that was a little bigger.
You're so hard for you to maneuver.
Should we pull him?
Should we grab him and pull him through?
You got this.
You're a panther.
You're...
If anyone asks, tell them I went down honorably.
You're not gonna die here, are you?
I have a 43% chance to push through or I'm literally gonna go around.
We have to push through.
I'm too stubborn.
You sure there's nothing we can do?
Standing back might be best.
And then twists and tightens in each turn.
I hope you lose the other eye.
Was damn right for a pubic.
All right, we did it.
Kill them.
Oh, our crit chance is doubled.
All right.
Also, yes, something you guys might not be aware of is if you stand next to each other,
you get like a defensive bonus.
You'll see like a little shield up here.
Oh, that's true.
Cohesiveness?
Yeah.
And I started blasting.
Oh, scalding rain.
Oh, this is gonna be insane.
All right.
Who am I doing this to?
You.
That was a pretty cool move.
It's because it's a well.
Oh, you heat it up with the fire stuff.
Okay.
Let's do it again.
Time for my secret move.
What does that do?
This makes you be able to move fast.
It's like an RP thing.
We get plus two movement, I think, when he howls.
That's helpful.
I'm going to do this fucking bite it.
It was a pig after all.
Oh, I was just keep doing it.
Oh, he blocked water.
Bullshit.
There's a lot.
Nice.
All right.
Now, I wish my name was cool like dogwood.
A snake stone sash.
Dodge plus five dodge.
Are you going?
My dodge is criminally low because I've got my big armor.
So I think it's kind of pointless for me to have it if Thomas wants it.
I'll take it.
Yeah.
Calamity.
All right.
Now, there's hordes of raccoons.
Yeah, the Gorgons are absolutely stacked right now.
Yeah, they are.
Okay.
Do you want to secure ghost ring to find an item or should we press on?
Oh, look.
All of the achievements have been done.
We can now assault life from where we can go all the way back.
Should we go?
I'd love a walk.
I think.
Yeah, let's go for it.
Do we want to get some items before we go?
By like securing.
I mean, there's no harm in securing, right?
Yeah, it's just a little bit more time passes.
It's okay.
I'm in the mood for some scaring and discovery.
We can sit in this place right as we go, can't we?
All right.
Yeah, let's find an item.
Might as well.
32 days.
That's a long time.
Keep your heroes busy.
Oh, we're not.
Okay.
There we go.
Oh, I see.
Oh, God.
Okay.
A little scary, but that's okay.
I think we can handle it.
Yeah.
Let them come.
It's a new faction that was.
Happy birthday, everybody.
Is it whose birthday?
Is there somebody's birthday in chat?
Happy birthday.
It strikes me how much there is still to find to know I am inspired.
Wood.
We got three wood and a gloom gloss strap, which is this is crit chance.
Fine.
Thank you.
Take it.
Oh, it is a is a wolfy thing, isn't it?
Excuse me.
We need before greed.
We need to need roll on that.
That's actually I was going to slash roll one to a hundred.
Whatever.
So we kind of messed up.
That's cool.
That's called ninja looting.
What you just did.
Well, you guys can have fun in dragon flight.
I don't have dragon flight.
Dude, I'm sorry.
I do, but I'd rather play Doctyde.
True.
None of us knew what had changed the beasts.
We could not change ourselves, so we blamed the beasts.
We knew something lived inside of them.
Blue burning hate that frenzied them, then left them still.
A stone sentence.
Worse and more deadly than any venom.
Today, we would finally find out where it came from and why it wouldn't stop.
Hold on.
Go back for a sec.
Like this is really framed.
Like you get a long shot from you.
Yeah.
We hired a ship photographer for our adventure.
Okay. Yeah, we can go.
Well, Lithgram Air Engine looks mostly intact.
Maybe the rumors aren't true.
It wouldn't make much sense given all we've seen.
Personally, I'm done expecting things to go smoothie.
Taps eye patch.
Yeah, I'm with you.
Why is this town named Lithgram Air Engine?
What the fuck is an air engine?
It's completely silent.
Except for this.
Oh, no, we have to explore the town.
That's literally our thing.
All right.
I'll check this house.
House looks good.
What's going on here?
I'll check the one on the right.
Anything in there?
Nothing.
Green bags.
Wait.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
Have the villagers turned to stone?
Look.
Oh, petrified.
Beyond our help now.
Yeah.
Oh, my goodness.
As horrific as it is fascinating.
What could have done this?
There's tracks.
They go up to that barn door.
Too many buildings around.
No idea what could be waiting for us.
And whatever did this could still be inside.
Hey, they come.
Stop doing the protagonist voice.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
I'm staying next to this fire.
I'm going to be throwing it to people.
I'm just going to wait here.
I'm going to extinguish the fire.
Don't do that.
I need.
Where are you going?
What are you thinking?
Perfect.
All right.
Who's priority?
What's priority here?
Probably the raccoons because they're ranged.
They're out of range for me here.
Wait, can I?
Wait, what did I do?
I'm going in.
Yeah, they're too far.
They're a little too far.
They need to be a little bit closer for this.
But I can do this.
I think you could walk and throw attached to the fire now.
Oh, I'm right.
I'm attached.
I forgot I could move.
For some reason, I thought I'd be still next to it.
All right, here we go.
I still can't.
Oh, maybe it's the limit.
Fire is the range.
OK, well, I'll just do this.
You eat almonds on stream.
A bunch of movement.
So I'm going to I'm just going to run over here.
All right.
Oh, everyone came to my rescue.
I want them to shoot me.
Oh, my God.
That was one hit kill.
It wasn't even your turn, right?
You just did that because it shot you.
Yeah, it was my first level up.
I guess because it shot him and we're connected that I'm able to shoot back.
I'm going to kill it.
It does.
I think I can hit this guy now.
He's just out of range.
Really?
Yeah, he's out of range still.
Let's wait till he gets closer.
Coming out.
Oh, good that you grabbed me.
All right.
There we go.
Oh, this is going to be big.
Instead of you.
How do you block fire?
It's an element.
I don't know, but I'm going to keep him here.
That was good.
Swap to the wand.
I have it out already, don't I?
Yeah, you have out.
Propaganda.
You got that raging coming in behind you as well.
I mean, look out behind you.
I'm going sicko mode.
All right.
Thornfang.
I wonder if we save these people.
Damn.
Oh, yellow knife.
Oh, whoa.
All right, I'm going to move.
I'm coming down here.
Thank you.
Why can't I use the fire?
When you use it, you threw the fire itself.
Oh, the fire itself was thrown.
All right, I'm going to move this one over here.
What do I want to move you to?
Never mind.
They're dead.
Really?
I can't really.
I guess I could infuse with like this.
I'm out of actions now.
Sicko mode.
How do you move people?
I wonder.
Oh, big damage.
OK, where was the bomb?
Because it was all the way to the right.
OK, let's start heading there.
I think that's where the beast will come from.
I got to defuse.
There's tentacles coming out of this thing.
It's probably going to be a boss in here.
Yeah.
I don't know if you guys want to get too close.
If you want to set up over there.
Sicko mode.
He's just going in.
I'm just I don't want to get hit by whatever opens this door.
OK, I think we I'm just going to wait a time and then we'll open next time.
Oh, the Gorgon.
The silent slithering approach fascinates the mind and haunts the heart.
Oh, shit.
OK.
Anything in there?
Let's find out.
Can't see anything.
12 health.
Wait, I think I think I can illuminate something.
I could try or I could just.
Oh, God.
I'm surrounded.
OK.
He fucked me.
Why did it so that I'd have him?
They got he dodged.
I guess.
Yeah.
No, I gain an action when I kill things, but that's probably better.
Oh, I've got you, Thomas.
Nice.
Remember when I was a guy.
Come on, guys.
Finish him.
I tried to move him.
Wait, did you see that?
You did a big amount of damage.
No, because it attacked Thomas last time.
He got plus four damage for lover's vengeance.
Yeah, I've been getting that.
Really?
Yeah.
I fucking love you, dude.
Let's give that to Thomas because that will take his bonus damage up by one.
Mario noise.
Did I just do a Mario noise?
I'm a Blue Horn warrior.
OK.
I can force a photo attack me.
My melee attacks just deal one damage.
That sounds pretty good.
My melee attacks deal more based on the health I'm missing.
These all sound kind of good.
Yeah, I kind of like viciousness.
Just one more damage.
You never go wrong with extra damage.
Sentinel looks like if I charge someone, it steals their movements.
They can't get to you guys.
But if you just kill them.
Yeah, you're right.
That could have gone worse.
Yeah, but it's certainly not your standard plow mule.
The hulking carcass steams from its many wounds.
Hideous convulsions course along its appendages to the extremities of its body.
Then why you know the things tremendous tail flicks across the barn.
It plucks up in on like he's a straw doll.
His weapons falling uselessly from his hands as it pulls him in.
Don't panic.
A voice leaks from a non's mouth.
It's a wrong voice.
Weird and discordant, like some fretting and plucking in a fiddle.
Who's ever picked one up?
Still yourselves, bone stacks.
This one speaks my words.
I shoot him.
I can make it die.
You are not alike to us.
Weak lungs, small minds.
Stacks of splintering bones.
Thin blood that will so readily betray you.
Why flail for your lives?
So noisy.
Be wise now.
Will you survive if you hurt him?
You think I flail for life as you do?
I am Gorgon.
The master Ulsterix has promised us silence.
The voice dissolves into a sound like rain or distant waves.
Wriggling grips tighten.
A tentacle invades in his ear.
Stop.
I really gave that one my all.
Thomas leaps forward in an instant.
Rusty saw leaps off the iron book hooks.
Metal ribbiting and rippling loudly.
Stop, I said.
Are you using your magic power to throw a sword?
The saw slices into the neck of the great beast.
As the longest rushes over to make certain of the Gorgon's-
Wait, go back a scene, go back a scene.
Look what happened to my face.
Look at the blue on my face.
Yes, you're going to be the next Marvel hero.
Is this my origin story?
Your eye's going to grow back.
As the longest rushes over to make certain of the Gorgon's demise,
Thomas supports Inon, helping him to stand.
Somebody said, you're only useful in cutscenes.
I'm doing okay, all right?
You're okay.
A strange stony affliction spreads from Inon's ear.
Inon?
This isn't over.
I saw his mind.
The stone was in his heart.
Inon takes the stone from a longus's palm,
turning it in front of his eyes,
catching the slender sunbeams that slice the barn wall.
The strange, polyhedral stone is slick with the Gorgon's blood.
Epichrist.
Each face is graven with an intricate image.
The word in the Gorgon's head was epichrist.
This tan, livergram air engine.
These petrified people, even this monster,
they're insignificant in the coming epoch.
The epichrist glistens, sticky and blue.
The Gorgons have a master.
Ulstrix, it's called.
He's looking for something, some myth or secret.
I think the riddle is in the stone.
I think we have to find out what he wants.
And make sure he doesn't get it.
I think we should, we all I think said that collectively.
Yeah.
So I lost a bunch of charisma because I got a fucked up face
and became a gigaloner.
And Thomas gained 10 years on his career.
That works for me.
One of us came off better.
Okay, so that is chapter one done.
So now it kind of tells us all the resources
and it says 10 years of peace follow.
10 years of peace.
Yeah, we did that.
So we lose some cards.
They lose some cards because 10 years of peace.
During the years of peace.
What happened?
The Gorgon's Mark grew and crusted over to cover one side of Inan's face.
It would be a grim reminder of the encounter that day
in the lithogram air engine barn.
Good job I'm blind on that side.
Yeah, that's true.
On his more civilized days,
Alongus would drop into town for gossip and tool repairs.
But on the whole, he felt clear headed among his wilder kin.
Now that the job wasn't quite as dangerous,
Alongus became a guide to travelers
crossing the more treacherous stretches of the swamp and the mountain.
Thomas and Alongus were married and one winter night
they held an ancient and evocative ceremony that Alongus had read of.
A feast followed.
The people of Sleeping Top were startled but pleased at the generosity.
Thomas displayed that night.
Alongus would always remember the moment
like a scene brought to life from history, from legend.
And he, he and Thomas indelibly written into the world's pages.
Transformations.
You have a choice to advance Alongus's transformation and get a wolf arm.
You'll be able to get a wolf claw for five to eight damage.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, you got like a whole inventory page, yeah.
Yeah, so basically you can see our current resources in the top left
and then we can click whichever player we want
and we can kind of kit them out.
With new upgrades.
So if we wanted to make you like a tier two bow
it would use up four hotwoods, an ingot, a hide, a fabric.
We could craft it and then give it to you.
So it's kind of like what are we missing?
What do we need?
That kind of thing.
I would say looking at our stuff
Thomas is the only one that doesn't have any armor.
So maybe we-
I don't, yeah.
Like maybe we click this and maybe we want to craft Thomas like a dusty drab
or an ember gown.
Which one of these like do you like the look of?
Let's see.
And so for every piece of like resource we're missing
we can spend an LP.
So we only have one fabric
but we can use an LP to make an extra fabric.
So these two star ones are expensive.
Yeah, we can click it and look.
So that would be- it would cost us three LP
but I think that's fine if you wanted to go for that.
I mean this drab, this two star drab seems like it's pretty good.
Three armor, two warning, one spell damage.
All right, yeah.
So just click craft.
Oh yeah.
Let's go.
There you go.
Snare your kid out.
Sweet.
So we've got a bunch of stuff left.
Let's have a look what we could do.
Would you rather have like a bow over like armor?
I want a dueling sword so I can be a rapier wielding wolf.
It just makes sense.
Okay.
As a ranger you can use a dueling sword up here
so we can make the giant scratch.
Yeah.
Or we could make the dueling sword.
There's only one damage difference
and this one cost nine.
I'm making it.
Okay, you're making the tier two or the tier one?
Tier two.
You have such a cool character.
Okay.
And on go first.
I think Anna needs just a big weapon.
I think I need a better than this spear.
What we got?
I'm thinking like a gray axe or something.
Ooh, like a mace maybe?
Do we have a hammer?
Yeah, gray axe or a great sword.
You think I'm more of a hammer guy or do you think I'm like a...
I don't know.
I feel like this is a hammer.
You're going to turn into a golem.
Golems are required by law to use hammers and maces.
That's just how it goes.
Golem with an axe, you're going to get laughed at.
Although great axe works too.
If we craft this we can only make the tier one rapier though.
We can't have that.
Star has to have the best weapon.
That's fine.
The mountain break.
That's what it's named.
I'm going to reroll it.
Tower sludger.
Yes.
Ooh.
Okay.
And then we've got this boy.
We can actually...
So you want a dueling sword?
We can make you a dueling sword and we could also make you a tier two crossbow.
Oh, I got disconnected.
We're out of money for ingots.
Why did I get disconnected?
We can use LP though.
I don't know.
Why are you running?
We can save and remake.
I think you could just rejoin actually.
Can I just rejoin?
I think so.
Let me try and rejoin.
Okay, disconnect.
It's thinking.
I think it might be crashing.
Okay.
Should I just do play or my legacy?
There's this play and there's also my legacy.
Do I have to select that character maybe?
I'm not sure.
I think we can remake the lobby.
I can just save and we can remake it.
Okay.
Let's let our boy build what he needs though.
I finished building that.
I clicked next.
Okay, let's do...
Okay.
Last save was three seconds ago.
Steam maintenance Tuesday.
Oh, that's what it is.
Is that what it actually is?
It's going to get all of us, yeah.
Oh, no.
It only takes like five minutes or so.
Yeah.
Five minute break.
I don't know if you guys can even see this or if I can save.
I don't...
Boy, you know, Strippin was the leader, I think.
So do you...
Save and quit is currently grayed out.
But it saved 30 seconds ago.
So...
So are all of our characters on your kind of client side
or do we have those here on ours?
I wonder.
I believe it's just on mine because I'm hosting.
Yeah.
So we can just remake it but...
Okay.
Yeah, we can just wait for a steam maintenance, I guess.
Is that actually what happened or can people confirm that
or are people just being goofy?
I'm online.
I don't know if you're offline on Steam or if you live time.
I know.
Somebody said, I got it too.
It's real.
I got it.
Okay.
Let's see.
Friends.
Yeah, it says I'm disconnected.
Let me try to get back in.
I'm going to add you to friends anyway.
Steam.
Oh, okay.
I can't even add you as a friend.
Good old Steam Maintenance Tuesday.
Oh, yeah.
The thing is like this has been happening consistently on a Tuesday for like 10 years
and every week I forget it exists until it happens.
Seriously, same thing.
I think I actually had a meltdown on stream one time
where I said I would never be live ever again
between like 12 and 5 p.m. on Tuesday ever again.
I think I say that every single Tuesday this happens.
Next week you were live between 12 and...
This is what I'm saying.
Like it's time to go to the...
Let's all go to the Epic Games Store.
Gamers rise up.
I'm going to go pee.
I'll be back.
Okay.
Hopefully it comes right back and doesn't...
Because sometimes it takes like 30 plus minutes.
Wait, really?
This happened before, yeah.
We'll find out.
I'll be right back.
Hold on.
Ashley called me two hours ago?
Okay.
Weird.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
So how long is Dr. Ted down for?
When does it come out?
I thought it would have come out in like an hour.
Back to the little stream.
10 a.m. PST tomorrow.
That's my stream start time.
The second Mario movie trailer was fun.
Does Mario still sound like Linda from Bob's Burgers?
Oh, yes.
I have such a luscious beard.
Thank you.
You have such a luscious beard.
Are you guys enjoying the stream?
Why'd you ignore me?
Thanks, man.
I feel like we're having a really great adventure.
I feel like...
Chad did a prediction on who was going to be the third whale
and it has 100% ended up being me.
It was inevitable.
You guys literally got married.
We really got like one romance option
and I was like, okay, let's get married.
Like four years ago, I was a little bit saucy
and it just from there was obvious.
Yeah, you're a little bit handsy like five years ago.
I just like complimented him like one time.
I think I don't even remember.
Yeah, it was getting super fun.
I slept on.
Remember when you stripped for charity on the Oaks Coast a decade ago?
I do.
I don't.
I don't have that memory.
Yes, you do.
I did not know about that,
but I'm going to be Googling that intensively tonight.
Tonight?
Yes.
You would be cheating on Thomas.
He doesn't care.
Are you sure?
Have you asked him?
When he comes back, we can ask him
how seriously he's taking our relationship.
How do you guys make out?
You're a wolf.
You know, you don't have to kiss to show affection
and I've got one human arm.
I just use that.
You guys like Eskimo kiss?
Like touch noses?
No, I sniff his behind.
Oh, oh.
Just keep it real.
You know, just keep it 100.
Yeah.
Staying true to me.
Is it back?
Looks like Steam is back.
Okay.
Nuzzles you.
Wait.
Yeah, nuzzles you.
It looks like it's back.
What?
What are you doing?
I'm nuzzling you.
He's nuzzling you.
Oh, I didn't know who you were talking to.
Oh, we're married, dude.
I don't even know.
All right.
Okay.
This is what married couples do.
So should we just try and remake, I guess?
I guess.
It looks like we're back, right?
Yeah.
It won't let me save and quit though
because we're like stuck in a story thing.
Should we just try to join off you again?
Yeah. Did you add me?
Let's see.
You might on Steam.
That is a great question considering I, dude,
I don't know how to even do that anymore.
Oh, okay.
If you open your friends list in the top right,
it says like add friends like a little man with a plus sign.
And then you just pop my friend code in there.
Oh, cool.
I haven't done this in a long time.
Okay.
That's you.
Send invite.
Show auto?
No, I'm not going to show auto.
Hang it out down.
Okay.
And then invite to lobby.
Let's see if this works.
He's down that way.
He's down there.
I'm not going to go.
Invite works.
Show auto.
No, I don't want to go get auto.
He's probably comfortable.
Did you say you tried to invite me?
Yeah, I'm in there.
I don't see an invite.
You don't?
I do not.
You mean like on like the Steam kind of like boom,
you got invited to something?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, I'm ice cream sandwich, by the way, just in case.
I sent you an invite to lobby.
Can you join game with me?
That's what I'm trying to do here.
Yeah, let's see.
Let's say join game.
Let's get started.
I think we can just auto forward.
Yeah, I'm just going to restart the game.
I think that maybe when it was the Steam maintenance happened,
it maybe has to be rebooted or something.
Thank you, Gaben.
You know what?
It's what?
Three o'clock in the afternoon Pacific,
like right in the middle of the day.
Time.
Let's say it's an inconsiderate time.
That's what it is.
How dare they?
I'm just kidding.
All right.
I'm back in.
Let's see if I can join you.
Okay.
I'm actually going to.
All right.
I am trying to join you right now.
I'm remaking the game.
Otto's comfy gaming in his gaming room.
Okay.
You should be.
You should be able to join me.
I made a friend's lobby and then I'll load the.
Hey, I can see it.
Yep.
There it is.
All right.
Hey, there we go.
I'm in.
Yeah, you're in this.
Okay.
He's not.
I can't see the current panel, though.
It's like blank.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
We made the lobby.
Oh, what the hell am I in?
I don't know.
You know, I don't want to know.
Yeah, sir.
I had to restart my whole game for it to show up if you didn't do that yet.
Uh, can you like settle down?
Yep.
I'm good.
Hold on.
I'm going to restart my game.
You might be on to something.
Wait, are you restarting or are you good?
I'm restarting.
Man, that's as beautiful as the song we sung together.
I wonder how that actually turned out.
All right.
I wonder, were we even matching the same tempo?
I who could.
All right.
Let's get back in here.
Can you see it?
I hope so.
I see like a blue screen with leaves.
Mine's blue.
Gray.
All right.
New threats.
Oh, yeah.
We missed the whole thing then because the last one was talking about like trying to figure out
what the crystal meant.
I feel like that might be a way to go back and watch it.
It's possible it just got kind of sniped from the steam going down.
That's all right, though.
We can just fill in the blanks.
Wow.
What does this thing do?
Well, we know you guys.
We know you guys got married.
We know that I was just a loner for a long time.
So look at that.
We have to go investigate Lambstream Altar.
Yes.
How do we reliably get there?
We're down from sleeping top?
Yeah.
We're back in thunder roast now.
This seems treacherous.
I feel like this is a treacherous way to go.
Yeah.
I think we go into the Dachia Forest, right?
That's our next play.
I think that's the play.
Okay.
We all aged 10 years.
So now I'm 39.
I've got gray in my hair.
What does it say?
What does it show your age?
No, no.
Yeah.
If you hover over yourself, it'll tell your age.
It's weird.
If you look at my portrait, I've got gray in my hair.
Hang on.
I've got side quests.
I'm the youngest.
Not one for festivals.
What's the point?
No one's having conversations.
Just songs.
And I don't like songs now.
Yeah.
I thought you loved songs.
I am over songs.
Once I went on a two-year trip to sing one.
Yeah.
I actually feel the same.
I love how the panel just completed your other arm.
But I'm trying to do my community spirit.
Right.
Yeah.
I've gained my chance then.
Might be stimulating.
Later.
That was damn right uncanny.
It was lucky.
Honestly though, do you have a secret?
I've never seen someone roll that well.
No secret.
I'll get on these streaks sometimes.
Cars, dice, coins.
But now that you mention it, I've always wondered what would
happen if we were just to pick a direction.
A direction?
Just pick a direction and go.
If I'm really on a hot streak, well, I bet we'll find a magic item.
Magic item?
Seriously?
You really are Scooby-Doo.
Write him.
Okay.
We're all going.
Let's go.
We're just going to pick a direction.
Apparently.
My trip took us like three days.
I see the edge of the forest.
Oh, I saw this forest as an edge.
That's nice.
What the hell was that?
Everything has an edge.
Including my patients.
It's like Yoda too.
Look, it was a joke in the first place, wasn't it?
Keep walking until we find a what.
Why would someone do that?
Just walk around and wander for no reason.
Nice to take a little trip with a trip.
Well, hang on a minute.
I've walked for two years for you.
You have no legs to stand on here.
I'm not seeing the point of this trip.
I don't understand.
Well, at least check out that castle first.
That's so funny.
Look.
Why are you huge?
I'm huge.
I'm giant.
Where there's presumably a magic item.
Follow me, Alungus.
Yeah, I'm getting bigger.
You look pissed.
You do not want to be here right now.
All right, Gemma, what are we doing?
Are we going in the front or are we climbing a window or a ledge?
Make Alungus climb.
I think that's funnier.
They climb through a crumbling window.
You certainly like to make things hard.
Oh, you're behind my arm.
I'm thorough.
Always start at the top of a problem and work your way down.
Goes for castles too.
Well, fine.
That makes some sense, I guess.
I'll have to tell the age.
These double beams are a hallmark of even way to build her.
She's 200 years dead.
Your neck seems a little stiff.
So does yours.
There's a pretty big gap you can see to the lower level.
Well, this stuff's more recent.
What stuff?
Stop.
Stop that.
Little trove collected from who knows where.
Does it look magical?
Not even a tiny bit.
That's the first time I've been happy.
You probably found a bone.
Tell you what though, it does look guarded.
Took you that long to see that thing in the room with you guys?
Yeah, it was there the whole time.
It was there the entire time.
The butler.
Look at this thing.
Oh my God.
All right, what do we got?
Look at Thomas, how much magic armour he has.
I know, I'm unstoppable.
Actually, I'm going to move again.
I want to get closer.
This thing's got a lot of health, by the way.
Pop them.
Nice.
Thomas, if you take damage, I'll get upset.
All right.
Well, that was a barrel mode.
11 damage.
Holy shit.
It's remarkable to find one alone like this.
Up here would be curious what directed its decision.
If decision is even the right word.
Well, let's not razz more of them, eh?
We can grab some of these materials.
Right.
That's what I mean.
And then back where we came.
A short while later.
So looks like I won the bet.
Seems you did.
You guys were betting?
What do I owe you now?
Socks?
No socks.
What you failed to mention is a size.
My neck!
On the journey back, my neck breaks.
There's a tea house not far.
Uh, hold on, but socks?
There are different socks sizes?
I thought it was just like a pair of socks.
It's like universal, isn't it?
Like size, like five through like 14 or something?
How would a size 14 foot fit in a size five sock?
I don't know.
Aren't socks like just one size?
No, it's the way like they're like brackets.
So like a size will be like 10 to 13.
And then like really nine to five and then like four to one.
Yeah.
Is that why sometimes I get fucking fucked up socks that just don't fit?
I thought it was just like medium, like medium or big.
I didn't know they had whatever.
I'm not kidding.
I swear to God.
This makes perfect sense.
I share socks with my four-year-old daughter.
Yeah.
No, I just, I, I.
My size 13 feet.
Dude, I have a pair.
I have socks and I was trying to figure out why the fuck this happened.
I'm not kidding.
This is a real story.
Every single pair of socks that I own has a huge hole in both feet at the bottom.
And it's in the same exact spot.
And it's definitely because I bought like socks that were way too small.
That's ridiculous.
I can't believe it.
Yeah.
You might have to buy new socks, but you didn't win the bet.
So I thought, man, and you missed black Friday.
They don't make it in time, but are soaked in the storm.
But the tea house is dry.
The fragrant teas and later the mugs of mold whiskey are hot.
Hot whiskey is the thing.
Yeah.
Hot whiskey is amazing.
You never had it?
You've had, you've ever had hot whiskey?
Had some honey.
Do you actually, have you had it a lot before?
I haven't had it before.
I'm not speaking to you.
No, there's one more round.
It's something I have whenever I'm like, I catch a cold or something.
I mean, America has hot toddies, but I think they're a bit different in America.
But hot toddies and I don't think, I don't think in America when we get sick,
I don't think we drink alcohol.
Hot toddies like England Island is like whiskey with honey.
And that's like it.
And some lemon.
Really?
Yeah.
And it's really good.
That sounds pretty good.
Hot whiskey.
Yeah.
I've never had it.
I'm curious if you had it.
That's cool.
Thinking about something.
Just rain.
Rain and all these nine mystical phenomena that paint our lives.
That we try to explain into mundanity so we can take them for granted.
You don't know what rain is.
What's rain?
Rain, but also all this stuff.
I don't know.
Think back to our journey's beginning.
Fortune is the spur of the moment that strikes restless hearts and sparks an adventure.
Luck is the people you share it with.
If I didn't know the crap.
I'm not as drunk as you yet.
Just one more.
All right.
I thought that was a sandwich.
You feel like you're getting hungry?
Oh, you leveled up.
Nice.
Plus 10 more time and age.
Okay.
And then gets two extra armor.
And I might just take two extra armor.
Every other turn as a swift action and then sheds two of a foe's armor.
Now, let's do it.
I want to be tankier.
Let's do that.
Okay.
They're shifting over to the Mortha.
How is it?
Morthagy?
Morthaguy?
What are you?
What's going on, man?
Is he having a seizure?
No.
The name of the groups, like the Gorgons.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I see what you're saying.
All right.
So you can see in Brandland as a recruit opportunity.
So if we had someone die or your character like had lost both his arms,
we could replace someone in our party and like recruit someone new.
If we recruit someone new, we would actually be the Fabulous Four.
We would.
But then it wouldn't be funny anymore.
I don't like that.
Yeah.
I think we should just like go past it and scout.
We're going to Dachia Forest.
Sounds good.
Dismiss.
Three more days remaining.
Oh, till the end.
Oh, no.
Great.
Okay.
Let's go.
What if we just wandered around for a bit?
Oh, event.
Oh, I have lost eyes, throwing them irretrievable upon the sea.
I have drowned my voice in those wailing waters.
Ochre at sunset.
The waves distance has washed my memories away.
I have seen the end, watched it come and watched it pass many times.
I know something of what lies ahead.
Along us and Thomas wait for Inon to come up the road,
taking shelter in an abandoned place.
They've chanced on another traveler.
That's a tantalizing crumb.
I don't want to do every single thing.
I was waiting.
I'm going to be the spooky lady.
I was hoping you were going to do all of them.
All right.
To someone who little knows the weight of knowledge, I am sure it appeals.
You must realize the only-
What has a star ever told me
that made me want less to know it?
Rain chatters on the thatch.
I see things written in the turning of storms,
in silver-wet letters and shaking pages of rain.
I read of dreams left behind this yondering.
I read of dooms the year is intent.
I read until my eyes shine and my stomach roars.
I have read of you.
I know what you are meant to be.
A dog.
You meant to be a full dog.
Not sure I believe in faute.
No one demands you believe.
You only must endure what happens.
The old storage building smells like ancient hay,
moist rock,
and the burning pine pitch of their torch.
The woman's robe moves like it's part of her.
She shrugs.
It's going to be really hard for me to continue
because I just looked over at my chat
and I just see Stewie being spammed
and it's like ruining everything.
Put the fingers together right now.
Fortunes.
I think you're doing a really good voice here.
Fortunes were given to crows to tell,
and crows were kind enough to share their gift with witches.
A witch, well paid,
shares fortunes with the way blind, Brian.
I'll give you my blood.
Wait, another transformation?
Another transformation.
For you?
Yeah, do it, man.
What are you going to turn into?
Then you have already glimpsed the form
your roving spirit must take.
You have seen it in your sleep
and it will not shatter you.
I dream that I don't see it.
I sort of insist on the different units.
You go winged but never flying.
Fast but rarely flinging.
Your wander leads you to things you never thought you chased.
Along us.
Thought we agreed I would be the one who you confided in.
The rain will pause.
I just ignore you.
Huh?
I just ignore Thomas.
I mean, I didn't even look at you.
The rain will pause in the morning.
Do not worry much,
for you will love yourself.
Lonelier though it may make you.
By the way, there was a queen in my dream last night.
In case that's important.
She halts momentarily.
The stillness of a startled bird.
Some dreams are only flights of fancy.
No, but like there was also a king and a castle
and there was these giant motorized vehicles with tires.
The night elapses.
The rain sounds like a river of dragonflies flowing by.
Snoring thunder is occasional and soft.
Growing ever more distant.
Along us.
And Thomas.
Sleep at some point.
Taking turns.
Am I just stuck out in the rain?
Yeah.
I think you're in the rain.
This is my life.
I'm such a disgusting loner.
The woman walks out into the pale predawn.
Without a sound or a pain.
Or any observed moment of metamorphosis.
Along us wakes up.
Boing.
You have crow wings on your back?
What's happening to you?
They'll continue on to word hero index.
Is that the name of a town?
It's a random town.
Yeah, they just randomly name them.
Word hero index.
Hey Thomas, there you are.
Along us with you.
Couldn't find you in the rain.
That's a camp.
What the fuck is out on your back?
I'm a bird dog.
Fight.
Time to dry out these wings.
So now you have wings.
Your character is so much cooler than all everything.
Thomas is just normal guy in a robe.
Yeah.
I'm like, I've got like a stone face.
And along us is like a winged wolf.
Can I get like laser eyes or something eventually here?
I don't think it does anything.
All right.
So maybe maybe increases your movement or something.
I don't know.
So what are we?
We've been attacked or something?
I kicked the door open.
Oh god.
Oh, okay.
I just walked back and forth like an idiot.
Does your sentinel trigger if they walk up to you?
Or they have to walk by?
If they move within two spaces, I'll run.
So if they move, I'll run into the building.
So if you want like a defense bonus to be next to Thomas.
All that.
Dogged.
Alarm.
Damn, you guys really just do.
You guys just crush.
Stormthroat bird?
What the fuck did you do to me?
One shred damage at the start of every turn.
Oh, wait, I can shoo the bird away.
My turn.
There we go.
I just smashed that.
There could have been a device in there.
There could have been like a weapon button.
I can't really get in there.
I can move.
Let's go up here.
Well, I think I need.
I guess I could take the axe out.
They're leaving you in the yard.
An alarm.
So I think something's gonna come.
They're not leaving.
Guys, I am like the casters support.
I am not supposed to be up there fighting.
I'm supposed to be back throwing fireballs at walls and collecting stones and stuff.
Oh, shit.
I will block his route to you.
Oh, that's so you don't want to be next to the bench.
You fool.
You what have you done?
Actually, I'm going in.
Oh, my God.
There's more than one.
All right.
I have to get in here because I can't target anything.
Hey, there's nothing in this room, guys.
You're just alone in there.
But plus 35 to Lona, I remember.
Oh, you guys go.
You guys got the easy.
Oh, good.
You talk about how much damage we do and then you just do the same damage.
Yeah, but I need a network to attack people.
Yeah, that's true.
You got like a big spider web going.
Yeah.
Well, my character is actually bottom tier.
You shaker of traction.
It's a new one that also contains a melee strike.
If they get too close, you can probably replace the axe with a melee one.
Yeah, I wonder because that's just spell.
Is it more spell damage than the wand?
Yeah, it gives you plus two spells.
I wonder if the spell damage like applies even if you're not using it.
I wonder.
We'll find out.
What's that over there?
Are you OK?
Swooping in like vultures.
They killed everyone.
My friends, my family.
I don't know why these aren't like voice dialogues.
He's I don't know why I was there.
And I've lost track of time.
Perhaps they meant to keep me as a meal.
I have no family to go back to.
I have nothing.
Don't force me back to that empty village.
Take me with you instead.
Let me seek your vengeance by your side.
OK, so we can either bring him with us
and cost two legacy points
and then we have a fourth character forever
that someone has to control.
I refuse or we can just turn him down
and leave him in the ruins of his village.
All right.
I mean, I guess it's been decided.
Revengeance will only eat away at you
and it's not a good reason to leave your home.
Maybe you're right.
Gave up so fast.
The end.
What a loser.
He's not cut out for this life.
He's not.
All right.
Should we find an item?
Wait, we don't have much time there, right?
Should we just?
We we're out.
Yeah, we have only like 295 days
before the world collapses or whatever happens.
We're just going to rush from town to town.
I have a wild suggestion.
OK, what if we just go to like the nicest town
and just hang out for 300 days to hang out with you anymore?
You're a crow wolf.
Everyone's afraid of you.
OK, I've got one.
What's your favorite fruit?
Never have a cliff cherry.
They're rare, but worth splurging on at least once in your life.
What's happening to Thomas's voice?
He's he didn't age like 20 years or something.
Oh, you did age 10 years.
Yeah, I mean, a little bit gray in your hair.
That's a little older.
Yeah.
All right.
Hold on.
I'll fix it.
Careful there.
Your fancy taste is showing.
Next up, a difficult one.
Favorite thing to fight.
What?
That's like asking my favorite rash.
Least favorite, then.
Is that because they're over the next hill?
It's the ick factor and even worse than frixel.
They don't taste bread and they're like walking diseases.
And here I am making a career.
I feel like you should start adding some crows to your.
You are really trying to get this callback for this role, by the way.
Yeah.
I wonder if the casting director is going to call you back.
This guy wants to be a dog so bad.
Sometimes I wonder if it's not too late to start over somewhere.
I wouldn't know realistically.
Why are we talking about our favorite foods?
Well, we appreciate that.
I turned it.
What's your favorite food into like my life doesn't mean anything anymore.
Maybe I can start over.
Maybe it's not too late.
Oh, Cliffberries.
I'm half wolf quarter bird.
What about you?
What keeps you on this mortal plane?
I can't last another day.
The opportunity to make history.
Honestly, the gear.
You mean other than you.
The face is too good.
I'm like rejecting you.
We're married.
And you're cringing.
You're visibly cringing.
Why are you cringing?
Yeah, he's doing like a wolf cringe.
You should not be cringing to this.
So many things, really.
That laughy form.
That dazzling smile.
The way you whisper my name before a fight.
Okay, I got to do that from now on.
That's not an answer.
That's random flattery.
He's just power game dude to whispering his name before a fight.
Plus, what kind of man would I be if I left you to get picked up by some beefy Gorgon?
I just said Gorgons are my least favorite enemy.
True.
Come hither.
Away from those tentacles.
And I'm toast.
Oh, wait, you're a hentai guy?
Thomas and Longus gain temporary damage and potency.
Dude, I'm going to be so low in the night.
Oh, Thomas.
Oh, get the squirrel.
Wait, are we?
Get the squirrel.
Check it out.
Squirrel.
Where's the squirrel?
Get the squirrel.
We're ready to go.
I need to...
Do you want a water crossbow or a water dueling sword?
Can we give you like water legs or something?
Can you transform again?
I feel like Thomas's side quest is going to be so mundane.
He's going to be like, hey, do you guys want to play Uno?
And then we just play Uno.
Well, yeah, wasn't your original side quest that you had, wasn't it?
Oh, let's play Dice for five minutes.
Yeah, yeah, it was.
Okay, you got Spineful, the water crossbow.
I renamed it to Doomsday of Doombow.
Interesting.
All right, using.
I'm about to die, by the way.
All right.
We're in the middle of a battle.
You need to focus.
Oh, my one eye.
Sorry, I got the bucket.
All right, I'm going to...
Oh, I can do Shackle.
Sick.
All right, I just heard these crow sounds.
I thought that was your character.
Oh, wait, if anything attacks Thomas, you get plus four damage.
Yeah.
Really?
Yeah, we've been over this.
Love is vengeance.
I think we're just rolling balls of infinite damage.
We're pretty strong, actually.
That's what I'm saying.
Like, let's just wait 300 days.
No, that would be...
Oh, oh.
I got him.
You got him?
Oh, my.
You killed him in one hit.
Nice.
I do have a really big habit.
Take this.
Time for the melee wand.
There we go.
Can I do this through walls?
Probably not.
That was a really stupid question.
No, you're not stupid.
Stupid, honey.
Thanks.
I appreciate it.
Dude, Thomas is falling behind.
I'm all right.
Another crit chance.
We all have a slot, right?
Yeah, it's going to take you past 20.
That's pretty good.
I'll take it.
It's not color, is it?
Because we know who that would have been for.
Do you remember...
Do people still do this in WoW?
I haven't really played it too intently or deeply,
but I remember back in the day,
everyone always agreed that you don't need...
You need, you know, greed, right?
If you don't need it,
you just greed it or you pass on it, right?
Is this those people in the five mans
that just need every single item?
This is...
You got a custom quest?
Yeah, this is what it is.
Thomas and Inon are called to a hill village
where an acquaintance of theirs has lost her wife.
After this rain comes, the farms will prosper again.
Not if there's no farmers left.
It's been a dry fall.
That's all I mean.
The funerary rites are brief.
The crowd that's gathered is impressive.
Such a small town.
As mourners disperse,
Thomas and Inon spot Baladchi
standing by a flower-strung cart
bearing a leaf-shrouded body.
Baladchi.
We're sorry to hear about Arthel.
Who are these people?
A lot of folks came.
Do we not...
Wait, have we been here before?
How many years has it been?
No, we haven't.
I think we walked through this place during the...
Up the road to her home on the hill.
Oh gee, you lose perspective sometimes.
Easy enough to do, sadly.
You think you all have years together.
Decades.
From your first hike to your middle years.
Old age.
Then.
And but...
Mickey Mouse?
Yeah.
To help Baladchi transfer the shrouded body
to a small prepared clay room
besides the house.
They settle inside
and she tells them of her plan.
One of the provincial customs she's observing.
Oh gee, Green Valley is called
a woven shrouded dawnshard.
Dawnshard grows thick around here.
In little woodlands you'll see
there's a strong aroma.
The body stays fresh
sometimes as long as four years or five.
By the way, you are just doing the other voice
but without the wolf on it.
Oh yeah, I'm just having a little bit of...
Just doing this one hair.
Keep hiking, man.
Keep it up.
We help folks genuinely build a wide shroud
as it means she'd be buried.
There's something very silencing in that.
I think it's a good tradition.
But I don't plan on waiting.
You don't?
Plan's a wait.
So you plan to bury her soon?
Tonight even?
No.
My wife, I already settled
and I will be going on a journey.
Hope you'd come along.
Brack.
Hard, sudden rain falls.
Chittering and droning like a swarm.
Is Andy what they're calling me over here?
Giving out advice?
What?
People calling me two-voice Andy
giving out vocal advice.
They're saying how I should not be giving you
voice tips because I have three voices.
I mean, you're going to criticize...
You're going to come at me
and I'm the one...
I'm doing it.
Would you like to take over?
Yeah.
Yes, I hope you'd come.
Be our escort.
It's a dangerous world.
And you're both strong.
Stronger than...
Stronger than I even remembered.
Stop doing that to me.
It's making me angry.
This doesn't represent me.
Oh, all right, fine.
Let's do stirr's voices.
I'll come along with you.
I'm going to get a little bit of protection.
Me too.
I have no idea what happened in that whole encounter.
It was apparently...
It's a friend of Thomas.
Her wife died and she asked us to escort the body in a wagon.
Just west of Nightgrave Threshery,
Baldashi leads her oxen cart,
carrying the body of her wife down through the hills
into the arms of an old forest.
Mist rolls in as twilight takes hold.
Behind a cloudy sky.
This forest was named Lagannet when it was on the maps.
Absent forest it meant.
It's not an encouraging name.
Can I ask about Arthel?
I don't think either of us have ever met her.
You missed your other character.
Place...
Place I'm...
Place I'm looking...
Place I'm looking for shouldn't be...
You do it.
I remember you talking about her.
Sleeping type.
Always wanted her to but she was never quiet and well enough.
And she insisted on staying home to tend the farm.
We met in the spring.
I remember clearly.
My grandma had just passed.
It sounds like Hubert from Family Guy.
Come here child.
Even when you're hurting.
We built the farm there on Lucky Hill.
She liked the farm, Arthel.
She was kind and humble woman child.
She was born with an illness that never fully left.
Our good times were great.
Doesn't look kind, humble, or shy.
She looks like she just beat up a child.
Yeah.
I like her both in on it too.
Like how fucking you got them.
All right.
But our bad times.
When she couldn't rise from bed.
Those made my heart splinter.
And one day.
It shattered.
And there's one thing I know is that I don't want to live in that empty house without her.
The forest had been dead quiet.
When they entered.
As they've gone deeper.
Noises have filtered into hearing.
Drips.
Scrapes.
No trills.
The smells have turned richer.
Of damp earth.
Spicy bark.
Quilted mosses in purple, green, and beige.
Soon.
The ox halts.
They come into a clearing.
Where a goddess lives.
Oh.
Glad she?
Yes.
I didn't find her.
The reason I thought Arthel was here.
The reason I'm here.
And you're here.
Arooey.
She's a goddess of borders and in-betweens.
This realm of hers welcomes both to death and living.
So I'm here to join her.
Slip my fucking throat.
Well actually.
You have to slow down.
Clearly this idea has been germinating for some time.
I don't know.
What?
Look it's this forest.
I read about it.
This goddess Arooey rules it like a region between our world and a place for the departed.
I suppose it exists for us.
For those like us.
A place Arthel can be without pain.
And I can be with Arthel.
But isn't it just like dying yourself?
Crossing over to be together?
We'll be able to leave this place.
But why would she still live?
She will too.
We'll just live here.
You have to understand this is what I want.
All I need for you is to help me complete the ceremony and take the Bohoroks back with you.
I did not expect this character was going to have this much dialogue for you to do.
You are monologuing as this.
Okay.
All right.
This is your choice.
I mean we can't just throw your life behind.
No we can't.
We can't.
What do you mean you can't let me?
We're not in the business of letting friends die by any name.
By their choice or not.
I know you feel this is the only way.
But why?
What proof do you have that it'll work?
Do you think this goddess will demand nothing else from you?
You're not doing this today.
That's a starting point isn't it?
All that matters is today.
Silent minutes slip by.
They pass without motion save for the roll of mist.
The blink of damp eyelids.
The fall of silver-struck tears.
Finally Baladji raises her head and addresses the shrine at her back.
Dear goddess I'm sorry.
Today I'll leave your wood to your own.
Let me be back.
They turn the ox around.
But surprising and slow a low long stretch sound coils from the stones.
The roots.
The earth.
Baladji?
I don't know.
As it speaks something huge crashes through the trees.
What?
Please stay.
It's a retainer of the old god.
It's gonna kill us man.
It's gonna keep us here and we're gonna die.
So wait this is what is this thing?
What what is this thing?
It's I don't know the stones that were part of the shrine came to life and it demanded that we stay.
So I think it's trying to kill us.
Oh shit all right.
Let's go.
The wizard runs at the giant beast.
Stick in hand.
Oh he's gonna kill me.
He's gonna I'm getting out of here.
I'm getting out of here.
Jesus Christ.
My turn from the shadows.
All right.
Love is vengeance.
I'm just imagining somebody during this screaming Jesus Christ.
You're wearing different.
I don't know the villain is.
They leave the forest.
I can't with this fucking segment.
The last light lingers.
This time of year.
This is your side quest by the way.
It's not even been about you owl.
You think we upset her the goddess.
Gods aren't like us.
The judgment isn't easy to sway.
But they do accept appeasement.
Speaking from all our red anyway.
It's a thoughtful journey back to the farm.
Belatia and Othell once built.
At least one of us should be getting back.
But one of us could stay.
Belatia seems to be developing a habit.
Oh you want to be in the right now?
No I'm desperate.
I thought it was her talking.
No you interjected and now you must leave.
Seems to be developing a habit for silence.
But then she sighs.
I think I will bury her.
I mean I mean come on.
I'm trying myself and slaying the god beast.
I think I might just bury her.
I'm grateful to you.
I'll keep in touch and oh well what can I really promise.
And so you guys leave.
She returns to her normal life and buries her loved one.
Okay.
Oh it's hard to let the good things go.
Yeah wishes come true but not always forever.
Friends are useful then I guess.
They pull you along when you just want to lie down in the road.
Oh along us wherever you are.
Maybe time to start looking into immortality.
The wind picks up.
They take their time returning home.
Oh we get some fucking hotwood.
We took our clothes.
We got some heartwood.
Thomas leveled up.
Oh I did all right.
Oh I'm not doing that.
Maybe naturalist.
You could re-roll these if they're kind of weak.
Oh infuse ranging.
Actually I like this.
That's I feel like I'm a little too far away sometimes.
Yeah I like that.
Let's head to Mist and Timberland then.
Push on.
We move on.
We press on.
By the way when I was I kind of had a moment back there.
When I was giving you shit bro.
Doing every voice like this.
Everybody in my chat was saying what about like Goku?
And if you don't know.
I do that too.
Everybody talks like this.
Everybody sounds like Mr Satan.
I just do a variation of that so I'm full of shit.
Everyone has two voices.
Yeah every yeah guys.
Well rumors of Gorgons have led the Bastion the Fabulous Four
through tangled woods to the side of a long forgotten roof.
Windborn rock and decayed edifices are all that remain of this ancient city.
Even the locals don't know who used to live here.
Petrified rat over here.
Nice of them to leave us a trail.
I wonder what lured them all the way out here.
Their trail was direct.
Calculated.
Might mean to stay.
Wouldn't be hard to make a place defensible.
The stoneworks set in good condition.
I forgot that your character looked like that.
It's been so long.
I jump out of the bushes.
One civilization falls another is built on the bones of their dead.
The dead.
Sometimes it's easy to forget they were real people.
Ordinary.
Most of them.
Probably.
Because you're a narcissist.
You know with all the usual hopes and fears and everyday concerns.
Thousands of feet must have trodden these streets every day exchanging goods and information.
And those must have been houses.
Not too fancy but the space a man calls his own.
I'm just you've been doing that.
I'm doing your voice now.
The space a man calls his own doesn't have to be.
Maybe we switch.
Like we've been married so long.
Okay let's switch it up.
You've given it a lot of thought love.
Wonder what kind of lives we could have lived if we'd settled in a place like this.
In the open pit of an old amphitheater.
Gorgon beast Bray and Mill.
Whoops.
Did we just walk in.
There are a bunch of them standing under that filler.
How about I bring it down.
Fire create confusion and the smoke will provide cover.
I'm an intimidation guy.
Yeah.
They've worked.
All enemies suffer two damage.
Oh nice all right.
Yeah where is everybody?
Oh they're up top.
Reveled.
Ooh howl.
What the fuck is your name again along us?
Along us baloney.
Is your name it's like a bug us but along us.
Is your name actually along us baloney?
Yeah no isn't it along us bolognese.
I feel like I feel like you wrote that in for like president at like an election.
Like I know I'm gonna vote for our longest baloney.
That's who I'm voting for this year.
I hit random and it was lungus and I had to change it to a lungus.
It just had to.
All right I'm close enough now.
We're pretty strong guys.
We actually are very strong.
It's pretty sick.
Oh watch out now.
What it didn't hit anybody.
Yeah one of my level ups was just plus two armor.
Yeah you're taking all these.
Here we go.
That's what I wanted to have happen last time.
I can kill that one.
I have a plan.
Wait I thought it bumped into the other one damn.
Oh was it was it one tile back further?
Yeah he's running.
Destroyed.
You activated my trap card.
We got level up.
Oh we do for a lungus.
Yeah it's a lungus bolognese.
That's your name.
Wait you can learn to fly now?
Swift action and 25 dodge.
Like you could do melee for your rapier.
Dude that whole battle you just threw some rocks.
Damage I mean I got the bite and the claw and the ring of rhythm.
Either of you two upgrades your speed.
Mine.
You should take it yeah.
All right let me get this straight.
People saying that all I did was throw rocks at people.
Um you don't think it'd be impressive if somebody broke up a pillar.
Turned it into three with their mind turned into three different discs.
And they flew out and homing missile hit three different enemies in the head.
Sorry I didn't um cast a lightning bolt out of my hands.
As they're breathing stills they hear the chittering of birds.
The buzz of bees overgrown grasses rustle in the breeze.
That rhymed.
Gone quiet.
Guess that was the last of them.
We should be sure before we move on.
Ancient settlement like this.
There's bound to be some hiding places.
Not far from where they fought a section of the flagstone appears to be coming up.
Thomas prized some away with his toe.
Uncovering what appears to be a way below.
Oh I'm moving with my.
Large and muscular toe there Thomas.
With a little more effort they widen out an entrance.
How deep is it?
Oh I was in the zone.
Stairs.
These stairs go down.
Gotta check it out right?
Any good reason not to?
Down they climb into the ancient city's underbelly.
Slimy things skitter away at their approach.
A rancid odor hangs in the air.
Torch over here let me just.
In a splash of light their surroundings take color and shape.
The passage opens up to a small enclosure.
An oval room.
Bits of the rotted wood and matted straw form the pale suggestion of a bed at one end.
Oh smells doesn't it?
I was expecting a crypt or storehouse not somebody's dusty old bed chamber.
Wonder why they're here beneath the city.
Scattered around the room are what remain of a life's possessions.
Most are decayed or moth eaten beyond recognition.
That's a garment of some kind.
Clay fragments.
Pottery pieces.
I see something over here too.
If the Gorgons found this place I'm guessing they didn't see anything worth taking.
I can't tell if you gave up on switching.
I kind of did.
He's just slightly older so there's like a gruffness to it.
Well no we switched so he switched to the dog did it for like.
Yeah but now he switched back he switched back.
He was like wait a second like this isn't fun to do for like four hours.
Yeah I came to that conclusion pretty quickly.
Yeah yeah like anyone would any sane person would come to that conclusion.
It's mental but there's one item that catches Thomas's eye.
A small bone flute sat atop a stone pedestal.
Alone it seems like to have survived the passage of years unmarred.
Moon colored its surface is smooth polished by the press of ancient fingertips.
It begs to be held again.
There's a look I know well.
Oh I.
This thing it's in one piece at least.
Not that it's anything special it sort of catches my attention.
I can't help wondering what it sounded like who played it and who listened.
The way it's placed I think it was treasured by the hands that held it.
Well looked after.
He you're taking the flute we know you're taking the flute.
Yep.
Oh plus 15 charisma.
I'll take it.
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
Nice bone flute.
Thomas moves forward and carefully plucks the flute from its stand.
It's not doing anything down here except gathering dust.
Those who made it you think they'd want that.
That's like an heirloom writing a way to be remembered for whoever left it behind.
So if you want my opinion nothing is good.
They put out the torch make their way back to the surface and seal the passage behind them.
So how about a little contest find out who plays best.
You can't even play it with the wolf mouth.
Yeah how would you play that.
Damn it damn these wolf lips.
And then I stand up there and I'm like and then we all know who won.
All right let's build a bridge.
How many more days 280 285 days.
I'm telling you dude I'm telling you man we need to just like hang out at the bar for like two years.
No way man look I think this is the thing we're all we need to get to the altar yeah.
Yeah we're nearly there.
Okay well then we get to the altar and then we like camp out it's like we have tickets first.
Somebody said I hope something bad happens to your character so it's more interesting.
Yeah your character has gone relatively untouched by anything.
I'm just sort of a normal guy that just is like kind of here hanging out with my spells.
Okay what difficulties five should we patrol or should we just go for it.
What do you I think we go for it.
Just go just we're slamming right we cannot be stopped.
This is the final fight of the chapter when this fight is over the chat will end make sure you are
ready let's go oh let's do it normal guy and his furry wolf husband look at this
have we decided who gets the spear yet a towering reeking of algae and old water it stalks sedately
on its stony limbs while the world quakes it's called the calabine as 22 health is immune to
compulsion it crushes any scenery it touches yeah we are not whatever you're sweeping attacks
wait you're not on the map no we're we're on like a whole like we're still reading oh I skipped that
entirely for some reason I never got the reading oh we're like we're at the door I'm gonna watch
I'll watch yours oh I just I just joined oh my goodness this thing is huge 22 health and we're
gonna kill in one turn all right I need to get in here so I can I can fuse let me fuse with this
he's such a good infusion I'm biting oh uh-oh uh can you back up sir no I can't I've already
attacked okay oh I'm just let him on fire okay we're getting a divorce oh going right next to
the other one I did say if you could move and you went like oh I love his vengeance
all part of the plan all right let's get what we came for right don't you wonder what that
thing live down there there in the chamber is clear and almost sweet the corpse of the great
guardian shrivels inside its carapace it on approaches the edifice the spear is glass like
grand it radiates legacy and power it's just strange what could this thing really mean to them
the boars are in a normal heirloom my guess is that the hero queen who wielded this lance in
antiquity was actually a gargon so it's kind of an emblem to them maybe of a past hero
as in and grips the spear a noise begins to grow in the outer tunnels it's the noise of feet and
hooves of tortured lungs shoveling air and the slickering squelch of scraping things water
the sound of it a horde of gorgon beasts is pouring towards the chamber
are you crying if the story was not that moving
we need to hope they don't call for escape i don't think we'll survive if we stay here
holy shit look at that thing eight damage great spin i do have an empty slot that thing looks
pretty great i should take it oh where are they where are they coming from escape the gorgons
oh we got a whole cave is there a whole cave here yeah back back the other way oh there's a
door down here what did we just find if you xp we could but you're not a gamer so you don't want
to do that i need to get my gear score up for the dragon's expansion what do you even know
about gear score what do you even know about eye level tell me i have to get my light level
up awful noises and rank smells rush out of the dark
he doesn't he doesn't care anymore i can tell from a different tunnel
your whole chat probably mocking me oh they're just oh they're talking so much
shit you have no idea it's like this is like a you're having a field day right now make it
funny does this guy really think that he's a dog they keep going omega low omega low stirs voice
omega low awful cringe i keep saying it's like if you type if you go if you type in like logs
and you look up like how many times like stir and cringe we're in the same sentence it's like
if i leave you alone uh you'll love again won't you escape is the only option
okay that's what we all get to no dog lol lol they can't even perceive me i'm unperceivable
oh i get oh you're actually kind of surrounded here i am intangible you just leaving i am leaving
yo look at that jump that was sick that was sick we kind of need you man where are you going
you're kind of dooming us to death i would secure your move speed sir i was just kidding
people didn't say cringe stir they were like i love this voice i swear i'm not making it up
i've been carrying this marriage for five 10 15 years see how he does without me okay
he left what he actually left you away you you're gone you actually left gone he extracted it like
now if we don't go out we die i he just dodged it he oh my god really bad it's really bad that
he left what are you doing what are you why what's with the sabotage dude we're gonna die we're
actually gonna die no we're not no what have you done we're not we're okay we're okay you need to
double move just run just just run we have to run move as far as you can okay oh this is bad oh
that's bad this is actually not gonna have you go this is not gonna be good i think you got me
you can move i think you can move oh no okay how don't go that way why not wait that's not the
right way oh it's all right go down you need to go down it's okay it's okay it's okay i can i think
i can make it from here as long as it doesn't turn around hit me i'm gonna sit here as a target that
was big okay just don't spawn in front of me you are so dead oh the dodge dodge again oh
wait you might be okay i think he's blocking
no thomas back on his heels pain doesn't come immediately but the wet stuff dripping down his
face is probably blood he's never taken a hit like this at least not one that he can remember
you're gonna use minus 10 retirement age but that's that's not that bad
focus on surviving nothing more i can do maybe i'll get an interesting character
character edition if i do this he runs hope for the bow could be won without him maybe i'll lose
my nose or maybe i'll lose my lose up to my hair alone he staunches his wounds one gash
particularly deep that's gonna leave a scar a character defining scar character defining
scar let's go uh you have to make it out too though i'm gonna make it man come on you can do
it you're not not much further a wound if i go down it might be game over oh shit oh this actually is
bad i don't understand you just walk to the exit
oh no he sees the shadow of his foe he knows what's coming he can lean a little to one side
or the other but it won't change much he feels something a heaviness in his hand it has a name
the petri glass sea spear there's a story maybe that it wants to tell
and only a sliver of opportunity left to tell it i can choose to break the spear or take
minus two health for the rest of the campaign the like main quest item and then don't we need that
thing i will take the the health indecision grips him the blow lance he tumbles to the ground
gravely wounded and clutching his weapon in the end he couldn't choose to part with it even if
it meant paying the price himself oh no star you have fucked us i what have you done he has just
enough strength to retreat and we'll spend the next days tending to his wounds over your head
propped up at his bedside petri glass sea spear will wait until he's ready to take it up again
and let it sing wait what happened victory dude look at the scar on my eye let's salvage this we
don't need it it's just a yeah good you were good scar i don't think anyone needs this
all right mystic there it is see now i get to talk like this the rest of the campaign you pull up
look at your scar yeah once per turn you can pull a mote of heat out of the air and create fire
anyway you want i'm doing that one what's mine i don't care i don't give a shit anymore i don't
fucking care this has to be you're the only one alive it's done oh we all of us together left
that canyon and cave behind the enemy's treasure in our hands it almost broke we should be joyful
but we know a clash is coming my books claim wars are one piece by piece trapped by trapped
winning one ill doesn't decide anything we can only hope this small victory buys us time wait wait
wait wait we don't you think that it's each one of us is saying one of those lines yeah i think so
yeah so we can only hope this small victory by the time you're fucking trader the game is crashed
yeah at the end of every chapter i guess that's the first time it happened it happened to me last
time but no i can still see everything 10 years of peace follow okay cool wait next that's all nice
many chapters are there um five okay look in the top left wait that might not be it
i'm actually not sure oh this is during the years of peace so what happened i don't i don't oh there
it is a lungus carried one of the large bedroll upon his back thomas a jug of wine on his and
they snuck off to the hills for some time to enjoy the views and each other's company
okay oh you forgave me and on would only find excuses to visit humble top smelter
his pan wouldn't sit flat his fire poker wasn't pokey enough whatever the reason it had absolutely
nothing to do with the strikingly beautiful smith who sometimes brought her work there
i give i give her the eyes she did not have red hair it's not gonna last true a lungus went to
the word hero index one day to research his family name apparently disappearing into the shadows was
a running theme i wonder thomas tried to take a lung as shopping at the local outfitters
plus they gave the bats of the fabulous four a great discount but i like the clothes i have
how many days straight have you worn that thing hey i watched it and on fell for a shepherd's
shepherd with a different lady the smith is i told you i was down i was down bad dude and on
what is a different person noticed in the hills hand in hand they would follow the flock for hours
in contented silence what you have a son i have a son has reached adventuring age and he's a
fucking wizard he's joined our group on bob proud has joined the bats of the fabulous four as a
mystic i thought just about hold on we already have a mystic i think um you don't really need
young and spry and he's really eager to earn wait along us and thomas's son all right dakin has
joined the dakin i was for as a warrior wait with this was dakin you guys had a son he doesn't even
have a single wolf arm yeah there's no wolf he has a wolf soul oh okay okay um he has a wolf soul
yeah he does okay what do you guys want to give dakin i feel like i feel like this guy
just every now and again when he's eating it's like he only eats meat he only eats meat that's
how you know oh it's what is a warrior yeah you gotta level him up what does he what's his starting
thing uh stir what do you i don't he's a raider you made him a raider wait you're transforming
again you got a bird leg dude you got bird feet crow's leg you got you're a mess achievement
unlocked i did it but i feel like there was a game like the we where you put different like
monster parts all over the the character and they they need like battled with them
for the we yeah what are we thinking of impossible creatures was we played that together
and i mean spore spore is pretty close yeah there was another one for the we too monster lab yep
so what are we doing with our points yeah what are we doing i mean i'm not long for this body
so i i don't think it would be appropriate to change jack are you ready do you want to
put stock in your son is that what i honestly want our our children to just jump off a cliff
i don't want them in our adventuring party leave them at home i want them to have
the life that i couldn't have yeah the adventuring life is not for them i feel
okay all right well let's let's see how they do we have to see how the how these two do
i want to see how they do i mean what we're just gonna they're ready to fight they're ready to join
the moment that my son takes narrative like priority over me i'm gonna flip out okay we
need to give thomas a new oh my god he can learn the giga great stuff tier three mythic stuff
oh we can give you a tier two and then we can give uh we can also give along us tier two stuff
as well uh you know let's go to your two i don't want to take all the points okay do you want
are you looking at the do you want to a mage stuff or you do you want to stick with the wand
um i wonder what would be better for what i have right now they're the same except uh wands give
you plus one magic armor and stars give you plus 50 in block chance um i'll do the magic armor okay
tier two wand then yeah because what do i have right now you got a tier one wand yeah let's
get the tier two okay tier two wand upgrade boom and then for along us you want what t2 rapier
or do you want t2 bow probably get both along us any thoughts no i think if my arm is going to get
replaced and i'm not going to be able to hold weapons anymore so i don't want to upgrade them
we'll just like you're gonna you're gonna get like a frog arm and you won't be able to grip
the sword anymore you could go tier two this armor here or this one up here this one looks kind of
cool um this one this top armor gives you plus 25 dodge which would yeah probably go yeah do that
one craft this sword is so cool and powerful that's an interesting way to describe that
you're reading my weapon description well none shall stand before the wielder you automatically
win every single fight you enter and nobody can stop you it also doubles as a gun what the
fuck is this weapon so strong and unstoppable oh you wrote this okay i was like what the hell is
this yeah if you think you need a gun yeah okay all right so what's next jammy gonna be on new
narita sure the rains had some storms got a compromise into combative neighbors grudges
are no shelter in bitter weather oh i'll press it the rains had been falling for a full week
with brief interludes of tense massing clouds and dripping branches mountain snows melted in
water roared from the heights the seas whirled and rung at the shores flung waves ever further
rivers conquered their banks and marched wider valleys turned to huge brackish lakes lowland
woods and the dams of dry times were swept away as creatures of all shapes and kinds sought escape
from churning floods everything are all strict boys and i think you have to i think you have to
add some crow to it now yeah and you also you're also like 30 plus years older right now aren't you
yeah we're like in our 50s um okay let me um did you put your name in the goblet of fire did you
put your name in the goblet of fire harry did you i already sound old yeah you do sound old
we're not doing this don't do this after all this time with word there's no rational explanation
for this confluence of catastrophes rain rain old people that demons nothing's ever made sense
about this but oh someone's at a door the strange party of visitors begs a fire they appear to be
on the edge here in a common dwelling and also very soggy arnon you know we're dangerous right
why are you here the haggard man behind the horns calls himself arnon anon takes a long
breath and turns to address along us and the right fucking goofy son is in the frame ask my wife
sounds like a punch line that's perfect we don't get the joke ask my wife she sent me
can you believe that at my advanced age i grew up here in serpent sable you know it looks different
must be about you know what no everyone knows it's those tensor clasts the gorgons they bring ruin
on us all and which gorgons they're blue that checks out but i mean who's there the gorgons
are flooding the world they've set it in motion and it can't be stopped almost how none of this
should be possible i mean the racy oh i like that that's the auto field vibe you're right
it shouldn't be the great balance should be unassailable but somehow they've thrown it over
so the torrents fall the sea's thrash the soil seems blacked out our warren's it's o's tricks
i knew it would be oh stress oh it's the gorgons i'm saying the beasts have our warren hemmed in
my wife's inside dry and warm you need to talk to her hemmed in but you slip by them it's what
had to be me i'm a moustache looping the light i tend to be missed you don't think we're idiots
is that it huh why i'm on and i'm nice he certainly gives us an option a strange one
but it's weather these floods what else can go on if you want to watch the world sink beneath a
rising sea watch all land things perish they're exactly where you need to be but if you see sense
arnon thuds a lump of soaked fabric on the table here's a oh it's wet i mean it's a map
sorry it'll dry oh crinkly follow the map come to our warren there learn for yourselves how
you can deflect this drowning doom and these lands all safe the shadows deepen all monster
groups will draw an extra monster card in every battle i sound like a robot i'm not supposed to
sound like a robot you sounded fine what the fuck do we do about the dumb kids i think we leave
them behind right just leave it into a battle and then like kill them yeah i mean are we able to
dump them well you can you can wait wait you can x them on that screen yeah yeah we can literally
like x them out and then just like go without them and leave them here yeah okay but what about
dakin's quest we can send them wait we can send them to build things that's a good idea we as we
go into a new quest we can just leave them to like build places i guess wait who's got a quest
no i don't think anybody know i'm 48 years old you guys are like i need to be like a grandfather
that's young i don't think people live that long in these times man yeah in these fantasy
times with crow people my health care just wasn't there oh i get the heck out of my party kids
leave this to the adults somebody yeah somebody said i found a book where we could go to a place
without adults um somebody in chat said if we don't have five people in the party we're just
gonna lose they're wrong they're wrong okay they're actually so off-based even what would you do
if you found your heart racing at the thought of another someone who stood beside through danger
and then oh well these versions are different i'd try to learn what they like what their feelings
are i'd form a plan of some sort stop that mumbling there's a sound
such voices and careful footfalls approach down the overgrown path to thomas's ears even these
muffled noises are perfectly loud oh dude you got a scar now your ears are like better
yeah if you don't make up for you like us wait you're like me we're both blind
come forward strangers you're friendly come forward slowly silence perhaps a minute of it
is all the answer that emerges from a thick wall of brush then you won't believe what happens next
click here i did the lady i'm not i'm not you don't they're not fooled by this we're prolonging the
inevitable yes mr sam this is what i offer myself introduce us we can we can hear you oh okay like
normal man are we gonna have to abandon this guy too this was the nutty guy that you did i think
oh you look experienced whatever you are bandits rogues not hounding for captives i hope
well move it you fool how are you so miserable at this i'm so sorry mistress here take my arm
a pair of travelers clambers free of the bracket they're clothing fine but a tad filthy hello
strangers i'm matic a servant and apprentice to this prestigious and lovely woman who well perhaps
we shouldn't use your real name she's the queen that's hunway oh he knows your name and why
wouldn't he i'm with the dream charter poet and peerless singer impossible to turn away near when
she's plucking strings spinning yarns deploying her famous vows well you don't seem like a threat
comes about a fire or you're not kind of bad business lunga fire sounds grand mistress
along us the small camp settles a little awkwardly introductions go with it shortly thereafter and
then can't help himself he bends hunwit's ear my fucking neck my reality is indivisible from
homophony that's a quote from millardine as i'm sure you know you rarely cemented the truth of
it for me though see got to listen to your performance in glimpsery and sleeping top
masterful remember was you in town all the old wine saga in a day and a night
i know i dare chew him also sir your character is always like right up in front with his eyes just
i remember those days i try not to miss him oh mistress you don't need to say that i do though
just that nothing lasts forever bad fever took my lofty registers from me my volume performance is
such a physical thing most forget that i'm weak nowadays i lean on him my student manic there you
are holding up a phone and like holding it like horizontal like you're filming this and making
sure that you're in frame because it's your video yeah i want to be the extra that gets noticed but
this is your video so like of course i have to be in frame even if i have nothing to do with this
mistress i'd love to show that gift to you again but it's gone now only the memory remains i try
a small dog for song even if it's quiet even if it's just a shadow of you you're gonna sing
as both characters you have to sing as both characters oh we can see what the apprentice has
learned and make jama sing what all right okay that's not what all right a night visitor's song
okay no mistress of course not so young maddox apprentice to hunwit the dream chanter removes
his instrument from its case his features composed take on a startling dignity let's hear it
first he performs a somber ballad next a rousing and farcical tune to dour lips up
smiles pool in the warm orange wash of the firelight and song he plays well into the
night until others begin to pitch in with stories or songs the night before the fight
at yuka's folly passes easily in good company oh yeah let's see how much we need those stupid
children those good-for-nothing wait i lost two health and i still have this much help that was
permanent to help yeah kind of makes me fearful for what is uh what's in here yeah and monsters
why did you enter the rest of us can't move i didn't mean to click oh you both can i've got
you hubby thanks no wait you can get the lover's vengeance though all right i'm going for a big
spell he's still oh that was huge see you lovers vengeance you have so much armor and it's actually
crazy what i was trying to be sus damn 12 damage yeah you all you have that super uh magic like
water spear but the god spare yeah this guy just did 17 damage he's nice work there's more
not that way they're in what about through this door on the left ow probably yeah in it nothing
in here at least i don't think so what's this back in the back uh yeah maybe our back god you
guys can move so far oh what is that oh once you get the spear of legend and all i get is a full
transformation of my entire body it's not even my spear i nearly died for it because you left us
to rock it's weird that you keep bringing that up like i'm gonna i mean i'm permanently oh
shit okay there was something in here it's weird that you keep bringing that
ouch it's been 10 years dude oh okay all right i i don't want i don't okay ow i don't all right
i don't need loved one hid that's why he hid i don't need another character defining scarf
i'm hiding i'm hiding you don't are you still i need to let go of this you need to wake up
oh thank god all right i'm good i'm gonna good murder 12 damage they're more thank goodness
yeah good thing our kids weren't there our kids would have died
plus two warding that would take over the for you tank oh yeah that'd be nice to me i think
and a shield oh boy all right um we could probably i mean do you want to shield give you some armor
i mean if it is the wand one hand yeah it is i'll take it yeah oh all right yeah sure that
probably helps i'll put it on the gorgonoids are slain battles led by them down a boulderous
room where gray grass matches the cloud color someone doing dragon pictures hey thomas oh thomas
a magic man you badly hurt what's your favorite monster oh uh why i guess the moke morrow creature
up all night crafting quarts out of moon beams you're really just gonna like you're really just
gonna read the dialogue like you're just gonna read the script and not really envision the
character at all show me how you would do it like what's what like what is actually your favorite
i just said it you're a lion is it yeah oh i didn't it didn't go forward
it gotta be a class and like it i like vampires though like actually
so you're you're as bad as him you're a sheep you're a sheep you're reading what's in charming
beyond all question i like vampires i'm like they had those answers are fine but
some of us will always love a dragon dragons imported the essence of the monster
that thing beyond human capacity not just fierce but impossibly cunning
wise artful distinctly above the human apex yeah i can't wait till we're around a fire
the stories will soar that shepherdess you you got with is a dragon wait you think so i'm calling
it yeah she's a dragon and you're just trying to like like lead us no we don't want
it's not a story he's just building okay they're trying to sneak into our fucking party
okay hang on i got a plan we're gonna do this and then we're gonna make them find us a magic item
just send them on like a 10-year circle have them going around a circle 15 times just keep
walking we just said just make them keep walking forever yeah put them on a journey wait wait wait
wait wait they're moving and we're standing still not doing it no we're building the we're building
the bridge okay yeah look at you whoa i'm i'm just trying to fly that's what it looks like today
i'm gonna jump i'm gonna jump are you gonna do it it's kind of high along us i'm gonna jump
the policies i'm gazing into space the landforms are just beautiful arresting
there's plenty to be interested in up here don't worry no danger spotted are you trying to fly or
what uh because i'll fucking throw you if you want to fly i want to fly hey you know throw me
yeah do it i'd be surprised if you remember the conversation but you probably remember the night
the night we what was the name of that story spinner you admired oh i'm waiting a dreamcatcher
i'll always remember wasn't this like four days ago yeah literally you probably don't remember you
are blackout drunk i'm a bit old nowadays right there's something that night keeps re-entering
my thought that's when you posed the question well remember what you asked me yeah yeah is
your dick still a man's dick given what you've gone through oh don't the other thing oh what
would you do along us if you fancy your heart racing in the form of another someone you stood
beside through danger oh you didn't forget what ended up happening with that nothing and seeing
sorry no no it's uh i just mean what guy what did you want to say i just want you've been talking
about me what is this like a you talking shit moment no this is like a he's trying to cheat
on you with me sometimes you display in a standing aptitude for missing the subtext
but along us i was talking about you gasp i hoped and i hoped i thought my chest would explode
i didn't dare hope what's happening forget thomas let's fuck it's the opposite of judicious
but will you try this with me oh that's your line i get why did you tell me what about thomas
yeah what the fuck up what about him i'll have to tell him maybe he'll take it all right i don't
know i just he's gonna hate me i tried to get him killed in that cave 10 years ago
he's just too normal for both of us look us not weird enough i don't have enough i don't know like
weird arms i don't have like a big don't ever identify with me he can't really connect it's
just too normal i don't think there's anything else we can do now we both know i'm going to the
costume store and i'm just getting like a weird mask or something and uh look guys i've got i've
got like a weird mask i didn't click it stuck like this what's happening we all are we going high
we climb the distances we walked let us here together we have fallen in love oh oh thomas
in and out of our rivals yeah slash duel i don't think you want that smoke i'm the penta of this
group fucking everything up i'm not weird enough oh no the gorgons moving great number of planes
would attack the lands that's so far away yeah they kind of this way around the corner they kind
of come in this way though i think we're good how long did you guys want to go for scary scary
here yeah i want to see how thomas reacts to our affair yeah no why don't you guys go defend the
land he's a what he's watching angry some kind of basement over here they've been late all day
late rising late on the trail late to recognize sunset and late spotting this ruin it's the
remains of a smallest structure and it rests on a cleared rocky slope where the trees find little
perches enon what do you know about this area all i've heard is that it used to be more thickly
settled guys you want to hear something crazy if if if enon and along us have a child then
we would have three new characters and then like they would all be like weirdly related that's
true i didn't mean to walk in on you step sis someone was born here oh your tail away an ancestor
of the pumpkin guy you know the guy with the pumpkins there's the serpent side line we're the
first down here in some time huh someone worked at the stable knife lines stains of sediment this
isn't about our relationship ash on the floor it's chalk what are these hash marks and what's in the
box no no why don't you open it and put open it really close to your face something wrong
that's the open border shadows back like ravens blood why is my voice being all different colors
you're reading the chalk off the wall i think oh i know how to read this it says i don't know
wait what i don't know i was lying wait you're reading a poem this place doesn't like that i
guess but nowhere is home perfect so do you see anything that we could use the box is puzzle
locked one of those magical puzzle locks oh it's a magical puzzle box magical puzzle box okay
interesting so like i could i could probably do that but you get you two could probably figure
it out you should maybe you should do it yeah useful for once you two could figure it out decide
to see yeah um so but i don't know how we can open that unless i think you two could probably
get really cozy down here and figure it out right well i think you could probably help
i could for once why can't we all just get along together remind me how these function
bogwin generations were bonkers for these things these puzzle locks yeah i could sniff or perhaps
there was some way i could bury my feces near our camp i could do that but the magic lock
presents a prompt with a clear slate to write an answer the wise wanderer finds home where
this is on you thomas you're the you're saying you can do this where does he find home
the wise wanderer finds home do i have an option or do i say it i think it's gonna give us multiple
choice i think no don't you don't give them don't make it easier what wait we want what's inside
i i veto this next i'm sure there's a systematic approach to this well air is turning out better
than i thought cook dinner and make a night of it talk some guesses maybe it's interesting
i'll grab the things i'm just as invested yeah i'll help they hold that gate on the slippery
steps thomas investigate investigates the blocked chimney pipe goes above ground a while and clears
it from the end anon's absorbed in a book he digs up it's full of creative geology a longus rushes
a rabbit stew and has to put it back on the fire after it does that why do we keep letting you cook
why do you keep killing us why is wonder where okay where where his books prove too many to haul
what were shrewd folks still are scarce i feel like thomas is onto it click click all right
i might have interfused that time sorry just then a clatter of hunting bird calls echoes into the
basement hollow must have heard our treasure box open up disappointed no i was on the wrong page
sorry it passed the time point legacy points two oh fight fight away out yeah we do oh squirrel
is it only two or it was like five right i eat it legacy point legacy point brie brie i put it in
my mouth sir could you please tell germa he looks crazy cute today tell him yourself gemma you're
looking crazy cute right now hey thanks i did put a new product in my hair oh is that like a new
webcam sound a little different all right i'm gonna ignite no i'm not oh you created fire
with it wasn't it i actually didn't i think just burnt you and then along us put out the fire
wow i'm gonna read the book that we found god this is a really dark arc for thomas
yeah oh no somebody spawned over here it's all right i don't need anybody's help
then it gets smashed into the ground there i turned off the light there the cheaters i wonder
if we're gonna have a big blow up i'm really surprised oh a tier two star you could replace
your tier one one yeah that is absolutely what i'm gonna do yeah maybe you should give it to your
son yeah i'm gonna i was gonna rename it poison apply poison as an action offhand plus two poisons
your weapon probably one of you guys right just give it no it's good to one of the kids i guess
my hands are full so yeah dakin can take it yeah he's poisonous um where are we going we're going
we're going here right yeah wait what the is the goal where's the goal down this video the raging
gorgons i don't know what we're gonna do about that war strength six mama mia wait where are we oh
wait what yeah we have this going all the way around yeah oh my goodness the only way a tile
will flood in 90 days oh shit okay they're flooding the world that march though for sure
yeah this this is the thing that we have to get rid of completely right yeah yeah let's keep going
okay these guys made us they got some stuff work and item question mark i think you can build
bridges on rivers now you can build bridges where it tells you you can though knee pads i'm gonna
need to see okay and then let's send the kids to your fabric hot fabric hide or two hides let's do
one of each all right now the item who investigate oh no no sorry that was them
i was okay oh wait we just went we walked by them they're destroying this world i guess we
gotta walk back we gotta go back we gotta go defend live stream yeah how do we we can't
because we're in the middle of scouting oh shit we just walked by them we're just doing a story now
okay
what's wrong i sense magic gorgons said magic oh it's this way what is it it's an overgrown mess
that's what it is help me uncover it ah there we go oh that's a nice strong font what a rush
well i don't know what words i just said what are you talking about we just pulled some weeds
i don't feel anything it's a font of spell thread it it feels like someone is pouring
honeyed sunlight woven with strands of fire through my body it feels so good honeyed sunlight
oh yes sunlight and starshine well at the same time it's an unfurling to the world around you
to the spirit of a place or a thing wow objects spirits well not like conscious ones it's more
that we're connected to everything spell thread woven between all of reality sometimes i feel
like there's an entire world that's how i feel when i talk when you talk about tactics ooh
i kind of like that one well i don't know i have always sort of worked with the energies from afar
i guess i could put my hand on it oh damn look at that evil grin wait go back go back you
you want me to die oh yeah our rivalry it's boiled over i it's now we're trying to kill
each other every time but that's you oh shit are you okay uh yeah no no i want that character trait
oh no that's not fair
i that was supposed to be my cool character trait
i feel connected yes exactly to everything around me
me
come on uh we can chat about this on the road i can't believe you got the awesome character
trait cosmic experience how do we we need to go back and defend how do we do this it won't
even look we need to go wait do we need to go to i don't understand he stole your man he also stole
your cool trait oh my god i did that actually did happen all right we gotta wait to defend the
world yeah enough petty bullshit we have to defend the world look how cool you guys look
i can't believe that happened dude i thought you were gonna touch it yeah
charging the battle i just we're charging charging in yeah we're yeah nothing can
fucking stop us we have a blue guy that's true you do have a blue guy no one's explained it
oh boy all right this is this is a big deal wait where are they oh they've got to be over there
right ruffle it up oh oh my goodness okay that thing is pretty scary and look at that thing
uh let's put people in cover yeah good idea what the hell is that fucking shut up
that person's like raging they're just pumping up they're getting hyped up when the
monsters actually show up oh there is a lot of monsters down there oh i have to fight the giant
bear oh i gotta i gotta get out of here i gotta run maybe character development i don't know
should i go with some character development you have to get out i'm gonna jump in where you are
oh yeah be gone did you send him away be back oh wait i thought that i thought that was me moving
is there anything to shoot there we go you need to run i don't have any more action points i don't
think okay wait wait in that case yeah this thing is going to kill me in one hit no i'm gonna stand
here and then we're gonna send out this lady to stand here and and protect you but i mean heaven
forbid i get a scar over the other eye nice sir why did you just say sis's wasd uh i can't click
out of the chat box so when i'm like going around the map it's just recording all of that
for people that don't know what i'm describing are you done i'm chat banned have you had your turn
no wait oh okay i'm chapping no that's okay five damage we did what has to be done man yep
all right i'm gonna try to uh walk backwards uh-oh thank god you were in the way
okay watch someone die you're supposed to be protecting thank god i should be attacking
those things that have hit my new husband hey it didn't say you didn't get married yeah i just
said we're in love we're eloping we had an end of a chapter cutscene of us getting married don't
forget you're still married well you know what they say say you're a real piece of crap you're
a bit of a homewrecker man uh what me yeah he's the lame boring guy who got a flute in like 20
years so much more 20 years and all he's got to show is he found a dead guy's flute and then
carried it and by the way any of the three of us could have taken that flute you guys just
let me have it yeah i lost an eye then got petrified on half my face then turned blue
you got a wolf head then a wolf arm then raven legs and wings and he has like a nice sash
yeah uh excuse me but i think i got the coolest uh outfit though this guy is wearing like all gold
how did you walk that also being a blue man oh god okay um no i'm too far away
nice so are we pick are we controlling these people too just randomly right like anybody
i'm just i'm just yeah anyone can yeah i'm uh i'm on overwatch so if either of those two things
move towards you i'll get them okay isn't your character better with fire germa yeah but where's
the i see one flame up here i'm so glad you put him there yep oh god just like our relationship
the fire seems to have burned out yeah yeah yep fuse oh that was a big hit that was big are you
staying there because you're gonna die um this this guy's here this guy's here i'm stuck i can't
move far enough i got i got to i think he should get targeted first denim denim should shoot there
we go oh actually this is kind of sad yeah we're just using them to protect you yeah oh my god
i really am i really am like completely useless we're just killing people to keep me alive
might not be enough though oh i'm good see you later i'm fine i thought that was me moving a
second time oops are you too far away to attack uh yeah but i've got my sentinel was like if they
move within two spaces i attack before they get their turn oh good good good so i'm will hit him
regardless i've no oh regardless oh another person dead man you guys i've only got one eye guys come
on no oh you think you can take care of that guy i can take care of this guy here yep um um
i think i'm i think i might need to save you might save thomas i mean i i could you should
save thomas all right he's still our companion even if the spark is gone hey i it is also a
possibility that i get a really cool scar i don't know about that champ i don't know it's up to you
you're gonna save your your actual relationship your actual husband which one of us do you save
yeah i don't know anon's looking pretty threatened right now i don't yeah maybe i don't think so though
what's your decision are you gonna let me let's see oh okay okay let's see what happens then
put that light out big damage blocked it still good we can't be stopped actually um i'm just
gonna leave and i'm gonna go like this uh until i die we're good yeah i didn't need any help
yeah see i got lover's vengeance down here because he shot at him last turn i i'm totally giving up
on you it's kind of harsh man well you know what the blue i took his blue thing imagine he'd been
blue he would finally been one of us i know it would have been so much more exciting i would
have been screaming i would have been jumping up and down in my room uh so what's the goal now
and we have to clear the reddit threshery it looks like our chapter three uh we have to meet anon
at nook belong where is that have we even found this place oh it's it's right here it's down here
lower left okay let's just go there then yeah the tile just flooded the one we needed to go through
what oh come on useless children yeah i thought that weren't they building dams and stuff over
here let's give uh dakin he's the warrior right yeah he can take that and then a pair of metal
braces yo that might make up my terrible eyesight true very true okay we can't go this way anymore
can we oh we can we're just traveling slower all right so have we made it we're nearly there
need on at the nook yeah this is the nook oh shit we should patrol it let's patrol first
you keep getting rid of the kids who wants them wait patrol in the wrong place what that's fine
we need you guys need to heal you need time to heal thomas is on three health oh my goodness
i really am almost dead dakin receives a challenge from his past he's fucking like seven what do you
mean boy one are we actually let's we're skipping this right our child's growth is irrelevant
oh it's literally it's the two children going on an adventure together no no kids can't go on
adventures my my my son is a buzzkill he says he says don't go i can't one of the real adventurers
get an opportunity right okay we cleared it no our sons what are they doing didn't we tell them
not to do this we're gonna see from a distance they're gonna be fighting this battle and that
we're gonna watch somebody die wait do we bring them into the battle is this their like coming of
age thing i think they just did it yeah now's when we find out whether our gamble makes us fools
a guy by honor's map we're nearly there are you good wrong page i read the next one
now as we find out our gamble makes us fools i've heard it said that to cut a noose is to gain a
dangerous friend in my experience i've never had the chance to test it dad why are you blue
oh yeah why are you blue you're gonna explain it for any chance limit
maybe do you have any chance hold on okay no oh dude this is rough are we bringing the kids
that's it kids are in let's let's stay back while the kids try and prove themselves
i don't like that idea let's look the kids will if they die they die man you know that was really
loud oh is it i'm sorry i went oh fuck that was loud oh yeah i don't think it came through your
mic you guys didn't hear it no you said hold on and then there was silence oh i see this is your son
this is your son control him well back on he belongs oh you motherfucker you're trying to
take me out what do you think you're doing thomas uh it was just a miscalculation that's all is that
so yeah i pressed the wrong button on my uh staff i pressed b instead of a sorry when i hold b and
i casted it uh went the wrong way i'm killing them all children protect me i'm living free and
wild what should i infuse uncle thomas what you should do is infusion is very difficult what
you have to do is grab a hold of elemental fire elemental water i think you are probably going
to be a water student if i were to take a guess grab the water there's a well over here craft it
hold down a don't hold down b i cast ignite okay you're still learning it's all right you're still
learning i'll cast ignite too i actually just walked over to him let me show let me show you how
it's done coming father i'll join you what what is this what is he doing this is your son
we shouldn't have brought these kids i'll go this way boom oh god all right i'm gonna leave
i can't go i love that voice holy smokes that was pretty good you're gonna want to flex your
violence wow use use my flame uncle nice one son i'm not your son i'm i'm in it son
oh that's all right i'm yeah come on how you doing over there son oh good dad oh think watch out for
the bear how come nobody is teaching our children i'm the only one speaking to them hides behind
double watch where that oh my my back
i just clicked a random button oh dodged it big swing oops nice we did it we have cleansed the
world a tiny little hand axe that you can throw hmm we could salvage it yeah is it more may not
be done fighting anon emerges rather suddenly from a damn shadow standing before a root framed
tunnel so you made it i was i was wondering i was wondering if you remember your dad we would
the old deepest leads them into the dark i guess he's the deepest i'm sitting here wondering what
is that the earth walls are slimy and black streams of water sloshing the side of hastily
heaped gravel path clods plop from the ceiling support beams have clearly been rushed into place
they're taking me off what tunnel they've been falling in my fucking neck deeper in
but he is the deeper the warren rots the flowing water follows cavern channels away from the main
tunnel to some dark end he's dead yeah yeah he's a he's a he's a bro oh no we can't don't do you
want uh breakfast oops it's like he doesn't speak english and he's like trying to find the
it's mid-afternoon ah but we're not chained to the sun cycle we have breakfast whenever
oh dude that's like the that's the expression that you see when you see the mcdonald's breakfast is
all day right like there are some that do that right what a weird smell beckons them through
to the other side here they are dear the badger and the root and more to follow did you offer them
sure i did no one wants lukewarm cheery old grub i keep saying well i was supposed to act in on
deep line oh i thought it was left to right oh i had interest this is some drunk i know
i come from sweden it said i was born in the basin of dried caldera the spirits of
sorted rock does get said a lot but not actually true right technically it's false you two
are married to each other and well mostly married in times of strife it's nice
oh i wonder about yeah which one of you are married uh and you've been here married
let's stay of course wait oh let's stay on course bro the reason we're in anon can they help us
the bridge speaks of recent language you came here because you must defeat the gorgons is that
right we were told you like knew how i know what the gorgons did their leader i learned of him
oothricks these are the bad guys a hundred tucks into a bowl of beige mush looks like shroomy gruel
with some kind of green gold dressing ostrich like we know that name well enough
yes oothricks raised the great number of his brethren
and they went to the valley of god beast moatana that that picture looks so weird
yeah dude what even is that uh try a little bit of foreshortening next time
and if that's a great gold beast they made
well the gaze is on all attempting from beneath the mess of
this is a serious lure come on the scowl twists are already crooked features
arnon finishes his meal pulls out his beard and wipes it on his cow
oh
dude i love how every time you do a dumb voice they have so much dialogue
yeah that froze off the water and the seas and the peaks all of a turn to big blue gorgon soup
that sounds tasty lord it'll don't it oh the carrots and the beans i'll take it and the onions
so that's why ostrich needed his army to slay a god well that's the point of what the spare
we bled over he wasn't even fucking born yet he wasn't wait i'm realizing okay we have we got a
10 year gap so these kids have to be less than 10 years old right they have to be like actually
they're like nine with beards it's like five and seven-year-olds
oh
what matters is this motana cannot die she's petrified the reason i called upon you here is
i've been hoarding a certain restorative spirit still from the roots of the extinct boutaxa what
i call it peter root beer i love root beer pug my root beer should be able to restore the great
Mo'atana, if you can get it to her.
My brain-god is Felda.
Well, assuming that's true.
Why us?
Don't you have your own lackeys?
The deep thongs some of it is.
We're afraid our people are made frail.
What are is the worst doom?
The Gorgon leader is strong and fearless, so too are his hordes.
We are too old, slow.
I'm scared to die.
Likely story, the Gorgons aren't gonna let us do this thing, are they?
Don't we know where to go?
Well, are we sure if Ivan is gonna be so fix everything?
The badger grows quite asky, but I'll answer all of your questions.
Oh, God, please don't.
Over breakfast!
I'm hungry.
Felda is true to her word and makes breakfast.
The food is surprisingly good.
What?
I've only ever had mush onion soup.
Lastly, Felda hands over a healing ale, a single sealed earthenware bottle.
Soon they're on their way again.
They carry the hope of all the land and this creature in one fragile bottle.
Uh-oh.
OK.
Confront Ulstrichs is our last thing.
The real showdown.
He's over there.
This is what everything...
Yeah, and we're taking the kids, too.
Don't leave the kids.
The kids are coming.
This is a long trip.
We're easily gonna heal up on the way.
Dachan's trying to have, like, a moment again.
No, he's not that one.
This isn't his story, it's ours.
He gets to tell the next one if he lives.
I'm kind of worried that you guys are not gonna be healed in time.
Maybe we should back up.
Uh, I think we're OK.
I'm ready.
OK.
Is this his thing?
Oh, yeah, skip that.
No one allowed to have interesting plots in our story.
Yeah, especially not if they're being the Thomas.
At least it's not you, Thomas.
OK.
This is it.
This is the big one.
We didn't even get...
True.
We're gonna patrol this over here just to give you guys more time to heal
because you're, like, half health.
Yeah.
This is it.
All our lives we've been preparing for this eventuality.
We're Gorgon slayers.
History brought us here because our people's history must continue.
Be sure of your gear.
This is our last sleep.
I'm here for your love.
Look at him in the background.
Go back.
He's lit.
And our kids are pretending to, like, not hear it.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Is my dad loving your dad now?
You're like eight. You don't get it.
They don't get gear like we do.
I don't. I'm...
Oh, my God. All this drama.
You still have one-star weapons.
You have one-star weapons.
You didn't grow a wolf arm, so you need to get something.
You need to eat them.
You should kill them. Betray them in the final battle.
You can, like, upgrade your rapier.
OK, hold on. I'm doing it.
You're giving it a terrible name and description.
So spend everything, apparently, because this is the very end, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we should.
Well, is there something cool I can have?
OK, I got my sword.
Yeah, we could give you, like, a tier three, like, wand or stuff.
Let's see.
Yeah, let me get this let me get this tier three wind twig.
Yeah, do it.
Is it? All right, I'm going to go for it.
OK, and we'll we'll give the boy a tier two staff.
I won't even give the boys a glance.
All right.
I was I was writing the description on that and you came over and just took it from me.
And we're just like, yeah, you can do it.
I pulled you hard. Yeah.
Well, I can I can go in the description and do it, right?
Yeah, you can do it right now.
Yeah, OK. Actually, we have to wait to lay out of this menu.
We're done. Yeah.
I was just etching that on the side of the staff in the corner,
and you came over, grabbed it out of my hands, just threw it into the side of the cave.
I threw it on the ground.
I'm sorry.
We can do it right now.
No, no, it's funny that way.
Wait, if we click back, right?
Oh, no, it's way funnier that way.
What does it say on it?
It just says lovers quarrel.
I was writing quarrel.
Oh, here we go.
The two the two lovebirds.
Let's see how this plays out.
No, I won't keep on.
The odds of our ever being here are beyond figuring.
Look at him.
Today, history hinges on the deeds of a few, very of one ordinary folk
and a few unique folk who took a tortured road and wound up in the way of destiny.
I'm glad it's us.
Yeah, one normal guy that got like bumped his head once.
And then we have all these superpowers.
You are a wizard though, that's kind of not normal.
That is true.
My shitty son's a wizard for no reason.
You know, what I like is a guarantee.
What if this creature we're trying to restore is just dead?
Like you saw, you mean the name of our image or ours.
A clear path climbs the hill ahead of them to whatever awaits.
There it is.
What the fuck happened to me?
I did some shit.
Some shit's gone down.
Yeah, this is the finale.
All right, let's get let's go for it.
Let's get it.
No sudden, no one pushing up willy nilly.
All right.
I'm making sure I stay alive.
Really?
Oh, there's two of them there.
I only saw one.
Nice.
It's me, dad.
Like dad, what should I do?
That's the job.
Oh, is this the final boss guy right here?
I think so.
No.
Well, I don't know if it's him.
I think he's a regular enemy.
Should be all strict.
Oh, yeah, it is all strict.
Have you been paying attention?
Jack and no.
Oh, like that hurt dad.
Jack and no bad dad.
All right.
Just throw the disc.
Dude, I love just throwing the discs.
That like hurts, man.
I love that voice you're doing.
Wow.
Oh my God.
All right, let's keep going.
I'm going in.
I think we should wait.
I mean, we kind of have to, right?
Yeah.
Hold on.
Let me scout.
You fucker.
Oh, very fitting.
The red tiles are shaped like a heart.
Nice.
Very nice.
Wait for me, Uncle Thomas.
Why is Thomas following us all this way?
No one likes him.
Somebody painted this on the ground
and I just, I don't appreciate it.
Oh, it hurt.
Ow, my bones.
Well, I'm have it.
10 damage.
Hey kids, time to activate order 666.
666?
I don't know that one, Dad.
Like, I'm seven.
I can't count that high, Uncle.
Shit Jesus.
We won.
Damn it.
No, there's supposed to be the boss.
Oh, wait.
Oh, that's right.
There is the big boss.
Nevermind.
Right?
I think so.
Yeah, it's right up here.
Yep.
This thing here.
Oh.
Send one of the kids to go touch it.
This fucking shaggy looking kid hasn't even said a word.
What do you mean?
I keep talking to Uncle Thomas.
We have been speaking this whole time.
Alungus, there's the time.
Bro, look at this thing.
Are you really here?
Alungus unseals Velda's earthenware bottle.
He's gonna pour it on the thing?
Don't see a pour-o.
He douses the petrified head of the god beast Moatana
in the spicy sweet smelling elixir.
We all look at it together.
Nothing happens.
Credits.
It's not working, is it?
I will.
We're out of time, Ostrichs.
Did they just give us a bottle of Sriracha
and just, well, I don't understand.
They didn't do anything?
They put the hot sauce on the head of the statue.
It was root beer.
It was literally root beer.
We did just pour a bottle of root beer on this.
Why did we do that?
The kid all the way on the right, no personality.
I'm telling you.
Shaggy needs to go.
Just like his mother.
Like, Ostrichs showed up.
You know how long we've been fucking,
like six hours, dude.
Wait, Ostrich, this is not Ostrichs?
This is Ostrichs.
Whatever is over here.
The bird is Moatana.
I think, I think, I think this is, this is Thomas.
Cause you remember how he was reading the book at the start.
Oh, okay.
Ostrichs knew.
This tale was of his telling.
When the first land was raised from the folds of the sea,
two worlds were born out of one.
To Ostrichs, a mighty and arrogant Gorgon hero,
this was creation's mistake.
And he dreamed he'd mend it.
Very little has ever been known of the things
that scrum and scoil beneath the tides.
We know the Gorgons are old.
Old, old, old.
So maybe they aren't easily moved.
My vanity hopes we threw him some surprises,
but it's possible we were his fools from the very beginning.
We unpuzzled the stone and chased that spear of petroglass.
We struck a blow, I think, in taking it.
But our grubbing plunder of a Gorgon heirloom
gave him a story to tell.
Our species cast as the scrabbling villains.
Incited, his Gorgon brethren together rose behind him
to imputer this gentle god.
And the ocean rose while the rain fell
and the ice of the world turned to melt.
For a while, I'm sure he believed his dream
would replace reality.
But it won't.
Is this you talking this whole time?
Is the thing behind us unpetrified?
Yeah, it is.
Ulstrix.
Oh shit, that is a lot.
Kids!
Kill Ulstrix and it will keep coming.
Where is Ulstrix?
Oh.
I don't even know.
All the way in the middle.
Ulstrix is kind of hot.
That's not the kids, that's you, man.
That was me.
That's you.
You tried to kill Ardbar
and you accidentally sent yourself.
Oops, score.
That's a lot of enemies.
My dad taught me that.
I can now.
Whatever, this is a live through it.
Yeah, so he can.
You think you've won, beast?
He's dead.
What are you doing?
You've got yourself a Gorgon stabber
and now he's got nothing left to lose.
Why did you do that?
His final act.
He stabs the beast but dies.
What?
He DPS'd it.
Yeah, he's dead.
He killed your son.
Flame eyes.
I will remove all the joy from your life
before this is over.
Whoa.
Secret bite attack.
He threw an enemy at you.
You all right?
Secret bite attack.
I was supposed to be like crying and like screaming.
He's screaming for his son.
You're like throwing up.
Oh, it's horrible.
Damn it, I can't reach.
Check this out.
Flame eyes.
Light up.
For my cousin.
Ulstrix, you piece of shit.
My boy.
Just like fucking tears are just streaming.
I'm going for Ulstrix.
Spin around and just throw.
Go for me.
Big hit.
And again.
Fire.
Wait, how am I?
You're just doing it.
He's just doing it so wrong.
Oops.
Even more.
Oh, he's ignoring me.
Oh, no, he's not.
Oh, that was eight.
That was seven, damn it.
Holy shit.
The fire actually worked out to be in a good spot.
Oh.
Father, it hurts.
Ardbar is not doing well.
Oh.
Ardbar is not doing that well.
What's wrong?
I don't want to leave my rock.
Oh, shit.
No, you still have armor.
You're good.
Oh, shit.
One damage, all that buildup.
Ulstrix.
I need fire.
There's two fires.
Got it.
Come on.
Thank you, father.
Wait a second.
Just like your dad.
It burns.
No, I was prophesied.
I'm really annoyed that he lived.
We did it.
The mighty Ulstrix finally crumpled before us,
his reeking corpse.
Twitch, Twitch TV.
Still, it was over.
Little plug there.
Some would say we saved the world,
but we did save the ember of it.
We cupped this red coal of life in our sweaty palms,
carried it to the next morning.
Through wreckage, loss, destruction,
it would take time for the water to go down.
The memories to lose their bite,
to rebuild,
to heal,
and maybe to live new lives someday.
It shows us without you.
Not just us.
Just new lives.
Just, yeah, just these two.
Nobody else in the story matters.
But our story was the one in many.
Didn't you write this story in the book
so you writ your own downfall?
No, I had blank pages.
Wait. No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, I did write this.
Thomas the Star wrote this exact story in the book
and made it real.
So he wrote that his husband would leave him
and his son would die.
The implication was that the end of the pages were blank.
No, he wrote the story.
I wrote the story.
Thomas made himself normal.
He made his son die.
He made his husband leave him.
The end.
That's, yeah, I finished the book.
The game has crashed.
The end.
You've won.
Okay, the end.
Oh, there's an after story.
Hold on a minute.
Thomas developed a passion for restoring ruined sites.
He rented out the finished sites to travelers
at a decent nightly rate.
Wait, so I just became like a landlord
or like a hotel owner?
Yeah, you just became a regular landlord.
And then it shows your memory of us singing together.
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
That's awful.
He doesn't even use magic anymore.
I don't, yeah.
Oh, that's, well, am I making money?
The thing is, I had like plus 40 to Lona.
So I don't even know how this happened.
Turned into a landlord Andy.
Odd boss dream of his own parcel research tower
had finally been fulfilled.
He kept it well stocked with flammable powders
and a couple of summoning circles.
Wait, one of the kids died.
Did we hear about that?
Yeah, your kid died.
Mine lived.
Oh, I tried to kill mine, but.
Dude, I was talking to your kid the whole time
as it was my kid.
I know, he kept calling you uncle
and you wouldn't catch on.
The Inon and Elongus could never fully abandon
their adventuring life.
While the danger had dimmed,
there were memories yet to be made.
All right, I do now grasp your reasoning
in bringing me here.
There's my brilliant boy.
I hope you don't mind bringing me Elmish wine.
Remember Thomas?
Yeah.
Whatever happened to him?
I'm sure he's onto something exciting and challenging.
He owns a hotel chain now.
There's 6,000 branches across the country.
He owns some B&Bs.
Elongus gathered as many of the company's stories
as he could and enlisted Ardbar to illustrate them.
Dude, your kid is working.
I guess they did have that many tentacles, didn't they?
What about, you don't wanna ask me about anything?
No.
About our adventure that we had?
We don't even know where you are, dude.
You're just like a fucking Airbnb.
By the way, whose memory is that?
Cause I look pissed.
You remember when we climbed this rock
and there was nothing on it?
Why am I in this room?
You would cheat on your husband on top of the rock?
Also, actually, I think this is the rock we climbed
that turned my face into the wolf,
but also my face is already a wolf.
Oh yeah, that one is.
Yeah, that's what we had.
Oh, weirdly enough, you had both of your lovers sparks
on a cliff side.
So that's just something that, okay, cool.
Yeah, we had a big rock there
and then you expressed your love to me.
And then another big rock shows up
and you express your love to somebody else.
What the fuck is going on here?
Are you saying I'm faking it?
We're saying that you're fickle.
If there's a rock involved,
you're likely to just make bad choices.
I'm just saying a large cliff face
apparently makes you want to like be lovers
with the person you're with.
All right, so we can choose that.
All right, Oddbar does not get Aldecan.
They do not get added to our legacies,
but the other three, they live on.
Choose one hero to promote.
Promote?
Select a hero and move on to the next legacy tier
and their new items, history and abilities
will go with them.
The higher a hero's legacy tier,
the more abilities the hero will come into game with.
Do people just die?
I think Thomas deserves it.
I think you just let-
Look, Thomas becomes a local legend if we promote him.
Oh.
Not just a folk hero.
I think we remain folk heroes
because we disappear into the folk legend,
but you actually stay around
and give people great rates on a room.
Okay, that sounds good to me.
Okay, elemental weapons have been unlocked.
I think this is all separate.
Oh, it is separate.
I chose to promote Thomas.
This character will never be used again.
He's dead to me.
The adventure is over.
Yeah.
He's like 68.
Oh, I see.
I'll promote him in my game.
Yeah, cool.
All right.
That's it, man.
Well, that was really cool.
That was the first campaign in Wildermyth.
How many are there?
There is one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
nine, 10, 10 regular chapters.
And then there's a special multiplayer one
that takes his five player.
Wait, hold on.
That was just one campaign.
One of 11 campaigns.
Oh shit, okay.
And that's not including like,
I think there's also like, you can mod the game.
There's like modded campaigns and stuff.
I've seen that there's mods
that add like more different types
of conversation encounters.
There's a ton of mods that add like new storylines
and like things that can happen to you
and all kinds of stuff.
But that was really fun.
Yeah, it was fun, right?
It's cool.
It's just like an enjoyable, like fun experience.
You just kind of mess around.
That's fun.
Yeah.
If we played again, it would be completely different.
Like everything would be different, which is interesting.
Well, that was a blast.
Thanks for inviting me.
Yeah, thanks for putting it together, stuff.
Banger.
So who's playing Darktide tomorrow?
All of us. Hell yeah.
Of course.
I'm gonna be sponsored to play it.
Anybody wants to play?
Dude, if you need a guy, let me know.
I'll be playing.
Yeah, well, okay.
Cause I think there's like a big pool of people.
I have to get to one now.
Cool.
So I'm gonna love to leave you guys.
Wait, what's yours?
What's the sponsor?
Oh, I have to play wow.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
All right.
So the excitement drained from your body.
Oh, wow.
Oh, cool.
That was a, that was like a little,
that was a little like.
You could have at least faked it, man.
It would have meant a lot to me
if you just could have faked it.
Yeah, that was like an, oh, wow.
Oh, okay.
Cool.
You're like, oh, okay.
That's actually cool though.
It's cool.
I appreciate the invite though, Stuart.
Yeah, we'll catch up tomorrow
cause I think me and Strippin
are probably gonna play Darktide like most of tomorrow.
Yeah, we'll play, we'll play some Darktide tomorrow.
Yeah, we should definitely play.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll see you then.
Thank you, Stu.
See you guys tomorrow.
It was a pleasure, Gemma.
No, it was great too.
I know we've played Darktide, but let's go.
Yeah.
All right, man.
See you guys tomorrow.
See you later.
Bye.
Yeah, more Darktide tomorrow.
I can't even talk.
More Darktide tomorrow.
It's gonna be sponsored, but that, I wonder.
Yeah, we'll probably just play Darktide tomorrow.
Darktide is the new Warhammer 40K co-op survival game.
It's fun.
Able to connect time out because the session ended.
Yeah, that was a lot of fun.
I actually didn't know what to expect going into this.
It was sort of a stir.
It was just like, hey,
do you wanna play this procedurally generated
kind of RPG DND game that just makes random stuff happen?
And it's like, sure, why not?
Hope it was fun to watch.
It was fun to do.
You were lost the entire time.
Yeah.
I think that's part of it, though.
It was definitely funny, but I hope you enjoyed it.
Yeah, so tomorrow we're doing a Warhammer, Darktide,
and then the day after that, Austin Show and I,
I'm gonna be on Austin's stream, gonna be in a big,
we're gonna be doing a flight simulator.
I have no idea what to expect.
I am, I wanna say, hopefully prepared.
It's gonna be a pretty wild experience, so.
If you don't, obviously go follow Austin's channel.
It'll be on Austin Show's channel.
Looking forward to it, should be fun.
Bring sorcery back.
Yeah, I know, and I told you this before,
but I do like these.
I mean, this is, I wouldn't call this a chill stream,
but it kind of was.
We're gonna do way more chill streams,
where we just kind of play something
and just hang out.
Breath of the Wild, yeah.
This was more chill than Miku Picross.
I think there was a,
I would say this was a little high energy at some points,
but it was just kind of playing, it was fun.
But that's it, I will see you guys later.
Have a good rest of your night.
Yeah, that's a perfect place to call it here.
Thanks for watching, everybody.
That was Wilder Myth.
Have a fantastic rest of your night.
See you tomorrow.
Thanks for supporting the stream, always.
You know Otto?
You'll see Otto soon.
But yeah, Darktide tomorrow, probably starting around,
what time?
That's a good question.
Not as early as this started, but not super late.
When, let me see, when should it be?
I don't know, maybe it'll probably,
I wanna play a little bit later in the evening, maybe.
Maybe start around, I don't know,
just keep an eye on Sus.
I don't wanna start too late.
Maybe like two, maybe two, three.
Let's just say three.
And I'm gonna try to make it for two.
I also don't want to have it be too late
because I wanna miss the 7.30 internet crash
that usually happens.
So that sounds like a good time to start.
Two, three o'clock, specific obviously.
Yeah, take care of yourselves.
Thanks for watching.
Thanks to, you know, thanks to the boys.
We'll see them tomorrow.
Take care of yourselves.
Good night, goodbye.
As always, call your mother, you know.
See you tomorrow.