Hey guys, how are you? How's your Saturday afternoon going?
Those of you on pacific time right now, we are still, we're still on Saturday.
I think it's uh, what is it, Wednesday for uh, some of you guys. That PST is three days behind, so
happy uh, happy Tuesday or Wednesday. The, the further you go along the, you know, the hemispheres
here. Imagine being still on Saturday. It'd be really weird. Those of you guys that don't understand,
if the world was much bigger, that would happen. If the earth was 10 times the size that it is,
and you had two places that were, and then the sun still traveled across the globe, you know,
the sun rotated around the earth still the way that it does, it would be Sunday when it was
Tuesday for some people. That's not how it works. Have you ever looked, have you ever looked in a
microscope before? You don't know how that works. Anyways, we're gonna play Celeste. We're gonna
finish it uh, fairly close to the end, so might as well do it. Long stream, because I think it's fun.
But yeah, if the earth was five times its size, can you imagine if the earth, if the earth was
10 times its size and the sun was half its size? What the heck would happen there? We'd be dead.
We wouldn't exist. Yes, we would. I would. I'd find a way. Uh, thank you Tim, Timmy, for the $50.
I hope you have a great stream. Also, I made this. Are you sure you did? Because there's a bunch of
people that are gonna counteract your point here in about five seconds. What did you make? This is
called Jerma Slap. All right, this is a Jermario Slap. Okay, that's pretty, that was pretty good.
That was pretty good. Very, that was actually really good. Show us? Uh, I can't, how come I can't link it?
I just, I just copy and pasted this. Why can't I? What the hell? I just, I just had it open.
There you go. Jermario Slap. Thank you Timmy. Thank you for the $50 too. I haven't even started yet.
Just turned the stream on already. Somebody drops a $50 fucking bill here.
5,000 bits. Thank you. And I don't think we need to waste very much time because we already know
what we're doing. Where is Shito? Shito is sleeping over here and he's not to be awoken. He's very
tired after last night. He was worked very hard. He sang his heart out for you guys and now he needs
a rest. Who is Shito? Oh, right. People that weren't here. I'll pick him up just very carefully.
Make sure that, no, he's still sleeping. He's still asleep. Maybe show him for a minute.
Quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet. Don't wake him up. He likes to be held like this.
This is Shito. You okay? Yeah, he's fine. Back to bed. I know my hair is wicked fucked up because
I was in the wind. I know my hair looks like fucking al dente spaghetti today and that's
because I was out in the wind. I was in the wind. All right, so let's go ahead and put Celeste on
the screen. We're going to finish it. We're very, very close to, well, maybe not very close,
but we're definitely close to the end of the game. And why don't we get it on there right now? Hey,
look at that. Celeste. Your hair looks splendid today. Thank you. Hey, thanks. That's, I've never
heard anybody say that before. Oh my, holy crap. All right, so here are your options today. We've
got, um, we can climb the mountain in Celeste. We can check out the credits or we could find out
once and for all what the heck's in that cube. I think I'm looking forward to that. Trying to
figure that out. Wonder what Epic's going to do here. Doing the same, same joke from yesterday.
Yeah, I'll get, okay, synopsis. Here's the, here's the, here's the synapsis of this whole thing,
right? The whole story of Celeste is you got to climb a mountain and there are trials. You meet
somebody along the way. They got stuck in a, a Fortnite cube. When am I going to get that
thing open? You know, the guy gets stuck in a cube. You got to help him. You got to break him out.
You're being chased by a version of yourself and then you get to the top of the mountain.
Did you know it's impossible to outrun your own reflection? Well, it depends on if you're on the
moon or not because the moon's gravity is like 10% of earth. So it's Celeste part two. Theo,
you're awake. Am I? I'm skeptical. I had a messed up nightmare. Yeah, about that. Wait.
Oh, yep. It's all coming back to me now. It's all coming back to you. Boomerang
from Cartoon Network. That actually happened. Thanks for getting us out of there. I'm glad we
were in it together. I don't know if I could have done that alone. What? This is the first time you
get dialogue choices? It only took them like seven hours into the game. Wait, why am I playing as
this character? What's really going on here? Clay, this is, this is not a normal mountain.
What's really going on here? Should have told you sooner. Back at the old ruins, a part of me
escaped from a mirror. A part I'm not very proud of. I swear I dreamt it. You think the mountain
made her real? Yeah, she's been haunting me the whole time. She lashed out at Mr. Oshiro. I think
she was the reason the gauntlet stalled off. She was there in the temple. Oh, fucking, why didn't
you say something, kid? I wouldn't have gone into that temple if I knew that mountain was capable
of doing this shit. I try to stop you. You could have mentioned that your demon doppelganger was
on the loose. Come on, Theo. You know how crazy this sounds. I didn't even believe myself.
All right, all right, kid. I understand. Next time just talk to me though, all right?
Promise I'll believe you. Voice actor. Okay, which is the right one?
Hmm. Thank you for believing me. He's trapped in the bit for believing in me back there. I mean,
believing in you was the easy part. I wish I could have helped. I was pretty useless stuck in that
thing inside the cube. You actually helped a lot. Honestly, I couldn't have made it without your
support. I don't want to do that one. Let's do this one. Why is it so easy for you to trust me?
Seriously, you barely know me. Honestly, you remind me of my sister. That's adorable.
What's she like? Oh, you love her. Actually, you might not get along at first, but you eventually
would love her. She's a literal rock star. She's a musician, kid? That's so fucking awesome. All
right, I gotta get out of here. I gotta end the stream. Okay, she's not literally a literal rock
star. Alex is just amazing at everything. She's studying to be a civil rights lawyer.
Wow, how do I remind you of her? You both live so deep inside your own heads.
Oh, Alex has this amazing internal compass. It's obvious that she'll get where she needs to be.
I can see that in YouTube. I wish I could say the same for myself.
Uh, they're sitting real close to the fire. I'm just realizing this now,
which one of them's gonna put their hand in it to prove how good they are at video games, I wonder.
Your sister sounds great. Your sister sounds great. Really remind you of her.
That's a reference from last night if you weren't here. Are you kidding me? You're the one who's
dead set on climbing the mountain, and you don't even know why. That's classic Alex.
Huh? I'm just teasing you. Why are you climbing the mountain anyways?
I don't even know why. I just had to get out of my head. I'm stuck in a cycle.
You're preaching to the choir here. I've had many a soul-destroying day job.
Work is fine, actually. I just, uh, I'm going crazy. I can't think about dumb crap. It doesn't
matter. My brain fixates on these stupid things that happened forever ago. I should be over them.
None of it even matters. But, oh, you didn't say but. I'm good at keeping up appearances,
but the truth is I'm barely holding it together. Sorry, that's pretty rough.
Can I help? You already are. It feels good to say it out loud. You don't talk to anyone about it.
No, not really. My mom knows I get depressed and I have panic attacks. That's about it.
No wonder you feel trapped. How do you cope with anything?
I drink mostly and get mad at people on the internet. Get mad at people on the internet.
Uh, I should get some sleep. Oh, are you sure you don't want to keep talking?
I'm tired too, but we have a lot to talk about. Fucking internet. Wait, skip? What do you mean
skipping? I just said I was tired. Wait, I just told you I was tired. I didn't say I'm done with
the conversation. I wasn't trying to skip it. Not skipping. You're right, I can sleep later. See,
I just didn't know what to do. I'm just checking all the dialogue options. I should get some sleep.
Hey, what do you think built this temple anyways? It looks ancient. It must predate everything
else in the mountain. The resort, the ruins, the city. Either you skip or you stall. There
ain't no in-between apparently. There's a lot of history here. Yeah, the mountain has meant
so many things to so many people. Mountain is always, um, it's always really, really pointed
out here. We're not really on a mountain. There's going to be some invisible link scenario where
they're going to be wiped away and it's going to be like this forest has meant so many things.
They're going to be a forest. Just watching. There's going to be trees behind me. There's
going to be birds. That's where the bird comes from. I don't understand why that crazy old
lady lives here. You ran into her too. What's her deal? I think she's just a mean person,
but she does seem pretty content living out here. Would you mind talking about what depression is
like? It sucks. It's kind of hard to do it. That would be hard to answer. Yeah, but what does it
feel like? Alex struggles a little too. I really want to understand. We can talk about something
else if you want. It's like I'm at the bottom of the ocean. I can't see anything in any direction.
It's claustrophobic, yet I feel exposed. I remember feeling normal, but now it just feels
out of reach no matter what I try. And again, I was probably always messed up.
It just took something hurtful to bring it out. There must be something wrong with me.
No, Mary, I don't believe that. What happened? I'm sure it's not your fault.
By the way, if you are depressed and you're having problems, it's sometimes not in your control.
So blaming yourself is the worst possible thing you can do.
Because a lot of times it has something to do with something you can't even control yourself.
I guess I thought that I could. I don't know. I'm just floating in this abyss,
swimming in a random direction, hoping that I find something that's really why I'm here,
but I can't escape myself. I'm literally fighting myself the entire way. Maybe this is all pointless.
John, you just saved my life. That's not pointless. Yeah. Look, you're a good person.
You're a little intense, but you're a good person. I think you're just trying to push
out of that rut you're stuck in. And that's a totally legit reason to climb the mountain.
Maybe. That's helpful. This part of you that's haunting you, maybe she comes with the territory.
So you think I'm stuck with her forever. Well, she's stuck with you too. That's not helpful.
So you want to destroy this part of you. Won't that hurt you too? If I don't, she's just going
to keep bullying me. She says she's protecting me, but that's obviously not true. Maybe she
thinks she is. She could be some kind of twisted defense mechanism. Honestly, who cares? She has
so much control over me. I hate it. Maybe you can learn to control her instead. The father,
the feather helps a lot. Thanks for teaching me that. The father, like just one of my grandpa's
many knuckets of wisdom. Father, the priest. That's what I got out of that somehow. I don't
know. My brain is... What brought you to the mountain? Why are you on the mountain? Why are
you here? What brought you to the mountain? I'm just kind of bumming around as usual.
Started this new job in Ohio. I thought I finally knew what I was supposed to be doing with my life,
but I hated it. So I quit after a week and I hopped a bus to Canada. I just felt this urge
to get lost in the middle of nowhere. Now that I'm saying it out loud, I realize how flaky it sounds.
That's a day-old joke. That's not a day-old joke. That's a game, a current game reference.
Just because we said this yesterday, we're in the same game. We got the same references
because we're doing the same thing, right? It just sounds like you're under a lot of pressure.
Not really. Everyone is so patient with me though. I guess I'm putting a lot of pressure on myself.
People always think I'm comparing myself to Alex, but I swear that is not the problem.
I'm just worried that I'll never figure out where I'm going.
You said you wanted to feel lost. Maybe you should just embrace that for now.
Maybe. Same game, same jokes. That's not a joke. I just said he was probably from some random
city in America, like Ohio, and it turned out to be Seattle. So in my headcanon, it's Ohio.
Where's the auto-clicker? That's a boring headcanon. Why? What? Be close to your
grandmother. Are you close to your grandfather? Are you close to your father? Yeah, I was.
Oh, I'm sorry. It's okay. That's just how it is. All I can do is stay positive and live a
meaningful life because that's what he would want. I'm so sorry, Keel. Thanks. You know what? I want
to remember this night. Let's take a selfie. I thought you'd never ask. You know, despite
everything, I feel pretty good right now. Wait a second. You're going to reach the summit tomorrow?
Don't junks it because I am currently John Junks. I tried with that one. Yeah,
I'm excited. I'm ready to put this all behind me. I'll be cheering you on. Yeah, but that's
if I'm in a Jax moment, if Jax takes over and does really well and I fail,
I jinxed myself. I Jonksed myself. That's a Jonks moment. That's a Jonks. That's a Jon.
Figured it out. Got it. I'll be cheering you on. We should get some sleep.
Okay, good night, Theo. Thanks for being cool.
What can I say? What can I say? Comes naturally. Let me just make sure I got that good feel here.
I do. All right, grab it. Okay, you go supersonic. New mechanic, supersonic. You gotta dash into
these ones. I'm probably missing a secret or something. What is he saying, Smash Brothers?
He growls and he says, now I'll show you where he goes. No, I'll show you. That's exactly how he
does it too. Like you might've thought that was like terrible and we're dropping frames here. Oh,
fuck. The Northern lights are so beautiful. Yeah. Where are we? We need to talk. Okay. Wait, am I?
Did I get to the summit? I'm above the summit. I did it. I finally understand who you are. You're
not my true reflection. I'm not. You're everything I need to leave behind. You're cruel, paranoid,
controlling. Why would you say that? No, it's okay. I understand now. I don't need you anymore.
So you're just abandoning me. I'm setting you free. We'll both be so much happier. You're so,
so stupid. You think you can just leave me behind? You think you can blame everything on me?
You think you're above me? That's it. I'm crawling out of the panel. Answer me. Calm down. Calm down.
Breathe. Use the feather. But I don't have my, I don't have my box. It's gonna take me a minute.
Unless you would probably be pretty hard to breathe right now with a tendril wrapped around my
diaphragm squeezing, right? I didn't do it. You're going to think about a feather to stop me.
You are not above me and you can't climb this mountain. It's time to accept that.
Oh, what's happening? Oh, God damn it.
Glass. Oh, come on. That's all right. I fell a long way. I did the movie fall
where you fall an incredibly long way, but you land on something that will save you every time.
Secret? Couldn't get the landing. No, I couldn't get the, I'm making a joke for the video landing
where I land and go two. That's what I was going to do. I was going to say two
and it's funny. 20 hindsight here. Looking back that actually would probably not have been funny
at all. All right, let's see. You're going to bring you over here. What's down here?
Maybe smash through here. Back up maybe. What about down here? I think I'm going to ride you back up.
Oh, feather. Oh, all right. Now what? I guess just go up. Is there any water
inside the water fountain? Well, I don't know. Okay, I want you to take a look at what just
happened there. I'm very serious. I'm very curious and serious about this. I pressed up on the
controller straight up and I went left and right. I want to make sure you understand. I just need to
make sure people know that. I didn't do that. Let's see. Take this over here. Wait, no. Can he break
all that? Hold on. I think I can break all that shit up there. No, fuck. No. That's kind of awkward
to do. All right. Tell me if I'm wasting my time here. Can I actually have him go up and break
through that? Or is this just a waste of time? Maybe it might be possible. I'll try it one more
time. I don't care. I don't care if it's a hundred thousand extra points. It is possible,
isn't it? I guess it doesn't matter at all. Shit. It's very easy. Well, obviously not considering I
couldn't do it. Oh, shit. Okay. Come on. This way. To the right. It's a giant mirror. I was so close.
It's over now. Why won't she leave me alone? I hate her. I'll never be able to get rid of her.
And she was right. I couldn't climb the mountain. No, that's not. I'm still on the mountain. So,
you know what I mean? I did. I did climb the mountain. Don't let people in chat tell you
you didn't do it. Don't let them get that. Don't let them say that. They'll use the little semantics
to make it so you didn't climb it. You got to the top of that mountain. You fell off the top of the
mountain, but you still got up there. You flew to the top. That's cheating. Uh-uh. Uh-uh. No.
See, there they go. There they go again. Use the semantics to try to tell you you didn't do
something. Oh, fuck. Wrong way. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I don't know why.
This, for some reason, this, this, this thing in particular is just my brain and has trouble
doing this of all the things in the game. Can I go through the top? I might be able to break
through the top. Where's the shot? You conquered the mountain horizontally. I guess I'm just supposed
to go up there with the feather, but I'm gonna be out the side here. What's over here?
Okay. Well, there's this. I can get that. Fuck. Come on. Oh, no. Oh, I got it. I don't know what
the hell's up here. I'm gonna just look. Nothing. So, I gotta go to the left, but man, I'm gonna
fall because I don't know what's over there. Oh, but what about, what, what's over here?
Shit. I can't hold on to anything. Oh, god damn it. All the way to the left. Well,
might as well get it. I'm here. Okay. Let's go. Oh, okay. Nothing else up here.
I mean, there is, but oh, oh, time to get trapped in a puzzle. What can I do? Can I even do anything?
I have to sing. Didn't I just try to do that? I swear to god, I dashed into that. All right.
Look at the bottom here. So, we've got play, pause, play in reverse. No, we've got play.
Yeah, pause. Okay. I don't think I can even do anything with this. Did I touch them? There's
something missing here. Maybe I have to get it. I can't do anything with this statue, right?
It's the infinity gauntlet. Well, I really, I don't have any idea.
Okay. Elevator close button. The hell is the elevator close button?
You should have jumped for the platform. It's a dash pattern. Okay. Well, how do I know what
sound it is? Those are all. Okay. So hold on a minute. Wait, wait, wait. There's two light
purples. I don't know what it, I don't know what the sequence would be though. The pattern comes
from chapter one. Okay. So I'm, I mean, at this point I'm in the room. There's no way I can do
it unless I go back to chapter one. Well, I guess I can't do it. It's impossible. Okay.
Could just Google it. Yeah, but I could, I could. What is it? What is it? What's the secret?
You want it? Yeah. What is it? Cheating. I'm cheating. Well, I didn't get the thing in the
first chapter and like, I want, I want to do that. I want it. What's the password?
It comes up later. Does it? I highly recommend you just skip this.
No, that's, did you give me the Konami code? That's not the correct, what, how do I do it?
That one didn't work either. Okay. It's a secret that I didn't get. It's a thing I missed in the
first chapter. I'm sure it's fun in there. Up, up, down, down. Stop. Up, up, left, right, left,
right, down, right, up. Stop. No. God damn it. Up, up. Do it again. Use the handy IGN guide. I can't
click on that. That means I have to alt tab. Up. I didn't do anything. Press play first.
You guys are putting random shit in here. Up. It didn't work. I'm not doing diagonal dashes.
You guys didn't say diagonal. You're saying left. Oh, you're saying what? No, say D. Up,
up, right. God damn it. Up, left, down, right. Up, left, down, right.
Just too many things. Just clear it. Clear it. Clear it. Got it. All right. What's,
hold on a second, guys. Is, wait, wait, wait. Let me be very, very, I gotta ask this. I need a mod
to answer this question because I don't trust anybody in here giving me up, up, down, downs.
Um, is that, that first one I didn't know, but am I about to just cheat through the whole thing?
Like what, do I not have the information to do the rest of this or will I get it eventually?
So don't just do this. Like that first one I didn't know because I wasn't going to get it.
Baked flakes. Who cares? No, I'm not doing it. I got the one that I couldn't get. I'm going to move
on. I'm going to, no, I'm not cheating. No cheating. I look, I'm the villain in the movie
that realizes what he's doing is wrong. No, fuck. You know what I'm saying? Like I can't,
I can't just have you guys give me the answers. Nothing up there. All right. What's the next one?
Let's just get, just do it. Who cares? Who gives a shit? What's this next one? All right. Torch three.
Just looking up on your phone. Up, up, down, down. Nope.
Fuck. I missed it. I didn't get it right. All right. What's torch four?
I don't fucking remember I did this. Okay. All right. Got it. I did it. Now everybody can go back,
go back to bed. I cheated. No, you cheated. Hey, I may have committed the crime, but you drove
the car. No, no, no, no, no. I drove the car. This is my stream. This is my broadcast. I'm,
I'm the driver. You committed the crime. I'm the driver. In fact, you're way more at fault than I
am. You're going to go to jail for way longer. And yes, I am the driver. I may have told you
to commit that crime, but you still committed it. I said, Hey, can you like commit that crime for me?
I'll drive you if you do. And you're like, sure. Okay. Then I open it. I opened it.
But one of these, it's going to be a cassette tape. Yeah. If they're not over 18, it's the
adult who is driving that is at fault. Oops. Oh, fuck. Oh my fuck. Oh my God. What did I do that
for? I'm a fucking God. I'm a God. I'm going to B-side. Now where the hell do I go? There's a way
to the right. What are you guys writing? Up, right, up, left, right. Stop giving me codes
for the crystal room. I already did that. I don't know where to go. I don't know where to go now.
You guys are writing codes for the crystal room. We already did that.
Bottom right, top left, top right, right, right. Don't do it. Don't. I can leave the screen by
going this right. Oh, what if I go up, up, right, right, up, right? Oh, okay. I hold on. Up, up,
up, right, up, right. Nothing? No. Just climb the mountain. There has to be a reason why I
can get in here. Nah. I don't even need that thing. Watch this. Okay. I think I need that thing.
Oh, shit. Fuck. This can't go up, can it? No. Just climb it. Oh, all right. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. For some reason, I thought I had to go up. There's two walls and a long corridor going up.
I thought I had to jump it. Oh, shit. I have to grab onto the other side. Oh, my God. That's
actually going to be kind of annoying. I'm telling you, these block people are causing me huge
problems. It's because when I was bouncing off, I didn't know. Look, have you seen me fuck up the
feather once? Oh, fuck. Okay. I need to stand up, I think. Stand up and I don't know. I have to jump
just like launch. Okay. Fine. Zoom. I hate these things. I really do. I don't like these things.
You have to jump and then fall and grab. I could have gone up. What is that thing?
Pinball? It is pinball. Anything I can do in here? Let's see what's up.
I'm just going to keep going until I run into something. Down or up?
I guess I'm going to do down. Oh, it's a bubble. What am I supposed to do? I'm going to break them
all because I'm going to take a guess here and say that I have to fly through all of this
or something. I wonder if I'm correct. Nothing else in any of these walls. Break this one
up and around. If I was a video game, I would definitely have a scenario where I have to fly
through this. But oops. I have to bounce off. All right. Now what did I hit? Should I just smash
into these things? That has to be a point to that, right? Is there no point to click
feather? Minus two for the scream title. Oh, I forgot about the scream title. You're right.
Come on. What's the point of this? Nothing at all. I don't believe that at all. I'm sorry.
I put it down. Am I in a maze or something or am I just progressing in a way that I can progress?
Just skip that one, right? Okay. You got to go bounce from that top right one to the bottom
left one. Stop saying passwords for the thing. Well, that was wrong. I guess I have to dash
left into it. Flame Xbox. Just use cheats. Bubble. I was pretty good at this in Yoshi's Island.
The helicopter levels. You're probably wondering, my god, how does he do it?
My hands were on the controller so it might work. The helicopter levels were great. They were really
fun. I made it to the lift. Oh, hello again. Of course you're here. He really doesn't seem like
he enjoys the game and is just panicking about how he has to play it right. What? I think this
game is great. It's hard. You can't do it perfect the first time. What? Didn't we already go over
this? Okay, if you made me a treasure map and you made a bunch and I've never seen... You made me
a treasure map in a state I've never been to before. Jeremy, I've got a really cool treasure
map for you. What you're going to do is you're going to find a treasure and I've hid it somewhere
and there's an elaborate set of instructions that you're going to go through. All right, cool.
And you hand me the paper. You hand me the treasure map. I've never been to the state of Utah
before in my life. It's in Utah. And I close the door in the car, right? Like I get in the car and
door closes. Engine turns on at the window. Roll the window down. Yeah, what's up, man?
Hey, why have you not been to the treasure yet? What are you talking about, man?
Why did you... You were supposed to take a left at the statue at the interstate 91. I know,
but I don't know that. I have the treasure in my hand. You just gave it to me. I'm trying to...
I don't... I didn't... I haven't seen that. I've never been to the state before. Wait, hold on.
You've never been to Utah before? You're terrible. Okay, thanks for the treasure map, by the way.
Okay, like roll the window up and then I leave. And then you throw in a rock when I'm leaving. No,
what I'm saying is there's no way to play the game right. I've never even seen the game.
I'm getting new mechanics introduced to me on an hourly basis. You didn't take a left at that road
that you had never been on before. Well, I got to read the map first, man. It was just one guy.
It's over. It's probably for the best. No treasure for you. Utah hater. What? I've just said I've
never been to Utah. That's a whole nother map you just made for me. No, you just like doctored
chat footage of me. The mountain doesn't pull any punches. Yeah, I get it. I wasn't strong enough
to climb your stupid mountain. Long story short, this game's a lot of fun and I've been very much
enjoying this game. I hate the game. Where are you getting that from? What treasure map have you
handed me? I wasn't strong enough to climb your stupid mountain. You can laugh at me again all you
want. I didn't mean actually laugh. He hates this game. Why would I stream it for another day in a
row if I hated the fucking game? Sometimes you gotta know when to throw in the towel.
You'll get over it. You know what? I had a lot of time to think climbing out of this cave
and I'm already over it. That part of me was right. I can't do this. I'll just go home to my sad life
and be miserable forever. You clearly aren't over it. I don't want to give up, but no matter how hard
I try, she sabotages me every step of the way. A lot of kids come here to climb this mountain only
to give up. It's a shame that you fell. I was starting to think you'd make it. What makes me so
special? I've never met someone so angry at themselves. Honestly, I thought you'd reached
summit just to spite yourself. Gee, thanks. This girl you're talking about, it sounds like she's
holding you back. Talk to her. Figure out why she's so scared. You think she's scared? I guess I never
thought of it that way. Stop wasting both of our time and ask her, what have you got to lose?
I don't know how to find her. She's part of you, right? If you look for her, she won't take long
to find. So you know about the mountain's power. Of course I know. I live here. I tried to warn you.
You need to work on your messaging. I'm sorry for being the one guy. Well, it happened again
and that's twice in one stream and that you know that that gets you. I'm not supposed to be doing
that. A glimpse of the truth is good for people even if most can't accept what they see. Why would
I ban them? What are you talking about? That's a valued member of this community. They're not
going to get banned. There's no shame in running back to your car and driving away. Hey, hey,
why are you not in Utah yet? No, no, I just closed the door. Where can I find a fucking rock?
Someday you'll be ready and then you'll come back. No, I'm gonna see this through.
No shame in driving to Utah. Oh, that's right, I gotta stop. I gotta be very quiet because the
louder I am, there's a chance that I can wake up Shito and I don't want to do that. He's been
having a really relaxing day. No more running. I thought so. Good luck. Good luck. So let's go.
Utah is a five minute drive from Las Vegas. It is not a five minute drive.
It's five minutes. Your map ain't even correct. I, in fact, I take your map and I drive to the
place that you put on that location. I get lost. A fucking wolf like runs in front of the car
and like barks and I have to smear off the side of the road and I crash and I get it. I have no
cell phone reception. Like where the fuck am I? And like I call you and I go, hey man, uh, just
was, I'm curious. What's what this map you gave me? Is this even, how is this? I'm not, I don't think
I'm in Utah. And you hang the phone up. I'm still stuck in the fucking middle and I don't know where
I am. How can you stand living here? Isn't it hard to deal with this all the time? It's true. You
never really get used to it, but it keeps me sharp. That's a funny prank to be honest. God,
I, I like that. But the mountain is so confrontational. Streamer dies after listening
to a chat member. Sure. It doesn't beat around the bush. Celeste mountain is a place of healing.
So let's just stop talking. Stop. What do you mean stop? This is a live stream. Stop talking.
Oh, God damn it. I'm sorry. She don't, she don't. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's like, it's okay. Yeah, it's okay. Back to sleep. Back to sleep.
Shit's okay. Yeah. Okay. Good boy. I'm sorry. See what I'm fucking saying? Stop them.
Wouldn't have fucking happened if I wasn't talking about this fucking car thing. Celeste mountain is a
place of healing, dear. The first step of healing is confirming the problem.
It's never easy. Tell me about it. What is Cheeto? No, it's Cheeto. Cheeto is my
actually alive automaton, near automata friend. What the hell? I guess I'm just going to walk
into this. What's next? All right. We've got to walk. Wait, secret. Oh shit. Oh, wait.
Come on. I think I'm just going to go down. There are no more secrets.
Ah, there are no more secrets. Are you sure about that? Oh, where am I fucking going? Wait a minute.
No, I have to think maybe if you didn't touch anything, maybe it would just go all the way
down to the fucking thing. I can't do the speed strategy to go that way. Oh, fuck. Okay. It's
right, left, right. Where are my berries? I didn't even say it right. Sorry. Nothing over there.
That feeling that face when you will never be the one guy. Sure about that. Where am I?
No, this is just battle toads. No, it's not.
How much further do I have to go? Let's do it again. I'm just kidding. Jump. Uh-oh, found you
looking for me. I thought you were done with me. That was a mistake. I'm sorry. You think you've
got it all figured out? You think you don't need me? I said, I'm sorry. We need to move
past this. You expect me to trust you? You aren't innocent here either, but I know you're scared.
Look, we're at rock bottom. There's no point in fighting. I can keep digging. I could pull us
down to the center of the earth. What would be the point? Let's climb out of here together.
Come close to me and I'll make you regret it. Do I have to just bop you again? Okay,
so it's just a question of... I hit you. I just have to touch you. Watch out for the falling cubes.
Nowhere to go except down. There you go. Laser? All right, so there's like a half second on it.
Where have I heard that sound before? I swear to God, I've heard this sound somewhere.
I'm like a Super Nintendo game. No! Xbox controller? Why have you given me a wrong
treasure map? Where'd the platform go? Oh, shut up. Not you guys. I'm talking about...
Oh, you had to do the little ball there. Come on. Damn it. I'm stupid. I had it. Keep overcompensating.
Look at the balls. Balls. How much further are you gonna go? I can make that without it.
Without using it. No, I can't. Oh, that's a big turn. Okay, I gotta start that way earlier.
This is a long string of events. Oh, shit. I didn't even see the fucking spikes. Oh, fuck.
I'm so used to this. That's the end right there. I got it. What are you doing? Stop. Just jump over
normally. Oh, don't... I don't want to wake him up. What the... Kaizo block. I did you a favor.
You aren't a mountain climber. I'm just trying to help you. None of this would have happened
if you had just listened to me. We're still going. We're still going. Oh, probably should have jumped.
I got it. Okay, we're fine. Stupid spike was there. Stupid jelly spikes. Oh, my God. They're up too
high. Delete those. Literally the stationary fucking object is the thing that causes so many
problems. Oh, my God. The Xbox controller. I'm going to beat it up. This thing sucks, though.
I'm gonna be real honest. I was supposed to get the other controller set up. I just didn't do it.
No. Oh, god damn it. Why? I just let it happen. God. Just slowing the game down. When you gotta
like... I need to go fast. You got me right at the end. Right at the end, you got me. I did it again.
I just have to... I don't have to dash. Oh, my God. Him would be done with this sequence already.
Oh, my fucking Jesus. No. Oh, what the fuck? God. You gotta launch off of it.
What the fuck? I always follow you down. Oh, all right. You always follow the direction that she
goes. She like goes down or goes right, and this time it's just spikes. That's the first time that
you've gone in the same direction where you couldn't go. My fucking Jesus. There's even more of this
shit. It doesn't end. I feel like I'm gonna dream. Maybe that's intentional.
No, wait. What do I do? I got you. I did it. I win. I win the game. That was fun. Fine. You win.
I guess you don't need me after all. If you don't want me to go away, I'll try.
That's not what I want. I need your help more than ever. Please, let's work together.
Work together. You're joking, right? It's okay to be scared. A selfie? I leveled up. What does that
mean? I can dash. I can dash twice now. They gave me the double jump that I so wanted so badly.
Perfectly balanced. Like all things should be.
Just testing it out. Now try to climb the mountain one more time.
Okay. Wait, I thought. Oh, how did we do that? If we can climb like that, maybe we can still
reach the summit. Before dinner. That's what you should have said. You still want to climb
the mountain. Why would we go back up there? It's good to see you two playing nice. Hey,
thanks for talking some sense into me earlier. Well, that's because I'm you from the future.
Glad I can still be useful every now and then. John? John, you're okay.
I ran down to help, but it looks like you're doing fine. Thanks, Theo. Honestly, maybe that
fall was what I needed. Is this the part of you that you were talking about? She's like
an adorable goth John. Hi. You were right, Theo. I shouldn't be afraid of her.
Haha, goth John. If her and I work together, I think we could still finish the climb.
That's so rad. Wait, no, I didn't agree to this. You said we talk about things first. You're right.
I understand that you're scared, but we both know that this is something we want to do.
We have to try one last time. That was the worst character. I don't know. We were so close and then
we fell. The mountain aka the forest tore us apart. Yeah, that happened, but I have to believe we can
put that behind us. I have to believe we're capable of this. It's not a bad idea. It'll still be
difficult, mind you, but I'm amazed you got as far as you did butting heads like you were.
I reckon you can make it if you cooperate, but please add me too and get a triple jump.
Can I help? You already done so much for me. Let me hold you back at least. This won't take long.
We're gonna get the rock music theme of the main theme on the last level. Less than 100.
And I got a B-Solid. This is the top. I made it to the top of the mountain.
But all will be revealed. That. Actually, I think I see where they're going here. We'll find out.
The summit. Here it comes. I'm gonna go.
Here comes the electric guitar. Watch. Come on. Do it. Here it comes. Here it comes. Do it.
It's building so much. It's a piano. It's not an electric guitar. Wait. What am I doing?
I was hoping for like a... No. No. Wait. Hold on. Secret?
No. No, that's it. That's gonna... I got it. I got it. I got it. I had it the first fucking
time. I had it the first goddamn time. I had it. I just had to go left once. I did it. So I need
to get that in a second here. Okay, I get it. To go left. Up left. If the Xbox controller
wasn't the worst human invention. I mean, we're talking about like number one worst
invention ever in the history of humanity. I mean, this is worse than the coffee maker.
Pretty bad invention. Whoa, wait. I thought we'd fly up. Things get clogged in like fucking two
months. Everyone's like, what are you talking about? Coffee maker. Use a coffee maker for a month.
And then guess what? You gotta fucking put vinegar in a damn thing. Do you not change the filter?
That's in the instructional booklet. We're getting the hang of it. You say so. I missed a secret.
And well, sometimes you get secrets missed. Stop jinxing it. Yeah, I'm talking about the clean...
Yeah, I'm talking about the clean. You don't know. I'm not talking about you put vinegar
in the coffee maker to make coffee. I'm talking about when you clean it. What?
And then the coffee for the rest of all time tastes just awful. Like salad dressing. Your coffee
tastes like salad dressing after you clean it. I need to look at this. Why would you do that?
Hey, I would like everybody in the chat right now to type in coffee maker cleaning clean
cycle vinegar. That's how that's it is in the instructional manual. Do it. Oh, I'm telling
everybody that you drink vinegar coffee. Don't you dare do that. Oh, no, you did. This looks
kind of elaborate. So let me see. Jump up. Let's just go for it. Forget it.
Okay. Well, whoops.
I guess I could go this way. Wait, do I miss out on something by not going that way?
What's the point of going up there? Secret or something? I guess I'll try it.
French press is a thing. I'm just, I'm just talking nonsense. Don't worry about it.
All right, I gotta pay attention. Time to pay attention. Back to pee too. Has it been two
hours? Because that's when I go to the bathroom every single time. No, wrong thing. I don't know.
Okay. I swear to God, there's something wrong with my body. I absolutely have to be. I have to pee
every two hours. Is something wrong with me? Are you doctors in here? Seriously? Is it drinking
too much vinegar? Damn it. Just trying to jump over it. Why won't it activate now? Like, activate.
What the hell are you doing? I'm going to scream. This is not even necessary. Just have to activate
the thing and then jump over it like that. Oh my God. Good diagonal jump. Xbox. He's starting.
I'm getting mad at circumstantial things. Not in the game. There's nothing to do in the game.
You guys are kidding me. Let's take a look. Here's the secret berry. Sick. Ah, sick. No,
that's not right. Am I beach ready? Probably not. No, definitely not.
Why are you asking me that question? I couldn't just grab the edge. Shit. I'm never going to have
a beach ready body. Is it like a thing? Is it a meme or something? No. What did I say it out loud?
I'm insane. Oh my God. I gotta pee. I didn't even get the damn thing. What?
Jeremy, what are you thinking? Why are you doing this? Oh, I'm going to say something disgusting
in a second if I'm not careful. Huh? Huh? I'm going to say it like pee. I'm going to say
something horrible about piss. I was going to be like, I don't even care. I'm going to pee right
into the ground. I was going to say something fucked up like that. Uh oh. I threw that without
dashing, can't I? Clappy bird. No pee until victory. I already made that video. Oh, well,
that works too. Doesn't it? Cool. Shit. Hydrant. How much time is left on the piss timer?
Uh, well, it's almost been two hours. So give or take 15 minutes. That's why I gravitated
towards the hydrant probably. You're right. How are you feeling? I'm just waiting for something
to go wrong. What's going on? What? We're getting a lot of time outs here. What are you guys
misbehaving? No matter what happens, I'll be right here with you. You know what's really scary? I'm
starting to believe you. 1,000 meters. Oh, ding dong. First try. Didn't even know I was
supposed to go this way. I keep thinking that song is my doorbell. I just go through twice.
Just go through twice. Making this harder on myself than I need to. That was easy. Oh shit.
Nice job Xbox. I wanted to go up. Relax. Relax. I don't know what to do. I know what to do.
Perfect. We're going too fast. Probably already missed a ton of shit. Nope. Nope. Can I stand on
something? No. What am I doing? No. Your shitty crusty muscle memory is not this way. Go the other
way. The way you were going before. I'll give it a shot. I've got the right to do. We've got to go
down. Complete the game with a rock band guitar. Sorry to disappoint you. I'm not sure it would be
possible for me to rock band this. Secret. That's the proof right there that the rock band controller
is not fucking very good. Saw that. Watch it happen. Nice job back there. Complaining about
the controller. All right. I'm going to stop. I'm going to stop complaining about the controller
because at the end of the day I'm the one that's operating. I'm the one that's driving the car.
So you know what I mean? Get a different steering wheel. Rip it out. Just get a screwdriver. Take
it out and just order one from Amazon and put it back in. Ms. Positivity over here. You're so
supportive. Don't push your luck. 1500 meters. No, I can get that straw. 10 minutes till I'm
going to pee my pants. And what are you thinking? You could have waited. You could have grabbed the
ledge. Why do I keep forgetting that's a possibility? Too much meat boy. I'm telling you. The piss is
causing this. Just got like electrocuted. Every muscle in my body just went like
I'm just trying to go too fast that you can't do that in this game.
You have to just do it when it's right. Not about who's operating it. It's having a bad car. I hate
this car. I hate. Oh stop. Have we found have we found the one strawberry in the game that's going
to make me like rage quit the whole game? And it's the it's arguably the easiest one in the entire
game in the whole game. Well, that's not correct. How do I get that one? I hate this shit. I hate
the like fucking moving little thumb things. I just want I don't want to do this one. Somebody
else do it for me. Not making it work. I gotta wait. In fact, tried to go up to the right. I
tried as hard as I could and I tried it again. Oh my god. I swear to you. I swear to you. I'm
about to go rip this fucking thing out and put in a fucking regular Nintendo controller for all I
care. What? No. That's what you guys do. No Jeremy. I just had to jump but I forgot it's over there.
It's all right. I'm fine.
Okay.
So I jump around and dash. Wait, I can stand on this. I'm thinking what am I thinking here?
That's what I'm thinking. Oh my god. I had it. I was at the end. That was the very end. We got
to deal with all these dumb things in this dumb world. That's dumb thing. I can't wait.
It's dumb worlds. Dumb stuff. Dumb. Everything's dumb. Nothing is smart. Everything's dumb. I'm
the smart one. Nothing. I'm the one that's smart. Please. You're gonna come up right there. This
stupid Mario fireballs. I had it the first time. Stupid fucking. I hate these things. I hate this
car. I love the road. It's a beautiful road that I'm on. I had it. Oh, I gotta pee in one minute.
I gotta complete the whole game in a minute. I see a secret over there.
The fact that those stupid, the thing grow. You can't stand on these for more than a second.
So how do you time? Again. I have to sit here and go at the right time, which is right,
which is right now. It would have been right now. And that would have been right now. Secret.
That's a diamond. What does it do? What does it do? I guess I got it apparently. More diamonds.
Holy shit. I almost just fell off the whole world. Okay, we're fine. Over here.
Whoops. Can I get that to move? I always feel like that should, not should, but my brain,
because I see the little beam go all the way up and I feel like I'm going up there too.
Check your pants. Why would I check my pants? Oh God. What happened?
This pee all over me. What happened? It's two hours in one minute. God damn it. You gotta be
kidding me. Pee'd my fucking pants. It was supposed to be two hours. All right. I'll be right back.
Hey guys. Let's get back to it. What do you say? Go. I got two jumps. And then this. Where do you
go from here? Ah, I see. All right. She goes all the way to the right. I really thought I made it
past. I pissed his pants. Oh, it's all right. I got plenty of pants. Damn it. Rich streamer.
Look at that. I didn't tell you how cheap the pants were.
No, I could say, guys, I eat out every day. You don't know what restaurant I'm talking about.
I could eat McDonald's every day and I would still be eating out every night.
I hope Mr. Ushiro is okay. Why? He treated you like garbage. Yeah, but I still care about it.
And you didn't have to. Whatever. I mean it. You're way too aggressive.
Well, you put too much energy into bad people who will just end up hurting you.
Mr. Ushiro isn't a bad person. He transformed into a monster. He tried to hurt you and now you're
defending him. I'm not defending him. Uh, 10 community subs from Furt Fernandez. Thank you.
That's a lot. 10. 10 community subs. And people that just got the community subs. Let's see some
fucking German boomer in the chat, please. I didn't name it that because that I don't want
people to know it's that name. It's just German old. That's not even a meme. That's not even like
a channel meme. We didn't come up with that. Somebody else did. I'm on your side here. I'm
mad too. I might still be in that hotel if you hadn't forced the issue, but I still hope he's
all right. I'm sorry for snapping at Mr. Ushiro. Thanks. It's in the past now. 2000.
Secret. Whatever. Mr. It's probably a secret over here. How would this be here? Bubble? No.
Oh shit. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Secret, right? Up, up, down, down. Not right. From there. I think I have to
fall, cross, hop. No. You have to fall. I mean, like you gotta really, you go across, you gotta
go across and then up and then jump, jump, jump. Question is how can you do that on the other side?
Close. You're really close. Close. You're really close. Is that what you guys are doing right now?
That's it. I thought you guys are telling me that I was really close, but you're just doing
the really close thing. Oh, I'm so far. Ah, my guess. Do the jump correctly. One thing I'm doing
wrong. Just don't know what it is. That's it. I got it. That's it. That's going to be the one.
That's it. Watch this. You're going to fall. Oh, that was so close. That was so close. I'm
going to be stuck here for a while. Just trying to do this one dumb jump. And there it is,
ladies and gentlemen. There it is. He got it. Got the secret gem. No, I did. No, I did, actually.
I did. I did. Just came from above. Jeremy, what are you talking about? No, me? No, me.
Are you serious? No, I did that. It was me. How was Utah? It was pretty nice. I'm wrong. It was me,
actually. Don't test my patience. I can't see. So back into the bubble. No, I don't understand.
What? Oh, no, I got to go forward. Oh, my God. It doesn't matter how many times you press the
button. It doesn't matter how many times you complain about it. You either got to fix it
or just deal with it. And that's the last straw. I was trying to go right twice. Mad because glad.
Mad because bad. Mad because sad. Sad because bad. Sad because mad. Mad because glad. Oh, shit.
Perfect timing, really. This bullet bill motherfucker over here. I'm going to be
done. Mad because bad. Mad because bad. Mad because bad. Mad because bad. Mad because bad.
What happened? That wasn't snow. That was spikes. I thought it was snow. Mad because bad. Mad because
bad. Mad because bad. Mad because bad. Holy shit. Grab the edge. Stop laughing and beat the level.
I just did something incredible and I spent the time laughing instead of doing the thing I was
supposed to do. You got to be kidding me. I was taunting the game. You know, I'm just not so sure
what I got to just jump. GG, idiot. Mad because bad. Bad at the game. Bad at the game. Bad at the
game. Bad at the game. I am trying to pull it to the left. Apparently not. I don't even need this
dumb thing. For what? That thing is just not going to work. Oh, that's why I need it. How do I do
that? What? What? I can't move it? Can I? I can't turn it or anything. I have to bring that other
one. I could drag this thing across the whole damn level. I'm trying. I tried to jump off of it and
wouldn't let me go. Let me go. Oh my god. Get it. Okay. I understand. That's a wall. It can go
through that. Jeremy, what happened to you? I'm fine. Bad because bad. Bad because bad.
Fuck the berry. Oh, I'm sorry guys. Sometimes you have to take a, uh, you can't get them all
the first time. I can get that one though, can't I? No dashing. Come here. Because you're bad.
Got it. Nobody can say that ever again. I like this. This is a good song. Some reason I thought
there was a secret. I think of the secrets. I saw the berry and it threw me up. Bingo. There's a
secret back here. I know there is. Too late. You gonna start me on the other side? No. Too late.
Uh oh. What are we thinking here? What are we thinking here? It was a close one. Yeah,
I wasn't sure if we'd make it. Maybe you were right. Maybe this is too dangerous.
I was wrong. We can climb this mountain. I got you back. And I believe in you.
That means a lot to me. Mad because bad. Bad because sad. Sad because glad. Glad because good.
Good because glad. Thrilled because skilled. That's the end. Yep, you guys got it right.
No, not so fast. Wait, wait, wait. What's over here? Anything? Nothing at all?
Don't count that as a death if you do, then I will be very upset about it. It's that easy.
Well, that's... I lean into the microphone. I don't know why. It's almost like I'm trying
to make sure you guys are aware of how... What am I doing? We gotta go. Okay, I think... Let me
think here. It seems like right from the edge maybe? Maybe. I just grabbed on.
What if I start from back here? That's it. I got it. Stop. What are you doing? Please, Xbox.
All right. Shit. I'm looking over a chat and I'm seeing... I'm seeing things that I don't know
and I'm looking at it again. I got the treasure map. Look, okay. Let me show this one more time.
I can do it my dumb way, but how am I supposed to know there's a bubble over here?
You know what I mean? This is like... I'm cheating. All right. Okay, okay. I did it right.
What have I grabbed from here? Holy shit. I thought I had it. I got the first part of this right.
Not the second part. Okay, now I get it. I'm gonna jump. You just jump, you don't dash.
I almost read it. I almost said it. You almost got me to say the word that I don't want to say.
Fuck you, Xbox. Shit. No. No. See, look, I did it. Look, I did the thing that everyone told me to do.
I did the thing. The thing I did not know existed and now I skipped the whole level. Cheater. Okay,
is it cheating if everybody screams at you to cheat? I guess it is still cheating, isn't it?
One guy? No fucking way. Not in a trillion years was that one guy. That was like 200 guys.
I don't have enough juice. That was more than that. That was probably four. That was a thousand
people. I gotta stop using those jumps. I'm gonna pull this fucking animal out of the pliers.
Another berry and a key. I think I have to go down. Hold on. I need to go up here first.
What's on the right side? I gotta go like this.
No, I don't have to go like that. I believe these are gonna open eventually.
It's a key. What's the counting for? What are you guys counting for right now?
Fuck. You guys ain't sick of that yet. What's the meme? How long does it take? Like seven years
for a meme to go away? Eight years? Like a decade? What's the meme? When is a meme no longer a meme?
After like 10 years? I'm gonna hug the left wall. Wow. I'm kind of freaking out right now.
That blew me off. I got it. That's it. So now I got the key to the door. Let's open the door.
Wait. Not yet. That's it. Anything else at the bottom here? Nothing. Hey Sonny, what's a pogchamp?
Well, grandpa. Pogchamp is when something is cool on the screen and you thought it was really like
high quality. It's a way to say, hey, that was high quality. Interesting Xbox.
Input's not even happening anymore. It's like the controller is getting worse.
Design a new controller. Sure. Let me show you the ideal controller. This is what we should be using.
I'm going to go over all this bullshit right now because it needs to be done.
Give me a second. Is this going to be the urinal? No, it's not. It's going to take not even five
minutes. So let's design the perfect controller because, man, like really, is it really that hard?
Here you go. So here we go. Let's get the grip right. Best grip that was ever invented was
the Nintendo 64 grip. That gives you two different grips to work with. But I'm of the opinion,
right? So here you go. You got this here, which leads up to down here. A lot of space in between.
You see what I'm saying? So when you grab under here, you can wrap your hand around the whole
thing. Your fingers can wrap around. This comes up like here. There's your base of the controller.
The first analog is here. Perfect spot. And it's make it a little bit smaller, right? But have the
divots here so you can actually move it around and it doesn't get stuck anywhere. You know,
have it have a little well like a moat, right? So there's analog. Down here, two buttons. These
are your extra remappable buttons if you want to play it on PC. OK, because this, by the way,
this controller should work across all systems because this is the number is the main system
controller right in the middle. One huge button here because if you're holding with two hands,
you get your left hand here and your right hand here. Huge button. Big enough where you can.
You're not going to miss it. And that would be jump on most fucking computer games here,
here and here across the top. These are like L and R, right? So this is L1, L2,
R1, R2. All these can be mapped, by the way, just in case you're curious. Trigger over here,
trigger over here, trigger over here, trigger over here. So you got two triggers. This would be
L3, L4, L5, L6. I mean, R5, R6, right? Space not enough where you can know where they are.
This would be A, B, no, this would be A, B, C, D, E, G, H, I, J. OK, and the reason why this is like
this is because you've got analog here, big A button here, right analog right here. This is
the other analog. This controller, what you're looking at right now, can be held in any direction.
You can hold this and use EFG. See what I'm saying? You can have your hand down here.
EFG. If you're more comfortable with a higher grip, put another analog right here.
This is called the uniform every controller. Where's the D-pad? It's all about grip right now,
OK? Because you can hold it on an edge, like your fingers can come up here, around this way,
grab that way, or you can have your thumb here, and these can be mapped. So you could not even
use this controller, this part here, and use these, depending on how much you care about the grip.
OK, now let's make the real one. It's going to take way too long. Here you go.
Grips. Actual finger grips on the sides. Analog one. Analog two. Not too close together.
The PS4 has a problem here, where the analogs are here and here. They're way too close. You
can bump your thumbs together if you push them right and left. Button one. Button two. Button
three. Button four. Start. Select. Tray. That comes down. French fries. Hamburgers. Right? Food. A
drink. Here's your lap. This is your lap. L-R. French fries. Two plugs. One plug into the console.
Second plug for the lights in your house. Here's a lamp. It's too long to draw a controller.
The first one was a joke. The second one was gonna be real, but it was gonna take too long.
It would take too long to design a controller. I'm not even making a joke. I just like didn't
want to take that long to do it. It was a bar of soap. Ugh. Tray. That's such a tiny tray. But
what you don't realize is that controller was huge. That was like a fight stick. Oh my god.
Speaking of controllers, I'm about to fucking go make one. Where was the urinal? No, I can't just
sit there and draw for like 40 minutes. I mean, you can. Yeah, I can, but I'm so close to the end
of this game that why would I just spend like 30 minutes right now designing a fake controller?
I figured it out. Take me up. Thank you. No, it's not. The game's not stupid. Right here. Tray.
Right here. This urinal made it. Yes. Over. Up. Up. Over. Ha. Ha. That freaked me out.
It was the dumb thing with the... It looks like you fly up higher than you do.
I'm gonna figure this one out. Holy shit. What the... Xbox controller.
I couldn't even do that if I tried on purpose. It's fuming because booming.
Ah, all right. Come on. You're really reaching on that one.
Come on. That's not even a word. Again. Again. You can do it again. I shouldn't have done that.
Fuming. This is it. The home stretch. We're so close. We're gonna make it. What's wrong?
I'm just... I'm sorry. I was holding you back. I need to learn to trust you. You must learn.
It's not your fault. I tried to leave you behind. And honestly, I've been trying to leave you behind
my entire life. I'm sorry. I wish I tried to understand you sooner. I was too proud or stubborn
or something. You wasted so much time and energy. At least we're finally talking about it. The
controller I talked about is real. Thank you. How do I get this? How do I order this? Is this real?
That looks like somebody... I want that. Look at how beautiful that is. The front one.
The little like Xbox dick. You can use that for like flight games when you fly. That's not real.
Tony made that up for fun. I thought I just crashed the game. Thank God. I'm glad the mountain
brought you up. I think we can move past this. If we can climb this mountain together, we can do
anything. What if we don't make it? I'd be okay with that. You would? Of course. I'm just glad
we're trying. I really need to do this. I'm finally starting to understand why. Let's finish it.
Three thousand. Twenty-nine. Great. Twenty-eight. He's gonna start fucking counting.
And I can't stop this shit because it's in the game.
Still happening. I will never stop it.
Secret? No. No, it's fine. That's it. I have to get a hundred berries. I went through it. I went
through that when I collected it. It's been 16 years since what?
Fucker. I swear to God. Come on. Oh, I gotta grab the edge. That's what I'm doing wrong with that.
I'm not, you know, I'm just gonna say got flag because I'm not gonna say the numbers.
Ninety-seven. Ninety-eight. I need two more to get a hundred.
Are you putting flags in there? Wait, what? Is that a flag? No, it's number one. I can get it.
Boomer vision. Activate boomer vision. Really? Don't worry. When I'm, when I do the bionic boomer
thing, there will be a boomer vision. Holy shit. I got it. Okay. And I will activate it and you
will get to see through my eyes. One more and I get a hundred. It's gonna be spooky. Yeah.
Well, okay. I screwed that up. Oh, it's the wind. I get it. The wind is doing this.
I need another berry. That's going to drive me crazy if I actually don't find one.
There's one right there. Okay. We're good. Shit. A second here. Where is it? Maybe I'm, I think I
have to get up with charge. Do I? I think I can. All right. I got a checkpoint. So drop down.
One hundred. Berry. Go for a hundred and one. One jump. Reset it. Oh, it's because I'm at a,
I'm at a hundred and one. Reset it. No, you've ruined it. I'll get an even number.
We'll go, we'll get one, one, one. Nothing safe over there. All right. I think I got it.
Damn. This is two, is it two jumps? Hold on to the edge. Is this a pre-recorded stream?
Yes. I'm sorry. Good shit. All right. You got to do to all sides. Yeah. I'm recording this. It is
August 3rd, 2018. I knew I wasn't going to be able to stream this week, so
I made sure to get something up here. Oh shit. God, man. This is, this part sucks.
That one is stand on. Nobody said that? Yeah, they did. Yippee. Ow. My skull. It's only one.
It's one jump. That's it. A half second. So precise. God damn. Oh, you suck at Fortnite.
I hope so. If I was good at Fortnite, that'd be a real weird problem. That'd be strange.
He sucks at Fortnite. This, this may be the hardest jumps in the game. Also, by the way,
also keep in mind, half of these where I jump into the ceiling is because the, the nevermind.
I'm doing it wrong. Well, I wanted to go up. I want to jump up there. That would've been great.
Sorry. I have, I have just stopped. Oh, I hate this fucking thing. Can I like record myself
burning the Xbox one controller and like peeing on it? And am I going to get in trouble for that?
Legally? No. God damn it. Get me out of here. There's more. Oh, that sucks. Total ass. I can't,
I'm going to pee on this. I'm done. Not like getting, I'm talking about like that can't make
a jump. Dash left and then up. It sure is. Good. Give it here. Give it here. Six. Where do I go?
Where am I going? Up? It's always up. I got to get to the top of the mountain. Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh,
uh-oh. I got it. I wonder where we're supposed to go. Climb the mountain maybe. I guess it could
look. Every time I look, it doesn't really help me. All right. So you got to go up and around,
grab the feather and then go the wrong way. Oh my God. What are you supposed to do there?
Wow. You got to go around the edge. Holy shit. I would have loved to have gone straight up there.
I'm ripping it off. I don't think I can get it. Nope. Wait. I think I can get it. It's
going to take some precision on my part though. And who says you can't fucking get shit done?
I want to know their name. I want to know their name. Donnie? It was Donnie, wasn't it? Tell
Donnie. Bring him up. Dude, he did it. Two. Nope, that's not going to help. That is.
Don't call him yet. Don't call Donnie yet. Don't call Donnie because he's going to turn the stream
on. He's going to be like, fuck, you kidding me? No, he's not. He didn't do it. And he's going to
load the stream up and he's going to be falling. Shit. Don't call him yet. Call him in like 10
minutes. All right. Ready? Call him now. Get him in here. Hey, yeah. Dude, Jerma is about to beat
Celeste. Shut the fuck up, stupid. There's no way he's going to do that. Okay. Sure. I believe
you. Open the stream, dude. I'm not kidding. He's about to do it. Yeah. Hey, I'm not going to.
No way. No way. He probably cheated. He probably like, you know, I bet he has a safe state.
We actually did it. I can't believe it. I didn't have a safe state. Wow. It's so beautiful. Look
at how far we've come. Glad I got to see this before I, well, before I. Oh, right. When we
leave the mountain, you won't be able to talk to me anymore. I didn't. How did I cheat? Because I
got a secret item. At least not like this. Yeah. I know that we need to go home eventually, but it'll
be scary to lose his body. Beat because cheat. He'll still exist though. You were part of me
before we came up here. Yeah, I know. But I'm going to have to depend on you to listen to me,
even if I can't talk to you in person anymore. I just can't go back to how it was before,
before the mountain. Don't worry. I can't go back to that either. I really want us to work
together from now on. I believe you, but I'm still nervous. So now what? Let's just enjoy this for a
bit. Selfie. Here it comes. That was a video. You went into video mode on your DSLR. You don't
really take a selfie with the DSLR, do you? Did it. I climbed the mountain. We're not done though.
That was a lot of fun. Am I going back down? That was a challenging, fun platform game.
Washed up Fortnite streamer. Okay. If I was a Fortnite streamer, I wouldn't be washed up
because I would be doing the current trend that's currently relevant right now.
You don't get washed up as a Fortnite streamer when Fortnite is currently still the most popular
thing in the world. If I was streaming like Minecraft right now, or like Five Nights at
Freddy's, maybe that's not what washed up means. What will you? Okay. There's washed up and then
there's washed up X. I don't even need to explain myself. Did they ever explain who that guy was?
Because I understand the whole, some of the other characters here.
But who's that guy? I know he was like the hotel and he was a ghost. But in the story, in like the
deeper meaning of the story here, is it just the hotel manager? That's just who he was. He's just
a ghost. B-sides, Jax. Don't be a normie. Oh my god. I already did one B-sides. I'm gonna do it.
We're not done. I'm going to the B-sides. We're gonna try it. But who's the bird? I don't know why
I can't do that. I would ruin it. Oh, that would be very bad. I was just, I had this flash
moment in my brain where I was just watching myself on webcam. Cheeto wakes up in his
chirping and I go, I go like mush up food in my mouth and like on cam like spit it into his mouth,
like feeding him. I'm glad I didn't do that. I was glad that didn't happen.
Like I'm feeding the baby bird. Hey, welcome back.
But then I wouldn't, I can't ruin Cheeto. I can't like fuck up the toy.
Did you make it into the summit? Yeah, we did. It was incredible. Beautiful, isn't it? I didn't
think it would be worth it, but it totally was. I should have given you my phone so you could take
the ultimate selfie. I thought he was going to say YOLO again. Good evening, everyone.
What are you doing here? A little bird told me there was going to be a party.
RSVP by bird, positively magical. But if I am unwelcome, I shall take my leave.
Please stay, Mr. Oshiro. It's good to see you. You know, this is the first time I've seen you
outside that hotel of yours, Oshiro. I'm glad you made it. John here is baking us a pie with
all the strawberries she's been collecting. Oh, that's what the strawberries are. That's
wonderful. I haven't had strawberry pies since I was a kid. This is going to be amazing.
Don't get your hopes up. She's not much of a baker. He also said I wasn't a mountain climber.
True. I made 101 berries. I can't promise it'll live up to the hype, Theo, but I tried my best.
I'm impressed. Put them in. How's it taste? Sounds kind of looks like it's pretty good.
I'm impressed. This gives my baking a run for its money. Good ending. Not bad. Holy crap. This is
so tasty. John, are you available to cater our reopening banquet? I thought he was going to say,
can I take a selfie with it? Can I take a selfie with it? You already is taking a selfie with it,
though. So that already happened. That really is too bad. The numbers there are the way they are.
102 out of 175. 1373 deaths. Eight hours and 26 minutes. Almost elite status. Can we get more
likes than the Kardashians on this cake? There's the campaign. There's an epilogue, though. Wait,
what's this? It's been two hours? No, it's only been an hour and 15 minutes. Why do I have to pee
again? This is chapter eight, the core. About a year later. Hey there, kiddo. Nice to see you again.
Here's the cave I told you about on the phone. Follow me. What happened? I wasn't walking up.
Wait, what's going on here? Why don't I have power? Um, okay. Strange. What is this place? How do you
have the lady do this? That's right. This passage leads to the center of the mountain. You said you
wanted to come back and explore deeper. Doesn't get any deeper than this. Be careful, though.
When you get this close to the heart of the mountain, the power will start affecting
you differently. Yeah, I already noticed some of that. Good luck in there. Where's that other part
of you? I don't know. I expect her to show up by now. Maybe I've changed and she's not part of me
anymore. Or maybe you've grown together. Maybe it's not so easy for the mountain to separate you now.
I'd wager she's still with you in some form. I like that. Still wish I could talk to her, though.
All right, bye. I'm worthy. Oh, I am worthy to go through. How does this work? Oh, all right.
Oops. Oh, that was clean. Beat level in the whole game. Oh, best level in the game.
Okay, we'll see. It does have flying objects, so I don't know. I might not agree with you.
Well, that's what that does. Why I keep doing that? They don't talk. Well, that's why. Because I have
to do it in one jump because I ran out of juice. Don't get refilled. Hmm. Not entirely sure why
they've given that to me, but I'm sure there's a reason. Let's go down. Shouldn't be wasting
one there. Looks like it's still naked. Left and right. Let's see. I'm trying to get lucky.
All right, let's go left. So am I supposed to touch it or something somehow? Can't jump on them.
It's over here. I guess this looks kind of like where I need to be. So I gotta jump across from
ran out of power. Whoops. Ah. Wait, what? I think I'm doing it right, I think. He's abandoned the
solutions. What do you mean, abandoned the solutions? I can't use the dash here. Except
I did. But I can. What about up here? The critical information is not accessible to him.
Oh, I'm not in assist mode. Oh, there's a fire. Wait, now it's ice. So you go from fire to ice.
Jump on these? Yes, you can. Now what? Uh oh. Oh. Yes, who is it? Ah, okay. Now we go back
and everything's frozen. Would you look at that? Icy to dull the pain and then hot to relieve it
away. Icy hot. I see what you're doing over here. That was a good chat joke. Now I can go. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This is now accessible. Washed up Fortnite streamer.
I need one more. I need to save one. That's how you do it. That is how you do it. You know what?
You're really starting to piss me off. You're really starting to piss me off. Don't you dare.
Don't do this. Why have you done this to me? Oh, I had it. I got you. I do the stupid bumper.
It's all right. Not this time. Okay. Now I can get up there. I think I need to
come at it from this angle. I gotta break them one by one, I think.
As they come around, maybe. I guess I could just go straight through the middle. There you go.
Now I can jump off of them. Oh, they respawn. I just go up. I don't, I don't need to destroy
them all for any reason. Just go up. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. I was right there with video game.
I didn't even want to grab. I wouldn't even hold and grab. I'm going to go from up here
and I'm going to drop down off the top rope. I think that's what I need to do.
Probably not. I think I do actually. Let me see. Yeah, I definitely do because then I have to dash.
Now I'll get up. I'm angling as hard as I can to the top right. I gotta pee too. Okay.
Now I got this. Oh, what the hell? I touched the stupid thing on the side. Oh, no. That's not good.
It's all right. Mad because bad. Mad because bad. Oh, dear. You gotta switch it halfway through.
Thanks. Okay. I don't even need to use that. Oh, no. Secret up there. Oh, well. Can't get it
anyways. Can I? How did I thread that needle? I waited so long. Oh, well. My fucking hands
are slipping with my greasy, fucking sweaty hands. I'm going to jump over on the second jump.
All right. He's got pee-coated hands. Shit. Oh, interesting stuff. So I'm going to hold and dash
here. Damn it. I blew it again. Why am I dashing there? I don't think it's even necessary.
Just die. I just panicked so hard. Nope, he's not going to do it. No, he's not.
Shit. That was right there. I had it. It was right there. Everything went so smooth. Xbox 360.
Oh, I swear to God. All right. Seriously, how come I can get that sometimes? The other half
of the time I can't do it. No, it's not. Oh, I'm trying to time it, but I just can't do it apparently.
Oh, fuck. You don't get it. If I don't get that first jump first try, I'm just falling down.
Seriously. I didn't even fucking need to do that. Holy fuck. What happened? Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I think I can use that. What the hell was that? Whoa. What? Holy shit. Timing on some of these.
It's like, come on, man. Okay. Hit the bottom right, pinball, jump out. No. Shit. What? I gotta
go pee before I spike this controller into the ground and have it shatter into 10,000 pieces
because that's how strong I am. Okay. Let's try this again. How much did you pay for a nude of
Jeremy? I'll give you one for free right now. Trying so very hard. Why? What do I do? What do
I do? Oh, hold on. Oh, stop. Stop moving. Everyone stop moving. Oh, shit. All right. How the fuck do
I reliably do this? The bottom right one is what everyone's screaming. But all right. So you're
talking about like on the way down, bounce off that. Okay. Oh my fuck. The stupid slow jump
over here. It's just, I can, I just, my God, I, I'm going to fucking get so angry at this.
It's like that, like wage up. I'm going to do that. I really don't even want to do that.
I don't care about the strawberry. Get me out of here. I hate that. That was the worst thing ever.
This is going to be, this is going to be hell. Oh, it's going to be hell.
Give me back. Get up. No. Strawberry? No. Fuck the strawberry. I'm not getting it. Oh, come on.
You got to put these stupid fucking pinball machines everywhere.
I had it too. Pain in the balls. Shit. I blew it. No, I didn't miss it. Go back and get it.
Wow. What the fuck happened? I did it. Wow. Oh, I'm going to go up. No, I thought I could just cheese
it. I just got to go fast. I can't just stop. I would have had it if I actually dashed right when
I pressed the button to do so. Sunk the hedgehog level. That's fine. Oh shit. Ice, ice, ice. Is that
going to hurt me? I actually might be able to go up. I already used it. Still going. Oh, what the
fire? No fire. I can't turn it off. I didn't know. Oh man. You got to be kidding me. No, I hate this
moving shit. I really do. I don't have any juice. I can't go anywhere. Oh, I can't do that. I need
you. Moving shit. Moving shit. Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Oh, wait just a
minute. Wait a minute. Oh. I got to start on this side. Oh no. That's how you do it. I can't do that.
Dude, just go from. They're just baiting me.
Fucking moving shit. Not every time. I am going to burn this on spring. I'm going to have a nice
fire in my backyard and we're going to burn this controller. Sometimes it does not. Nope.
That needs to be perfect. I think I need bulk dashes too. I'm not getting it right. I got to
jump off that into the wall and damn. Sometimes you just end up doing that. He's making it look
hard. It is hard. How is this not hard? You got to be like the fucking alien to not think this is
a difficult portion of the game. You're making this look hard. The bonus epilogue chapter.
That's way past the end of the game. In this hard platformer game. Good time. I got to get higher.
Holy fuck. I had it. No, that was it. Oh my God. No, don't do this to me. What if it happened?
What happened? Where'd it go? Where is it? No. I wouldn't have had it if I didn't dash. Oh my God.
No, don't do it. What do I do here? Oh my God. Get up there. No, no, no. Hit the ice. Wait. Wait.
I don't know what to do next. Oh, this is hard. I need a dash. I got to go. I have no idea what to
do there. Get that. That's how you do it. Oh man. Oh, come on. What did I even bump my head on? That
makes no sense. Oh yeah. Bump my head again. No, I can't climb that. I don't know what the hell
I was thinking. You beat the levels. This is getting repetitive. I know you guys are just
joking around. I know you are. There's no way this is not a joke. You have to be kidding. Okay,
here we go. Dude, how the fuck was I ever supposed to do that? Touch it. I win. He can't be this bad,
can he? There's no way he's this bad. How can he be this bad? He's bad. Bad. Bad.
Give you a second and I'm out of it. I'm out of it. Oh no. Shit. It's gonna. Oh my God.
One of those hard ones. Jerma, come home. You've been playing this game for months.
No, it's on this screen. Oh boy. Oh boy. That was not too bad. Not terrible. It's gonna get
way worse though. I think I understand. I gotta just bounce across the whole thing.
That blended in with the background. That was a shadow. That shadow blended in.
Oh no. Wait, that's not. I need to. We already climbed the mountain. We're in the heart of the
mountain now. This is the epilogue level. The bonus chapter. And I have to. I have to beat this
to prove the one guy in chat that called me a normie. I don't even. Holy shit, man. I played
this level in a Latin and I hated it just the same. How much did I bump? Oh God, sorry. God,
please. I don't have any. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. That was it right there. Oh, I just. I'm rushing
now because I want to be done with this. All right, I gotta slow down. This is just never
gonna happen. B-side or normie. You know, what if I don't care if I'm a normie? Huh? Is that really
that much of a problem for some of you? This is it. It's normie proof. This is what at the center
of all of this. It's so empty and vast yet it feels nostalgic somehow and peaceful. Heart of
the mountain. All right. Yo, he's not a normie. No, that's not true. I have to beat the seasides
tape. I'm not going to do it, but that's okay. There's no way I'm going to do that. Absolutely
not. Well, there's the bonus chapter. Now I. Wait, I did the first B-sides. Where's the other one?
I did this one already. Yeah. 200 times died here. All right, this is the celestial resort.
I think we got a B-side here. One B is not unlocked. That's okay. This feels great compared
to the thing I just did. I say that now and I'm going to eat those words. I'm going to
inhale those words very quickly, aren't I? Shit. Well, uh-oh. Did beating that last bonus chapter
just set in complete gamer fatigue? Am I? Can I even do this anymore? I might not be able to.
Let me see. All right. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I think I have to jump around.
Oh God. I don't know. Up and then over, up and then over again. Maybe. Let's try it.
I might need to take a Shito break. Again, I did the same damn thing. All right. Maybe. Let me try
this a few more times and then we might take a Shito break. Oh my God. I blew it. I blew it.
No, I didn't. It's still possible. It's still very possible. Hair got in my face.
It's like eating my hair. I'm just going, I'm shaking the whole thing off. I'm going bald.
I don't even need to do it. I can just fall down and grab it. I was not doing the same. Oh my God.
Shito time. Yeah. I don't know. I might, I might have to put the cap on, Celeste.
It's a great game, but it's kind of only so much you can do in one sitting.
Well, last night it was like five hours or so. I beat it four hours.
These kind of games, they just drain the fuck out of my brain.
I should be able to do at least somewhat. I think you got to go down. I saved the dash maybe.
Yeah. Game of Fatigue sets in and then you kind of, you kind of can't do anything.
This might turn into like a fucking automaton scream. That was it. That was it. You get to
jump around. I got it. I got it. I'll get it here. You got to jump around and grab the weapon.
Like that. No, it's no good. It's so frustrating. You trying to move with your hands in the same,
in the right direction. It just doesn't happen. It's a great, it's a great game.
It's one of, it's very challenging, very fun. As you can see, I'm still playing it even though
Game of Fatigue is set in. We're still going. Oh shit, I don't have two jumps anymore.
I can tell he hates it. I don't, what are you, I don't hate it. Holy shit. How am I going to do this?
You got to go up and then cross. Yikes, I don't know. Yikes, yikes, yikes.
He has tears rolling down his cheeks. They're streaming down my face.
Guys, the bottom is going to cause so many problems because I have to go back, don't I?
I'm just going to wait. That's going to be unbearable. Okay. Okay. Hold on. Ah, fuck.
Oh my God. There's no way to stop. You just have to go. You can't stop for anything.
That's not correct. Oh, I got to go up to the top right. This is how you do it.
The one thing is though, I got to take a look at how the hell I'm going to get the one on the top
right. I haven't even seen it yet. I haven't paid any attention to it. So it's off that and then into
the wall and then back around. And I have to grab that ledge there at the bottom. Nope. I need that
dash. Oh, come on. Why? Why do you have to be down here? Don't ever beat this level. The music's too
good. How many screens are left on this B side here? No, that's not what I want to do. I just stayed
down. That's it. I figured it out, but I'm not going to have enough strength. I'm going to grab
the ledge and like slow these guys down by like even 5%. I'm so sick of this. I just freaked out.
No, I would have had it. Just the timing, timing, timing, timing, timing, timing. Like, oh now. Oh,
go. Okay. Go. Okay. I can't stop right now. I'll lose all this progress. I have to get to the end
of this. And then I'm going to transition to like IRL for like 40 minutes. Oh yeah. Yikes.
Suck cost. I already, look at this. It's like screen number five.
There can't be that much more happening. I had to grab on. The one thing that sucks is because you
have such a small amount of area to have to grab and you just suck to it. And it's so difficult
to just not jump. You've got such a tiny little area. See, like I just grabbed that. I really
didn't want to. And I could have, I could have around, around, around. Oh man. Absolute zero room
for error. Zero. You gotta be a fucking robot. Like that. I, and I didn't want to jump meat boy.
You fucked my whole game up. Fuck off meat boy. I had no, oh, I couldn't believe it. Fucking
Donkey Kong. It's going to take all night. No, I thought I had two jumps. How do they take that
away from me? I should have done this earlier. No, I shouldn't have. What are you talking about?
Anybody know how many screens I have left after this one? Two? Let me sit here for a second.
Aye yi yi. There's just so many moving parts. There's so many moving parts that need to perfect.
Eat my ass. Let's go. Let's skip that one. Just go to this one.
Where were you when Shito died of neglect? He's flying. He's eating today. I threw up in his mouth.
He's gonna be just fine. Oh yeah, I gotta, I don't know. I'm sorry. I'm trying my best.
And it's just like, it's so much to have to do. Yeah, where the fuck was Einstein during this shit?
Do you think Einstein would have been able to do this? No, he would have been like, what the
fuck is this shit? I have to climb on the side and just, I don't get it. And then people would be
like, oh, boomer. Einstein, you're a boomer. What is, what are you saying? I don't get this either.
Boom, boom. Oh, that's the spikes. It's just like, you gotta go down when it's up and up.
When it's down, your brain doesn't work that way. Your brain doesn't work in that kind of order.
I'm gonna beat this one. Trust me. I can go through. I can dash. I jumped for no reason.
This is not nearly the hardest B-side. I'll never do this. Just torture yourself. You know,
I don't want to torture myself. I'm gonna do a couple of them. A couple as in just this one.
I already did one. I did one yesterday too. Now I get, it's like running in with the background,
that little tiny two boxes. I thought I didn't grab the edge, this small little fucking area
to grab. Now I'm getting angry and you're not gonna, I can't play well when you're just
fucking angry. See? I have no idea where to go. I have no idea what's happening that way. You know,
I probably would assume that this would be the hardest. I'm going to open up one of the other
B-sides. As you all know, like the whole game I've had trouble with the things that move in
up and down, up and down. They've caused me a problem the whole game. So, you know, this might
just be my kryptonite. Like I have to wait for the perfect opportunity. All right, I guess it's now.
I'm so screwed. Oh, it's so painful. I tried to let go. I tried. Now I guess, and then around,
I guess, oh my lord, you gotta, probably the correct way to do it is just wrap around the guy.
Right? And yeah, that's it. I did it. Oh, that took forever. Not this. What am I supposed to do about this?
Fake bits. You made me laugh and it ruined everything. $300 in fake bits.
No, no more of these moving sponges. I got it. Yeah, you did.
That's kind of what I need to do. Kind of. Maybe. In some weird wild world. Hey, thanks for the $500,000,
guys. Prove this is pre-recorded. How am I supposed to prove that? That, that's how.
No, stop saying these things. And what am I? I didn't get the diamond. Didn't get the diamond.
Money is all he cares about. That's not true. Oh my god, no. I just, oh goodness. Just jump over it
and then across. Yes, I just do that. That one was not that bad, but this is probably going to be bad.
Turn on the face cam and that falls. No, no face cam. You need to do that.
Please just jump off it over and over again. I would love it if you did that.
Here's the funny thing. I am never going to be able to play Meat Boy ever again. Nothing like I would,
but I'm going to try to like climb onto walls and stuff. I have no idea. How the fuck would
you ever do that on the first try? I win. No, I didn't. Oh no, this guy's back again.
Jump over that. Jump over it. I have to jump on his head.
Cheeto's coming. Um, honest to god, it's the analog or the d-pad. Even if you had something precise,
this would just be fucking so hard to get that. You're going to jump up and grab. How the hell
are you supposed to do that? You got to go around and grab it again. That has to be how to do it.
I'm going to be so glad when I'm done with this. Just get me to the end of this.
But you can only do one of these like once a year. Or you're going to lose, you're going to just go
hollow. You'll just lose your sanity. Doing like the B-sides is seriously, is like smoking
three packs of cigarettes a day. This game isn't even that hard. Just put your face on the stove
tub. That would be so stupid. Like you have to be so perfect. Why? Oh, I think I'm done.
I think I'm done. I gave it a good attempt, but I'm too fatigued. I'm too drained to do this.
I'm giving up at the finish line. I don't want to smoke any more cigarettes.
I don't want to smoke any more cigarettes. You understand? Oh, just put your face on the stove
That's it. I ran out. The spring was so close. I just had to touch the spring and I would have had
it done. Oh my God. Okay. It's been like 150 attempts and that's the first time that guy has
hit me. You don't even need to be here. This will still be unbearable. Wait for me. Did I win? I've
got to jump on him up there. I got to hit him. No, I don't. My God. You've got to be kidding me.
I, what happened to my jump? What? Do it for Shito. I'm going to try. What else have you got for me?
I got to hit him. I got to jump on his head. How am I supposed to get that one?
Give Shito the controller. It's not going to help. Oh fuck. No, I almost got hit him in the head.
Oh, you got to. Oh, this is just a noise scream. All I'm doing is making noises and shit.
Just getting my ass kicked and making noises. I didn't even get that one over there.
No shit. I would have had it. I got to get it done. I fucked myself so hard.
Screwed myself. Oh my God. I just screwed myself over so badly. So hard.
Not get that by jumping on his head. That's like what you're supposed to do.
And that is what you're supposed to do. I didn't want to jump that way.
What hit me? I don't even know what hit me. I'm still not even understanding this yet.
This is going to take me like another 300 attempts to beat this stupid fucking level.
I didn't, I just, all right. It's the let go of right trigger. I would have probably had a good
attempt there. Screwed it up again. I can get it back. Eat a snack and regroup. No, I can't. I'm
never coming. I'm never opening this game ever again. So I better do it now. I better do it now.
Hates game. No, I just, I can't. I'm at the point of the game where I'd beat it and it's just the
excruciating shit left. When am I going to have time to do this? I'm not going to stream it.
I got to like cook food and shit. I had to cook food. Ah.
Guys, do you understand my daily routine? I stream a game and then I cook food for
seven and a half hours. I'm done. I've lost it all.
It's just my brain can't handle these emotions and movements. I have to finish it though.
Otherwise we can't see Shido. You got to do it on this one. You got to hit it there. I fucked it
up. What even hit me? What the fuck even hit me? This sucks such ass. Oh, I'm gonna, do you want
to talk about a 2018 meltdown? It's going to happen right here. This is too much. Why did those pop
out? I thought I had to touch them first. I'm not even close by the way. There's like another
whole, I'm at like the first third of this whole page, this whole screen. He's losing his mind. I
am starting to lose my mind. I got to hit him. I have to hit it. What the fuck happened? What? No.
Oh, I'm being shocked. I'm being strangled. It's this fun, really fun mechanic called stuff
grows out after you touch the wall. It's the funnest fucking mechanic in the game.
It's my favorite. Have I told you about my favorite, Tweety? It's the best. And suddenly I
begin to see. Suddenly I begin to see. I've got a golden ticket. It's ours, Charlie.
I didn't even move. Why is it growing? All right. All right. Like fuck, fuck that dumb watch. You
want to know the part that's really annoying when he's about to dash and he distorts the screen.
Like, look at it. What? Like what? Why? Why does it have to happen? Like, is there a reason why that
has to happen? Can I like turn that feature off? It's giving me blurry vision. I had to be too.
Unbelievable. Again, I didn't fucking move. I didn't do shit. It was the opportunity. That
just fucking ruined everything. But no, it didn't. I have to hit him in the head.
Don't grab. Over. Don't even think about it. Remember I watched this guy stream this game
and it's not even hard. Like I do this in like fucking two tries. It wasn't mine.
It was like crazy. Have you heard of this guy? Oh yeah, he's terrible at the game. He's like
really bad and blames a bunch of stuff on his Xbox controller. I don't think he even has an
Xbox controller. I think he's using like a PC madcast controller. I don't know. I think he's
just an idiot. We gotta time this. We gotta wait. I have to go now. I have to go now and then oh
I gotta land over there. Don't move. Okay. Now I've got an opportunity. I gotta bounce
and stupid game. I did it. I win. I win. I win. I win. I win. I win. I did it. I did it. I did it.
Just touch it. I win. No, not that number.
Of all the numbers you could have given me, you have to give me that one.
Uh, well, okay. All right, wait a minute. 342, 243. This is actually cursed. I need to never play
the game again. I don't get the reference. Uh, that number was like a meme joke number
from like a year and a half ago. It was killed last year or the year before. That's weird.
The best song? We're about to hear it. Where's Shito? I know, but just wait. I just need to see
how this one is. This one's not bad. This one's okay. That was close. Oh, well, I didn't know that.
Is my brain fried? Oh yeah, it's fried like an hour and a half ago.
It pisses you up in the ear. Take a guess. I think I need, no. Okay, hold on, hold on. I can get it
from there. I'm gonna need a caretaker if I play for another five minutes. Yeah, I just need
to see what this one is. I'm not going to play through this one unless, hold on. We get to see
Shito and then I'm probably going to go for like, maybe like an hour from now. Wait, but yeah, I'm
addicted. Okay. This is okay though because there's no moving parts. It's just spikes
and be careful. Don't screw it up. That's the name of this game. Holy shit. The moving part.
God, that was supposed to work. How are you supposed to get that done?
How are you even supposed to do this? It's not even possible. It's not possible to do this.
It's impossible to do this. What do I do? I did it and I needed another centimeter.
Why would they even put the spike? You like, I beat the level. You really have to put
a huge thing of spikes at the very fucking end, right at the end. Like, I already did all this
bullshit and you're gonna make me do it again. And just derma overrated. Auto-updated. Long
have we awaited. Shito activated. You know, when you get to a position like this where you
watched the level get completed, I already, I completed it. So I'm going back and doing it
again and I don't like it. You know, I don't like that. It was completed. Yes, it was. I completed
it. I did it. No, I did. I did. I did it. I beat the level and that's all there is to it.
I had an unfair troll spike at the very end. That's on Xbox. It's me, Xbox.
Just when you thought you had a good attempt, Xbox comes around and gives you extra sodium.
I'm all the way back in my chair. I did it already. This guy's a fucking nutcase.
Hey, I made some mashed potatoes. Would you like some? I would love some. Please put some on my
plate. Is this real? Are you kidding? Dude, don't do that. I love mashed potatoes. Don't fucking do that.
He's awake. Do you want to, do you want to be on stream? No, you don't want to be on stream.
Is there, is there a reason why? What's wrong? Chat was being very mean to me and you don't like
that. No. What, what should I tell them? Okay. That if they, if they want you to be on camera,
yeah. Oh, to be, to be nice, being nicer to me. Oh, okay. You want to go back to bed? Okay. Well,
um, have a good rest. There you go. Do you like your new bed? You need like a water or anything?
You gotta, you gotta get to bed. You got school tomorrow. No, no, don't give me that.
Excuse me. You have school tomorrow. You gotta get up. You gotta learn. No, go get to bed. I'll
get you. I'll read you a story later. Okay. You want a story? Okay. Sure. Everybody see you later.
Good night. I'm sorry. I wasn't paying attention to what was going on here. What, uh, what's going
on in chat here? He's talking to a toy now. Toy. I mean, she told me. Okay. What am I doing wrong
here? I swear to God, I don't get it. I just dashed down, right? I'm just overthinking the
fuck out of that. And it's the very end. It's the block. Oh my God. What am I doing? Fuck. I just
got, oh man. You just have to dash or do you? I don't even know. I think my eye might be bleeding.
I made it. Okay. I'm good. My eyes bleeding. No, those are just cheaters. You just gotta be quick.
I gotta get right to the bottom. I jump. How on earth am I supposed to get up there that fast?
Like that. Okay. This is Wynn. Thanks for watching. I'll see you guys later.
See you guys in the next stream. It's going to be a fun one. We're going to be playing on drink ass.
Remember that? I'm actually not entirely certain on what the fuck I need to do here.
What stream do I die? Uh, January 23rd is when I'm supposed to be dying. That's the date that I was
told from the fortune teller thing. You have it marked on your calendar. That's kind of morbid.
That's how you do it. Okay. It's grabbing me. Get on top and jump again. That's how you do it.
Gotta get it. You dumb game. It's so strong. This might be one of the last screens before I, uh,
literally shit my pants on camera. No, don't say that. No, I get it. I'm just, I'm very
frustrated and I'm saying things. Okay. I'm fine. Take a break and come back refreshed.
No, I'll be all right. I think, I think I'm over the, uh, over the hump there. I can just relax
and just chill and like, I can do it. Ball. The wind is so bad because it just, it, everything
you've known and done the whole game, the compensating for the jumps and the dashes,
it just makes you everything you've done the whole game. You have to redo it again because you have
the muscle memory for jumps and dashes and they just make you slower and faster whenever they damn
well feel like it. Oh my God. I didn't even, I didn't know that was it. $50. $50 from Colonel Zero.
Thank you so much for the 50 bucks. 5,000 bits. Didn't I jump on that? Why didn't it refresh my
jump? Uh, German for the love of God, please stop is what they say. I'm doing just fine.
I appreciate the concern. Stop. I'm still having fun. If I wasn't having fun, you'd know
because I would say things like, uh, I, this is stupid. Uh, fuck this controller. Uh, this game is
too fucking hard. Why am I doing this? I have to stop like stuff like that. That's what you typically
would hear. Another great one is, uh, why is this in the game? Uh, like for instance, if I were to
take like a, I mean, I haven't done this, but like you could tell if I was like a little bit upset
about something. And if, uh, you know, you know, what's with the wind mechanic, it's fucking ruins
the game. If there's stuff like that, that's how you can really have an indicator of how things
are going with the stream so far, you know, or, um, holding right on the Xbox controller for some
reason makes you go upright. If you hear that, then there's a possibility that I might be a little,
just a slight, small amount irritated. Again, all things that have not really happened yet.
So I'm fine. Beat that screen. That was fun. Well, this one's not going to be fun. Can I not move it?
I think I just have to grab the wall. Uh, the other side. I don't think I even need the spring.
Holy shit. I gotta go much faster than that. Say something funny. Um, how about
0.01% of your body evaporates every time I die. That doesn't sound good. Well, how, how much of
there is, how much is left of you? I, okay. So I might have to dash underneath like this. Like,
no, that's the live way to get around the other side. Straight up dash above the platform. I mean,
isn't that, that'll kill me, won't it? So I have to talk about dash up and then move around. That's
going to be absolute hell. How many cigarettes have I spoken so far?
Okay. I, you've got to be fucking kidding me. How are you? Why? Why do you have to do that?
Is there really a reason to do that? Have you switched sides like that again? I can't even do
it again. I'm out of grip. I'm not even sure if I'm halfway up or not. I gotta get around again
and then around again and then around again. I did it. Wow. Okay. Bullshit. Another big bits.
Uh, G-H-Y-D-H-F-E. Thank you. Uh, GID. Thank you for the 50 bucks. 5,000 bits. Thank you so much. Hey,
Jerma, I've had countless sleepless nights for years because of the single question. If you got
cloned, would you, um, well, to answer your question, throw right into that. Uh, I would,
um, I'm going to, I'm going to go with a no. No. What was the answer to the question? What kind
of question is that? Answer the question. No. All right. I got it. No more clone. No more clone
question. And I have to wait because so many of these levels have the one thing in the level
that's timed. I got a timing moving object and I also have a bunch of fucking wind.
How many times I've said, oh my fucking God, it's probably been like 5,000 times.
Is this, I think I'm, is this where I turn this, just turn this off and eat a packet of cigarettes
on screen? I think I can make that. I have to wait. No, I didn't. All right. I think this is where I
give up for another day with my, like my niece or my nephew when they're old enough to play it.
Cause I won't open it ever again. So we'll see whenever, whenever, whenever they play it in like
30 years. What am I doing? Name your child. Honestly, I didn't even want to. Can I, can I
even make that jump though? I don't even know if I can. Like, can I make that? I don't know. How far
down did it go? How did I not make it there? So one guy said it was too loud. So I am inclined to
agree. Apparently not this time. All right, here we go. That window almost just screwed me over
there. Oh my God. What the fuck happened? What am I doing? How did I just do that?
I don't know how I did that. I closed my eyes. The wind is even stronger now. How am I gonna,
I don't have a dash. You need a dash, you can't do it. Holding right. This is the last time I'm
ever going to use this controller, by the way. This thing's actually going into the trash.
And I'm going to actually set up a BS4 controller. This thing is absolute dog shit.
God. Put a camera on the controller. Just like botched inputs. Again, nothing changed. Not one
single thing changed. I was holding it in the same position as the last one. But for some
fucked up reason, I didn't want to do it. It was like, no thanks. We're not doing that now.
Yeah, now there's no more wind and it's like ruining everything.
Does that go all the way up? I fucked it up. Wait, no, I, no, I gotta jump around and down,
I think. Yeah, I gotta go down on the same one. Like this. Then go around and then, ah, then
fall and jump through. And then that's it. I should be there. I could probably go now, but I can't.
It's close. Just not fast enough. More moving parts. Um, oh, I gotta eventually be on the
middle one. That sounds like a defeated man. I mean, yeah, but not really though, because I'm
still completing screens. I might be complaining the whole way there and I might be annoyed by it,
but it's not defeat until I press the exit button, which will probably actually truly happen.
Um, at the end of this B-side, because there really is only so much of these games you can take
before you have to, you have to just stop looking at a screen.
When the game forces you to go a certain speed, you're just dangling in so many directions. Like
I want to just go with my speed. Grillmaster Braid. Wasn't he voted worst character last year?
Yeah, he was. I think that has to go first. I gotta, I gotta go. I'm doing it in reverse.
Touch the damn thing. You finicky dumb cloud. What are you doing? Did it, what did it just hit?
What? What did it hit? Uh, what is it hitting? I have to pull it. This is so, this is pain.
It actually is pain. Oh no, man. What does that thing have? Can somebody explain to me
what this arrow above me is even for? If you just touch it and it moves, why is it here? What's the
point of this being here? It doesn't change it. It just, it's just annoying. What was it even there
for? It's just adding an extra two, three seconds to the game. For what? This is so painful. This is
the last hard game for like six months. Seriously, my God. There's no Grillmaster Braid. He's not
even real. Say it's not real. All right. Okay. That's time to go. That's time to go. I can't
take this shit anymore. I have to pull that out of the way. You got to pull that shit out of the way
too. Wrong side. I hope this is one of the last screens because you know what I mean? Like, nope.
The fact that you got to just get on the other side so quickly. It's just, my God, it's, it's so
excruciating. It's excruciating. Is it jumping and moving? It's just so, my goodness. The fucking
cloud. Nice cloud. Why? It's like, oh my God, this stupid jumping mechanic is so fucking annoying.
It's like, it makes me want to scream. Trampoline effect that you have to produce with this thing
every time. Oh, old man yells at cloud. That's a Simpsons joke. Grabbing the edges. There's so much
room for error like that. Like just trying to get on the other side of this stupid fucking
Minecraft block. It's got to be perfect. 100% perfect. You got, you got two tramp,
you got three trampoline clouds to deal with here. Get it out of the way. Is this the last screen?
I hope it is. My nieces and nephews are going to love this game. Why didn't, what, why? Why is this
stuff holding on to it? Oh, but so, why did it not move for that time? What was the reason for it? I
don't understand. It, I grabbed it. Dr. Phil raid? I don't care. Dr. Phil. I'm gonna need to go on
Dr. Phil after I'm done with this. Why can you please just move out of the goddamn way?
Move! Wait, what? Wait, I have to stand on top? It wasn't in the right spot? Oh, I don't know.
It has to be in the perfect middle spot and you ride it. Ah, I didn't even know what the,
I've never seen it before. Okay, that's it. That's it, I'm done. No fucking way. I thought
there was space to ride it up. I didn't know I had to go right on top of it. If only there was a
telescope. But I don't, I'm too angry to look at that telescope. It's gonna kill me. Watch. Look.
I thought there was space on side. I really did. I, I don't think I would have had it anyways
because I didn't get the top one fast enough. I'm so close to doing this. Like, I have to do it. I
have to at least get past this screen. Like, I have to. I'm already, I've already been here so long
memorizing the whole damn level. Doesn't matter. Even if I touch it. I didn't grab it in the
perfect place. I didn't, that didn't catch. How did I not jump on that second one? And I'm just, I,
I'm so annoyed with this level. Like, can't I just jump around? Do I have to do this, like,
pull the lever bullshit? I feel like I'm playing a different game. Get out of the fucking way.
This game is ripping off Celeste. Who are we raiding? Jerma! Oh, it's a Jerma raid!
Thanks a lot, Jerma! This is gonna be really hard to do because I have to change the analog position
a lot of times and we all know how well that goes. The dash out of that? I have no idea.
Can I just jump over it? I think I've tried that like twice and it doesn't do anything.
Yeah, for my sanity's sake, this has got to be the last time I fucking do this.
I'm talking like tonight. Like, this is it. When I get to the end of this, whatever, whatever this
side of, whatever tape this is on, whatever mixtape this is, is it. I can't, you have to,
how am I supposed, how do I do that? Go back. If I dash, I hit the wall. If I try to jump over it,
fall over, I hit the wall. I must have to fall a little and then dash up. Yeah, I just want to
go up. No, I'm just trying to rush now. Fuck off. More wind. This has got to be it. Oh, the wind
starts and goes different directions. How, fucking gimmicks, man. Like, any, any more gimmicks? You
got any more gimmicks? I just have to, this is the last screen. Nope. Wait, don't go. Just wait.
There's no reason to. I'm going to jump directly into the fucking wind and I'm going to wait for
the wind to pick up here. I didn't even mean to do that. That was the end. I could probably
have done it in one go. What are you guys even doing? No, I, no, I had to do it because I was
going to fall off anyways. I could, hold on. Not it. We're going fucking insane because you
Okay, that's enough. I'll see you guys. I'll see you guys later. All right. That's going to be,
all right. This is, this is, no, I have to hold it. No, this is not that bad. This is not that bad.
It's way worse than you go. You go on the stepped on gum and then you fall. Okay, hold on. All right.
In 10 tries. If I don't get this, I'm turning it off. One, two, three, that one didn't count.
I'm angry. I can stop counting. Whatever that was. It was a four, five, six, seven. It's just like,
give me a goddamn break. He's throwing on purpose. I promise you I'm not. It's just,
it's just that unbearable. It's just that fucking excruciating intentionally doing it.
Okay. All right. That's enough. I'll see you guys. No, don't shut off windows.
I just hit alt F4 and it was trying to shut windows off.
Save and quit. I don't care. My nieces and nephews are going to love that game.
This is too much. I looked at chat and somebody wrote that this screen took me an hour to beat.
It was like, I don't want to do that shit. Maybe my nephew will.
Oh, she don't raid. Are you serious? All right. Well, I beat it and I did a couple of the sides.
I just, then I know myself. If I sit there for another fucking hour, I'm going to turn green.
So here's the deal. Let's go over the rest of the week because yeah, I got to take a break.
I got to get out of here. I got to go like do an eye wash. I have to go do one of those chemical
eye washes that are in your science class. So the remainder of the week,
I'm not going to be live tomorrow. I have a lot to do tomorrow. I've got much to do tomorrow,
but we're going to go Friday, Saturday and we'll see what from there we're going to go.
Guess what? Guess what? The Dreamcast is actually going to happen this weekend. It actually is
going to happen because it's already getting set up. It's already happening. Trust me.
I promise that the Dreamcast stream will be on Saturday. Promise. 100% promise.
I probably should do this. But that was Celeste. It's a great game. It's very, very fun.
If you like platforming games, it's fantastic. It's one of the better ones I've played in a
long time. If you like hard, very, very hard excruciating stuff, it's in there. It's there.
It's there. If you like hitting your face against a wall in a game for two straight
hours, you can do that. It's available. First impression? I would give it a solid
wind gimmick that really brought it down, like two or three full letter grades.
I would give it an S+, an S++. But the wind and the moving objects and
the going back and moving that block back and forth brought that down like four letter grades.
I give it an A-. I give it an AA in 88 or like a 90. Oh yeah, the YOLO too. 85, 86. No,
it's not an S++. It started in an S++. Yeah, 88. No, 87. 87. But thank you for joining me
on this. What do I look like right now? Let's see. Let's see how I look.
I look a little fucked up. That's just what happens when you play a game like this. He looks
fucked. Yeah. How my eyes look. You see? He's blushing? No, that's a zit. I mean, it's not
that big. It's right there, but it is. How do I not age? Just ask me tomorrow when I've aged like three
cigarettes worth of years from the last like two hours of levels. But that's it. I'll see you guys
on Friday. We'll go Friday, Saturday and do some Dreamcast. There's something I want to do on
Friday. Hopefully I can get it ready. It should be a lot of fun. Grow out your beard. I can't grow
another beard. It doesn't work. It just becomes this mess under here that I just, I can't get rid
of. And it becomes to a point where it's itchy. It's annoying. It just looks like it's just dirt
on my face. It looks like somebody just like rubbed dirt like all over here because I don't grow it
here. I only grow it like here and here. So not gonna happen. It's okay though. Break the controller.
This is the one I'm talking about right here. This is what I've been using. This guy right here. And
yeah, I got some, look, I got some like gamer sweat all over the controls. I've been, look, I've
been playing a tough game for two straight days. You gotta give me, hold on here. And yes, I need
to cut my nails. I was doing gardening work today before the stream, all right? So I needed those
nails to rip into the garden and tear out the weeds. We're doing bits? Yeah. Yeah, I got time
for bits. Let's do them right now. But thanks for joining me. It was, it was a heated, heated,
heated gaming moments. Hopefully you had fun. It was very, very difficult, but very fun at the same
time. Otherwise I would not have been doing it. I'm not, I'm not gonna do that. All right. Anyways,
see you guys on Friday. Celeste gets the recommended stamp of approval. There's a lot
of content there. There's a lot of time to put into that game if you are so inclined to do so.
It is there. But thank you Topeck for the one dollar first cheer. Alec four by four. Thanks
for the one dollar. What's up Jerma? I just got off work and I saw you were streaming. I just had
to come in and say hello. Well, hello. Was this the last Celeste stream? Uh, yeah. Just because
the only, I think content that's really still available is those like really hard versions
of everything. And I need to take like a break from it. I don't think I'll go back to it
after the main story in the bonus chapter. It's Friday stream is not going to be Celeste.
It will not. But I still enjoyed my time in it, regardless if I stream it again. And yes,
I made a few jokes about how I'm never going to open the game again. That might not necessarily
be true. We'll see. Hey bake me home thanks for the one dollar. Sticky brick thanks for the one
dollar. Hey Jerma, you or Ahmad should highlight the movie night VOD before it gets deleted.
I know you've said you don't want too many highlights, but if there's one VOD that deserves
to be saved, it's that one. Uh, I think it's, it's already on the, it's already on the archive
channel. I believe in its entirety. So it is, I think currently preserved, at least from my
understanding. What if the archive channel gets removed? Uh, that would be, that would be
unfortunate, I guess. But I'll save it. I'll just download it. It's not going to be that hard for
me to get it. So, but thank you sticky brick. Thank you man boy for the one dollar. Just remember
that I've never shown you this. It's called fired man. Fired man. So it's just fireman without the
fire. Thank you topac for the two dollars. Imagine watching this with your grandkids.
Oh oh oh this is so fucking hard. Oh why would you watch this with your grandkids?
And that, by the way, that wasn't even from today. That might have sounded like it was from tonight,
but it wasn't. Thank you dork cube for the one dollar. I don't know why everyone tries to get
you say to say fucked up shit in these bits. It's just that I'm a, I've gotten a lot better at
refraining from saying, you know, I've gotten a lot better at finding what bits are trying to
get me to say things or that maybe shouldn't be read. Getting better at it. But thank you snoozing
copter for the one dollar. Jerma, are you kidding? Your hair looks splendid. Splendid. Thank you
snoozing copter. I appreciate that. Devlon two million thanks for the ten dollars. Hey Jay,
my winter break ends today and I'm moving back into my dorm tomorrow. It's been great watching
you again. You've helped me decompress after an emotionally taxing first semester of college,
but I'm probably just being melodramatic. I wouldn't be keeping, I wouldn't be keeping up
as much as the semester goes on. So take some cash for a shitty ten dollar stream joke.
Shitty ten dollar stream joke. No, there's no such thing as a shitty joke on this channel.
There's only, only good jokes. I'm gonna make, you want me to make Shido a bed and just have him
be able to lie down in a bed over here? Uh, thank you killcode for the one dollar. Hey Jerma,
I just wanted you to watch this cool clip. Nothing weird about it. I bet. That one? It was,
that was the joke. We had to get rid of the, we had to get rid of the gnomes.
Does that make you feel better? Thank you dork cube for the three dollars since we're coming to
the more emotional part of the game. I just want to say that when I played this game a year ago,
I was really worried about going to college with my siblings moving away to the city.
I felt really lost. I still sometimes worry about what the hell I'm gonna do with my life.
But after playing through this game, it made me realize that the end goal shouldn't get in the
way of the here and the now. Climbing the mountain is important. Climbing the mountain is important,
but you get there one jump at a time. This is true. Uh, Rome wasn't built in the day. It's
a series of steps that you take up. That's it. Trying to do something in a second or in a day
or a week. Life is a, is a never-ending process. As my mother once said, the road to success is
always under construction. Oh, what a cool mom. Thank you, dork cube. But yeah, it uh, it does,
it does speak, it does speak very, very soundly. You know, overcoming obstacles. Thank you for
the three dollars. Thank you, Divus for the two dollars. Appreciate it. Two dollars from Divus.
Thank you, Timmy Tim Tim for the one dollar. I would like to apologize from comparing Shito
to my brother's kazoo. Shito is a beloved family member to you and I see that now. Hope you and
Shito can find it in your hearts to forgive me. Thank you, uh, Corsure for the two, three dollars
here. Just use an xbox 360 or ps4 controller. Both feel much better than an xbox one.
Now it might even be my controller. There might be something wrong with it.
I did like drop it in the bathtub like three times. It might have something to do with it.
And the worst, worst controller ever made was the game cube and the n64 controller.
I love the n64 controller. I think it's great. What was it doing near the bathtub? I was playing,
I was really addicted to Binding of Isaac and I was taking a bath and I needed to keep playing.
So I brought my entire computer into the bath, like the bathroom, set it up. I used to do this,
by the way. This might, you might think this is like funny and dumb and bullshit, but I used to
bring my computer into the bathroom and go to the bathroom. I would sit on the toilet and have it be
on the computer. It was such an elaborate setup. Yeah, I've told you that before. And then you
finish, you're done. And then you like sit there saying to yourself, oh man, I have to tear all
this down and put it back where it belongs. That's impressive. Hey, mostly lost. Thanks for the one
dollar. You actually do use vinegar. Derba is right for once in his life. I feel like you've,
I feel like you've wrote a message. Listen, I think you've wrote a message talking about how
I'm right once in my life, like 30 times. So am I right once or am I right 30 times? What happens
when you're right once in your life a shitload of times? Doesn't that mean that you're kind of right
sometimes? 30 is way too low. Yeah, I'm talking about this week. Hey, it's time for slime. Thanks
for the one dollar. Hey, Jeremiah, I made you a cool treasure map. The old back seating treasure
map. Oh god, hold on. Let's look at this. Hold on, I gotta put this on screen. This is great.
Let's see. Okay, so let's look. The old chat back seating treasure map. Okay, so start here.
There is a secret here that you should know about. Well, I didn't, I, okay. Okay, again,
right. Idiot. Here we go. Let's keep going. Blame controller here. Wrong. Jebaited. Toxic chat swamp.
Just go. Why haven't you found it yet? Treasure. And we're going to Utah.
This is great. I'm going to frame this and put it on my desk. Thank you for that. That gave me a nice
little chuckle. Captain Worgen, thanks for the one dollar. Everything you say statistically has
a 0.8% chance to become a meme. I don't know about everything. Maybe 0.8% of the things I say
have a 0.8% chance to become a meme. Hey, dork cube, thanks for the one dollar. This stream
brought to you by mad cats controllers. Mad cats, at least we know how to make a d-pad.
This stream really was. Well, the last two streams were just the quintessential
blame the controller. It's the controller. It's the controller, but it was. It was.
Trust me. I know that in quotes, it's the controller, end quote, is the cheap,
easy way for somebody to tell you why they're doing something wrong.
It's the controller. It's not me that sucks. It's everything else. Controller can.
May as well blame lag while you're at it. Well, I can't blame lag because it's not connected to
the internet. I would have. If there was an opportunity when I fell off the ledge or something,
oh yeah, I got like 200 ping. It's impossible. It's unplayable. I would have done it. I absolutely
would have done it. Would have done it. Would have done it. It's like not rolling off my tongue
that well for some reason. Hey, dork cube, thank you, but you just said the mad cats thing. Thank
you. Thank you. Genie boy for the one dollar checkmate. Those who say German mustard
isn't an instrument. An instrument. What do you mean instrument? Thank you. Gorsh. Corsure for
the two or three dollars here. It's like you really want to wake up Sega and Shito. Stop yelling.
Well, the sake is not alive. She told us and then Corsure with another couple of dollars here. Here,
take my money. That's all my bits. I'm broke now. I hope that's not true. So I get, you know,
old 90s shows, but what about early and mid cartoons like Samurai, Samurai Jack, Danny Phantom,
Star Wars Clone Wars? It's actually pretty interesting that I have never seen
any of those. I've not seen Samurai Jack. I've not seen Danny Phantom. Well, I've seen it on the TV
accidentally flipping through and I've not watched the original Star Wars Clone Wars animated series.
I have not. Sorry. Hey, Rapid Wave, thanks for the five dollars. Captain Worgen, thanks for the one
dollar. There's an image here. It's another controller. Yes, I'm well aware that my drawing
of the controller looks like an enemy from Undertale. I get it, but it's okay. Thank you,
Captain Worgen. Thank you, Freudian Weapon for the one dollar. Just curious, what are your thoughts
on the new Spider-Man Far From Home trailer? I really don't know what to even think, because it
it seems like a lot going on. Spider-Man takes a trip to Europe. There's a water monster
that comes out and then Jake Gyllenhaal slams down with green acid around him and says,
get out of here, kids. I don't know. I mean, Homecoming was really well received and really
great, right? We'll have to see. What do you mean, no? Homecoming was very well received,
wasn't it? Thank you, Dorkcube for the one dollar. Jerma, yesterday, you sick fucks
stop. What? You sick fucks need to stop talking about farts. Jerma, today, I'm going to pee all
over the controller. Yeah, but I was saying that out of frustration. You weren't saying,
I, you were saying, I love this stream. I can't, you know what I mean? You, that was not out of
frustration. You were just saying it because you wanted to say that, because you thought it was
fun to say that. I didn't, I wasn't doing that having fun. I was going to piss on the controller
out of anger. It wasn't, I'm having so much fun. I'm going to pee on the controller.
You wouldn't do that. You'd only do that out of pure frustration. I'm not going to pee on
the controller. I'm just going to put it in the blender and put it on the ice crush setting.
We all, you know how powerful that is? The ice crush setting in your, that's more powerful than
a superhero. I don't know and tired. Thank you. Compact viewer for the $3. Wow. I joined at the
right fucking end. Late viewer, just at the end. Oh, you said that three hours ago was still here.
Was I going to end the stream three hours ago? Holy shit. Did I really get that mad?
All right. So if we got a scale here, I'm going to give you guys a scale.
Um, we've got personal, personal anger and annoyance, right? With like myself,
we got skate three kind of somewhere there. Where was this on the scale of like skate three to
hotline Miami two, you know, like skate three is angry. Actually, that's two different scales.
Let's go. What, what's like the best stream, like the most fun and relaxing stream I've ever done
Labo from Labo to a hotline Miami to where does this sit? Labo was not relaxing. This was a little
under Mario tennis. I don't know about that. I remember Mario tennis being actually truly angry
and being upset. Almost Mario tennis. No way this is near Mario tennis. Mario tennis was traumatizing.
Uh, that's live. That's live TV guys. There ain't no going back. I can't pretend like that never
happened. This is real live raw. Jeremy, I kid, what am I? I can't, I just, sometimes it happens.
I don't want to put on a face and pretend. No, I'm not capable. It's just me. But thank you,
Breen Bin for the $5. Congratulations on climbing the mountain. Hope you gain some pro gamer skills
along the way. Like an hour or two later, that might've been a debate there. Goose cap,
thanks for the $1. Hey, Jeremy, you're one of my favorite content creators and I love your streams.
Also, I made another baseball related green screen video that I actually saw this. I saw this,
didn't I? No, I didn't. Where's the one with this? The base is clearing. Let's watch this one.
No, but the Encore Knight, the Encore Knight. Oh, we're going to do this soon. Probably very soon.
These are, these are fucking funny and I'm not supposed to be doing this. I'm not supposed to
be showing green screen stuff. Hold on, hold on, hold on. There's another one of these that it has
a basis clearing fucking brawl and I was laughing my ass off at it. Ours is with an absolute rocket
into the Boston Knight and the Red Sox lead the series two games to none. That's it. They add back
the Red Sox has looked for. I love those. I did so many baseball swings and baseball things.
Show the other one. Where is it? Does somebody have the other one where there's a basis clearing
brawl? What gaming chair did you use for that home run? Uh, one I got, I got it from like
the store. I did the Ortiz Grand Slam also. Those are all so good, but thank you for that.
Thank you Goosecab. UltraLaven thanks for the one dollar. Although you did not stick
with the original title idea of what is inside the cube, I forgive you and wanted to actually
thank you for the incredible streams you provided me and countless others with. I try. I'm trying.
I hope it's fun. Thank you. Babby, Babbyty thanks for the 11 dollars. Do you think your Pac-Man
will come out of ranked retirement? It's possible. It's very possible. It's still,
I still have the, I don't have the actual, do I even have? I have the suit, but I don't think
I have the face. I don't, I think it might have gotten lost in the move, but thank you for the
11 dollars. Smellyboy thanks for one dollar. You should play Civ 6. I'm not sure I'm cut out for
that. Seems really interesting, but I'm not sure I'm capable. Demoniccucover thanks for the one
dollar. What's with the physics for scientists and engineers with modern physics joke? The cat,
the chat keeps making. I don't know. I, what is it? I didn't see it. Hey Superintendent Chalmers,
thanks for the two dollars. Hey Jerma, today's the 10th anniversary of Meet the Heavy,
which means 10 years without a Meet the Heavy Jerma dub. If you don't want to dub it and just
show it. And there's a gnome here. I'm not, I, I'm too, I'm too tired to do a dub right now.
No down under. What have we done as a society? You know what I mean? Think about that. This is a
clickable link. Do you understand guys? What's happening? This is a clickable, this is something
that, this is a link. You know, I, I, what's next? I can't believe that that's even possible to do.
The world has progressed so quickly. We just made up the TV like 60 or 70 years ago.
Color TV. And now people can sync the gnome to a song of their choosing.
That's truly unbelievable. Where are we going to be in 30 years?
Are they going to be flying gnomes in 30 years? Not even cars. We'll figure out how to fly gnomes
before the car takes off the ground. Thank you Amanda Requiem for the two dollars. Thank you.
Thank you Binko for the one dollar. Had to give you a dollar to tell you that there are golden
strawberries for completing a chapter without dying. And I have gotten 15 of them. Some for
A size, some for C size. Nonetheless, you've been making progress faster than I initially did.
So you're doing incredibly well. Thank you. That's, I don't know how you can do that. It's
I told you some of you guys have this alien video game IQ. It's like otherworldly how good
some of you guys are at these games. Otherworldly. Not even Earth. But thank you. That sounds really
intense and sounds like something I would probably never do. I do appreciate the fact that it's
available and I do respect the fact that people are capable of doing that. So cheers to that.
It's the funniest, what's this clip? It's the funniest, it's the funniest mechanic. It's the
best. What is this? It's this fun, really fun mechanic called stuff grows out after you touch
wall. It's the funnest fucking mechanic in the game. It's my favorite. Have I told you about my
favorite Tweety? It's the best. What are you, whoa, what is this?
Here's another one. To Lewicki, a couple of doubles last night. He's hit in 10 straight.
And it's a right back at Hosea. This is so good. These are
so good. These are actually so good.
Motherfucker did this shit. Imagine like the living shit post you would be if you tried to do this.
You guys are fucking too funny. What if it worked?
I'm so glad. You guys are so fucking funny. Hey ckluck, thank you for the one dollar.
German next, German next, German next, German next. When are we going to get the encore movie
night? Probably very soon. I want to give enough details. So there's like a week to kind of compile
them. Maybe a little bit more. Because the mods did so much last time. I'd like to give a lot of
time to make it work. But thank you. Demoniccucumber, thanks for the one dollar. Stream the cook food.
Oh that's right. I said like all I do is stream and then go cook food for 12 hours. I don't even
know what that meant. It was just steam coming out of my eyes. Something or Auder, thanks for
the one dollar. When you die on the toilet next week, can you leave me Shido in your will? Uh no,
sorry. Shido is going to be given the, Shido is going to be the, what's it called, the eulogy
at the funeral? The pallbearer? You can't hold the casket. Ckluck, again thanks for the one dollar.
If you have not pre-recorded a stream yet to play in like two years from now, referencing old jokes
and shit, you're missing an opportunity. Imagine you streaming like the launch build of No Man's
Sky and talking about like Germacraft and Rewind to Flanker and old stream jokes. It would be
amazing. I actually, there was something I was going to do a while ago where I was, it was going
to be too much, but it might have been worth it. I was going to pre-record like seven streams and
then just play them all back to back to back to back to back to back and go on vacation and see
if anybody figured it out. And put pictures on Twitter of being somewhere where I'm, where I'm,
it's very far away. Like how would I get back to my house and stream? Where even is he?
We would find out in two minutes. What if this is one of the streams I pre-recorded?
That's right, now you're thinking with portals. I've thought about it though, it just, that means
I have to do seven full live streams and not stream them. You know, I would have to turn on
a stream, but not actually broadcast it and just stream for like six hours. Think of the free time.
No, I've got lots of free time. I mean, I would consider myself busy. I try to keep up and try to
plan things and do things. And this is like a lot of like real life stuff that I, you know,
have to do. I stay fairly busy, but it's not like I have zero free time. Hey, yep, so thanks for the
four dollars. All jokes aside, please don't overwork yourself. I would hate to see you
have an early streamer burnout. You're my favorite internet boy. Please stay safe. I'm just fine.
Don't confuse, um, frustrated with video game with frustrated with live stream.
You know, that's, there's a two completely different things. Frustrated in playing video
game. It's nothing to do with it. Broadcasting stream. I'm not that that doesn't, I don't think
that's ever, I don't think that's happened. I'm not sure that actually that has happened.
I don't think I've ever gotten to a point where I've been like annoyed at the stream, like at
streaming or being live or being recorded or I'm not sure you don't have to put on a persona,
which really must make it easier. Um, yeah, I'm, I don't know if it's necessarily a persona thing
as much as it's look, I get pissed off at stuff all the time. I'm a fairly, I'm a fairly like
laid back person, but I can get red hot about random stuff and energized, right? But not at
I love streaming. I think it's one of, it's one of the most engaging, fun things.
It interests me every time. I'm not sure there's been, if it has, it's been very few times, if at
all. And I, you know, it, it happens. I can't tell you guys that I'm some perfect pinnacle of,
you know, collected, being collected all the time. I'm just like, I'm a person just like anybody else.
Sometimes I have a bad day. Sometimes I have really good days. Sometimes, you know, you got
a really, sometimes you have a bad stream. Sometimes you're off. It can happen. I'm not
going to pretend like it doesn't, right? Not like today. I mean, it's not like it was, that was today,
but it's, I'm not going to pretend like it's otherwise because pretending otherwise means
that I'm not like a person. Nope. Every single day we're having so much fun and every day is just
welcome to the stream. Like that's not, that's not reality. I didn't know that streamers were human.
That sounds so much better.
How, how quickly would people leave if I was like that every second? I don't think I would be able
to handle it. Do the YouTuber voice stream for six hours. I wouldn't be able to do that.
I almost left right there. All right. What's worse, being frustrated and dying a hundred
times at the same level and being angry and talking shit about like the clouds
or the YouTuber voice. I'm having tons of fun pretending. Which one? I feel like that's like
the opposite ends of the spectrum there. That's where my love of the stream comes from. You always
stay grounded. You always stay real because yeah, I, I, I don't know. It's, it's, it's hard to,
you can't put, I don't know if it's even possible, maybe for some people, but not for me.
I can't put on a fucking personality for seven straight hours. It's been six and a half hours,
right? At some point that becomes exhausting. Even more so than anything else, right? I'd be lying
if I said I didn't miss the old German 95 cut down edit styles of videos you did yourself,
but the stream is great. Yeah, but I, I don't think very much has changed. It's just the format has
in regards to how I go about doing things. I wanted to keep the same kind of energy level
and the same attitude that I had in my videos. Why? I mean, I made the videos the same way.
You want to know, here's the difference guys. Ready? You want to know the big difference
between making a YouTube video and streaming? You're, you're here watching me record the game.
That's really the only difference and I, and I'm not editing it afterwards.
I mean, they do get put into highlights and they do get edited down for a second German,
but if I was not streaming, let's say for instance, Celeste, right? If I wasn't not
streaming Celeste and I thought it would make a fun video, I would have just done what you just
watched, but it's almost easier now because there are people here that can react in real time
and can see it in real time and we can talk about it in real time. We can laugh about something in
real time. Somebody can say something that's really funny. Maybe I will say something and
then people react to it and we can go off from there. I, I love that back and forth.
The whole like treasure map thing earlier, that was, I loved that. That was a lot of fun.
That doesn't happen if I'm alone in the room recording by myself and the in-person skits.
I mean, those, those really haven't necessarily stopped either. Think of some of the streams
that I've done over the last six to 12 months that have had just kind of just skits, like jokes,
you know, like the lie detector, the dinner, even like the Christmas Eve stream, the New Year's
Eve stream. Those are all bits that took a while to set up. It wasn't like I just figured that out
and did that in one day. The lie detector was a joke? Well, I mean, the stream that I really did
that, I, that was a, I was really hooked up to a fucking lie detector, but that stream was a,
it was just for fun. It was just like a thing to do. That wasn't just, uh, it was, it was a skit.
It was a thing. It was like a comedy, right? It was, hey, I'm going to get this guy to come
and give me a lie detector test. Isn't that fun? He's a liar. Did the doctor watch the vaude?
Oh, Dr. Schmikeson. I feel like YouTube is harder because you have no one to interact with.
I do, I like, but I also love making videos. I do like it. I do. It's fun to do,
but it's hard to do them both because see, like, for instance, uh, I streamed for seven to eight
hours yesterday, wanted to take a break, got tired and, you know, ate some food and relaxed
and then went to bed. Kind of same thing like today, right? So another day goes by, here we are.
Six, seven hours go by, you know, I want to get food and relaxed. I don't really want to go like
make a video after that, you know, after sitting and doing stuff for six, seven, eight, sometimes
10 plus hours. The next day, if I'm going to take a day off is a lot of it is what I want to do for
the stream coming up. What are there any upcoming streams that I want to try to start working on?
Is there anything fun that I want to try to get ready? It kind of takes up a majority of the time.
Plus without like, we've talked about the YouTube changes and all the, um, now YouTube has kind of
ran itself into the ground over the last couple of years anyways, but we'll move on. Not to go
down that rabbit hole again, but that was Yepso for four dollars talking about don't overwork
yourself. I'm not. Don't worry about me. And again, I'm going to reiterate that one more time.
Uh, don't take frustrating video game and back and forth kind of jokey banter with the chat with
I'm not having a good time streaming. They're very different things.
Just want to make sure that's very, very clear. Uh, thank you to CK luck again for the one dollar.
Hey, German, if someone managed to acquire a sample of your DNA and cloned you, do you,
we already went over that. No, I, someone, some with, uh, you're asking like, all right. Um, thank
you. Future gamer for the two dollars. So in like five years, what will your acceptance speech for
the number one top streamer on Twitch award be? You know what it'd be? This is not my award. I want
to give this to chat because they're the reason why I'm here. And I would donate it, melt the
fucking gold down and donate it. And then I would laugh my ass off and be like, I'm just gonna get
this. It's mine. Chat sucks. Chat sucks. Chat sucks. And I would get a whole, the whole audience would
be chanting. I would just, I would, I would just start fucking screaming it. They would cut to
George Clooney in the audience and be like, chat sucks. Chat sucks. Like a huge smile on his face.
And I walked down the Island. Every single fucking row is high-fiving me. Every single one.
And then you wake up from your fucking nightmare. Why I fell asleep at the award show because all
award shows are fucking boring and horrible with this stupid. Oh no, he's doing his acceptance
speech. And I would, and what would happen is I would give it to chat. Hey, future gamer. Thanks
for the two dollars. That was you. Hey bro luck. Thanks. We have to stop the future. The premonition
that we saw. Oh my God. Thank you bro luck for the one dollar. What's your political opinion on
politics? That's what I think. Hey compact viewer. Thanks for the one dollar. Thanks for another
great stream as always. Keep cranking out the good content. Dash a fan. Thank you. Thank you compact
viewer. Thank you Tingy for the one dollar. Thank you Sticks Renegade for the one dollar. Thank you
Corsure for the one dollar. Turns out I still had one more dollar. So a quick question. Do you still
use your steam community or no? No, not at all. Steam community is going the same route as the
Facebook, which is it may become auto-deleted because I have not touched it. That's where we
are right now. Facebook might get auto-deleted because I haven't logged in in like fucking two
years. The steam group auto-deleted because I haven't used it in two, I have no idea.
I came to this realization real quick that I don't do social media. I don't use it.
I don't have... and it's not because... oh I know here come the boomer
emotes right? It has nothing to do with that. I just don't... I don't have much to say on those
platforms. You know, I don't have very much to say. Talking about maybe a stream change or a
schedule announcement or a stream announcement or something that I thought was interesting
once in a while. But I'm not gonna tweet you guys like a selfie of me eating like a
fucking hamburger or something. What the hell? Why would I do that? What am I like looking for
likes or retweets or something? What's the point of that? You know, I just don't do the social media
thing. I never did and I still really don't. Why not? We want that. Do it. I want that. Do it.
I would enjoy seeing you enjoy a burger. All right. You ready for me to get real? Uh oh.
Uh oh. Uh oh. You want your privacy. I mean it's kind of a privacy thing because
you know, not everything has to be shared. We're in this kind of weird mode where everything has
to be shared and you have to share everything with everybody. This is what I did. This is where I went.
This is what I ate. This is what I did today. This is what I'm doing tomorrow. This is what
I did right now. Just a constant stream of sharing everything. It's weird how it's now kind of nice
to not share something. That's kind of the other way around 10, 20 years ago. You told everyone
you pee in the shower. On Twitter? When did I do that? He's keeping secrets from us. No.
And like another thing too is like let's say for instance, right? If I was going somewhere,
I was doing something. I think part of me, if I'm doing something like really, really fun or
something really cool. Hey guys, look at how cool I am. Look at the cool thing I'm doing right now.
You're not doing that. It's like, I think part of me is just like, I don't, I don't really like want
to share it. Oh, look at how awesome this is. Don't you think I'm awesome? And I know that's
not what a ton of people think when they're posting on social media, but I just, it itches
in the back of my head. It really is like a look at me sometimes. All I want is a selfie with your
big Mac. Streamer has lice. If it's so cool, why are you worrying about posting? People like seeing
people they care about succeed. Yeah, no, I get it. It's, I just don't, it's, I don't want to like
brag to you guys for something. I just, I find it unnecessary. Succeeding in eating a burger.
Jeremy's withholding all of his cool shit from us. And that's part two. Uh oh, are we still live?
Yeah. Uh, that's part two. I don't, uh, I don't do very much cool shit.
It's, you know what I mean? It's not like I'm, oh, by the way, today I'm here. And then tomorrow,
look at me, I'm on top of a mountain. And hey, look at me, look at this. Look where I am. Oh,
I'm at the premiere of this movie. I don't, what? Have I tweeted every day? Three, four, five times
a day. I'd be like on the couch sitting there like watching TV. Upload the same photo of you
on your couch every day as a new tweet and just give it a different tagline. Like, hey, I'm checking
out the new Star Wars premiere. And it's me on the couch. Dude, I found the sickest restaurant
in Vegas. I'm here at blah, blah, blah. And it's the same picture. And one of them is just hanging
out on the couch, taking a little snooze day. You know what I mean? Hashtag snooze day. And it's,
that's the, that's the correct tweet. That's going to be like eight tweets later though.
You better do this. I'm getting myself in fucking trouble. I'm going to tweet out about how I met
the Star Wars premiere and like Disney's going to send a message like we are in no way affiliated
with German 985. He was not invited to the red carpet premiere. Wait, are we, am I still live?
Yeah, we're getting some bad frame bullshit. Late night cocks problems. That's true. Thank you. I
am monk for the one dollar. Uh, say Tupac, you know, like the rapper. Good. Now say Topac. See
what you're doing wrong. Thank you. I am month. And, uh, thanks for the a hundred dollars core
Cormac McCarthy. They gave a hundred bucks and there's no message, just a shitload of bits,
a ton of them. Thank you so much for the a hundred dollars, 10,000 bits. Really appreciate it. Thank
you. It's a lot of fucking money. There's a grill master imposter in chat. Read the message that
no, this, there's no message. Just cheer 10,000. There's no message here. Thank you. You are too
kind to me. Seriously. Bring back the schedule. I'm not going to bring back the schedule.
We're getting more streams more often and it's able, it gives me a lot of opportunity to change
each week to exactly how I want the week to go. Sorry. We're going schedule list for a while.
They may even be scheduled as permanently your tone. Whenever you get big bits,
it's like you're addressing someone whose dog just died. I, it's a very grounding,
like humbling thing. Somebody just gave me a hundred dollars. You know what I mean? It's like,
I, I don't know how to react. It's, it's a lot. I mean, could I be like a hundred dollars?
Whoa, what the fuck? Hey, yeah. But I think that's, I feel like that's, that's not as genuine
as how I would really react, really react to it. And it's, I'm shocked. I'm floored. I'm surprised.
I can't, when it happens, when people give a hundred dollars, $50. Thank you. I don't,
I don't really have a reaction. I don't know how to react because it's a lot of money.
Someone take that out of context and make him look terrible.
Brag about the hundred dollars on Twitter, on the couch, in the same selfie. You should dance for
it. No, because I don't want to give incentives for it. If I, okay, if I, here, listen. Oh, how
come you don't like make a huge deal when somebody gives like a bunch of money? Because then that,
that incentivizes, oh, if I give him a hundred dollars, he's going to do a Fortnite dance on
camera. You know, I want that to be genuine. I don't want that to be something that people
are paying for because they know they're going to get something. I think I'm going to do something
crazy, right? Because then if that would happen, let's say I said, this is by the way, this is not
fucking real. I'm just saying this as a character in my own TV show. Okay. If I were to say for the
next 30 minutes, if I get a hundred dollar donation, I will dance like crazy on stream.
It would probably happen. It would probably happen at least a few times at least.
I don't want to like tell people to donate, to give money. I don't want to tell you to do that
because it's, that's your decision. It should be something that you make your decision that just,
words are difficult is what I'm trying to say. It's hard to say words, especially in a sentence.
Any news on merchandise? Yes. I just talked to Ashley and we're in the final home stretch
of little final tweaks for the new shirt. There'll be two shirts to purchase very soon. Hey,
you know what a Twitch Prime sub is? You should use it. That's your decision. If you feel like
subbing to this channel, I hope you think it's worth it. I'm not going to tell you to,
I'm not going to remind you to, I'm not going to make it a point to make sure you're aware
that you have the opportunity to pay me. That's your choice. That's your decision.
Did the shirts have a genuine German smell? Yeah, I roll around in all of them.
Let's say there's like a thousand shirt sales. I'm going to throw them all in a pile. I'm just
going to roll around in them, but here's the real kicker. I'm going to cover myself in disgusting
old man cologne. So the shirts are going to be unwearable. All right, let's get to the end here.
Where were we? Brawluc, thanks for the one dollar. Please revisit this game. It was so good.
Demoniccucumber, thanks for the one dollar. You should do a Shito cam
that you turn on to tuck Shito into his bed at the end of every stream.
By the way, you haven't told him his story yet. We'd like to hear that. Now that's off. That's
me. That's between me and my son. Sorry. Started to share everything on social media. Case in point.
Thank you, Clueless Sniper for the one dollar. Will Shito be in the next German rumble?
100% absolutely guaranteed, yes. Klosky, thanks for the five dollars, Klosky.
Put this on black for me, okay? The next time I find myself in a casino, I will put five dollars
on black just for you. Thank you, Lula, for the five dollars. I know it might be weird when people
send you messages about being depressed and you helping them, but it's true. My dad has been in
the hospital for the last few weeks and I've been in a dark place, but your streams have really made
an impact in my days and I always look forward to them. I know you think you're silly, but you're
doing a good thing here. Keep it up. You're my favorite streamer because you're silly real.
I'm really sorry to hear about your father. That sucks. That can't be fucking easy. I wish
nothing but the best for your dad and I'm absolutely, absolutely honored that you have
that kind of stuff to say about me and my stream. Seriously. Hopefully it's nothing serious.
Hopefully your father has a swift recovery. I'm really sorry to hear that. Thank you so much
for being part of this community. Thank you so much for the five dollars. Much love to you, for real.
Thank you. Look at those hearts in the chat. That's what I like to see. I like to see that.
PeacefulHaley, thanks for the one dollar. Have you ever drank apple cider or vinegar?
I had to drink that one time because my stomach was fucked up and that stuff is
poison. Never again. Apple cider vinegar is actually, it's pretty good for you.
I wouldn't drink it straight, but it has some health benefits. It's also a decent salad dressing.
I've had it before in various things. Demoniccucumber, thanks for the one dollar.
Hey Jeremy, I was watching last night's VOD and when I went downstairs I thought that reality was
a VOD and that I could pause and I also keep forgetting this is live. I think I've had a
minor breakdown. Either that or I need some sleep. Either way, mind how you go, man. I told you guys
about how I used to play so much Diablo 2 that Diablo 2 sound effects would wake me up in the
middle of the night and I could hear them. That like, I would hear that and it would wake me up.
What happened? Did something drop on there? Loop drop? I can relate. Hey compact viewer,
thanks for the one dollar. Watch both Star Wars Clone Wars cartoons. They are great,
especially with Clone Wars coming back this year. I have heard that sounds great and it does include
my favorite Star Wars character. Do you guys know who that is? Do you guys know who my favorite Star
Wars character is? I'm not sure I've ever talked about this. It is not Chewie. Yeah, yeah I could
got it. This is General Grievous. Jar Jar? No, it's General Grievous is my favorite Star Wars
character. You're a nerd. I'll tell you a quick story before we move on. I went to the land of
Disney. Disneyland for those of you that can't really keep up and follow. I went to Disneyland.
Disney, yeah Disney World actually. The world of Disney and that was right after the acquisition
and they bought everything and they had you know if you wanted to have something Star Wars related
there were a bunch of gift shops, tons of shit everywhere. Oh you couldn't you couldn't sneeze
without looking in a direction and seeing another shop that had figures and clothes of every single
potential Star Wars movie ever, right? So I walk into one of the 500,000 gift shops and I'm looking
around for a Grievous, a General Grievous action figure. I'm gonna make like a little statue like
maybe six, seven inch statue of Grievous. And so what? I can't get it anywhere else. Where am I
gonna get this? This is the perfect place to get it. I'm not, I shit you not. I had to go and ask
somebody behind the counter and they didn't even know who the fuck I was talking about. I was like
do you guys have like any Grievous stuff? Like a t-shirt or a clothes or a figurine or something?
General Grievous. Who? General Grievous. He pulled up a radio.
I didn't even hear what he said. Somebody else came down and they were they actually
couldn't figure out who I was talking about. Finally they said is that prequel thing?
Yeah he's one of the the villains from the prequels. Well you know I don't want to have like any prequel
stuff. And that but that was a lie because there was like podracers and stuff. How do you not have
a General Grievous t-shirt at the HQ of Star Wars? And I looked it up and it's actually they
they never made any. I think there was some toys but I'm talking like a real one of those
figures that are like as if you bought a collector's edition for a video game.
The gift shop is fucked. They have to have made something. I don't think they did. The guy told
me that they didn't have anything and I was like what? What? General Garfield. Count Dooku is better
than General Grievous. Well Count Dooku trained General Grievous so they're best friends. You
don't want to have the second part of that team. They're not toys mom. They're figures.
I wanted it made out of pewter. Yeah that was surprising to me because General Grievous was
a really popular character. I know he's very prominent in the Clone Wars and he's he just got
released into Battlefront 2 right? Like where? Give me a Grievous t-shirt. Give it to me.
The only reason why I ever considered downloading Battlefront 2 was just because they just added
General Grievous. But I digress. TLDW. Too long didn't watch. I went to Star Wars headquarters
in Florida and they didn't have a General Grievous piece of merchandise.
Uh but thank you Corsure again for the one dollar. I just borrowed
my sister's gift card and Sega are I mean Machines Sega are alive. I mean
Explain Detroit Become Human. Don't steal anything from anybody. That's not good. No stealing. Don't
steal things. Hey yes Vess is online. Thanks for the two dollars. Missed part of the stream
because of my terrible sleep schedule but that controller complaint is a big meme in fighting
games. Here's a link of a list called Scrub Lords. Scrub Lords. I like to call this the
Scrub Lords prayer which goes like this. My controls weren't working and if they were you
were playing dishonorably and if you weren't you were playing without skill and if you were
it's not fun to play that way and if it is then you only care about winning. We know all of this
is nonsense because Guy just doesn't know how to block. Of course it's easy to roll your eyes.
I know what I know and I know that I pressed up and right at the same time and dashed and didn't
work. I know what I know. I didn't say any prayers. Thank you Garfield the Monday Killer for the one
dollar. Please rise chat it's time for a touching speech written by Sam Eagle. Dermot Sam Eagle
isn't actually here. I promised he'd be here at the event but he got delayed by cartoon traffic
chomp. To your best Sam Eagle impression to fool the audience I wonder how many phrases
he might do like two or three words or one sound before sighing under his breath and giving up.
If he does do it I'll eat my shoe. Time for a funny Garf joke. Celeste more like a mess.
Was the game good? I just tuned in. The game was great. Those b-tapes though.
Oh you know what I mean? Hard. Thank you I'm Vinny JK for the one dollar. When will you play
Mountain Blade? Maybe one day. Timmy Tim Tam thanks for the one dollar. Are Shito and Otto
best friends? No they don't really get along. Otto doesn't like the way that he talks. Hey mostly
lost thanks for the one dollar. You need to do a stream on January 23rd until midnight so we can
also be watched someone. I mean I thank you Dorkcube for the one dollar. Here's another emote.
I know you really don't take emissions uh emissions.
All these emissions. You really don't take submissions for emotes but your streams have
been giving me inspiration recently. Oh look at little Shito. I think I would want a Shito
emote to be a real picture. Can you draw my OC drama? No I can't. I don't know how to draw
but thank you Dorkcube. Thank you. Issu- is this backwards? Issu-bet. Issu-a-bet for the two dollars
and 45 cents. Thank you for the years of comedy. Jerma Heart. Jerma Heart. Jerma Heart. Thank you.
Thank you so much. Uh Distroke thanks for one dollar. Hey random inquiry do you like Denzel
Washington? He's a good actor. Man he's a good actor. Guys Shito is the automaton Jerma got for
Christmas. Yeah yeah that's that's the automaton. But yeah Denzel Washington's good. Thank you for
the one dollar. What did you do with the gnome you got? Uh it's still in the box. I I refused to take
it up. Uh thank you MostlyLost for the one dollar. Thank you Tingy for the one dollar. MostlyLost
thanks for the one dollar. Just tweet out a picture of Otto every hour and we'll love it.
No no no no. Uh CosmicHuend thanks for the one dollar. You should brag about the hundred dollars
on Twitter. We talked about it. No I don't want to do that. No we're not gonna do that. It's your
decision. It's your choice. If you want to give me money I'm grateful for it. We don't have to have
like incentives for it. If you thought it was worth paying for then sure. I'm not- I'm not
gonna stop you. Kisco thanks for the one dollar. Write my name on the short whiteboard behind you.
I don't have a whiteboard. What? There's no whiteboard behind me. What happened to
Wailord and the Pokemon socks? It got uh it got lost in the mail. I put in like three inquiries.
I've asked. I've called the post office like 30 times. Where is this stuff? I'm sorry Mr.
Albertson but it went back and forth from the factory back to the factory back to the original
factory and I'm like this is ridiculous. This is absolutely ridiculous. Can I talk to your manager
please? This is ridiculous. So hey this is the manager on the post office. Let me let me tell
you something. This is the last time you're gonna lose this. I'm gonna call- I'm gonna call the FTC
on you. I'm gonna call the Better Business Bureau and they're gonna figure this out.
Unbelievable. I'm sorry Mr. Albertson we have no idea where it went back to the- I think it went
back to the factory. Unbelievable. Hey thank you Bruce Lee for the one dollar we told you to donate
so here you go. Love you germs. You told- I didn't tell you to donate. Show us the order and then
that was another thing. When I ordered I had to call that store. They messed up the order like 10
times. Somehow the food was on there. I called them. Like this is unbelievable. Why is there-
why is there an order of cocktail shrimp on here? You better be careful. I'm gonna call the FTC on
you. Sorry Chad. He didn't order it. He really didn't. All right how about this? You ready for
it? You ready? I 100% guarantee. Clip this so you know. That this time, by this time next week
on the day of Jeremy's death. I don't like to even say that. I don't like- I'm just gonna say the
23rd. I'm gonna- okay the goalie stream where I'm dressed up as a goalie. All right so on the goalie
stream I will be wearing the socks and the whale will be in the room. Clip it and guarantee it.
Stamp it. That means I said it so that it has to be done now. Hopefully I could get it not lost in
the mail by then. Uh thank you mostly lost for the one dollar. Hey everyone check in the top right
corner to see if your prime sub is available. Oh are you making one of those jokes? Hey dubskidoo
thanks for the one dollar. Pretend that my dog just died and that this donation is actually 10,000
bits. Only your epic gamer voice can console me right now. Uh Corsure thanks for the one dollar.
Will you make any action figures of yourself or characters? Um prob- I mean glue man's a really
easy idea for that but that's that's a whole- I don't want to talk about ideas because every time
I talk about ideas I make them real and then oh fuck like that was an idea. I- when can I act on
this? Can I do this? How much money does this cost? So when I'm ready that's when I'll talk
about some stuff like that if it ever happens. I have this tendency to be like I want to do this
and I want to do that and I want to do this and I want to do that and it's like oh holy shit look
at all this stuff that's coming and it's like oh and those are the things that I want to do I'm not
ready. So we'll see stay tuned. Dr. Steen thanks for the one dollar drink. Water on face cam to
prove you're a hydrated streamer. Uh no it's all right I'll just lie down on the ground when it
rains and just like absorb it. Thanks grill master barbecue x that's not even the correct name
I mean what the heck it's x barbecue. Uh grill master pro tip when grilling sea lizards try adding
a bit of brown sugar and a hint of spicy mustard for a sweet dessert treat. That's the end of the
bits let's take a look at the credits all the subs you guys are amazing thank you for your
subscriptions everybody's too kind thank you thank you thank you guys have a great night everybody
thanks for staying up late I'll see you guys on Friday sorry for my rage but it wasn't really
that bad I would know if I had a meltdown it was barely it was like 40 mario tennis
but I'll see you guys soon. Do you remember with wings what do you mean with wings butterfly wings
you yelled at us no I did when did I do that I didn't yell at you guys I talked about like
how I didn't like the clouds and the buttons I talked about the treasure map I wasn't yet
when did I when would I yell at you I didn't yell at you guys when did I do that I yelled I did I
did not yell at you guys you said that chat sucks no I was that was a dream you had in the audience
all right shito shito you awake oh okay you want to say bye okay shito wants to say goodbye see ya
see you next time kill me that's not what shito said I really I'd really I'd love shito
I need to get shito clothes balls deep in a glass of milk I don't get it I don't understand
why did somebody just write that why did I read that why did you write that why did why did you
write that why is that you why is that your name uh thank you guys I'll see you Friday
have a great rest of your evening see you real soon goodbye