Hey, what's happening everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight
I'm gonna be playing as the soldier with the black box, but who cares? Because there's something way
more important to discuss and talk about, and that's the fact that over the last couple of days we
have heard some news trickled down from the competitive community that TF2 eventually here
is going to be getting a matchmaking system put into the game. And my reaction to this is,
I'm sure a lot of your reactions to the same exact news, it's about damn time. It's taken Valve,
what, like eight years or something to figure out that there is a whole community around competitive
that want this, that have wanted this for a long time, and even the people like me that aren't
into competitive really at all are excited for this update as well because it allows everybody
to play the game that they want to play. Because as it stands right now, Team Fortress 2 has a lot
of servers, right? Some of them are geared towards more serious, some of them are Valve
servers. A lot of the Valve servers that people play on are just extremely reliable, and they're
always there, and it's just easy to fall into a Valve server. It just is. But whatever server
you happen to play on, 90% of your Team Fortress 2 in-game time will be on an open public game
server, and TF2 is an incredibly unique game where in any of these given places, in any of these given
servers, there's like four or five different types of people playing the game. Maybe you've got like
two pyros that just installed the game 10 minutes ago. They don't have any hats, they're walking
around spraying shit, and they're having a blast. They might even be at the wrong point. They might
be going backwards to the other point that's already been capped. On the same team, there's a
scout that has a hail zone scatter gun. He's on his 18th kill of a 17 kill streak. He just got 18.
He's going, oh, I just got 18. Sick. He runs up the stairs. He's trying his ass off. He's dodging
like, oh, the sentry almost got me. He looks to his left when he gets up the stairs on Gorge,
and there's two sandwich heavies having a fucking picnic. So he stops for a second. He goes,
two, and he walks forward and gets blown up out of the next door by a soldier's rocket, and he
rages in the chat, or he sits and sulks in his chair and goes, what the fuck is going on? The
two sandwich heavies then decide it's time to move their picnic. There's ants. There's ants here,
honey. I want to get out of here. So they get up. They pack up their sandwiches. They pack up
their lunches and their breakfast and whatever the fuck they're eating. They get up and they
walk out the door to go towards red because they think that's spot near like the A point for red.
It's pretty good. They walk out the door and they see four level three sentry guns pointing at them.
They get shot a million times and blow up. There's like nine engineers running around swinging their
wrenches in random directions, and then they get mad, and they just say, we're just trying to have
a fucking picnic here. What the hell's going on? The blue scout at this point respawns,
and he walks by the at least three or four statues because we all know there's at least
four people AFK in spawn when you play this game. You go by the museum of people standing still.
So he walks out the door and he readies his weapon. He's ready. I'm going to get another
20 kill streak. Just you watch, Gavin. I'm going to praise Gavin. And he goes forward, he runs,
and he starts shooting, and he gets backstabbed by a spy that's been sitting with a cloak and dagger
in the corner for at least the last 68 seconds. So there's like four separate video games being
played in the same server at the same time there. And I've been all those people. I have been every
single person I listed there and I talked about. I've been them. I've wanted to play and try really
hard and get a good score. I've been the dipshit throwing sandwiches around or like being a spy
and like cloak and daggering and just messing around. We've all done weird shit like that.
We all think this game is amazing. That's why there's so many ways to play it. And there's so
many different people that play that the variety there makes it so you could be in the same place
and be wanting to do completely different things than somebody else that's on the other team or
even on your own team. So having a matchmaking system will split up these entities. The new
players can play in a random server and not have to worry about some guy that has 10,000 hours in
the game killing him every two seconds. The people that want to throw sandwiches at each other can
throw sandwiches at each other. They won't queue up for the matchmaking to play sandwich heavy.
It's just going to be good for everybody, especially if the process to join a queue for
matchmaking is as painless as possible. It could be a button you press and it'll put you in a queue.
And if it doesn't take like more than five to ten minutes to get in a game, so many more people will
be inclined to use it. And competitive can grow. And wanting to be good at TF2 will grow a little
bit. It would be crazy to see that because it's been like almost 10 years for a community like
this. It blows my mind every day guys. It seriously does. That TF2 is like people are still this
dedicated and they still... This would be a fucking one for the history books. If 10 years later TF2
will have a resurgence in competitive, like 10 fucking years later, it would just be cool to see
it happen. As long as the system in place was any good. Which is the last thing we're going to talk
about here in this video. Will it be good? Not necessarily will it be good. I hope it's good.
Because there is a huge potential here for this to go in one of two different ways.
And the first way is Man vs Machine 2.0. You just get into gigantic dump queue and maybe you're
gonna get into a Man vs Machine game with a bunch of random people. I don't want that. I really don't
want that. If that's what it is, at least it's a step in the right direction. But I really hope
it's a realized thing. With a ranking system, actual stats you can see, potentially leaderboards,
top players, separate queues for Highlander, 6v6, 1v1, ulti duo. Imagine the possibilities.
And imagine the shot in the arm this could give this game if it's done right. And if it isn't
done right, if it is done in this sort of gigantic Man vs Machine dump queue, then I'm just not so
sure I'm gonna care that much about it. But we're gonna have to see. We're gonna have to wait and
see. I know as much as you guys do at this point. And over the next couple of days, over the next
couple of weeks, I'm sure we'll hear a lot more about it. And I'm excited. I'm excited. I'm a
pessimistic excited. Because I don't want to get my hopes up for this. But anyways, that's gonna
wrap it up, guys. Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. We'll see
what happens. Take care, everybody. And goodbye.