Hello, hello, hello. Good afternoon. How are you? Good. I'm doing good. I'm doing okay.
Got some good news for those of you that were at the stream yesterday into today.
Memory card works. I got a uh, got a new one. Chibi-Robo is a go. No corruption,
no reformatting necessary. We're good to go. Already tested it. I played through the first
part of Chibi-Robo to make sure I could save the... I'm not gonna swear yet. Make sure I could save
the darn game and I can. So we're good to go. If you missed the tutorial, uh, just
watch the rage-filled first 40 minutes of yesterday's stream and you'll see it.
I'll give you a quick rundown. Uh, it's, it's, it's Ribbit Girl's birthday. Happy birthday.
And we have to make the family happy. That's it? Did you make the ghost leave? Yeah, I've been
burning incense in my room all day. I keep hearing this faint screaming coming from the corners of
the room. All right, I got, it says time in here now. Good luck. I got time incense around the whole
room. Good luck. Made a couple of phone calls. Bugleberry told me that that was the best thing
to do. Sprinkle time in the corners of your room and wear a garlic necklace. And the memory
card works. So I, I don't know what to believe anymore. Where's the real German? Show us the
necklace. Well, the thing is it was a garlic necklace and I love that stuff. So after a few
hours of sitting here waiting and meditating and had a little bit of a snack, I can't help myself.
You're a vampire hunter. Yeah, Chibi-Robo, I'm so excited. Now I can actually enjoy the game for
what it's supposed to be. That poor garlic. Yeah, I'm ready to go. Here it is. You want to see? Would
you guys like to see? Check this out. Ready? Let's plug it in and just make sure that this works.
There's the plug. Okay. We have to gain Chibi ranking again. It's okay. 60 more happy points.
While you're here, Chibi-Robo, would you like to save? I would love to. And look at that.
Now saving. No corrupted memory. I'm so happy. Please reformat. Don't say that shit.
Did you slam your memory card into the door? Fuck that thing. I really thought it was going
to work yesterday. All right, I'm ready. So the whole goal, I know a lot of you've been waiting
for the Sovi. Now the goal is to make everybody happy in the house. You do chores
and I'm going to go do them. You pick up trash. You do laundry. It's like my favorite game ever
made. All right, let's go. This game is going to make me depressed. What? Why is Chibi-Robo going
to make you depressed? He's emulating. Cut the stream. I'm not. Yeah, Dad had a lot of fun at
the birthday party. Again, this was a birthday party that we were at. Yeah, sun symbol during
the day, moon symbol at night. The moon is out right now. That means it's nighttime, of course.
All right, let's get happy points. Time to clean the lid. All right, we did this stuff before,
but I'm going to do it again. Offer trash. We're going to throw this stuff in the recycling bin.
We're in the trash can. Show the new memory card. Nope, I'm not touching it.
I'm going to pour cement into this hole where it's plugged in. This is never coming up ever again.
Oh, we saw this yesterday. Dear Diary. Yeah, we were looking at the diary. It's not going to
work again. I'm going to put super blue in that hole. Now, but tonight he was lazy and I can watch
Drake while he patrols. It's so hard to watch him. That knight in shining armor.
Will you poop? I said I'm going to pour cement into the hole.
You heard that wrong. Dude, I saw something actually so funny today. This is not a connection
to that, but I had to tell this story. So I'm out doing errands and I'm getting shit done.
And I pull up and the thing about living in Vegas is this tons of crazy shit that happens
all the time in Vegas, right? So there's a big intersection, huge intersection,
probably at least a hundred cars on all sides of the intersection. And on the corner
of the intersection is a guy in a frog costume dancing around with a sign,
which that's not completely out of the ordinary. He's just doing all these crazy moves. He's like
lunging forward, lunging forward, spin, spin, spin, point, point at that car, point at that car,
point at that car, right? And that's, there's nothing, it's not like, oh, well, that's hilarious
or anything, right? But like for 200 feet down from this guy is a bus stop. And the people at
this bus stop were fucking furious with this guy. All of them had this face. They were all just so
angry. Like, what the fuck is this guy doing? I'm just sitting there going, this is, I mean,
yeah, how can you be, can you, can you really be mad at the dancing frog guy? Like, come on.
And I'm sitting there thinking, because this is a red light. If people start to go after the frog
guy, I gotta get out and I gotta, I would pull over and I'd get out and I would defend the frog
guy. You know what I mean? Why would that? I don't know. I don't know why they were so angry with
him. He was giving it his all. He was dancing so hard. He was doing so many moves
and this whole, I'm talking to all the people at this bus stop. It wasn't just one person.
They're all just staring at him with this face, like this. Well, not like that, but like this.
Just saying, what the fuck? Are they gonna like fight this guy? Cause he's dancing for like a sail?
Star Wars! That's your resting face. I, it was ridiculous. I'm just sitting there going,
why is this happening? All right. Let's, we, we, we did this yesterday. We got some big bits too.
We just got like $50. Hold on. They all have resting, like mad frog face. I want a free shirt.
Is today the last wink day? No, not today. It's coming up soon though. Where's the wink discount?
It's not today. It's not today. All right. Passionate love for Drake Redcrest. It's fine.
The discount is going to be 67K. That'd be funny. I did fix the memory card issue. We're good to go.
We're just trying to get to the point where I was at last night, but yesterday afternoon,
just pretty much like right here. After the diary part is when I started to go, guys, you know what?
Oh, you know, you know what? No, I can't. I'm going to have to pivot, right? That's,
that's kind of when this happened. All right. But we, hold on. We had huge money coming. We
have 5,000 bits coming from Bitslave. Thanks for the $50 Bitslave. They say, Hey Jerma,
I want to thank you again for taking a couple of days off streaming just to play League of
Legends with me. This didn't happen. I had a lot of fun yesterday when we had that whole bottle of
Johnny Walker and we were just running it down mid. Thought my account was going to get banned
again. Laughing my ass off. Anyways, I can rest easy now that you've played League. No sense denying
it now. Chat knows the truth. Just come clean. Also sorry for calling you a boomer the other day.
Dude, we got to, we got to get you another game. Can I, can I interest you in a GameCube?
All right. You can climb wires here. Dude, I love the GameCube. Thanks for the $50 dude. League was
so much fun when we played it last night. I, dude, do you remember when I was twisted fate
and I did that fall almost penta? I'm not a jungler typically. So that's why it was hard.
We've ran it down mid. Me as the jungle. You as the solo lane. We came and we rescued all. Remember
it was, um, oh dude, our team, our team consisted of, God, who was it? It was, uh, Teemo. Me as
twisted fate as always. Um, Ewan rise and, um, dual lane was, uh, Vi and Garrett? Garrison? What's
the guy with the sword? I forget what his name was. Who's the guy with the sword? Oh no, wait.
That's it. That's like a different mobile game that I played. Hold on. What's the mobile game
with a guy with the sword is the first character. It's like a mobile MOBA and I downloaded it for
free. I played it for 10 minutes. Who was it? No, it's not rage shadow legends. It was another one.
It was another, it was a popular one. It was a, no, no, no. What is it? Arena of valor. There it is.
Yep. All right. Uh, I'm going to run. Wait, wait, wait. I got to do some stuff. I remember at the
last Twitch con or maybe we have, it was a Twitch con. Arena of valor was in the Twitch partner
lounge and it was like, Hey, you guys want to play arena of valor? I'm just like, God, no, but,
Oh, yeah, sure. Like, dad, that sounds like fun. And I played like one run. How do I climb down?
And after, um, and I know they were going to come over and ask me all these questions.
We played one round and it was like, dude, Hey, that's just, you'd finished.
How was it? What do you think? Oh, it's fine. It was fun. Oh, all right. It's okay. My spine is intact.
And what do you say? I think I played, I played smite, but no. Are you going to save? Yes, of
course I am. But yeah. And then I wanted to like avoid the tables where they were. I'm fucking weird
guys. Like I didn't want to like go back over to the tables because I was like, I was one of the
people that played the game and it was just, if I sit over at those tables against me like, Hey,
you're back. How about another fucking round? Yeah. No, thank you. Yeah. I guess I'm just here for a
water. I just came in here to get a water, but I mean, it's all right. It's a cool games. All right.
Yeah. Just wait till we throw this shit in the trash. Always pick up the plug because you run
faster. That's a tip I got yesterday. Even without any, I haven't even started the game yet.
That's why, I mean, you might think I'm weird, but going to like Twitch con and stuff,
I almost want to put on like a disguise, like a mustache, a hat and like sunglasses.
Cause it's like somebody, if somebody ever comes over and like a partner lounge is like, Hey,
Oh, what are your channels? I don't have, I got the mustache. I don't have one. Oh, okay.
See you guys around. You have to do an incognito cosplay like Savage does.
No, I'm talking about just like a mustache. That might be a good idea. I don't know.
Maybe I would do it one day. Oh, there's a coin in here. Nice. Just put on like fake eyebrows and
shit of a glue on big bushy mustache and like a fake chin strap or something and just walk around
and just, and if anyone comes up to me and asks me what channel is, I just say, I don't have one.
Hey, can I, can I interest you in playing some arena valor? Wait, wait, wait, who are you?
Don't have a name tag on you. Who are you? I don't, I just walk around with my mustache.
Oh, and I don't give a shit. I don't fucking care about you. Any, any partners over here?
Be so much easier. Can I get in here? Come on. I can get that. All right. It's time to go to bed.
Oh, there's so many coins. All right. I have to turn the TV on and wake up dad, right?
Don't forget the chibi coffee. Yeah, that's right. That's right. I do have that.
I'm just so happy that I actually get to play the game.
Hannah Montana. No, but Hannah Montana just had a different color hair. That was it.
If I walked into Twitch con with just like orange hair, I'm still, I'm Jeremy. Like that
doesn't change anything. It was two different people. No. Okay. If Miley Cyrus had a must,
if, okay, Miley Cyrus is Hannah Montana. She put on like a wig and like a mustache and like sunglasses
and that was Hannah Montana. It might be, you could hide. Spoiler alert. You don't, please.
Why do you know so much about Hannah Montana? But that I know that Hannah Montana is Miley Cyrus,
the actress that plays Hannah Montana. Oh, is that so? That's not a whole lot of information.
I need, I need to get some real happy points here. You bet your ass I want to say.
Is it banned? That show's not even, it's been off the air for 10 years. What are you talking about?
Well, I thought we were going to bed. Oh, I just got up.
All right, fine. I thought I could go to bed. I thought saving did it. So did you watch it? No,
I didn't. I, yes. Okay. I have watched Hannah Montana in the same way that you've watched
Hannah Montana. When you go from Fox Sports to the Disney channel, to Cartoon Network. So I've seen
12 seconds of Hannah Montana, maybe like four or five episodes worth. So
we've all seen it. Can you make the noise this thing is making? Yeah, probably.
That's pretty close. Yeah, I can turn into a super frog.
Who owns the super frog license? And can they become in contact? I have some consulting I
could do. I got some consultant work I could do for that new game, bringing it back.
All right. Oh, yes. Of course. Every time it tells me to, I'm going to save every time.
All right, let's go. I don't think anyone owns super frog. Somebody does. All right, let's get
going. Coins. Happy point. Give me that. Give me that frog binky, whatever it is.
Wait, does the music change how fast you walk? That's insane. Really? Bring. All right. Yeah,
whatever it is. Frog ring. It does. You're always on beat no matter what in Chibi-Robo.
That's crazy. All right, let's go get some happy points here. We have to
make a Ribbit girl laugh or something, right? Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit. Yep. Climb on
my hand. Climb, ribbit. Oh, I didn't even realize that. Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit. Make the same joke.
No, I can't do that. Drop it. Clean up. I need to pick up all the trash. What does Dad want for
happiness? We got to go faster. Dad, what does Dad want? Hey there, Chibi-Robo. How goes it?
You're getting used to our hubs? My wife sheep mad at me. Sheep, but I don't worry. Sheep about it.
Just go get a load of happy points, okay? What do I put up here? Is there still
some trash right there? I got seconds on me at time. Am I going to Pax? I am not going to Pax.
I will not be at Pax East. I ain't going anywhere. If I do go, I'm going with a Mustat. Three happy
points. Six happy points. All right, I have enough happy points to upgrade the character.
You got 120 bucks too. Nice. All right. What else is up here? It'll be there in disguise.
Can I open the door? Chibi-Robo? Oh, it's just a sticker that someone put over the cracked window.
If you shoot that with the Chibi Blaster, I bet you can go outside.
Breaking windows won't make Mrs. Sanderson happy at all. Can I just say, can we just ask her to
slide the door open? Can I climb this? All right, I got to use the Chibi Copter. Oh wait, there's
Cheetos under here. How much does it cost to get a birthday shout out from Bugleberry?
How much does it cost? It costs absolutely nothing. Oh, I heard it was somebody's birthday.
Someone, someone told me there was a terrifying birthday party. I wish I was invited, but happy
birthday to you and to all the people at your birthday party. I'll be here in Jeremy's room
warning off the ghosts and ghouls. Goodbye. Get out, get out. Do I have that on a hot key?
But let's charge. I'm losing viewers. I'm losing viewers.
Oh, it feels so good just to be able to go like this. Oh, that probably hurt. All right,
what's left? Let's go up. I'm going to climb the chair. Wait, there's trash. Up on the chair
there's tons of trash over here too. Oh yeah, I love picking up trash. Nice. This game is like
exactly what I'm looking for. How do I get up there? All right. Well, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. I can, can I jump on this? Oh yeah. Oh yes, I can. So why can I hold on? Oh, I need to pull
this. Push it right up against the wall here. I want to, I can get these bolts and up. Yeah.
Nice. It's $50. How much, I'm almost out of time. All right. Then I'm going to fly over
to this here. Let's pick up the trash. I love this game already. I love this game. It's so,
it's exactly what I'm looking for every time. Oh, I'm almost out of battery. It's just about
picking up trash and it's so, it's, there's no stress here.
Space hunter Drake Redcrest is on soon. Can't wait. Woo. It's on TV. This is a fake news
emergency alert. Huh? This just didn't. Chibi Robo's everywhere are coming under attack
and the perpetrators appear to be the spy doors. Where do they come from?
Why do they attack? We don't know. I thought it was going to be, perhaps they hate Chibi Robo's
winning smile. Viewers ask yourself, is your Chibi Robo safe or is it in mortal danger?
This is Ron Brokejaw reporting for Faux News. Is it Fox News or Faux News?
Now let's go to Sunny Merriweather with tomorrow's forecast, Sunny.
Thanks, Ron. You're going to life by forecast. Tomorrow will be sunny, rainy or uphilly.
Same energy. No, that's all wrong. The spiders are the Chibi Robo's friends. They are,
at least they should be. Ah, frosting. Listen, Chibi Robo, you need to be careful. Those
spiders are dangerous right now. If something were to happen to you, I'd be really sad. Got it?
Why don't you fucking put some like anti-spider defense system in the house?
Oh, we just had five community subs just coming. Just some normal guy 25. Thanks for the five
community subs. I gotta, no, no, no, no, I'm trying to pick up the, I hope you make it a number one
in the Chibi Robo ranking. Oh, by the way, the room looks really clean today. You must have
worked so hard. Yup. 10 happy points from dad for cleaning up his mess. All right, cool. Now I need,
I don't think I can make that. All right, I gotta go. Let's go plug in.
Fuck. What happens if I go to zero? Um, I need an outlet right now. Outlet right now. Where's an
outlet? Right now. I need an outlet right now. What about, I'm going to die. What happens if
Chibi Robo dies? It's okay. We got saved by the bell. Chibi Robo, time sure flies when you're
making folks happy. Oh, the day has ended. Let's return to the Chibi house. Plug in.
I got 60 happy points though. Great work out there. Let's adjust your happy point total.
Your Chibi ranking has gone from 591,000 to 192,000. So these are, I'm against other Chibi Robos.
What are these other 300,000 Chibi Robos doing? 400,000 of them. I picked up like five pieces of
trash. Battle Royale. They're dying to spiders. In order to get the next bonus battery, you need
eight more happy points. You're ever going to become super Chibi Robo. You need some advice,
namely mine. Use Y to activate your Chibi vision and scan your surroundings for items.
Use R to open up a map of the room and find yourself a nearby outlet. Oh, that's good to know.
To celebrate opening my advice booth, I'm handing up free advice.
I would love to save. Going up the rankings.
All right. Now, can I do anything? What can I do with the Chibi computer?
My online shop. Timer 10, timer 15. What do these do? 10 minutes for half a day
for a leisurely pace. Come on. Timer 15. 15 minutes for half a day for a truly leisurely pace.
So what? Is this just better? Timer 15. Oh, it's a timer. I get it. So I just get more time.
Pink flower seed. Pink flower will grow from this seed.
Nectar. Chibi blasters. 1100 bucks. I get 15 minutes. Yeah, that's better. I get these seeds.
All right. Pink flower seed. Blue flower seed. And white flower seed. Okay. What about recycle
atron? I have to plant these? Timer 15. Chibi Robo and Smash Brothers. Yes. No, not yet. He's
a spirit. He's a costume. Oh, yeah. He was a me costume. He should be a real character, Pepe
Handsome. All right. What about Drake on the TV? Drake on TV, right? Here's the map. Backyard.
We got plugs. C is zoom. Oh, that's cool. We got plugs everywhere. Okay. I'm going to turn the TV
on and then go read the diary. What does this do? What's going on? A little toothbrush? What's that?
Is this a toothbrush? Hey, look at that. It's Mr. Sanderson's toothbrush, but let's take it anyway.
I bet he won't miss it. Now that we have this nifty device, but you can clean all sorts of stains.
Oh, yes. Press X to open the equivalent menu. Like the toothbrush with and use A to hold it.
You want to put the toothbrush away. Press B. There's a stain right there. Why don't you give
it a good scrub? Yes. Oh, yes. I'm so happy. I can clean surfaces. Look at all these stains.
Over here. I don't even get this dog stain. It's odd if the TV just turned on all by itself.
All right. Well, let's go. Can I turn it off? Open the drawer. Chibi. What's the proper way
to address Chibi Robo? CR? Chibi? Chibi Robo is too long. Chibs? Robo? Look at that stain right
there. How do I put the stain on the wall? There's a stain right there. How do I get that stain?
I can't. How do I do this? Oh, fuck. I'm out of battery. How do I use first person again?
Where's the TV? TV's like up here. Hold on. I got another coin over here. Another coin this way.
All right. There's a plug. I got a plug. I got to get up to the TV.
Chibi, you're dying. All right. Would you guys take Amazon instant delivery? Like when you clicked
buy, you got it. The technology, like we're at like 10G. Technology with just instantly a drone.
Got it in front of your door when you press buy, right? But this is the noise you hear in your house
24x7. No. That would also be bad. Okay. TV. All right. There's the TV. Don't look at it.
Don't look at it, Chibi Robo. Get away from it. What the hell is that? So confused. So conflicted.
People say evil. People say justice. But what is justice? And what is evil? Do I truly fight
on the side of justice? Or am I just a fool, a blind fool? No, I fight on the side of justice.
Those who think they can disturb the peace will get a taste of my space fury.
It's I, Super Frog Falcon, space hunter Drake Redcrest. What are you doing here?
Drake Redcrest, you're you're still as sharp as ever. Hi, space hunter Redcrest. Good morning,
Chibi Robo. What's this? No answer, eh? Space Hunter Code Part One. Greet everyone by yelling.
Perhaps you have been shocked into silence by the sight of toys moving. Do not be afraid,
friend. The toys in this house move and speak when humans aren't around.
Enough talk. It bores Drake Redcrest. Let us be friends, oh diminutive one.
As a friend, it is my duty to inform you that your life appears to need more justice.
Drake Redcrest can solve that problem. Take this special gift. It's just for you.
What's in it? Drake Redcrest suit. Um, yep. Have I show you how to don it, friend? Yes, how do I
put this on? Immediately. Your honesty is noble and must be rewarded, therefore Drake Redcrest
shall teach you. Next, open the equipment menu. If the chibi gear on the top bar is selected,
simply tilt down, I say. Two weeks it will let you access your suits. Is that to select
the suit you wanted by person left or right? Oh, what? You can put on costumes?
You are a smart one. Ha ha, we shall meet again. But for now, we ride. If you are ever interested
in achieving justice, wear that and speak to me. We shall learn the facts of justice together.
I'm just along for the ride. I'm the baby that gets brought to the convention.
Dad's in Superman costume. Mom is superwoman. And I'm also dressed as Superman and with a helmet on
and stuff. Take me around to the convention floor. Everyone will be so excited to see me.
The way I talk to him again. Space Hunter Drake Redcrest. Okay, so I talk to you again if I want
to do justice. Looks good on you, little man. So you wish to fight for truth and justice, eh? Don't
lie. I know these things. Yes. That's a specialty of mine. You just sit back and enjoy the ride.
All right, let's go to the convention. Hold, stand your ground. Very well, my small metal friend.
I will now administer the test of justice. It'll be long, hard, and a word I don't know.
But you must endure no matter the cost. Ready? Then we ride. Mark my word, mark my wealth.
Space Hunter Code Part 2. True justice cannot exist without a pose. You'll never be an agent
of justice unless you master this. Old friend, you must be the one known as television.
Oh, how did you know my name? You laugh a lot. Ha ha ha. I could scream, but I don't want to.
That's justice 101, my flying metal friend. Wow, that's impressive. We're about to enter
dangerous skies here. You must fly back. Are you ready? Here's the skinny. When I start to pose,
press Z immediately. Easy as pie, right? Sure. Press Z immediately when he starts posing.
You can do it, Chibi-Robo. Okay, here we go. I did it. Too slow. Curses and blasts. Try it again.
Space Hunter Drake Red Crest. I learned the pose. That's fantastic. You're the best, Chibi-Robo.
Ah, stupendously done, Chibi-Robo. I mean, Space Hunter Robo. I am now proud to appoint you as the
universe's 99th space hunter. Climb the rankings and assassinate the other 98 space hunters to
reach number one assassin. Oh, I got 19 happy points for that and 100 bucks. Spread the happiness.
You mastered Drake Red Crest Z action. Show everyone what you can do with it.
I just have a pose in front of people. Think of justice when you wear this. You're around, Hunter.
Wait, what? Oh, I'm just showing it to him. Space Hunter Drake Red Crest. Hello, Space Hunter Robo.
Your excitement is indeed impressive, but it seems that the living room is currently in a state of
broccoli-ism. That is a word, right? Of course it is. Irregardlessness,
I shall lead you in charge of tomorrow's patrol, Space Hunter Chibi-Robo.
Let's clean up. Wait, doesn't... All right, the person over here with the diary. Should I do the
pose? I'm going to freak this person out. They're going to think, look, this is a reverse disguise.
Ready? Who it is? Hey, what do you think about this? Oh, my. What's that sound? That's handsome
sound. Drake Red Crest. Oh, my gosh. You patrol really good. Sophie, no, that was so stupid.
What's up with her? What the fuck is going on over here in chat?
Put it in sub-only. Put it in sub-only. We got to... Come on. What is this horse shit? Sub-only. Let's go.
Let's get it in sub-only.
We good? We good. Okay. What the fuck?
All right, it's... We're back. All right, now we can go into the kitchen.
But no, we can't. I got to plug in first. Imagine eating ass. Imagine.
You're fully recharged. Now, yes, I'd love to save.
How many costumes are there in the game? I feel like this should be a lot.
I need to collect at least four of them. I want to be free. Don't worry, you will be soon.
In fact... All right, you know what? Put it in follow-only mode instead.
But follow-only... You got to be followed the channel for at least what? Like 30 minutes,
something like that. Follow-only. Let's see if that works. It's always in follow-only, but...
Length of time, though. One day follow-only, maybe? One year follow-only. I don't know about
that one. No, I got to clean. Hold on. You can't even do that. I like cleaning with a toothbrush.
Remember, you're almost at 10 million views. What do I have right now?
TV Robo, all of your hard work has made Mrs. Sanderson happy, happy, happy.
You see, she's given me a bunch of bonus happy points in Moolah.
And when you clean enough, I can give you a nice little cleaning bonus.
MonkaS, what's he doing? Your happy point bonus is...
8 happy points. That doesn't seem like very much. 10 million... What am I? 9,995,000 views? Holy shit.
9,995,000. Well, come on, guys. Tell your friends. Spread the infection. Lick the germs.
Tell everybody that you know to check out this stream. Get us over 10 million.
Pog, we're doing it today. We're doing it today. Am I doing it right? How do I clean stuff on the
walls? Fuck, I'm almost out of battery. Come here. I got a lot of... Wait, there's a plug right here,
right? Oh, fuck. There's no plug here. What does the 10 millionth viewer get?
There's no way to tell. There's no way to tell who is the 10 million viewer. This isn't a radio station.
Breambin, thanks for five community subs, Breambin. Appreciate it. Thanks for the five subs.
Community subs. I want to get that frog coin in there. Yeah, I'm going to call it frog coins
because I love Super Mario RPG, Legend of the Seven Stars. I want to get up there. There's so
much to do. All right. Let's trash, trash. Throw the trash away. Play Bowser's Inside Story. LOL.
That's as good as Super Mario RPG, Legend of the Seven Stars. It probably isn't. No, it probably
isn't, but it's still probably just as good. It's my favorite game I ever made, but it's
going to be hard to top it. Five community subs from Jamie. Thank you, Jamie. Thanks a lot for the
sub. Oh, what's the candy wrapper? Five points. I got a lot of money.
10 millionth viewer gets a dork cube, but there's no way to tell who the 10 million viewer is.
You can't. There's no way for me to tell. All right, I want to get up there.
I can plug into this guy and give this guy power. All Sub-Aleem mode does is just give
plebs extra space for sub points. I know. I know. I know. I know. I know. I know. I know. I gotta
make that more money. I have to make that more money. What do I do? Charge him? Oh, is this a
small door? That's odd. I have no info on it in my memory bank. What's in here? What the fuck? Look
at all this money. Whoa. There's a little secret, uh, charging power money station.
Imagine paying five dollars a month to type poop dick. Um, that you don't think that's worth it.
Dum dee dum dee dum. Hey, since this small door has your eyes, let's call it a chibi door.
Guys, I got a lot of money. It's so, it's so simple. If I say one thing, you guys, it's so
simple. Everyone just starts saying it. Okay. We didn't do an experiment. I'm going to say
something and you're going to repeat it. Okay. Celery. Celery. I love celery. Celery. Interesting.
Interesting. Sailboat. I was in a sailboat one day and I love sailboat. Sailboat. Sailboat.
Sailboat. Cleaning bonus. Nice. Okay. Let's now subscribe. Subscribe.
Subscription. Subscription service.
Nice. Okay. You do. All right. You guys are good. Yep. I saw scam like 10,000 times.
All right. I got, you guys, you guys can resist. Sell out. Selling out.
Sell out. Best stream. Stream I'm on currently. That is the best stream. Best stream. And don't
stop saying it. Best stream. You fuckers. I didn't see once my name. I didn't see one time.
Really? Not even once? Let's try another one. Poopoo. I want to have that one. Poopoo.
Poopoo. I wanted people to write that one. You guys are fucked. He's an egomaniac.
Well, in this industry you gotta be. Can I climb this? Can I? Maybe I can float.
This is exactly why I don't like Twitch. Wait. What? I can float over here.
Got it. Yes. Can I climb here? Oh, we can go up the whole thing. Play better. What? I just did
something good. Now I can float from here. Is there another coin up here? Oh, I can turn the
light off. All right. Turn the light off. Oh no. I can go up. Derma lied about the frog coin. Thanks
for the what? Thanks for the subs. What do you do? What? What does that even mean? All right. We're
up here. Ooh. There's another chibi door. All right. Put this shit away. Come here. Is there a plug?
Oh. I almost died. Look at all this. Okay. Wait. Let's charge up. Wait. This is going to take a
lot of energy. How much is it going to take? It's okay. There's money in here. It's a lot of money.
All right. I can't clean anything up here yet. Should I knock this off? I'm going to knock this
off. Push it off. Right? Should I push this off? There's probably something in here. It went too
far. What's it doing? It's a funeral? Oh, chibi robo. Look at the state you're in. I thought maybe
we could make it to the top of the chibi ranking together. Is that it? Oh, I can move. Oh, you're
alive. I was worried sick. Remember, you're a robot. If your energy ever drops to zero, you'll
switch off just like that. Watch your charge and use an outlet if you have to recharge.
Oh, and you should know, if you ever pass out like that again, don't get too worried.
Your faithful friend, Television, that's me, will carry you back to the chibi house.
Oh, another thing. If you press X and select remove, you'll change out of your trauma suit.
Oh, it looks like you lost some moolah. What? Don't look at me. Oh no, you lose money.
If you're a robo, you can buy chibi batteries from the online shop now. They'll come in handy,
I think. If you get one of these, you can recover just enough energy to go in and recharge yourself.
Pick one up and try it out. I'm definitely upgraded.
I'm in the top 25,000. We're making it into the top 100,000. Citrus Soft has sent you a
special gift, a brand new bonus battery. Would you look at that? Your battery power went up 100.
Oh, nice. I need 21 more happy points. All right, they wanted me to buy something.
I'm sure we can save. From Soft? All right, take it off. Stop bowling. All right, get it off. Stop
bowling. Okay, chibi battery. All right, I can buy the blaster or a battery. Can I get a battery?
Why were we on sub only? Because there was some fucking plots.
Trying to eat that, you know what I mean? All right, so here we go. Blaster,
chibi blaster. It allows you to fire sonic blasts. Got it.
I don't have any more money.
Thank you for your visit. So now I have a gun. Okay, put it down, put it down, put it down,
put it down. Aim that at me, you stupid. You've upgraded. Keep it up, chibi robo. Let's go.
Freedom, freedom. Sub only forever. Did I take it off? There we go. Okay, welcome back. All right,
I want to do, I want to get back up there. Released from pleb storage.
Pleb storage. All right, that's funny. Press Z? What just happened? I just took like 400 damage.
I don't have any trash. Why would you, what's the point of that? Oh, excuse me.
All right, let's put a hole in the door, right? We can go chibi blaster. Okay, and fire.
Why am I hurt? Because I fell off the top of the building, whatever it was.
Yikes. Didn't do it. Wasn't me. Don't deactivate me. We're in the backyard. They've welcomed you
into their home. It's so cute. I love it. Oh, you can do first person. Oh, wow.
Okay, don't. It's Donald Duck? All right, plug this in. Put this away.
All right, I need an outlet back here. I love these little chibi doors.
Is there outlets outside? Probably not. There's so many things to do. I have so many jobs to do.
I need outlet. How would they be outlet outside? I know, I know, I know. I'll get in a second.
I have to leave. 27 stains. Happy point bonuses. 14. I have outdoor outlets. Yeah, you can have
outdoor. That's not out of the ordinary. Your very presence makes everyone happy.
Okay. All right. All right. All right. Pick up this. Let's go. Plug in. I need an outlet. I need an
outlet. Outlet. Outlet. Outlet. The nearest outlet is... No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, there's one over here. I almost pressed Z. I almost just hit my head on the ground.
Well, it's almost time to go home anyways. All right, here's an outlet. Wait, was that lied to?
An outlet right here? What was that lied to? Where is it? Where is it?
Is it up? Where is it? Oh, fuck. It's up there, huh? Uh-oh. What do you mean blind? Behind what?
Behind this? No, that's up. What do you mean blind? It's apparently up here. Is it behind this?
Um, Chibi-Robo, did you just hear that totally weird sound? Yes, I did.
I heard a strange noise coming from the far side of the foyer. I'm scared.
Wait, there's... Okay, there is one behind here. There's one right here. It's dead.
It's a fart. I'll never get over that, will I? Okay, let's go.
All right, so there's one back there. Did I pick up any? I didn't pick up any trash.
Almost time to go to bed. The coin? Here's a list of your nominees. Can we remove that?
Oh, I gotta cancel SurveyMonkey. All right. Yeah, what has it been? Like three months? All right.
All right. Yeah. Oh, trash. Get behind this? No. All right, we're about to go to bed. I should have.
I think I upgraded. Fringe streamer won't use SurveyMonkey. What the hell do you want me to use
it for right now? It's coming from the foyer again. Yeah, well, I don't have time to investigate. It's
time for bed. Fringe. He said it, guys. It's a stupid word. I can say it. All right. What's
left in here? Can I go back up? I want to go up here. You know what I mean? I want to go up there.
I gotta climb up the thing, the lamp, like I did before, and then I have to fly over here. That's
what I'm doing tomorrow. Blaster cleans wall stains. Really? All right. I got a lot of happy points.
Good morning. Let's adjust your happy points. New ranking. Top 1000. Top 10,000.
I'm going to wait for a battery now. 120 battery points. Those other cheapy robos
are just paperweights. I am the number one. I need 200. Okay, this is where the game really
opens up here. Cross small gaps. Use the cheapy copter. Really, all you have to do is press A.
That makes you fly horizontal for a little while. Thank you. And we have an alert. What is this?
Secretly developing an all new brand of cheapy gear. Isn't that exciting?
10 million? Wait, did it happen? Did I really pass 10 million views on Twitch?
Let's see. There it is. 10 million. 331. Hey. Hey, everybody. 10 million.
Base reveal. The wing came in. Thanks to the 10 million views, guys. That's a lot of people that
have clicked on the stream. That's a lot of clicks. We need a speech. Let's get to 25 million. That's
a new milestone. 25 million views. What a speech. Dude, 10 million views. Give us a speech. What a
milestone. Get me to 25 million. Okay. Anything else? No. You're welcome. Thanks. All right.
Seriously, give an Animal Crossing speech. That's it. Can I do anything else with the family?
Animal Crossing. All right. I'm going to the foyer. Where's the foyer? We need to do...
All right. To the foyer. There's a sound coming from the foyer. Let's do it.
Do a credit card reveal. Hey, guys. You got the 10 million views. Here's all my credit cards.
Hey, who's that? Hex Frisco. Yes, sir. I want to report immediately. What is that thing?
Omitted intruder, sir. I think it came from the living room, sir. From a form of perimeter, man.
Yes, sir. Go, go, go. Defensive positions. There's a lot more than I thought there was. M&Ms.
Nice move. What the fuck was that for? He just killed that guy. An unauthorized intruder has
entered the area. Free ranger's pride is at stake. Stop the intruder or I'll make you egg salad.
If he comes into range, let him have it. Don't let your guard down, men.
Um, I just look for a plug. T.B. Robo, this isn't good.
No. Yes, it's not good. Wait. No, it isn't good. Or yes, it's not good.
It's kind of a hard way to answer that question. This isn't good. Yes, it isn't good. Yes, that's
yes, it is not good. Okay. Strange sound is coming from over there. It'll be really hard
to get over there. These rangers mean business. Okay. Well, then so do I. Don't think I mean
business too. This is okay. Let's put it away. First person mode is here. Well, how do I go
to first person? I can't go to first person. Z? You can't move and go FPS. It's not Z.
It's why? Why? Why? Why? Okay. Okay. Hold on. I'll just plug in.
All right. Now they're fucking dead. Just stay plugged in.
And where's the extension cord? Why can't I just stay plugged into the wall?
Uh, I don't need to save right now. All right. Why? Where is it? Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All
right. Let's go. Let's go FPS these guys. Here we go. Unauthorized intruder. Don't let him pass.
Take him out. T.B. Robo, this isn't good. Yes, it isn't good. It's going to be really hard to
get over there. You'll never get through unless you find something you can use to cover yourself.
Okay. Literally impossible. Literally impossible. Literally impossible without a new item.
This action is physically impossible. It's not possible. T.B. Robo, you can't do it. I get
yelled at every time I go. All right. Physically impossible without a shield. Run? That's physically
impossible. The television told me. Everything you see on the television that comes out of the
television's mouth is real. You can't move while in first person. I want to do the thing I wanted
to do before. I want to go up over this way. Oh, look. This is up there. Okay. So I want to go.
Oh, I love this game. Okay. We're going to go up there. Up the lamp. Over there. Open the secret
door. We're going to fall on the top of the couch. Grab the coins. What a good game. Get up there.
Boy, mate. Turn on the telly. All right. Put it away. Let's go. Now, can I get that door again?
Anything from here that I can do? Wait, what's that? Can I climb that?
Maybe. Whoa, whoa, whoa. That's not solid. I thought this shit was solid.
Jump over it. What's the problem? Let's get this money again.
Fuck it. Okay. I already got it. It was a permanent. Okay. Because it took the money.
All right. From here, what am I doing? I got to get a good look. I'm going to push this down.
I'm not going to fuck this up this time. Okay. Walk down. Now, I'm going to float from here
over there. Can I make it? Float down? What was in the box? All right. What was in the box?
What was in the box? D-Squad. What? I didn't, I thought I was, I didn't even know what was
supposed to be in it. All right. Can't return this way. All right. No for you. We're going to
the kitchen. Kitchen time. Say hi to the frog girl. I already did. All right. We're going to
the kitchen. Turn around. Can I go in the kitchen yet? Is the kitchen open? I guess so. Oh yeah. The
puppet thing was in here. Kitchen. What we got? Oh no. Just being eaten alive by the dog.
What's a dog toy? That's okay. It's a dog toy. That makes sense. That's a dog toy.
Let's plug it in. Dogs are friends. Does it make her any less human? Well, if you're a dog toy,
that means you are not a human. You are a stuffed dog toy. Crash. Can I get, can I crawl?
Oh, whoa. This is the dog's bed. Wait, hold on. How do I get up here? I can't get up there.
There's a box and there's like a necklace up there. All right. Well, I, I, I get it later.
Little track. Can I open it? I can open this thing up for her. Can this be opened? Nope.
Are you talking to the dog? What's the dog going to say?
Tao. Not in the house. Yipe. Yipe. Climb the chair. Oh, can I peel the sticker off?
Or can I shoot the sticker off? Uh-huh. Let's get up here. There's a gold coin. A new spot.
To find trinkets. It's shit. What's up here? Oh, what am I going to do? Okay. I can grab that.
Can I not grab that? I can't grab like the yarn. There we go. Keep going. What else is over here?
All right. Get on this. No! Oh, what's the, what's the point of being on the towel? Wait,
what does it want to do with the milk? Oh, this trash. Okay. Toaster. Do I make toast?
Did I plug into the toaster? Come on. I've got to be able to do something with the toaster.
All right. This time I'm not going to push that off yet because I know I'm going to need it.
Right? Let's keep going up while I still have power. What is all the way up here? Oh, there's
a door. There's a demon door up here. Can I grab onto the clock? Let's go. Pretty high too. Nice.
All right. Now let's, I want to take a look. Mug. Spoon. Dog tags. Okay. I could float from here to
there and get the dog tags. I could go get the spoon. There's a bandage. There's a frog ring.
Go to mom. All right. I got to go from here to there. All right. Let's make it. Let's go. Let's
go. I need an outlet. Can I grab this thing when it comes back around? Can I jump onto the clock?
Or should I just float from here to there? I don't know. I'm, this is kind of freaking me out.
Can I hold onto it? All right. Let's go. Hurry up. What's the fast forward time button?
Jump in the toaster. Hey, can I grab it? Grab the, grab it. I can't grab it. Toaster. I need a
battery. I need a plug. I need a plug. I need a plug. I need a plug. Where's the plugs in here?
I need a plug right now. Come on. There's got to be an outlet over here. Ah.
Where's the, okay. There's a plug across. Oh, fuck. Um, all right. I'm going to go for it.
I don't, I'm dead. I can't make that shit. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
How do I, I just did so much stuff. I'm not going to move. Time's going to run out. Go to the plug.
I can't make it. Five, four. Oh, I can make it. Yes. Oh yes. Ah, I didn't know if I could make it.
Stop dying. I've only died once. I've only died one time. Come on. Stop dying in plies. I've died
like five times. What the fuck was that? Where did that come from? Oh, am I all right? I fell off.
All right. Well, I already got this one, right? Yeah, I got that coming in. Can I get and let's
talk to mom in the few minutes we have left. What about the dog poop? Can I talk to mom?
I'm busy right now, Tao. It's me. Boy, I can climb this. These little lips. Oh, that's it.
Wait. Grr. Grr. Be quiet, Tao. If I can get up there. Look out.
That was close. You almost hurt yourself. What? You be careful, Chibo. I was trying to figure
out what people call him. It's Chibo. Mug. Oh, Chibo. I'm sorry for saying you were a waste of
moolah on Jenny's birthday. I'm making my husband sleep on the sofa until he's sorry for what he
did. What? I thought you just said sorry to me. Don't worry about it. It's his fault, not yours.
Mug. My mug. That's a Drake Red Crest mug. Cool. Chibo, that belongs to my husband. I don't know if...
Oh, forget it. Go ahead and take it. He's got so much Drake Red Crest stuff. He'll never know I
gave something away. Get rid of this fruit. It flies everywhere, mom. Come on. Really? Disgusting.
All right. I got like 10 seconds before this is over. We'll collect a few coins. Turn the stove on.
Can I turn on the stove? Turn all burners on. I guess I can climb it. Can I not climb that?
It's a ladder? It is a ladder. All right. Should I get this thing? The ladle? A pan? Wait. A fan up
here. Oh, I can clean this. There's oil up here. All right. Give me the cleaning brush. Nice.
Oh, look. More oil. That's it? There's a little more. That was a tough one. Any more oil? Hey,
Lord Repta. Lord Repta, thanks for the five community subs. And also Bitslave gave another
$50. So Bitslave is at 10,000 bits today, which is fucking crazy. A lot of money, Bitslave.
Bitslave says, do you have any plans on Majora's Mask or Wind Waker? Maybe both. I do not.
I do not have a plan to play any Zelda games. I'm sorry to say. Well, plan on it.
I don't know. Look, I got all this to do first. I got Mario Sunshine to do first. That's priority
number one. I was slowly going up the rankings now, not as fast as it was before.
I also played those old Zelda games when they first came out.
I did Ocarina of Time. I don't think I ever beat Majora's Mask.
All right. Okay. I'm going to say something. I'm going to say something.
This is a real, real opinion that everybody's going to hate me for.
I think I've said this before on stream. Zelda games, although I respect everything they've done
for the industry, I respect it as a series. I understand why people love it. They don't do it
for me. Zelda games don't do it for me. That's it. Of course I know everything. It's an incredible,
incredible series. It just doesn't really do it for me. That's it.
That's it. Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong. I've played through all of Ocarina of Time
and it is fantastic. It's very, very good, but I'm just not into them. I'm just not into
Zelda games. I'm just not into them. I'm sorry. I know. I'm sorry, but I'm going to be truthful
with you guys. I'm not going to lie to you. Now, that wasn't a wink to tell you. Just kidding.
This is a joke that I actually do love the whole series and I played all the time. That's a wink
because somebody paid 75,000 channel points. Breath of the Wild, that'll change your mind. Yes,
now Breath of the Wild is a different story, I think. I probably would really, really like that
game. Something fell. Look, it's the chibi-robo-chibi manual. All right, well, what is it?
Breath of the Wild sucks, in my opinion. Everything I've seen of it, it seems more my jam.
It seems more my style. We'll probably end up playing that at some point. I'm certain
I would probably really love it. I've already stored this in my memory banks, but I think
you should read it. Okay, let's read it. Chibi manual. Thank you for purchasing chibi-robo,
a member of the Citrus Soft Robotics family. We appreciate your support. Chapter one book.
All right, well, this is just the game manual. Welcome to the family. Welcome to the family,
can I get on his hand? All right, get on it. You're missing Laura. No, I want to get back in the
kitchen. All right, back to the kitchen. Oh, let's log in after the kitchen. I've still got to get
up there too. Put his hand in water. You've recharged 15 times. Are you going to save?
What is that saying? I'm doing two? I'm overcharging? Ribbit robot squad. All right,
now I'm going to go into. All right, let's clean up this shit because look at this dog
shit all over the place. Lord mega law, Lord mega law. You only have 50 charging cycles left.
All right, now is the dog sleeping in here? Oh, where's the dog? Clearly no dog in there.
Yeah. Well, wait a minute. What a fucking mess. It's a sound. I'm busy cleaning.
This is just easy happy points. It's like 10, 20 happy points. There's a little cleaning bot.
All right, now you're the blaster. Does this actually work? Was I being lied to?
Sorry, I was a lie. Chibi robot, please. Jesus Christ. What is this? Frog? What's a frog bus?
Okay. Nice. Yeah. All right. That's a good image. It's the bus story. Yeah.
Um, I will. Wait, what's this? Why is it all me? And by the way, the frog was a lot further away,
at least 200 feet away from the bus stop. All right, I need a battery pack charging station,
which is over here. And then I'm going back up. I'm going up to the top. This world is a
journalist world. Awesome. The guy was going so crazy. He was doing so many movements.
I need to go explore over here in the kitchen. Oh, look it. She's on the counter.
I gotta go visit. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Quest, quest, quest. Give me a mission. Give me something
to do. Hello. What do you got? Just thinking about being near Drake makes me nervous. That's why
there's no way I can confess. After all, I'm just a woman who gets used as a dog's plaything. I'm
nothing. Jesus. Drake? Oh my, you're here to see me, you little old bee. Wait a second.
You're much smaller than Drake. Is that you, Chibi Robo? Uh oh. Uh, no. Uh, do I know? Yes.
What should I say? Busted. No, it's not me. It's, it's Drake. No, it's not. No, it's me,
Drake. You can't fool me. Drake is much too manly to be so small. Don't startle me like that.
All right, let's say yes. Drake? Oh my, you're here to see me? You're much smaller than Drake.
Is that you, Chibi Robo? Yeah, it's me. Whatever. I want to go this way because there's probably
something else I can do over here. There's coins. There's fish over here too. Can I feed the fish?
What can I do? You want to give something to the fish? Cookie crumbs. Cookies? Let's give
cookies. Cookie crumbs? You got 16 happy points. Wow. And they paid me 16 bucks.
Are there any more cookies? Would I like a twig? Should I put a twig in here? I mean,
maybe a little more environment stuff. No, they can't eat that. All right, well, I'm not gonna
give them trash. What does this do? Okay, let's keep going. There's more. There's a bug over here.
Let's charge up. Fish love trash. Um, I, no, nothing else.
Am I gonna save? No, no need. Is it a jar of honey? Oh, okay, there's another demon door over there.
What is, what about this? Pick up the honey. Pick up the jar.
This is coins. Ooh, that's a demon door. All right, hold on. Let me, I gotta get up here.
I can't climb that. Oh, but I can't climb this can of beans or whatever this is. No way.
I know the sound. Shit, I can't get up there. I have to go up this way. Um, hold on. Let me see.
If I go up here, I can. Okay, wait, there's a spoon up there. There's a spoon. All right,
I'm gonna go this way. Wait, wait, what? Can I go down here? Can I get back up?
Should I go in the drain? What the fuck? I, I've got, I'm going to unclog the drain.
This is crazy. Chibi, you just earned a cleaning bonus. Your happy point bonus is
15. This game would make a really good base for a counter-strike map.
Any more trash? Dirt over here. More over here. Let's keep going.
Trash is down here. Look at this. Disgusting over here.
It's all this junk. Okay, gonna fly for us. What's that? There's a rat!
Uh, shoot him. I'm almost out of battery. I gotta go back up. All right, I'm almost out of battery.
Look at how much money's down here. I gotta go. I gotta go. The audio is fucked up. I think this
is the game. It's not happening anywhere else. I think that doesn't happen up here.
Yeah, that's only happening in certain places. Uh, okay. Um, I need, where's that, where's that
battery? Like right here? Right there. I'm dead. I'm right here. Lower the game audio in the settings.
I don't, I don't think this, I can't even do that. Lower the game difficulty.
Should I go back down? All right, I'm gonna charge. I'm gonna charge and then go back down
into the rat cave. You're gonna hear some crackling, but it's all right. In the emulator settings.
This is not on an emulator. All right, let me go back down. I want to fight the rat.
Technically, the Wii plays GameCube games by emulating them. Okay, fine. Okay. Sure.
It's, it's emulated. All right. That's not even, that's not even true because the Wii is just a
GameCube. We already went up with these yesterday. The Wii is a GameCube. All right. Don't clean.
Don't clean. Nope. I'm compulsively cleaning. I want to kill that run. All right. So the plan is
get those coins. If I see a rat, shoot it with blaster. Any rats down here? No rat, right?
I want those coins. Can I knock this down? All right. There's a rat in there. All right. This is
blocked. All right. Blaster. Let's shoot him. Um, wait. What's this? Um, can I jump? It's to hide.
Is there any way I can climb up or anything? I can't climb up like this.
Shit. How do I get up there? I can get up there. Try to push the thing over with the blaster.
It probably is like a, I'm going to assume there's a spring. Yeah. No. It's probably a spring.
Let's get out of here. We'll come back here later. There's a lot of money over there too.
Yeah. We'll come back here later. Dragged you down by the cord. Oh fuck. I'm getting low.
I'm getting low. I'm getting low. I'm getting low. Oh no. Oh no. Is it?
Is it three? We're good. All right. That's cool to know.
Remember the drain because I got to remember the drain. I'm going back down there. When I get this
guys, you said this is like Zelda. No, this is like a Metroidvania. I'd say that's more
like a, well actually Zelda is like a Metroidvania kind of. Yeah. You're right. Fuck.
You get an item to come back and do something else later. Yeah.
And it is like a Metroidvania. Oh wait. This is the dog house.
Shit. These are the dog tags, right?
TV robo. The free rangers were wearing the same kind of things around their necks.
Safe passage now, right? All right. Somebody said to do that. It doesn't work.
Five happy points. All right. Nice. So now I can go back to the, we'll go back to the foyer.
I might not have enough daytime for this. Again, fully recharged. Are you going to save the game?
No. What am I playing this on? I'm playing this on a Wii. I have, that's going to keep happening.
I think I have a Wii which is plugged in HD and I'm using the original GameCube game chibi robo
and that is capturing through a capture card, which is being shown to you on the screen right
now. Show the disc. I did yesterday. What's with this? Like I need to prove I did this yesterday.
I did this exact thing yesterday. I'm here. Where are those demon doors? I have enough time to just
fuck around out here. Let's go outside. I have plenty of battery. Let's go. Remember, you can't
afford chibi robo. It's just like, what does that even mean? Yeah. What are you talking about?
You can't even, you can't afford chibi robo. Oh, I got to throw my trash away. It's a dead frog.
Oh no. Oh no. Ribbit, ribbit, wheeze. I need frog medicine. She's all dehydrated and shriveled.
Hasn't rained lately and it looks like she's really weak. This is so distressing. We have to
get her some water. Mug into the sink with water. Is there a hose out here? Stop cleaning. She's
dead. I need, I don't know where to get water. Oh, I saved an ant. Wait, there's water right here.
How do I open this? That's like a water symbol, right? Crown pound? The tap in the kitchen?
Or is there a hose? Oh no, I think it's just a weird symbol. Oh, is there a hose out here?
I got a decent amount of money.
Is there a hose out here? You'd think there might be. I mean, can I get up this? Climb a tree?
Hose. Water. Some kind of water hose. Over here? What can I do with, lay on this?
What is that? Uh, it doesn't do anything. Well, we'll see you tomorrow, frog. Dead. The frog's
gonna be fine. Morning. Suggest your happy point. Your chibi ranking has gone from. That's a lot,
actually. 93 more happy points. Hooray. If you see a sunshine sticker, I suggest you pop it with your
chibi blaster. Try using your chibi vision as a scope. I know that already. Would you like to
save? Yes, I would. I also want to try this. I want to try this. Give me one second while I do this.
Let me see if I can. I think it's just the way that it's being fed through. Ladies and
gentlemen, I just fixed it. It's been fixed. I just fixed it. You should not hear any more
cracking or popping ever again. It's been fixed. Thank you for the applause. I hope I did fix it.
Let's see if I can prove it. He said that last time, too. No, no, this actually should work.
Let's see. Because through my capture device, I could see it peaking when I just pulled it up.
So it should no longer be peaking on my capture device, which means I'm going to
artificially inflate the sound like this. So I've artificially inflated the sound.
I've dropped the actual input. We'll find out. You tell me if you still hear it. All right.
Let's put the dog tags on. Do I just own them? I think I just own them. Crackling
sound made it more authentic. Let's go to the fort. I now have a dog tag.
I would clean this up, but I mean, I can't leave a mess.
I told you this and you wonder why I can't play Luigi's Mansion 3.
Because it sucks? No, because I suck up everything. I suck up everything. It's bad.
I have dog tags. Unauthorized intruder. Don't let him pass. Take him out. What? Keep your rubble.
This isn't good. Yes. It's gonna be really hard to get over there. These rangers mean business.
The only way to get through this is to find something you can use to cover yourself. Well, I can.
Haha. Haha. All right. Where am I going? Where does it want me to go? In the basement? Does this
thing have infinite health? Is it gonna break? How do I get to the basement? Over here? Son of a
battle tank. Well, I guess he didn't look like an enemy. Come to think of it, he may be an ally.
But still, my men were just pitiful.
TV robo. I can't believe my electronic eyes. That was truly amazing. You ran through those
fearsome free ranges without getting shot. They really are superb. Of course, I was able to fly
right over them. Uh oh. Larry David just said something potentially controversial.
That strange sound seems to have come from here.
Between you and me, I'm a little scared, but I think we'd better go investigate.
Okay. Outlets in the basement? Staircase. Oh man. Easy. Easy. All right. Push it off to get the
the goods inside. Oops. Can I get back up? Five happy points. Nice. Okay. Wait, what? Is there
something up here? I gotta go to a wastebasket. I probably have a lot of stuff here. I haven't
done it in a while. All right. Cool. Wow. Look at all this trash. It's so much of it.
Empty bottle. Broken bottle. All right. There's gotta be an outlet down here. Everybody has
outlets in the basement. How the fuck does your laundry machine knock? You know what I'm saying?
Where is it? Yeah. There's an outlet right across the way. All right. We're good. Where is it? Just
so I can make sure I know where it is. All right. Clean this up. The tough mess. Do I appear at the
toothbrush at any time? All right. Mess contained. Any more? Yeah. Oil over here. Nice. All right.
Wait. I know. I know. I'll be fine. There's a little bit more oil over here. Cleaning bonus.
Whoa. That was loud and crackling. Well, I think it's just the way that the Wii plays the GameCube
game. I mean, this is not like there's anything weird going on here. Good emulator. I need to
update the emulator. There's no updating emulator. I mean, I thought it was fixed. I looked over at
my gacha software and it was blowing out into the red. I guess not. I can power this person.
Hold on. I gotta clean this shit up. I think it might be the memory card.
Can I power him on? It's probably like a boss fight. I'm not doing this yet.
How were the tacos last night? They were fucking incredible. All right. Well, let's blast this.
I had a range.
Really?
Fully charged. This is a half-life puzzle. All right. Let's turn this guy on and hopefully not
blow out everybody's speakers with the loud crackling noises that the original GameCube
disc in the original Wii does. That's part of the game. Chibi-Robo. Are you all right?
I think so. Stop fooling around. Come on. This place gives me the creeps.
Hurry and get out of here. Oh, your eyes.
He fried his circuit. No. Chibi-Robo.
Don't die. No. What is going on? Am I going through like robot? Is this me and my family?
Wait, I've downloaded all his memories. This guy's huge. Emulator virus. But then they powered him
down because he ran out of battery. What's he doing? Is he... was he catching? When he threw a frisbee at
him too hard? Wait, he got beamed up? $100,000 to fix? Too much money to fix. Too expensive. That's
so sad. We can make that money. That's the whole game. Too much electric bill. Chibi-Robo. You died.
Huh? Ah, phone call for Telly. Gotta go. Wait, he's gonna dip out like that, Telly? They just
gave birth. I can't believe he can move after all this time. I wonder what this might be.
More importantly, Chibi-Robo. We would just get... Can you cry into the mug
and dump it in the frog's mouth? We were just getting used to this house and now you die and
leave me all alone. Alone. Alone. No, alone. This took a really sad turn. I was just cleaning
stuff with a toothbrush. I'm fine, see? Oh, you're alive. I'm so glad, Chibi-Robo. I thought you'd
kick the bucket. I suppose I shouldn't have worried. I was gonna fix you no matter what, even if I had
to use my own parts. What a true friend. So tell me, did you dream? Yes. You didn't dream, right? I
just said I did. It's quite possible that you downloaded data from Giga-Robo's memory banks.
All this excitement is really talking me out. See you later, Chibi-Robo. This is Giga-Robo and
Chibi-Robo. Giga. Let's pick up this thing. Giga battery. Giga-Robo, wow, that's a...
What is it? If you plan to take that battery, I'd thank you to charge it up and bring it back in
one piece. And yet, that's not what you want, is it? You colossal matey. It's Gino. It's fat Gino.
This is where he's been the whole time. This is where he's been. They've kept him in a basement.
Grotto's hair. If only you could speak to me, Giga-Robo. Is that really a Giga-Robo? Is he
d-d-d-dead? Robots don't die, you flying boy. Oh, right. He sure is big. He's a lot taller than
you, Chibi-Robo. One moment. According to my data, he's a very old model. He started a trend known
as Giga-Robo fever a long time ago, but his energy consumption was too high and is popularly plummeted.
Shut your blowhole. You think you're smart, but you know nothing about him. I'm so sorry.
Anyway, thank you very much. If you'll excuse me.
Furl your sails, matey. You can't go anywhere yet.
Jerma has an opportunity to do an Irish pirate guy. He's gonna build this all stream.
You come blowin' in here like a summer, squall, and leave without introducing yourselves.
I'm sorry. Uh, my name is Telly, and that over there is Chibi-Robo. Don't mind him. He doesn't
talk much. And who might you be? It's about time you asked. My name's Captain Catview.
I'm the scourge of the seven seas, the overlord of the oceans blue, the king of all pirates,
Captain Plankbeard. You're a pirate? Hey, or at least I used to be. Now I'm
nothing more than a shipless landlubber. Oh, how did you lose your ship? That tail's as long as
the sea be deep, and as sad as a tailless mermaid. But me throat's as parched as me soul,
so I'll be safe in this story. But I mean, yeah, I love the taste of water. Oh, give me that.
What say ye? Will ye return some day and listen to me sad tale of woe? What a boring shitty pirate
character. I love the taste of water. Oh, I'm just so... Look at me. I've got me ship in...
Oh, I love water. Hydrate, kids. There's supposed to be rum in there or something.
There's supposed to be something in there with like three Xs on it. I promise.
Never make a promise you can't keep. That's the pirate's code.
Bugleberry voice. You do well to remember me words, you evergrown piece of plankton.
I won't forget them. Even if I die, I'll come back and remember them.
What did I tell ye? Robots don't die, and ye don't get a scurvy neither.
You're right. That gigabatter is no good by its lonesome.
You need to search the house and find the giga charger.
That was scary. Anyways, let's go back. Need to plug it in to a Tesla battery charger.
All right. Give me that water, though. He loves water. Give me that water. I want your water.
Nice. The gigabatter alone will do you no good. Take the giga charger with ye as well.
I, when the battery's full, juice bring it back here. Ah, yes. Okay. I can't get the water.
He loves water. I need water. All right. Can I do this now? Am I allowed to do this, yo?
Will we get coaxed? Are we still live? What are you talking about? I'm live.
I haven't dropped any frames. What are you talking about? Mini coax? I haven't dropped any frames.
I have zero dropped frames. Maybe it's a twitch problem. I don't know.
Looks like it's about to snap. I've tried this before. Come on. Let me get it.
Yeah.
Find you where you aimed that thing, laddie. I'd not see anyone hurt by ye careless ways.
Nice. I love it. Okay. Is this a photo? Shoot him. Why would I shoot him?
Boil. Pull. Trash. Get it. Oh, I gotta pull it out? Can I pull it out? Uh, well, we, uh,
I just got 20 community subs just came in right now from Jerma's average dong. Jerma's average
dong. Thanks for the 20 community subs. Gunpowder. Appreciate the 20 fucking subs, dude. Thank you.
Average. I'm not even going to respond to that. That's a lot of subs though. Thanks for the subs.
Jerma's, uh, by the way, it's, it's not average. It's Jerma's average dong. The average is misspelled.
Now let's float over there. So wait, do I have enough power for this, right?
Let's put this coins and shit. Ooh, wait. Okay. Um, all right. We got a, I need a better camera.
I'm going to float into the cage. What the fuck was that? All right. What are you doing, Chibi?
It's a dangerous game you be playing. Yarr. What be this? Aye, I see. You're searching for
Giga robots, Giga charger. Chibi, you be lad. You're a slippery fish to get a handle on.
Ha ha ha. Oh, there's a door up there. All right. I'm running out of, uh, all right, put this away.
So now I can climb that. Give me this. I think I found it. All right. Hold on. Can I, give me first
person? There's a frog ring there. I don't think I can make that though. Giga charger. All right.
But can I float from here to there? I don't think I can fly from here to there. That seems
like a long way. Just climb it. Can I climb it? Climb from the other side. Hold on. Let me just
get down here. Another 10 community subs from Jerma's average dong. I need battery before I do
any of this shit. No, no, no, no. Oh God. Oh God. Uh, thanks for the 10 community subs. 30 actually
from Jerma's average dong. Appreciate that. Five more community subs from Jerma's sucks.
You know, let's, you know, let's give some community subs. Uh, Jerma's dick. Jerma's sucks.
Jerma's, uh, Jerma's big dick. Jerma's average dick. Jerma's sucks. Jerma's sucks too. Jerma
lied about how big his dick was. How many of these do we have? How many? Like there's,
there's a hundred of these. It's so funny. All right. Climb up from here.
Not enough. Can I climb this? There's gotta be a way up there. Let me see. How do I get up there?
I can go from here. How do I get up there? Can I, all right. Can I float from one of these steps
over to there? The sling, this, the, the swing you were on. Can I get it from there? From where you
were? If I think it might be too far. Yeah. There's a bunch of bird shit in here. Hold on.
So from here, you, you saying you think I can make it from here?
I doubt it. Oh, I doubt it. I don't think I can go from here to there.
I climb, I'm going to climb up. Oh, I, I can climb up this fucking thing. Oh man. Nice. All right.
Hold on. I got, um, we'll come, we're going to come back. I need to move this. Oh, this is a way. It's
wasting battery. Jerma the rope. Jerma the rope. I know, I know, I know. Don't worry. I went up.
All right. I'm going to, oh, there's a demon door. What? I can't push this anymore. Why not?
Jerma the rope. Jerma the rope. I want to push this the other. Why can't I push this anymore?
All right. That's not important right now. The demon door is important. Now don't, I'm going to,
that's waste. Watch out for the bird shit. And I'm going to float down. Money, big money. All right.
Now we float. We float from here. Here. Okay. There's another demon door right there. Is there a plug?
All right. I'm going to, there's a plug right underneath me. Look, lit, literally. And I use
that word actually, literally. There's a plug right underneath me. Okay. This way. Get the frog
coin. Float down again. Monkey. I mean, I thought, I didn't think it was going to take that much
power to float down. I thought it went to zero. All right. I'm not done in here. I want to,
I want to get up the rope. I'm going to open that demon door. Same deal. I'm up.
A couple of nails. Frash? Or is this a block? I can probably float around it, but not yet. I want
to get this demon door. Okay. Put it away. Open. I've got two grin. That's a lot of money. I'm
almost out of time, but can I go up here? Is there anything else up here? I guess I can just go back.
And I can, wait, is there enough time to go get the, uh, I don't think there is. It's okay.
We're about to, it's about to turn off anyway. Save the frog. I got to come back here tomorrow.
This is the plan. Come back here tomorrow to get the, get the giga charger. You could have made it
monk ass. I don't think I'm going to save the frog. The frog will be fine. Am I going to save?
Of course I am. Do I have enough time to get it now? Maybe. Let's go chibi robo. The frog will die.
The frog is not going to die. This is a children's game. Game deal. Do I have enough time? Okay.
Float around here. That didn't work. That didn't work. That didn't work. That didn't work. That
didn't work. I thought I could float around it. I will come back tomorrow. Whatever. See you tomorrow.
Let's start the stream. Sorry. The other one. No. Time sure flies when you're making folks happy.
Back to the chibi house. Great work out there. Download.
I'm in top 1000. We're making it to the top 1000. Citrus office into your special. Get a brand new
bonus battery. Ooh, that's a lot. Now let's spend some money. We should do a happiness calculation
every stream. Top 1000 chibi robo stream. Giga robo who is making that noise.
You might not know it, but Giga robo is the brainchild of legendary engineer Dr. Joy
Ebisu of Citrusoft. He made you too. Even though he designed both you, Giga robo is 10 times
bigger than you are. He's a hundred times heavier. Don't get me started about his battery. Who made
you? He uses a thousand times more energy than you do. There was an energy crisis a few years back
and all at once everyone just stopped using their Giga robos all together. These days you can't even
pay someone to take the poor guy off your hands. Sad to see something like this happen off the side
like so much trash. Poor guy. Enough moping around. We've got work to do. Let's go earn us some happy
points. Every time you talk, my ears pop. How do we get you to stop talking? Just take out the
Giga battery you're carrying with you. That's it. Look at that. It's already bigger than you are,
chibi robo. Pretty heavy. Let's set it over there. Emulator noises. If you want to recharge that
Giga battery, you'll need to find a Giga charger. There's got to be one around here somewhere. I know
where it is. You and I both looked at it at the same time. All right, let's get this out. Okay.
Online shop. Charge chip. Chibi battery. Range chip. Hot rod. Space scrambler. There's a charge
chip. Enables the chibi blaster to fire a charged shot. Pretty good. Chibi battery. Chibi robo spare
battery. Yup. Range chip. Enables the chibi blaster to fire long distances. Nectar flower seed. A
cute nectar flower will grow from this seed. Charge shot. All right, I'll get it. I still don't have
enough money for any of this. Thank you for your visit. Charge chip. Chibi battery. Whoa. Chibi
drugs. You've upgraded. Let's go. Let's save it. Back to the downstairs. I want to get that charger.
Put the trash away. Yup. Clean up the confetti. Can I? I don't think I can. Oh, I can. Why are
you throwing trash everywhere? Is this trash? Wow. This is where your utility bots come from.
They're your backup buddies, your support bots. If you have scrap, we can make some utility bots
with the chibi PC. Think there's any scrap in this place? Okay, so that's where I put the scrap. All
right, let's go. Save frog, you monster. I'm on it. Soon. I need a waste basket. Okay, what do you
guys say? You guys say trash barrel, waste basket, trash can. What do you guys say? I say trash can.
Trash can. Or just the trash. Throw it in the trash. Speaking of which. Here we go. Two bottles.
Ooh, look at all that. More broken glass. That's a lot. You got a total of 86 happy points. Holy
shit. Chibi Robo doesn't recycle. Is that demon door? No, let's get that demon door open.
I bet Chibi throws his car batteries in the ocean.
Let's get a, let's plug in. It's illegal and free. Throw batteries in the ocean. You are
fucking crazy. What's wrong with you? No, I didn't even say the damn thing. Save it. Hey.
Baste. Shut up. Oh, baste. Throw your batteries in the ocean. Two hours and 40 minutes. What? Time
flies when you're cleaning up dirt. F***ing pollutants. Ooh, I still like, I still like,
I like can like get up there. I think, I think it was like a, it should be like a ladder. I can
like probably like get on or something. I don't know. Or like go from here. All right, back to
the basement. How is that a tuber? Me saying like a bunch of times is a tuber? People do that? E3
presenter? Uh oh. Crying ribbit girl on stairs. Demon door. Tears on the battlefield? Hi, it's me.
I thought, I thought this was mom. I thought this was mom's foot like going up to, I thought it was
mom standing here. Mom's like an elephant, apparently. Always charge. Always. I'm not going
to save. There are two demon doors. One here and then one under there. Elephant mom. I mean,
whatever. Manka A. What's Manka A? Oh, I didn't get one. Turn it back on. Let me back in. I missed
one. It's the first Manka. What are you talking about? We've made it all the way to Manka S.
He's got that, anything to say? Private Frisco on duty, sir. We can't train when the family is around.
I'm anything in, in direct reach. Not really. Uh, plug in. What is Manka S? Frog face going
fuck. The soldiers remind me of you because you look like an egg. Not even, not even close.
Not even, not even close. I mean, I'm talking not even 1% close. I couldn't be more incorrect.
Well, we're just talking facts here. All right, there's a photo. Free ranger's photo.
Um, I not get up here? Shit, I need like a springboard. There's definitely going to be a
springboard. There has to be. All right, let's go see what's going on. What's the matter? Pick me up.
Ribbit. Hello, bit. Jenny, what are you doing up? Go back to your room and go to sleep. Uh, Ribbo.
Night, Ribbit. Gibby Robo. What are you doing? Uh-huh. I see you're trying to reach the second
floor. But these stairs are a problem, aren't they? There's nothing here that you can use as a ladder.
Well, there are ways, but you'll need some special equipment. I'll look into it for you.
Goodbye. Do not leaving. You're just flying behind me. I know you're always there. It freaks me out.
Okay, back to the basement. Back to the basement. I want that, uh, that charger. He's the cameraman.
Yeah, it's like, uh, it's like Lucky 2. Ooh, wait, coins. How did I not get that? Nice. I want to push
this off. Free happy points. Take it. I have to pee. Um, we can take a bathroom break here. Just a
moment. Okay, now I'm ready to get the supercharger. Pee into your, what, pee into my streamer diaper?
You start advertising. Like, Nvidia starts making diapers for gamers. They're all branded. They're
black and green and shit. Play your foolish chatter. You're a cheatin' lion demon crab.
Cheating, how rude. You fail because your soul has not been properly cleansed. Who do you take
me for a brainless piece of kelp? I know you decide whether your eye opens or closes, ye filthy
bilge rat. That is untrue. A person with a pure soul would be able to see this clearly.
Me soul's as clean as the waters of shanty Pete's blessed harbor. Yar, one more time, ye scurvy scum.
There's no way the king of pirates is losing to some half-baked sea cucumber. Ooh, gambling
is the game and there's a casino here and yep, yep, yep, yep, yep. Get on with it, you scallywag.
How frightening. Very well, I shall begin. Everything is nothing. Reach out with your soul,
feel, let it flow to my right eye. Will it open or will it remain closed? What do you feel? Will
it open? Yar, last time it was your portside peeper and the time before that starboard.
Yar, you shall open the eye, says I. Are you certain? Wait, he can just open it whenever he
wants. What certain as the tide do ebb and flow? It'll open, I tell you. You're with me, ain't you?
Yes, of course you are. Are you certain? Yar, me pirate's word is as good as me gold.
Very well. It opened. Yar, it opened, I tell you. Put it to your left eye.
Unfortunate. Don't play dumb, you miserable lifeboat leech. You're nothing but a liar and a thief.
There was a wink on screen already. Great pico, great cheeto is more like it. I'll have you
clapped in irons and kneel, keel-hauled. You're lucky I'm without me ship, you great blinkin'
sea slug. I've had me fill of you. Is there actually a wink? Alright, well, my turn. Another
sucker. I mean, oh, hear me, your soul is unclean. Will you cleanse your soul? Sure. Your desire to
achieve enlightenment is quite admirable. Moolah corrupts the soul. If you use your moolah, then
your soul is gradually purified. Now then, allow me to take your moolah as ablution for your dirty
soul. Alright, ten dollars. Let the cleansing begin. By repeating this process, your moolah
will be purified and returned to you in time. This is the one true way to abandon worldly desires
and become one with a higher plane. You have 1,628. How much would you like to purify? 100 bucks.
Let us begin the process of cleansing your moolah and your soul. Everything is nothing.
Entrapment is release. Abandonment is friendship. It worked. The cosmos embraces you with love.
Let your doubts and fears melt away. Doubt corrupts the soul. Release, release your moolah.
We return to a new beginning. Do not let your lack of experience make you nervous.
If you are nervous, then I too am nervous. Let us begin. Oh wanderer, preach with your soul.
Feel with your soul. Let your soul flow to my right eye. Will it open or will it remain shut?
One whose soul is clean will be able to see the answer with certainty. Well, will my eye open?
Okay, what if I say no and then shoot him in the eye? It'll have to be closed. No, it's not going
to open. You believe it will remain closed. Yes, I'm ready. Please do not be staring at me so much.
You will disrupt the cosmic balance. And now, closed. Closed! It's closed! Closed! You are
correct. Oh wait, those are the classic scam. Classic scam. You win one or two times in a row
and then the scam starts. And then you're like, holy shit, I just won 10, I won 100 bucks. I can
do that again and you do 500. And then the scam starts. And the women alike will rejoice in the
presence of your soul. You have gained 200 dollars. I should have went all in. Your noble intentions
and trusting soul have birthed a miracle. I must spread word of this miracle. I must share this
joy with others. Will you continue to cleanse? Nope. I'm out. See you later. Oh my, this is not
part of the plan. You're gonna stop? How unfortunate. Your mula and soul have been cleansed and now
are returned to you. Please come again. Whenever you are, close your eyes, please think of me.
See ya. Thanks for the 100 bucks. I am gonna save and I'm also gonna pee.
Trying to scam a Vegas man. Good luck. All right, I'll be right back. It's gonna be,
you can listen to this music in the meantime.
We love the music. It is pretty good. It's pretty good. It's got a nice little ring to it.
All right, let's go. All right, I'm, something's wrong with me. I thought that was a doorbell.
I thought that somebody rang the doorbell. That was like a perfect dodo. Okay, whatever. All right,
what was I doing? Oh yeah, getting the, the, I was getting the, the giga charger. Okay, up over.
Let's go chibi. I have a question. Why is nobody making me apologize for saying the word chibi?
You guys are okay with that one? You're okay with that one? That's fine. Okay.
Do I just climb the rope? I know. I can't see. I can't see. He's not kawaii robo.
Now I have to apologize. Now I have to apologize. I'm sorry. Now that crossed the line. Let's go over
here. And then get the giga charger. What? Wait, this box is everywhere. Can I not push these off?
How do I get this off? I can't push you off. I can push these ones off. Shit. All right. Um,
hold on. Not too much to do. Okay. I'm just going to get the charger.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Just push it. I can't get them. What? Don't matter. Charge shot. Oh, okay.
Oh, this can soda. He can. Here it is. Let's see. Give me it.
Giga charger. Yes, that'd be it says I. If you don't play more visceral cleanup detail,
I'm refunding the game. Uh, all right. What does that have to do with me?
Do you truly mean to set giga robo to sale and once more? Yes, I do. Let's turn them back on.
Oh, chibi. You're such. Uh, I got one thing for you to remember. Don't use the outlets in the house
when you fill her up. You'll be drawn so much power. The poor Sandersons will go bankrupt,
causing the family hardship wouldn't sit well with giga robo. Ain't that right?
The giant can opener. This just sounds like a vomit sound effect. Somebody's just puking over
and over again. Your I almost forgot giga robo be missing a leg and no peg leg neither.
If memory serves, Captain Sanderson put it in a clear sort of treasure chest.
Sort of a steel trunk with a handle. Okay. Let's float down. Don't run out of battery.
Your energy is all. Are you going to save? All right, so I gotta go find his leg. Is that it?
I think it did everything I can do down here. I need a leg. My leg. You let an unauthorized
intruder walk straight through. Wait, what? What are you talking about? Didn't they just call me
an ally? You incompetent fools aren't fit for egg salad. You disgraced the free rangers. Don't I have
for after me? I'd say you should all be poached. Private Memphis would have been ashamed of you.
Okay. Private Detroit, wake up. Listen up. I'm gonna beat you eggs into a fearsome fighting omelet
and you'll thank me for it. Yes, sir. All right, soldiers, what are the five free ranger rules?
Free rangers rule number one. When Sarge gives an order, private say sir, yes, sir.
Rule number two. Leave no egg behind. Rule number three. Snooze on patrol, get thrown in the hole.
Rule number four. Show up for roll call or suffer the consequences. Rule number five.
Failure to follow orders is punishable by scrambling. All right, never forget the five rules.
Together we will defeat Tau. Go. Text Frisco, begin roll call. Yes, sir. All right. Um, kitchen.
Should I? Where do I want to go? I can't go up to the second floor. What do I have?
I wonder if I should go over here. Save the frog. Save the frog. Save the frog. Should I just,
I mean, can I talk? Save the frog. I need water. Are you the robot that breached our perimeter?
No. Roger, I've got nothing else to say to you. I think I want to go up. Can I go up?
There's nothing over there. I can't really do anything. Red block. Can I climb something? I
don't think so. Wait, can I climb that? Say yes. Why would I do that? Why would I say yes?
Aren't they looking? They're trying to kill me. Are you the robot that breached the perimeter?
I should. Oh, yes, I am. Then they're gonna start firing at it. He'd be a depth charge and call it
a biscuit. Very impressive. Not bad for a pencil neck robot. Just don't let it go. I'm getting,
I'm getting Tasmanian devil vibes from this guy right now. Don't let it go to your scrap metal
head. You aren't half the robot that giga-robo was. Not even half of the half of the robot or
half of that. Do a Tasmanian devil impression? I don't, you, okay. There is no Tasmanian devil
impression unless you go all fucking in. And I'm, I don't know if I'm prepared to go all in. A non
all in impression of Tasmanian devil is bad. And it's gonna be like, duh, that wasn't, come on man,
that sucked. Oh, that was a little, you gotta go fucking all in. Otherwise it's, I'm not, I don't
think I, I don't know if I'm prepared to go all in right now. It's like, it's fucking a hundred percent
all in. Otherwise it's not gonna, I'm not thinking I can go all in. I tried, I tried. I was close.
I got, I was close. You can't, you have to go. You have to be standing and have your arms in the
air and fucking go nuts. Otherwise it's bad. And I fucked it up because I didn't even end it with the
so it's, I couldn't do it. I'm going fuck, you want to go all in? I'll go all in. I gotta stand up.
Okay, I don't have like any close neighbors.
That's not even, I don't even know what that sound would be. That's like, I'm in,
I just got thrown into like a blender. Like what's going on? Outlast? What do you mean outlast?
Wink? I would never do that on camera. Doing a Tasmanian devil impression on camera. No way.
No way. That would be, the word I'm looking for is embarrassing.
An all in Tasmanian devil is impressive. Otherwise it's embarrassing. And there's a very
fine fucking line. I'm not even sure I hit it. All right, what do I need to do? It was on the mark.
I need water. Wait, I haven't been up there. Green screen request is to do that on, oh my god.
That would be so fucking funny. I already see, I can already see the edits of me spinning around
and doing that and it being in like Looney Tunes cartoons. All right, yeah, put it on,
get it on the recommendation when I finally fucking do that. I'll spin around and shit. Oh,
that'd be so stupid. I can't, can I make it? I need, can I climb up here? I need water. Water.
I can actually, I can do it from here. I should be able to do it from here, right? All the way to
the top. Get on the table. Drink. Okay. Pretty good. All right, so from here I should be able
to do it from here, right? Oh no, I'm almost out of time. Way to go. Call it a day.
Okay.
Remember, that was the poison cup.
Somebody came in here and poisoned it. Oh, 700.
I think I can buy another upgrade too. Now just take out the Giga charger you're carrying with you.
That's it. Look at that. It's already bigger than you are, Achieb. I know, everything's bigger than
me. Let me guess, I have to pay money to fill this?
Okay, let's, let's check it out. What's the, what's the deal? What does it take?
Looks like the Giga battery doesn't have any energy stored up at all.
Gonna take a whole lot of juice to charge that battery.
I can't charge it from the outlets in the house. That would break the family's bank.
Well, I, I'm getting paid from the family. So the more work, if I do extra work and get paid more
money, it is their money. If I want to charge it. Um, sure. Thousand kilowatts equals a thousand
dollars. How many kilowatts will you charge? Thousand. Well, that's not very much. More,
Chibi-Robo, more. I'm gonna get a nectar flower seed. Okay, I have, where do I plant the flowers?
More, Chibi-Robo, more. Sorry about that, my bad. Don't be sorry. Just don't do it anymore.
All right. We need water for the frog outside. Back to the kitchen. I talked to the little girl
again. Let's talk to the girl. Anything else for us to do with the girl? Oh, she's drawing a picture
of me. Ribbit, gimme ribbit. Gimme, gimme what? Oh, gimme. Gimmie the little girl. I got no water.
Oh, gimme. Give the little girl a gunpowder. Frog ring? You want this? Thanks, Ribbit.
Sixty-six happy points. Holy shit. Do it again? Eight more, Ribbit. Okay, here. Let's, oh no,
I'll give you another present. She's demanding them. Thank you. Eight more. All right. Uh,
we need to go to the kitchen. Oh, did I give both? Maybe I gave both.
We haven't even tested if this has synced up or not. It's been like three and a half hours.
We need to do that. Ready? Bum, bum, bum, bum. Are we good? Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
All right, good. Bosh up, bosh up. Crazy into, crazy into you. Now you guys are making me do it.
Chibi-Robo already? One day shipped memory card? Hey, when I tell you I'm gonna make something
happen, I'm gonna make it happen. Bum. Hey, hey, hey. Hey, bum. Say, Chibo, you saw Jenny, right?
Yes, I did. Don't you think she looks weird? I mean, she thinks she's a frog.
Uh, she's just a kid having fun. No, she just, she just, she's just a frog. She's a kid. She's
like two. One day she just started saying Ribbit and nothing else. I don't know what happened.
I know, I live with freaks. Holy shit, mom. Would you like to chat with me for a bit? Yeah, sure.
Oh, you're well made. Now that the water is boiling, let's have tea.
Since you're so small, you can sit over here. Okay. B-movie? That's what I was thinking too.
Oh, do you see my husband sleeping on the sofa? Lazy, no good, so-and-so.
Mm, that's right. Sure. But you think I'm too harsh? It was his fault. He bought you without
even asking me. He's between jobs right now, and yet he spends moolah like crazy. He's a slacker
and a bum. Uh, I mean, we're having tea. We're like-you're venting. Should I-is this like a
no? Yeah, yeah. Or is this like a no, no? No, he's just, he's just between jobs. Oh, I'm sorry.
It's not fair for me to go off on you like that. You know, tea always tastes better when you have
someone to talk to. Thank you, Chibo. 13 happy points. That's it? I mean, someone who says
something other than ribbit. Maybe I made it a little too strong. I think this tea is too
bitter. Oh, very nice. You've been cleaning up the house. Thank you, Chibo. I think mom needs to go
on vacation. Oh, my little teacup. Can I drink it? Sugar? Oh, you want sugar? You'll stuff anything
in your head, won't you? You want some sugar? Sugar cube. Oh, you want some? Uh, I'll get that.
Let me get that for you. Oh, cookies! Yes, those are delicious, but they'll make you fat if you eat
too many. Mom, can you stop being the ultimate buzzkill? Oh, that? Yes, those are all bills.
My husband is constantly blowing all our moolah on his stupid toys. People are supposed to grow out
of toys. Sooner or later, at least normal people are. If you put that in the garbage can, it would
be a big help. I bet Jenny would really like that. I know she would, because I actually talk to your
daughter. One of these days, I'm going to sell all his toys at a garage sale or just throw them out.
Can I do anything else? No? Okay, I got everything on the table. You gotta clean up your cookie
crumbs, though. I got this. Don't worry, Mrs. Sanderson. I bet the goldfish will eat it. Yep,
make her tea sweet. Hey, Chibo, did you bring me a sugar cube? Yes, I did. I'm here to serve.
Gunpowder. No, I'm not going to poison her. I want the happy points. I'm trying to save money to
bring back Giga Chad or whatever his name is. How thoughtful of you. You got $36. Spread the
happiness. And his dad still watches space hunter Drake Redcrest. It's like living with an infant.
I mean, he's an adult. Don't you think there's something wrong with him?
I'm not a marriage counselor. Okay, let me answer this truthfully. On one hand,
he's spending all their money on toys. They got bills to pay. It's pretty irresponsible. I mean,
that's like, what the fuck are you doing? On the other hand, probably six months ago, I watched the
entire first season of Spongebob. Just in bed. So this is a tough one for me. Now he's projecting.
Let her vent. All right, vent. Yes. Yes. Come on. What's he doing? He buys all these. You're very
understanding. Our upstairs bedroom is crammed full of that pathetic Drake Redcrest junk.
Say, how do you reach high places when you're such a little guy? I bet that chibi robo manual
that Jenny's dad got would say something about that. Oh, no, it's bitter. I forgot to stir it.
Let's see something to stir with something to stir with. Wow, that's a kid's spoon, isn't it?
I bet you could use that as a shovel. Isn't there a spoon around here somewhere?
I got it. I got this. I got this. Where was it? I got this spoon. Where was it? Spoon. All right,
I got this. It's up there. How do I get up there? I can't. I remember I couldn't climb that.
All right, I'm going to just jump. There's I there's no jump in this game. You can't reach it.
There's no reaching it. You can't reach it yet. There's no you can't reach it. There's no reaching
it. Well, I guess I should get back to work. Well, okay. Back to the grind. I'm going to feed the
goldfish again because mom won't do it. Can I help with the dishes? Can I fill the mug? Yes,
I want to give the fish a crumb, cookie crumb. I'm going to give the fish gunpowder.
Okay, can I fill the mug with water? You're so kind, Chibo. I should have married you instead
of that slob. I just nodded my head. All right, give me water. Mug, water, fill it. Mom, you missed
a dish. Just kidding. It's me. Jenny's dad. Jenny and Taro are such slobs. We have garbage
and stains everywhere. I love it when you help out. It saves me a lot of trouble.
I'll make sure to give Telly your moolah bonus. All right. Jenny's dad. Not even addressing him
by his name. Jenny's dad. No, I won't. Okay, we're good. God, their marriage is over. Jesus.
All right, I need to get up here. What is this? Yeah, those are deadlines from bill collectors.
We're pretty far behind. This is bad. This is bad. All right. Yeah, I'm on mom's side.
I'm on mom's side. Wait, can I plant? Hold on. Don't I have seeds? Can I plant them here?
Oh, I need to shovel. Yeah, okay. What do we got? I need the spoon. Can't get up there from here.
What about this way? I can't. How do I get up there? See, I'm saying like there's no reliable
way. Maybe if I can, I get on the fish tank and climb up on that thing. I can't climb this.
This would be the way that I would say you would do it. Can't float from here. Can I?
Cannot climb these bottles. That seems strange. I feel like I should be able to.
The game cube on the shelf? Is there? Where? There's no game cube. All right, I can't really
do anything. I need water. I can't fill the mug. Can't get from here. Turn around, you fool.
Is there anything else I can do with mom? Mom, help. I fell in the drain. Turn the garbage
disposal on. I don't think that's going to help me. Wait, the water. Tea. Can I get water from the
cup? The tea thing here? I can get water from this, right? Water. Is water in here? No. Oh, cans.
That's it. I can climb this. Chibi, you can't climb this. It's perfect. It's exactly what you
need to do. Oh, crumbs. Get the fish. Climb up on the ladder. That's not a bad idea. Not a bad idea.
Up there. I know you can get up there. I've gone up there before.
Chibi. Oh, it's this side. Can I climb this? Oh, I can. This is where the grease is in the fan.
What are you doing up here? What the hell is he doing up here? Why is this wrong? The families
here. I can't let them see me. Aha. You have tone up me. I simply got have misunderstanding.
Mis...mis...mis...un...parestimated? What? You have mis...misnuparestimated you. Oh,
fuck. That's 33 points. 500 bucks. I am training to achieve enlightenment up here.
That's all. Look at all this junk. I know! Energy, energy! Okay, I'm out. Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay,
oh your battery is low on energy the battery's low on energy you use it when
you run it up power it's gonna happen press z i it doesn't do anything it
worked oh yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes quickly where is it recharge
the game has been successfully saved sick all right i have to leave here so i'm
gonna get out of this and we're gonna go i don't know
I'm not sure what to do. I think I've exhausted all the things I can do right here.
Electrocute mom. Um, how about you relax? Press Z and wait. Press Z and wait. Press Z and wait.
Press Z and wait. Press Z and wait. Press Z and wait. Press Z and wait. Press Z and wait. Press Z
and wait. Why would I do that? Finish cleaning the grease. Why am I doing that? It's gonna take
me back to the... Why am I... Why would I do that? I'm gonna go clean the grease. Press Z and wait.
Why am I gonna do that? Why would I want to go back to the chibi house right now when I can clean
the grease? Press Z and wait. Press Z and wait. Press Z and wait. To clean the grease. Why? One
happy point in one dollar? Grease is lifeblood. He lacks critical information. Oh megalo! I want to
get that grease. Derma, go die in front of mom. All right, fine. I will go die in front of mom
after I clean all the grease from the fence. Just look at how much of it there is. This is
free happy points. Good shit. And done. Look at that. All those points. Wait! Oh, I could have
landed on the mushrooms! Fuck it, we'll do it another time. Okay, I'm gonna go save it and then
I'm going to go die in front of mom. Press Z and wait. Press Z and wait. Press Z and wait.
Press Z and wait. Press Z and wait. Are you gonna shave? Probably not for another few days.
Okay, go! Push the button! Mom doesn't care. Are you all right, Chibi-Robo?
Hang in there. I'll take you to Chibi house now. Oh, Chibi-Robo. Wait, what? Why am I a ghost?
Don't freak me out like that. I got a Halloween costume.
New suit. Top 200. 33 more happy points and I got a new battery. Top 200 streamer. What happens when
I get to number one? Press Z. Chibi-Robo, you can't use Z to pose here. Fine. You get a mixer
contract when you get to top 200. So what's the pose? It's scary? I wonder what that does.
All right, back on track. Fully charged. Back on track. I need 33 more points.
Ow! Okay, where am I going to go? Can I go talk to dad? I feel like I haven't... Okay, I've been
I've been neglecting dad. Like, I need to talk to dad. We got mom's just bit... We got mom's side of
the story. Let's get dad's side of the story. Whoa, it's a ghost! Don't go around scaring people now,
you know, like my wife does. Man, that's pretty cute, Chibi-Robo. That's it. Boomer humor. I'm
gonna have... I think I have enough to upgrade battery. I went on the second. 4, 5, 30. Yeah,
I got enough. Let's go. New battery. Battery, battery, battery. More battery. More battery.
Get to go out. I think Otto needs to go out. He's giving me the take me out look.
How much more battery do I get? And upgrade happy points.
Your Chibi ranking has gone. I'm in the top 100. Bonus battery.
160. Very, very useful. 99.
Okay, I need 472 happy points.
What if I get this scrap metal? No, I'm trying to pick up the trash.
I want the trash. No, trash. Sorry about that, my bad. Yeah, well, I mean, you've messed
enough the whole house. Talk to dad in a normal outfit. Will that work? All right,
hold on. I gotta take Otto out in a second. You wanna go outside? Okay. I'm gonna take a little
break and let Mr. Otto outside. All right, dad, what can you tell me? Something to tell me?
Hope you make it to number one in the Chibi-Robo ranking. Oh, by the way,
did you pick up my garbage? Thanks, Chibi-Robo. You're a pal.
Dad. All right, what can I look at? Is it in the manual?
Is it worth it to buy an automaton? Yes. Utilibots. Chibi-Robo is very eco-conscious,
and so one of its primary functions is to collect scrap from around your house and recycle it.
While you will not see the scrap being recycled in Utilibots, please be sure that they are
constructed in an environmentally friendly manner. Wait, recycled products inside the
Recycled Lotron Chibi House. Should I be putting my trash in there? Platters, warps, bridges.
Studying hard. Got any metal? All right, changing suits. Let's just skip this to get free points.
Read the whole thing. Scrap is different from trash, okay?
Ah, I'm wrong. Skipping lore. We already know this. It's like 20 or 30 free points. Bonus batteries.
Auto has to shit. Now, he's fine. I'll leave. All right, let's go, Auto. You ready? He's like,
yes, I am. He's just rolling around. He's ready to go. All right, I'll be right back. Give me like,
I don't know, three minutes, three, four. I don't know. He might have to poop. Okay, I've returned.
Let's go. Bacon should be banned. The food? I don't know what that means. All right, so
almost time to have the day end. I still can't get up the stairs. How do I get up the stairs?
I think I need to buy something. Oh, wait, I'm gonna give the frog ring. I have a ring for you.
Give me. Yes. Can I get a cookie too? 33 happy points. Seven more. Do you want a cookie?
Ribbit, ribbit? No. All right. Boyer backyard kitchen. What's the current task? I have to
get the frog water. I have to fix their marriage. I need to get the spoon.
Let me talk to dad with the red. What about the Red Crest guy?
Easy. Yeah, that should be easy. Hey, look. Wow. A space hunter Drake Red Crest costume.
Good gravy. That is so cool. I want one. I want one. I want one. I
want one. Oh, let me see you pose. Come on. Let me see. Am I enabling dad to buy an expensive
cosplay outfit? Nine happy points from dad. That's it. It's a shame my wife can't understand just how
cool he is. Okay, maybe he is a bit weird. For a break, chibi robo. He pogged his pants.
That's great work out there. 84. I'm climbing. What's the gunpowder for? I got money. I got
money. What can I buy to help me from a suit? Another battery range chip. What's a hot rod?
A popular car among racers. Perhaps you will race one day. You can buy a car. It's a full
letter grid. I'm saving for the car. Yeah. What's going on? Did you hear that?
I'm scraping my ears. It came from outside. Wink. All right. It's just Mr. Red Crest
stomping around. What do you think that noise was? Frog ring? Blood? Wait a second. What's that?
Is that oil? Why is there oil in here? Investigate. Yep, that's oil. All right. I wonder where it
came from. Huh. From above. It's dripping from. Oh, it's just dripping from dad's fingers.
Uh oh. It's spider bot. Those are the things from the news. The spiders are here. Uh oh.
I know this move. It's the enemy spider circle. Spider roulette. This is going to be bad. Really
bad. Quick. Get the chibi blaster. Did I leave the oven on? Oh, scrap. That's what I think it is.
It's scrap. Yes. Collect enough of that and you can build a utility bot with the recyclatron.
Spiders are good for something after all. They're good for recycling. Tee hee hee.
I have enough to build a ladder. Kind of clean up their fucking mess.
That was brutal. That was pretty cool. All right. Here we go. Let's make the ladder. I have 300.
I missed a spot. Kind of cleaning robot, am I? Let's do it.
Okay. Chibi manual. Something to say about utility bots. Yeah, I know.
Welcome to the chibi pc. Recyclatron. All right. Living room ladder. A ladder that reaches high
places placed near the chibi robot house. Build it. Put your scrap into the recyclatron. Nice.
And what is it? Something came out. Set it out in the living room. I can finally reach high places.
Very cool. Where'd it go? Underneath that big big present sheet. Congratulations on building
the utility bot. Tee hee. I feel like we got a new partner. I'm so happy.
Abnormal activity detected while on patrol. Uh oh. Space hunter drake redcrest. Alert. Alert.
What have we here? Now chibi robot, are you ready? Yes. Everyone, I'd like to introduce you to the
newest member of the family. Ladder guy. Hey, it's me ladder guy. How are you? I'm so happy
to be part of the family. All right, come on. This nifty ladder utility bot will let you do all
sorts of things. Push or pull it in addition to raising it up and down. Isn't that something? It
talks, right? Drake redcrest is confused and angry, but it does not appear to be evil.
In addition to normal, situation peaceful. The patrol must continue.
Well, keep up the good work. Thank you. We can reach the high parts of the house, chibi robot.
I have no mouth and must scream and cannot scream.
I present to you my new song. Are you ready to be amazed? Sure. I, television, will now enthrall you
with the gift of song. This one is called teriyaki blues. I see somebody spent 20 minutes in garage
band as well. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Ha ha. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't cry on the new
equipment. I've heard you've been interrupted by a malfunction of some kind. I'm sorry you couldn't
hear the whole song. Thanks. Anyway, you were a great audience. Okay. What do you got to say?
Well, now that that's out of the way, press eight next to me and I'll lift it up. Press left and
right. I'll move left and right. Right? Come on. We need it. Let's hear it. Start your plug to raise
the ladder. If you want to lower it, tilt down. Change the ladder's direction. Plug yourself into
a different side. You can push or pull freely so drive moving. Okay. Okay. I get you. How far does
this go? Holy shit. This takes a lot of power. We're just gonna just let it go the whole thing.
I'll be back. You're gonna die. Yeah, that was close. Your energy is full. Would you like to save?
No. You're making them bankrupt. Blame dad. I'm doing my best. I'm just gonna climb it.
But still no memory card. Now it's okay though. We've been on it for four and a half hours or so.
It'll be fine. All right. We're going from here to there. Oh, look at that. That's so sad.
All right. Let's do it. I'll go this way. That way. One coin in here. What am I gonna take this from
now? All right. We can go up there. We're going up here. We're getting that frog ring. I love this
game. This is a fun game. Oh, shit. I can. Oh, it's very cozy. Yeah. It's just very nice. It's
very nice. It's not a whole lot of like stress or anything. It's just fun. Who doesn't love
Chibi-Robo? I don't know. I don't know who wouldn't. It seems hard to not like it. All right. Let's move
this this way. No, no. Wait. I'm assuming it has to be on the right. The plug has to be in the side
that you want to move. Wait, am I in the way? How do I move it though? Can I wait? Can I just push it?
You just push it. You do? No, you don't. Oh, you do? Okay. I was freaking out. That's how you tilt it.
It hurts. All right. We're going up. Nintendo hates it, apparently. Yeah. Nintendo did this thing
where they really, really, really, for some reason, want you to really like Toad because
they have all these cool characters and all these interesting franchises, but
like, please like Toad. What's wrong with Toad? You want to go over the things that are wrong with
Toad? I don't know if I want to do this. No, not in the same stream. You just spread this out.
You got to spread these out. I can't tell you that I don't like Zelda and that Toad is dumb in the
same stream. If I do that, I'm going to lose like 50,000 subs. So we have to spread this out over
the course of like 10 months. One controversy per year, Jeremy. One controversy a year. The plug-up
here. Oh, dude. 10 community subs from Desoid. The reverse happened. Hating Toad is not controversial.
I don't hate Toad. I just, I mean, there's other games they could make besides Toad's like
Treasure Tracker. There's like three of them. How many Toad Treasure Tracker games are there?
That game's great. Now imagine. No, hold on. That game's good, right? That game gets a good game.
Wait, what if Toad Treasure Tracker was Chibi-Robo 2? Think about that. Chibi-Robo isn't by Nintendo.
Chibi-Robo 2 exists. Oh, yeah, but it's on the DS, right? It's not the name. Oh, fuck. I'm on
battery. I'm on a set of battery here. We are dangerously low on battery. Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Oh, my God. I think I'm gonna die. There's a plug right here, right?
There's a Japanese-only DS sequel that plays like the original and is a direct story continuation.
Why? Okay, what is with, why don't they think Western audiences like this? I don't get it.
This is, why wouldn't they? Why would it not come out in America and in Europe and stuff?
Because of translations. It's because they lose money on a translation.
Um, is this high enough? I think I have to go down. Can I go any higher?
I don't think I can. No, I'm gonna have to go back down.
It's also localization. American-only. I want gun, burger, and car. What are you talking about?
That's as high as it goes? Come on. All right, let's move it down here because I want to get
up to there, up there. All right. Can I like retract the club? Club, the plug.
Do you guys understand how fucked up my brain is? I just said plug backwards, essentially.
Gulp. The plug. Too high. Too high. Too high. I'm so fucked up, man. Relax. Drink some water.
Oh, man. I'm so fucked up. I don't even know, man. What was the point of coming up here this high?
Hmm. Demon door right there. Ooh, demon door. And another way to go. Ooh, can I climb up this?
Shit. All right. There's nothing up here. Just a plug. Wait. Weed, dude. Weed, weed, weed, weed,
pog, weed, dude. Weed, pog. Can I open this? Ooh, happy point. Okay, so from here, can I do anything
else? I guess I can go down a little. Dude, epicness. Epicness. Epicness. Demon door? Yeah,
I've already gotten it. There's a demon door back here. I have to push this back.
So much to explore. We're going up to the telephone. Sure, you just won the internet.
Whatever. Oh, can I use the phone? Thank you for the gold. You know, I didn't know what the
hell that did or what it meant or what it was until seven or eight months ago. There's a ring
up there. There's a plug up there, too. All right, I'm going to move this back again. We're going to
go here. Can I reach this? Nothing on this side of the phone. Can I climb? I can't climb that. What?
Uh, remember, say three. Three. Who cares? Why don't you stream on Reddit?
Reddit live. Holy crap, two golds. This blew up. I don't, I still don't even get what it means.
So, okay, I want to repeat this so I can make sure I get this right. Stop throwing shit at me.
So, Reddit has a system where you upvote stuff. So, okay, let's say somebody makes a comment
and that comment, people, a lot of people agree with it and they, a hundred people press the
button to go up. Yeah, and that's one of the top kind of comments, top posts, right? So, somebody
can pay money to put a stamp on that post, right? And that just, that's it. It's just somebody
decided to be like, holy shit, I loved what you said so much that I paid 44 cents for it, right?
Or something like 20, a dollar or something, right? Is that what it means? And then they get
some website perks, okay? It's five dollars. All right, so it's five dollars, okay? And then
how long does that last? So, let's say I wrote something on a thread and I got, I got gold.
Somebody was like, holy, well, dude, I don't know who it was, but thanks. How long do I get gold
status for? Wait, the TV shows a month. Can I do something with the TV right now? But it doesn't
do anything. You get paid, you get, it's a, to browse Reddit ad free. Can I put this up to press
the button or something? Well, here we are. Let's go. Let's go. Nothing on TV. What the fuck?
Nothing on fucking TV. What the hell? Well, okay. Go inside the TV. What do I get in the TV? Remember,
you're about to get 10 million views. Already got it. We already got it like a couple hours
ago and it was crazy. I popped a bottle of champagne. It was nuts. I still need to get over
here. Hold on. Turn this around. Can I make the platform just be here so I can? All right. Now
bring it down. There's a hole in that wall over there. Whoa. Burn it up. I can probably blast that
wall. Let's get it closer. All right. Let's get it down here and yeah, that's it. Let's go. Yep.
No, I don't want to go to bed. I don't want to go to bed. I don't want to go to bed. I don't want
to go to bed. So anyways, um, Reddit, they pay Reddit gold to somebody and they get some perks
for the website and they know who, but they don't know who it was. So anyways, Reddit, rank 80.
Get off Reddit and go to bed. That's why they say thanks for the gold, kind stranger. Let's see.
Whoa. Pretty cool. Thank you, kind sir. Thank you for the gift sub, kind stranger. Thank you for
the gift sub, kind stranger. Boom. And brought coin. Thanks for the wink, kind stranger. Yeah,
whatever. Yeah, whatever. All right. Let's get on top of the chair.
And then we're going to go over there. There's a lot of places to go with this.
Real wink. Let me check. Let me verify it. Okay. It was real. My eyes are so red. I don't know why.
I can climb this shit. Clean the trash up here. How come some people get full face cam winks and
other people only get a tiny window of a wink? It's the same thing. See, it's the same thing.
All right. 50 cents. Reddit silver versus Reddit gold. You guys are fucking crazy.
All right. Have I gotten everything in here? All the demon doors and everything.
Pouch behind dad's head. Demon door up there. Next to the clock. We haven't gone over there yet.
What about on the table? I haven't been on the table. How have I not been on the table?
That seems absurd, right? That's absurd. It's a full screen wink for 150 million dollars.
All right, dad. Oh, he's running out of power. Plug into dad's head.
You didn't even give me my wink. You turned the camera on and said,
if you get a wink. Nope. And then end of the stream. I was heartbroken and despondent. I
won't be redeeming a wink again. I want to get the, uh, the thing. I want to go on the table.
Let's make it easy. Omega Lala. I'm sure germ is upset to hear that. Why are you making me some
kind of villain? Why am I a villain? Is this the highest this shit goes? Like, oh, I'm sure germ is
so sad to hear that. Oh, I'm going to turn the CD off and then dad's going to freak out, right?
Just barely. Candy bar wrappers. Cookie box. That's going to freak out. All right,
turn the TV back on. Did he figure out how to pronounce refuse yet? That's how,
that's what that word sounds like to me. This is way too high. Oh wait, he's on top of the TV.
Should I talk to him first? Look up, you fool. I know, but I'm not tall enough to get over there.
I know there's a frog going over there. All right, I'm turning this TV off. All right, dad.
You're going to have to find something else to do. TV's going off. Hey, hold it. Hold it. Whoa.
Space Hunter Drake Red Crest is on. Dad just gave you 19 happy points.
How can I get a three shirt? No, Ribbit. Chibi-ro-bit. That was close. Ribbit. Oh,
do you want one of these? I have one. Ribbit, maybe? Yes. Yay, a bit. 13 happy points. Ribbit,
Gibby. Cookie box. You're encouraging her too much. This isn't Monster Rancher. Six more. Ribbit.
All right, good. Where else do I need here? Up there. Up there, up here. I can't, I don't think
I can reach up there though. There's a frog ring in there. I'm getting it. Can I get it? Mr. Wink?
I just did it. There. Two Winks? I got the one from before too. The one from like 10 minutes
ago. I got it. No, this one on the other hand, I didn't get. Shit. It's just barely not tall enough.
Come on. Wait. All right. I have a plan. My plan is to push that onto here. No, it's not going to
work. Does he not know it's on? Whatever. Do you think I care about the webcam being on? I'm a
streamer. It should be on. He doesn't know. You guys shouldn't have said anything. You would have
got me fucking putting my finger up my nose or like biting my lip and like eating boogers or
something. You guys fucked that up. Big time. I really did not know it was still on and you could
have seen like a booger reading. Wow. You, one opportunity in like seven years. That was it and
you ruined it. You've, you just missed a full booger being swallowed. I can't believe it.
Oh, Chibi Robo. I love it. All right. I'm going to bring, can I bring this thing into other rooms?
Redeemed a German booger. Dude, hog super frog voice. So this can't go up any higher.
For real. All right. Go up. Shit. All right. I think I've done everything I can do with
how tall this is. Maybe not. Wait over there. Jeremy, you missed two boogers.
If I had a booger eating channel point redemption, I wouldn't be able to produce
that many boogers. What are you talking about? I know this dirt over here. I'm trying to get up
there. Oh, okay. All right. You got, okay. You guys are starting to disgust me.
You're starting to disgust me. Nothing in here. I'm just barely not going to be able to make this.
Come on. Yes, I can. No. What? What? Are you kidding me? I can't make this. Really? That's so sad.
I'm done. I'm done with this game. I'm done with this game. Wait, there's a book here. Hey,
it's a photo album. Neat. Do you want to check it out? Yeah. I'm done with this game. You're
having a barbecue. Sniff. I never get tired of looking at photos. Don't I have a photograph?
I'm having a barbecue. Don't I have? I have a picture. Can I put it in there?
I guess I can't put it in. All right. I think that's all I could do with that.
There's not much else I can. I got to do some cleaning. Anything else I can get with this
ladder? Bad streamer. I think I got everything I can get. Maybe up this way? Have I done
anything up there? Let's check. Lady Powas. Wait, is the Powas over here? What's the plug over here?
I'm not giving in. I'm not giving in. I'm not giving into this shit. That's all I can do. I
can't get up there. Not yet. Oh, then we're gonna do some cleaning and I should have enough points
to upgrade again, right? Is Otto a... Otto's doing just fine. He's over here. He's hanging up.
Cleaning time. Like a good robo. Wait, I can go upstairs. I have the ladder. No, I don't.
Cleaned up a total of 135 stains. Hardware cleaning. Happy points.
Oh, happy points. Doing the super frog noise.
Somebody was outside with their muddy shoes. Okay. A bit more over here. I gotta be close. What about
outside? I'm kind of stuck with what I should do next. Let me see. Let me see what's available to
buy. Missed a stain. I'll be fine. Upload those happy points.
55. I'm almost in the top 50. How much do I have? Do I have enough for the car?
Yeah, nice booger image. I saw it. How much is the car? Hot rod. 2740.
I'm almost there. I'm going outside. I feel like I haven't explored outside a whole lot.
Outside is... Why did I say the booger thing? That's on me. That's a mistake. I have to remember.
I have to remember that there's a bunch of people here that are going to say it and repeat it.
And again, it's going to follow me around. Okay. We need something out here.
Fighters! See you next time on Dragon Ball Z. It's find out next time. Fuck. No, now they're
going to know I've never seen one full episode of the show. And all they know... They're going to
know that the only thing I've ever done is I've YouTubeed random scenes from Dragon Ball Super
for no reason. I've watched a bunch of Beerus stuff for no reason. I have no intention to watch
the show. I don't know why I did that. They're going to know this. Backyard. Did you watch JoJo
though? No. Still haven't given the frog any water. This is so sad. It's actually sad.
Why hasn't somebody like picked up the frog? Where's the family? All dad does is watch cartoons
all day. Oh, shit. Frog coin. Wait, this means shoot. This means shoot this... Shoot this. This
dog bone over there. Donald Duck. Can I pick this up? Wait, why can't I pick this up? It's stuck in
the goddamn ground. I need to dig it up. Metroidvania. There's a demon door up here.
There's a spider nest up here. Open the demon door. Remember, you're very likeable and admirable.
What's up? Thank you. The spider's nest. Can I shoot it?
Fuck out of here. Singalata. Sleeping baby birds. Hello? He's in a deep sleep. If he
doesn't move, we can't get to the other side. How do we wake up the bird? Recycle the bird.
I don't think it works like that. There's another demon door here. I gotta be careful though.
I can buy the car. Can I go anywhere else? I can go over there. What's that? Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Where's the plug? Where's the outlet? It's just right here. Where is it? Isn't it right? I thought
it was right here. It's a plug right here. Isn't there? Where is it? There's no outlets outside.
No! I have a battery, right? Okay, my battery. Oh, the battery is consumed. Shit.
Oh my fucking god. I just lost like $600.
I've only died twice in five hours. Come on. You're making a fucking mess. Wait, how much?
For your ladder. Oh, I'm gonna, okay. It's daytime. We're gonna go kill some spiders and make a ladder
of the foyer. Your chibi bank account is chibi low. All right, I need to do.
Fuck, I'm so mad. I have to go kill spiders. I'm just gonna clean. They have to be there. I have
to go up in the backyard during the day. It's okay, Derma. Everything is gonna heal. Time for some
chibi tax evasion. All right, any spiders in the foyer? I need scrap. Maybe you should crash the
chibi housing market. Chibi gamble all your money away. I can't even do anything in here.
I need to get attacked by spiders and then we ran out of time last time. Can I go back to bed?
Would I dress up as chibi for a Halloween special? Talk to the eggs? Wait, I didn't already do that?
How does one dress up as chibi robo? Private Vegas reporting for duty. Uh-huh.
You know that beautiful hunk of hot rods sitting up on the second floor?
Yeah. You got a good eye on you, kid. Uh-huh. I've got a tricked out hot rod. When my tour with the
free rangers ends, I'm gonna be a race car driver. Sounds pretty cool, Vegas. The broomer. All right,
he's gonna waste time until tomorrow so I can attack by spiders outside. I think I'm done with
the game. I'm done with this game. It's like, all right. It's like fun, but yeah, it was like,
all right. Are you gonna stream it again? Um, I don't know. Like maybe. It's like maybe. It's
like possible. It's not like a priority, but like maybe. I don't know. I'm not like, you know what
I mean? Pranked! Pranked! All right, let's go back in here. Can I get to the spoon? I can't
probably until I get the ladder in there. 61. All right, I don't need to go to bed.
I don't want to save. Where's the sleep button? Can I just go to bed? How do I shut off?
All right, chibi robo, smash your head against the wall as hard as you can.
I'll put the put the costume on. That's a costume you can get. Oh, you force the next day with a
costume. Wait, can't I just do this? Just buy the shorter clock. I could do that.
This is probably something else I can do just to pass the time. Oh, let me like clean up some
junk. Let me pick up some Cheetos on this guy's fucking couch. The dog's on here. Can we talk to
the dog? I guess not. Talk to the eggs again. All right, I'll get out there after I get these, uh,
coins. And we get the boots. I kind of wonder what this face looks like. How about some trash?
Put the camera on again. If I laugh, he doesn't know. If I laugh, if I laugh, if I face, he doesn't
know. Doesn't know. Medic, we've got a robo down. Wait a second, you're not hurt at all.
That is one sick joke, soldier. Ah, TV Robo, I knew that was you. You can't scare a grizzled
veteran like me. Wait, TV Robo, I knew that was you. Space Hunter Drake Redcrest. Oh boy,
could you, uh, autograph my, my, uh, oh man, I'm so nervous. Private Frisco on dirty, sir.
Freed Rangers rule one. When the Sarge gives an order, you say, sir. Yes, sir. I'm Tex. Sarge
had the free Rangers photo last, but he lost it. That photo has to be around here somewhere. I have
it. I'm Tex. Sarge had the wifi photo last, but he lost it. I have it.
We took this back when we were first deployed at the Sanderson house.
General Sanderson took this photo. We were a full platoon then. That was before the incident.
We were doing our daily physical training routine. Okay, that's when the enemy attacked. The dog.
Ooh, he's gonna eat him. Memphis. I know what's gotta be done. We have to train harder so that
one day we will win the war against the great beast.
We need to make sure we never lose another Ranger in battle. Thank you,
Cheapie Robo. You helped me remember my true purpose. 20 happy points.
Where are the happiness? Anything else? Slap me with a landmine sandwich.
We're still a man short. You're slacking. Start over again. Initiate roll call. Sound off.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen,
fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen. Everyone is accounted for, sir.
Show up for roll call or the whole army suffers. It looks like everyone's here,
so today's your lucky day. No one suffers. 20 happy points. Good, roll call is officially done.
Go, go, go. We're getting physical training. What do we have to do for physical training?
Have to do this too? I'm Montana. We're working out. I'm Orlando. Private Memphis used to stand
right there. Now the Sarge screams at us every day at roll call. It's all because he's gone.
I'm Cincy. We're working out. I'm Oregon. Sarge still talks about Private Memphis all the time.
I'm Tucson. Free Ranger's rule number five. Failing to follow orders is punishable by
scrambling. I'll rest until the great hairy threat is defeated. All right, fighters. All right,
gentlemen, army, roll out. Let's go. I have enough to build the foyer thing. Thanks for nothing, guys.
I'm gonna do this.
This is the resting. Hey, it looks like you found yourself a nice place to rest.
Oh, you still have work to do. Make hay while the sun shines.
No, I think I'm gonna just take a break. That was nice.
I'm gonna make myself happy. You know, Chibi-Robo is all about spreading happiness. But what about
Chibi-Robo's happiness? Don't we need to be concerned about that too? What about that?
Let's buy the new ladder. He's a robot. He has no feelings.
But what if he still has to? His joints have to rest. His robot joints. Otherwise,
we're gonna overwork him and he's gonna break. There you go. There's your reason.
I gotta be in the top 30. 43. It's time to make the ladder. For your ladder. Let's go.
50 streamer. Oh, man. Seriously. Damn. You're still going with this game. Wow. This is like
one of the most classic video games ever made. This is, this didn't just like come out in the
second new release page on Steam. You know, like not, you know, you don't
guys know what I'm talking about. This won an Oscar. I don't think we have enough time,
but I want to go see it. Let's go to the foyer. Oh, it's, yeah, that's right. Let's go, go, go.
This won five game of the year awards. What's wrong with, uh, Falcon? What are you doing standing
here? Island's Fool. An ill wind blows tonight. Has something happened to Mr. and Mrs. Sanderson?
Break Red Crest also heard Jenny weep large, bitter tears. Pursue sadness. I will continue
my patrol upstairs. An ill wind. All right, let's go. It's got a lot to explore today.
I'll set it up for tomorrow. Go over here. What is that? A stain? Not on my watch.
Let's juice it up. Oh, can I get anything from there? Yeah. Well, I can get the cookies.
Move it back a bit. Was it hitting the, is it hitting the thing?
How's he stuck? He's stuck. I gotta put him down.
All right. Ah, this game's noises are 10 out of 10. They are actually really good. They're very
good. Good morning. I'm fucking doing that. Don't do that anymore. Look what you're doing.
Still 43 Omega Low. Yeah, whatever. No, I want to pick up the trash.
I'm just leaving it. Oh, people were saying that if I'm going to do GameCube,
I should get Cubivore. Now that's a very interesting thing to say. I looked up Cubivore.
It was like, wow, that seems interesting. I think the game is $300. Is it worth,
is it worth $300? It's a $300 game. You could emulate it. Is this on Dolphin? No,
this is on original hardware. But all right, but if it's $300, is that, I mean, these are going to
appreciate in value. If I, if I hold like a, this is Chibi-Robo. This game is worth like a hundred
bucks. In 10 years, this game's going to be worth like 500 bucks. These are assets. All right,
where's, I need to go to the foyer straight ahead. Like is Cubivore going to be a thousand dollars
in 2028? That's Beanie Baby logic. I'm not so sure about that because these people still want to
play these old games on the original hardware in quotes. Only ones in mint condition will be worth
it. Have you seen the condition of this disc? Would you be willing to take a thousand dollars
from someone for this game? I'd be willing to look at who's giving me a telephone call.
Well, I don't, I don't know. What's, if someone's going to pay me a thousand dollars for this game,
would I do it? Yes, absolutely. Why wouldn't I? You mean like right now? Why wouldn't I do that?
All right, we're going to go, uh, where do I want to take this letter? Okay, go up on the sofa. Red
block. My Cubivore still has the $20 sticker on it. Wait, I can't go on the carpet. Uh-oh, I have to
shit. Use it right here. Hold on, I gotta put it up. What if somebody gets the rights to this game
and plans to make a million copies? Well, um, this thing's going up way higher than it did before.
I need an outlet now. So you're saying that somebody's going to buy the rights to Chibi
Robo and then flood the market with Chibi Robo discs. What's happened with Nancy Drew?
Wait, you know, you can sell, yeah. Okay. What's the rights to Chibi Robo? Oh shit, I have to hold on.
Fly, fly, fly. Look at the trash. God, I'm so pissed off. I have the rights. Do you really? Holy shit.
What? No way. That's fucking crazy, dude. Get out of here. Yeah, the person that owns it is here.
That's so fucking sick, man. What was it like working on the game?
All right, now what can I, I can't do anything with this, but the
Millennium Falcon thing and I fly over there. Let's get a good view and go up there.
I wonder if I can make it to the red block. Upstairs time. Pog. Not yet. I'm not really into
the game. Like I'm just going to say it. You know what I mean? Like I should have made that fucking
jump. I think I'm done. Let's go even hot. No, pull back. He's just doing this joke for the third time.
I'm going to move this out of the way. Stop. Maybe he means it this time. No, it's not even stuck on
anything. It's not even stuck on anything. I just saw, I just did it. It's not stuck on anything.
Stop going up. Chibi. Chibi. Pull it. What the fuck is going on here? Why is it just going up?
I did lower it when I lowered it five, six times and it went back up on its own.
Get the fuck over here. Stop going up. Stop going up. It's going, it's going.
And when I let go of the stick, it goes back up. Yeah. Stop it. This is going back up. It better
not be. Grab. More. Of course I'm out of fucking power. It doesn't even read chat. Yes, I do.
I see it. That was just, I was in, I just rewound. How long have I been streaming? Oh,
probably one of the longer ones. Like 13 hours. 12 and a half, 13 hours. All the way past the plants.
That's as high as it can go. Recharge. Streams with lifetime. Five hours and 36 minutes. Well,
I mean, it's going to say that because I disconnected like four or five times. So
flat. I mean, this is probably the stream. I have to disconnect. I mean like four. Three. It's three.
Yeah. Well, we definitely can't get up there. We can get over there. We can get up to the,
all right. Can't move this out of the way. Maybe I, yes I can. Oh, this is so, so addicting. Stop
being so addicting. I have to move the, I gotta move the ladder across the whole thing. Trash.
There's one of these. I can push it over there.
Okay. Break the photo. You fucking monster. I'm not going upstairs yet. I want to get that demon
door. I want to get the demon door across. Speak to the eggs. I will. You're running out of time.
All right. All right. Just wait. I'm not, there's no such thing as running out of time.
I'll come back in the next, tomorrow. It's fine. I'm going to kick your ass.
Oh, are you? Okay. Do you want to do some spy training? Yes, of course I do. Find the spy.
You're free rangers. You're hard-boiled. I'm Detroit. I'm Tex. I'm Frisco. I'm Orlando. I'm
the spy. Hunt down the spy. I know who the spy is. Got you. Two happy points. Holy shit. What?
That wasn't even worth doing. All right. I'm the spy. Oh, I think I might have lost it.
It's one again. One again.
Again.
Oh, you didn't even fucking move. I'm the spy. All right. Let's go again. I'm Detroit.
I'm Tex. I'm the spy. Three. You got me. All right. Just gave you two happy points.
Number three. Let's go. I'm standing in the fucking way. I'm Tex. I'm Frisco.
I'm Orlando and I'm the spy. Two. Two. Four happy points. Number four? I thought he said do it three
times in a row. I fucking lost it. I think it's two. I think it's one. It's three. I wish I was
standing in the way. Three, I think. Let's do the three or one. Yeah, I got this one. Five happy
points. Let's do this again. Ready to sharpen up. Five. Okay. I'm going to need you guys' help for
this one. Four. Four. Got it. How many times did you do this in a row? Seven happy points.
Okay. Two. I think it's four. Four. Four. Four. Four. Wink. Three or four?
Is it three or four? Oh, we have some division here. It's three. It's three. I would have said
four. Is it four? Four. You idiots. Four. I'm gonna say four. I said four originally as well.
Yeah. No! It's all right. I passed it. Sorry, Jerm. We said three. Well,
other wheezes said four. Handrail training. Handrail training. Are you here to try handrail
training? Yes. This is going to teach you how to run fast so you can catch Tao.
Just run on top of the handrail and to the end of the course, then run back.
Free, Rangers, you're hard-boiled. Go, go, go. How's this? This just don't fall. Now run back.
Finish! Handrail training time. 31 seconds. You passed handrail training. So talented.
That's a lot of points though. Jungle training is next.
We're done with training for the day. I thought you wanted to do jungle training.
I'm almost out of time so I might as well clean up the puke.
Need more trash. There's a little bit of trash over here.
No, no, no. I want these. I want the scrap. I want that scrap. I thought an ad was playing.
All right, we're going to come back tomorrow and we're going to go upstairs.
Tomorrow is when we go upstairs. But I'm going to see if I can get in this demon door before
time runs out. How high is it? High enough? Let's hope so. I'll stop streaming yet. Oh no,
I'm talking about like tomorrow in the game. Another demon door up there too. I have enough
for the car now for sure. 29. Just don't die. All right, I think I can get it. I just have to
put it up a little higher. I'm going to run out of time I think. I'm going to say nope.
Better to be safe than dead. That's yes, that's true. Can't go up any higher.
Why not? It could go up so high. You saw how high we could just get this to go. Really?
Doesn't know. What do I not know? Cam's on? Oh, I can't get the other one over here.
Even if I push it down this way. This thing's not big enough.
But can I get to anywhere else? Oh, I can. Quick, get the snack. Get the can.
He is unaware of future events that may transpire, resulting in him having a negative
experience that would be humorous to his viewing audience. Pepe laugh.
Cam's off. I gotta be pretty high. 26. I would love to save. I would also love to see if I can
buy anything. What else you got in here? Kitchen ladder. Yep, yep, yep, buy it. We can finally get
the spoon. We can get the spoon to stir mom's drink. It's a utility bottle. All right, so buy
the car. We're looking for advice. Is morality objective or subjective? Thanks. I don't even
know what that means. That's too much for right now. I don't even, I don't, I don't even know.
Okay, I'm gonna get car. A popular car among racers. Buy. One full letter grade. I'm so excited.
I'm playing chibi-robo right now. I'm not going to question life's moralities. I'm cleaning as a
robot. All right, where's the car? Where's the car? How do I, where do I get it? Oh, all right.
All right, let's go. We're going upstairs. Wait, where's the trash? I want to throw this crap away.
I don't get to give it a full letter grade? That's kind of unfair. All right, we're going upstairs.
Please read this important haha nerd. Time that person up 10 minutes. Because, I mean, you're
gonna, hey, read this extremely important. No, come on. You're drunk. Why is he in the way?
But you are a nerd. Read this haha nerd. You're trying to get my attention with all caps. You're
gonna, I'm giving you 10 minutes. We've got, we've got to start to, we've got to start to quell.
Read this penis. That person 10 minutes too. Guys. All right, I'm going upstairs. People are crying
upstairs. So, I hope you guys are ready. By the way, Frog still has not received any water.
I want to make that clear. Okay, ban that person for 10 minutes. Okay. Ban that person for 5
minutes. I don't want to see them anymore. Yeah, get rid of that person. Oh, I need the thing.
Ban that person permanently. Because that's, oh yeah, I'm not going to look and fucking say
that to me. All right, I just gotta go up and then I can get over there. So, I need to be charged
first. You got him? All right, good. Permanent, right? Good. Thanks a lot. All right, let's go
upstairs. You can't stop me. You can't stop me. I am the stream. He did the funny voice. Hello.
Give him 15,000 upvotes. Wait, can I, can I even get over here? Am I even gonna,
can I even climb up this? This room is begging for upvotes. Please. Please. Wait, there's like
photos over there. Why is this guy gonna fight TF2? It is a TF2 waiting room. You mean TF2 like
purgatory room. You're not going anywhere. I'm gonna try to get it from here. All right,
what's up here? Pick a photo? Oh, look at how happy they are. Demon door. Rain world purgatory.
Rain world. Where's rain world? They got lost in the mill. Anything else over here? All right,
I'm gonna use the railing now. There's a lot of things that are in purgatory, I think, right?
Yeah, you. Imagine if this was purgatory. Imagine if we were in purgatory right now.
Fucked up. What if this is hell? On that railing. I went over it. Fuck. I mean, technically,
you can be in heaven or hell on earth while not being there mortally. Oh. Here we go. And here we
go. Here we go. Well, everything after every sentence I say go, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Right.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Fucking railing. All right, I'm on. I'm car. I'm here. Car. Car. My car. My car.
Open the door. Give me my car. What? It's just a neutral. There's no gas. Sad human detected.
Sad human detected. All right, I'm coming over there with my car. We're gonna work this out.
Well, let me get the money first. Okay, well, let me plug in first. I need to have a full charge
for this. I'm going. I put. You want me to try to help somebody without. What if I run out of battery?
All right, I'm here. What's going on? Oh, hello, chibi. She's talking. You came all the way up here
because you heard Jenny crying, right? And he says thank you. The bear can talk.
Somebody said, oh my god, the bear can talk. Jenny says she's upset because mom and dad aren't
getting along. All right, this is getting heavy. All right, no more comedy. Mom won't let dad
sleep in their bedroom. I want to go into mom's room, but I can't move since I'm a stuffed animal.
All right, I'll get you in there. Just get in my car. What do you mean you did this? I did this?
What do you? This is no, this is like 30 years of trouble with marriage. I didn't do this. What do
you mean? I didn't do anything. They ordered me on Amazon like six days ago. I didn't do anything.
Mom walks the door at night, but she leaves the door open all day. All right, so we're gonna come
back during the day and go into mom's room. How am I gonna reach it? Give me my fucking car.
I can't. I want to just use the fucking car. Why? Why? I just want to drive around.
Come on. I just want to be like Stuart Little for once. Please. Fine. What else is over here?
I think I can get there from here. The demon door. Wait, shoot this. I mean, this is a confirmed
bed in the Metroid Prime mechanics. I gotta come back during the day. I have enough juice
for the demon door here. I don't know. I'm just getting some juice. Hold on. There's too much to
do. I'm going. I go back up there. Just hold on. I can go on. I know I look. I can get on the railing
right here. I just want to get the demon door. You saw what I was doing. I'm stomped up. You're
hurting his spine. Be all right. Energy wasted. We can go faster. Someone just said literally
fucking for IQ. What a fucking idiot. Stupid fucking moron. Relax, dude. And that guy forever.
Actually, I'm going to report him. You can walk off ledges with the chibi copter and float normally.
You don't always have to press to fly because you walk off a ledge to use it.
And then they say it's stupid fucking dumb idiot or IQ fucking moron. What the fuck?
All right, let's go in your room. I'm going in. It's open. The door is open.
Oh, I just picture you go, you tell your neck, you know, you mean, that's what I imagine.
This is what I imagine people were doing there. The door is open. You can go in. Oh, like you just
point your eyes and then you fucking scream three teeth. Oh, everybody. It's okay. I'm going to get
there. Lots of trash over here. Lots of trash in the kids room. Get it quick before time runs out.
Oh my god, there's so much trash. Get it all quick. Time's running out. That doesn't matter.
I can come back tomorrow. By the way, everybody has one of these under their bed,
especially where your head is, where your headboard is. So hard to get under here.
Um, Jenny, what are you keeping under here? Jenny, uh, thank god there was an alien in his chest that
killed him. And I scare you. Yeah, you did actually. I thought we were going to be in trouble.
Oh, you'll be nice. Everybody's got one of these under their bed.
I already have random wrappers, throat lozenges that you just find under here,
which by the way, those are still good. You know how many times I found vitamin C drops under here?
They're probably three years old. They're going to be fine. They have like a 30 year expiration day
and they're in a wrapper. That feels so good. All right. More trash.
True story. Uh, this is a real story. So Kim and I, uh, we did some cleaning and we found,
uh, we found a container under the bed of Ferrero Rochers. It was a sealed container.
It was covered in like dirt and dog hair and shit, but it was sealed in the box and we knew
they were probably like at least three to four months old, but they were still all right. They
were still within expiration. So we were going back and forth about like, is this shit? We can
eat these, right? I mean, they were under the bed and covered in dog hair, but they were sealed in
a container. That's okay. That's a great find. Now don't turn me off. Don't do that. That's not
that gross. That's not that gross. No, I don't, I don't want to turn the stream off. All right.
All right. Okay. All right. We'll see you tomorrow.
As long as it was, it was a sealed box. Yeah, but it was fine.
I'm number 14 in the world. What do you think? Is that a good place to stop for today?
I'm being realistic. Yeah. What? Like six and a half hours.
Let's do the rest tomorrow. I think that's a good place. We've got another probably six,
seven hours. I want to do this over two streams. This is like a 14 to 15 hour game, right? Like 12
to 14 hours. Is it another like full probably six, seven hours of this game? Roughly, roughly.
Okay. This is, this is two hours max. No, that's not 12 to 14 at the rate. Yeah. That's yeah.
Whatever. That's another like seven hours stream tomorrow. Six to eight hours stream tomorrow.
Yeah. Yeah. That when we have to just getting upstairs. I'm going to do it. I think this is
a good place to stop a little bit more. Oh, no, no, we'll stop. We'll stop. We'll stop. We'll stop
right now. Plus this is a good time that people, uh, you know, I started a little early. No, I did.
I started. Wait, let me, let me correct this for your warp. What does that do? Let's do it.
You're not halfway through the game. That's what I'm saying. The game's addictive. Yeah, it is.
I just want to leave enough time for there to be a full stream for this tomorrow.
And then after this, that's a really good question. What we're going to do after this.
There's a lot of stuff that I have back here, but yeah, I'm going to, we'll plug in, we'll save
and we'll, we'll pick it up after this tomorrow. We're still going to hang out for like 20,
30 minutes and do the bits. This is a good place to stop, I think.
So we'll see you tomorrow around 2 p.m. Pacific. See you then or chibi robo part two.
I am actually going to do something. I'm kind of freaking out about the memory card scenario
because I mean, this game's already safe and good. Well, I'm, uh, before I go to bed,
I'm going to turn this on and turn the we often turn it back on and hope that the thing's not
corrupt. You know, that's like, that's for scaring me. I don't know why it is. It shouldn't happen
though, but, uh, we'll end it here. Probably see you guys maybe tomorrow starting around that,
like 1 30 to 2 p.m. Pacific. I just said that, but I'm repeating myself. It's okay.
See you tomorrow. Thanks for watching part two tomorrow. It's corrupted. God leave the we on.
No, I'm sure it'll be fine. Yeah. If this if it's been working this much, it's it would be fine.
Let's go back to earlier today. Take care of everybody. If you leave them. We had 250 from
gnarly earlier and they say, do you really think you can climb the league ladder playing troll
shit like twisted fate jungle? Oh my God. Jeremy, you have to do well with me. I play top. My scion
is clean as fuck, but I also play jacks and gnar. If you want to jungle play around top with someone
like Zach, he's even real league. These league champions. I'll carry you to gold. I feel like
you're just making up names. I don't play league. Don't listen to any person that tells you I play
league. Grandpa played league once and it's one of the worst videos I've ever made. It's still up
and it's still there. You can watch it if you want right now and see. Thanks for the 500 bits.
Is this the first strand type game? Maybe I'm not going to watch it on stream,
delete it on stream. No. Belsix. Thanks for the 500 bits. Belsix. I came home from college this
weekend to visit family and introduced my sister to your streams. My parents saw and they told me
there is something wrong with you. That's telling them. Just you got to say, you got to introduce
me as like a comedian. You know what I mean? Like, oh, there's this comedian. He has this show.
And then they'll be like, oh, okay. I get it. I get it. I see. It's just a show. He's a comedian.
And then that's, he does, everything's fine. I hope you're not introducing me as a doctor or
something. Hey, I watched this doctor on stream. Oh, he's a doctor? Oh, he sounds like a fucking
idiot to me. Always introduce me as an e-clown or as a comedian. Fire 25 shadow. Thanks for the 500
bits. Five dollars. Thanks for the fantastic streams. You brighten up my day. Looking forward
to the rest of the year. The more hilarious content. See? I'm not a doctor. Also, you missed my
wink when Drake Redkiss first appeared. Missing fucking winks. I think that was a lie, but
whatever. Anyways, thank you for the 500 bits. German lied about the frog coin. Thanks to the
five community subs. This, I'm telling you, why can't you even have a name that long?
Why is your name not like striker two or something? I don't know. Why is it Jerma lied about the frog
coin? Why is your name not something just like, they'll get them. Six, seven, eight. Thanks though
for the five community subs. Breanne Ben, thanks for the five dollars and 10 cents. Do you think
Jerma is more compact than chibi robo? Considering I am at least as tall as a fucking chair.
Um, no. Yes, I am. Yes, I am. I mean, yes. Get out of here. Thanks for the five dollars. Hey,
wingman. Thanks for the 500. Five community subs. Thank you, wingman. God damn it. Uh,
Jen or Gen Pendulum, thanks for the 300 bits, is another bit dream. I once dreamed that you
were streaming puppeteering with a Yoda puppet and at one point you forgot his name.
It's pretty funny. Swoosh. Thanks for the 500 bits. Today's my parent's birthday and we both
love your streams. All right. Can you wish Marty a happy birthday from me? It'll make their night.
Happy birthday, Marty. Happy birthday, Marty. Hope you have a good one. Take care. Thanks a lot,
guys. Hope you enjoy it. It is birthday, man. Yeah. We also had 500 bits, five dollars from
Yucatare. They say, thanks for doing my sale of requests yesterday. Congratulations on 10 million
views. An amazing amount for an amazing streamer and content creator. Look at me. Thank you.
PS item filter as in something that makes a custom sound when an item drops in game. Oh, okay.
I get it. That makes sense. It'd be a thing. Uh, Jerma's average dong gave 30 community subs over
the course of the night. So thanks for the 30 subs dong. The username. That's a username that
you have spent money on a lot of money with average misspelled. He's wonderful. Wonderful.
Where's where the fuck is striker too? Stripes beast. Thanks for the 500 bits. Thank you again
for playing this game after watching you cut burn and crush an Asian mother's hand yesterday.
I'm relieved that you are playing a game about family strife. I'm doing a big road trip soon.
I'm heading through Vegas. Any spots a poor man would like. Love you in the community.
Thank you. He called the message one more time.
Message needed to code. You got it. That's where I think you should go.
Best restaurant in Vegas. You're a peanuts adult. Red rock is a bit outside town. It's amazing.
Hiking, walking. That's also true. Red rock Canyon is beautiful. Highly recommend. I have seen it.
Those are Mount Charleston. They have lodges up there, but that's not really going through Vegas.
Mount Charleston is like a ski resort, but it is really nice.
Say hi to my parents. If you see them, they're going to Vegas on Sunday. I will. What are you
doing? Why? I don't, I don't watch links anymore. Half the time it's, it's fucking Rick roll.
Hi, what do you got? What is this? Be careful what you wish for a German. I'm curious. What is this?
I actually really want to know about the music. Hey, what is it around?
Come on. I just want to feel like Stuart little for once. Please, please, please.
I don't, I don't actual size. Okay. What do you make this shit? So all right, let's go.
Hey, there it is. That person said their partner, Marty, not their parents. What?
Today is my parents' birthday. Let's go back and do that one again. That was swoosh swoosh. Today is
my partner's birthday. And we both love your stream. Can you give Marty a happy birthday? Happy
birthday, Marty. Not somebody's parents. You're somebody's partner. I read it wrong. Thank you,
sorry about the mix up. Yeah, I was right. It's like my parents birthday. We both love your stream.
For a second I'm like, wait, are you both, are you one of the parents? And I'm like, what the
fuck am I talking about? Does that sound weird? Yeah, I was wrong. I'm an idiot. It's okay.
All right, let's keep going. We had, I don't know. Where are we? Right here. We had Jay
Hawn, Jay Hawnizzle. Thanks for the thousand bits. 10 bucks. Hey, Jeremy, today's my 20th birthday.
Happy birthday. I'm glad this game was postponed today and I'm sorry about the memory card.
It's all right. I'm glad that I didn't try to continue to play yesterday. I'm glad we
pivoted to Cooking Mama. That was also a very fun time for me. So we're good. Thanks for the
last of the years and I look forward to any big future projects you have planned. Also, please
show feed on stream. Thank you. Uh, no, I don't think I'm going to do that. Thanks for the 10
bucks. Appreciate it. Erotic Frankfurt. Thanks for the 300 bits. Hello from Australia. Please
say g'day mate. G'day mate. Hello from America, specifically Las Vegas. He did the super frog
voice. Now I'm going to be conscious of that. Potato Chief. Thanks for the thousand bits.
Great impression of someone being attacked by bees.
Oh, I want to see that clip. Somebody give me the clip of the Tasmanian Devil. I want to hear it.
I want to see how close it was. Does anybody have it? Also, can't wait for you guys to,
every time we get raided, to have a perfect clip of this. But when anytime somebody raids
us or a new community comes in to say hello, can't wait for this to be with your shoulders.
Actually, not that bad. That's actually, it was a little too high though. I think it was too high.
No, I'm not trying again. No, I can't go all in right now. It'll be embarrassing.
Hey, I've been attacked by bees. Apple Shift. Thanks for the 250. Yo, you planning on doing
any conventions this year? Not this year. No, not until probably TwitchCon. I think I'm only
going to TwitchCon. I have no plans on going to E3. I have no plans on going anywhere in the
immediate future. Any packs. TwitchCon's the next thing that's in the radar here. DexCon delayed.
Yeah, now it'll be embarrassing. We already talked about this if you weren't here before.
If you do a Tasmanian Devil impression, if you don't go fucking as hard as you possibly can,
it's going to be embarrassing. It's zero and a hundred. If you don't go to a hundred,
it's going to be like, whoa, that was horrible and embarrassing. I'm embarrassed for you.
Trust me. I know. It was still embarrassing. Not for me. Hey, Sir Canine. Thanks for the 250.
My face when Jerma makes the short jokes himself by celebrating that he can reach high things when
he gets a ladder. Feels bad, man. It's Chibi-Robo. You're as big as eight thimbles stacked on top
of each other. Of course I'm going to be making references about being smaller. Sir Canine, thanks
for the 250. Local Chibi streamer loses it over a Chibi children's game while drinking Chibi Cola
and giving out free Chibi Winx. Thanks. Styx Renegade, thanks for the 250. Hey, Jerma,
haven't cheered in a while. Trying to save cash for some incoming car troubles in a furry convention.
All right. Turns out the car trouble wasn't as bad, so I'm passing a few of my savings on to you.
Also, three fucking years I've been subbed. It's a long ass time. What's that three-year sub badge?
Where's the three-year sub badge? Yeah, I know. Also, Crash Team Racing, Nitro-Fueled,
and Burger King Xbox 360 games. When are you going to play them? Also, Draw My Fursona.
I'm busy, but I'll probably get this Burger King games. I'll do them all in like 20 minutes or
something. You could probably beat all those games in an hour or so. Yeah, I've got Xbox games,
360 games. They're all good, too. Here's what happened. As you all know, we've done a lot of
PlayStation 2, PlayStation 3, random Xbox games. We've played a lot of shitty, terrible, crap old
games, and the only ones that are left are the good ones. There are a bunch of games over here
that are all the good ones that are just here. There's at least probably 20 games over here that
are all worth playing completely all the way through. So, we got a long way. I bet I could
find some more trash. Oh, don't worry. There's too much trash on these consoles that it'll be
impossible to not ever do that again. What are some of them? Well, I don't want to give away spoilers.
Just speaking GameCube. I mean, Mario Sunshine, Eternal Darkness, both beautiful Joes.
I don't even want to go further than that. I don't want to go for Gotcha Force, which is one of the
best GameCube games ever. They're so good. They're going to be all done to their completion.
Kirby's Air Ride. I don't have it. Maybe I'll get it. Anyways, we're almost done with the bits here.
We have about five or six more to do. Tar Alecran, thanks for the 250. Jeremy, I want to thank you
for being so accommodating to those with those busy schedules who can't catch the whole stream.
If you didn't reuse the same joke three times, we might miss some content. All right. I'm just
I'm looking out for you. I'm looking out for you. Don't you guys ever watch the news? If you ever
watch the news, the news is on like, for instance, some networks that are 24-hour news networks.
And it's just it's the same two-hour broadcast for 24 hours. You know, I've got a cycle in the new
people that are coming in. They got to know what's going on today. And it's all fake.
Play Ill Bleed. I actually tried to track a copy of Ill Bleed down for the Dreamcast. Did I play
that? Did I get one? No, that's a different game. Sir Canine, thanks for the 250. FocalStreamer
lists games he has promised to keep playing to chat with literally no intention of ever playing
them again. This dude is fricked. James O'Byrne, thanks for the 300 bits. Doc 3660, thanks for the
250. My mom just asked why her 22-year-old son is watching a 35-year-old play a 15-year-old game
meant for seven-year-olds on a 19-year-old console for over six hours in 2020 when he should be
studying six hours for his arts degree so he can work eight hours a day at a Burger King for 30
years until he dies. Damn. Holy shit. That was fucking crazy. You're laughing? Yeah, because
that was a crafted comment. That was a carefully crafted, like, okay, I opened up the jar at the
candle store and smelled the fresh clean vanilla laundry one. You know what I mean? Like,
ooh, put the cover back on. That was like fucking, that was worth sniffing. It was crafted.
Thank you, Doc. The 250. I'm gonna keep that one. I might buy that one. I might, you know,
I might buy that candle and smell it once on the ride home in the passenger seat while somebody's
driving. Just like, oh, yeah, that's the right way to use this. And I don't ever light it once. The
candle has never used. In fact, six months go by and I don't even know where it is. And no one
knows where it is. Four years go by, moving out of the house. You find it in a closet and you go,
whoa, holy shit. Yeah, I remember we got this. Oh, it smells good. Pack that. You pack it up.
Goes into a box. Six more months go by. It's still in the box that you moved with.
And the cycle repeats until you die. Put that on a shirt. Pass it to your career. No music. Oh,
what the monk. Hey, whatever it is. Hey, thanks, Doc. That was a great comment. Smelly boy. Thanks
for the 250, smelly boy. Picking up on the Alfredo talk from yesterday. I contend that
spaghetti noodles outperform fettuccine as Alfredo noodles. They're easier to come across and easier
to eat with a spoon and fork. Also, do you prefer the chicken in your Alfredo noodles breaded or
bare breaded? Breaded thinly sliced. Fettuccine soaks up more of, fettuccine soaks up way more of
the sauce and juices. You get way more sauce per bite. The spaghetti falls right off the bone
on the spaghetti. You know what I mean? Breaded. Yeah, breaded. Oh, yeah. Just thinly breaded.
Thinly breaded. I'm not talking about like fried chicken. I'm talking thin,
little bit flour, just thinly crisp. Thinly crisp. That's it. Thin. Tar Alecran, thanks for
the 250. Jerma, when are you gonna play some Shenmue? I remember asking ages ago when you
were playing Dreamcast games and you assured me that it would be soon. And here I am paying
another $2.50 for my hard-earned dough to call you out to fulfill your oath. I own them. I bought
them on PC. The reason why I didn't play them is because they were coming out. They hadn't come out
on PC yet, right? Or at least what, two didn't? They remade them or something? Like three was coming
out. So I was like, no, you know, I'm just gonna wait till three comes out and then I'll do them
all. And then they took a long time. And then it came out and then three wasn't very good,
from what I hear. And then I was like, wait, oh, shit, this is not very good.
Well, and then I remember, wait, two and one aren't even very good. They're like 180-hour long games.
And I was like, wait, fuck. But they are. I remember playing Shenmue 1 and had fun.
Like, you drive around in a forklift for 12 hours. Yeah, wait, do I want to play that? Maybe. Maybe.
That was fun. It was fun. Joel's playing it right now. Well, you're gonna go say hello to him and
tell him that I said it was 180. He's Joel playing it right now. Stream Joel's... Okay. Okay. Just
pretend I'm streaming when you watch Joel's stream. We're both doing it at the same time.
My spirit is there in that forklift. Anyways. PeacefulHaleigh gave 5,000 bits. We had $50 from
Haleigh. Holy shit, Haleigh. More huge, insane money drops. Pog. Thank you, Haleigh. Jeremy.
Just kind of felt like showing my love. Have a good night. That means a lot. Thank you. That's
a lot of money. Hopefully I use it well. Thank you, Haleigh. Enable Pog. No. It is enabled already.
Pog is enabled because I want to read it. PogChamp is different. Pog, I want to be able to read it.
It's a different meaning for me when I read it. Show Joel sneeze. Sneeze on Joel. What? How
would I do that? But thanks a lot, Haleigh. That's a ton of money. And right after that,
MechaMurf gave 1,500 bits. Thank you, MechaMurf. It'll be $15. You gave a shitload of money last
night, so thank you. Back on top. Love supporting you, Jeremy. I've been watching since 2014. It's
not a contest, but I appreciate it nonetheless. Thank you. Thanks for sticking around for so long.
We got Stryker2. 300 bits from Stryker2. What's going on? Good to see you again. Hey, Jeremy.
Thanks for the recognition for once. I'm donating to say that Stryker Underscore2 is a fake and not
me. Love watching the streams. Keep up the amazing content. I'll keep that in mind. Thanks a lot.
Hey, Bitslave. Thanks for the 250. Hey, Jermo. I was watching your VOD on Diablo 2 and I stopped
watching because it sucked. Okay. Now, what else? Just kidding. I bought it and wanted to play it
with no spoilers. I've never played Diablo before and I'm excited. It's one of the best
games ever made, so I wish you the best of luck. Actually, one of the best games ever made. It
really is. Truly. You're going to love it. Thanks for the 250. The Dreamcast sucks. No, no, no. You
got it wrong. The Dreamcast fucking sucks. Just the culmination. That was like the 10th Dreamcast
game. That person didn't have like no sub badge. It was just no nothing. It was just a name that
just said like just fine in a Dreamcast stream. Dude, this console sucks. Everything about it
makes me happy. Everything about it makes me laugh. It's a perfect, perfect, perfect, perfect
piece of humor. Oh, it's perfect. Those games are all so bad. I know. And that's why it's
the one guy moment of the decade. It's just because I knew. You know what I mean? Like those
Dreamcast streams, some of them were really fun, but there was one in particular that was at least
three or four games in a row that were horrendous and they weren't funny. They weren't even fun.
And it just sucked. And I knew it. And like three or four hours go by and that's the
message I look over and it's like fuck the Dreamcast. That's your only view of the Dreamcast.
Dreamcast sucks, man. Well, this is what it has. This guy's streaming this shit. This guy's
streaming these games. It's got to be worth playing. And so no, these games, this console's
terrible. Oh, I love every second of it. Anyways, I could gush about it forever. Anyways, uh,
Jobbed Bone, thanks to the 250. Jerma, how do I tell my mom I love her? Go up to your mother and
first of all, before you do this, um, take, maybe take care of a few things around the house.
Find out what your mother's got going on tomorrow. Does she have some errands that she needs to run?
Do them. Oh, ma, I just want to let you know, but before I, uh, something came in for the mail,
I took care of it. I took the mail in. I, um, cleaned the windows and shit. I, there was, uh,
you had an appointment. I got, I wrote it in the calendar off over here. Find out what your
mother's up to. Make her life easier for the next couple of days. You don't have to say anything.
Reread the message. Jerma, how do I tell my mom I love, love her? Okay. I'm trying to give
advice. Don't ever give advice ever again. Bitslave, thanks for the 250. Please play
Billy Hatcher and the Giant Egg and Kirby Air Ride. It's a great game. If you don't believe me,
fuck me, I guess. Okay. Check out my OC. What the fuck are you doing? Check out my OC.
What is, what's going on? Okay. Here, we'll check it out. Sure. Cool. Thanks for the,
thanks for the OC. Yeah, Billy Hatcher and the Giant Egg is on the list. Hey, Jake Lemons.
Thank you, Jake Lemons. 1337 for the 500 bits. Do you think, Murph, that Arabian Prince Donator
would play League with me? What the fuck are you talking about? Peaceful Haley, thanks for the
$10. And here's some more money so I can get my 25,000 badge. God damn. Thank you.
Thank you. Thanks for the thousand bits, Haley. On top of the fucking huge money
drop from earlier. Thank you. Sasha Green, Spider Queen, thanks for the 250. Jeremy,
what animal would your fursona be and what color would it be? I see slash S. Is that supposed to
be like sarcastic, right? It was a frog. Frog. Yeah, I'm a frog. Frog. Done. I already did it.
A frog. A rat. I don't know. Who cares? Mecha Murph, thanks for the 1500 bits. I can't stop.
I won't stop. Can't stop. Won't stop. Mecha Murph, another $15. Thank you, Murph. Appreciate it.
Beautiful Jen, thank you for the 250 times two, which is $5. Jeremy, any plans to do anything from
Pikmin? It'd be a real treat to watch you play one of them. Also, congrats on 10 million views.
You deserve them all. Thanks for all the laughs. Yes, there is. The thing about Pikmin, I'm going
to need some help on this one. I don't think I would play all the Pikmins. Pikmin as a series,
to me, is Pikmin one versus Pikmin two versus Pikmin three. I feel like two is just kind of a
more engrossed version of one, a more expanded version of one. Right? Does that make sense?
Am I crazy? You guys have to help me here. Two is the one to play. Play two. So if I just played two,
then I would get good. That'd be fine, right? I don't know about three. Two is way better than
one and three is okay. Okay. Only the second and the third, right? Three is harder for your small
brain. It doesn't matter how small your brain is. It's about how many fucking neurons are in there,
though. And I got a lot, so please. But yeah, definitely. Pikmin two will be probably the one
I play. Kar Alekran, thanks for the 250. Jeremy, with all the utter nonsense you play, you are
seriously turning your nose up at Shenmue, one of the most famous and storied and beloved franchises,
really. Those games you're describing are not 150 hours long. There's a difference between
cooking mama for four hours and playing Shenmue one through three for 400 on stream hours.
I think there's a big difference. They're not that long. How long are they? Like 50 hours. Sorry. It
would take a full month. No, look, I've said this before a million times. I will never completely
tell you that I'm never going to play something because I have no idea what's going to happen in
the future. A couple months might go by and I'll be like, fuck it, man. Let's play Shenmue. Let's go.
I don't have a plan. My plans on this stream are only, only the big projects that take
a few months to put together. There are no fucking plans on this stream besides those.
Zero. I don't have a game that I play any time of day. I just, each week, each month, I'll sit down
and be like, what do I feel like doing this week? What do I feel like doing in the next couple months?
It's this. I can never tell you that I'm never going to play something
because who knows? It could happen tomorrow. Is community content night this Saturday? Uh oh,
wait. Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa. Yo. Okay. Hold on. I may have screwed up here.
Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday. Friday would be four. Well,
uh-huh. Community content night is going to be moved. Not far, not far. Only a couple days.
Only a couple days. Only a couple days. Would you rather me, would you rather have community content
on a Tuesday or on a Saturday or Sunday? Which one? What would you prefer?
Tuesday or a Saturday or Sunday? Which one? Which one? Sunday? Weekend? Sunday? Like I said,
on a Sunday? Okay. All right. The real date for the next community content night, and I, this is,
I screwed up some planning here. It's because I had to, I had some shit to do. The real date
for the community content night will not be March 1st. It's going to be March 8th. Sunday, March 8th.
We're going to have a lot to go through. I never plan. There you are. There you go. In motion.
In motion, you're seeing these things. Thank you, King. Why are people doing that now?
I've seen that a lot. Hey, what's, when's this happening, King? Oh, that was so good, King.
Well, I've seen that a lot. Is that like a thing people are doing now for fun? I keep seeing it.
Anyways, yeah, it's not going to lie because we're doing like four or five days in a row,
at least four days in a row here. And I have some stuff that I have to do on the weekend.
So I fucked up. I don't, hey, no plan. Nancy, whatever you want to call me. Anyways,
we're almost done with the bits here. We have a goo berry juice. Thanks for the 250. Hey-o,
Dr985. Just wanted to donate tonight. Just want to point out that one of the funniest things chat
does is when they point out games no one has ever played, but just talk about it like it's the best
thing ever. Like I saw one guy call you a four IQ idiot for not playing Stuart Little Two on the DS.
Well, you haven't played Stuart Little Two on the DS. What are you fucking dumb?
What's your IQ, dude? What the fuck? Okay. Well, anyways. Also, by the way, can you please play
Alpha Chimp on the Xbox Live Indie Arcade game service? It's off the market now, but please
trust me. It's good. I swear. Pepe hands. Please. God. Um, how am I going to get a copy of that?
Xbox Live Indie game services offline, but get it. How am I going to get it? Please. God. God was
in all capitals. You haven't played Alpha Chimp. What's wrong with you? What are you fucking two IQ?
Excuse me. Thanks to goo berry juice. Appreciate it. Please. God. Striker Two. Thanks for the 300
bits. Hey, Jeremy. Striker Two here again. How do I tell you that I love, love you? Well, you just
did. Sorry. I'm taken. Thank you for the 300 bits. Bulbaswag Desu. Thanks for the 500 bits.
Do you have a mental image for us or are we just a mindless blob? Um, you know, I have a mental
image for chat. I kind of sort of a bunch of, a bunch of small talking dogs, like little dachshunds
and like chihuahuas and stuff. And they all talk. Everyone has like a dog voice this way, that way,
this way, that way. No, I, I just, I honestly, emotes. I see you guys as like the emotes that
you're currently writing. It might be a dog. It might be a smiling face. It might be a rage face.
I don't know. Hey, bit slave. Thanks again for $5 dude. Fucking Billy egg Pog. Yes. Fuck. Yes.
Oh, w I just gamer gassed. Holy shit. Thank you. Thank you. Jake lemons for the 300 bits. He's
playing league with me from Mecca Murph is playing Jake lemons and Mecca Murph are cute. Wait, what's
going on? Well, I, okay. So you're playing league together. That's not me though. Oh, this is weird.
You're freaking me out. Goobery juice. Thanks for the 250. I'm just going to throw these bits on
here. My last donation was too long and to just be 250. That's inaccurate. You can give
250 and say whatever you want as long as it's, you know, appropriate and you're not
putting porn codes into a fucking chat room. But thank you. Goobery. Appreciate it.
Mecca Murph. Thanks for the 1500 bits, 15 more dollars from Mecca Murph's bank account here. I
am the Arabian Prince. Jake lemons was taught. So I got it right. I said it right. It's Jake's less
space M O N Z is what he referred to as Jake lemons. I said it right. I was talking about
playing league with just got back from my deployment from Jordan and Syria. So he calls me that I'm
currently playing league with him. So don't worry. Welcome back. Welcome back playing league together.
Is league getting fun? Don't answer that. I know you don't have to answer that because I know it's
not fun. You don't have to answer it. I already know. Thank you, Mecca Murph. Seriously, both of
you. Hope you guys having fun together. Off futz. Thanks for the 500 bits. Hi, have a great night.
You too. Thank you. Jobbed bone. Thanks for the 250. Seriously though, I don't want to hurt what
mom and I have, but I wanted to know how I feel. This is a you scenario, man. I got nothing for
you here. I got nothing for you here. This is, this is a you thing. I have nothing. I got nothing
for you. Have a great night. Thanks a lot. Let's run those credits. What do you say? Stop the music.
Yeah. Well, the reason why we stopped the music is because we're almost done with the bits,
but I do want to get these going. We don't need music for this. Here come all the community subs,
all the new subs, all the old subs, every sub that happened on tonight's stream is going to run by
you. There it is. Thanks again, guys for supporting the stream. Lots of you. Thank you. Thank you.
Every single sub from today. What a bunch of nerds. Why did you ban that person for three
minutes? My sub ran out today. So it's all good. Don't worry. More jelly. Thanks for the 250.
Jerma, I'm going to go see Blade in Brooklyn in May. Can I get a win? A W. What? I guess.
Is the movie any good? I don't know. We'll see. Thanks for the 250.
A bit slave. It's like just came in with 50 more dollars. 5000 bits going nuts on the bits here.
They say support the troops stream at Mecha Mervin. I need you to play League of Legends.
Also, the gamer drink of the day is Guinness. Good smooth beer. Drink it now if you're of age.
Remember to game on gamers. Game the F on also four more days and I'm unbanned from leagues.
Can we get some fucking pogs in the chat? LOL Tyler1 sponsored this message. I don't think he
did. He's drinking again. He's drunk again. Don't play League drunk. That's the number one thing.
Don't do it. Guinness. No, I don't drink Guinness. It's liquid bread. Not for me.
I can't play League. I'm not playing League. It's not going to happen.
It's not going to happen. I'm never going to play League. It's never going to happen. I'm sorry.
German only drinks wine. I mean, I like wine. Red wine. It's fucking good for you. Polyphenols.
Any polyphenols in liquid fucking sourdough? I don't think so. Thanks a lot for the 5000
bits though, Bitslave. Really. More jelly. Thanks for the yardie. Did it? That's it. Good for you,
you wino. Wino. Bitslave. 1500 bits right at the very end. 15 dollars. German, you make me cry if
I saw one game as Grandpa Diarrhea running down mid. Was that my name in League? My name in League
was Grandpa Diarrhea? Am I allowed to have that name? Why was I allowed to have that name?
It seems weird, right? All right. We'll see you tomorrow for Achieve Your Robo. Try to finish it
tomorrow. Stirr is streaming right now. We're going to go say hi to Stirr. He's doing custom
workshop balance. I don't know. Apparently he's sick. Sick. But he's not too sick.
Go show Stirr some love. He's playing Overwatch. I don't know how vile that word was to you all.
Were you going to raid Joel? But just hop around. Hop around. I never catch Star when he's streaming.
He's always not streaming when I stream. I want to say hi. Let's say hi to Star.
Good. Bye. See you tomorrow. Good night.