Hey, what's going on? Sorry. Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry. I was like ready to start like 25
minutes ago, but I couldn't find my fucking brace. And after last night, I was like, I have to have,
I gotta find it. So I was going through all the laundry trying to find where it was. Did I wash
it? Where is it? And I, uh, I got it. I found it. Thank God. I was here like 40 minutes ago.
When you lose something in your house, you just can never find it. It's the worst. I hate losing
stuff. Everybody does though. Anyways, uh, today, I hope you're having a good day today. We're going
to be playing Mega Man Legends finally. Not pushing it back anymore. It's happening today.
Not going to say, yeah, then we'll do Mega Man Legends tomorrow. That doesn't happen.
Next week. And it doesn't happen. It's been delayed like five times. So here it is.
He's actually playing it. I can't fucking Pog. Pog. Black and White 2 is, no, I'm not going to
enable Pog. I'd like to read it. It makes, it has more meaning for me if I read it out loud.
There's already PogChamp. Pog is, it needs to be, I want to read it. Uh, but what did somebody just
ask? Somebody ask something? Paperclip game? Oh, we, I beat that whole thing yesterday. Black and
White 2. There it is. Okay. Right. So Black and White 2, uh, I had technical issues with it,
but now I, it, it should be good to go after a few more tweaks. So that is on the table
after this stream. So Mega Man Legends tonight, I think I can do this in one stream, right?
Because Mega Man Legends is only like, like a six, seven hour long game, isn't it?
No, it's not. How long is it? Okay. According to howlongtobeat.com, it's a seven hour game,
but you have to add on the three or four hours of ADHD. So we're looking at probably like
eight to 12 hours, seven hours. Well, we'll see. We'll see how far we get. I could do it another
time. The goal is to try to get it done today. I'm not going to be live over the next couple
days. I have physical therapy, so we'll do, we'll try to get another long one tonight. I've got my
boomer brace on. I'm good to go. The Sonic movie was good. That's what I heard that week, but that's
what I said the other day, yesterday. Prove that you have your boomer brace on. Okay. Hold on.
Remember these guys? Nah, what if I just was lying? No, no, I don't need to put it. Nah,
my camera's not working. I can't, like, it doesn't work. My fucking, the plug doesn't work.
Hold on here. You want proof? I've got my, I've got my backpack on. So you can't see down here,
but what this does. Villain. Yeah, I know. What this does is that it's not just this.
It's here too. You're like, it goes all, I don't want to, I'm not going to like stand up on my
chair, but it goes all the way down and wraps around my bottom of my ribs and like pulls them
together. And it feels pretty good actually. Wesker? I could probably pull off a Wesker if
I had the glasses. Do you think so? All right. I'm ready to play. If I had the glasses and,
what's the buzz? I hear a buzz. What's the buzz? Hold on. If you guys hear a buzz,
you will. Why is it buzzing? What the fuck is going on? Hold on. What the fuck? Why is there a buzz?
It's getting louder. Why is it like somebody turned on the microwave
next to my PlayStation? Oh, hold on. Give me a second. Let me fix this. Is it gone? It's gone.
All right. Hold on. I got to like, somebody move. Is it gone? It's there a little. It's all right.
It's fine. Okay. It's there a little, but why is this happening right now? The cable is fucked up.
All right. All right. Here we go. We get big bits. Where? It's not as loud. It's not as loud
as it was before. It's something to do with this cable, I think. Cable's fucked up. I don't know
what I did to it. Maybe it has something to do with turning the console upside down to play
Jeremy Lammy and like breaking it. All right. Everything's fine. Everything's going to be fine.
All right. Welcome to the stream. Let's start a new game. Mega Man Legends. I had a big bit.
I like the voice acting already. So where does this sit in the timeline for Mega Man?
He's like 20. How old is he?
Be careful.
You got the crystal? We had big bits. I'll go over in a second. Hold on.
I remember this game being fucking awesome. Am I wrong? Am I right here? Is this a running
sequence? It looks pretty good still. It's it's whole it's hell. This is PlayStation 1.
This is PS1, guys. This is not emulation. This is not. This is all original hardware. Well,
PlayStation 2. But still it looks pretty good for PS1. Oh shit. All right. Hold on. So that's
oh wow. It's it's full 3D. One of the first ever full 3D games.
Okay. Reaverbot. Reaverbot. Okay. You square to fire. Press the R2 button to automatically
lock onto the nearest target. All right. Yeah. These things. Oh, there it is.
Oh shit. That's awesome. All right. Let's go. All right. I already love it. I already love it.
This is janky. No, it's not. This is mega. Hey, this is the fucking this is the most legendary
Mega Man game that's ever been released. I do. It's right here. It's right in front of me.
Dude, I can't wait just to do the fucking stock market midi game that's in this one, too.
That's it. Yeah. Always open stuff. Oh shit. Is there a zoom out the camera button?
I can't watch like it upgrades. I don't know. No, I don't like this. This is not. This is I want
to pull the camera out a little bit. No, I don't like it. Increase FOV. No, actually, it's pretty
good. One thing I wish I could do is make. All right, I can jump, right? A, B, X. Use X jump.
If you can't make it in one jump, you can sometimes grab onto the edge and pull yourself up.
Cool. There is a jump here. I want to make, uh, can I free look law map now? Wait, directional
button turn. So wait a minute. So I can do what the hell does that mean? Because I want to make
it so I wish I could do my right stick, but the right stick didn't exist for PlayStation one,
right? The voices are quiet. I mean, I don't think there's anything I can do about that.
Did it? No, it didn't. It did. It had the left stick, right? No. What? Did it have two sticks?
Did a PlayStation one originally? No, it didn't have any. Oh, that's way better. Yeah. I don't
want L1, R1 to turn. That's so much better. Yeah, that's a thousand times better. I can actually
turn. It's kind of like tank controls when you do this, but it's all right. It's much better than
it was before. What is that? Oh, it's alive. Wait, should I jump on it? Okay. Can I not grab this
ledge? Oh, it's a ton of money. Oh, nice. Explanation. Quantum refractors are large
crystals that provide energy for machines. They can also be used as currency. Not a big deal.
If you're finally lucky, if you're really lucky, you might find an orange energy cube.
Grab it to recharge your life gauge. Oh my God, it disappeared. What? Oh, that was so much money
that I don't have now. Holy shit. I was too slow. How could I have been? What was that?
Oh, it's an energy field. Wait, Mega Man. Wait. Okay. Fuck you game. I thought Mega Man was two
words. Do I have to change everything? Do I have to change my title? Use R2 to track enemies above
and below you that are out of your field of sight. Oh look, you're up there, aren't you?
Oh shit. Maybe I actually want to keep it on L1, R1. I feel like it's a part of the... Yeah,
maybe I do. What do you think? Yeah. Yeah, I think I'll get used to it. I'll get used to it.
Because then I can actually keep enemies in frame. Yeah, I'll get used to it. L1, R1. Say the line.
That wasn't even a giant. That was not even a... No. I don't say the line for things that aren't
even the line. Come on, get it. Just like the original Mega Man. You jump and jump, jump,
jump and shoot, jump and shoot. Yeah. Oh, you found 560 zenny. Hold on. There's a Kingdom Hearts
currency? You got Power Razor. You said 10... We had... Hold on. Wait. We had $50 come in too.
We had 10 community subs from Wosse. 10 community subs from Vertible Giant.
Thanks, both of you. And then we had 5,000 bits from Bitslave. They say, hey, German, thanks to
you. I got Johnny Walker. Check out the review. What Johnny Walker... Wait, what Johnny Walker
did you get? That's important. Got Black Label. It's all right. I said that's pretty good. I mean,
I'm a Johnny Walker blue guy myself, but... Let's see what you think. Don't smell it. Just drink it.
Look at Mr. Fancy Pants. You buy a blue label and you drink it over the course of like five years.
I'm going to defend that in just a second here. Hold on. What do you think?
Pretty good. Pretty good. Pretty good. I think he liked it. 895? What? 895.
German 895. Oh, that's fucking funny. Liquid. All right. I quote, first of all,
thanks for the 5,000 bits. Glad you like it. Also, Plane Dad says hi. Tell Plane Dad I said hello.
Thank you. Oh, I'm glad you liked it. It's good shit. Explanation. Hold on. We'll talk about this
in a second. Power Razor is a Mega Man Buster part. Attaching Buster parts allows you to power up
your Buster gun. You can attach Buster parts by pressing the start button to go to the menu
and select equip from the Buster. Buster parts. Why is there nothing here? Oh, attack plus one
attack. Sick. Oh, I love it already. I love it already. It's already equipped. Let's go.
Look at it. It's a little bigger too. Nice. I haven't even found that if I didn't go down
the right hallway. All right. Anything else? No. How do I get a big view of the map?
Select. And they thought, look at how far. Look at fucking Capcom. You know what I mean?
Is there a door over here that I could've gone in? No. Just didn't explore it. Oh, Capcom does it
again. There's a blue door over here. Oh, no. I got it right in the plasma.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
That's not a bad Mega Man. That's not a bad Mega Man at all.
Boss battle. How do I do the dodge? There's no dodge roll. Yeah, there is. I did it a few times
already. Shit, I'm just going nuts. Do I have to be locked on first? I'm gonna need it. Yeah,
you can lock on. You don't have to lock on though. It goes in the direction that you're aiming
whatever enemy is there. Buy no helmet. He's protecting everything on his whole body except
for his head. The most important part. You can get one later? All right, cool. All right. Anyways,
if you buy an expensive bottle of alcohol like whiskey or like an expensive tequila or something,
you're not supposed to drink it all in one, two, three days.
You don't buy like a $300 bottle of whiskey and drink it in one day.
No, you drink. That's a special occasion alcohol. Again? Okay, if you buy a bottle of
um, Jack Daniels, what like, who cares?
Sponsored content. There's actually people that think that Johnny Walker Blue is disgusting and
that I'm disgusting for liking it because it's a blend. You are gross. You should be drinking
right out of the barrel from one source. What's going on? I thought the game froze. Why does
this ship look like it's flying upside down? It is. Oh, we're not at work anymore. You can
call me. You can call me Dave. We should be able to get by with that for a while.
We're as easy to find as this. Don't worry. We'll find it someday.
And your parents too. Thanks. I know we will.
Who is this guy? I can tell he's going to be shady because he's got one of these
voices that they have in every single cartoon. He's going to be a little weird.
Mega Man, go help the guy. That's why you wear a fucking helmet.
Both of you. Hope this is a lesson for all three of you actually.
I can't wait for the upgrades. I'm so excited to upgrade. Who cares about the game? I just
care about the numbers going up.
soon. We'll be here for a while, I guess. This island. What do you call it, Mega Man?
Catalocks. I think you could go take a look around. Sure. There's a kick. Who's this?
Hi, my name's Data. But you already knew that, didn't you? I mean, we've been friends for years,
right? Right. Yeah, of course I do that. Come talk to me if you want to. Oh, save. All right.
What do you want to do? Recharge energy. Save the game. Remember card one. Yes, I want to save.
Do auto voice. You got it. For this character, I will. I promise.
Tell me. Tell me. What can I help? What can I help you with? Uh, no, I don't need. This is like
tutorial info. Okay, so, uh, I got a map here. This is a big place. Let's go to the, let's go
to the market. Let's just go this way. To town. That's a pretty good Minecraft sign.
What's going on? The police are here. Um, can I? Police? Oh, there they are. What's the matter?
Well, you certainly put on quite a show. And it looks like everyone's all right.
Glad to see you're all right after the crash. Okay, bye. Secret. Always check for secrets so
I can kick trees or something. Do a Trump voice instead. You know, I love how the court of, of,
of chat's opinion on the Trump voice has increased. Remember when I first did the Trump voice and
everyone was like, Oh, it's don't, no, no, no. Stephen Colbert does a better job. Did it like
five or six more times. And now it gets, it gets requested. I want to go down inside the ruins
to look for some part. Am I too loud? Why do I feel like I'm loud right now? Am I, am I loud?
No, I'm good. Okay. Fine. Okay. Look for some parts and other stuff. I'm afraid of reaver bots and
whatever else might be down there. But if I don't find something to sell in my shop,
I'll be in trouble. Go in it. And why just looking inside? What do you have to say?
Is this your ship? It shouldn't be here. This is a no parking zone. It ain't mine. This gate's
malfunctioning. We can't get it to lock. We'd better fix it soon. Were you in the flying machine
that just crash landed? If so, could you wait until you've spoken with the inspector before
entering the city? I believe the inspector's gone to investigate the crash site. Didn't I already,
I don't, I tried. He didn't say anything. What? Oh, here's the little Lego guys.
Hold on. Why is it so much reverb? That one's loud. Those are tuber voices.
Come on. If I have, if I have access to it, do you think I'm not going to use it? It sometimes,
if I have access to, I know, I know that everybody that has one of these does this shit,
but if it can put a little bit of a robotic tune to my voice, whether there's a robot on the screen,
like I, I'm going to enhance my volume and my data that I'm putting through to the street.
Oh, you certainly put on quite a show, but it looks like everyone's on.
No, how would they do this? All right. Well, talk to me. Isn't this the inspector?
Talk to the inspector. What the heck? The police saw us crash land and came to check up on us.
Ramps is the, you certainly put on quite a show. That was close. I was in the same ballpark.
Let me welcome you to catalogs Island. I'd like to ask one of you to come with me to the station.
We need you to fill out some Bernie voice for the Bernie voice.
Can you do anything besides a Bernie voice? You can't enter the city without me.
Don't worry. It won't take very long while you're waiting. You can spend your time
in the shopping arcade next to the city. You don't need an ID card to get in there.
Are you ready to go professor? Go to the arcade? Are you fucking kidding me? How much is the arcade?
And why is this the best game ever? Ditched. Wait, did they? So wait, me and Roll were left behind.
So they deemed the save game little monkey character more important than me. I can understand,
like grandpa, he's the guy, he's the one that has to repair the ship and has to give a police
report. What's the save monkey doing there? What's this? Oh, that was cool. All right,
hold on. This is kind of bright. Failure. Taylor. Oh, let's go in. I can put new clothes.
That customer there spends all his time staring at the mirror and never buys anything.
Look at me. Am I cool or what? Yes, you are. Yep. Yes. So far the coolest character in the game so
far. I don't know what this guy's problem is. You should let him stay as long as he wants.
This is Apple Market, the biggest shopping center on Catalox Island. Why is it called Apple Market?
See those banners up there? When you want to look up or down, push the directional button while
holding down the R2 button. It's called the Apple Market because you decided to have banners that
say apple on them with an apple. Not like this town is known for its apples and farming market.
No, we just decided it was going to be an apple on a banner. That's interesting. Oh,
are you one of the people who just crash landed? Want some fruit? How about some fresh vegetables?
All right, now here we go. Yeah, I do. I want them. Cabbage, mushrooms, carrots. There's a
lot of vegetables lined up. There are tomatoes, cucumbers, and other vegetables lined up. Where's
the fucking meat? Where's the meat and cheese? Dressmaker hip bone. There's no apples there.
Say, you're kind of cute. Your name's Mega Man, isn't it? Well, you're my type of man. I don't
know if you like looking at women's clothing, but come back and see me anytime. That was a little
forward. A high welcome to town would have been nice at first. I really like this dress.
Do you think it would look good on me? Yeah, I mean, sure. Really? Will you buy it for me then?
Who are these people? Who are you fucking people? No. Oh, don't worry. I was just
kidding. Hi, Mega Man. Welcome to town. I love you. Okay. Mega Man, do you think this looks good?
Buy it for me. What the fuck? Who are these two people? Get out of here. They must know I'm famous.
Like, they think I'm like loaded. Is Mega Man loaded? Probably. Caprica.
I mean, this is like late Mega Man, right? He's like 22 or 25 or something. Isn't he in this game?
He's probably got like 10 million in the bank. Have you heard about the ruins just outside the
gate? You can go inside even if you don't have a digger's license. I hear the junk shop owner
next door is always going in. They're looking for parts. We have our grind missions. That's pretty
cool. What do you got here for me? Anybody give any fucking cheddar cheese? My favorite cheese.
This is my dog, Paprika. He's cute, isn't he? Yeah, he is. That reminds me. I fucking love dogs.
It's a box. Is there anything inside? There's a refractor shard inside. You found 100 zenny.
I'm gonna just throw $100 away. Why? It's a garbage pill. There's a refractor shard inside.
You found 20 zenny. Excuse me. This is my dumpster. Anything inside? It's empty. All right. Um, cool.
This is a nice little area. Did I not do anything? Wait, there's like, oh, toys. Wait, hold on.
Yeah, of course. I didn't do the entire right side of the mall. They're trying to fix inflation.
Leave that shit in the trash. Broken cleaner? What? I think I find items. Who are these people?
You're looking for the treasure too, aren't you? Just like that girl was here a minute ago.
Well, I don't know nothing about it. Even if I did, I wouldn't tell a stranger like you.
By the way, do you think that this vest looks good in these sneakers? Yeah, they do.
I hear you're loaded. Can you buy them for me? There's been a lot of strangers coming here lately.
I don't like strangers. Yeah, you don't look like you're from around here either. Go away.
What if I wasn't here? Record shop? What is this? There's a listening station where you can listen
to CDs. Can I find CDs and play them? Boy, this song is really good. What OST are you listening to?
What OST is he listening to? There's a jazz CD on the player. Remember we talked about jazz
yesterday? In German, not all music is OST, but all music in a video game is an OST because it's
part of the game's OST. For instance, this song we're listening to right now is on the Mega Man
Legends OST. I wanted to get a CD, but I didn't have enough money. So I'm just going to listen
to the samples. Oh my God. I remember this. Holy shit. You guys. All right. Some of you guys that
are old enough. Do you remember going into the record store, the CD store and being able to
listen to like an eight second sample of the CD? Wow. They had these headphones that were lined up
on the cases of the CDs and you could listen to samples. I forgot about that.
And it was always so stupid. I fucking hated it so much because every time you scanned one to play
a sample from the album or from a single, it would pick a random spot. It wouldn't play the
bridge or the chorus, but you'd have an insanely famous song and it would play like in the middle
of the second verse. It's like, I want to fucking give me the chorus. Not that
what are you doing? You caught me right in the middle of your second verse. That's not what I
wanted to hear. That's a bad sample. Be sure to listen to our sample CDs before you leave.
All right. Where's the arcade? I'll spend an hour walking around here. I don't care. I love this.
Electronic goods store. It's an electronic shop, but the junk store probably has a better selection
of parts. Yeah, but what's in it though? 50% off a TV. Can I buy this stuff? It's a TV, but it's too
big to carry home. That's not too big to carry home. What? You can definitely. All right. If you
can carry a 24 pack of water to your car, you can carry that to your car. Mega Man, please.
What else is in here? It's a VCR, but you don't need one. I already got one. Oh, it's a Tesla
fridge. It's a refrigerator. What do you do? Parts for a flying ship. You're better off looking at
the junk store. All this stuff in here is junk. Everything's 50% off. You got nothing full priced
in here, man. You're selling an old fridge for like 30% off. Here you break. Toy store. Yep.
This is that new game called Mega Man Legends. It looks pretty interesting.
Can I play the game within the game? All right. Junk shop. Where's the arcade? Ego Mania Mania. Oh,
man. This is not even. All right. This is a lost and found. This is not even a junk shop.
Junk shop lady. Parts for your ship. I'm sorry, but my husband's out on a dig right now.
You know what a dig is, right? It's where you go underground looking for old machine parts.
That's condescending. I wonder what's taking him so long. Hey, little blue boy. Would you be willing
to go find him for me? Yeah, sure. You will? Oh, thank you so much. You'll probably find him
somewhere near the entrance. He's really just a big coward, you see. So I don't think he's gone too
far in. What do you have here? He's 100% dead. It's a stuffed re-robot. It's an old family heirloom.
We call it Rover. Let's go find the junk guy. All right. No arcade? Where's the arcade? Look at
how happy the dog is. Oh, I know somebody that like just got out of the bath. You just took a bath.
Yep. The only difference is you're not like rolling around on your back and going.
All right. So we need to go to the. All right. Let's get out of here. Can I throw this away?
Can I open the garbage and throw it away? Wait, there's 50 dollars in here. All right. Kick it in
in the basket. No, whatever. I love the way this is. Look at this. Bang! Bang! I love it. I just saw
an older man go inside those ruins over there. I wonder if he'll be all right. If you want to
go check on him, you should probably save first. If you want to save, just talk to me, okay? Okay.
I forgot. I know I forgot. The man of five voices. He can go like this. He can go like this.
He can go like this. He can go like this. The man of five voices. All right. The ruins. Let's go
in the ruins. Where are the ruins? The ruins over there. Over here? This isn't the guy's store.
I thought this was the guy's store. Oh, man's voice. Help. Somebody help. Dungeon time. Look
at the parts too. I need junk parts. Oh, easy. Can I move when I'm locked on? I can't move when
I'm locked on, huh? All right. Let's get this money. All right. So if I move... Okay. I can't
move left and right. Is it like a dodge or like a... That's kick. Part two. Left, up, down. No. No.
How do I do that dodge? Why am I playing the worst Mega Man? What? What? What? Hold on. Dude,
that's like I'm eating my favorite spaghetti dish in my favorite restaurant. And you walk up
as somebody that's never been to the restaurant before. Or maybe you have and you don't like it,
but you tap me on the shoulder and go, hey, the spaghetti here sucks. It's the worst. The meat
sauce is terrible. In fact, I think there's rats in the kitchen and then you leave.
What? Help me. Where is this guy? There's got to be a way I can do that dodge.
Yikes. I'll take the range. Oh, fuck. Can I only get that dodge roll if I do the other control
scheme? R1 plus X. Ah, yes. Yes. Yes. Look at how much better this is. Does that help? Oh my.
Apologize for what? I just airstropped that guy. What? What am I apologizing for? What did I do?
I didn't do anything. There is just a secret. Don't worry. I ain't going anywhere.
Thanks. You saved my life. Phew. Thank you. Ah, Mr. Blue boy. Come on by my junk shop.
I'll give you some thing as a token of my appreciation. If you don't know what you did,
it's worse. Is this about the like, yes thing? Don't worry about me. If nothing else, I'm a
fast runner and I'll make it out okay. I ain't saying sorry. I ain't saying sorry for that one.
Not going to happen. Let's go get secrets. He didn't do anything wrong. Yeah. What did I do
that was wrong? Oh no. Minus two. Unbased streamer. Unbased. I got to find, let's look,
I got to look for some secrets. Any secrets? Secret. There's a hole in the wall. Is there
anything inside? You found a refractor shard. You got 20. That's a lot of money.
It looks like a binding of an Isaac. I got to get up there. How do I get up there? Like is there like
zoom shoes? Zoomer shoes or something? Like jump shoes?
I don't think I can get up there. All right. Well, let's go with the actual exit.
I got money now. Boss? Oh, wait, hold on. Easy. Oh, it's the classic Mega Man villain. I'm not
going to do anything until you get too close and then I'm going to come up and I'm going to have
Oh my god. Did I get the money?
Nice. Wait, what's that? Nothing. The sound design is dope. Yeah, it actually is pretty good.
Is it going to blow stuff up? Ow. That hurt. Hitbox fucking hitbox reddit, whatever it is.
Is there only one guy in here? No, there's two. Be careful. This is a tough room. Does that guy
move? All right, let's let's get this cheesed. Okay, that's done. Now just get in. Let's fight.
Don't stop saying reddit shit. Unbased. Oh, that was a good chest move he predicted. He just
walked into the wall though. Big money. Zero out of ten. Unbased. Oh yeah. Rapid fire. Rapid
fire is a Mega Man buster part. Attaching buster parts allows you to power up your weapons.
You can attach buster parts by pressing the start button to go to the menu screen and selecting
equip from the buster parts menu. I think I stayed in here. So I'm gonna have two on. Equip
up. Rapid fire increases rapid. They can have two parts on at the same time. So I have.
Let's take a look. How much better is it? A little better. Oh, we'll test it on you.
You can get at least three. Yeah, eventually probably. I don't remember much from the game.
Besides, that was good that I got. All right, anything else in here? No. Leave the ruins.
You can strafe while locked on. You cannot. You cannot. I believe that is somebody said that is
only in Mega Man Legends 2. Yes, you can. Are you sure that's not a suit upgrade or something I get
later? It was. It was. They were. They're jaking you. Did you bait? Oh, big door. There's a wall
in the way. Maybe if you had something to break through it with. Worth a shot. All right, I got
money and I just rescued the guy. So what else is it? Nothing. Nothing. I can't get up there.
Come on. No. Mega small. Is German in a space cam is on? What the fuck, dude? Use the ladder?
We would ladder. In the other room? Wait, what am I getting lied to? Ladder in the first room.
Oh, that's a ladder. Oh, that's a ladder. I thought that was just cool artwork on that. I didn't know
that was a ladder. It was like, all right, here we go. I'm back. Hey, look at this. It looks like
Spotter's car. I wonder if it would run if we would fix it up. Probably. I hear you helped out
with the junk store owner. He says he wants to thank you. So you should stop by his store later.
Good job. This dude is just vibing. Yeah. He hates the auto voice. No, I will. I just keep forgetting.
Back to the junk store. Wait, another person here? Where do I kick this? Somebody said behind the
counter. Behind the bakery counter? Is that real? All right, I'm gonna go for it. Get it behind the
bakery counter. Well, you must really hate this place. You look like a Slytherin. Yes, I know.
I know. I look like a Slytherin. And if I tell you I'm Slytherin, that means I'm actually Hufflepuff.
And if I get Hufflepuff on a test, it means I'm actually Slytherin in real life.
That's how this works. Got it. Nice shot. Thousands, any. Keep our streets clean. Put
trash in its proper place. All right. Junk store. I mean, in the bakery. Wait, what? Bakery is
behind the bakery counter. Our trash belongs in the bakery. What the fuck? Fuck the bakery. What
are you guys doing? Oh, you came back. The bakery has aggressive energy. Were you surprised I came
back? I'm here for my reward actually. Oh shit, I didn't think you'd be back. Thank you so much. I
don't know what I would have happened if you hadn't gone looking for junk store man. Ha ha ha ha ha.
Thanks for helping me out back there. Here, take this as a reward. You got mine parts kit.
Did you see that old beat up car outside the city walls? That's the car we used as our support car
when we were younger. Anyway, you can have it if you want. It doesn't run anymore, but you should
be able to use it to exchange buster parts and stuff. Like storage. It's a stash. You're looking
for parts for your ship, right? No, I don't have anything like that here, but I've got weapons and
upgrades and other stuff I can sell you. Why? Why are you the store that has all this stuff?
What did you say your name was? My name is Hippopotamus. Hippopotamus? What kind of name is
that? Well, anyway, come back soon, Mr. Hippopotamus. Only you guys know. Oh, I was the
digger and he was my spotter. I'm back to buy something. Parts for a flying ship. I want to
buy. Do you want me to come back and buy something? If you got a Class B digger's license, you can get
into the ruins in the southern forest or the one up the north in the closer woods. All right. Well,
thanks for nothing. They were just being polite. Hey, slow. No running. No running. You're going to
slip and fall in the pool. You know, what it is around the edges. God, people just don't ever
fucking understand that rule. Who are you? Are you a digger? I'm here going doing research on the
ruins of this island here. Sure. A lot of them aren't there. That's what I used to go. They were
just being polite. They usually don't have any stuff here. Well, OK. Come on up north. Thanks
for nothing. Drunk shop. That's the stuff. Yeah. OK, goodbye. We sell parts and upgrades and armor.
Come back. Whatever. All right. Now let's go turn that car on. I've got parts. Do you need to do it?
Mega man, were you able to find anything? Voice acting. If you can't find any parts in town,
I guess we'll have to try digging for them ourselves. That's what the man at the junk
store said. That might take a while, which means. I don't know if. Mega man, what's that? That's
what the man at the junk store told me. His info you should really go off of for much. Yeah. The
junk store man gave it to me. He said we could use this car to hook it up. Mega man. You mean
we can use this car? Well, come on then. Junk store man. He's really putting a lot of weight on
the junk store man's stuff in the things he says. Have you talked to the mayor yet? It's ready.
This weapon lets you use landmines. Just drop them in front of an oncoming enemy. And just remember,
there's a limited number of mines, so make sure you use them sparingly.
Do you want me to explain what this weapon does again? I'll get to work on fixing this car up.
I'll be able to help you out and maybe spot for you if I can get it running again.
Item development. Once the support car is fixed, I'll be able to use it to make all sorts of new
things. If you find something interesting, bring it here. You never know what I might be able to
make for you. All right. That's it. Yeah. We get like a mobile development.
More stuff to give. Wow. I only had to walk around for 10 minutes.
Citizenship.
And locking the gates evacuating. Our grandfather is still inside the city.
Will he be all right? Well, I'm sure he's heard the announcements about the pirates.
Oh, that's that's not. Yes. That's not. Yes. If you'll excuse me, I'm worried about grants.
I hope he'll be OK. I'll go look for him. You wait here. We're evacuating the city.
Pirates, eh? Well, they shouldn't give you any trouble. But be careful anyway, OK? I did it.
I did it. I did it. That was perfect. I thought this was a Canadian forest. Let's go. So I have
my citizen's key card now. It doesn't look like much of an evacuation.
Hey, we're having a secret meeting. Get out of here.
If I'm careful, I should be able to get close without them noticing. You can move slowly by
pressing circle and the directional button at the same time. Is this sneaking or is this
more pronounced than what I was just doing? That's like the get the fuck out of my way walk.
Whisper, whisper. That girl looks suspicious, I tell you.
She has to be a pirate. She said she was looking for treasure.
No one believes us. We're going to have to get her ourselves. Hey, someone's spying on us.
It's that blue guy again. Come on, everybody. Let's go. OK, got it. Once the decision's made,
there's no turning back. The pirate. Nothing less than 100 percent. And remember, it's more than
just guns and ships. Holy shit. It's whoever has the most information that wins, right?
That's what they got the entire idea from. We understand. Keep your costs as low as possible
and stay on schedule. And they just scrambled all the dialogue so they can just localize it
for free everywhere. Holy shit. Genius. Wait, that's me? I thought I was a camera.
Wait, you just drew. Hey, pay attention. I was in a fucking crosswalk. There's nobody driving
these cars. Kick mailbox. Kick mailbox. It's a mailbox, but you don't need to send any letters.
I bet you the cop does it too. Do they crash into each other? Uh oh, big school bus. Haven't you
heard about the pirates? Everyone in town's evacuating. You'd be small. OK, that's why
everyone's getting fucked up. I get it. I know everyone's afraid and wants to get away,
but they should be more careful when they drive. You better watch out too and make
sure you don't get run over. I know. Oh my god. It's a fire hydrant. You could probably jump on
top of it. OK, and why did I do that? Garbage pail. Is there anything inside? No. Achievement.
In the back of the guest truck. Yes. Nice. Ice cream. Vending machine. Do you want to put a
hundred zenny in? Yes. You got a soft drink. Pretty good cat puke sound. Nice. You got a soft drink
for free. One more. Hey guys. I love it. Thief. It's quiet inside. Looks like everyone's evacuated.
All right, let's go. This is a plant. Nice bitrate, idiot. What? Oh, that's all right. Nice. Cool.
Um, wait, no. Mega Man, look out for that car. Mega Man, watch out for the car. The audio is
desynced on me or on the game? Because I could probably fix it. What are you? Is it me desynced?
We'll do a test. Ready? Ready? Kick. Kick. Kick. Kick. Kick. It's fine. The bus stops, actually.
Really good driver. Thank you. Smartest person in the game. Look at that. What about you? Test
number two. No. He just saw. He just saw the bus stop. What? I just went down to the sewer?
Oh, nice. All right. Like dungeon. Let's go. Why didn't it just say it like that? Dungeon.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. This is just. Oh, okay. This is where it was before. It's all
connected. Can I do anything in here? This game's kind of like Doxels. Yeah, kind of, kid.
Oh, enemy. I can't fire right now. Police. Fire it. Huh? What do you want? You've been following
me all around all day, haven't you? Sorry, but I don't have time to play with you.
Just stay out of my way. Okay. Oh, don't you know that all civilians are supposed to be evacuated?
You just like that girl over there. Don't you know you're supposed to do what adults tell you to do?
I thought he was going to walk into the road and get like clipped. This is really bright.
It's a fountain. Watching it makes you feel very relaxed.
Unanimated electricity. Wouldn't this kill me? I've got like 400 pounds of electricity on me.
The bank. There's a bank. The pirates aren't coming, are they? Please say they're not. ATM?
It's an automated teller machine, but you can't use it. You don't have any money in the bank.
Well, let's go. Let's open up an account. It's getting too dangerous here.
I'm thinking that maybe we should shut down temporarily. This is the bank.
Completing on evacuating. Please be sure to withdraw money first.
No, don't tell everyone to withdraw their money first. That's how you crash the whole economy.
The desk filling up forms. Pens are attached to the desk by a chain.
It's a comfortable looking sofa. I figured that since I was evacuating,
I should withdraw my money from my account, but I forgot I only have 980 zenny in the bank.
Why are you telling me how much money you have? Wait, you can't take it out?
All right. At that point, I'm going to be like, all right, hey, dude, here's a 20.
Just put it in and then take it out. Have a nice day. What? Knock, knock. Looks like nobody's home.
The legendary mega... Yeah. No, what's on the other side of this gate? The Yas Plains. The Yas
Plains. That's what. Right now, it's full of people who've evacuated from the city,
so it's a little crowded. Oh, chat, chat. What are you going to say about that one? I wonder.
Dermot, this fucking music never ends. It's just standard default background. You're in town music.
All right. City hall. Let's go to city hall. Is there anything else up here that I need to do
that I didn't do? That's my favorite part. It's coming up right now. We got city hall, downtown.
So where should I be going? Pirates are attacking. Where are the pirates attacking from?
You're such a fucking elf. Big building. Police. Let's go to police station. Holy shit, this game
looks like shit. This game came out before you were born, probably. This game came out before you were
even alive. It looks different from the ones in the downtown area. This game came out in like 1998.
You were born in 1999. It looks pretty good if we're coming out in 1999. I'm not here to
spy. No, not me. With these pirates running around, I'm glad we have such a well-trained
police force. To the news. It's a newspaper. Let's see what it says. Flying ship crashes in
forest. No injuries reported. That's the last article. Not much happens here. No matter how
brave those pirates might be, they wouldn't attack the police station. Would they? I don't know.
Turns out your grandfather, Professor Barrell, is an old friend of the mayor's. I didn't know
he was such a renowned archaeologist. The cat is getting toxic and we have sub-only mode. Turn it on.
Turn it on. Our job as police officers is to serve and protect the people of Catalogues Island.
Only authorized personnel are allowed inside the office. Don't I have a citizen card for this shit?
Oh, they're cheating. They're using only authorized chat only. Or you gotta pay channel points.
Oh man. City hall? Is this a church or is this city hall? This is a church. Uh oh. Sorry, no
unauthorized entry allowed. Do you have a business here? Sub-only mode is meaningless. He's in a
meeting with the mayor. Please wait one minute. All right, turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off.
Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off. No, no, keep it on. Keep it on.
Keep it on. Make him waste all their points so I don't have to wink. Keep it on. Keep it on. Make
him waste all their points so I don't have to wink ever again. Hey, Mega Man! Yes. Here, let me
introduce you to the mayor of this island, Amelia. Amelia, nice to meet you. I'm an old friend of
Professor Barrell's. I worked as his assistant for a while. While I was in school. I don't have a
fucking backpack on. To tell you the truth, we've gotten reports that-
Keep it on. Keep it on. Make him waste all their fucking points. I was asking the professor if he
might have any idea what they're after. Anything thereafter the legend supposedly buried on this
island. There are a lot of stories about the treasure. Knows exactly what it is. I thought
maybe you might know something about it, professor. I mean, I'm not gonna lie. That's a pretty sick
creamsicle hair. But I haven't been able to find out anything about this island. I strive for that
every day. Except legends and myths. Fuck, Mega Man. I'll be here for a while talking with Amelia.
So why don't you go back and keep an eye on her? Tell her not to worry about me, okay?
Thanks to the five community subs at the Starfish. Congratulations to the winners.
What do you have to say? Sub only is useless. I know. Or, I mean, is it? This is a-
This is my equivalent to World of Warcraft letting you level up to 60 for like $5 or $10,
whatever it was. Wow, that ruined the whole game, didn't it? Holy shit. You could- You can buy-
You can pay like $10 and just level the fuck up to max level with a new character.
Holy shit. I forgot about that. What did they want me to do? I was- I was paying attention to the
tyrant that I am. Very Treasured is the legend that says it- that says if the seals are broken,
a terrible disaster will occur. Even if it's only a legend as mayor of this island,
I can't ignore anything that might threaten it. I'm going to stay here and talk with Amelia.
You take care of Role in case those pirates show up. All right, is it like any money in the desk?
Why is the chat sub only? It's a 9- 100 million IQ play to make people waste all their fucking
points and it's working. You're from out of town, aren't you? Are you a digger? Don't worry,
everyone here is very friendly. You may not know your way around yet, but you'll find that you'll
get along just fine. I don't have any problem. All right, I'm probably gonna get- I'm gonna get
cutscenes here in a second, aren't I? Yeah, here comes a cutscene. I'm like, what do you mean it's
a dog? Who is- am I pretending to be them or are they pretending to be me with the kind of
stretching up on the toes thing? Do I see the adults doing that? And I'm like, yeah, I did that
too. I don't know. Wow, he was trying to hit me. All right, um, let's go back. He went around.
He circled back. Hey, Frank, we didn't hit that fucking kid, did we? No, no, no, no, we didn't.
Turn around and fucking drill them. But it's true, officer. My paprika found a suspicious
looking girl. She must be a pirate. Please come here to check things out. I'm sure of it.
Okay, bye. We sell stuff only on- nice, keep it on. What's going on over here? What did you do to
upset my dog? What? What do you got? You got like- what are you- what are you- well, what are you
doing? I need to get like a bone or something. All right, well, should I say stop? Did I give
food to dog? You don't understand. I'll translate.
No, he didn't say anything after that. That was it. He just wanted to tell Megaman that he was hungry.
Holy shit. That was one of the worms from like a worm's armageddon. That's what they- that's what
they look like. I was trying to figure it out for the longest time. I haven't said anything yet.
But they have- they have worms faces. I was like, what the fuck do they look like?
I'm like the worms franchise. Sub chat is worse. All right, turn it off. Turn it off.
Break- like sub chat is worse. Turn it off. It's a junk store. No, I want to talk to this person.
Hey hippopotamus, what's up? We're always open for business no matter what. If we can do anything
for you, just ask. All right, now does that mean I can buy something? Yep. Ooh, 8,480
time currency. Whatever that is. All right, buy parts. Power razor. Ooh, range booster. Turbo
charger. Dude, I could get double power booster. Double power booster, I think I want to do.
Real wink. Why does it do that? All right, I'm doing double power booster. Give it to me. Power
booster. What about items? Life gauge. Adds one point to life gauge. What? Yeah. Ooh, I could do
that. Another one? Repairs damage- repairs damage to life shield. Used to restore life gauge. Can
be refilled. All right, no, the energy canteen. Extra pack adds points to the canteen. All right,
I don't want to use all my money. I'll get one more point to the life gauge though. Fuck. Shield
repairs damage to life shield. Adds points to get another canteen. Oh, god damn it. Another one.
God damn it. One more. And another one. Shield repair. Life gauge. Done. All right, let's get
up. Refill the canteen. All right, what about sell? Parts. All right, so. All right, hold on a minute
here. Sell this shitty power razor and equip the new one and keep the rapid fire on. Life gauge is
goodbye. Yeah. You get money so easily, don't sell it. No point in selling. It's not even any- oh.
Cool. Look at that. Look at that life. Nice. All right, let me, uh. Bust the parts. Equip.
Should I- all right. Power razor. Double power razor and just have a ton of attack? Or should I
cap- I think I'm going to keep that on for now. Double power. The rapid fire is not that fast.
Each person that says this game sucks, I'd like for you to delete their account.
You guys have dedicated mods. Can you do that? Mods. Mods. Mods. Mods. What do they sound like?
Omega. Omega man. Omega lol.
What? He's talking with the mayor at city hall. I hope he'll be okay. Did you see those weird
looking ships that just flew past here? I've never seen ones like that before. I wonder whose they are.
There goes one. No. Roll. That's just- that was just a projection.
Oh, there goes one. Uh. The fence is still in there.
Mega man, I'm going to go make sure he's all right.
I haven't eaten all day. You want the carrots in here? I'm useless unless I fucking eat. All right,
let's go. There's birds that are louder than the war going on in the city. Roll, hold on. Oh shit.
I'm sorry. I'm obsessive. Holy shit. This song. Oh my god. I- okay. This is where that song is from.
I- I tried to remember what this was and I'm not even talking about recently. I'm talking about
like two or three years ago. This. I was like what the fuck is that from? I hum it all the time.
You know when something just like snaps into your brain like that and you realize how much you cared
two or three years ago and now you just don't at all and you're like wow why did I care that much?
But cool. Now that I'm glad I know this. Yeah, this is the before the boss.
Oh my god. This is night. This is my I've had nightmares with this music in it and I've tried
to figure out what the fuck it was. That's what I know. That's what's going on. I've had nightmares
like we could fucked up dreams with this song was play in the background slower and like the
tempo was just decreased. Holy shit. This is fucking messed up like slower like oh my god.
This is insane. I forgot. This is kind of like I'm gonna have to like go.
Hold it right there. You can't go in there. This area is closed off. Please officer let us through.
And father's in there. You can't go in either. It's dangerous. How about this? We arm wrestle
and if I win in less than a tenth of a second I get to go in. Those pirates have attacked the
island. We'll find out. Just like they said they would. They're after the treasure that's supposed
to be buried here. Enough talk. You have to leave here now. Pirates. They've occupied the gate over
there. I'll take care of it. They're too heavily armed. We can't even get close to them. I can.
Maybe I can do something. Mega man I'm going with you. No role is too dangerous. Let me handle this.
All right you look out for gramps okay. Wait are you crazy? Wait where do you think you're going?
He didn't hear that. He was gone. The two different cops there. One cared one didn't at all.
But had to make it sound like he did in case he was somebody was around to witness it. I thought
it was bone. It's not trombone. It's tron bon. Why would it be bon? Why wouldn't it be trombone?
That is way more tron bon. No tron bon. Like a tron bon. Get the key to the gate. One of the three
serp bots has the key. They can pass it back and forth between them so you'll have to figure out
which one of them has it. Each of the three serp bots robots is unique and has different capabilities.
Red is built for combat. Blue is built for speed. And yellow is built for endurance.
Mission start. Oh that hurt.
Dodge. Where's the key? All right let's go for yellow. I'll go I'll go for blue.
Kill blue first. Blue's got speed. All right key. Thanks for the key. Mission complete.
Let me hook it. That was a first try. Easy. Okay I want to pick up the money.
Time. I can't take my eyes off you for a second can I? Just you wait till we get back. You're
in a lot of trouble. Oh no. What was that? Wasn't that the same boy as before?
He disabled the bloom bears by himself. I don't understand. Whenever I think about him I get this
funny feeling. Oh forget it. Who cares what this feeling is? It's all his fault. His fault.
How dare he? Does she like me? I'll teach him not to mess with me or my kids.
Here we go. Those are your kids? I thought you built them in a factory or something.
Thanks to you everything's a mess now isn't it? Aren't you the girl who's being chased by that dog?
Shut up. I don't want to hear about that. Do you know what you've done?
We do have a pretty good boy song in the background. You should have known better than
to pick a fight with the bums. Of course if you agree to become one of my servants I suppose
I could forgive you. What do you say? Think so. All right then forget you. Fine see if I care.
I gave you a chance and you turned it down. Don't come back crying to me later.
Oh now you've done it. Now you've done it. Now I'm fucking mad. Ooh I got no range. Go for the
legs first. No I got this. This is not it. No no I'm not saying it. This is that's not a correct
line. This is this is this is a giant enemy squid. Ooh that hurt. Cover the bombs. Giant
enemy squid. I like to run and shoot. Very useful. The Mario gal. Whoa that was violent.
No it's okay she just got daffy ducked. She'll be fine. I mean you're stronger than I thought.
Give you credit for that. Get in quick right. It's not over yet. Don't think you've won.
Next time I won't be so easy on you. I'll make sure you pay for this. Let's go.
See what would have been really funny would have been door closed and they cut inside and she goes
how are we gonna pay for this? I could have wrote this. No come on that's that's a perfect
kids show for the bad guy to be like next time we see each other you'll pay for this. Oh wow
scary. Door closed. Turn to the minions. Oh are we gonna pay for this? Really? You don't think
that like your 10 year old little brother would have laughed or little sister would laugh at that?
Of course they would. You don't have to think it's funny. Your your eight year old kid did.
That wasn't that's not for you. That's not for you. Indications are that the mysterious group
of pirates will continue its offensive for the foreseeable future. Recapping our top story of
the day at two o'clock this afternoon the city center was attacked by a group of unknown pirates
who demanded they be given the keys to the caves and tunnels underneath. Is that one behind you? The
mayor has refused to give in to their demands and is currently under siege alone in city hall.
Local police are helpless in front of the power of the pirates weapons. It may be only a matter
of time before city hall is destroyed. Hopes are rapidly fading as I've just been handed this update
viewers. It appears that the robots and machines being used to lay siege to the city have been
destroyed by a single young boy and now that same boy has come through the gate and is heading
towards city hall wait there he is interview i can see him he really is alone can this lone
hero save the mayor defend city hall the red robots will attack city hall while the yellow
robots will attack the nearest building protect the city the police station and the bank get this
on camera is this an enemy give that money shit hold on it appears the boy is is a little confused
he thinks the local trash compactor is one of the robots attacking the city
ladies and gentlemen the john deere tractor over there seems to be getting a lot of attention
you there all right i gotta fucking bombs all right you uh oh can i aim up that far
holy shit it's gonna grab me backseat reporter
i don't understand what's happening ladies and gentlemen i think he might be blind
can't what's wrong streamer blind i'm sorry megaman megaman blind i gotta attack the
no no the thing the thing that's flying around local boy is pretending all right where is this
thing it's up there how do i get up there kill kill that thing i don't know give let me get
control the game oh my god there's so many these my minds oh shit i have mines uh what button do i
use how do i activate those okay it's it's triangle all right i got i got that side secure
where's the thing flying around there it is can i reach it from here come on i'm out of range
no i can't i can't reach it wait that's the news oh shit
he's firing at us everybody get down he's deranged i'm gonna deal with the other buildings
ah get it ah ah don't kill the flying thing get kill that all right this is the one
okay come here you walk over it what about the mayor i got it there's only a couple more
this one's an idiot this one's just punching a tree we're fine i'm trying oh all right i
can't hold them i thought i could throw them come here all right we're good how many more just one
more oh he got the tree fuck fuck no not the fence not the plastic fence frog boss whoa oh
my god they're fucking homing they're homing i think i know what i gotta do to you oh boy hi all
right oh my god been around turn turn turn turn turn turn turn turn turn turn all right we're good
good a lot of bosses in this game just like three back to back here i guess we kind of
walked around and did nothing for like an hour so getting like three bosses in a row is kind of
welcome right it is mega man yeah or not
he decapitated that guy no i didn't that that was his whole body and brain he was screwed into a
fake body that was animatronic and shit like that was his actual body come on guys don't
you know anything about video games no i told them they were in charge so i won't worry i'll
let them take care of it themselves hey look at the clock it's almost time for my favorite show
i almost missed it next story city hall was attacked by a mysterious group of assailants
this afternoon but their offensive was beaten back by an equally mysterious young boy pictured
here on screen favorite show the news who the heck is that blue boy so bond was defeated but
what about drawn this is a potential disaster we could end up losing a lot of money on this one
all right it's obvious that i diesel bond will have to assume command who needs that key anyway
it might take some time and it might take some money but who cares i'll use my ultimate digging
machine the moral wolf to dig up the treasure myself and i won't let any little blue boy get
in my way either that was a great laugh wait a second bond's probably okay but what about
drawn i feel like it's talking about the same person tron is okay not bond is fine but bond
is tron tron is tron megaman you did it megaman let's go look for gramps tron and bond bond why
is it not bone tron bone on bone megaman roll sorry to give you a scare like that don't you
worry though i'm as healthy as i ever was that's a relief we were worried about you graham looks
like he's a statue actually with your help we were able to keep those pirates from getting the key
to the ruins thank you Amelia says she'll give us a digger's license as thanks for helping her
now we'll be able to look for parts to fix the flutter i know it's not much but it's the least i
can do for you you got a class a class be like excuse me your honor we got a new problem those
pirates have started digging up the northern forest what they weren't able to get the key
so they must be going after the treasure directly i'm amazed they'd go to that much trouble
even if they are criminals you've got to admire their persistence who knows what will happen if
they get their hands on the treasure inspector i want you to arrest them immediately yes ma'am
did we do it did we arrest them we'll have to make sure we get to the ruins
before the pirates do i'm sure they won't leave much by the time they're done
they're going to go to the ruins with a class b digger's license you can get into the ruins in
the cardan forest to the south and the ruins up north in the closer woods where the pirates are
now closer woods by role wait a minute oh you didn't talk to me i'm going with you look mega
man i fixed the car the junk shop owner gave us i may not have been able to get it fixed in
time to help you before but next time you can count on me car that you've said you're going
to fix up nice there goes the inspector color man off to get the pirates i wonder if he'll be
all right if they're using weapons like they did before the inspector might have some trouble
not to mention not to mention that the pirates are likely to steal everything if they get there first
well i think i better go help them be careful mega man i'll wait for you in the car we don't
get it i do is all the parts that you think might be useful bring them back to me i'll get them
fixed up and attach them for you right see you later what's wrong with your face nothing
the inspector is left to arrest the pirates i wanted to go too but it's just
as important that someone stays to guard the mayor you why are you parked like this that's
not a backpack he's buckled into his gamer chair so it doesn't look like a ride at universal studios
hey we'll show him just like we showed that officer we ain't gonna lose this time
oh yes you are
oh wow i could i could explode
i don't think okay yeah i think he was sleeping in that one behind me too no someone's led
now i might get up there give me that come on give it to me
okay higher good oh fucking i can't get up there you got you good how am i today i'm doing pretty
well everybody's in here nothing like this has ever happened in the history of this island the
police don't have any kind of weapons i can stand up to those pirates oh it's you those pirates
weapons are too strong we can't get close it'll only be a matter of time before they find the
treasure we got to do something but what can we do i thought i would be safe here but there's
nowhere to run they're everywhere maybe this is the legendary disaster that's supposed to happen
to the island what we never expected them to be this strong they're more than just run-of-the-mill
thieves can i not get up there let's go over here i need to upgrade my weapon this thing sucks
i don't like it i got the only attack on it i need more attack this is where i came from i have no
range well i'm just gonna grind some money 13.8 streamer omega low that's really good actually
that's like in the top 0.02 percent of people that have ever gone to that website that's all right
what's happening i can't shoot these guys i can't kick you out you can only kick when there's no
um to shoot take them i can't kick i don't have to kick i don't have to kick
crash nice 200 zenny and when this house can realizing how bad this house is
it's just a sink a door that leads it where's the bathroom is there even any kitchen in here it's
it's to block this is a shed yeah i think i can reach this now yep and chests up here
not really but i can go down here another trash let me go this way i got two at the same time
yeah i'm gonna get range i said get range you're you're very very smart oh i'm gonna die
okay what's that canteen button i actually to open the inventory okay uh normal items
broken cleaner special items energy canteen refractor found in the tower okay energy canteen
use one whoa i used all six slow down man you drank all six servings to drink one serving
he's thirsty don't drink them all you're gonna space it out can't jump that
this is a good money grind though cash i can go over here what's over here oh monkey
refill everything somebody said buck reddit okay um i don't know why you need me to see that i don't
own that website i have nothing to do with that web be careful recharge energy
allegedly allegedly i don't want to go in there yet i want to explore a little bit
high high sell low good advice this is hot where's this go oh it's a little
let me just check it out let's have to check it out this is chest right here
here
yep this one's actually a good edit no how it's the same picture that somebody's been
talking about the images we gotta talk about the images it's trapped
all right but is there anything is there something in it oh yeah there is a shit load of money in
here that was worth it there's a hole 1510 zenny i got a lot of money
that's patched up hole this is just like a little random dungeon this is actually pretty sick
oh i think i know what this is probably have to come back here later
but i mean i'm here might as well look there's a chest up there
all right let me get up there go to the ladder oh yeah ladder you're right
go to the ladder yeah that's cool what the fuck are you doing there's a ladder yeah i know
wait let me look the streamer is a cheater just checking to see if there's anything else in there
want to explore the whole thing on the ladder that you're talking about the big chest over there
there's lots of chests up here all right be careful damn it all right get over here come on
all right can i reach this by jumping yes i can wait don't be so hasty
what's in the chest cannon kit yep there's another one on the other side right
i thought i saw another chest i got a lot of money too no other chest no other chest
look it's right there it's so close i just want what's in it
give it to me i deserve it all right well i got a cannon kit what the fuck was that
we're gonna have to backtrack to get these yeah whenever i get this whatever upgrade it is to be
able to jump higher we're gonna use it although i'm gonna forget where all these are you can rocket
jump with a mine that doesn't need no it doesn't i'll why did i even listen to you for even us
and why would i even think to do that all right let's go save it again did i do everything in
here do i remember how to rocket jump like yeah if you put me in front of a computer right now
with a rocket jump mechanic like a soldier in tf2 i'd be able to do one decent crouch jump rocket
that's it just checking this perimeter okay so now we're gonna go into where the that monkey is
and do the mission what do i have now why do i want to pick this flower up i feel like i want to
okay you want a flower all right
remember you're the jeff bezo said megaman what what is that logic
okay you can hit them because you just can't lock on he's not smoldering pirates are digging
in here get in there quick you fucking killed him you killed him you killed him yeah sorry guys
i may have killed the guy that was driving the tank trying to shoot and kill me and other people
in the town sorry the guy was shooting missiles at me and other people that live here
music got him
he just got hit by his own thing i didn't have nothing to do with that murder murder murder murder
murder i dig it i dig and i'm still nowhere near the bottom maybe we will need that key after all
diesel he's coming all right everyone quick digging our priority now is to get rid of our
little blue friend all right and eliz be careful and don't be fooled by his size he's already
beaten barn and drawn let's do it oh he was doing two steps at once that was ridiculous
showdown with t-bone he must destroy the digging robot marlwulf the robot's outer shell is heavily
armored but the hatch is nearly defenseless treads to slow the robot down then jump on the robot from
the rocks and shoot at the hatch thanks but everything thanks for the wiki article to
describe it to beat him mission start
come on mega man
okay watch it watch it
stop open this fucking hatch here we go all right what does he think he's doing
there's shit everywhere give me help give me give me your life for it all right now shoot
i gotta go all i gotta climb up hold on why is it empty didn't i refill it
then as i get up on the like the what's the ledge or something wait i have to refill it at the shop
oh fuck i'm gonna die let me find a good spot to get up here first all right it's this one in the
back and then that puts me oh shit oh i almost jumped into it all right now can i get on
is he not destroyed uh can i jump on that hit the hatch
fuck i tried to jump it didn't work all right so i gotta get back up there i tried jumping
what i can't i can't grab on to the top of this thing these things are still chasing me too
i'm still like all right i made it go in can i go in look i gotta fall oh shit my save file is
fucking corrupted revenge so shoot his wheels he breaks down and then you climb up jump on his
back and then shoot him from some on his hatch
like restart because that start you must destroy the robot yeah hatch is nearly defenseless
the treads to slow the robot down then jump on the robot from the rocks and shoot at the hatch
that's what i was gonna do but i got fucking the guy came up with a bomb
all right let's go all the way back not this way up here
really other one was the other one okay get on the hatch and then shoot when the hatch opens
it Jesus okay give that help i want it oh okay what the fuck god damn it
shoot the hatch did i get it why don't you jump on the robot just shoot when it opens like this
god fucking camera tune in the hatch oh my god
fucking boy i'm trying to shoot the dude dodge roll all right shoot it open oh i fell off the
god damn stupid oh i have to mash and press as hard as i can on r1 and l1 to turn this
fucking camera i can't even mind oh my god it's a bomb other way why did i not get hit
it i need that range why didn't i get the range upgrade i got double power i should
have the i should have brain oh my fuck don't die here please work go run get these bomb bats
get the bomb back get that bomb back dude what the fuck
it's grabbed a ledge dude it's fucking doesn't you fuck okay god it just
why does some of them fall the fuck out of you you can't do it behind
i get it i get hit once i'm dead
you should have seen me in marvel vs capcom 2 with this little motherfucker i was pretty damn good
blue boy i'll get you time to go home oh okay okay once i have to do that all over again
there's no more tanks right okay um how do i get the hell out of here mega man can you hear me
wait the mayor says there's something real important she has to talk with you about why is
she in the tree can you come back here is she in the suit roger i'll head back to city hall
that doesn't sound like a radio that sounded like she was talking to a pillow
or like through a wall if only we'd known there was someone like him here in the first place
we won't fail next time we'll ambush concentrate our firepower on him we won't cut him any slack
just because we outnumber him that kid's going down just wait till you see diesel i've got a new
robot i've been wanting to build that'll do the trick that'll teach him this time
we get rid of blue boy for sure and get that treasure did they make a cartoon about this
mega man good going you showed those pirates who's boss it looks like a screen name doesn't
look like i'm mega man that looks like my screen name is mega man you've done so much for us
i hope this will convince those pirates to give up i'm afraid to think what might happen if
they get their hands on the treasure the legends say a horrible disaster will occur if it's ever
unearthed even if that's just a myth lately we've been detecting increased activity underground
the reaver bots are apparently activating of their own accord it has me concerned maybe there's
talk about we gotta talk about the images about a horrible disaster let's talk about the images
i wonder mega man would you be willing to explore the caves and dungeons on the island
and see if you can find anything why why does it say no to this that's pretty good
you will oh thank you so well this is back when video games had a no response to everything
and it always was no you won't how could you say something like that will you and then you just say
yes right like they used to do this i don't know why why would what was the point of that
old games did this all the time it was always they give you a yes or no question and then you
just said you would answer no and it would be like a one sentence joke and they would go back to yes
only the best diggers are able to get a class a license the best of the best with that license
you'll be able to get into the sealed off sites sealed off sites the ones those pirates have been
trying to break into i give you my permission to dig in the island's sub gates just let me know if
you find anything that can tell us about the treasure or that disaster that's supposed to
happen and i hate to mention this but if while you're digging you find anything of value it would
mean a lot to us if you could donate it to help with the restoration of the city
thank you again be careful can somebody give me a health potion i am i was stubbed toe away from
dying three different ways underground ruins called sub gates one is in the garden forest
where we crashed another is in a lake in the uptown area which is to the west of the city and the last
one is to the north in the closer woods which is where pirates just were i wonder which one you
should check out first um we'll go to the crash site where we actually crashed oh i want a bank
account too uh let's save save i smell a car joke um i mean that would have been bad it would have
been funny for a sec but then i would have had to do the entire boss over again and i'm i'm not i
don't want to no that's that's too far back we got all the dialogue to go through the cut scenes
no no no no not gonna happen all right talk to roll i have some equipment let me tell you about
what i can do for you yeah i look at first of all you can change your special weapons here
you can only use one special weapon at a time let me know when you want to switch
also it costs a little money but we can enhance your special weapons here
is item development i might be able to make something new out of things you find
in the ruins find something interesting we should bring it back here last we can use the support
car to move around the island nice fast travel capcom thought of everything here i made a walkie
talkie for you can use to call me anytime use it when you want me to pick you up in the support car
i can now give the walkie talkie back and make it into a weapon there's a few places i can't get
the car won't be able to pick you up even if you call me sorry okay uh item development okay i'll
take a look the cannon kit was used to make powered buster special weapon this weapon has
a really long range in a pretty good punch but it's great a fire isn't that great don't forget
that when you get into a fight don't forget what oh don't forget that all right any more item
development what about um okay special weapons change weapon splash mine powered buster
let's try it here you go enhance weapon first choose a weapon powered buster what do you want
to enhance oh man all right how about uh i can't enhance any how about it let's like how much money
21 000 1 3500 zenny that car do it again 11 000 that's a lot of money ammo make it even more range
okay even more all right all right stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop i'm going to use
all my i don't want to use all my money cool all right let's go uh take a support car downtown
we're here how's the game the game's awesome i love this game it's got it's got quite a kick
uh where's the junk store south right
he loves it people happy just it's real it's just fun to go to the bank i will eventually
let's upgrade my body okay bye item another life gauge uh jacket reduces damage by one
fourth repairs damage life shield yeah this too um okay hold on parts last unit okay hold on super
what is that's energy range two energy one pack one energy two range two energy two
uh super sniper unit right well i want to get this one give me that one give me the sniper unit too
i'll put these both on and uh i can afford another pack i do another pack and they have another one
refill the canteen cluster parts so we have plus one attack we'll do last unit uh keeps the one
attack but adds energy and then i can get the power razor replace this with the more i need
the range so bad i don't lose any attack or anything so yes i do fuck energy and range
i'm losing a lot of attack though i'll keep it for now special items yeah good
busted hearts energy means more shots at a time so that's more dps that's more dps i'll take it
you can't nah all right come get me special weapons special weapon status arm normal arm
infinity oh okay um come get me i know you're right down the street but come get me
now let's go to let's go to carton forest take the game charge everything up so i have to go back
to the crash site let's check this out let's see how it looks how it looks whoa one two three four
five six seven seven shots and it's much higher range too and a big gun cool
all right recharge me out you killed that guy i did not he's fine all right we're looking for a
dig a site thought i'd come out here to look at the sub gate but i can't get anywhere near it
with those pirates running around these are some loud ass birds somebody said it when we first
started playing new it's seriously it's looking for a sub gate what does a sub gate look like
it's not bad right i mean it looks like it could be a sub gate but haven't we gone in here before
i was looking for mushrooms on the other side of the passage when a tank rolled up out of nowhere
i'm getting out of here that was quick holy shit that was fast
okay everybody on your toes let's show miss tron what we can do
what do you want to do continue on
no no no get out of here roll get out
do much if you get in trouble get inside the car okay get out of here the magic school bus
is not going to help us against the tank almost there what i love having the extra jobs
if you're in trouble use the car as a shield roll use the car as a shit was a payload
all right we're almost out to this first checkpoint this i'll get too much damage
i want rapid fire i feel like it'd be more useful to me the cart has almost reached the final
this thing moving got it get the hot points stupid this is a great game
some would argue one of the best team fortress 2 is the simpsons of uh of the rainy shooters
at this point there's a fence they everyone took food now they did it first everything
payload they did it class-based shooter they did it opening boxes they did it oh we did it victory
new area it's a new zone oh this is an ice zone what will this watch over that item over there
what chat what chat what do i do here fucking chat you know what i mean
can you hear me megaman can you hear me yeah i'm picking up high energy readings from close by
it looks like it's a refractor and a big one too i can't i'm not gonna be able to take this
is the refractor shielded most high level refractors are protected in some kind of shield
you'll have to look for the control console and deactivate the shield
thank you for the info hamster in my front pocket nothing it looks like the starter is missing
it's probably hidden somewhere nearby you'll have to find it
remember there might be more than one starter key too more than one key all right we're gonna
activate the refractor they got super powered super charged up fighting abilities
and look at this range i don't think that ai doesn't start and i win oh my god that's a lot
of money that's a lot of cash those are just treasure boxes holy shit right where's this
last one where are you there's one more flying around right i'm in look at i'm being seen
where is it no no no i thought i could jump to it no oh it's a bridge here okay damn it
that's a lot of money it's okay you can leave and come back yeah but that i don't still i'm still
upset about it i'm allowed to be upset about something that horrible it just happened to me
me let me get back up here my itchy eyes
god damn it no i thought okay you have to die now i'm stuck here
how much health do you have all right i have my powers i have really low power i have low attack
right right right i forgot can i get up there from here i gotta pee yeah i gotta pee
there we go now the next opportunity i take uh yeah let's go i'm gonna take a peek i'll be right
back you guys in a minute i'm gonna grab a water too might as well okay i've been back for
maybe a minute two minutes i've just been spying on you just kind of seeing what you guys are
writing when you know i'm not here interesting stuff uh my favorite one was uh derma sits in
the bathtub to go to the bathroom like with water or i don't know what you mean by that
i'm always watching i always have eyes oh ah that's how you do it
so
i thought this was an urn i had to get down also uh don't mind my my chewing sounds sorry
i'm gonna try to keep it as discreet as possible i've got a absolutely delicious
bag of craved chili lime deep jerky some would say the best where's the ramp where's that ramp
don't choke on it this time well i didn't choke on it last time i aspirated it into my lungs
oh it was a slight difference oh fuck any more britches i want to get up there though all right
whatever let's go because the cannon dude is a big explosion
what's this what's that do what's this uh there's buttons hold on let me check out over here first
remember the first time you went on a dig mega man i wasn't used to being a spotter and you ended
up getting lost underground for three days remember yeah i remember i didn't have any food either that
was great it was fun i don't know what i would have done if you hadn't been there that's something
we laugh about now the fact that i was starving to death for three days well i'm glad you can enjoy
it oh shit this ice open it what what wait my goodies what's gonna happen will it open it
is this gonna open it uh wasn't gonna go through the smasher oh nice all right there's a crusher
all right i could be ready
i need one more reverse it oh so it goes the other way how long is the game um i don't know
it says like seven-ish hours so hold on a sec there's another one in here
sounds i can make without making noise with my mouth
it's longer than a typical mega typical mega man typical i'm gonna say this typical mega man game
um anything can i go i want to go back like this i'm missing holes in walls you're right
fuck you're right you're right you're right you're right you're right right i'm missing a lot of holes
all right if i felt the i yep grenade kit i didn't even look all right what about over here across
the way just don't fall through the ice just walk over it normally you're fine big bit big bits
let's check on the big bits we had five thousand fifty dollars from bit slave again
it's late just gave a hundred dollars today ten thousand fucking bits reviewing the johnny walker
best uh best spring set was that uh they say now hey germa since i started watching your streams
you helped me get through some of the worst times of my life doesn't look like there are any big
reaper this day i can say that watching your pods really helps me you better stay on your toes
also uh being in the air force means i meet some of the best people in this country has to offer
but at the same time it means i must bid farewell to them and never see them again
i've met some of the greatest friends i had i met some of my greatest friends and had to say
heartbreaking goodbye to them within a single year you are therapy to me thank you so much
for this message i i um i actually know somebody who's in the coast guard and they have
they're always moving around every like three or four years they move and they kind of have to
say goodbye to everybody that's in their life and change uh essentially their whole life again
and meet new people and stuff every couple of years so i'm not sure exactly what you're
referring to here but it's i i could never imagine doing it so thank you for doing it
because i can't imagine doing it and if you can come and watch the stream and it's something that's
familiar or fun or whatever that's that makes me happy i'm i'm glad that this stream is something
that you can get out of it thanks a lot for your huge support and thank you for serving the country
you can't escape us turbo what what do you think i'm trying to escape play the game
jerk breather i'm eating jerky right now come on this is i'm trying to get new strategies people
made fun of my baby food so i'm trying to eat like a real a real steak dude you eat baby food
no i don't this is beef jerky yeah do you like me an old bone here link looks like i'm i'm like
dipping tobacco i promise i'm not three buttons doing a certain order it's another energy barrier
i'm getting the same kind of readings as before yeah do you see a switch anywhere nearby i do
all right we're gonna go uh what's the one on the very end purple that's how you do it
got the last key that's it now you should be able to access the console
uh
monkey s trapped monkey s he's trapped do i make my own monkey s like you know i mean here well this
is an emote oh yes uh uh mr trebek i'll take uh ways to stall so he can put more food in his
mouth for 100 please thank you i want to get up there oh no that was okay i was already there
you're eating expensive meat i just i like this brand dude just buy a slim jim just buy a
an ultra slim jim they're like a dollar at the gas station no no i don't want to eat like i don't
want to eat that this is my brand some people wear like louis vuitton sneakers i eat crave
chili lime beef jerky this is the wrong way why are you addicted to advertising is it advertising
if i'm just recommending what if this is just me recommending something i'm not advertising i'm
just recommending something is that an ad is it if it is i'll take if it is i'll take it back
hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait hold on here's the thing though i've never been
paid to tell you guys anything like this only me has i'm i'm i'm advertising to you nobody else
has threw me i've never been paid to advertise to you guys i just do it for me because i it's i'm
advertising to you right you can't lie about that germa monka s i've i've never done a paid
stream before ever not one time literally literally and i mean that word like i know literally
literally it's never happened once so i mean what do you want me to say i've never done a paid
stream when i've never accepted money for a stream we'll go brain fluid that's my company
don't touch it use gloves oh he has gloves on never mind he's fine nothing's happening what
so i got i got it all right sometimes when i eat chili when i eat chili lime from crepe
i uh i have to sneeze does that happen anybody else i i mean i people think i'm making that up
see why does it happen is it one in your nose uh you're allergic
oh it's a yellow refractor and a big one good going mega man we can use this to power all sorts
of things well it's a nice small little fix to the flutter but i wonder what we can use it for
let's think of something we can do with it super voice no no no no no that that's radio car
commercial voice the grenade kit was used to make grenade arm oh it's grenade bombs if a bomb hits
a wall it will bounce off so be here rat s rat s mega man i came up with something the spring
set was used to make jumped springs interesting this time springs that will increase your jumping
power now you'll be able to get to all sorts of places you weren't able to get to before
be sure you put them on okay let me take a look at that weapon this is that one where's the
grenade lunch normal arm splash mine grenade arm kind of let me try it i try it no i already
have this good one on i mean i got the i upgraded this one three times do what you want laughing
my ass off okay i'd like to have another piece of my crave chili lime beef jerky how much do you
think that okay so i'm doing that for free right now how much do you think it would what would it
cost to be paid by a company to do that am i missing out on a bunch of money or something
should i like do that am i missing out on there's a bunch of money how much money am i missing out
on 10 000 literally thousands unironically thousands of dollars flower it's a nice flower
you got there you can have it unironically thousands of dollars but who gives a shit uh you
save the what do you mean save it but do i what if i want to give it to roll this is for real no
give it to tron i'm giving it to roll no i like roll i like roll i'm gonna give the flower to roll
no i to try i'm getting like angelica vibes from tron rugrats you're like the no no no no no
i want to hey we're good friends and we're gonna be co-workers that's fine this is your sister
i can't i can't give like a flower to like of your sister what are you talking about
no there's more than one flower on earth there's different roses for different things
right okay carnation let me see carnations carnation meanings light red carnations
represent aberration dark red is deep love white carnations represent good luck right
this is this different kind what does it have to be a red rose we're talking about
i've never heard of this how have you never heard of a different carnations different
flowers mean different things or different occasions what just discussed that for a little
you know you're making shit up you guys never heard of that you guys because like
the gent the zoomers aren't buying roses figure it out done what are you doing out here
hi i can't go in and do any digging there's a big fence block in the entrance
do you see it fence is gone dude what really that means i can go use my class b license
and do some digging class b what you mean i can't get in with a class b license oh
oh shit it's just been pretend all along people are pretending to die all right where's the other
one the other one was in um i need give me the car car uh what was the other one uptown is three
right uh downtown uptown so how do you get call me insane for this i don't uptown versus downtown
like what does it uptown even mean what does that even mean i don't even know what the fuck that
means uptown we're gonna go uh west does that just simply mean north is that all that means
is that all it means it means a wealthy area rich area uptown is fancy i mean fancy maybe
but pretty poor music choice not very good music choice midtown we've been waiting for you you're
one of the contestants for our hit show dangerous games aren't you let's see which event are you
signed up for beast hunter balloon fantasy i'm on balloon fantasy need to go to studio number seven
have fun our next challenger is megaman volnut megaman's name is volnut david volnut what are
the rules you release a lot of balloons into this room and your job is to see how fast you can shoot
and pop the red ones be careful you don't pop the blue ones if you do your time goes down
you win if you can pop all the red ones within the time limit there are four different ranks
and as you win your rank will go up higher your rank the shorter the time limit you win at the
highest rank you'll win a prize good luck pretty good like hey arnold emotes don't oh don't make
hey arnold don't say that jeremy people will be yelling you and hate you for making a hey arnold
reference i forgot about that your time is 16 seconds you did it six six six six thousand
zenny nice let's try again 18 seconds you did it you went 2 000 zenny right again 16 seconds i
gotta wait for good rng here now wait i thought you no you don't lose you don't lose i thought
you lost instantly okay i did it three thousands any last time try again 12 seconds you do it again
you do it again okay that rng there was two blue ones right from oh it was right behind me
good start what i fucking had it if it wasn't for the blue one yeah look at this rng over here
good come on really oh it's right behind me did i do it yes congratulations you win mystic orb
is that it do i do it again yeah i went so that was fucking much better than last time
what do i get 42 50 zenny nice all right i'm done with that one let's take the orb back to a roll
waiting for you you're one of the contestants i am dangerous games i'm signed up for beast hunter
i have to kick a ball oh no i'm gonna be here a while
megan and walnut do you want to hear the rules yes i do kick a ball at the dog chasing the man
there and see how many times you can hit it your number of hits is better than the par you win
start at rank d and you keep going and harder and harder the power will go uh
okay instructions might kick left kick are 10 how many times there's a hit 10 hits
wait why did this take that dog all right i get it i get it i understand
do i be kicking the dog it runs by all right again let's let's do it again oh i can put i can put
like spin on it i get it oh fuck what the hell oh boy oh god this is fucked up it's all right
that's fucking that's really really really huge all right this i don't like this one at all
oh don't pro tip do not rotate at all don't move at all oh that would have been like quadruple
points your score is 14 you did it thousands in it all right try it again this is 12
we hope i want you to go faster faster you go the easier it would be for me to do
oh thousand try to get our 14 he's got it you got to lend the dog on the dog that runs by
and then you pretty much can win got to get it right though all right that was quick but i got
it pretty good pro tip considering i probably actually don't have to move 3000 do it again all
right here's the big prize 16 i got 18 last time should get it again 16 one more all right
we're looking for this one you win a zet saber let's do it one more time to get the money
uh zet saber is zero oh what do you think like 5000 zen right four thousands any
ladies and gentlemen megaman you did it thank you for playing megaman all right well i got two new
items but what do you do want to see the high scores for each game it's gonna be both times
don't worry i'm thinking about making a new program about racing i just need to find somebody who can
run fast what a sonic the hedgehog movie there are several different shows being shown at the
same time the world where the stuff on tv is worse than the game looks on playstation 1 oh
geez rick looks like we've got some really great come on don't do me like that come on
come on come on i know it's the voldemort of tv shows and you don't say i know but come on
come on this is catalogs hospital we don't get many patients actually everyone on the
island's pretty healthy it's a tv it's you you've never seen yourself on tv before what
oh it is me i mean it was the atari golf version of me but it's still me cool it's a newspaper
let's see what the headlines say mysterious blue boy awarded class a digger's license brings back
refractor from forest everything's about me i'm the biggest thing this town hopefully that wasn't
they go in the back i'm sorry but you can't go inside without checking in
the reception desk all right i need uptown right am i am i in uptown 800 zen broken propeller
weird thing to find in the trash okay i'm in up dog oh wait what what what what is up dog by the way
vending machine no it still works nothing in there what's down there
i'd say toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat almost had it whatever i
had it three times willie's boats did you hear what happened someone stole all the boats here
now the only one left is an old broken down one no people didn't steal all the boats what's happening
is that they're you know fine just leave i won't even explain it to you oh no this fence is keeping
us kids out hello german chat what's up the model of a boat you won't be able to use this
need a boat normally you could take your pick but we don't have any boats right now sorry
need a boat just kidding we don't have any of those a lot of trout out there in the lake
customer the docs out that way you won't find any boats there heard someone's stolen all the boats
need a clip that's an old one all right no boats there someone's gone to stall all my boats
i've only got one left it's broken won't be much use to you
grandma i think the boats are all gone all you needed to say sound
where's this i'm in uptown right i'm not even in uptown all right a good self this is uptown
what is c oh that's e down is this uptown finally a free drink what is a wink what's this the door
is locked what's happening here this is a computer game school i'm going to go here and learn how to
make really cool games like resident evil computer pog all right i'm leaving i'm leaving roll i have
items for you to look at who let that girl play resident evil all right development what do you
got for me no what what are those two items used for jumps rings i have mystic orb toy sword old
bone missed where's the gate can i look at this looks like someone's drawing the hospital and
its surroundings something's missing what's that voice action what do you think i should have
some talent what did you just say
there's red rose of red i said talent did you just say what i think you said
could you repeat that yeah i said talent that's what i thought just kidding can i have the item
that you're gonna give me something's missing what do you think i should have i'm red i'm fresh
out of red which is why i haven't been using it but i suppose it is a little dry but there's
nothing wrong with this cold rock either the red paint how do i use the jump springs are they just
on you have to do something special the jump springs okay there we go oh my goodness that's huge
this is huge all right i'm going i'm going not east i need to go i'm where am i going
i'm just gonna go anywhere else there's no gate here i'm looking for a sub
gate thing oh fuck i just jumped up a whole building wait wait wait wait get back up there
what all right guys i don't i don't think this exists it doesn't exist i'm out
the fence where the boat is jump the chest in that cave yeah yeah yeah i know i will
just ran over a kid want to make sure you're aware of that you just want to make sure that
you know that you just ran over a child all right roll let's get out of here take me to
where the hell do i want to go it said up down right i already did the card ruins
the data yeah i did yeah yeah i had to do it i'm sorry what should i do now what are you going
to use the yellow refractor for let's think of some way to use it remember the sub gates aren't
the only ruins on the island have you been inside any of the others i think so i knew a digger as
good as you wouldn't miss them did you find anything good inside losing control of the
steering wheel dance now that looks very that looks intentional to me that's like here we here
we here we go and then you rip to the right and then the car goes um all right so what do
i do with the yellow refractor what the hell am i supposed to do give me back to downtown
all right let's talk never mind broken motor broken propeller broken motor can i fix one of
these boats do i need anything else kick the garbage bins jerma roll can you fix this stop
stop stop tried uh item development propeller in a come on broken motor broken propeller and broken
cleaner used to make the vacuum arm this arm's a little different you can't use it to attack with
but you can use it to easily gather up scattered refractor shards this that's horrible
i don't want this it's the farming arm please use this to clean up your car i could go back in here
was it down here this is the original dungeon right right i'm right aren't i right munkah asked
me right now what this is where i need to be right isn't there a way to go wouldn't there a thing i
could do in this dungeon don't rat-ass me right now
so high level for this
tis this the way i haven't explored it yeah this is it tons of money
new place rain world of waiting room no nope nope nope no no no it's trapped
i wish i had that vacuum i haven't been in here but let's explore elderborn waiting room no
one day i'm just gonna turn the stream on and i'm gonna be in a fucking actual doctor's office
waiting room and then what the hell are you gonna say what are you gonna say to that
oh waiting waiting doc waiting room waiting room oh no it doesn't compute that's all that's in here
kidding me that's it
i feel like sometimes i feel like i'm your guy's mother at dinner
this is what we're eating today i made peas carrots and chicken breast
mcdonald's waiting room this is what we're doing this is what we're eating today
no cheese and shells waiting room uh sun and cheese and carrots and soup
can't have macaroni and cheese every day you can't have cheese and shells every day
can't have pizza every single day and sometimes sometimes i don't even understand some of your
recommendations or things you want to see a brick of velveta uncooked waiting room
why do you want to eat that you don't want to eat that if you do then you're fucking crazy
you're gonna you're gonna have diarrhea for a month imagine digesting a brick of uncooked
like just velveta cheese a whole brick no no i'm not talking about the single serve ones i'm
talking about the family size the one that looks like a joke gold bar from the old movies more
items not this shit more to explore
eat velveta on screen you know i'll give you a quick little story all right so
kim and i made macaroni and cheese one night in quotes from scratch right we didn't get out of
a box we got a bunch of velveta we got some other cheeses we got elbow macaroni and we got some
spices we're gonna make it was like a little date let's make our own mac and cheese great
and you guys don't know about velveta i'm that's gonna kill me well it will if you eat too much
but i'm talking about the game um velveta is so heavy and so thick that when you're hungry
and you make macaroni and cheese with velveta you always are like you know what fuck it let's
put half the brick in yeah yep that's what i want to do don't do that don't put in oh my god
oh my god oh my god oh my god dead oh he's killing everything he's coming back he's coming back he's
coming back he's coming back he's coming back he's coming for me oh the fuck is that move dead oh
oh my fuck i freaked him out is he still alive got it the big ones at least okay that was
fucking crazy all right the cheese right so if you use more than a half a brick of velveta
it's really tempting because you just plump it in there and it's melts but that shit turns
into cement wait and when you start to mix it up and it starts to lose some of its liquid content
it turns into this thick cement like substance it's it's crazy how just too much it is
fuck you germa i have fucking mirror spell on tonight you know what that means link wink and
wink wink and wink wink and wink wink and wink wink and wink i can't even what hold on okay this is
that's it i was putting in cylinder fan i that actually happened that's why links are going away
no they're going to be concentrated in a central location that's going to be easy to pull up
secret
that little rabbit what's a little rabbit oh whatever it's dead winks or links both
he's gonna be a regular boring streamer now that just goes
gaming veers veers big jump this place is huge i gotta get explore all of it every last piece
and no mom i'm not going to bed he still hasn't figured out what to do with the boat
well i've only been there once let's go um down let's go i'm gonna sneeze again
go to bed jeremy mom says no i'm not going okay
get off that computer right now
mom's just never got it right like i can't stop i have to get to this i can't pause the game i
can't stop anything i'm gonna lose like two hours of progress mom you don't get it
i don't care how far you are you've got school tomorrow that game can wait i'm less 10 000 bucks
oh you're killing the bunny stop wait i'm back over in this dungeon how i could jump from there
all right was there anything in this place that i could jump to this place is huge
holy shit it's been four hours yeah i mean i'm okay i need some um i need some anecdotal
herald elbertson 985 thanks for literally stealing and leaking my entire name
appreciate it um anytime you guys sit in there about to talk or if you have something to say
or you're in a conversation anybody ever do this you don't say anything yet you kind of just
hanging out and you make this weird noise where you go does that happen to anybody else you go
like yeah yeah i was probably tomorrow afternoon yeah i think so or it's even higher than that it's
like okay good thank you stop
oh
you're a psycho i saw at least 10 people say yes
those are all germa alt accounts they got me it's my posture i'm like i have to have my posture has
to be fixed i have this right there i have a brace on that means no i was already up there
and definitely i'm wearing a brace that makes it so i can't now i'm lost in here
it wasn't this way this is i gotta get out of this over here uh yeah the brace that i'm wearing
it means i can't physically put my shoulders forward i can't it'll be tension on my back and
chest and stuff and stomach
and it also puts a little bit of pressure underneath my rib cage which
makes me feel a bit better roller board you're just strapped into your boomer seat
so we can go we went this way let's pack it back up and go up let's go
all right so when i did this because remember i this my ps2 is going through a capture card
which is then upscaling it to 1080p right i have a device that does that for that operation to
happen it takes about one full second so i just got terrified because on my left monitor there's
a small pre there's a preview window over here at the stream so when i went like this
i almost two full seconds later i thought my other monitor blue screen
i was like what the fuck is going on it was very very scary
that happens a lot that shit happens all the time
especially when i'm playing uh an old console that has to go through the capture cards
so
i slenderman myself yeah all right what have we got chest here
just on the other side too all right well how do i get over that way i make the jump it's two
chests over there you kidding me here we should do a making pasta stream i don't know how to make
buster unit let me just think i know how to make pasta
oh i open up the box of the straw of the what could be hay and boil it for seven minutes
you said you made it from scratch 15 no i mean kim did not make elbow macaroni from scratch
i thought i'd blue screen again i'm saying like we made macaroni and cheese from scratch not
because most macaroni and cheese is out of a box you know you get the crap you got like
cracker barrel you know you just mostly make it out of the box
you guys make your own elbow macaroni pasta you don't you guys roll out your own pasta every no
some of you guys aren't even old enough to drive okay no way you were making your own
pasta from scratch i'm 24 you're old enough to drive no it's not even old enough to get your
license 25 you can see these fucking psychos that are on our roads your own damn pasta
make your own pasta so you're good for you roll up the dough and now you're telling me you make
your own pizza dough too no you don't you go to fucking dominoes like everybody else does
i don't care if i don't care what your tinder profile says you don't do that
awesome come on bounce it only has to rise once pizza dough is so easy
lazy millennial make my own pasta every time you make your own bread too no it doesn't count if
somebody made it already in a bread maker and you eat it yes it does no you didn't make it what you
can't hold on i i make my own bread is not the same as i eat the bread that somebody else made
it a bread maker that's not what you didn't make it you didn't do it what is a bread maker
it's a thing that you i don't know it's the box that sits on the
but you know you can't you didn't build that oh you guys are making me fucking laugh
what do you mean what's a bread maker it's the thing you make bread in
makes what do you roll what is this like the fucking 1400s you making bread about like hot
coals your backyard no you guys definitely make bread and it rises so you guys are fucking awesome
they're trying to say oven dodge right there making bread in the microwave oh my god
put the dough in the pan and put the pan in the oven i bet you i bet your bread is real
gross i'm just kidding i'm just kidding pen lights all right no more no more gas lighting all right
i'm done no more i'm done you can't insult chat's imaginary bread we gotta do a public apology
hi guys so a lot of you may have been aware of some of the things that i may have said
on stream recently um i really don't mean that i didn't mean that at all i talked about if those
of you don't don't i talked about uh my one of my chat members read and i said it was probably
gross and i don't know anything about that person's bread i was frustrated with the video game i was
playing i said in direct quotes you have gross bread and i got a lot of flak for it and i just
want to say um sorry i guess i mean i apparently did today we're mad about it um yeah i just kind
of want to go back to uh the kind of way it was beforehand and i'm very sorry uh so we'll see you
next time on stream thanks for everything i'm really close to the camera yeah i guess either
you are you are too the music's still playing i forgive you thank you i'm glad i'm glad
your mic volume whatever keep the music no what apology rejected
well here we are again i just want to say on the bottom of my heart that i'm very sorry about
the sorry that i did before that it wasn't up to the state or that i should have done it and
if you you know like speak remember that we'll go we're going back to that a speed video is coming
out like tomorrow uh maybe we'll can move on after that use of the speed video that's coming up
tomorrow um thank you everybody for your support i want to say i apologize again for all the things
the nasty things i said about that person bread and uh i'm very sorry better but that's better
right like if everything's better now everything is better apologize to the bread i didn't even
mean to do that i'm gonna die all right no more bread jokes no more like apology bread jokes
uh i haven't saved in like an hour this would be really bad if i died here i don't have any more
god damn it this is bad how could i be all out of of gerbil water how could i be out of it
you better not be lying about me oh yeah i did say that cue the music again
anything on this side that i didn't see ah there's this old shield holy oh my god i love all the
little secret little trinkets that are in this game waiting for that shi video tomorrow no that
was like a fake thing it was a joke video that was a joke that was doing for the screen
there's no there's no video coming up that was a joke that was a that was a little
you're on camera right now look around you yep you're on camera it was a joke for the stream
and yep you're on camera you got pranked there's one there behind two die already
okay let's get back up here i've not gone this way yet i need help i can't do any more exploring
without more health this is just dangerous to do this this is a bad idea i'm gonna get tapped
once by these am i gonna screen the sequel the the sequel is in a case directly behind me
i own megaman legends 2 and the answer to that question is absolutely yes
absolutely tractor shard 780 but you're gonna stream the sonic movie from your phone
thank god for the health oh my god i'm gonna die i need to i have to leave
oh let him through let him first he probably all right now i know it's not safe it's not safe
it's unsafe now now now now run now run now run now run now run now run now run now
i'm alive right okay bye i'm leaving get the fuck i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm going home
uh i'm going home i'm going home i'm going home this time it's gonna leave i'm just gonna go
in the way i'm gonna call roll and say roll come pick me up i'm done with uh the exploring
oh my god there's something in this room there's two things in this room please drop health
please drop health please drop health please don't shoot at me drop health okay it was fun
when you dropped health when you don't shoot at me and you dropped health that was really fun part
of the game you drop health that was fun when you did that what the hell no no health okay
i don't even i don't know how to get out of here i don't know what the way to go is
which way is it best way through that i don't know how to get over to the left left and up or
around through this tunnel left and up the tunnel no it's not that is it through the tunnel this
shit in this tunnel there's stuff in this tunnel there's an enemy in the tunnel
all right this doesn't i know there's an enemy in the tunnel this is the thing all over again
where is it
okay holy fuck i thought i thought from my perspective was weird
what why is he here why is he in here what what the fuck why is that guy in here
i thought i was dead on the first hit and then i got back up and
oh no i was like 45 fucking minutes ago oh my god i why is that guy still in there
and he's he's bond right he was he was it he was right next to me oh this is so bad this is so bad
that was at least 30 to 40 straight minutes oh come on come on i don't even have to boots
equipped that's how you know how long ago that was oh fuck that enemy what's it doing in there
it's like the boss that takes 5 000 hits and he's and he's right next to me and i oh i'm so mad
what the hell that's so stupid that's stupid stupid stupid stupid stupid stupid stupid stupid
he was a boss the guys know the bosses don't respawn and now i gotta go through all this
shit again and i had all those items i don't know what everything even is
what the bunnies jump get me out of go go to left i probably wouldn't even go on the right
oh that's so frustrating 10 000 i was here for like a fucking hour mate i was here for an hour
so it didn't have anything okay i tried to leave but there's only one there's only one fucking way
to leave these goddamn places genuine despair yes sucks i'm so sad that i have to do this again
i'm gonna i'm gonna miss one of the items i know it i'm gonna fight that stupid asshole again
i'm gonna fight that stupid asshole again
i'm just picking up chests
a chest that i missed no shit millennial enraged
no this sucks
oh you can call it whatever you want this is this is bogus
i got cool items too i was going to go back and return in and i can't even do that now and now
i'm rushing to try and get through this crap why does this do 50% of your health why now this
mother this fucking green crab guy is gonna chase me the whole way down rapid fire barrel that's
so cool like i wish i had the other stuff keep an eye for the holes in the walls yeah i collected
almost all of them in the pre meltdown run and i'm just running bio cannon on that wall i need a
drill for that okay i have to go through this again don't i this is bad oh shit i have to do
this again just avoid getting hit i didn't even know i could stop here i didn't think there was
enough room i'm so mad i'm holding it in everything's fine all right i need to find that
shield and i'm gonna go do the boat thing that sounds like a plan right
but did somebody just write tf2 waiting room like six years later
i'm waiting a long time bad upload speed
oh give me my shield there it is yes all right now get me the hell out of here
no this is where this guy is is it wait okay i remember this part
all right this hole's in here didn't kill him in one hit bro you gotta make me some new shit
there was something in here right tiny object all right i'm almost got them all
was there anything else down here i don't remember i think there was just give me the big one all
right just you we're just here to watch and suffer did you even say that what did you write
what did you just write what did you write can i get somebody to read that back please
so i have to try on bone game i do not have to try on bone game i actually didn't even know
that a game existed flip him flip him he said you should have left the stuck robot getting hit to
suffer what the hell what a psycho oh my god that's horrible even more shit two dollars on ps3 right
now are these games even all i you can only get this on playstation 2 right
you can get this on psn as well it's pretty cool
pen light got it there's an n64 is there really wait why do i think that that's not
bullshit i've done everything i can do time to leave i got the pen light got all the stuff
at full health i don't need to get upset about anything we're just gonna go go go go go we're
just gonna go go go go go gonna get upset he's gonna get upset here it comes all right left left
here it comes if they laugh here it comes the roller board though wasn't down here
what was the roller board no i got it didn't know that was the first thing i got
yeah i have it buster unit that was the one i didn't have all these all right i'm okay relax
because i could never happen
that's it gets things done around here
okay time to get up let's get out of here the adventures of trombone
wait let's check over here i see a ladder nice ah yes okay call the taxi
what is that that's stone calls jay boston
okay all right roll make some items go rapid fire barrel was used to make
buster part machine gun i shoot a lot of enemies at once nothing else
let's check it out please save the game i got it man hit the game i'm dying i i got it
you lied about no more heroes too no i didn't i haven't played it yet all right um i want to
let's go back to town take me to downtown i want to go buy some upgrades a lot about god hand
no i i got like 60 games to play there's so many video games i have we want to go so skip this one
i know what i'm playing it all right let's do buster part equip so we have plus one attack
two energy plus one energy two range rapid fire is just that's it oh machine gun energy three
rapid one this is energy one range two attack one range two pack one energy two energy one
i'm gonna replace this machine gun that's energy three rapid one i lose the range there but i'm
gonna be shooting at a ton of bullets blast unit attack one energy two i could put this on
or just keep that one on it's pretty balanced oh that's good to know all right you talk to me
oh items life gauge black jacket reduces all damage by one fourth give it to me thank you
kevlar jacket oh chameleon net camouflages user for a limited time piper cartridge life gauge
mike fart i mean fart fart on fart in the mic fart in the mic okay i got the most health i can
have extra pack here wait let me parts laser holy shit attack plus four turbo battery eight laser
is plus four attack that's crazy i want it i'm gonna buy hyper cartridge and chameleon net or
extra pack i don't have enough of the kevlar all right let's go put this on refill the canteen
all right buster parts here we go this is energy three rapid one attack one range so we're going
to replace we're going to keep machine gun on and we're going to put on laser so we lose range but
we have a ton of bullets that come out and they all do a shit load of damage special items black
jacket put it on yellow refractor blue refractor all right sounds good what's with this whole
farting thing what are you guys talking about because what are you guys doing can i give the
bone to the dog pause the screen somebody went to go get a drink thanks for reminding me
all right i have to go to the closer woods closer woods so that's right that's north
and then all the way around into the closer woods right closer woods up you're gonna go north
take the dog ban that person permanently and i mean fucking permanent permanently full moon
werewolf crack viewer i never go up again and then right he kicked the can he did he kicked it
into the bakery how do i get there from here can i go up again yeah here we go what do you think
yes that's what i thought what were they thinking taking a big hole like that around the ruins
i wonder if anyone will ever be able to enter there again okay so now we have to go through
down to the closer woods can we look up a guide no no no not yet like i'm going down to the where
another one of those refractors is closer woods they don't look up a guide yet although i can't
get up there now look at empty safety helmet look at that faster that's a ton of damage
oh put the helmet on
fart into your face cam all right shut up
what is wrong with you why are you even saying that special weapons no it's not a fart i can't
even put the helmet on fart into your face cam what are you even talking about somebody check
on that guy is he all right all right i gotta go around closer woods okay so this is yes plains
fuck i did it again is this the closer woods okay yes so i keep going cringe boomer cringe boomer
cringe boomer cringe boomer okay um this is it right this is the closer woods right here
because that yeah it's down here so have i not done something in here wait no this is where i
what is it the other one that's the main dungeon there's a talk to grandpa oh okay
it's the one that the pirates dug around so then here use the use the damn rocket so is it around
here you can't enter it right now above nothing here okay um anybody know what to do i have the
big yellow crystal the where's the one in uptown uptown i went to uptown like three times
all right roll come get me back to the boat i'm sorry mega man i can't get over there come on
the boat boat boat boat boat boat boat all right we'll go to the boat i'll check the boat
this game sucks it really doesn't though it's fun i mean you can't get over here why
why the fuck not super powered mind mechanical k9 rescue the day from destruction why are you
writing that it's a cool theme song though okay over to the boat show let's go we are in
downtown we're gonna go down and we're gonna left south and then west boat show wait was the boat
show here or is it it's an uptown isn't it what about the library and manslaughter all right let's
go to the boat boat show boat show party yes making me upset willies boat boat show okay i'm here for
the boat show eat a boat normally you could take your pick we don't have any sorry what are you
guys talking about talk to grandpa is grandpa just in city hall still probably okay city hall
hey roll we need you to come get me apologize to the chat now i don't apologize for literally
everything i ever do you guys slipping into crack mode are they slipping into crack mode uh-oh
uh-oh uh-oh it's getting close to midnight eastern oh the bank right i want to make it an
account bank needs all the help it can get right now i'd like to open an account reopen for business
i'd like to open an account i can't finally got my money out it's an automated tele machine you
can't use it you don't have any money in the bank why there's so many viewers um i'll ask them i'm
not sure what they're doing here i don't where i started streaming like a couple weeks ago all
right i need an appointment waiting room they're just waiting they're just here waiting
so i can't go up here all right where's grandpa hello there mega man what can i do for you i'd
like to make a donation you will oh thank you so much i wonder where we would start um make a few
condos we need an additional 5400 how much do you want to donate it's tax deductible
oh where's grandpa fuck where is he i don't he's not in here how do you have a shop class blade
oh all right doesn't that look like a standing saw is he on the ship where the fuck is grandpa
you got a class a license yes with that you i know where's the okay i can talk to the monkey
in the northern forest yeah the mayor must really trust you all right get yes long-winded you could
have just said thanks it's data not monkey all right let me give the helmet to roll item dev
i got a helmet you won't get knocked down by enemy attacks as easily as before and you'll be able to
survive long falls even if somebody throws you off a cliff nice i got it all right data
i need your help tell me what should i do i use the yellow refractor for let's think of some way
to use the yellow refractor what am i supposed to do with it on the boat but i can't get to the
boat because the boat's the store is empty there is the helmet is now on yes look at we're really
mega man now one guy in chat says talk to the door next to the boat guy yeah i did remember he said
no no there's no boats out there i promise don't go out there i can go you got to talk to the door
next to the boat guy multiple times do it twice all right okay that sounds like a bait yeah it
does that does sound like a bait yeah that's a bait it has to be it's not it's not it's not
somebody got a wink please do i actually have to do that that sounds like it's absolutely not true
is it actually true my fucking god didn't i do this like three times
i did this already i talked to the door at least twice all right what do you guys need to make the
boat work uh wiley asked me to fix this boat for him but it's via wait dr wiley can't fix
in the place the only thing that's wrong with this boat is the refractor casing and the couplings if
if i had a big refractor like yours i could probably fix it hold on i gotta call my sister
progress that must be taking really let's put some let's put a brick of velveta cheese in it
mega man what do you think no no no roll roll no no no uh you ruined it do you really think you
should be doing that fix the transformer and just the second should i drink a monster no eat a
banana instead every time you want to drink a monster just eat a banana there we go sorry
i just started fixing the ship and you really love machines don't you i can tell just by looking at
your face well your face it's covered with grease i'm glad i'm talking as pretty as you would fix
my boat for me that's what is an eye patch or do you just have no ice in the eye socket
anytime you want we'll be able to get to the island right now see you later okay i want to go
now you know that to get into the boat you have to use the door in the back right wink because
i've only been playing the game for three hours and 40 minutes but i've been streaming for five
hours and 13 minutes math doesn't add up it's the boat call roll two wings mega man are you ready
yep let's go here we go we lost an hour of progress oh that's right another one no that's not
one two three i'm picking something up on the sonar keep an eye out mega man okay
they're here is she driving robots are here water battle protect your boat from the enemy's attack
shoot and destroy the red subs torpedoes and the yellow ship's missiles before they hit the ship
mission start let's go i can say things loud too roll can i get off really could use rain for this
no don't don't have any rain
it's a wink storm
i can't hit anything from here one two three three more i'm getting multiple signals on my
sonar a lot of little things coming from around this ship must be getting a slight electric shock
free time ah no rain oh fire i'm having fire's rewards
no refund i see it it's over there mega man mega man ahead i don't see where
fart redeemed fart points fart redeemed oh my god you guys
fart redeemed fine nobody wrote omega omega i was here what are you talking about
imagine i was hearing over a fucking fart sound oh you have to we need another refractor this
thing's going down slam your desk slam your desk
looks like we got rid of all their little ships wait let's see it on this way you guys are fucking
crazy i knew our little blue boy'd show up i figured we'd run into him sooner or later if we
waited here crazy into crazy crazy into you slow ahead slow ahead slow ahead
well that's a big uh that's a big thing concentrate your fire on the blue blow
him and his little toy boat out of the water what but jesus we sink his holy shit what he
fought it on camera if we can get him to smash his desk now if we just say it with all capital
it's a meme all right men let's do it what's wrong with me why should i care if he
if that little brat dies i shouldn't i really shouldn't dies we didn't they want to kill me
strange look at the boat's damage too i have i think i hit it in the eyes
pull over
pull over just pull over to the island i'll climb on
roll roll just pull over we should pull over pull over retreat thank you how do you get range
i don't have any i can't even hit him for all slow down that was full speed all right i need
oh let me uh i gotta take uh auto outside do you want to go yeah yeah he needs to go out
i'm gonna feed him too i'll be back in like two three minutes show auto no no no no he wants to go
he might need to go out he's gonna he's gonna pee imagine you had to pee and somebody picked
you up and was like look over here and don't pee yet i'll be back so auto uh did not just have to
pee he did the other thing he went to go find a perfect little spot so he's uh he's now good
to go thanks i'm eating i didn't i didn't say anything i said he's doing the other thing
it could i don't really could be walking around all right uh very very we need range
two range plus two range i mean this is it's a this much range is that too much
or should i put the uh laser back on i think that's enough range what about special weapon
oh that's fine i don't think it's enough it's probably enough this is a child's game just do
what looks cool this is this is mega man oh shit we're just going right into it okay
i can reach with the eye not reaching wait am i even hitting the base i kind of it's
definitely right in the eye no huh where are we going where the hell are we oh um what the
fuck now can i hit it um
what yeah you didn't fall off or anything no i'm all right what's in the back there
ah something in the back there goes the arms all right those are hard to hit
arm walk onto the arm come on hit it in the arm waving his arms around too much
hi is he back yeah just refresh the page man in the eye we dodged that
this is dps race that's all dps race just barely out of range there
i did i take out the entire tron bone family here i guess i hate to admit it but i can't admit it
i'm sorry tron who talks first here all the trouble to make us such a magnificent robot
what can i say cheer up diesel don't worry we'll go back to the ship and come up with a new plan
yeah that's it that's the spirit thanks you two now i couldn't have asked for a better brother
and sister than you what blue boy next time who are your parents oh this 60 age gap here
honest 14 that dude's like 45 or 50 he's supposed to be 29 he's 29 all right well i made it to the
island it looks like you well i'm older so here comes the rain train nope nope nope nope this
dude's ancient kill me i do need the two keys i gotta get this image thing set up
that's a good one that's a good hold on that's a good one so in the very near future there's
going to be a place to put image links so i can easily have them captured already and be able to
cut to them immediately so they don't have to be in the chat it's going to be it's going to be
pretty good that's the plan not there yet but we'll see you'll see soon let's put it on the
screen i think it's actually pretty fun it could be my hair on on a given day it could be
all right not not a good time for a call
uh sure thank you yes all right talk to you soon
hey new spotter bro oh i'm okay there's a hole that is a hole i have the laser on
yeah i got i have it on i have laser in range i'm actually kind of liking it thanks for showing
my hard work as soon as my birthday started you're very welcome you're very welcome
range will save your ass yeah just so much better
and i like energy too though just because i like getting more out i feel like it's kind of hard
sometimes with some of the enemies to get more than two or three shots off before having to move
oh happy birthday yeah i didn't why did i say happy birthday what am i crazy
high energy and rapid is fun yeah we'll see what i end up with just old hover jets i have a board
and i have jets you know what that means hover board incoming go up where it's gonna go just up
yeah where we going we don't need roads i hate these guys i also i don't actually don't really
like this canon thing that much i really i don't i think i want to change it it's a little too slow
and it's uh it's all right the power plus mode back on i like the range vacuum maybe we'll just
does it cost energy to use it no it doesn't all right maybe i'll try it
and upgrade it pretty cheap too all right so remind me to look at the vacuum when i get out
of the game but when i get it into the boat it's a car whatever the thing is it holds
you were that was deceiving you were in a different spot than i thought you were
okay
first co-op juke no that's not a co-op it's not even some different lines
that's not even that's not good come on you tell me there's a co-op juke in chat and i don't see it
dog
okay big jump
this is a lot to explore in here all right let's take it easy uh i want to go over here like no not
yet there's probably a chest or something there is there is a chest something dbz
kind of yeah they're like joint plug these one of those and they come well they can come out they
can come out they can come out these are just like the things from um uh you know the game
that i was playing yesterday rain world holy fuck there's more of them i'm just trying to get some
money i have a full canister right should fucking my god i gotta run
just too many does that this looks like it's gonna move no okay look the holes i don't see any
oh is there anything there not picking up anything on my radar i'll try i bite down
uh is it soft no ow how are my teeth what did roll just say
oh if i'm reading this right there's a huge refractor there there is we should be able to
repair big flutter it's shielded isn't it you'll have to look for the starter keys again god damn
it not this it looks like that's the last room you must have missed some rooms on the way in
don't give up eat the whole thing that hurts you unbelievable all right i need keys
wait is there a way to jump anywhere over here no it's just this one room
you didn't cook the desk no i didn't you're right i did not cook the desk
back into the alligator room all right i'm just gonna i'm just gonna try to range it
oh man oh man oh man oh man oh man oh man oh man oh man oh man how did that miss
we're good disaster averted where where is he
still two or three more in here then i can look around for a second all right i can go down here
which way i'll go this way the full cut scene to go through the door all right how many keys do
any three i used my canister already too this is bad very bad what's a himbo i don't know
they call it they call me that all the time i don't know what it means
rapid striker sword and striker have it pretty neat it means you're sexy and stupid
i'm gonna go well i was here that's that's my favorite comment of the whole night
i was here still can't get in here so at least i explored it wait
so i'm gonna go back this alligator room is gonna absolutely destroy me later i know it is
i know it is
uh bang on right
okay knock on this way for keys keys keys everybody see any keys
ah is there another jump that's higher than this i'm going here
yes i got uh the one in the middle i got that already i think it is
uh silver flame don't do your fucking homework please hey zebra lord thanks to the five community
subs zebra lord thanks to the five subs to giving the five subs to this community
thank you whoa bloomed right out of here i see it oh yeah gattling oh i can make a gattling gun
uh can i really starter a key what did you find our key well the might even tell you
probably a big refractor in here somewhere good luck well i already found it all right i've
explored a lot let me maybe i should maybe i should go back pick a starter all right i'll pick a
starter sure um i'm kind of a i would say more of a water type so i usually pick the water type
in the pokemon games i've never played it i played pokemon diamond for about two hours before i
stopped playing and i never played it ever again um that's what i did it's the best one i've heard
that's what i've heard no i've i've been listen pokemon uh green tea whatever better what's the
what's the one the green leaf leaf green i've heard that's also the best one or one of the better
ones double somebody just woke up oh jeez wait mega man still fuck what was that anything in it
a ring and it's oh it's just a green fucking salad i don't even want to identify it
all right now over the to the right side yeah i haven't gone over there
can i get up there i don't think i can get up to this i can't get up there it's our tower the last
emote that's been added to germa985's twitch.tv channel no don't not yet not yet i want to see if
i can go anywhere else the one spot that i what about over there can i get there from
i think i can jump from here and then jump over oh no shit how am i supposed to get up there
are you bilingual no no not at all oh it's a little hallway
here we go and there's a hole in here too another starter key and some money nice
no i cannot speak another language as much as i'd love to i just i just thought it's not
gonna happen all right there's one more key i gotta get so if i go from here over to here
and i jump from come on i jump from here to there and no i definitely can't that means i must be
able to wrap around here there we can go to the left i can teach you spanish i can't learn it
experts have tried and experts have failed i'm gonna go back i don't want to lose all this progress
so
refill everything deposit the items yeah i'm referring to i'm referring to my my eighth grade
spanish teacher expert you have to be an expert to build a teacher like a classic
let me get out of here and go deposit it's never too late to try again
and it is for me because i just i don't i don't want the time you want to go back to town
no no i just want to have you make stuff yeah let's go back to whatever like talk to you all
right roll i want to i would stole my boats and use them to make that giant robot a wonder what
they were planning to do out in the ruins make winks i know all right roll i need you need the
car deposit items no that it was real shave head you legend legend all right item development
make something the roller board and hoverboard jets were used to make jet skates jet skates with
these you'll be able to move a lot faster than you can by running just be careful you don't get a hit
like cars if you use them in the city all right activate hold down the circle button
the jet skates will turn off if you release the circle button but when you take damage from an
enemy attack you can slide while using the skates to use the directional button all right cool
the joint plug was used to make adapter plug attached to your mega man buster until now you've
only been able to use two parts simultaneously right well with this you'll be able to use three
different parts at the same time fuck yeah what do you think about that i think it's pretty great
actually all right let me take uh change weapon grenade arm it's a vacuum flash mime normal arm
powered buster yeah what's the vacuum grenade arm what where is it normal arm did i miss it or
something is it not on here i'm looking for the vacuum when i oh i didn't get the last part
because the reset uh the outright okay all right let me go um let me put these on ever stream
jet set radio i have and i got really angry at it because i i played to play it when i was younger
and it was a quote i got really like pissed off at it it was hard how the fuck do you get mad at
jet set radio because it's it's it's very uh it's a very precise game i the jumping and the landing
and grinding and i got upset by it all right sniper unit laser do we do some just mega power
or do i do rapid fire machine gun and i think machine gun will be pretty good or just
hyper power i'm gonna do machine gun look at that this looks pretty good and i'll keep yeah
sniper yeah this is good special items jet skates okay cool and then adapter plug they're already on
all right need one more of these keys special weapons no no no yeah i have to go get it
uh but nah i want to go back uh no i'll get it's another trap it's in a trash can right just go
get it this is awesome actual travel broken propeller there it is is that the full the full
star no no no this is not a car i mean am i tech wait does this get plus one letter grade on
technicality because is mega man a car it could be he's in is he in a car wait i want to go talk
to sure a car like mechanism because he doesn't have wheels do you have an engine does mega man
have an engine in his suit am i missing something else what am i missing motor is it just in random
trash cans these are i already went in these ones right he's a robot yeah i kind of sound like a
vacuum it's in a very specific trash can which uh which can is it in somewhere here the fuck is
hitting me okay i just got double hit by a car that's great all right and it was it in here
no garbage pail is there anything in it um the bloom bear parts that this garbage over here
does anyone know what this where the specific garbage is gotta get the screwdriver no i had
it made before i had it made before i just found it in a trash can it was like the list
okay broken cleaner broken propeller yeah i lost progress because i died in a dungeon
i was not happy about it broken motor there it is all right good let's move next these buildings
this town looks like ass let me get a drink i do appreciate the fact that there's three chugs
a lot of video games for some reason they do a single and it's not accurate i appreciate that
developing it's been five minutes without a joke streaming career over machine buster
unfortunately it's not that great in terms of power so you might have to put some thought into
how you use it vacuum arm special weapon yep here is gonna be over okay let's see it change weapon
so here we are grenade arm vacuum arm enhance it the vacuum arm no i want to do the vacuum arm
increase weapon use time like yeah holy shit this is maxed out what about the range 500 that's cheap
more that's pretty cheap one more range is maxed out increases suction speed most expensive part
more suction speed level three the highest amount of suction you could possibly have
maxed out maxed out maxed out but what was the new thing i got too it's not splash i don't like
the mice normal arm machine buster machine buster here it is firepower special what is this
this is fire spread i'm gonna save my money for now save it so i don't get this problem again
get the next key machine buster can be awesome spell coconut you got really really really good
that's an original username there that's just that's just germa lied there are people that
would probably pay you for that username i'm that's probably you know like how some websites people
just like squat on them let's check it out it's on right it's equipped let me just make sure my
zero ten how do i i gotta fill this in the town no fucking i don't even need it fuck it germa's
tallest fan is the best name no it isn't no not not even not even close not even close
he hates his fan he's jealous all right can i what's with these stupid doors these doors are
annoying no honestly one of my okay okay one of my favorite usernames so as the name germa lied
about way is one of my favorite usernames just because it's so it's so specific and never used
and that use case is just at as close to zero as you can get i have two starter keys need one more
let's start skiing how much energy does this use infinite energy yeah i say yeah should be
why is it using the bat i'm just testing it well it's pretty good pretty useful
look at how much more damage i'm doing too this is great it's such a huge range too
it's a speed run gun is it actually i feel like that's not lies i feel like that could be pretty
accurate just a hole i got that hole before pretty satisfying to use too where are we going i need
one more key wait two holes what time is it your bedtime yet not yet how do you sleep when you're
sick um it depends on how you stuffed up i always like to put a couple of pillows underneath my
head and shoulders because then when you lie back if you have a stuffy nose and a sore throat
it it starts closing you up so sit making lying down and having your head propped up a little bit
help uh somebody said humidifier that was like the next thing i was gonna say was uh
humidifier potentially and don't don't abuse it because it's really not great for you
but if it's really if you know to open you up a little bit and make you go to sleep the stuff
like nyquil is is in very very small moderation is good i think make sure you stay make sure you
can play in water one of the things about nyquil is nyquil uh uh has a cedaminophen in it and it's
i got a full dose of a cedaminophen and people just go oh i'm just gonna drink some more nyquil
have like double triple the dose you're taking like a two to three times a dose of cedaminophen
that you should be taking and it's really not good for you at all it's actually very bad for
you so you shouldn't be doing that it's really really bad for your liver it can make you pretty
it can actually make you sick really sick you take too much cedaminophen in one day more than
the recommended amount actually you can get actually very sick all right let's go where
am i going to go farming right now same with caffeine oh hold on we don't we don't talk we
don't talk about you know caffeine or anything in here we don't want to talk about caffeine
coffees you know if you drink one coffee a day you'd be one coffee in the morning
it's you'd be fine there's like this one way to get to this spot that i can't get to how where is
it i gotta go that way how do i get up there from there maybe i'm gonna go crazy with a
crazy i get that from here i gotta get up there where did you come from
my new viewer here do you hate me uh well exit this door what he hates he hates all new fans
until they prove that he should like them who said that okay now bingo starter key yeah
that's three keys that's in that's not that's not it say germa germa says that the germa says that
there's true fans are made after a few weeks of watching the stream then contributing to the chat
he hates new fans because hold on what the fuck are you talking about he hates new fans
because they haven't paid him yet and he deems all non-paid fans as unnecessary and not even
needed what the fuck are you talking about this is fucking kind of annoying
i didn't say that i'm fucking responding to it all right where's the reactor is it through here
jzzb thanks for the five community subs hey thanks thanks for showing some of those thanks
for giving us some real fans do you think people actually really think like that they probably do
right now it's probably not as much as do people really think like that 100 fucking percent that's
so bad snarbos is 10 community subs thank you thanks for the 10 i've done this three times now
when do we put it all together people get greedy thank you for the money thank you for the money
it was a joke germa germa lied what a great username be careful megaman the thing behind
me is gonna be boss and i have a vacuum cleaner for a weapon this is good picking up a reaverbot
signal it came out of nowhere it's a big one the readings are going off the scale the vacuum is
perfect for getting money oh dear all right what's this move set study the move set for a little bit
so the move set and him right in his little head gotta be right in the head right yep okay
where is he wait for him to dodge okay that fucking really hurt oh my god oh my god can i run can i
leave he has this like shockwave dude i can't even get him to stay in frame holy shit this is
horrible i can't even do the camera is just fucking i'm gonna run canteen's empty i'm dead
dude this is so bad what the fuck are you supposed to fight this guy jump and shoot
no i can't i can't do that can't that i saved outside here use the lock on it doesn't it doesn't
do the thing it doesn't it doesn't turn around they have to be in frame if you lock on you can't
move oh wait down and circle is a quick turn i wish i knew that i wish i knew that why did i
not know that even the damn canteen too i'm fucking going here prepared why do i have to fill the
canteen at the fucking store well i can't just go fill it up with like a water fountain or
something why do i have to go all the way back to the store to do this mega man legends is like
six hours well we found out today that that was not accurate found out that was not accurate
you know they go to the only place that sells water the trash store should i get this i could
have that i could have tons of attack i got the laser yeah but i could do that too super range
no no let's just keep it the way it is all right what can i sell
hypercar recharge a special weapon how do i use this this is a regular item damn okay
i'm sorry but vinnie's about to start his sunday stream good luck no don't leave don't leave please
stay here please i'll do anything i'll do anything if you want to wait
hey you stay staying wait where's this where am i aesthetic goodbye why is it like dogs chase
why is it like why the rapid dogs are they rapid why there's so many of them oh shit he just ran
into me i didn't mean to do that oh shit all right get me out of here what's going on in this town
get me out get me out get me out get me out get me out get me out get me out get me out
how did i what did i get in here oh where did i come in from over here why did these mean dogs
everywhere what the fuck where am i no i'm i want to go back to the you're an old town he's waiting
for me he's waiting for me he's waiting for me this is definitely end game where's the door to
go through that's i need west w dude what are you doing out here they call this part of this
they call this part of this i'm trying to stand on his head they call this part of the city the
old city a long time ago people used to live here but the only things living here now are the dogs
well if you came here to see the main gate then you should go to the south gate if you want to
go to the power plant it's to the north dog all right let's go back in there let's fight this boss
so now i gotta go with
75 000 points for a non don't leave the stream week
anyway how much um those who that have played through this game what's uh what remains i want
to call the car you actually lost 200 viewers whatever don't worry four hours at your rate
why do you say it's so why do you say so cute like that huh why is it gonna be so cute like that
uh what time is it it's still it's not that bad i started at like two yeah we're fine
you're fishing for viewers it don't matter it's the boat let's go move to speaking simulator all
right and now that i you know what i'm gonna change the weapon too should i yeah yeah no i don't need
it i'm not i don't need it no i'm just gonna jump and shoot open mario sunshine um i actually
don't have mario sunshine i will not write the second i'm getting it i'll have it by the end of
the week all right i just i know where i need to go so let's skip skip practice the quick turn sure
boom boom got it please don't worry i'm gonna play mario sunshine i would hate being a twitch
video game streamer it seems like so much pressure but when people tell you to to backflip i mean
yeah that's a little too much pressure i think i'm not sure i could do that all right uh fresh
my memory it was over here right i had to go through like that this door spin around
we're here right through the doors and then left and then around
um no it's not this way i still i need the last shard where is it all the side oh wait there's
an item that i could i didn't get too right i remember and i'd like to know what that was
that hit me because it wasn't on my screen wasn't on yours i didn't see shit did i get already there's
one on the other side isn't there don't i don't remember was it over wait was it over here yeah
it was right it was all the way around you left i'd get out of my goddamn way i guarantee if you
opened up mario sunshine right now you'd get 10 000 viewers i don't have it i don't own it
there it is starter key how do i do something i don't have go download it you don't want to go
do you want to go download mario sunshine right now no even but even you saying those words
even us just saying this out loud together you just got me on like the nintendo fbi list
okay do we can't even talk about this right now like that's a first party nintendo game are you
out of your goddamn mind saying that out loud here we go no i we also i guess i go to my favorite
games i don't like the look uh i got both beautiful joes which are fantastic best fucking
games beautiful joe is so much fun the music is perfect too all right let's do it
keep him in range just jump over that miss sorry why are you not really it
what in the name of fucking god the game locks onto bats 5000 feet in the air but not on this
guy's head holy shit this guy sucks this boss eats ass you're gonna dive across the whole room
what what what what we're both doing the same fucking moves i'm gonna jump over i'm gonna jump
over him fuck what in the name are you doing what are you doing it's gonna hit me take the
fucking goddamn thing what he stops what the fuck is happening to my brain i was here don't say that
yet i gotta move this back yo was crying what happened why is it so dark in there it's not i
just my streams start at about 2 p.m pacific which is during the day sun is blazing outside right sun
is outside signing down on my face and it's bright into the windows and it's bright in the room there
it's this daylight over the course of the stream time goes by and it becomes a night time at about
nine o'clock pacific time i have lights on in here it's just the exposure from the camera want
me to prove it in real time in real time ready see let's go back to being a little bit that's
too much it's i i stream over the course of a whole day goes by nice chin beard that's a shadow
and i'm ready for school with my backpack don't die here
but this could be a good farm spot right now didn't even take one point of damage
all right bye you're gonna fart so people come back didn't even take one point until right there
all right let's go is it this one i don't i don't i don't remember
he's recreating the lighthouse
this game's boring is to read chat every 12 seconds to keep himself entertained i do that
already i read it's to my detriment is what you meant to say i will get lost in a i would get lost
in a room with one door because i look at chat every five seconds i love reading chat i love
participating i love seeing what you guys have to say i love it it'd be like if i was on stage and
there was 5 000 people in the audience and i was facing away from the audience just talking
no i want to see you guys who's back there get some more grind a little bit
oh good i'm getting hit you must be getting hungry actually i kind of am
i made some apricot you could have said anything else anything else but that apricot weird champ
what is weird champ i've seen people write that i don't see it though what is that
when i um when my like back and chest were hurting last night and i was like ah fuck
i was like making weird faces i saw a bunch of weird champs what's that mean
oh oh okay so what what is it what is it what is it what's the emotion what's it conveying what
do you use it for let's go back to time confusion unacceptable behavior okay i'm fresh out of ideas
you know you're sitting being creeped out out there digging up all sorts of stuff
calm down teasel you're going to burst he won't beat us to the treasure no one will as long as that
big door is still locked all we have to do is make sure we get rid of him before then
what if he digs up a few scraps that would be funny he can keep that garbage all we're after is
whatever's behind the main gate i tease up slam the desk see you're absolutely right then that
will be our new plan we'll wait for him to open the main gate we'll let him keep whatever he
finds until then he'll see it'll be the bonds you have the last lap in this game
i'm the casting director for gremlins 3 we're wondering if you'd like to play gizmo we would
save a lot of money on puppets if you agree all right but this one was is way more important my
back is killing me from my current office chair i do a lot of 3d modeling at home so i sit in it
for many hours i'm going around asking streamers what chairs they're using you wouldn't mind if you
tell me what your chair is um i actually have a really really really good chair
i have this is let me get the name right this thing was like 400 dollars it's one it's like
one of the best chairs i could possibly buy what the hell is it called it's called like it's it's
uh got a name it's like it's like the quadro or something what is it called it's got a name
it's got like an actual name here let's see what is it what's called is this a bit no no no it's
not uh let me see no no no what is it called that's the q the chic the quattro the chic
quattro titanium what the fuck is this chair it has a name and it's a weird name it probably says
it on the back all right it's called important for your safety during assembly make sure to
tighten bolts it's like the quadro the quattro quad it's got a name oh my god i don't know what
this is called it's gonna i'm gonna lose my mind quattro no somebody have it no that's me standing
on a stool that's like just p okay is this it oh you said i've already seen it um office chair
it's like the quad the quadruple just hold on it's not from staples i'll find it i just need to
just give me a minute i just typed in office chair quadra quad office chair quad oh my god
i'm i'm gonna go to my email and like look up the receipt for this uh did you get it the work pro
quantum 9000 series i think that's correct yes it's the work pro quantum but i think it's like
the 4000 how did i how did we find it yeah work pro quantum ergonomic chair there it is you found
it that's the chair that i have i couldn't think of the word quantum because i didn't think that it
was that because we just were saying the word quantum a bunch of times like a week like a day
two ago all right let's go it's a quantum chair my old office had those they're amazing yeah it's
very good but i i have i need it it's got this great lumbar support it's got a really good
seat it moves around i said it was 400 dollars yes it's three it's what 315 now so i mean i bought
this chair like almost two years ago so of course price is gonna come down with this we should be
able to repair the flutter hooray let's go mega man let's go fix the flutter
now this i can assure you this chair is definitely a thousand times better
mega man could you take care of the refractor and those like men in black seats
that everybody sits in for some reason on twitch finished it's ready here too
mega man you grab that over there gotcha this one right i worked at office max and no one ever
bought that chair ready listen up switch on refractor rotation speed increasing
engine field generation at 80 safety lock check initiating countdown three two one mega man now
here goes thick field operational pair production active let's go we did it we made it but we should
be able to get around the island at least what did i eat today and you'll be able to reach that cave
chili lime let me know when you want to start a dig at the cave and i'll take you there anytime
we're flying we're flying not mac and cheese i'm trying to stay away from cheese kind of cut down
on on cheese and bread i'm trying to cut my intake of cheese bread and red meat but i just ate a whole
package of red meat so that's going well all right so what if we do with this looks like a large
computer vegan well no i said red meat off limits to everybody it's certainly well made but it's
pretty strange looking it's the best room in the game oh there he is finally grandpa hi mega man
milia asked me to find out what i could about that treasure that's supposed to be right here
this island just got so many mysteries i just don't know where to start looking
it have you ever heard of the main gate yes yes i said oh you have hey and you probably already
know this but the largest ruin on the island it's called the main gate and can be found near the old
city what's unusual about it is as far as anyone knows there's no way to get inside i have a theory
that's connected to some it's connected in some way with the sub gates tell me mega man you found
a passage in the sub gate that connects to the main gate no if i'm right sub gate in the closer
woods there's some kind of key for the main gate and i'm willing to bet anything it's treasuring
those pirates a little after it's inside the main gate they probably realized how close and they are
and the treasurer don't let your guard down thank you elderly fuck hey all right time the person up
five seconds this is rose room nice any items hi okay bye this is mega man's room where's mega
man's room is my room now this is an old person's room for sure it's a first aid box but you don't
really need it as long as data's around it's your bed why do i have a heat lamp my room sucks wait
all right what's the old guy's room this is the old guy's room it's a chest is there anything
inside bomb schematic uh grandpa's does he sleep in the sarcophagus yeah was he a vampire all right
i'm getting out of this we have to go what do we have to do i don't remember it said something
what does it say we have to find a way to open the gate talk what a wonderful little ring
did you really find it underground it's so nice you can have it you mean i can have it well thank
you so much mega man i promise i'll always wear it i wonder what's inside the closer woods sub gate
whatever it is though you can be sure those pirates will be after it too be careful
wasn't i already there there you go bomb schematic was used to make the grand grenade special weapon
allows you to shoot out even stronger grenade bomb they're really powerful you might even be able
used to blow up walls inside the ruins well would you look at that that's how you break open the walls
okay grand grenade and now we're gonna enhance the grand grenade we're gonna make it that's
a hundred thousand dollars this is all very expensive damn if you compliment her every
week for a year you can i don't know no grinding no i'm gonna use it and let's go
closer mine support car take me to where is it uptown downtown uptown quickly for a year
other weapons can break walls too that's why i have to go talk to her in her room to get the
next dungeon okay monkey never stops dancing you think that you would stop at some point even to
rest for one minute all right we're gonna where was it we're gonna go back to the
back to the forest right yeah we'll be at the flutter monkeys weren't a diaper
try to get in let me in all right what where's roll hey there she's finally fixed well it's not
100 fixed but we should be able to get around the island to be able to take us to the other
sub gates or the closer woods go to the r&d room oh go to the sub gate yes
remember what are those three wacky numbers in the back of your credit card
they're kind of weird like what are they even there for that's so strange let me see oh no
right i don't have a credit card i don't even have a bank account i pay cash with everything
absolute fucking chad yeah when i bought my car i just shook the guy's hand with like nine grand
in hundreds he was like sir sir the car was only 6400 dollars i was like yeah he's like okay all
right scary site like this before there's a big pit in the middle and i can't get any readings
from inside jump in the pit mega man or punch your desk it will make my daughter really happy
tell your daughter that i would talk to my daughter that's like just are you okay
no can you see a door somewhere there are many doors this is a big place
we got it's my guess the computers out in that room can you see a switch anywhere i don't see
any switches but there's some writing here let's see it says operations room two
emergency system activation requires direct password input from eden or the insertion of
three level two or three id cards prototype and throw unit id cards what's the prototype
and throw unit stop it's supposed to be like 10 well whatever that is you need if we're lucky
you'll be able to find them inside there it's ancient writing yeah well guys he's not reading
off of a dinner menu this is ancient alien text you think he can read that well there's a door back
here oh whoa oh shit there's more than one oh there's three now are they multiplying
i got an idea just all of them that was fantastic
all right i missed my vacuum check the lice
well i just jumped off the edge because i got scared at the
and there was a chest right there wonderful that's wonderful
okay we're good guidance unit that's probably homing i'll i would absolutely take a homing
missile right now let's explore the rest of this hold on
it's like the when nice knock them off
this end game are we in the end game anybody know
i don't think i can get up there from here i might really
this big one all right i got one id card this one did you find something mega man
so i don't have lice i think i found an id card good going i'll go back to that control room
once i found the others
oh it's past midnight it's past midnight it's past midnight oh and they've been eating macaroni
and cheese right out of the stove top thing right out of the pan oh this is bad this is bad they've
been eating mac and cheese right out of the pan i don't know what to do uh i'm gonna slowly make
a quick uh a joke i'm gonna make a small joke and see i mean they're very rowdy
oh look at that uh look at that enemy spider right here giant spider
i need more damage than this this is for just atrocious
damage
it's right here huh i just did it i did the ceiling was breakable
breakable wait is this is this ceiling not breakable it look at that no it's not yeah look at
that it's on the map never i can't open it this night i'm trying just to open a weapon no this
is the super grenade thing you have to throw it higher no fucking way how did i not i did that
twice if you did a back lip i'd be stoked maybe one day if you're good
there's no response looks like the power is off there too
maybe you'll be able to find the generator somewhere in there now i gotta find a generator
hey really you can't you can't be serious
okay what the hell are you doing standing here well i have we're not gone i have one key card
there's a bunch of places back here i could have gone i'm gonna try this way this is the way out
or is it please there's no response in here either okay great chat's gone cyclic yeah that
this happened like three hours ago i don't know what you're talking about go back this way okay
this way haven't been in here
oh you can open doors you need to open the mean never when i tried to kill the chat with sub only
i do oh i'm raising my hand shit they're learning they're learning like seven plus hours into this
game and you give me less than a thousand zenny hello lens let's go right in the middle here now
this is the exit where have i not seen like one you only need two more id cards
shit sorry this message requires a gerba gold account i'm not going directly in the middle
but i did here we go
okay i don't think i have any more canteen i gotta be careful here
i don't want to repeat the last time behind me too
fuck
down put it down put it down is this nintendo 64 no this is just on playstation playstation 1
on a playstation 2 ps1 on ps2 it's emulated this is not emulated sorry i did not download this
uh this is a no i wanted to it's a boss room what the hell is this shit that looks like the
generator you've been looking for oh i can use the elevator can you get it to work all right you
should be able to get the elevator to work now don't turn around it's gonna be something right
behind me if i turn around then it pops in and it gets actually rendered into the game's engine
so don't turn around it's probably a hole in here test their id card i need one more and then
where's the last boss that's what um one person told me they said dude you're at the last boss
with these id cards and i'm like fucking nice i am gonna leave and save so and refill my canteen
this is dangerous coward i want to live i don't want to lose 40 minutes of progress again
straight down
uh oh are we getting a wait this is i know where this is
was i not close enough or what was it not close enough to that
oh dude this is underneath my house what no fucking way all right i'm going back i'm going
back i'm good i got two id cards i'm going back i'm out of here it would be a mistake to try to
keep going you're gonna brush your teeth how do i get back hey remember who's back here right
i need to go down this way
at least it's health i have items to give to roll as well i yeah i don't want to stay down here
target sensor front clips front clips are superior well front clips are actually harder
to do i think than backflips in some regard i definitely can't do it anymore and i really hope
that there's some recording of me doing it but i used to actually be able to do a full backflip
from standing on the ground i could not do a front flip though no matter how hard i tried i could
never do it front flips always were impossible for me can i get out of here from this i think
i can right if i go this way ancient book well that's cool nice
i can't leave though i just want to get out of this all right is it straight ahead i think it's
straight ahead and not destroy those walls i don't think i can destroy those walls i'm so
turned around right now this is the generator room i gotta go back to the room with the chest
center and then i forget after that we're gonna go this way
germa do it i it's the debated song that's okay i got it
now is the secret room
here we are so back this way
okay in here right i think i don't remember i have no idea uh yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
what's over here i can't tell if you hate this game or if you hate streaming in general
i can't tell if you're really mr comcaster if you stole that name and it's identity if you're
stealing a company i say identity that's right i can't tell we're both on the same page
i have power holy shit i got power wait a minute we have you on camera all right i gotta stop reading
chat and then figure out how to get the fuck out of here here we go germa doesn't pay taxes
yeah i i do actually i'm back all right roll come here what is that reaction
yes i do yes i do okay let's make him make an item he's probably painfully aware of how much
he pays active buster fires a homing missile that will track the nearest enemy okay so homing
still a lot of enhancements that could make i'm enhancing this one i'm gonna spend a ton of money
on it buster sniper scope it increases your firing range as far as it will go so i max out
my range hold on let's take a look i keep the grand grenade on though i feel like i need it
if there's a level arm machine buster uh what should i put on maybe the machine buster i want
to try it for active buster powered buster grenade arm vacuum arm active buster it's
an answer active buster attack it's also expensive homing capability i have a lot of money but do i
want to spend it on here upgrades its homing capability let's go i want it more spiring speed
more range that's 20 000 dollars um ammo i think better be good talk to data energy charge okay
save again this is a boss wrecker cool go back in uh we want to talk to roll this is my first time
playing this it'll go back to the far away that's where i want to go wait because that's where i
want to go right no no i want to go to the sub gate no no i'm already at the sub gate right
just leave uh this is my first time playing through this game yes i've played it before a
long time ago i never got past a certain point i actually think the first two hours three hours
of the game they get the energy canteen nah all right now we can go to the elevator
so that other elevator was where was it i don't remember over here i remember where the other
elevator was i don't have any idea what else is lost as i am it might be time for food real food
because people are writing hash house a gogo in the chat and i mean you're you're you're trying
to get me to turn the stream off like that's actively oh my god hash house a gogo is so
fucking delicious current i'm turning off the stream and that's what's happening with what you
guys are doing i just want to be completely transparent with you banana cream pie wife okay
thanks see you guys later it's been a fun stream i had a lot of fun this game's good i want to see
what's up at the top of this let's test this item pretty good looks like arcane missiles all right
where's that elevator please play this again oh i'm i'm gonna absolutely finish this game the next
time we stream 100 i probably only have like a couple hours left get that i have 1000 i'm
gonna finish this the next time and then we'll move on to something else i have a ton of playstation
game i've got a lot of stuff behind me um don't play this ever again it's right here is it right
here is this it no two holes in here though did i open these
leave it actually yeah it's probably time to call it i'm getting really hungry i'm glad you guys
have to do that why'd you got to say all those delicious food places and now i'm having trouble
remembering where doors go yeah it's time for food that's that's that's how you quantify if it's time
to stop streaming do you remember where a door leads to i don't know it's probably time for you
to take in some protein and uh maybe some milk almond milk not cow's milk i don't drink that
i really want hash house to go go now i really really want it really bad
like really bad
let me see what's up here first i don't have to blow this up again oh come on what the
fuck i gotta blow the no i don't i already did this shit can i just shoot it i don't need to blow
it up right this is where it is though
oat milk i don't i don't like i only like almond milk i don't like soy milk i don't like oat milk
i don't like coconut milk i only almond milk is the only one that i drank that i've said i
don't like rice milk
i changed my weapons because of this damn it oh the stream i was about to turn it off
the stream goes on i was there all right let's go dude dude dude hang up
or is just the reveal where she's the one that's been making them
oh i almost killed you before you got over to me that would have been awesome
whoa oh my god what a reaction that was that was i haven't had a hash house to go go hamburger
yet so that was that's why you got that reaction hooray girl
no it's too late for that for me don't don't don't don't don't don't why did you have to
fucking say that why did you have to do that to me it's over the stupidest thing it's not even
epic bacon i gotta you know hold on that's not how you do that i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead
i'm dead no canteen no i can do that i can beat that right now it's like this boss right here i'm
up i'm not done i can beat that can be that boss i know where it is i just gotta beat it i'm just
gonna spam the fuck out of it one more one more try one more and then we can get out of here
i already did all this stuff let's go check my normal items let me see if there's any more
oh my god normal items shield repair what i can eat repairs damaged life shield but i've used this
oh that's the health when it turns red all right i see that's why i'm not dying instantly
very good i forget where to go where do i go i actually i why am i like this it's like i try
to put it into long term but it just it will not get it will not go into long terms i sit there and
i go like it's this door right here this door this door with the secret thing we need to get rid of
the bugs this one and then my other brain just goes no no i don't care i don't care nope don't i
don't want to know don't tell me anything nope
he's still playing yeah i'm i'm gonna be stopping though i'm not gonna be able to finish it in one
bill it's all right i'll pick it up i i love it it's great i love it i love little item combinations
and upgrading and finding the item it's it's fun i think this still holds up pretty well even though
it came out 20 years ago i think this holds it pretty well you know i would love to see another
i'd love to see another megaman legend megaman legends 3 new with the same kind of idea
megaman i'm seeing something funny looks like there's a false wall or something
there's probably a secret room in there we all would like to see that yeah bad news for you buddy
what's the matter what did they announce it and cancel it or something they don't make good
games anymore capcom's been on a tear making amazing games the last two or three years what
are you talking about and why is he actually not no what it's almost like
mega marry reaver bots close by watch out hold on wait wait let's gotta get rid of one
gotta go for the bread bun sometimes you gotta jump learn to scrape no i i knew how to scrape
i didn't have a big enough space to do it yet though this is a really big space that's a lot
of stuff oh my god and quick work of you i told you i was gonna do it late night get it now i just
have to go through here and get the last key card and then i'll put them in i'll just finish this
active buster is incredible but wait i'm i'm up here now remember i was saying i don't know if
i can get up here i can go gonna be a key card right id card got them all cool there's something
else over here all right got all the key cards that's it let's go
can i just save it what do you think it's like down here isn't it finish finish it um i'll
leave at least to the control room yeah i'm in no immediate danger unless there's a back-to-back
boss fight i actually don't know what the control room is i should have like a legend
or something and i know i should know by now but the columns columns
there are items in the pillars
wait this this counts as a hole right okay i guess it is just a hole drag the shard
all right uh yeah you know i think i'll just call it yeah eight hours we're good we're good
that we'll pick it up we'll finish it when you start the next room yeah yeah yeah yeah that's a
good place to stop yeah yeah he's never gonna finish raid joel he said you're not a gamer enough
okay you know you can tell joe when we raid joe
because i'm not gamer enough for this you jumped in didn't wait go back what do you mean go back
oh sorry i was talking to you guys wait what
don't ever talk to me wait hold on i ran past it i'm hungry i'm hungry i need food
i need red germa needs food red germa needs food badly red germa is about to die
that game is so good too is that rose colored uh goggles or is that game actually still amazing
i used to play that game in the arcade every weekend gauntlet legends that game was so
good they used to have the thing in the arcade cabinet where you had to you put a password in
and it kept your character in the cabinet and you'd get these guys that would come in and just
load up eight bucks worth of coins log into their character and they'd be level 99 and they would
just smoke the whole game like why why are you even playing at that point these guys have beaten the
game like a thousand times all right let's save it so for the next couple of days uh i have physical
therapy so i'm not going to be around tomorrow or the next day sorry to say but the
plan is to do wednesday thursday friday we will finish megaman legends we're starting black and
white 2 and that's what i want to give black and white 2 time so it might be a full two streams
maybe we'll throw the bachelor in there for some fun maybe rain world play it again but black and
white 2 has been on that no more heroes too yeah there's a lot i had so many things i started so
many new series megaman legends gotta play megaman legends too no more heroes no more
heroes too tony hawks underground tony hawks underground too all these games have twos head
rising 3 yeah but that's not a priority because nobody likes that game mario sunshine yeah you
say black and white 2 i did we're gonna finish megaman legends which should take another couple
hours and maybe surprise playstation 2 game maybe just go right into black and white see what i
want to do but that's gonna wrap it up here right at right at almost exactly the eight hour mark
thanks for joining me i had a lot of fun i love just playing games that are just fun to play
and we just talk it's fun i have a blast every time i play these games all right so we're out
of here i'll see you guys in a couple days on let's give you an exact date so you can
sus will be updated too uh wednesday wednesday afternoon i'll be starting i'm gonna go do some
pt and then wednesday thursday friday we'll see what happens during the weekend i think we'll
come back or maybe we'll go four days i don't know we'll see wednesday thursday friday friday at least
but uh take it off we'll see you soon we're gonna raid joel in a little bit
and we'll see you soon good night goodbye let's do the end of the stream everything is saved yeah
i saved it like three times right now good turn this off and turn this on let's go back earlier
we actually had another 50 dollars from bitslave bitslave has given a lot of money this large
amount of money from bitslave more than 150 dollars they say this video is in our interest
this is in our interest let me see i'm gonna change my monitor real quick i'm still here
drunk i'll take care of yourself drink some water drink plenty of water stay hydrated get some good
sleep make sure that for every one or two drinks you're drinking you're drinking a full glass of
water people saying how do you not have a hangover that's how and just take it slow yes that cures
hangovers oh yeah it does it makes you not have them and eating food that's true all right so
what's this video this video is in our interest this is just titled february 17
all right general i got banned for 14 days on my league of legends account
wait why because this johnny walker's real good real good drink right there so if you
gamers want to have a good drink gamer drink you better drink it all right drug and playing
league of legends i'm probably not a good probably not a good mix johnny you got banned
but what did you do what did you do it started drinking water somebody get some water into this
man that's the only way to enjoy that game didn't somebody say that or am i just pretending like
somebody said that to put forth an opinion of mine i'm not sure take care of yourself
and get some water and eat some food too thank you for the huge amount of money over the course
of the night bit slave appreciate it thank you hope you having fun but let's teleport back
to earlier in the evening food true go yeah go eat something go eat some food we had with
thousand bits from am ferrick thanks and ferrick boomer brace ready mega man legends time yeah i
had a lot of fun this game is really fun it's challenging but it's also still very accessible
it's not too hard it's fun it's not that it's hard it's just fun to play with items and
find stuff talk to people don't imagine donating to a millionaire i don't have a million dollars
i just want to make that real clear yeah i don't have them i don't have that much money
it'd be cool if i had a million dollars of your fund i would use it to buy i would buy i would
buy a house in cash imagine i don't have a billion dollars i don't happen to have
close to a billion dollars i don't even have close to i don't even have close to ten percent
of a million dollars right now not even close i don't even have close to 20% of a million
dollars right now i'm close half a million i don't look at those calculators they don't make any
sense one of those calculators said i was worth like eight billion dollars and that's not even
true is that even a visit a virus website what is this
germa's night second germa is smile my second germa account is worth
three hundred and thirty seven thousand dollars
so that's what it would be worth if i sold that channel
how much money does the second germa make
no that social blade yo and this here's the dumb thing about social blade
social blade likes to do this fun thing where they're not possible to be wrong
germa 95 is worth thirty eight thousand to twelve million like oh okay that's
quite a window but what about the what about the main
channel what about that well how much is that worth
is it even on here it's not even listed it's worth nothing
main channel is not worth anything it's worth a hundred and twelve thousand
dollars fuck off it's worth a hundred and twelve thousand what
that channel is worth like two million dollars that's where that's a million
dollar channel you know there's no growth like five
years ago so i sort of what you're saying is i
should have sold it five years ago i held it for too long now it's only
worth a hundred and twelve k oh well well uh what was that oh yeah
right i've i've i'm not a millionaire oh you guys will know
if i if i if i have a cross million dollars
you'll know you won't know how you will know if i ever cross one million dollars
in my like savings account or something if i have a million dollars
um this is gonna i'm gonna do something
ridiculous i will spend like five hundred thousand dollars on something
insane i will do a mega stream and then that
would be it what do you work wait we don't we're not
playing all right hold on a minute we're not gonna play the like hey
which money you got you what you want me to hey look at me this is the money i
have who hey look at me let me tell you those things you don't there's things
you don't ask somebody how much money do you have on your
checking account right now you know what why would you ask me number
two how much money you have any savings account right now
number three um i i know i'm not telling these things these are private things
that i don't i don't this is my thing my life
it's broke i'm not broke but i'm not a millionaire
i'm okay i'll give you a social blade window here
i'm worth right now anywhere from twenty one thousand dollars to
sixty one thousand dollars at the moment right now
pretty sick somebody said yeah right well how do you are you know that
net worth is about i i spent a i spent a lot of money
last year on twitch on the stream and when i do my taxes this year
uh my cpa is gonna be probably calling me and talking to me about
the some of the financing that i've done on some of the streams that you've seen
last year and so gonna be like jerry um
your your net worth is twelve dollars what happened
well i uh decided it was a good idea and i'm very nervous right now
he's gonna be like calm down calm down i'll be like okay sorry sorry
real voice robots are expensive yeah they are
like they did they they took care of me very very very much so
it took oh okay now i'm let's just go this way i'm doing just fine
i'm doing i'm doing better than fine way better than fine
thanks to you guys and all it took was somebody saying you donated to a
millionaire for me to say no no no no no no excuse me
ah but that's because of you that's because of you guys
and all the all the names and all the messages i'm about to read right now
that's kind of how this works let's see who the top heads were
still inaccurate four and a half months later twitch do your taxes no you gotta
do taxes on your own because i had not a twitch employee i have to
have a i have to get a somebody to help me do
my taxes with me anyways now where the hell were we thanks
for the 500 bits to vertible giant five dollars thank you i'm so excited to
be playing mega man legends this game enchanted me as a kid it was the reason
i even got into games in the first place hope you enjoy it
i did and i do i'm gonna finish it bulbous wag thanks for the six dollars
600 bits just wanted to share a weird dream i
had so in this dream i had a tree in my backyard and i
climbed into the tree and looked into my neighbor's backyard
i saw you sitting in the tree in the yard opposite of me
like in a bench inside the tree and i said hi but you just stared into the
distance with sunken eyes staring into the distance it's already
scary it's pretty weird hey niall aureon thanks for the 300
bits every other streamer i follow is playing
league of legends and then there's germa playing mega man legends
the real legend the only legend thanks for the 300 bits though
that happened bit slave thanks for the 250 you forgot to check out my follow-up
on johnny walker is this a drunk video all right update germa i've already
drank this much it's been like 10 minutes and it's going pretty good
also you need to play league of legends it is the number one i'm not playing
league of legends gamers this is wait hold on this is before he got banned
this is before he got banned for 14 days this is pre-ban because this was like
six hours this is like seven hours ago pre-ban if you don't believe me i am
iron four i'm an atrox main a lulu main and he got banned
he drank like five more drinks and got fucking banned
that's so fucking funny that is very very funny
oh i love how we can go back in time and see this
i only play drunk so if you can beat me if you can get iron three i will donate
one thousand dollars i won't
what is some music that's the second lowest rank
is this oh i'm i'm not playing league i can't i'm not doing it i'm not playing
league league is just one of those things
where i feel like when i do it if i would ever play it
you get assimilated into the borg and then you just never stop and that's all
you do i know i'm trying to resist the borg oh
that's so funny though that was that was a great eight hour setup for
that thank you bit sleep hey germa 13 thanks
hey 985 this is 13 again thanks to the support from your amazing
community we've been able to locate an apprehend germa 65
before he was able to gain control of the jex module commissioner germa 3 is
incredibly relieved since he was worried we're going to lose
this planet as well our first line of defense has received
significant upgrades we're confident we'll be able to defend
this planet in the future thanks again for the immense help 13 out
i didn't do anything um you sent me that message and then
i ate a few tacos and went to sleep so whatever you did was
good work i didn't do anything i woke up at like
one o'clock in the afternoon today i i had nothing to do with this
but thank you for continuing to defend our planet
hey noma gusta thanks for the 1500 bits 15 dolls first time catching a stream
live hello from south korea hey hello from america specifically las
vegas thanks for the 1500 bits and hello
from korea pretty cool viewers all over the place
this community is everywhere nasty banana man thanks to the 500 bits hey
germa just want to say you're one of my favorite streamers and i'm really happy
to see you playing one of my favorite games
it holds up very well i will say it does hold up
incredibly well we also had 250 from jewels
jewels say hey germa after watching the end of the stream from yesterday my
brother has been making fun of me relentlessly
all day today that my favorite streamer doesn't wash his hands
after using the toilet he said the origins of your name is probably not
related but he also said that you did not deny
not washing your hands after touching the toilet handle and your
privates please tell him the truth otherwise i'll have to suplex my brother
to the next dimension and i'm half his weight what i
yes i wash my hands after going to the bathroom
in fact let me go over this with some of you guys
um i pre-wash before going to the bathroom
you get people going into the bathroom i'm just talking like
going to the urinal and they just pull up down their pants and pee
and like grab their you know private and pee
without washing their hands first so that's
all the stuff that you've been touching throughout the course of that day why
not wash your hands first before you touch your bear you know
and then wash again there's a pre-wash to get the germs off your hands before
you touch your and then there's a sec second wash after
you're done think about that imagine like grabbing
like the door handle to even the like pushing the bathroom door open that's
been touched 500 million times and probably cleaned once a week and
then you grab your penis i just spit everywhere but i'm
being dead serious can you imagine not doing a small pre-wash
a pre-wash is not the same as post wash a pre-wash
is just a little bit of soap and just a little bit under the water
just a little and then the post wash is a little bit is to
really clean it up i don't know how this is such a strange concept to some of you
guys say a pre-washing your hands before you
touch down there is apparently weird do you pre-wash before a shower
when i'm taking what do you what the shower is the wash
the pre-wash of your hands before touching your
penis is because that's saying that word people are gonna fucking clip this and
take it and put it somewhere um before i go in the shower guys i
don't like just start grabbing and like what you know what that's a good idea
right now before i get in the shower i'm just gonna like mush my hands down
here and what are you talking about so you
open the door or open the curtain to the shower and you
get it and turn the water on next time you go to the doctor
i'm say i'm next time you go to the doctor listen to me next time you go to
the doctor i want you to ask the doctor say hey um
as a medical professional do you think it's a good idea
to wash your hands before you pee into a urinal
and i'll bet you the doctor is gonna go yeah that sounds like a good way to
avoid getting sick and germs and touching
touching your dick with your hands that you've been grabbing all over stuff and
grabbing it on escalator rails and then you pee
actually yeah i think that's a good idea that's what would happen anyways thanks
for the uh thanks for the 250 i wash my hands
multiple times potion toilet thanks for the 250
so glad you're finally playing this series it's one of my absolute favorites thanks
again don't forget misadventures of trombone is the mid game
between one and two and it's fantastic it's over 2 000 people here right now
and i know i know for a fact that at least
aura 500 people are sitting there on their tv they've
eaten a fucking pizza and they're pointing at the screen right now going
he's got it that's it he knows i know we both know and this yep
and then they rushed to their phone i gotta get i gotta log in and subscribe
to this guy quick i gotta watch every fucking single
stream too i gotta stop all right all right uh
now to happen new year by the way new year's resolution i'm not gonna make
the like subscribe joke anymore okay that that i know people like oh he
makes the joke and then somebody people sub that's
like reverse psychology all right i'm not gonna do that
happy new year i'm not gonna do that joke anymore new year's resolution
vr josh new year resolution pre-wash good that's a good resolution i hope you
do it uh siku thanks for the thousand bits thank
you siku appreciate it no message just that just
ten dollars in bits thank you it's slave thanks for the 250 germa
sorry i got drunk off the johnny walker and laid down my heart
it happens but it's true keep streaming until your boomer body can't take it
anymore boom on boomer boom on i found 34 i felt like 80
this is you know like this is not like the it's
1400s of people live to be like 48 that was like wow that's old
but now don't worry about it just take care of yourself drink some water get
some food get some rest 34 is 50 in internet years
that's a really great way to put it it actually is anything over 30 is
like 60 in internet years hey sprite 37
thanks for the five dollars sprite hope you enjoy megaman legends germa
this is uh this game is what got me into
animation and game development without it i doubt i'd be in the
professional industry so i'm very happy to watch you play it
it's very much a needed pick for me in the
busy past weeks thanks again yeah that's awesome
that's really really cool thank you so much for the five dollars and i think
the game's great that's the dev in chat well that's a dev that's in chat
not this dead then we had harold elbertson nine eight
five thanks to the 10 community subs we caught it
um cool name i mean it's mine but i guess you could have it too whiskey
ding thank you whiskey ding for the thousand
bits i'm a maker of bread i can teach you what is the over under that with 5000
people watching earlier today that there was at least
one baker that was in the chat it's probably pretty high
this probably one of each profession is sitting in the chat
five averages about the streams usually average somewhere more like four
4500 like 5000 people 6000 sometimes one of those four or five thousand
people has to be a baker one of them has to be a doctor
one of them is the president a president here
astronauts i'm sure there is would you guys know that's not even gonna
why would i do that and plus no one would answer it accurately
but like a chat census that would be kind of funny but it would be
all fucking wrong uh niall aurean thanks for the 300 bits the bread apology sucked
the guy with bad bread died because of you
i forgot about this uh you got all right every time a stream is more than eight
hours it's like three or four separate streams
in my brain i completely forgot about the whole bread
thing and the apology videos i couldn't that that may as well have
been two days ago for me that was that was like six hours ago
you're talking about in internet years it was like two days ago but yeah
thank you for the 300 bits i hope my apology was sufficient
uh cherry milk thanks to the six dollars 600 bits
hey germy wormy i just want to say thank you for always making me laugh until my
stomach hurts speaking of stomachs please tell me what
i should eat for lunch tomorrow a turkey and a turkey and avocado
club sandwich oh that sounds really good right now i wonder if i can get that at
hash house a go-go at the link it's a zoomer sandwich no it's not i've
been eating that since i was like fucking 15
come on uh zebra lord thanks to the five subs
avocado is gross well when you put it on stuff or you mash it up and spread it on
bread you don't even know it's there and it's really good for you
i only really eat avocado when it's on the turkey sandwich i don't eat it
anywhere else unless it's a guacamole so i don't it's just good for you it's
really good for you and you you spread it on stuff and it adds a little bit
i only eat it in guacamole or in turkey sandwich
i actually can't eat an avocado just out of the
shell just open it cut it in half pit it pull the center out
and eat it it's kind of mushy and too heavy and oily for me kind of i don't
like it i like it when it's in other stuff but
not by itself you wash your hands before and after
eating an avocado an avocado is not my dick
how clear do i have to make this to everybody i don't understand
why does this have to be such a point of contention
oh fuck uh oat horse thanks for 300 bits thank you oat horse
uh socomimus thanks for the 250 is that back brace for your it's sort of
costochondritis but thanks i appreciate it mr him thanks
for the 500 bits money for sleeping money for the sleeping while sick
advice thank you germa yeah just add a few pillows
drink some water take a little bit of nyquil not too much
should be good in a few days uh thank you mr him for the thousand bits don't
worry germa i'll never abandon you for vinnie's stream yeah i appreciate
that but if you know this it is a look listen to me
let me tell you something if you were to be on if you would watch tv right now
right you just sit down and i gave you the
remote and i said i'll be back in a couple
hours just uh put on whatever you want you're cycling you'll watch something
you'll change the channel you'll move like you people move around when they
watch tv it's the same deal people move around how many people
are streaming right now like 700 000 people it's a lot of tv
channels what the hell is a tv oh sorry your monitor your monitor or
your ipad screen or your iphone screen so no i
that it's all right it's all good don't worry thanks for the thousand bits
they'll appreciate it uh vincessity thanks for the 300 bits
why are you guys doing why are you guys adding each other and putting this
for and after eating an avocado you wash your hands before and after eating an
avocado avocado is not my dick it's not this is good
it's true what's wrong with that oh no we're gonna
do the uh credits now i have the credits i mean all that clip
is is me just saying a stay a factual statement there's
nothing else on that it's just i just told you a factual statement
let's uh change the scenes here around the credits thanks a lot everybody for
subbing all you new subs all your old subs and
everybody in between thank you bro a lot of you have decided
to give this stream five dollars a month every month some of you for more than
five years in a row which is fucking insane
i can't believe that people pay this channel and continue to stay here
especially for that long or if you just signed up for the first time thanks
you use twitch prime then fucking hell yeah thank you you could give that to
700 000 other streamers and you decided to give it to this one
we also had a couple more uh bits come in we had
another one from bit slave 250 from bit slave i hope you do i hope you get
better don't over exert yourself the more you push your body through its
disabilities the worse your outcome will be
have your girlfriend give you massages and sexy hot baths
relax don't go to the vegas strip instead strip in your home
i'm just kidding fellow gamer take this time to chill and be careful no bad
intentions to you or your girlfriend thank you thank you bit slave
i look forward to you getting your league of legends account back
i'm good i'm good don't worry drunk donation
maybe hey trilled hey trilled chaos thanks for the
1111 bits 11 dollars and 11 cents thank you
thanks a lot they say thanks buddy thank you
bit slave again we have 250 from bit slave here it is
i donate to you because i can afford it and i want you to be financially stable
i can live off the money i earn and donate to you
funny enough you pay my salary through taxes
and i think of it as me paying you back for doing we're doing harder and more
intense work than i do ah i'm not so sure about that i hope
you understand you mean to the thousands of viewers who stream to your legend a
league of legends it's still on the brain he hey guys he
just got banned come on i just like having fun and if you like
having fun too and you think that this was fun and you think the stream is fun
then we can have fun here together that's it that's pretty much all that's
it thanks for the support thank you for the
250 bits slave thanks frozen thor thanks for the 500 bits
germa funny thing happened the other week i was turning into a small artist
art stream and i used your sub emotes in her chat
and out of the five total viewers three of them were germa fans who have
recognized the emote we chatted heaps about you in your past
videos and we made song requests to the art streamer to listen to germa's songs
such as the berries song and the marching band song
additionally we also watched both rat movies on stream
she was confused but enjoyed them that would be pretty confusing man
jokes about having an avocado for a penis and makes ten thousand dollars a
month federal agents hate him i will tell you though all right
if you're watching another stream and you're enjoying somebody else's stream
make sure that when you're in that stream that if you're there for that
person that you've given them the attention
too you know what i mean make sure you're giving them attention not just
talking about germa streams you know you want to
support that person too support them first
like when you raid you when you raided joel
wait what we haven't done that yet he's pretending to be humble so we don't
notice he's a millionaire but you can't wait you can't be both
but how is me about being pretending to be humble to not have you not
noticed that i'm a millionaire i'm not a fucking millionaire
i'm not a goddamn millionaire you can't be humble
and a millionaire oh yeah we'll see we'll see we'll see we'll see
like it's about to happen you wouldn't be a millionaire for long
no i probably wouldn't and whatever all right i'm getting off this topic
i'm the king i'm humble don't ever say it's not me that's humble it's me that's
humble how dare you say otherwise do you know
fuck you're talking to ftk when good question
i actually have to talk to those developers getting close though
was this the super stream um no i mean it's it's about it's going to be about
the same time as lat yesterday's i wanted to do two longer streams i knew
i was going to be uh doing physical therapy so i want
because only two days in a row i like to do i'd like to do three days in a row
before i take any time off or take like a day or two you know what i mean i like
to do three i can't accidentally hit enter and fucked up
the last we'll get there in a sec anyways thank you
archive for the 500 bits durma you need a cigar care package
package filled to the brim with awesome smokes and insane natural flavors i
don't smoke why are you writing this that's strange
you sure sound like it i sound like a smoke
no do i no i don't you sure do sound like it
now i'm gonna say i'm gonna think about that all day you sound like you roll
your own cigarettes i've smoked a cigarette one
time in my whole life and it was to try to
do an audition i told you that already you guys already know about the cigarette
commercial audition i did remember yes how many do and that's
it we got one more from uh edmund akari they say the 500 bits five
dollars they say what and apparently they screwed it up
i wonder what the rest of that message won thanks for the 500 bits
edmund appreciated good night i'll see you guys in a few days
uh i will see you on wednesday to be more precise and exact
wednesday afternoon you know the time you know the day
we're gonna raid joel because i know i haven't said hello to joel in a few
weeks couple weeks at least hope you had fun i'll see you soon
good night and goodbye