Hey, Fred. Hey, Fred. Hey, Fred. What's up? How you doing? Welcome back. Hey, Bonnie. Well,
you said B-A-R-N. It's Bonnie. B-A-H. If you were going to be Fred replying. Hey, Bonnie. Yeah. I
just don't, I don't want to correct you in front of a hundred thousand people, but I'm going to.
All right. So today, last time we were live, last time I was live, it's me. Can you do a Gandalf
voice? I'm ready to do voices today. I'm ready to do some voices today. The, I was going to play
Final Fantasy 16 because I just want to play Final Fantasy 16, but we got really into Sorcery a couple
days ago and it's like, all right, I, we left on a cliffhanger. I can't just end it on a cliffhanger
like that and maybe not play it for like three weeks. Let's play Sorcery. We're going to chill
out. Audiobook Andy is here tonight. I'm going to read this story, go over some of the choices.
Why don't you relax? Why don't you get comfortable? We've got some work going on
on the second monitor. We've got something going on, something else, killing some time.
Or maybe it's time for you to go to sleep. Maybe you're, you know, could be in Europe.
I'd be late right now. Turn the volume down. And I really mean that because some of the sounds in
this game are loud. All right, so we'll pick up right where we left off. Not much else of an intro.
This is a three minute intro. This fastest intro. This is the fastest intro I've ever done.
Can we get a recap? Yeah, we'll get a recap. Honestly, we didn't really do that much.
We walked in a big circle and I lost a finger. I just did a huge circle, learned two clues about
different serpents and then lost a hand or whatever it was. You didn't even need to lose it.
Yeah, I know. I feel like I did the same thing last time too. You snorted the horn dust. Oh,
yeah, I forgot. I didn't even get out with the horn. Hey, remember you are bald also. Well, no,
I'm not. Okay, here's the thing. You can call me, oh my god, he can't even do puzzles. He's a fucking
idiot. Oh my god, he's 5'8". I'm taller than him. Oh my god, there's a lot of things that you can
say about me that are true. And it's like, whatever, that's fine. I have beautiful hair.
It's very healthy. It's, it's luscious. You don't have that on me. You just don't.
And I'm almost 40 years old. And this, I don't have a single gray fucking hair on my whole head.
It is wondrous what my hair is like. So you can, that's one of the things that I, you can call me,
you can say anything about me all you want. You don't touch the hair though, because it's healthy.
I'm going to wake up tomorrow and it's going to be receding. And it's going to be such a disaster.
I'm going to be like, oh, I'm going to be doing my, you know, washing my face. And I'll go,
I'm going to have just pulling clumps out or something. I know. I just going to stop talking
about it. I, my hair is very healthy. Every time I go get a haircut, they say the same thing. They
go, your hair is really healthy. And I always do the thing. I don't know. Does everybody else
do this? But I'm getting a haircut. I kind of be like, yeah, you know, it's thinning. It's thinning.
I try my best. You know, it's, it's, it's thinning. I know it's a, I'm losing it. And then they always
say the same thing. No, no. What are you talking about? It's, it looks fine. It looks good. It
looks healthy. Am I, am I just being lied to or does everybody do that? He's fishing for compliments.
Now I genuinely kind of feel, I don't know, because when my hair is really wet,
it's really obvious that it's receding. I'm also one of those people that never knows what haircut
they're getting. As a 37 year old, I'll sit down in that chair. Cause sometimes it's, it's a while
and it's like, what, what do you want to do? And I'm just like, ah, I don't know. I have no idea.
It's like, oh, do you want to take some off? No, I want to leave the length. Okay. Do you want to
take up some of the back or the sides? Yes. How much? Um, can you just, you just do it with
scissors first and then we'll figure it out. It's like, okay. And then it's always just with scissors
and I never go any further. Can you just trim? Why are you, why are you going? Cause you got to
clean it up. You can't just let your, even if you grow your hair out, those of you that have
grown your hair out long, you know, you've got to clean up the ends and shape it. So it grows out
and makes grows onto your head and makes it look, you can't just have it. You cannot just
let your hair grow completely wild without cleaning it up. If you want to have it, you know, fall on
your head and shoulders correctly. Is this a PR stunt? Me telling you that I've, I sit in the,
what do you mean PR? A PR stunt would be if I turn the face cam on right now and I was completely
bald with like a completely shaved with like a Gillette razor. And I started just ranting
about hair or something, but no, this is just me talking. Is that what's going to happen?
Shave your eyebrows off. No. Is he actually bald? Okay. I just said a brand name. That doesn't mean
I, I just was talking about the, I said, Oh, I said a brand's name. All right. Are you ready?
You guys ready to play? We, enough people trickled in. I know the sorcery streams aren't necessarily
for everybody, but they're for me. So I'm having a good time. And there you go. That's all I have to
say face cam. No, no face cam ever for sorcery. It takes the immersion out. You end up being able
to just the reason. Okay. Here's the reason why I don't want face cam on during sorcery streams
because you know, the behind the scenes videos of the actors reading the script in the studio
with all the soundproofing around the walls. Imagine if that was in the corner on every episode
of Spongebob. I don't, I think you'd be like, I, there's a, there's a guy in the corner.
I just, I want, I want Spongebob on the screen. That would be sick. Yeah. It'd be cool for a,
but like, but then it's not like Spongebob talking. It's, I have a live cam of the actor doing
Spongebob. Let's just use that as an example. It's just Spongebob is talking, but also Spongebob,
the actor is talking. You know what I mean? This is a bad take. I don't think it is.
I, I don't think this is a bad take. I mean, for a behind the scenes video,
that makes perfect sense to me. That's really cool. I love that stuff, but I don't want that
like on the episode. He's right. He's right. He's right. Yeah. Thank you. One guy, Spongebob,
the author, Spongebob, the author. Are you our Spongebob? No, that's, I'm not, I'm not,
I'm not, I'm not, no, I'm sorry. I ain't anybody's anything. Okay. Let's get that real clear.
You turned into Spongebob for you. You're doing Spongebob for PR right now. You rejected our,
in quotes, not Spongebob in quotes. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Oh, it's very, very, that was very clear.
This is the shortest intro I've ever done. Yeah. Well, whatever. Sorcery crew is here. And you
know, this is, we're good. This is the sorcery crew. I can be way more candid with the sorcery
crew. You know what I mean? Like I can be, I can talk to you guys. I can talk to you guys.
That's what you guys, you guys get it. Except almost 90% of the chat is contradicting everything
I'm saying. So maybe I can't trust the sorcery crew as much as I thought I could. Hmm. Are you
high right now? No. Are you? Are you? All right. Here comes some wind. All right. So let's do a
recap. This is where we were. This is where we left off. Hello. Welcome back. So we are right
outside this looks like a some kind of dwelling. Let's go. Let's freaking go. It's a sorcery stream
of course. Well, whatever. That's a, that's between you. It's between you and God. And you know,
obviously the legality of the state or county that you're currently in. I was talking about,
somebody said they were smoking weed. I'm not in the US. Can we get a recap? All right. So here's
a recap from a couple days ago. We started here. I went over, I went to the bridge. I actually,
actually where did we start? We started here. Okay. Yeah. So I went over the bridge. I climbed
down it. I fell off. I broke both of my legs. I got fixed. I went backwards. Tried to cross
the bridge normally. Lost a finger to the toll. Went up through here. Decided I could not go any
further. Went through here into this town. This town was pretty interesting. They told us about
a mine that was a tunnel that was essentially very dangerous. Went through that. Did not pick up any
of the items. Did not talk to the dog that was in here. But we made it out alive and with full
health, which is a huge deal. And four rations. Made it through here. Got to this point. We fought
a couple of Snatacats. But I lost a finger here. So we have made our way through. We went to the
forest of Snata. We did find this lake. I snorted a mushroom and passed out face first into the water
and had a bunch of hallucinations and a bat saved my life. That was pretty interesting. And then we
walked up here. Ended up in the north side of the forest of Snata. Leading us to here. Which this is
sort of some kind of house or hut in the woods. And we can go knock on the door. Remember,
recap. We are trying to hunt down the seven Serpents. We do not get rid of the seven Serpents
if we don't stop them. They will tell the Archmage that we are coming. We don't want that to be a
thing. We want to stop the seven Serpents with our various quests. And when we do those quests,
we will complete those quests. It'll be good to go to episode four. You mean six? Yes, that's
right. Six are dead. No, six are alive. Wait, what are you asking? One is dead. Six are alive.
Let's go knock on the door. Okay. The door is made of heavy wood carved with various runes and
symbols in a language you do not know. Do I just open this? Oh yeah. Mind your volume tonight.
The like, yeah, see it's a little loud in some places, but one of the spells to open any door
is stop opens locks and doors. The door might just be open. This might be a waste of time. I
have a lot of stamina. I could throw a grenade at the door. Wait, what? Didn't I get a pebble?
What happened to my pebble? I got pebbles. It was too hot. You dropped it. What? Oh, it was.
I could see. Oh, I could read minds. All right. I wonder if I can put, because I have, if I put
the skull cap on and see if I can read somebody's mind. I mean, it doesn't cost any stamina. I could
just do it. Let's see. You turn the stars into shape around you, pulling on the cloth skull cap
as the magic takes hold, but you are alone. So there are no thoughts to hear. What if I just
open the door? You tried the door. It is not locked. A dark passageway is revealed. All right.
So we would just open the door. I probably should have knocked, but we're already here.
The door opens through a short, dark hallway, descends into the hill. This is a tomb. You begin
to see a glowing light ahead and hear a voice muttering low, angry curses. Make a move. A little
sunshine falls through the doorway. There's still time to turn back. We're just going in. You keep
moving forwards and the passage quickly opens up. You enter a small room lit by a single candle on
a wooden table. Seated at the table is a spindly creature whose attention is focused on a glass
orb set on a plinth. We should take that. Let's watch. Oh, I think I remember this.
You watch as the creature stares into their orb, which swirls with colors and shapes.
It mumbles something quietly. Announce myself. You open your mouth to announce yourself,
but the silence is broken by a squeaky voice. Yes, yes, yes. All right. Don't stare like a half
orc. I'm busy. Sit down. Thin finger gestures towards a chair in the corner. What can I even
do here? I could do nap cause sleepiness. I don't have pendulum. Uh, that's it. I could read minds
in here. This is going to be weird. Me holding like two fingers up, like, uh, X-Men style.
This also is, what's L? This is law. Law is controlled, non-intelligent creatures.
I feel like this, this, I feel like there's intelligence here though.
Mud. Oh, we just, I could make quicksand. I have sand. Do I just make a just giant
death trap in the middle of this person's house? Why would you do that though?
I don't know. Oh, this could be a sorceress. It could be a sorcerer. I don't know.
Let's talk. I'll sit down. Sit. You sit down as instructed. After a few minutes,
the creature leans back from her orb and looks up at you. So a visitor, a human too. Greetings.
Greetings to you indeed. As the light from the glass orb fades a little, you see this speaker
is a woman, some kind of elf, though she appears somewhat disfigured. What is your name? Finestra.
Now human, as my time is more precious than yours, I will soon lose my patience with you.
What in Gred's name are you doing in this miserable fortress? Forest is not a fortress
anywhere to be found. That's in Mampang. Uh, I don't think you just, I don't think you put
all your cards on the table. I'm looking for seven serpents. Uh, I'm going to Lake Iklala.
I'm going to Lake Iklala. You tell her, cautious not to reveal your true purpose to this stranger.
She nods. It can be hard to cross the lake. There's only one ferryman and he is old now.
I have a whistle which you may use to summon him if you wish. Thank you. It's not free. I will charge
you five gold pieces. I don't have that much. Shake my head. Just, no. Trey Pang 2 released?
What the fuck? Oh, cool. I'll play it. Uh, let's haggle. I will give you three. Okay, very well then.
Agreed. You hand over the money and she places the whistle into your hand. How does it work?
You put it up to your lips and blow. There is nothing magic about it. It's just a whistle.
If the ferryman is about, and he is most mornings, then he will hear you and come. You stash the
whistle away without further comment. The orb on her table swirls with color ever more violently.
Benestra sits up sharply. You must go. I have work that must be attended to. What do you see
in the orb? You ask. See for yourself. Pointing into the glass. Shapes swirl inside the crystal.
Should I look into the orb or don't look? Look into the orb. You peer into the orb and then your
jaw begins to drop. For inside the glass is a winged serpent. It is the Sun Serpent. The one
called Flanker helped me to trap it. I lured it down from the skies using a rain spell and offered
it shelter. But the Sun Serpent cannot tolerate water of course. And then he trapped it. I know
Flanker. I know Flanker well. This poor creature despises him. Don't you? She taps on the glass
and the serpent lunges uselessly against the glass in reply. Why not kill it? The Sun Serpent
is the mate of the Water Serpent. They have a doomed, impossible love. It is enough for me
to lure the beast. And when it comes, I will kill them both. But the creature might escape.
We must destroy it for good. Be warned, Annalander. This serpent will reach into your mind and control
your will if you allow it. It would do anything to be free. I gotta smash it. Smash it. Take it.
Smash it. Look into it. What can I do here? Zap. Boom! Out of the finger. Same joke. Same joke. Same
joke. From 2016. Same joke. From 2016. Are we going same joke, Andy? Is that what we're doing?
Like eight years later? No. I'm going to, I'm going to read her mind. You place the skull cap
on your head as if you craft the spell. You hear the serpent's thoughts enter your mind.
It is swirling in anger around cursing Fenestra and you. Oh, I can't get the fuck out of here.
Okay. I don't know what to, what's the, I don't know what the, there's no right answer in this
game, but I wonder what the path of least problems is. If I look into it, will he like control me?
Take it. Take the orb. There's no way this orb can hold the creature and should it escape,
your mission will be revealed. The orb must come with me. The fate of the land is at stake.
You may take it and return for two promises. No. First, that you will destroy this orb and
the snake inside in such a fashion that they cannot return. Know that breaking the glass
will set it free. So be sure you do not do that. I shall drop it into a canyon.
That sounds like a good plan. I will bury it. I shall drop it into a lake. And what is the second
thing? You nod understanding. The second thing is more important. Find the water serpent in Lake
Lala and do not leave it alive and do not die in the attempt to kill it. Will you do that for me?
I shall do my best. I shall. Wow. Oh no. I shall. You vow. Then with a nod, she steps aside and
lets you take the orb with the trapped serpent inside. It will not serve you for the casting of
far. The serpent will not allow it. I have an orb of my own already. You too. I have an orb of my
own already too. Well then we both own orbs. Yes we do. Then I'm going to put the strange orb carefully
into my pack. You turn on your heel and leave the underground room. So let me get this burn into
memory here. I can't break this. If I break this it will come out and that's bad. There is a serpent
in the glass cube. I need to make sure I destroy it. The water serpent and the sun serpent know
each other very well. So we have to destroy it somehow. Okay. You got it. Well let's head there
now. Yeah I think we- here's the plan. Ready? Streamer's Choice. Streamer Vito coming in here.
We're going to go down here. Stop by whatever this little hut is. And by the way get Elden Ringed.
For those of you that just got here. Yeah. You get a problem? All right so I'm going to go this way.
I'm going to go down. Cringe. Is the story in Sorcery the same every time? It is. The- the A
and the Z are always exactly the same. And honestly so is- so is like the LMNOP is usually
kind of the same like throughout as well. But everything else is kind of your- on your own.
But I mean well it really depends. Everybody's goal is exactly the same. You're the Annalander.
You're trying to go get the Crown of Kings that was stolen from you and the Crown of Kings is
the Infinity Gauntlet. It's like the god power. It literally makes you unstoppable. You're unbeatable.
And the Archmage has it. The Archmage is evil. You're back in the sunshine of the clearing.
You feel the serpent in your bag and angry as it senses the heat and light around. You have the
sense that things are watching you from the trees. It's time to move. All right so I want to go down
because going back wrapping around left is not a good idea. So we're going to go this way. A wide
track leads away from the door into the trees. And here we go. So we're going to stop here.
See what this is. The goal is to eventually before Stream ends today to go get the Water Serpent.
And you're probably asking yourself bro it's like right here. Yeah okay yep it is right there. See
you in like four hours because it's good. That's how long it's going to take us to get over there.
The heckin Infinity Gauntlet? Yep. I just spilled all over me. Hold on a second. Okay if I got like
a huge replica Infinity Gauntlet and just like put it on and turned the cam full cam and just
started just played the like Avengers theme song. How long do you think we could keep that up?
Where I was like yeah no it's like holding it up into the camera and stuff. How long do you think
that could go on for? Do you think more than 10 minutes straight of that would be unfair before
a DMCA? Before you laugh 10 seconds? No no no no I would get in character. You guys there okay there's
two different ways that I operate on Stream. There's like I'm into this and I'm dedicating
into my mind. I'm an actor and I am I will you can't break me. You never will. But then there's
I'm just hanging out and I laugh in five seconds. Which one of them will it be? I mean if I treat it
like it's a you know like a character or something then it should be easy. It's gonna be so hard though.
You have to be committed. What's this worth to you guys? That's what I want to know.
What is a 10 straight minute Infinity Gauntlet pog stream worth to you? And no laughing. I can't
make any sounds. I have to just be excited and going over all the stones and what they do and
shit and like aiming it at that camera and like holding it up and doing like the two fingers like
I'm gonna snap and stuff. Was it worth you? Because that's it that is 10 straight minutes
of embarrassing myself in front of millions of potential people. What's it worth? You should
paint yourself purple. I'd rather you don't do that. Yeah put up a paid poll for bits. He
he's gonna do it or he won't do it. What's it worth to you? That's actually kind of funny.
I would pay to have you not do that. I would pay to have you do that. Have like a fucking money
fight to have the 40 year old clown either put on the Infinity Gauntlet or not. What a strange time
we live in. Don't you think? I think these are very strange times. These are very interesting times.
It's very odd. All right let's keep going. No no no don't actually do it. Don't actually do it.
Did you actually do it? Okay yeah I don't I don't no we're not doing that. I'm saying it's
really funny but okay it's just a regular poll okay. Somebody okay if I do a paid version somebody
is just gonna be like you know what? I got a lot of fucking money in my account and I'm making sure
this motherfucker does not do that. There'll be one like thousand dollar drop or something
to just ruin everything. That's why I don't want to do it. Please change your wallpaper. I like that
wallpaper. It reminds me of going to the beach. It's a beach right? Yes it is. It reminds me of
going to the beach and I like the beach. I've been described as beachy. I've been described as beachy.
So I have like a beach aesthetic. I like the beach. I've been described as very beachy.
I've been described as enjoying the beach a lot is what I'm trying to say. The path winds
tortuously through the forest nightfall as you need to rest. The path passes by a heavy thicket
of tangled branches. Let's investigate it. The dense bushes curl up around themselves in a tangle
but in the darkness you can make out nothing more. I think this is good it's night time we should
sleep. The thicket will make a good shelter. You clamor into a hollow between its roots and lie
down. Laying your pack down by the roots of a tree you try to rest despite the strange noises
that float across the landscape. At least you have eaten already today. Then we're good. The
stream runs tortuously through the Thanos rant. You got I I really do wonder because the amount
of people that would pay to make sure I ended up in cringe compilations. Do you know what I mean?
Like there are there's some of you here that that's worth a lot of money to you to make sure that
that happens. You know like I know that's what you'd be doing it for. You don't need to pay to see
that. Are you already in them? Nah you already are there. No what? Stop. Do we live rent free
in your head? Not really. I mean during streams yeah and maybe like maybe sometimes. I feel like
by the very nature of being a live streamer I'm constantly thinking about like the stream and
stuff. All right I'll think about it. I'll think about it. Maybe I don't know maybe I'll just put
it to charity or something. That'd be it's easy way to do that right? I don't it's like a better
way to do it probably. I don't know. We'll see. I'll think about it. Charity incentive war to have
me do it or not do it. The easiest way to do it is to never do it. Actually true and that is that is
a that chat comment is just like you get it. You get it. But I'm sorry I don't. I guess I'll never
learn. That's what makes me the cool streamer. I did that to specifically get into a cringe
compilation so let's go. All right your eyes close and you let your tiredness overtake you.
You wake suddenly. There's a flapping of dark wings from overhead. A giant bat is circling above
you. Your journey has been plagued by these creatures. What can I do? Let's see. You should
title that stream to cringe or not to cringe? That is the question. Oh man and I'm dressed up in a
Shakespeare outfit. Uh there's obviously danger. Pep is strength. I think I'm just fight. I don't
want to waste any stamina. Let's fight. This bat has a lot of attack power. This guy is the CCO of
off-brand. I just came up with an incredibly engaging live stream event right now. Are you
trying to tell me that that was not that's not what just happened? Just tell me that's wrong.
I'm going full blast. All right it's actually good that I did.
Have Ludwig do it. No it has to be me. Although I kind of like that too though.
Uh I'm going to defend. Yep. Uh I'm going all in. Sorry. I would I would read these but it's pretty
you can read them. It's just kind of like you swung and hit them. Okay what about all the Avengers
or different streamers and during the all the costumes are on the ground and we are over the
course of the next 45 minutes going to get into these costumes and like if there's enough money
that's telling us to no to not do it then we don't do it and if there's enough that that says yes
then we continue to put it on over then after 45 minutes we end it and see where it is. Could have
gone fallen. Would you say what would the point what would be the point of that just to see you
guys in costumes? No because once we get yeah what is the point of this? The point is to get
in the costumes and be and just and do like Avengers scenes and because people hate it
fairly. Fuck I thought he was going to go low. Avengers hot dove stream. It's going to be the
Hulk and they just get into the water and they're just green paint just starts coming off. All right
this little bat is fucking me up. I gotta pay attention. Stop defending when you're being good
at the game and it's annoying. I could have done it again. All right I gotta all right all right
that's a that's a fun idea. I'll add it to the to the notepad. Here we go. Only one? Okay creatures
eyes are fixed on you. There comes a big one. I'm getting I'm getting absolutely destroyed right now.
This is ridiculous. There's no way he's going more than 3.0 and he's not. All right I gotta go
all in. There's no way he's gonna go out. No he's not. Yes he is. Oh my god I'm just getting outplayed.
Oh my god fuck you. Why this bat? I I I fought like I fought a gigantic like Chimera and I beat it
easier than the single bat. What the fuck? What? Fucking die. Yes all right. How much did I lose?
12 health. Whatever. The creature falls from the sky dead. You lost some gold. Entered the
Vishalami Marsh and you collected the sun serpent meaning there are now only five serpents remaining.
And we have to make like an original song and put like different memes from all the Avengers
characters. Like you know sing about like a Thanos is gonna snap you and shit. It's something fucking
awful. You know what I'm saying? An original song that we all have to sing in unison.
It's it hurts. I'm just trying to figure out how to get the most money.
Only if you paint yourself purple. All right I'm I'm stuck on this and I need to get off of it.
Well I've what I said for charity. This is not most money for me. I said this would be a charity
stream. That's the best way to do it. This is guys this is not happening. I just puke out random
bullshit sometimes. This is not happening. We're not doing this. This is not a thing we're doing
tomorrow. Let's say that's how you reel them in right? Now they want they want it to happen.
Hey yeah you and me get it right? We know. Okay all right I let we're playing we're playing we're
playing again. The bush is a thick tangle peering between the branches. You can make out something
covered over. Oh I have the axe. You hew the branches away with the axe in swift easy strokes.
The foliage falls away to reveal first a glassless window and then the top corner of a door. It seems
the branches are growing in front of and out of an ancient hut. Go in the window? Did you? Yeah I
took 10 damage from the bat. I'm gonna cut free. Cut free the door. You keep cutting until you have
uncovered the door enough that you might be able to pull it open. Let me look in here first. Before
going inside you think to peer in through the window. You can make a little out through the
thick foliage that continues inside. When it seems the hut is otherwise empty then for a moment
something seems to move. But looking again you see nothing. Could be a genetic health. I'm gonna go
in. I would say I had a lot of health but I have a lot of food. You heave on the door hauling it open
ancient dust spills out into the forest air and a million crawling things scuttle from holes all
over the ancient wood. Smell the air. The air from inside the hut is an old and stale air but it does
not stink of death decay or animal. You look about for where to go. Are we going in or am I running
by? Go in? Going. When are you going to drink the grimace milkshake? I don't know. When I go to
McDonald's I'll make sure to get one. Okay. You push your way inside the ancient overgrown hut.
There are patches of yellow moss. Much like the one you tried earlier. Growing on the back of a
wall. Oh really? This is edible. You gather up a handful of moss. It is much like the last bunch
you ate. Eat it. There we go. You chew through the moss. Feeling much better for it. All right I'm
gonna I'm gonna do suss. What do we got? Definitely there's suss. There's also sap. Cause depression.
Also by the way for those of you that have never played this game. If you sap and there's nobody
to sap. It happens to you. You literally cast it on yourself because it attaches to the first
living thing in the room. So I don't think I want to do that right now. You can do sun. I have a sun
jewel and it's free. Just brighten it up. See the future. I can use the crystal ball here. The
crystal ball is useful. Sense danger. I'll do I'll do the meme. Cast suss. Craft the enchantment and
a steady voice begins to speak to you. It informs you quite calmly. The hut is not empty. Goodbye.
Okay. Something here. Let's look around. In the thin sunlight through the windows of the hut,
you can make out writing on the far wall. This is the house Elisey built and in its doorway
blood was spilled but that blood has dried and gone and poor Elisey is still alone.
Hmm. Look at the doorway. Looking at the doorway you see the dark shadow of a bloodstain
wiped carefully around the sill like a ward against an evil spirit. Not that such magic
works of course. The only true magic comes from the stars. At least that's what they told you.
There are a few more things scratched into the wood. What does it say? You look at the other
scratched marks. They're they are hard to comprehend precisely. One appears to depict a person in a
circular bubble floating harmlessly above a raging tornado or a whirlpool. Another shows a fiery
ball. Perhaps the sun. Perhaps not. Being drenched by a fist squeezing what looks like a handful of
berries. Interesting. So we got floating which is the float spell. Raging tornado is I think
with the horn right? It causes like a windstorm. Fiery ball that's hot potentially and drenched
by a handful of berries. Let me see. Looking into the dim corners of the hut you uncover an
old vial of water. As you lift it to the light it gives off a very faint shine. In your mind
you feel the ape's gentle voice. Watery this vial is blessed to the god Gred. Gred. Do I take this?
I'm I think if I take this and I drink it the ape is gone and we might get a new god. We might get
the god Gred. I'll keep it. I'll keep it. You place the vial of holy water into your pack.
A lucky find. Oh all right so let me just what do we got here? There's some obviously some puzzle
here or some secret to do. One of them was floating. This is see the future. I can't do
floating. I could just cause depression. What is it? What is this? Doc is heal disease. I need a
medicinal potion. I could do sap but who would I even do it to? I think I'm missing information.
I'm gonna look into the future. You settle into a sitting position by the roots of a tree and take
out the orb of a crystal. Reaching up to the constellations overhead you create the spell.
You're somewhere new. The world seems to disappear replaced by a vision. A ring of tall shadowy
stones in a desolate waste. You stand by their center holding above your head a long yellow
feather taken from some colossal bird. You are casting a spell of curious power. I did this
before. Should I drop it? Dude you should use phar to see if you do the cringe avengers stream.
I'm gonna drop it. As the spell builds you panic and release the feather. Slowly it flutters to the
ground but as it does so the spell of this strange place takes hold. The feather erupts into vivid
flame and you shield your eyes. It fades. The day is likely to be clear and will be hot once more.
Did I just do that to get the weather forecast? The day is likely to be clear will there be hot
later in the afternoon. Showers coming in tomorrow evening. Okay I don't think I can do anything here.
You know what I'm just gonna cause depression. Why not? Sap. You gather the constellations into
order around you and immediately feel yourself losing your energy and drive. With no other
creature nearby the magic is turned on you. Oh great. What the hell is it? I'm missing an item.
I can't do it I don't think. It's probably dock. Yeah it has to. It's either dock or damn it.
I can't. I can't do it. I gotta go. Go back outside. Can't do it. Damn it. I couldn't solve
the riddle of the hut. There is nothing more to be done here. You leave the hut behind. Okay well
I wanted to go over here. Oh I can't go over there. That's like a hundred that's like 300
feet in the air. I need this to be fixed. Let me see what happens if I go down here. You walk on
between the trees as the sun climbs towards its zenith. The winds pick up. A large ancient tree
has fallen down across the path. I'm the trunk for review. You clamor up onto the trunk and look off
into the distance of the trees. To the east the mountains rise tall and cold and to the south
you see the forest pool. A soft plop echoes from the tree trunk. You leave your pack on the tree
trunk and move carefully along its length. Eyes peeled for what it was making that sound. Suddenly
of its own accord your pack topples from the trunk and onto the ground. Somebody invisible? Pick it
up. You return to your pack and reach down to pick it up and something bashes you backwards.
Fresh blood springs into your arm. You have been scratched by deep claws but you can still see
nothing. God damn it it's a snatacat. Let's talk with animals. All right we're doing yap.
Grabbing the wig from your pack you put it on and weave your spell. The faint growls in the
trees slowly begin to slur, turning into distinct words. The creature appears to be talking to
itself. Side open. Stay down. Stay low. I can hear you, you call back, speaking in the creature's
language of growls and whines. Stay where you are. It tries to fool me but it can't.
Being invisible has clearly driven this creature quite insane. Leave or I will skin you. What are
you? It wants to know what I am. It wants to know what eats it. It wants to know what eats it. It
wants to know who. Leave or I will skin you. This is your only warning. The creature seems to consider
for quite a moment. Then it launches itself forward. Suddenly long gashes appear on your
arm as claws that you cannot see seem to rake your flesh. For a moment you feel hot breath
on your cheek. Then it's gone. You could have casted sun in the hut. I thought all I had was
um I could. It wasn't just sap and sus. Really? Really? Really? Really? Like really? Really?
Really? Really? I'm going back. That's one out of three. That's all right. Okay look at the doorway.
Look at the scratches. Search the corners. Yep they take the vial. Okay cast a spell.
Oh you weren't full of shit. All right let's cast sun. You craft the enchantment until the sun jewel
starts to glow with a magical white glow. Nothing. Nothing. Didn't do anything. It just looks cool.
Remember why do your tags say thinking about beans? I don't think they do. Huh maybe combine
with a different one. You have to sleep in here. Really? It does. Thinking about beans. I don't know.
I didn't do it. All right see what happens. God damn it. I think I have to come back here.
All right well now. All right it didn't work. Your tags are fucked up. It doesn't matter.
Okay soft plop move. I'm not fighting anything. You rise quickly and gather your things listening
carefully for any suspicious sounds and you catch one a soft deep growl a few feet away.
So just run. I'm just gonna run. You waste no more time and scurry away between the trees. Okay
here we are again. I need to move this to the right. I wonder is there a way down here. I could
go down here and see if I can get across somehow. We haven't gone down here at all. I haven't seen
any of this. I'm gonna turn this over here and see if I can do anything or maybe I'll turn it down
this way. I can swim. It's it's fine. I lost a fucking food. Your fragile possessions are ruined.
All your soft food has been ruined. What the fuck. It's all right. One food loss is fine. Yeah it's
fine. Okay I still can do this but I'm afraid to touch it. So what can I get up there if I go like
this? Is that intact? I don't think it is. Is the bridge intact if I do that? It's hard to tell. I
don't think so. What about this way? Looks like it. I wonder if I can get. I'm talking about over
here though. It might be hard to actually do it. I have to activate another beacon I think. Yeah it
gets kind of messed up on the left side. It's all right. I'll aim it this way. I don't want to aim
it all. This is a town over there. I'll aim it over here. That way or something. Oh so this is
the town in the past. This is the town now. It looks pretty much in ruins right now. What do you
think? Should I go to Tin Pang? Tin Pang in the in the past first? Yeah let's check out the past
first. So that'll be fine. Now I could just go down. This is another beacon so I'll go like this
and we'll explore Klattaback. Klattabang? Klattaback? All right I'm going down. I'm going to eat.
Somebody said eat food before you lose it. That's a good idea. Let's eat a cooked meat. Make a move.
Get the ring please I beg you. I don't know how to get it because if I break the branch it falls
down. If it falls down it falls into the water and if it falls into the water I can't get it.
If it falls down in the water I can make the beam go over there but I did that and I can't get it.
I don't know. It's tricky. Maybe the other tower? Point it at the other tower. Just take it off the
branch when it's smaller. The ring doesn't necessarily fall in the water. If you go into
the past the tree won't be grown by then. Hey. You know. Hold on. Can I concentrate this beam
that way? Because if I can concentrate that this way then this can go in the past. Come back here
when the ring is. Yeah. Maybe it'll reach. One of these will do it so I'll leave it. All right so
we're gonna head down here. I got this pointing over at that of the town. Let's make a move. Wait
I have to swim across again? I can't just like bury my face through the trees? God damn it. Okay
well whatever. I'm good. Your videos on this game got me through a day where I was throwing up every
half hour. Well that sounds awful. Okay. Things flutter in the trees all around. Hope you feel
better. Wait that was like eight years ago. Hope you felt better eight years ago. Things flutter
in the trees all around. The sun is all but gone. Soon it will be dark. A movement in the bushes
catches your eyes. A glimpse of red and a snake's body. This is the red snake that we've seen a few
times. I might be getting I might be being watched. Let's go. Let's investigate it. Why not? The snake
disappears before you can catch it. God damn. Do I want to go up and around or should I just go
straight down? I'll just go straight down. Easier that way. The path winds torturously through the
forest. Darkness closes in. You should try to find a suitable spot to sleep. Underfoot the earth has
been churned to mud and you notice the branches either side of this route are broken. Let's look
at the mud. You pause to check the mud. Sure enough you quickly find a sign. A paw print at least
twice the size of your palm. Yeah there's a snat of cats everywhere. We need to go through this
quickly. We gotta we gotta go. You keep moving hoping that whatever lives around here doesn't
find you. Snat of cats are everywhere here. They're very dangerous. We don't have time to
investigate every branch that falls. You walk on between the trees in the darkness you can see
nothing through the curling branches. Almost out of it. Are they invisible? They are invisible.
You trace what might be a path and might be an old river through the trees of the forest.
The moon sets. More stars appear. You've reached the edge of the forest. Through the trees you
can see the level steps extending into the night. Now might be a good time to rest before
you go much further. I really don't want to do it here but I need to sleep. Removing your pack by
the roots of a tree you try to settle despite the cold. At least you have eaten well already.
You lie back and try to forget your troubles. You wake halfway through the night at the sound
of breathing from between the trees. Snat of cat. What if I stay still? You stay quite still.
Something is sniffing the air. It is a wolf. Padding closer. It's a wolf. Maybe I could talk
to the wolf. Tell. Read minds. Wrap. Talk all languages. Raz. Sharpen blade. There's always zap.
Always. That's my entire first playthrough of the game. Pep is strength. There's also pop which is
grenade but I don't have a pebble. Let's see if we can talk. Talk all languages. Grabbing the
wig from your pack you put it on and weave your spell but this spell is intended for translating
non-human speech and not the utterances of beasts and animals. Come here talk to me. Oh okay. Yeah
rap is talk all languages. Yap is talk to animals. Okay well why can I not do yap? I just don't feel
like it. Just zap this fucker. Zap. You gather the constellations into order around you building up
a charge of electrical energy around your palm. Fire the bolt into the sky. This would be scary
right? Into the sky? All right I'm going into the sky. You fire the lightning bolt up into the air
and the flash cracks the heavens. The wolf squeals in fear and turning on the spot it bolts away into
the night. The silence of the trees returns but I have alerted every single person in this five
mile radius of my existence. You wake with your head on a tree root and the smell of fresh dew
in your nostrils. Time to choose a direction. There maybe is something to be said about going
up this way and investigating whatever this is but hey that's for you to do in your playthrough.
I'm getting out of the sonata forest. It's too dangerous. Jeremy can you ask my mom to get me
the grimace shake? I don't I don't know I'm not your parent. I'm not it's not like oh hey let me
go ask the streamer to can hey ma streamer said I can. You head out across the steps the air stirs
a little still cold but fresh. In front of you stretches another plane more rock than dust this
time and built of layers and layers of stone stacked like scattered papers. These are the
clatterback steps said to be the home of strange half human half asymian creatures. As you walk you
see a strange sight a village of listing huts in the middle of open space with no walls or defenses
at all. Ugly villagers lope from tent to tent dressed in animal skins. The men and women are
strong and lanky dressed in animal skins by the gate two creatures stand with hefty wooden clubs
clatter men. What can I do? Mods please link him the grimace shake on TikTok. You don't need to give
me the I know what the grimace shake is. I can go invisible. Invisible? There's also big I could grow
in size to be huge. I could say what's safe passage here. I could cause stench but I don't
have a nose plug. I could also summon a giant. I could just walk in there with a giant and be like
hey me and my giant friend. How many of these I think I only have two or three of these left right?
Invisible might be interesting. I'll let you guys decide. Here's the choices you have you have
literally 60 seconds. Invisibility, summon a giant, or become a giant. Which one? Those are your
choices. You get 60 seconds. Summon giant, become giant, or what was the last one? Oh wait what was
it? Oh I forget it. Why do I forget it? Invisible right okay. Invisible, summon giant, become giant.
Those are three very interesting routes to take. Don't be a coward. Don't be a coward. Can you play
the grimace game boy color game on stream? Maybe one day. All right what's it what's it look like?
It's still close. Become giant and invisibility. It's kind of trending in one direction but I think
we have our answer. Become giant is the winner. All right big. Grow in size. You cast a spell
inflating to more than twice your usual height. It's actually it's not a giant it's just like
you're kind of bigger. A path a path leads into the village or you could skirt past it. Why did
I do this? I just got taller? You approach the guards. The guards are clearly impressed by your
size. They stand quickly aside and let you enter the village without question. You flick one over
as you pass. What? Oh this guy's impressive. Okay you step into the center of the village. Gradually
you shrink back down to your normal size. Is that bad? So I walk in the front door and they're like
yeah bro step right this way. Is that bad? Okay large hut. One hut is much larger than the others.
Above its door is a sign depicting a picture of an owl and a hammer. It is amazing anyone here can
draw let alone perform crafts. From inside you can hear the sound of hammering. Look through the
window. Peering in through the window you see a clatter man working away at a bench. He moves with
unusual delicacy for these creatures. His long thin fingers carefully adjusting the position
of whatever it is he's working on. You can't help noticing he has an unusually large skull. Okay
well let's go in. The clatter man looks up as you enter. He puts down the tiny hammer and pincers he
has been using to repair a piece of fine jewelry and tilts his head to regard you and greet him.
You greet him with a nod. He seems to understand this and nods in reply. He's in his workbench.
You step forward and look over his workbench and he gestures with an open palm to let you look.
The clatter man has a variety of fine tools, pincers, all spikes for scratching and etching,
even a vice. He's clearly a master craftsman despite his species. When you are finished he
steps forward to you gesturing for your pack. Pack? Show him my pack. You hold out your pack
to him. He begins to rummage through investigating everything with his long supple hands and
occasionally pausing to scratch his bulging skull as though his brain is itching at the sight of
your gear. Then he digs around under his bench before finally pulling a long metal shaft and
a hooked metal grip. He pushes the two together screwing and clamping with a strange hooked tool.
After a short while he produces what appears to be a well-weighted long sword and hands it to you.
All right I got him. I'll pay him. You pull out your purse to pay the clatter man. He seems more
interested in the operation of the drawstring at the top of the pouch than the money. Really?
Take the sword? You accept the sword with some suspicion. Uh I just get a free sword? Let's see
ask him what he's doing. You try to ask him what he's doing but he ignores the sounds coming from
your mouth as if they were just the banging and ringing of his tools. Seems like he is carving
jewelry from colored stones. They do not seem to be precious or even beautiful but the weird
twisted shapes he is carving are complex and intricate and remarkably precise. Can I take one?
Take a piece. You reach out to take one of the pieces a bejeweled item of clear value but he
responds much more quickly than you expect snatching up a strange two-handed contraption.
He opens the handle and the device expands a series of criss-cross bars. At the far end is
a blade which skewers you through the shoulder pinning you to the wall. Holy shit. Uh oh. He
tilts his head the other way and to make his point wiggles the contraption making your shoulder
bleed. Uh oh. You try to spread your arms to collect the starlight for a spell but the clatter
man simply twists the contraption. You howl in pain and cease your attempt at enchantment.
Release me! You demand. The craftsman listens with interest but does not retract the extended arm.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean I didn't mean to go for the jewels. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Please
take me with you. Take me with you. Uh I can't cast a spell. He's got me like pinned by the
fucking shoulder blades with this like weird device that's sticking through my shoulder.
I beg of you please please please release me please appealing to all the gods and the spirits
you can name. The craftsman appears to respond when the name of Herm the cloud god is mentioned
and slackens his grip on the contraption enough that you are able to push it free
and stagger clear. Not taking your eyes off the dangerous creature you move backwards towards the
doorway then hurry out of the low hut. Jesus. I feel like I don't I feel like I probably should
leave now. By the fire you head over to the fire pit but it is unlit during the day and there is
no one here. Stop and eat. Taking one of your smoked fish from your pack you fill your empty
stomach. You look around the village once more. I guess I could I could be here I could come here
at night. I did get a sword yeah well let me see the sword. A plus two long sword oh
all right I think that gives me plus two to all of my swings that's huge. He gave you a sword and
you tried to steal from him. Well I was gonna pay. Hey I tried to pay. Remember I was like here take
all these I want to pay you I have coins. I guess that doesn't mean hey dude just like put your hand
into the fucking like pasta sauce. That's not how it works. Oh no no I have money I have money I'm
gonna put my hand in the pasta sauce and just take pasta out of it. Yeah that's like give you a
fucking hand out of here. Don't touch my what are you doing? All right I'm gonna get out of here
before I cause it any more trouble slip away. The village has no walls you slip between two huts
and back out into the plains. Let's check out over here. You march onwards ascending and descending
as the ground breaks and changes level. As the morning moves on the wind begins to rise. A small
patch of flowers grows here just by a small rock. Ooh flowers. You smell the flowers they emit a rich
thick smell that makes you feel somewhat giddy. Still you feel somewhat better for it.
Smell the flowers again. Uh smell the flowers again. You take another long sniff of the flowers.
The scent is so strong that it makes your gaze turn briefly red and blotchy.
Oh all this guy does is do weird organic drugs. Smell them again. You lie down on the ground and
bury your nose deep into the flower patch and sniff. The effect of the smell is not as powerful
now as though the effect is wearing off. All right all right let's get out of here. You continue to
walk. More? No I don't want to do more. That's dangerous. Sunflower update. I am pleased to
announce our biggest sunflower has officially opened and we did we have one two three four
there are five sunflowers this year and we did one of those loot boxes where we don't we didn't
know what the colors were going to be because it was a kind of a mix of the sunflowers could
be like red or orange or brown or purple or there's a ton of different combinations. I'm pleased to
report color of the main sunflower the big one is a pale yellow with a big brown ring in the middle
it's a beautiful pattern it's pale yellow with a brown ring around the center of kind of where the
petals are going out it's a brown almost painted ring around the middle it is gorgeous picture
hold on the pictures are coming but the thing with the sunflower I want to make sure it's fully
opened and has time to breathe so you get a really good picture just opened as of today
still don't know what the colors of the other ones are though do it after the ad break
all right let's keep going rule of third andy you'll see one is grimace purple might be can
you play as an ad please um okay I will play I'll play an ad if you can get more than 95 percent
that says yes on a pole you can just start it now that's been not it has to be over 95 percent
that's been 96 percent or higher all right you walk on climbing slightly across the dusty steps
the sun continues to climb the steep sky in the middle of the steps you come across a strange
site a wooden pole as high as a tree with nothing around it it has no knots handles or holds of any
kind nothing except a level platform right at the top clumps of the yellow moss you saw before grow
around the base of the pole I'll have way more of this let's get to full health look around you
stop and look around but can't make much out across the contours of the plane you might be able to see
more from the top of the pole of course from somewhere nearby you hear singing bang on the
pole watch an ad is no you guys not even close I said it has to be at least 96 percent you're at
71 percent right now that's just not happening now I'm sorry I got I like apologize I'm sorry
yeah 71 percent is it's yeah I can't show you an ad yeah it sucks like I'm fucking sorry
maybe we'll try again later it's like really disappointing but it's all right all right
listen bang on the pole or cast a spell what can we do uh h oh wait I do have a gale horn
when did I get a gale horn like episode two how long have I had that for is that why I snorted the
other one I've had a gale horn this whole time you do big again big is pretty cheap it's only
one stamina so something's obviously buried here can't do doc you do sus just make sure that
yeah it's just us you look to the stars and craft the magic into a steady voice it begins to speak
to you the voice informs you that this is a pole or a priest of froth who is fasting and contemplating
the procession of the sun he's likely to be quite mad okay listen you concentrate and listen
there's definitely a voice singing somewhere close at hand but there's no one anywhere in sight the
pole is set into a slight rise into the ground and you can see in all directions an invisible
creature perhaps dust funnels across the empty plane bang on the pole on the spell's information
you unbelt your blade and wallop the pole with the weapon in its sheath the wood vibrates
a moment later a shaggy face appears over the edge of the platform overhead
who's that who's that yeah yeah he's doing the singing are you fasting you demand no I'm not
doing the fasting I'm only not doing the eating what I am doing is he's doing the singing he is
bawling every word his throat must be sore now hmm what can you see the future and past is one
joining is separating and ghosts walking back and forth none of us are quite when we believe
ourselves to be I have experienced this myself shut your face hole I don't sit up on this pole
to learn what you muddlers can learn crawling around the ground with your full fat bellies
ah would you like some food I can give you some food he calls you something terrible in response
I was being generous do you suppose it's generous to torment people not doing the eating with food
oh why do you think I'm up on this pole oh he's fasting holy shit that's actually awful
hey you're fasting up there aren't you don't you want some food I have food that's just I'm
just taunting this is taunting this is not okay this is actually bad all right I would like to
learn from you the man does not reply but leans away however a moment later a hand appears over
the side of the platform and something falls to earth is a medallion is that for me you're a
sorcerer aren't you come up I hope you're a sorcerer otherwise I can't get down again
oh okay I gotta take it you take a hold of the medallion nothing in particular happens
come on then let's go you turn the medallion over in your hands it is a jewel studded and set loose
on a chain it is probably worth something to the north mist rolls across the edge of the forest
all right this is definitely a hover medallion or teleporting medallion zen hover in the air
require yeah okay so I can float up there yeah what else can I even do here I can take I can
just like blow the fucking gale horn and cause a tornado on this dude that would be so fucked up
well I'm gonna do zen the zen is how I mean this is they're teaching me to do zen you spin the
star light into a pattern around you and the medallion begins to glow as you rise gently up
into the air you are now floating off the ground float to the top of the pillar here we are up
here with this guy the man shuffles aside to allow you to bob down while taking back the
jeweled medallion now he took it back so you are a sorcerer I thought so I might have been a thief
you might have never gotten your medallion back that's true oh my sight assures me I will not
need it still I'd rather have it welcome to my little eerie what are you doing up here you demand
hi from the world I can see diagonally downwards onto the world I can see through the layers of
curse that affect this land the whole place has unraveled like a poorly woven shoe yeah from up
here I can see all right I'm at it float down I don't even have the medallion anymore I would
just be jumping off and dying I don't have the medallion why would this is bait that would be so
fucked up to see no I want to talk to him do you know of the seven serpents you demand
I see much from up here I know of the winged beast in their quest to devour you grind your
bones to dust and then spit that dust into the cup of the king of aniline east of bottles to
scratch underneath his loin cloth so do you like it up here the view is superb yeah I do not see
how a view can be superb it is only looking after all after he speaks you feel a weight
gather about your shoulders as you settle down onto the platform the way I was floating that
whole time the spell has worn off can you get me down from here where can I find the serpents
they are looking to find you anilander each is waiting for you some are hiding some are not
one waits for you in the very depths of lake eclala he means to pick you off when you're at
your weakest how can I find him you must encounter him I fear the only way would be to swim
until he senses your tiredness but that is a most foolish course can you tell me the serpent's
weaknesses these are most secret but some I think can be guessed at the time serpent cannot be
defeated from the forest of the north the trees seem to part and a gigantic bird lifts into view
its talons gleam in the sunlight he could get out of here bird yeah go away grab the platform
what do I do I think I'm gonna hold on okay I'm gonna grab the platform you grab the platform
below more to stop yourself from falling off in surprise than anything else the bird approaches
and swoops low the priest screams then a moment later he is gone and the bird is flapping gently
away you are alone there is nothing on the platform apart from a few stray spots of blood
from where the winged creature's talons punctured the man's side and the jeweled medallion oh no
save him uh see the future oh no I I think I think we're I think he's I think he's gone
he's gone you can see him getting fucking eaten save him you're a monster say I can't
all I can do is cast zen hover down what about hot no rewind no I think it's all right
I think it's all right I don't have the medallion yet I just leap off all right I'm taking the
medallion this probably explains how we got up the pole in the first place okay I'm going let's
okay rewind you monster can't rewind everything I can't I got some decisions have to be final
what do I sit on the pole the spell was free right sit on the pole you float down onto the
pole's platform and cross your legs to contemplate the sun a few meditative minutes go by and you
feel cleansed and well rested oh time passes a moment later you feel a great weight settle
about your shoulders it is your body weight returning your spell has evaporated and you're
now stuck at the top of this gigantic pole in the distance a dark speck appears above the forest
is the bird coming back for another like meal there's a wait wait and watch the dark spot
resolves into a bird-like shape and swoops low a moment later you have been snatched up into the
air by the sharp talons where are we going carried away great wings beat above you you wriggle and
struggle but there's no safe way down below the steps transform into thick tangled forest
we do have the ape what if I try to talk to the bird talk to the bird or pray to the ape climb
the creature I like that one let me go you demand of the great bird hoping it perhaps can understand
the common tongue even if it can't speak it and indeed perhaps it can the talons begin to slide
from your flesh and you are about to fall grab hold on wait you grab for the creature's feet
and it lashes back kicking you sharply in the face the talons retract and you are tumbling
you're tumbling downwards through the air towards the canopy why did I do that you plunge to earth
the trees breaking your fall miraculously you are largely unscathed by your ordeal
get up you pause as a thin red colored snake slides across your path this fucking snake
what if I play what if I play the flute imagine going through all what I just went through
and then being like no it's time to like you play a flute a few notes on the flute but it seems you
are no talented snake charmer the snake appears to be watching you but then it lowers its head
once more and begins to slither away down the path yep I can become a giant or I can summon
a giant rap talk all languages no it's a snake I'm gonna follow the snake you follow the snake
into the undergrowth for a moment you lose sight of the creature then a flash of red reassures you
that you are still on its tail but the snake should be far ahead of you it is almost as if it
wants you to follow the snake reaches the foot of a tree and coils around the trunk okay as you watch
the snake slithers quickly up the trunk a moment later its head drops down from a branch to stare
at you you approach the tree catching a glimpse of a thick red band in the branches and suddenly
the whole thing erupts into flame charge forward you charge forward convince the flame is an illusion
it is not and you feel burning heat on your skin but just as soon as it began the fire goes out
leaving a badly charred tree looking up into the branches you see the red snake peering down at you
it has grown tenfold in size and two fiery wings are now folded across its back
sly eyes watch your movements as if deciding its next attack you stare in shock and fear the blaze
of hissing fiery must be the fire serpent sap i don't have the ring um stench speed i could go
really super fast float in the air sap let me say something about the water i don't have like a
water spell fireball why would i do fire against fire wind i could just cause it out i'm gonna do
gale horn i'm blowing the horn and i'm causing a fucking tornado here tornado let's go oh boy
consulting the constellations above you bind the spell placing your gale horn to your lips and
playing a clear tone a strong wind is summoned from the horn that blows down the serpent's fires
it hisses in fury and frustration and falls from the tree to attack you but without its flames it
is severely weakened dude how am i okay i gotta play well uh you've got much more attack power
than i do i'm gonna hold off good thing all right now i can i gotta do some stamina management
crash against your defense the creature coils its scaly body okay it's getting ready
does that mean it's gonna attack i'm gonna go like 3.6 good good like stab cuts through the
serpent scales the serpent is rearing back but you catch it as it retreats so it's rearing back
now i think i'm going all in yep good call what an unbelievable fucking sword play that was
your only hope is to keep up the attack you do not hold back laid high above your head the serpent
is rearing for you you drive your blade into its open jaw the serpent's fire flickers you'll die
i can do better than that you will die here fire licks the edges of the serpent's mouth
i'm going again you will die here alone the creature's claws draw inwards all right it's
not going to attack but i think it has way more than i can yes 1.6 all right i have to defend i
need to build this back up you jab and step back the snake is clearly fearful moving back attempting
only a minor attack a line of fire streaks along the length of the serpent it's gonna come all in
good you draw back as the serpent arcs forward quickly sidestepping the creature
smashes into the bushes behind sending a wall of sparks snake eyes narrow and watch you
just did 4.4 i'm going all in all right uh he's got a ton of power now i'm gonna hold back the
flames around the creature flicker a deep dark red the creature seems to flash with heat yep
here comes a big one kind of all right the creature flies a short distance into the air
i think it's probably gonna defend the bat was harder than this dude uh i'm gonna defend twice
shit that was a stupid idea now we both are gonna serpent lashes out quickly with the tip of its
tail didn't dive in heat rises from the creature scales all right is it gonna be more than 6.7
all in that's really unfortunate because that's horrible i just took four fucking damage
it's really unfortunate the serpent's fire grows dull after that all in again it's all right fire
serpent rears back escaping the worst of the blow the creature shifts back a little i'm gonna
die fire creeps around the open jaws i don't have enough yep see but now i do okay creature turns
its fire okay turns let's do four four point five again all in five point three all in no i'm dead
no shit oh that was risky that was risky oh damn it it's okay i got so unlucky then all right all
right all right so i'm gonna go at four point four point oh good four point oh six point oh
really good start serpents fire flickers the creature's claws draw inwards okay two point
seven you're not going for an attack you draw any claws in oh shut up lost by all right i'm
being watched defend i didn't have one point six a line of fire streaks along the okay i think it's
coming in for an attack it's gonna be more than four yep all right now i have the advantage it's
going in the air it's probably it's gonna do a little tail whip let's do four point eight okay
the fire grows dull all right i'm doing literally point eight no one point oh it's safe right one
point two oh that's all right the creature flies in the air opening its jaws wide all right it's
gonna be a huge one you only got like four or five after that flash with heat i think you're coming
in twice yep creature retreats a little into the trees all right all in again that's fine um i have
complete advantage defend okay i think a big one's coming in the fearsome serpent rears its full
height up into the air oh yeah this should be a win right now it's gonna turn let's do like
three point eight good one more of those all in heat rises from the creature scales all in
dead is that panic you see in its eyes or murderous intent you risk another heavy cut the fire
serpent's eyes turn coal black and it looks upon at you questioning helpless in the final second
before it turns to a dark dead husk you step back wiping your brow sword heavy in your hand
you have now defeated three of the seven serpents you need to rest and recover your
search for the serpents is so far taking its toll you move on through the trees yay back
wait where are we right now that was interesting how that played out i fucked around here for
too long my buddy got grabbed maybe killed and eaten i got grabbed i fought to get let go i drop
right here snake is right here that's that was cool you gotta go get the water snake in the lake
yeah that's true i need to get over here all right the the game plan is still intact i wanted to go
this way because i want to activate this beacon things scurry in the branches all around you
clouds rumble as they roll across the darkening sky the path looks wide and well used but there
are no signs of who or what uses it then a little further along you reach a spot where the trail is
suddenly narrower with bushes tight on either side let's take a look oh dear you pause to look
at the bush and see that its branches are twitching ever so slightly curling and uncurling like
reaching fingers i don't think i want to walk through that squeeze forward is not the play
it's not the game plan i think i draw my sword and try to cut away at some stuff you draw your
long sword warily the branches seem to curve back as though recoiling but surely it's simply
the breeze i don't want to lose this sword if they grab it i think i'm just gonna i don't know i
think i'm turning around i'm gonna leave because i'm more of a punk kind of guy who listens to rock
wait what not someone who watches germa sorry i mean i'm kind of a punk rock guy i don't want
to be here all right that's i like that comment that's fucking funny oh i don't want to like
okay you draw your i mean this is clearly dangerous i'm gonna go in here and it's
gonna hurt me for like eight damage i'm turning around i'm not doing this is this is very clearly
that dangerous situation that i don't want to put myself in risk on i have to leave i'm kind of a
punk rock kind of guy don't just squeeze in there i'm sorry i'm going in you squeeze your way forward
between two bushes which have overgrown the path only to find yourself quickly tangled in them
it is lucky the sight masters cannot see this far it would be embarrassing if the sergeant could
see you now swing my sword you raise your long sword to hack away the branches they react faster
this time long wooden tendrils whip out grasping your wrists your wrists and arms you cannot swing
your sword now and meanwhile another tendril is looping itself around your neck maybe the
ape can come and help us here i'm gonna pray to the ape you close your eyes and raise a prayer to
the ape but nothing seems to change the bush keeps tightening its grip around your neck
you look to the heavens to cast a spell but your arms are held fast by the strangle bush
and so you cannot craft any magic the vice-like grip tightens it's beginning to pull your body
in two directions the grip of the strangle bush is turning to steel around your arms and neck
you can barely
you struggle and thrash and then finally the ape comes to your aid as the moon rises brightly
and the bush turns involuntarily reaching upwards instead of towards you you waste no time in
slipping clear you shiver wanted to leave this spot as fast as you can the ape i think it's funny
because there's the ape and there's also the monkey right well there's a there's a few different
apes and isn't the monkey like doesn't monkey laugh at you sometimes if bad things are happening
to you i remember praying to the monkey and it was like the monkey uh you can hear the distant
laughs of like howling laughter as the monkey like watches you get like hurt all right i just
distinctly remember that happening okay well let's go ape has been really good to us though
the path winds tortuously through the forest you still feel shaky from your encounter with
the strangle bush i didn't even get hurt actually probably the best way to do that
are you gonna play final fantasy 16 today um i thought about it but i think we're into this
right now i'd rather get to a good stopping point here i mean i'm not the stream's not
over i'm just saying that probably not lies of jay yep look the high council of the sorcery
enjoyers have been waiting 296 days for this you know what i mean i think we we owe them a little
a little extra the path winds time to move you must find your way to the shore of lake eclala
somehow it seems impossible and yet it must be a way the seers in aniland saw a path
dangerous fickle but present you must find it i wonder what happens if you stay with the bird
this is probably like a big bird's nest it's probably i wonder if he's here that like other
magician guy i'm almost out of food again all right you walk on between the trees another night
begins you need to rest in the snata forest this is not good but whatever laying your pack down
by the roots of a tree you try to stretch out despite the unsettling noises in the trees
i have eaten today right yeah you stretch out and rest you dream you are trapped in a low straw hut
its door sealed with bolts made of bones a small fire is burning in one corner it quickly spreads
until you are surrounded by flame you feel yourself starting to sweat from the heat
and you wake up to find a ball of fire raging mere inches from you look at it jesus the fire
does not seem to be fueled it is a ball about three feet wide gushing with smoke and steam
a moment later it unravels uncurling into a long animal form it is a fire fox and it's coming for
your neck in a blaze of fur and fire sharpen blade this rock which is turned to stone
fog summon darkness oh that's kind of cool i imagine when this bell gets cast
it plays the diablo 2 sound effect you know the one i'm talking about the one that goes
oh you know that one that like
when the darkness is summoned in act two the fox is made of light you dope i could like stink but
i can't do it fire is not a good idea i'm summoning darkness i think it's fun or i could do a force
no let's summon darkness let's just who cares fuck it let's go you move the stars into alignment
around you in clouds of dark fog bill about from under clothing your clothing but they are quickly
lost to the winds okay well i have to fight it uh we're going all in good idea three damage points
all in again the fire fox paces the earth before you sparks a fire flashing across its fur driven
by fear you charge headlong it snaps at you which your blow lands in a spurt of blood and fur
it limps back bleeding heavily dark blue flames gutter between clumps of ragged fur
all in again it's gonna be close uh i oh that was really painful you feel yourself weakening
that's not good at all that's the worst thing that could happen yes get that sneaky 1.6 okay
we're a big one's coming really the firefox drops to a crouch are you gonna defend again
i don't know that's all right okay but he killed me shit i thought it was i thought it was gonna
be one damage i took i did two hell the firefox's jaws close around your throat as it tears its head
back your death is brief but very very hot okay well we're trying again i'm not gonna go all in
this time we're gonna go six yep perfect okay crouches down and snarls we're doing
two this is gonna i think he's just gonna defend two point three point one it's all right firefox's
eyes flash a deep hot red that hurts so much it's gonna kill me in two hits firefox scratches at
its fur even with defending the i just shouldn't even defend i have to go all in i'm dead what the
fuck what it crouches low and growls it scratches at the earth are you even gonna do anything i have
to go in it moves away again i'm dead let's go six point five point eight five point nine
okay crouches down and snarls defend good build up my meter it's flashing its eyes
deep hot red six damn it retry just kill me fuck again defend six point seven there we go
okay now i just gotta it's he's gonna defend watch this zero point five
absolutely massive what just happened it dodges back a little again you're gonna defend again
aren't you zero point one point oh i fucking i'm gonna die i can't believe i lost four point four
oh my god just restart restart restart restart what the hell why are you so much better at this than
all in every time i'm dead wait no i don't want to succumb i'm just running i'm running away
i'm running away i'm not getting soft-locked i already did this i'm out of here see you later
goodbye chad fox versus virgin jeremy this is the sorcery enjoyers high council we just wanted to
say thank you very much for playing this again this game does not get enough love and it's
wonderful seeing so many people enjoying it council is few in numbers but our hearts are big for these
books and games so we thank you for playing and entertaining our little jokes hey i love this game
this is like this is like how i started on twitch this is this holds a very very deep
sentimental value to me so yeah i love this this is great okay i'm just gonna keep moving
i'm not sleeping i'm not gonna get attacked by a firefox back to the town the path leads into the
village oh i could go into the village again at night this might be a bad idea oh i'm not big
anymore they're not they don't care push my way in i could get big again will they think it's cool
they took it from me i can't kid create illusions god illusion of worship i don't have a gold jewel
read minds sense danger i guess i could i could try um what else is there
rap tall talk all languages don't we talk this wait pulling out the green wig you wear it and
cast a spell but the clathamen are not speaking so there is no language for you to understand
what do you want you ask the clathamen look at you without expressions if they
if they have understood you they gave no sign let me pass you demand they remove the wig in
irritation i just think have this green wig on darn it whatever put my wig away i can't they
won't let me do big again they want they don't want me to do it again i guess i'm just gonna
have to pay i'm gonna run out of money what about kid create an illusion requires a bracelet of bone
let's do it you move the stars into alignment around you and the bracelet at your wrist begins
to glow you have just a moment in which to choose your illusion turn myself invisible turn myself
into a monster monster they like when i was big remember when i got huge they were like come on
in you create the illusion that you are towering infernal beast but the clathamen barely react
it seems they are too stupid to find you threatening what there's nothing you can do
but wait for the spell to fade and try something you hand over two gold pieces the clathamen
nearest to you seems to love the shininess and takes the coins the other stands aside to let
you pass they do not speak but when motions towards a fire where an animal is roasting on a spit
okay well you look around the weird houses by the fire you make your way to a space by the fire
several clathamen and clathawomen are sprawled around singing songs that consist of barks and
squawks and occasionally turning a roach pig of roach pig on a spit reminding you of the poachers
you met in kare one stands as you arrive slapping her chest and then her head in some kind of
greeting i'm not doing that i'm not doing that i don't know i don't know what that what i'm
i don't know what i'm saying i don't know what that means i'm just gonna say hi greetings they
don't understand speech she slaps herself again i return the gesture return her gesture you reply
with the same gesture and the clatham woman stares in amazement then falls about laughing
she repeats the gesture again what what am i doing all right repeat the gesture myself
you repeat the gesture again the clatham woman's eyes seem to all but pop out suddenly
she leans forward and smiles strangely drawing up her lips and showing her teeth which she then
begins to pick this continues for a moment but when nothing happens she stops in evident
puzzlement perhaps she thought she was looking into a mirror one of the clatham and by the fire
waves you over and tears off a leg of a pig i mean i haven't eaten you accept the roast meat which
is almost raw and barely palatable another of the clatham and brings you a mug of tea like broth
that accompanies the meat the way of running nose accompanies a feverish cold jesus uh okay eat
more i should probably have i wonder if they might know something about the serpents i wonder ask
about the serpents do you know of the seven serpents you ask one of the clatham and stiffens
at the words perhaps he recognizes them or has heard them from someone else either way he begins
to point vigorously at the fire with one hand while with another he lifts a handful of dust
from the ground and makes it as if to throw it on the flames you realize he is telling you the
weakness of the fire serpent sand oh sure wish i knew this he's already dead this is where i take
out like i just i pull out like the serpent's head i already got him he repeats this pattern
a few times before seeming to forget what he's doing and sitting back in silence let's have
another piece of pig you tear off another leg of pig and munch down on it the clatham and seem
content presumably living so close to the forest they have a good supply of creatures to hunt
suddenly there is a sound behind you followed by a hushed silence turning you see a well built
clatham in taller and stronger than the rest approaching with unsteady gate before you can
react he lifts you and tosses you across the fire to a patch of ground near the gate am i
getting kicked out oh i thought they were throwing me out the arena the large clatham and stumbles
after you growling loudly you cannot understand his meaning then he raises a large club oh uh
greetings is he is he coked up wait law control non-intelligent creatures this dud illusion of
treasure there's sap i could cause depression gack which is fear i don't have the mask law
is expensive but it would probably work do it you craft the spell and begin to attempt to take
control of the clatham's mind spell only works on unintelligent creatures now you will find out if
they are truly if they truly are unintelligent the clatham and raises his club to swing it down on
your head i really hope you're stupid make him strike himself down you hold your nerve trusting
to your spell the clatham's great biceps tense and then the club comes crashing down hitting
into the clatham's own groin his eyeballs twist about in their sockets like flowers turning towards
a sudden ray of sunshine then his face turns a deep shade of blue and he sinks into the he sinks
to the dust he turned he turned blue by hitting himself in his his own balls okay the other
clatham and around the fire nod appreciatively they seem to consider this a fair ordinary fight
and you are the clear victor the other clatham and go and find their fallen champion one of the
clatter women slaps you on the back making you cough and splutter another clatham and beckons
from outside a nearby tent his face is painted with strange spirals and markings okay let's go
you head over to the beckoning clatham man from his tent you catch faint wisps of strange herbal
smells get over here attack him uh let's greet you nod a greeting which he returns
placing both hands on either side of your face then he begins to murmur a strange blessing
you feel strength filtering deep into your bones his gift is a powerful one and deep when you
step back you feel stronger taller and more confident got a max health upgrade thank him
you bow and thanks he smiles and walks away from the fire any more serpents intrigued by
the clatham man's first clue you try and ask him about the serpents once more but he merely
repeats the same performance try communicating further you look around for something to use to
communicate further point into the teacup point at my sword point into the teacup you point down
into the water in a nearby teacup and the clatham and nods grabbing a handful of burning fat from
the pig on the spit he tosses it into the cup the clatham and whose cup it was becomes enraged
and the two begin beating each other around the head with rocks still perhaps it is a clue should
you try something else i love these guys all right point at the ground you stamp on the ground one
of the clatham women shakes her head perhaps they do not know how to defeat the earth serpent or
perhaps they think you are asking if you can plant vegetables here it's impossible to tell
one clatham it picks up a stone and then punches it is that a clue what about the sword my sword
you indicate your sword and the clatham and nod to one another but it's unclear what they are saying
perhaps they simply like swords enough of talking to these idiots it is like communicating with a
trained dog what the fuck what about the forest what can you tell me of the forest of snata you
ask the creatures look between one another blankly for all their human shape they do not seem to have
a human thought in their heads you stand and take your leave of the fire okay i could probably get
a night's sleep here though one corner of the camp is slung with hammocks what they are for is
unclear as the clatham folk seem to have tents but a few creatures are asleep in them already
you haul yourself up into one of the hammocks they're far from they are far too large for a
normal human but this in fact makes it only more comfortable and ensures there's enough room for
your pack i think i'm safer you stretch out and rest you seem left alone here and your night is
untroubled by dreams during the past day you gained a little max stamina change to using the
long sword used one provision and some gold enter the steps and you collected the sun serpent and
the fire serpent meaning there are four still out there next morning i'm going to get a send
off from the clatham in you wake after a peaceful night in one of the hammocks feeling much refreshed
i think that's it appreciate it thanks for the help get out of here thanks a lot i have much
respect for the clatham folk you should ever need anything do not hesitate to call there are no
phones i've ruined everything all right let's go down you keep moving the ground dropping a little
there moves a little still icy but fresh to the southeast a huge mountaintop rises its peak
dusted with snow it is the southern extent of the horns of iklala near its base is a carved shape
a turreted tower built into the stone of the slope you march onwards all right we want to go here
you fall into a steady pace as you walk ascending and descending the moaning winds tug at your pack
and sword the scrub land is broken quite suddenly by a small waist-high post to which is a nailed
written notice you pause to read the sign the writing is crabby and difficult but you slowly
decipher it stop traveler every wish can come true for this post marks the grave of the god
call name close to see your eyes blessed forthwith call the name vinanga rose shift button is broken
uh let's go ahead and you know you know the one we're doing you cast sus the voice indicates
that there is some danger here but it does not specify what it is be careful all right i don't
know what happens if i do this should i say it i say vinanga vinanga you stand carefully by the
post and call out vinanga to the empty air nothing seems to change there is no sense of danger or
blessing in the air wait i have to close my eyes you close your eyes as the note instructed
nothing happens you sense no danger vinanga you call out again but there is still no response
then you feel something move under your feet wait you wait and then your stomach churns you are
falling you tumble landing in the bottom of a conical sandpit that has opened beneath your
feet the top of the post is now only just visible sticking out of the dirt at the bottom of the pit
yes invisibility oh this is a good place for it too i'm so glad i picked up so many of these
items in this first and second game there's something that you don't know uh you actually
can do playthroughs of this game and not have any of these items and it like sucks because like
fuck i want to do i want to do that i don't have the item let's do it let's go invisible i want
let's see it doesn't cost any stamina slip on the pearl ring and cast the spell and slowly a filmy
light extends from the jewel of the ring surrounding your body something stirs in the
dirt underfoot let's dig you dig a little into the sand around the base of the pit after a few
minutes you uncover the bottom of the pole and beneath it a chain this is part of some mechanical
contraption a claw appears through the sand in the side of the pit are we just gonna are we is
this a way i'm gonna unclog the drain here pull on the chain oh shit okay you tug the chain and
the floor of the pit shivers slightly but you're not strong enough to haul the post back
the side of the pit collapses as a baby badu beetle emerges there's no time to do anything
but draw your sword this is this thing is stronger than a serpent yeah i don't even have 11 stamina
11 power i have eight stiffens and rears up we're gonna go very small like 2.8 good okay that's
clean you aim a blow for its bug eyes the badu beetle mid-lunge bends away from your blade the
creature is losing its spines one by one all right we go again i think 4.2 good it's skillful
okay green blood oozes from between the beetle scales its long claws stretch i think it's ready
to come in defend good call good call okay you fall over yourself trying to escape it's a reach
it straightens up just i think i'm going straightens up all in stupid but i still got it
you prepare your sword you swing hard the battle beetle leans aside avoiding most of the blow
okay probably coming in hard no all right that's fine we'll both do it you circle away from the
battle beetle it circles the other way creatures vicious claws open and close i think that means
like snap snap snap snap snap snap snap like i'm coming in yep all right now i have all the control
here we're going in at like a two point we're going to like 2.5 it scuttles backwards it's okay
that's all right now we're going it waggles its antenna tilting its head full blast
i'm winning so it's okay this is fine battle beetle bugs the badu beetle bug stumbles and
its jaws stretch wide in rage the thing's cruel claw claws grasp at the air i think it has a lot
i'm gonna defend yep it waggles its spiny arms in a strange motion and stands erect for a moment
all right well we're going in it i have to go in you never know you never know it could have been
honestly look at how much bigger the bar is you just got way more to work with scuttles forward
and i could have probably no i couldn't it stiffens i think i'm going all in still winning
defend all right that's fine i think coming in for as high lens begins to dig in the dirt all in
nope defend it shifts sideways okay if he goes all in i'm in trouble i'm gonna defend again okay
uh its back legs throw up more sand it's coming in for a full like 12.0 oh my god do it already
it stoops down endlessly patient it hurries a few steps back do it already i don't want to
okay it rears up really a 2.3 you smart piece of shit because now you still have enough to
beat me if i go all in i'm going i don't care oh my fucking god what a disaster
oh my god a huge this is a this is awful this is really bad i got him that was so annoying
outsmarted by a bug you rush forward and stab then your blade lands deep you cut again twist
and the badu beetle collapses on the dust the beetle has died on its back you could scramble
up its body to get close to the edge of the pit let's look at the beetle first you look over the
dead beetle around one leg is a small metal tag on which is inscribed the word benanga most curious
benanga is the name of the beetle it's not a god or like a priest or it's literally the name of
the beetle that somebody put here somebody was warning me stop traveler every wish can come true
for this post marks the grave of the god benanga who put this here i'm climbing up the beetle's
body you clamor onto the beetle's hind legs then scramble by leg by leg up the body to the edge
of the pit the beetle's body shifts under your weight and you clamor out just in time as it
slides down out of reach look into the pit the dead beetle's body lies in the bottom of the pit
you leave the side of the pit you continue to walk okay well that was eventful uh let's go
over here first i guess i want to turn this on actually no let's explore all this so then i can
turn it to the past let's explore all of everything in the present first it's the best way to do it
okay you march onwards climbing slightly the dewy light from your pearl ring fades and disappears
but i was invisible that whole time how did i you smell me i was invisible you notice something
white stark against the gray of the dust look at it it's just a sliver of cool white visible
through the thin dusty scrub something is buried here clear the dust you wipe away the dust from
the object it is short dirty white and gently curved take it up you dig around the object
and find two similar objects to the left and right of it they lie parallel in the dirt keep
going you squat down on your heels and dig in the dirt a little more eventually you uncover three
short white rods and at that moment it becomes obvious that they are finger bones of a hand
clenched into a fist the fist points upwards as though its owner had been buried standing
upright in the soil keep digging you keep digging the fist gives way to a wrist and then an arm
it is as though the creature was trying to climb out when the soil of the land closed over its head
as you go lower the bones start to accumulate a leathery coating at first you think that it
is the remains of a coat but then once you locate an anchor and sail tattoo it becomes clear it is
skin somehow preserved in the soil you are now seriously digging which is hard work you pause
to take a break every few minutes and stop once more and you have the figure on earth down to the
waist its skull is a dried leather ball with two gray brown eyes shrunken in the sockets it wears
a metal ring through its nose and the remains of a beard are just visible its jacket is better
preserved its color faded but its buttons still intact it wears a small three-cornered hat
sticking just above the waist are the remains of some kind of harness it is possible this figure
had a false leg uh keep going oh it is hot now you're starting to sweat in your tunic you work
harder still creating a deep pit and getting down as far as the figure's knees one leg is indeed
wooden the other trouser clad bone you have the ape yep we're good keep going the sun has reached
its highest point now out of the shade the air is baking hot you dig down to the figure's feet
so it is standing proud in a five-foot hole water begins to pool around your feet heat beats down
from a cloudless sky the figure keels over face down against the dirt you've wasted a lot of time
on burying it but have discovered nothing search the figure you rival through the figure's jacket
but find nothing of interest in its pockets not even one gold piece take the hat you take the hat
from the creature's head but it is of little use it crumbles to dust in your hand more interesting
is what is left behind under the figure's thin covering of hair you can see a dry leathery scalp
inked with another tattoo you examine the tattoo carefully it shows two long thick lines that come
together to form a v at the top another stroke crosses so the shape becomes an inverted a inside
the top of the a near the tip is a black x inside an o perhaps it's a map but if so it is surely
too vague to read rebury the body you begin to pull dirt back into the pit intending to rebury
the body suddenly the creature in the pit begins to shiver and shake it is moving arms reaching out
to grasp you how do you skewer it it's a skeleton ah through the bones it's not gonna hurt doesn't
do anything he's got a tattoo map on top of his head um i'm gonna watch you watch in horror as
the eyeless creature drags itself up from the pit to the edge and stumbles and clatters away westward
across the steps it disappears into the dust though after a short while you hear a clattering
sound most likely the sound of its bones falling to bits around it look in the pit the pit is now
half filled with sparkling gleaming water there must be an underground river that is feeding it
you move quickly away from this ghoulish place okay there's this kind of rundown building
because these stones are already up here or i can turn on the device this thing i would like to
explore first so let's go here we can turn this back later you walk on the ground dropping a
little the afternoon is starting drawn the sudden sound of voices to your right startles you look
around oh dear you spin around to see seven hooded shapes squatting on the ground playing some sort
of weird game chanting in a curious tongue listen to the chant you listen closely to the voices
then stiffen as you realize one is calling you by your name we have awaited you you've made good
time to us we are the seven spirits come join us you raise your eyes to the heavens but there's
nothing here strange you've heard rumors of spots where no stars at all are in alignment but you've
never found one before the figures beckon you towards them into the very center of this magical
darkness there's no stars in the sky here i don't know they seem kind of friendly seem approachable
warily you approach who are these creatures how do they know your name will they offer advice or
are they dangerous as their skull mask faces suggest the spirits rise from the ground as
you approach gliding silently through the air passing through one another as they mingle and
encircle you linking hands that's not this is where you run caution is understandable but fear
us not what are you these bodies are not our natural bodies merely shells we cannot touch you
we cannot harm you how can you help me we can give you knowledge the chant we know will protect you
from all harm show me your true forms tell me the chant oh yes the spirits begin to turn and dance
around you chanting in a whispering unison but you cannot understand the words repeat kissing
with us repeating words in a language you cannot understand is difficult you try but stumble over
the first few lines a bill mandible as they chant you begin to feel stars appearing in the sky above
you magic i can see stars now protect from magic that one works there's also zap i don't think
that's gonna hurt anybody there's mud quicksand rap oh i can understand i can understand what
did that was like a super that was like a boston moment right there oh i can understand all
languages all right um well i can understand the spell now is what i'm saying that one's interesting
uh read minds is interesting let's get a couple of options for you guys to decide all right
rap which is talk all languages and understand all languages is mage which is protect from magic
mag and then there's also zap which is great lightning 60 second poll let's do what do you
want what do you feel like they feel like doing there's also some other stuff too there's i guess
tell is there but i think those are the most interesting yeah one is understanding one is
protection and what is just chaos so however you feel which one is reading minds tell although it
might not work because they might not be physically here the person has to be physically in your line
of sight for it to work and these are specters i don't know if that would work possible it might
all right what are we what are we thinking here is it rap it's overwhelming all right we're gonna do
talk all languages taking the wig from your pack you pull it onto your head and form your spell
suddenly the words of the chant resolve themselves into something you can understand
i call to be damned i offer a sign i call to be damned no idols are mine the words go round and
round over and over building in force with the wig on your head it is almost more than you can
bear to listen they're gonna slurp the ape they're gonna slurp oh no he said usurp the ape like slurp
them up they're gonna slurp up the ape i gotta run they actually are gonna replace my god with
something horrible i think they're gonna slurp the ape up they're going to usurp us us usurp how do
you say that word or how do you say this word or serp that sounds weird usurp usurp usurp i don't
the word doesn't sound right anymore usurp usurp that word does not sound real anymore right say
it a few times out loud in your room that word doesn't sound real anymore i i don't have an
offer i i'm gonna try to keep it on i need to run i need to get out of here should i keep listening
or take off the wig and get out i feel like if i keep listening then i'm probably gonna die
keep listening you keep listening the chant goes on and on the clouds begin to churn in the sky
then a loud crack breaks the stillness as a bolt of lightning skewers the place where the seven
spirits stand the light clears and they have vanished i'm running i'm running something is
very wrong you turn and start to run but you cannot get free something like a clawed hand has a hold
of you and is pulling you towards the top of a low mound the ground itself is transforming into a face
and you are walking into an open wide smile you struggle and strain but there is nothing to fight
with the wind your heels score tracks in the dust the force on you is like a hundred invisible hands
then you are above the wide open jaws of a face in the ground this must be holy ground to some
dread spirit long forgotten by the civilized people of the world but you will not learn its
you are not to be a follower you are to be devoured strike back strike back you raise the
sword to swing but stumble back onto the weight of it your arms seem unable to lift the blade
i'm so weak but no looking down you see your legs are suddenly thin and your hands are thin and bony
reaching up to your face you find your hairs coming away in clumps and wrinkles are spreading
over your skin the serpent face in the ground laughs the jaws of time are inescapable
you look to the heavens intending to cast a spell you cannot see the stars anymore your eyes
have grown blurry and unfocused and the night swims as if you were underwater
tumble to the ground and you hear the snap as the bones in your hip and pelvis give out
the serpent shifts closer you open your mouth to cry out and your teeth scattered
a moment later you are a skeleton you stare out through bone dead eyes cold dry bones you are
nothing but cold bones but then the winds drop once more the clouds roll back the steps are clearing
you've failures of becoming young once more bones strengthening skin tightening whatever was pulling
you towards death has released its grip you turn to see a gigantic shape lift into the ground and
swoop away northeast it leaves a strange trail as it flies and the wind from its movement knocks
you to the ground you stagger backwards glad to be alive and keen to leave this accursed place
made like ripples in time interesting well that's the time serpent and this is where the time serpent
is now that was the time serpent just fucking with us i do want to see what this is
before i aim the uh beam at it you set off across the steps with an easy stride but the firm dusty
ground becomes spongy and after a while you're no longer walking on firm ground but rather
striding between waist-high weeds in a deep and stench-filled marsh the evening is drawing in
soon it will be dark suddenly you hear a loud shouting and splashing from the ground of reeds
close at hand am i wrong you stand your ground as the voices approach you soon recognize them
as marsh goblins they enter the clearing panting hard as though running from something greet them
i mean if there's they're running from something i think i could hold on try bring a goblin out
and be like look i got a goblin where we're got i got a goblin will they be annoyed by that or
would they be i wonder talk all languages is interesting i could talk to them uh cause
sleepiness can't do smell uh i could do i'm gonna let's talk i'm gonna talk i'm gonna talk okay
removing the green wig you put it on and complete the spell the goblins guttural tongue begins to
transform into words what is this creature first goblin says we gotta go right out of the gate here
i mean you no harm you reply the goblins almost jump out of their skins as they realize
you can not only understand them now but also communicate we don't have time for this
we must escape what are you running from we're being chased by a terrible serpent it does not
seem to matter how fast we run however it is always ahead of us it's like it knows what we're
doing at each turn why is it chasing you it's been coming for us since we encountered the sorceress
bria she told us this parchment would save us but we're we've been persecuted the serpent is
clearly scared of it whatever it is i don't know what it is give me that parchment what serpent is
this which one like this is bad enough one's bad enough it seems to know every moment before we
know it ourselves give me that parchment he will save you from the serpent to be rid of it goblins
look from one to another uncertainly this parchment is our only hope i am a sorcerer i will read it to
you for you it is of no use to you hand it over or i will run you through i'm a sorcerer i will
read it for you the sorcerer it is worth trying they hand over the parchment and step back as
though expecting the ground to open underneath you of course nothing happens read it you unroll the
paper and look it over unfortunately it is written in a language you cannot understand despite your
spell licks thank them you thank them and they shrug it will do you little good stranger you
nod to the goblins thankful for their help we must hurry we must go they select a path through the
marsh and begin to move attack them let them go we need friends you stand aside and the goblins
hurry away through the marsh they move with the speed of rats still peering into the distant fog
you cannot see what it is they are afraid of links l i x all right let's go over to the room
the marshes give way to more solid barren ground the sun is now in the lowest quarter of the sky
something is visible in the distance to the south perhaps man-made or perhaps a freak of nature
carved from the rocks but it resembles a low stone building interesting the temple behind the temple
all right okay uh some very clear directions to go to this looks interesting this is interesting
this is interesting i'm gonna just say let's go uh maybe the well first start at the well you skirt
around the building and the bits of rubble that surround it around the side of the ruin you find
an old well house the well is an ancient mud brick structure if it once had a cover it has long since
rotted but the metal winch handle is still in place and an old bucket on a rope hangs from it
drop the sun serpent orb into the well i kind of want to see what happens when i do this i'll
rewind drop the sun serpent orb into the well you lean over the well and then drop the orb containing
the sun serpent deep into its depths for a moment your heart swells with excitement but then as the
dust clears you realize you have not destroyed the serpent you have only set it free it boils
upwards like a rising fireball radiating a terrifying heat the serpent is a blaze of
yellow fire almost too bright to look at directly cast a spell i don't have anything that connects g
damn it i need that fucking ring okay shield no no i no no no no we're going to rewind
uh i'm gonna look in the bucket you haul the bucket over the side of the well and look into it
it is quite empty clearly this well has not been used for a very long time let's lower it
with some effort you get the handle of the well to turn and lower the bucket down into the well
shaft keep going you lower the bucket all the way to the end of the rope there is no splash from
below it seems the well is dry after all okay raise the bucket you turn the old creaking
handle raising the bucket up the shaft anything in it you look into the bucket a snake leaps out
at you from inside and you spring back just in time to avoid being bitten the bucket falls to
the ground and the snake slithers out towards you fangs bared is this one of the dreaded seven
serpents it seems very small this is bait it's not a serpent talk all languages again um illusion
would work fix requires a staff of oak sapling wait was it licks or fix you know you know i'm
asking it was licks um let's do something fun let's make an illusion we have the bracelet might
as well use it you bind the constellations into design around you the spell has no effect it seems
the snake is not intelligent enough to be fooled by an illusion okay well this is pretty evenly
matched we're going all in 50 hp done already the yellow snake looms up from the bucket spitting
you lash wildly aiming to chop the creature down as it also leaps forward thick snake blood
pours along your sword blade i think i can go again because that was all i'm going again
and it was huge and it was almost a two-hit kill snake is weakening its snarls across the
ground i think i go again there's no way you're gonna be able to do it by it better than that
and you're dead perfect sword play flawless fighting you slice a side blow the snake hisses
as it dies all right you return to the side of the well we're good what else can i do here maybe
should i float down force field float in the air let's do float in the air see if i can go in there
oh that lower the bucket oh fuck okay climb climb i'm gonna go climb into the well you feel inside
the edge of the well for handholds it has been at least a day since you last wandered through a
sewer after all but there are none the stone edges of the wall are smooth and the well itself is too
broad to shimmy down you could always climb down the rope of course yeah i'll be good i'm
floating i'm literally floating right now you steal your courage and swing your legs over the
edge of the well regarding the darkness far below the rope is old and probably rotten and should it
break there will be no way back up i'm done hand over hand you lower yourself into the ancient
well shaft okay with your reduced weight you scramble down the rope without difficulty until
you are until you are hanging just beside a crystal seam in the rock look at the crystal
dig out the crystal with my sword use the aniland sword instead okay what is this the seam of
crystal is quite beautiful the soft rock walls are studded with fists and lumps of green and
blue gem glass there must be a fortune down here perhaps even a layered strata of pure wealth
only the backlands could be mined by the king of aniland uh let's use the shitty sword using
your old sword awkwardly in the narrow confines of the well shaft you dig a fistful of gems out
of the wall of the well shaft you cannot catch them all and they fall but thankfully land in the
bucket a short distance below you oh i didn't lower it all the way the bucket was lowered
halfway right next to me you have blunted the edge of your blade in the process however
should i dig for more more you keep digging hoping to get even more crystal from the rock wall
and you do getting several crystals the size of skulls but then your spell wears off the rope
and then starts to spin violently it is unraveling there's nothing you can do to stop it
then it snaps and you fall hitting the bucket below saved for a moment you think you are saved
but of course nothing is holding up the bucket you fall into the depths of the well when the bucket
shatters your neck goes with it you fall into your death your adventure is at an end okay well i got
greedy okay uh thankfully land the bucket dig for more wait shit i did the thing as it says
it says it's the same thing okay use the sword okay go back up i'm all right all right all right
i just i didn't know if i could do anything else okay go back up not wanting to risk the spell
wearing off you clamor up quickly okay now i'm gonna get the gems raise the bucket you bring
the bucket up to the well look in the bucket you check inside the bucket the bottom of the bucket
is also filled with uncut gemstones and glittering rock this hall must be worth scores of gold
pieces take the gems scoop up the gems from the pocket you scoop up the gems from the pocket and
pour them gleefully into your money pouch an excellent find the gems are an assortment of
different types of stone and will require an expert to sort value and cut them but the sheer
size of them is jaw dropping several are the size of eggs and one is the size of a small cat who can
i bring these to the jeweler from the village is the jeweler from the village ah maybe i can go back
okay leave the well please with your work you stride away from the well i need to eat
because i'm dying and i let's see good uh let's go in here oh i love this art style what's the
artist's name i what's the artist's name look it up sorcery artist i should know this why
don't have how have i forgotten this ian livingston that's where it is ian livingston is the artist
i love it you climb up onto the plinth on which the structure stands it appears quiet enough
so whether it is structurally sound or not is another matter cool one of the pillars of the
temple seems to take a step sideways or was that your imagination you step inside the temple the
floor space is quite empty but the walls are decorated with long lines of strange hieroglyphs
that remind you a little of the symbols decorated the ancient shrine of corga in kare you cannot
read them but may be able to decipher them if you look more closely a little dust trickles down from
the temple roof okay so this is a corga shrine corga if you recap andy here corga is a god in
this game a god and if you it's very god's very easy to anger it's the god of what is it chaos
or something you have to do a very specific step of instructions for it to get the favor of corga
or it'll kill you instantly um let's let's just read the hieroglyphs are not exactly like any
language you have seen before but they are similar to others you know you spell out the first few
words allowed this temple built by priests yadu in honor in honor throth goddess of earth wrong
lore fake fan oops those not of faith are forbidden and these must not speak the name
throth you stop suddenly there's a deep rumbling in the ground below your feet
don't say the name throth while you're reading the name throth uh i forget what happens here
if i don't have throth for a god i can't be here i think i just need to get out of here
ian livingston is a different author john blanche the artist really i always thought that ian
livingston did the art let me hold on let me let's confirm this ian livingston is an english
fantasy author and entrepreneur along with steve jackson he's the co-founder of a series of
role-playing game books fighting fantasy and the author of many books within that series something
also very interesting about eating livingston and steve jackson right uh they he co-founded games
workshop in 1975 just to make sure you understand who you're talking about and who you're dealing
with here this the this is the guy who created games workshop so those of you that want to know
this is the start this is the the pavement of the road for a ton of things that you think are cool
nowadays uh time the person up that is resident sleeper i don't want to ever see them ever again
i never want to see them in this chat ever again until tomorrow they can come back and by tomorrow
i mean in in um in goldfish years so like maybe 10 minutes all right uh i am don't think this is a
good idea i i don't want to beg throff for mercy that's me saying throff i'm not allowed to say
throff if i'm not a throff follower i'm getting out here i don't know why i thought that just
said beg throff for money uh i'm leaving oh fine i'll read more death is certain unless the victim
will become a follower of throff well there you go at the third use of the goddess's name something
happens the rumblings subside and a woman in leather armor steps out of a carving in the wall
mortal you speak my name thrice in my temple do you wish to follow me yes no this is really
important because say goodbye to the ape um i need a i need a uh a poll here saying yes removes the
ape permanently by the way but we'll have throff throff is a very powerful god very powerful
goddess we need a 60 second poll are we becoming followers of throff right now yes or no john
blanche did a lots of warhammer illustrations it's like i think the founding fathers of all
fucking like role playing games no i'm seeing a lot of nos i feel like there's a lot of people
here that are going to be upset about a the ape being gone where's the poll um i'll get it let
me see here we go all right what do you what do you think i'm gonna say yes or no you know what
it is or throff or no throff you say who roth or ape there you go uh oh oh boy sorry i thought this
is going to be the complete other direction nice background idiot what's your background
i'll let it play out but it doesn't look good but wait a second apes are coming in roth is holding
it though i don't know i don't know it's going to be close it's going to be really close
some of you just sprinted to your computer to click the ape button i could hear the footsteps
down the hall it was you were running to get over here okay no then i will bury you replies throff
opening a crack in the ground beneath your feet from above the roof cracks and a slab of rock
falls do not alter my beliefs your heart is resolute and you are fixed the rock overhead
falls it is your capstone and the ground below is your grave you have been buried alive okay so
we just don't step over here all right i'm gonna push one of the pillars testing the strength you
have you heave against one of the temple's pillars it seems solid then a moment later it shears and
gives way the whole structure is sliding down on top of you dodge you dodge backwards as the gigantic
roof of the building tilts sliding in your direction you are still alive but you're now
trapping ease an enormous pile of rubble help help me help you cry out feebly for aid but of
course no one comes these are the clatterback steps and no one lives here broth traders deserve
the kid oh my god uh i could summon a giant please giant friend help me i'm buried under all of this
i can't teleport i could grow in size that one works i'm dead in one hit you cast the enchantment
rapidly growing to 18 feet in height but in such a small space there is no room for the transition
and you end up terribly squashed i just made it worse all right push the stones i'm big now
you even push with all you might and finally a few of the stones begin to move you keep pushing
yourself through until you squirm out from underneath the giant pillar and lie gasping
on the stone the temple is now completely destroyed thus spiraling up into the air
you search through the rubble but find nothing of use the plinth is now knee deep in broken
stone and pebble sized rocks take a pebble okay i now have access to grenades you gather up a
couple of pebbles from the plinth of the right size and shape to be useful in spells but of the
ancient temples treasures and artifacts there's nothing more to be had oh did i lose access to
this i think i did i destroyed the whole place there's nothing more to be done here you leave
the ancient building behind and you stride forwards okay okay we're cool what about okay
so now i'm going to go over here and let's aim this in this direction and see what this looks
like in the in the past then we can aim it up here too got a lot to do okay you sink lower
in the mud we already did this you go through the marsh uh just keep walking we're fine we won't
sink it's just the marsh lands and now let's go into the mountain last hit point dude uh it's true
i gotta pee let's take a break i'll be right back seeing some people saying woman throff
hell seems like it's a little bit of a war here we got the age still we're fine back to it all
right so we are at another tower you want a quick little recap we ruined this temple pissed off an
incredibly powerful goddess chose the ape uh got like tortured over here by the time serpent time
serpent kind of fucked off over here i said it looks like at least it looks like that and now
we're here at one of these beacons you approach the edge of the mountains in the base of an old
stone tower carved from the cliff face itself from the battlements of the tower protrudes a strange
brass cylinder nestled between the stones there's a large closed wooden door okay let's just knock
on the door you knock on the door there's no reply i only have one hp so i can't really cast any
spells so we're just gonna have to go in you try the door to the tower it's locked but the wood is
ancient and rotten and could most likely be easily broken break down the door you take a run up and
then charge at the door smashing straight through and tumbling to the floor inside hopefully this
doesn't kill me oh no i'm dead i'm gonna die here okay you pick yourself up off the ground
only finding yourself staring into the snarling jaws of a wolfhound it's clearly half mad with
starvation there's no time and no choice let's go six good okay that was clean it limps back
bleeding heavily if i get it close again here like three point let's do all in i just completely
ruined everything i'm dead i thought it was good okay uh this time it's gonna defend i'm gonna
defend too and then we full blast uh yep all right we're good full blast again that should do it
barely but we got it all right i'm good wolfhounds howls a gurgling blood-soaked
sound that rings inside the tower and then it dies you wipe your long sword and how much
harder would this be without the long sword i wonder plus two you wipe your long sword and gas
for breath as you look around the room the wide tower base is empty except for a flight of spiral
stairs leading up to a hatch in the ceiling overhead search the shadows you try to ignore
the smell of wet blood that fills the chamber and search the gloomy arches under the spiraling
staircase in a forgotten corner you unearth three gold pieces take the money you take the coins and
drop them into your purse time to leave this gloomy place yes we're going to go turn this on
i should sleep here you clamor up the spiral stairs to the hatch and go through onto the roof
of the tower the cool wind of the steps hits you full in the face snatching your breath away
this tower stands on the slope of one of the horns themselves looking out over the hole of
the steps the tower bears another brass cylinder similar to the last there are powerful unusual
stars here unusual stars why are they unusual unusual i could see the future again here
hmm activate the beacon takes a moment beacon is now activated and ah okay look what i could do
here's okay here's here's the i could aim it here or actually right here i could complete the bridge
with this one and turn that beacon into the past is there anything here worth exploring probably
that so remember this is the past so this was the temple now it's something else now it's just
the one little spot this is still here let's check out this because i want to see what this is
i want to see this in the past and i want to see over here in the past too that should do it right
it's also rest go get the ring i'll go get the ring you could not choose a better place to rest
you close the latch and lie down on top of it nothing will cost you now unless it has wings
at least you've eaten once already today thank god you close your eyes and let your
tiredness overtake you you feel quite safe you do not dream you ran out of provisions and gained
some gold and you collected the sun serpent so you now have destroyed three of the archmages
serpents okay look at the view you go over to the battleman and lean out looking north you see the
edge of the thick and virgin forest the fabled trees of santa you heard about them as a boy of
course but never dreamed you would see them for yourself between there and here is nothing but
the level flats of the steps layered like the scales on a serpent's back a thin column of
smoke rises from a point just before the treeline it must be the village of the clatterman
you look away from the view once more let's get down here okay good good mountains easter
impassable huh all right so let's see what this is now i feel like i'm gonna get fucked with by the
time serpent again but this is in the past you're walking through boggy marshland a few clouds
hurry across the sky you cross the marshland and pause inside a ring of seven standing stones
look at the stones each stone in the ring is the size and breadth of a man they stand straight
upright except for one which has listed sideways like an arthritic finger a few are carved in the
very center of the ring a flat stone lies an inch or so below the water level of the marsh wet
things gulp and groan in the mud below one time i listened to one of your streams so i could go
to sleep and it gave me the worst nightmares it's not my fault that's the entire like four or five
servings of macaroni and cheese you ate before going to bed has nothing to do with me that's
nothing to do with me come on gwen okay uh should i go stand on it look at it you trace the carving
on one of the nearby stones shows a fearsome bird rising up into the sky wings blotting out
the rising sun let's just go stand on it fuck it why not you go stand on the central stone but
nothing special occurs if there is magic here you cannot fathom it you step out from the circle
once more and plod on through the marsh water so i don't get it maybe this is where you cast licks
it's been a long time i don't remember i besides last year when i played it yeah you gotta go back
seven or eight years okay let's go i want to see this too and this laughing my ass off what is
this youtube donation shit i don't know i i didn't even look at it yet i have not even opened up my
twitch dashboard to even see what that is like i know what it is but i haven't even looked at it
all right the ground itself seems to give way to bog land until you are splashing through marshland
once again you stumble upon a low round structure it is the mouth of a well oh it's the well the
well is the only thing that's here is there more gems in here i'm going in should i throw a stone
toss a stone you toss a stone into the well it falls for a few seconds and then you hear a splash
so there's water in the past as you stand by the well side you hear a scraping noise from within
and after a few minutes two curved claws emerge through the opening hooking onto either side of
the well mouth something is pulling itself up dislodge the hooks acting quickly you knock the
hooks free there is a scream very human as the figure inside the well falls there is a distant
splash and then silence oh shit are you in there you cry leaning over the edge of the well there
is no reply i think i just killed somebody look into the well you stare down hoping for a response
but can make nothing out below toss down the rope ladder acting quickly you tie the rope ladder to
a peg on the well house and toss the rope ladder down for a moment you think it has done no good
but then the rope goes taut someone is climbing up am i just running at this point like why would
you run wait you wait as the figure clamors out of the well and then dusts itself down
they collect up the rope ladder and hand it back to you thank you stranger the creature declares
greetings you declare the creature doffs its hat rubbing a bruise on its head as it hands you back
the stone you threw down the well then without a further word it turns and disappears across
what is there something else i could have said it's just okay you continue to walk a big bruise on
his head uh can i go up here uh the air is warm oh wait a minute i can what's this have i been i
don't i haven't been here you keep moving ascending and descending the sun is beginning to lower and
the air begins to cool this is the eastern slope of the baobab ridge move on oh it's too steep i
can't get up there it's too steep but i want to who's in this hut could i have floated or
i guess i can let's do uh this doesn't cost any stamina let's hover looking to the constellations
you craft the spell then the medallion begins to glow as you rise gently into the air you rise a
short way up the rock chimney but the whole ascent is a long way keep going spell carries you high
and without incident or weakening you land gently on the mountaintop here we go oh okay your weight
returns and you settle gradually back down to the ground this was once perhaps the cone of a volcano
now it is a wide dusty stone bowl but it is not empty in the center stands a circular dwelling
with a steeply pitched canvas roof look at the chimney looking more closely at the chimney in
the rock you notice a faint purple aura surrounding some of the stones near the top
and a few faint purple glows further down perhaps there is some enchantment on this
blue or perhaps it is simply a color the owner of the hut enjoys cold winds claw your skin it
might just they might just like the color you're going the wrong way there is no wrong way there
is only there's only forward in sorcery there's no wrong way drop a stone down the chimney what
can i do here i keep dropping rocks on people's heads uh i mean this is a great opportunity
to send a goblin in yeah let's do it i'm doing it okay casting your spell across the goblin
tooth the tooth erupts into a column of smoke and a moment later a goblin warrior is standing in
front of you order the goblin into the hut you point at the hut door and order the goblin to
proceed it does so but a moment later has vaporized into a pile of dust clearly something very powerful
lives within all right now drop a rock down the chimney you grab a nearby stone and toss it over
the side of the mountain it plummets just as fast as you might expect careening and bouncing from
the chimney sides until it explodes into particulate dust halfway down a few loose
stones tumble over the sheer drop to the east and disappear uh send another goblin in that
was funny i could do big safe passage how is a good one here do another goblin what about sus
i mean we we casted a free sus because i said to a goblin to go in there and investigate and he got
fucking liquidated so we know it's dangerous in there let's do big and just like walk over there
why not you line the starlight into shape quickly expanding to triple your size let's go into the
chimney i can't can i no no no no no no this is i'm gonna slide down
pass no we're going in the hut i'm going to the hut you approach the hut its walls are made of
painted wooden planks well set into the rock below this is no temporary shack or a traveler's tent
a little thin smoke is rising from the stack there's strong and generous magic here as often
occurs high up knock on the door you approach the door and you knock from inside of wizened voice
calls you're late enter the hut intrigued by the voice's words you open the door and hunch down
low and squeeze yourself into the oh i'm big what what's the point of being this huge okay
inside the hut there is no room to stand up it is a small place made even smaller by your spell
of giantism let us suppose that i am a sorcerer and you are a sorcerer too do you know which of
us is the more powerful uh there is no contest it is i guess so a moment later there is a snatch
of music and suddenly your legs and arms jerk upwards then fall still what was that there's
another burst of magic and your legs begin to kick and pirouette you around you are dancing
oh i'm getting i'm getting a jig uh stand still you try to hold your body still but it is useless
it is not that your limbs are under external control but rather the compulsion to dance like
the compulsion to sneeze is so strong you cannot resist for more than a moment i see you are not
powerful enough to counter that stop the music the music stops and you collapse into a nearby
chair i know the spell you hear the speaker rise and approach a wizened calloused hand is offered
welcome i mean you're no harm as you can tell by my advanced age spit on the hand
no greetings okay gentle light is filling the hut and you can now see the sorceress a woman so ancient
that her features are lost within a mess of wrinkles she smiles as you look at her i could
be anybody under all these years could i not who are you my name is bria i am a sorceress of high
zamen though i left that place some time ago you're welcome she frowns though if you continue
stomping around in here at three times your proper size you're going to knock something over so we
won't have any more of that it'll it'll pass hey it'll pass soon don't worry it'll pass
cancel the spell no i'm good i'm hanging out i'm big it'll pass soon you reply casually not soon
enough bria clicks her tongue and reaches into a pouch by her side producing something the size
and shape of a die what what is that you say as you lean forward bumping the part of your forehead
that hurts the most onto the beam that is a support beam of the roof ow the giant's tooth
she replies casting it onto the floor a moment later smoke is hissing from the tooth are we
having a giant fight uh step back you step back quickly expecting a giant to materialize in the
middle of the hut but nothing happens the smoke from the tooth quickly passes a moment later you
are shrinking back to your normal size a counter spell yes the spell of giantism is countered by
that of giant summoning cheeky very cheeky you are a follower of the archmage jumping back yes yes
yes you are worried but please the archmage of the fortress was not always as he is now gradually
you shrink back down to your normal size ask about the archmage can you tell me of the archmage
imagine if you will a country of great peace and prosperity ruled over by a group of wise and
powerful sorcerers and sorceresses they tended the fields managed the weather healed the sick
they chose their leader by an arcane process any child from the land might become that leader
and be taught their role from an early age what of the crown you demand the crown of kings a
powerful thing certainly but nothing against a fortress of sorcerers working in concert the
crown was given to the human kingdoms to let them feel themselves self-governed imagine the archmage
as a peacemaker teacher but also a thinker a discoverer of many secrets of the stars he looked
too far this archmage he is evil yes now yes that is probably true it was not always so but you
should not let that trouble you if you need to kill him and kill him you must she gestures you
to sit down and takes a seat herself what about the serpents what do you know of the seven serpents
they are the archmage's servants but even they cannot travel the backlands without
fouling foul of its terrible curse i see that you search for them do you know where they are
i've seen a few things the earth serpent lies in wait in a fissure near the great lake eclala
and the serpent of time is the worst of the seven swift and all but indestructible
fissure near the great lake does he have a weakness he does i do not know it it is a secret known
only to the marsh goblins if you can find them i did find them you thank her the old woman stands
suddenly and goes over to a table tea yeah thank you i'll stay i i licks how do she nods and boils
a pan of water by holding it between her palms for a moment she drops a pat of goat butter and
stirs it around and pours out two ceramic cups i did this routine last time but we're doing it
again you see i swapped the cups when you turned around and then i thought you poisoned your cup
but then the fact that i swapped the cups means the poison was in my cup thank you i will bow for
that one inconceivable i love when he just falls over he just goes he's like completely still and
he just goes just drink it normally i'll just we'll just drink it i'm gonna drink mine you
lift the cup to your lips and drink deep it is warm and rich and refreshing didn't need to swap
cups don't need to do anything weird i don't i don't think that rea is gonna hurt us goat cheese
tea i know i wouldn't drink it this is the anilander not me my suspension of disbelief is
only go so far i mean i it's actually kind of hard to believe that somebody would drink
goat cheese tea it's that my disbelief is hard to to quell when i think about anybody eating anything
goat cheese i just you're losing me a little tell me more of yourself you ask sipping your tea
me blushing a lot there was little more to know i lived in the fortress for most of my life
i came here in my old age she winces hot tea is dripping from a crack in her tea cup cheap
pottery rubbish she grumbles digging up a small pot of glue from a box and repairing it she leaves
the glue pot on the table do you play swindle stones i mean can i have the i need glue for a
spell you pick up the pot of glue and put it in your pack without another word the sorceress
watches you with some amusement though you cannot think why she stands i'm tiring of you you should
go but first one more thing if you are traveling to high xamen to face the archmage hadn't you best
know a little of the higher functions of magic you speak of countering good you know it
it can take a lifetime to discover the pairings and to master them but i can show you something
simple she raises a finger adorned with a wide collection of rings one made of green metal begins
to pulse but she does not fire right away she's giving you a moment to react run for the door i
gotta get out of here oh shit what do i do counterspell my spell of teleportation i have
already given you the clue as to what spell you need it's glue it's glue great glue that she did
it on purpose you weave the spell and toss the glue over your own feet you feel it binding your
boots to the floor the sorceress smiles as she completes her spell firing at you with her green
ringed finger you stare her magic in the face but nothing happens very good every magic has
a counter magic the enchantment of gluing matches the spell of teleportation your own spell has
evaporated as well your boots move freely once more prepare yourself she shows you an open palm
filled with rock dust hey can you stop afraid of them afraid of the ape save me ape that's my
counterspell faith that's my counterspell faith to the ape and it always works okay sand that's
quicksand that would be uh gale horn zen i don't zen's not available it's probably gale horn
oh wait hold on it could be wall so this is quicksand so floating would probably work
i think that's it yeah okay feeling your body weight shifting to a mere fraction of normal
just as bria's spell of petrification begins to take hold the two forces one turning you to
air the other to stone fight within you but with decreasing force moment by moment eventually your
body returns to normal yes indeed the magic of lightness is blocked by that of petrification
you've learned enough you must leave but not without a gift she slides the ring of green
metal from her finger and holds it out to you teleport ring take it you take the ring swiftly
and slide it onto your finger you feel a pulse through your veins i wish you well now be gone
okay now we know where two of them are oh i think okay it's in the it's in the present
yeah because this is uh i have this going to the past where even are we oh we all the way over here
geez return to the hut should i go back in no no no oh she'll probably kill me um what what's
over here let's just look it's a big circle you head over to the mountain pass look around you
glance around the wide pit of the old volcano but there's little to be seen no doubt the ash
mixed in the dust is what makes the forest you saw on the slopes so lush and verdant at least
it seems fairly unlikely the volcano will erupt again so this will take down through here where
this is where we started by the way it's here uh we need to go back in this way okay make a move
into the chimney okay you begin to plunge down the mountainside knocking and scraping the rock
surface on either side you close your eyes and your heart begins to move up your throat wait i
just jump off the cliff oh i just jumped off you followed speed a dead drop down the side of the
mountain the rushing wind snatches away your breath death is certain you take a moment to
arrange your thoughts do i die you're almost at the bottom the sharp rocks rush to meet you
then a few heartbeats from a terrible death your fall is suddenly cushioned
and you are brought to a gentle stop at the base of the mountain i landed you stand hearts still
racing at the bottom of the stone chimney quite amazed to be alive but there's no way back up that
you can see what plot armor i think it was her i'm going to assume it was her okay let's go back here
because i want to point this over here see what this was like in the uh in the past keep going
mm-hmm i'm also going to try to hit the bridge too with this i can sleep up here too which is
perfect i don't have any food but it's all right ah see the hut up here i wonder if it's worth
going back there back in the past there's a lot going on in the swamp i think there's probably a
serpent in the swamp before it became the forest but that's not what i'm going to do my goal is
to go like this try to hit this part of the bridge so it's complete so i can go across it
and at the same time hitting this needs to be complete because then i'll aim this one over here
na aim i'm good is that enough i think that's enough because then i can just connect these two
let's go for it and i'm going to teleport over here let's go sauron chop chop we got more reading
to fucking do i'm going i'm going um i need to sleep let me sleep first let's go sauron you've
not eaten your pack is empty that's all right it keeps reminding me of this even though i did
that like four days ago okay now i'm going to go get the ring what's the spell to uneat the
pack of ritz crackers i just inhaled um we'll just wait like 16 hours or so and then when
you're sitting on the toilet pretend to be casting a spell when you know that makes sense come on
dude what no they want to eat them again oh but i mean like minus two respectfully
grow up that's not what i'm saying that i meant like oh that's like a funny oh how do i like get
rid of the ritz crackers i just ate i don't know i thought like oh yeah to the stars those ritz
crackers come on that's actually kind of funny the wretched dung eater that's not what i was
saying and you know it don't put words in my elf or i'll ban everybody this should work now
slipped over the tip of the branch take the ring that's fine i can break the branch snaps into
the ring goes off disappears into the nearby trees that's fine it did not go into the water scan the
forest look down from the view okay climb down did it work yeah the undergrowth here is quite thick
and despite thrashing at the bushes you cannot see any hint of the ring that fell from the tower
it may not even have fallen this close to the tower base so is most likely at the bottom of
the marsh by now what unspeakable i'm floating you are not floating high enough to clear the
tangled bushes oh fuck off shit force field no no where how do i get that ring i don't know how
to get the ring but whatever uh i need to aim it this way just let it go dude let it go yeah
yeah all right i need to move this though i don't know i don't know how to do it the bridge is
successfully repaired kind of ah is that accurate hard to tell i can't get the ring i don't know
it's i gotta do something like very special and specific okay i have to kill the seven serpents
not talk to them this doesn't look like it's connected is it though it kind of is okay it
breaks up every now and again though uh i have to teleport see it's like broken up can i climb
this okay like can i climb up here climb the pillar here we go all right let's do it there's
no way up the bridge from here really i have to go over here then i can climb the bridge in the
past i should probably teleport to here and then walk yeah that is the past you could have gotten
a serpent ring in kare it's okay you can't get every item you can't get every single item just
to make sure i'm gonna aim this one over there too we're hitting this with every single one
looks like you're playing the elden ring map one of the first things i thought about when i saw
the elden ring map was that it looked exactly like sorcery and i love the style of this map
it's super mysterious like the little buildings are just kind of it's not like oh look at this
here's the point of interest here's what it is it's just kind of like a little hut
and you can go look at it i really like it a lot like for instance stuff like this is just
what even is that i don't know but i'm gonna go look at it oh yeah what is like what's this thing
i don't know seems like kind of like a broken down building i guess i'm gonna i want to see it
but it looks um pretty similar i love it so i'm glad it's here i'm glad they did an elden ring too
does skyrim do that does skyrim have a map like that fastest way to make me play that game
just kidding oh i have right i have to aim at this to get it to aim that way okay i am actually
gonna go teleport to that one you sound like you have a library card i actually don't
but the first thing you think of when you hear me talk is this guy reads a bunch of books
i don't know where you got that from it's almost kind of overlapping yeah it's overlapping oh p i'll
keep your leg right here all right let's go to the bridge finally it's time to cross into the next
area in the time between the sorcery streams i was able to beat sorcery one through four normal and
new game plus i love this game thanks for introducing me to it i am ecstatic that you said
that genuinely okay here we go at least somebody is finishing it um it's been 295 days since the
last sorcery stream before these last couple they've had a lot of time to play it if they
don't mean like in the last two days they mean in the last year uh i think it's safe here wait
hold on all right we have been through this area a couple times but we have an event here you stretch
out and rest suddenly all around you goes quiet the night air itself seems to still you hear a
distant voice listen you stay quiet and strain your ears to listen greetings in tones of voice
aged and self-satisfied i trust the backlands are treating you kindly as my fair city it takes a
moment to place the voice it is lorag the wizard of kare what are you doing here i'm here to help
as you helped me in my fair city you have a message in a language you do not understand
i may be of some assistance very well i would be glad of your aid in the marsh you were given a
parchment show it to me you pull out the parchment given to you by the goblins and you begin to feel
a strange sensation as if someone else was controlling your eyes moving them backwards
and forwards across the words that's creepy read you have little choice but to read yes
i was right to come you feel your finger lift and tap the paper it is most interesting indeed most
valuable the voice vanishes promptly what does it say but the wizard's presence has gone you are
quite alone once more and none of the wiser for it oh great you seem guarded here oh come on man
what did he just do he's you're gonna take that and what are you gonna do with it
typical lorag why would i yeah why would i trust lorag that was a bad idea lorag is like chaotic
neutral he's i mean he usually he's pretty chaotic evil i think sometimes you just got don't know
walled yeah okay well thanks for nothing lorag it's kind of a dick oh he's a he's a very he's
a big dick he's a super dick i would say that's a understatement the sunrise up so high is cold
you get to your feet here we go oh look it actually fades out i have to hit it as it's still
there you step onto the bridge the early morning sun makes the air glow keep going okay you make
your way under the stones of the bridge which form a broad solid path thick marsh we already know
yes we can still keep going gotta catch it the right moment oh come on don't do this to me
yes what the stones underfoot begin to disappear revealing a void below no oh come on i have to be
faster come on really shit that's very unfortunate missed it okay wait wait wait wait here's my idea
i need to wait and i need to i'm gonna i get a spam move on i have to wait till it's selectable
it's not it's not selectable for a second or two here comes where is it fuck you shit no
oh if i gotta go back and move one what's the problem here i have to sleep okay i gotta teleport
around i'll get there i'll get there i'll get it i'll get it i'll get it so then i guess this one
has to point over here how do i get the whole bridge to be intact i feel like i can hmm it's
probably i could probably get in the mountain somewhere too like in here or like down here
light up the end of the bridge and climb the middle part that's probably the right idea i'm
gonna go see if it's possible you have the beacons just wrong you can do it let's find out i thought
i had them in a fine place that was fine let me see can i all right if i go like this uh hold on a
second here watch this they're fighting each other that's why there we go so now that will be perfect
i have this the other one is aiming over here i have to turn that one away and i'll aim this one
this way um where should i point this we did this over here in both past and present i could aim it
in the this like marsh area yes this is probably a couple of events here that i have we didn't get
to this looks perfect now the only thing that's concerning me is this that's concerning me should
i be concerned i hope it's fine i think it's fine all right let's go very cool all right let's move
the third and fourth game they are a lot there's a lot of backtracking so this is not abnormal some
of the complaints of the third game in the third book series whatever you want to call it is people
don't want to do the go back and backtrack three times but i don't mind it i think the beams
they're going back in time and doing stuff differently i think it's fun all right move on
here we go yes finally gonna make it across the bridge i don't think this is gonna be a
problem i think we're good an eagle hovers above the valley waiting to scoop up its prey
i don't want to wait around for that you walk across the bridge a little light glows in the
east there are no handrails here sitting by the sheer drop at the edge of the road is a
starving looking man with legs folded beneath him and head bowed to the stone he is perhaps
asleep or drunk or dead let's wake him up you touch him on the shoulder and he sits up sharply
greetings well met spare a coin he slides his palm he perhaps does not have the energy to
lift across the stone what will you spend it on you ask noting his red rimmed eyes and two aged
skin that's my business isn't it i have to live don't i we talk very similar you and i here you
can have a coin use it wisely he nods thank you stranger all right let's get some info you open
your mouth preparing to ask the man for information to return for your gold but the words fail when
the beggar holds your gold coin out over the side of the bridge and lets it go it twinkles as it
sails out of sight that was careless what i dropped it i didn't fumble it i don't have the
shakes i'm not ill then why did you do that you demand somewhat outraged isn't falling wonderful
you should try it he chuckles perhaps one day i will i'm just waiting for the right weather for
it he lies down and peers over the side of the bridge at the distant valley floor lost in thought
you leave the man and move along the bridge what the hell was that okay here we are you've reached
the other side of the bridge in the distance the sun breaks over the horizon you have been awake
all night and are weaker for it from here a set of chiseled steps leads downwards towards water
you feel cheered by the sight you have crossed the horns of eclala now only the lake stands between
you and the road to high xamen this is not a place to rest do you still have some way to travel
before you are clear of the backlands and then some it's still serpents up here probably still
serpents we just need to get more info and down the slope that's where we will go next time we
have all of this to explore end of the stream some you guys just know it's coming um yeah my
stomach's kind of being annoying so i'm gonna go take care of myself you know what i mean i was
gonna get farther this stream that's the beauty of sorcery sometimes you just don't make any
progress well that's not true we killed the fire serpent learned about the time serpent we have
come across at least three of them we know where two of them are these will be bang bang right here
he just made that sound so dirty he's gonna go take care of himself
oh
yeah yeah i'll be back guys uh i'll see you later i gotta go take care of myself
that's so stupid they're like oh man all these old wizened uh you know monsters and old ladies
and old men screaming at me and throwing rocks at me i'll you know i'll be back i'm gonna take
care of myself this stream is earning its maturity rating in the last minute
it's been on for 10 years come on all right yeah that's it i'll see you guys the next time i will
stream will be we got here we're gonna pick up exactly what we left off i'm not gonna play it
off stream don't worry get some music up here let me take a look at the let me look at the
calendar for a second because i got some stuff to do all right what we got i will see you guys on
probably wednesday yeah wednesday makes sense if not wednesday for some reason there's some
things i have to do but at the very minimum i'm going to implore you to watch seadog's stream
this coming week on the 29th i'm going to have some items that are going to be up for seadog's
stream i don't know if i have an opportunity to say that later if i do not stream on wednesday
because it's on the 29th but i'll i'll be pushing people to it yeah i don't want to say what it is
because i think that's i think i'd rather have connor be able to announce that i don't want to
kind of say hey it's this and this this this but there will be an item or items that will be part
of his charity stream so go check it out it is not that it is absolutely not that i don't even want
to say what that was no it's not i'm telling you that thing is i'm gonna bury that thing that
thing's gonna get buried yeah if you don't hear from me i just keep an eye on the sus there'll
be another stream this week uh but at the very minimum on the 29th please absolutely go support
that stream not only because there's gonna be stuff of me on it but because it's a great cause
and you should go and support it so go check out seadog's stream 29th go check uh go check his
twitter there's a lot more info on it too no it is not an ass baseball it's pretty it's pretty
cool just telling you it's pretty cool yeah thanks for hanging out thanks for watching thanks for
obviously subscribing and doing what you guys do appreciate it keep an eye on the sus i have
i kind of to be determined i'm trying to get over this annoying bullshit with my stomach intestines
whatever you want to call it but i'm fine don't worry it's not the first time it's not my first
i'll be good don't worry so yeah keep an eye on the sus i will be very clear yeah i put the sus
pretty vague but you will see me again this week take care of yourself good night have a great
rest of your evening call your mother call your father too call him both i always say call your
mother why does it never call your father talk to him both get him on speaker yeah take it easy
take care have a great night see you at some point this week bye bye i don't want to startle you so
it came in pretty quietly i'm going for four hours and 30 minutes on the dot see if i can do it here we go