Hey, what is going on everybody Jerma here with one in the chamber some more one of the chamber because I love this game mode
It's like one of my favorite things in Call of Duty black ops. So let's see if I can get like a flawless run here
Anybody want anybody want it check that UAV
No, there's no way I miss
What the what that guy was like 10 feet away from me. I gotta see that. Oh
Oh
Alright fine. Fine. I'll let you take it the guy right here
Yes, yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Anybody else anybody else want to get this around this corner
Around the corner. No UAV. I'm gonna win. I'm gonna win. Watch this ready
That guy just died. Oh
That guy seriously just died like one second ago. So there's a person right here. Where the hell is this guy?
Yep, what I'm so confused right now. He's up top
That was full. It's alright. I got him. Anyways, yeah
One dude over here. I'm gonna get you. I'm gonna get you that doesn't make any sense at all
I'm gonna get picked off right here
This guy knows I'm coming behind him. He's gonna play some weird game with my head here. No where he's upstairs
Dude, I'm gonna smash you in your face. Oh, he was right there. I just saw him now
I caught no man's land here jump out into hell. Let's get myself killed this guy. Come here. Quit running away
I know you're up there. This guy's running around in circles
Areas
Finally for crying out loud. Let's go this way. Let's try to get this guy on the left. It's right here
Oh, you're gonna show yourself. I'm gonna put it in your face. Oh
damn it
Yes
No, oh baby, I
Only died one time. Damn if I didn't die that one time. I would have had a flawless run right there. Oh
Alright, I'll do another one that guy almost had an awesome game ending kill cam right there. Let's do that
I ruined it for him. Hell. Yeah. Alright one down. Let's do it again. Here we go. Three two one action
All right, don't freak out in the very beginning here. Let's be
Got yeah
Sprinting around I gotta learn how to not sprint around like crazy and I there is the guy. Oh boy. Damn it
There's another guy right here. Is he? No, he's coming around the back. What did you do? But yeah, there's no way
Oh, yeah, there is a way cuz I have a three bar
Yeah
Three bar this guy right here. Oh boy. I'm scared. This guy's waiting for me to climb up
Running this way. This guy's just sitting right here. I'm going I'm going around the back
See if I could sneak up on though and now he's trying to come behind me
Get out of here. Get out of here. Damn it. Oh, I'm on my last life. I gotta be careful here
Come on. Oh, no, I just saw bullets. He's he is the guy in the window over here. I don't know
I just don't know very cautiously very cautious. There's two dudes right here
Get out of here. Oh
Let's only there's only two guys left one guy in front of me one guy behind me
I'm so scared. I don't know where this guy's gonna come from. Oh, he's coming from behind. Oh you son of a
All right, it's gonna be the last one third times a charm. I almost won two in a row right there. Let's do it
Let's go nuts. Let's just go nuts here
Where oh where has my little dog gone? Oh where oh where can he be a guy just spawned back here?
Where can he be?
I'm like lagging right now. Wow, come on. How does this guy not know I'm right behind him? Oh
That was close. Oh
Man, give me this. Oh get shot in your face. Oh, I'm gonna roll here. I gotta be real careful
Oh, baby, this is gonna be the one. It's gonna be the flawless run. This is gonna be at this last guy. Oh
baby, oh
Oh
That's a good way to end it nice. All right. Well, uh, thank you so much for watching guys really do appreciate it
I love this game mode
So go play it if you have never played it before it's so much fun and I'll see you guys all next time
And of course, take care
Everybody ten and oh