Okay, so I think what I want to do is I want to play the game. I want to play the game
that I was gonna play instead of this. I want to play Wizorb, another requested game. It looks
like a lot of fun, and it's a good, I think, little short little game just to play in the meantime.
It's, we made a reference to it during Nancy Drew. Just chill out for a little bit. I'm gonna give
it a try. Let's open it right now. If I can get, where's my library? Diablo II. I do want to
actually play Diablo II. I want to play Diablo II on hardcore and keep that character alive as
best as I can. And if the character, you know, that's it, hardcore. Try to keep that character
going. Maybe jump in random servers with people. But I don't want to boost, I know, I don't want
to do a thing where you join the cowl level 10 times or you join the tombs 10 times. You do
Tristram 30 times in a row and you level up 40 times. I want to do it legit. But anyways,
I'm gonna play Wizorb. It was in the recommended channel and it actually looks cute. It looks very
cute. It looks very fun. We'll see. I'm gonna give it a chance. It looks pretty good. And good thing
I turned that volume off because holy shit, I would have just hurt a lot of people. You can
probably hear it through. It looks like Game Boy. Okay, hold on. Look what was said about you. Hold
on. I'll look at it in a sec. No vibration. Full screen on. Paddle speed. What am I supposed to do?
40%? This is still loud. 20%? Yeah, it's still loud as fuck. Hold on, I'll look at it. Beat Dark
Souls real quick. Um, I, no, I don't think so. Let me get this captured. Can this be captured?
Let's hope so. Let's hope so. What was it? Let me see that clip to people spamming this clip.
What was said about me? What did Joel say? Let's see. All right. What does he say? He's like
stretching something over my face. Did he trace my, what did he trace over my face? What the hell is
this? That's not even that funny. That's not even funny. Oh, this is kind of funny. Hold on,
hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Let me just get this captured first. He thinks it's his real face. He
thinks that, no, I don't. I mean, it could have been. Wizard Orb. You guys are gonna like this.
Look at how cute this is. Look at how fucking cute this is. All right. I gotta show this shit
because everybody wants to fucking laugh out loud.
Everyone's just laughing out loud about it. Okay. I gotta also do this. It's being stretched.
It's being stretched. It's being stretched. All right. I'll see you soon. Bye. Thank you.
All right. I'm going to, the image is being stretched. I got to change this.
Uh, let's do, it's called Wizard Orb, right? I think I got a prediction here. I think you guys
are gonna really like this game. This is like a breakout. Breakout. I think I'm gonna like this
game. Time to get addicted. Let's go. Uh, new quest. Difficulty. What do we do? Easy. No. Ah,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I wanted to do normal. Oh no. Back it up. Back it up. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no. I got to turn it, but I just found out it's too loud. Let's turn that down.
Shit, it's fucking loud. All right. New quest. Yes, I'm sure. Is hard. Let's just, let's just do
normal. How hard is hard? I wonder how hard hard is. Hmm. All right. I'll try. How do you control it?
Oh shit. I have to hit the bears? Wait, I can shoot? Oh, I think I can only do that. So wait,
I can only do that a little. I think I just wasted all of it. It's all gone.
Yeah, that's all gone. God damn it. It's breakout. Yeah. This is sick. Thank you for helping us.
The citizens of Taro are the only ones to have escaped the curse cast by demons.
However, monsters came from Gerudo castle and attacked our town. Please save the kingdom of
Gerudo. All right. Go ahead. I can wait. I can walk around too. The mayor cares more for his
citizens than for himself. I'd rebuild his house if I had the funds. Donate 999 GP.
I don't have that. Once united, the four sacred children of Gerudo have the power of summoning
the forces of nature. They could help us if we could find them. All right. This is fucking
pogchamp if I've ever seen one. Does he have to like rebuild shit? All right. Let's go. I can't
do any business without a nice shop. What shall I do? Donate 700. I don't have that. All right.
This is all upgradable. It's already got me. It's already got me. All right. Those little cows are
so cute. It would be a shame if they got lost and hurt themselves. Yeah. All right. Again, 100 GP.
Please accept this reward as a token of my gratitude. You got a key.
Well, you're welcome. All right. What about you? What does a poor peasant like me do without his
farm and his land? Donate 350. All right. I need to get GP. Time to unbox. Without a watermill,
we can't produce flour. People are starving. Look, I can only do one thing at a time here. All
right. How do I leave? Do I just leave? Oh, shit. All right. Clover village. Oh, all right. Let's
do it. This is it. This is where we get money. I don't have any fire left. All right. Hold on.
What am I doing? Okay. My brain is freaking out. It's just mouse. It's just the mouse.
I'm doing like WASD. You can move it with WASD. Okay. I got fireballs now. Can I break them?
You can break them with the fireball. Holy shit. All right. This is overwhelming me. This is fun.
I actually like this. Yep. All right. It's on hard. Fuck. It's on hard. All right. All right.
It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. Continue. Continue. I only have three continues. What?
Not rich is rich. Oh, okay. Hold on. Hold on. Re, um, reach. Do I only have three continues ever?
All right. Don't mess with me. Oh my God. Why am I so, I'm like, I'm so overexcited and shit.
Like, what's wrong with me? I'm freaking out. All right. I got the bad guy. Am I getting, am I
getting GP? Holy fuck. That was close. I can break the last two over here. It's got, the ball moves
really fast. Got it. All right. Oops. So red rupees 10 GP. Cool. That's level one. All right.
I got to get it up in the top. So it bounces on top of everything. Here we go. Ready?
First try. Get it. Thank you. And I can't shoot these. So I have to, it has to go up there.
What is K? Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. What did I just do? All right. Well, K does what? Oh, it's wind.
It's the right amount. I'm not sure what it does. I just fucking blew that. All right. Let's go.
Alter? So you can blow it the other direction?
Huh. I see. All right. Well, that was easy. Push me towards the paddle. Is that what's going on?
Remember this shit's on heart. Let's go. Where should I go? I'm going to try to go. I'm going to
try to get stuck in the top right. Fucked it up. Sorry. Open the crates. Stay on that right. Stay
on the left side. Yeah. When did this game come out? Why did I not know this game existed?
Came out in 1980? No, it's not. It's got great sounds too. I have enough to do with the lumber
mill, whatever it is. Maybe I'll do that. Get on there. The farmer? Yeah. Yeah. We'll, we'll pick
one. 2011 was almost 10 years ago. I know it's ridiculous. I'm making a lot of money though.
Jeremy, this is a fun mini game. Can you please go back to solving the main mystery in Nancy Drew?
Nah. Nah, I'm good for now. I only have two more continues though. I'm kind of concerned about
that. Did I blow the whole thing? Do I only get three continues the whole game? I wasted all my
ammo. Can I sneak it up the side? Yep. Oh, this is, this is nice. I like this. This is relaxing to me.
Shit. I missed the coin. Whoa. What just happened? I was like, it's like pinball.
All right. Pop it. Pop it off. Do I have any time or is it just whenever I fall?
Oh, this is cool. There's like 20 plus hours of Nancy Drew on YouTube now.
What do you mean? 20 plus hours? You're talking about from this channel? I mean, yeah.
We played three of the games and beaten two of them. I have to be careful though because
if you, there are some Twitch metrics that you can look at and you can see, you can analyze your
stream. You can analyze data and all this shit, right? Once you, I don't want to cross the
threshold where Nancy Drew is in like the top five of most time on stream. I have to be careful with
that because oh, Nancy Drew, 20 hours. Nancy Drew is like Nancy Drew, 40 hours. Nancy Drew is like
180 hours of Nancy Drew that trumps every single game I've ever played. Oh shit. I can press the
button and go in. I didn't know that. I'm going to use the fireball here. Right in front. Get in
there. Give me the bonus. Bonus. Give it to me. No. No. Get in there. Does it close? Get in. Get in.
Get in. No. Yes. What is this for? 75. Is this a magnet? Let's the orbs stick to the magic one
when they collide. Oh, that's pretty good. For 75 though. I don't know about that.
This is just another live. I think I'm going to get replenish his magic. I'm going to get this.
Yeah, that feels, look at my bar. All right. Cool. All right. I'm going to save the rest.
What is this? I don't get it. What did I just do? Is that a curse? Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. What? What's
wrong? Are there bosses in this game? Yeah. He doesn't know. What happened? Oh, I had 666 coins.
Now I see your concern. It's okay. I'm fine. I feel like I don't want to touch that.
There are other spells available when the ball hits the paddle. Really? Oh shit. There is. What
is the, what does K do? Get in there. Get stuck up there. Come on. Get stuck up there. Get in the
middle and bounce around all over the place. Oh shit. There is. Oh, it turns into fire.
I don't have enough to do it. What is, what's, I don't understand. That's all my magic is gone.
I don't know what that did for the chest though. Get up close. Fairy lets you control the ball. Oh,
very cool. Streamer plays mobile game for 6K viewers. This game ain't even, this
ain't even on mobile. What are you on about? You can't even get this on mobile.
You should be able to. I feel like it would be hard on mobile. You have to have your finger
on the screen just drag back and forth like crazy. I mean, maybe it would not be hard.
A lot of money. That was awesome. How is that hard? It just, it is. Your finger gets like
greasy and shit and you can't register. By the way, I think this game is like $2. I'm not kidding.
This game is like $2 or $3. Tops. No, I can still save it. Just get up there. Get in there. Come on.
I can still do it. Yes. No. Get up there. Don't break this. Whatever. It's over. Okay. That's
amazing. I just was shocked. That's awesome. It goes through everything. The save up for that one
is literally $3. Yeah. This game is $3. I think I'm playing pretty well. Ooh, that was close.
All right. I'm just going to get it. Kill the two bears. There it is. What's left? What is left?
Oh, the top left corner. Shit. All right. Let me just box top left. I got it. $4. Wow. This game
must be bad. $4 must be awful then. No, if a game, it might be fun. No, I want to. Ooh,
not worth it. I'll buy this. Saving. You're a real stinker. What do you mean?
I want the magnet. Well, I want to fix the town up first. I don't want to just go straight for the
magnet. I think that's using keys. What about the left door? Get in that left door. All right. I
got to feed it up there. Very gently. Damn it. Jesus. Get up there. Yes. What about the button?
I didn't get the button. I feel completely unsatisfied. Oh, I feel terrible right now.
All right. Watch this. Jesus. Give me it. Yeah, that's pretty damn good. I don't want to get...
What? Teleport spell? I didn't want to get grabbed. I still don't know what the grab does.
You're cheating. You lose money. Oh, that's terrible. How much do you lose? I feel like
my paddle is smaller. Or am I making that up? Oh my god. I'm not making this up.
Sorry, I got plenty of lives. You've always had a small paddle. I don't even know what you're
referring to. Keep going. No, no. Turn, turn. Yes. We can just watch the movie play out.
Here it is. I don't even have to do shit. Telekinesis achievement. I want to see another
scare Saturday. Well, a scary game that I want to play has got to come out. This one's odd. Although
I can go straight up. Do I have a key? I've got two keys. Oops. Get in. The same magnet. I feel like
I'm trying to get it. I mean, it's just going to be here every time. I'm getting it. And I'm getting
the heart. No, I'm not. Yeah. Fuck it. I'll give you the magic. Yeah. All right. I'm up. Should I
get the heart too? All right. I got plenty of money. Wait, what? Adds one life. Oh, I can buy
this as many times as I want. All right. I'm doing five and I'm up. Watch it. I'm going to sneak it
through right there. Does it keep the same trajectory? No, you can actually move it.
That's great. Maybe it does. It's not cheating. It's an item in the game. So I got to use
so much magic. I couldn't get them both. You know, I couldn't. Am I in easy mode? Well,
this is level one. I have to assume it gets harder after this. Sure it does. Kappa. I actually
don't like it. I'm trying to figure out how the trajectory works. So I think it just keeps
following. No, it doesn't. I thought it kept following the path. It's based on where it is
on the paddle. That makes sense. So I want to get it on the left side. Like this. And then,
yeah. All right. I feel you. I feel you. Come on. Get over there. Nice. VIP this person? VIP who?
Somebody here? I'm falling asleep here. That's all right. We're just chilling.
We're just chilling right now. I'm relaxing. I'm just fucking chilling.
Just lying back. Yeah, this is like pretty nice actually. This is pretty nice to me.
Honestly, all I need right now is just a large pizza. I just want a large pizza.
After every level, I take just a huge bite of like this crispy pepperoni pizza. You know what I mean?
I love pizza. I know. Every time somebody, when you ask anyone what their favorite food is
from the second to the eighth grade, pizza. But I love pizza. That's seriously the best. One of
my favorite things on earth. I would probably still have like the fourth grade answer. French
fries? No. Pizza. Pipo happy. Pizza. It's so good though. It really is. I could probably eat pizza
every single day. You know, I could. That sounds bad. I'm just saying. I'm not going to do it,
but I probably could. I'm actually pretty easy to please when it comes to food.
I really am. There are people that would say like, man, I mean, I've eaten pizza like four times
this week. Fuck that. I want something else. And I'm the guy that's like, yeah, fuck that.
I would eat it again though. If you like wanted to get it, I would eat it. I would eat it every day.
I'm pretty easy to please. Yeah, fuck that. I've had pizza like three times this week.
Fuck. But I mean, like what else is open? I mean, it's like, we could go to like McDonald's,
but that's like, I mean, what else is open? And we don't have fucking options besides maybe like
pizza. And that's true though. It actually is. But Uber Eats is a thing now. Oh, hold on. We've got
a boss battle. Do I have a health bar? How does this work? Holy shit. All right. All right. I got
to get like the... I'm wasting these shots. No, we are. All right. Giant wolf. Watch it. Yeah,
there aren't many, there really aren't that many foods I could eat every day. But pizza. Uh oh.
Very small. Tiny. First boss. Seven lives too. All right. Am I going back to town?
There's another slime fort. No, let's go back to town. Kingdom of Gerudo. All right. Who do we,
who do we give money to? I have 1400. I love my tavern. I'll be ruined. I'll miss all the
gossip going around. Donate. Yeah, let's get the tavern going. You just saved my business. Please
accept this reward. You got an extra life. All right. Well, we're going to get a tavern.
What is this? An enormous flying eye struck my house with a lightning bolt and burnt it to the
ground. Yeah. All right. Let's get your house built. Got a key. Woof woof. Donate to the dog?
Barf. You got a key. Let's open up the shop. I need a nice shop. What should I do? All right.
I gotta do the shop. Yeah. 750. Shop will be open after I do one more. All right. I got three keys,
eight lives. Let's go to the next area. Slime forest. Level two, one. Wait, do I keep everything
from lab? Oh, I do. I keep everything. I still have the magnet. That's pretty awesome. I gotta
get in the corner. Get up there. Dammit. Dammit. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Magnet run. Magnet run. Why can't I go in there? Is there a button somewhere missing?
Get it. I almost have 10 health. Oh, there's one problem I'm seeing with the magnet. I can't do the
fireball. I don't think the fireball is possible to do because it gets stuck. How do I get in that
door? Drop the magnet or I'm going to bed. Relax. What? This is just a slime room.
Holy fuck. That was okay. I had to use it. Wait, what's my what happened? My paddle's back to normal.
I don't have the magnet anymore. I draw. Okay. You're staying up then. You're not going to bed
anymore. You lose whatever you get when you. Oh, that sucks. Okay. Well, good to know. Holy shit,
dude. Germ is a god at breakout. I appreciate that. Thank you. What's going on? Oh, I think I just got
luigi'd. If it becomes impossible, it just gives it to you. That's pretty cool. I'm going to sneeze
though, just to make everyone aware. I do actually like breakout. It's fun. I don't know what that
does, but I don't want those bad apparently somehow. Germa, how do you I don't even know
what that is. I'm not going to answer it. What do these slimes do? I'm terrified to touch them.
Germa, quick. Give me your opinion on this thing. You don't know what it is.
Oh, all right. He knows. He doesn't. He doesn't actually know. I don't know what you're doing.
Guys, I didn't know what uh-oh stinky was. Why would I know what anything else is? And yes,
I've seen the video. I've seen it. How do you know what ayayaya is? Well, that's easy because
you know how many times I've seen that link put in chats on Twitch?
You know how many times I've been linked that video randomly by people? You know how many times
I've seen that random thing pop up? I've seen those words pop up a hundred times.
Apologize. I already did. I said I was sorry like five times.
How many times do I have to apologize? Do I have to apologize every day?
Hey everybody. Welcome to another stream. This is stream number 15 since the ayaya incident.
Just want to make sure I make this really well aware. I'm really sorry about that.
I'm incredibly sorry. I'm embarrassed about it. Ooh, huge paddle. All right, that's good. Is this
even any bigger? It doesn't even look that bad. Much bigger. Yeah, I have to apologize every day
for saying the... doing the ayayaya thing. I have to say sorry every day. All right, I don't die
because you'll lose your power-ups. I have to shoot them. God damn it. Come on. And I didn't
even need to do that. Ugh. You have to apologize to God. Apologize on Twitter. I already did my
apology. I already said I was sorry. I don't have to... what? I'm not apologizing on Twitter.
That would break my... uh-oh. Get it off. Oh! Now that would break my rule of having
like five tweets a year that aren't going live tweets. Get in that cave. It's gonna be a bonus
for my Jess. Know it. You have five new tweets? No, I don't. What are you spamming here? Attention
parents and grandparents. Herbal life. Hold on. You're gonna make me pause the game for this.
Get in the cave. Fall in cave. Fall in cave. Attention parents. I don't even know what it is.
Look at all this money. This is crazy. Oh, I got them all so far. Come on. Keep it going.
Get them all. Yep. I'm gonna get them all. Funny memes. Have you ever listened to penis music
before? You just replaced a noun with the word penis. That's all you did. I mean, come on. You
gotta get a little more effort than that. It's gotta be some more effort than that.
You guys critique my jokes sometimes. It's time to critique yours.
Just kidding. I'm not gonna hit that one ever. I got nine lives. I'm gonna be doing just fine.
You cry laughing at fart noises. So did you. Don't throw stones if you live in a glass house.
Some of you... I can pretend that you didn't, but you know. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Where'd it go?
Wait, is Pac-Maning? It's Pac-Maning. Holy shit. It is Pac-Maning. I don't know. This is perfect.
I don't have to do anything. I'm gonna shoot this one. Didn't even need... All right. No, no, no,
no. Get that chest. Yes. Yes. Did a raid just come in? Or am I crazy? Why is it not listed here?
Was there a raid? It's not on my... Why is it not on my streamlabs? It's... I mean, it says that...
Who came in with the raid? It was a while ago? When was it? Hold on. Where? No, it wasn't. No,
this just happened like right now. Why is this... I swear to god, I just saw that a raid came in.
From... from... from GMART? Am I making this up? I swear to god. I'm... I have to be insane. I swear
to god, I looked over and I saw it. Thank you for fucking raiding. Seriously. Thanks for the raid.
I swear to god this happened. I'm not crazy. No, somebody look up... Is somebody like... Is
somebody hosting this channel right now called like called like GMART or something? It was like
600 people. I swear to god. I'm not... I'm not insane. Thank you so much for the raid. Seriously.
No, yeah. Thanks a lot. Seriously. Whatever you were doing, hopefully you had a good time.
We're playing. We are playing. I just lost my paddle. Fuck. Uh, we're playing this breakout
game. It's only three dollars on Steam. You can do shit like that. Pretty damn cool. Uh, welcome
though. Welcome. Get it. Sponsored. Sponsored by a three dollar game. What are you talking about?
This was made with passion and love. And they're charging almost nothing for it. Gah! I thought
I was gonna bounce higher. All right, I'm... I can't... I can't get cocky. That was pretty pog
champ right there, I'll tell you. That was pog. Yeah, like I said again, welcome.
That... I'm saying... I'm saying your name right? GMART, right? GMART. You're so bad at this.
But I'm hard. What are you talking about? So why did that not show up in my streamlabs? I saw it
like blow by the chat. That's a lot of free... that... that's two free lives. I wonder how many
levels are in the game. Holy fuck. Another door. Another key. What is this? The orb starts at speed
twice slower. Yeah, let's get it. And here's world magic too. Holy shit. Wait. Oh, I didn't
want to do that. Yeah, that's too slow. I just increased the time I'm gonna play the game by
50% or 100%. That's all I did. More time on stream. Yeah, I don't like this. I want it to be faster.
No, I didn't want to do that either. Fuck. I'm gonna... all right, I'm gonna let it fall. I'm gonna
let it fall. I'm gonna let it fall. Just fall. I don't want this anymore. I still have it, don't I?
Do I still have it? I get... no, I don't. I feel like this is slower. I know. I'm trying to get it. I
can't get it. It's too... it's a weird spot. The reaction times have ascended here. Yeah, just throw
coins in the trash. You're right. Unfortunate. Unfortunate. Damn it! I tried. I tried to get this
sneaking in there. Oh, it would have been awesome too. You know, it would have been so cool.
Oh well. I would have eaten everything. How many of you guys got a pizza? Seriously, how many?
At least like three of you? Actually you? Good. Explain how it tastes to me. How is it? Like,
what is it? Is it crunchy? Is it doughy? Is it deep? Explain it to me in full detail. Is the sauce
tangy? Is the sauce... is it like thin sauce? Is it soupy? You know, don't ever think that a soup pizza
is bad. All right. If you don't get it, me and Burger Boy used to call them soup pizzas because
when you got a fresh hot pizza that was so hot that just came out of the oven, where the cheese,
the sauce, and the oil all mixed together into this moving lava and you pick up a piece of pizza
and it's just... the whole thing is liquid. That's a soup pizza. And don't... don't think that a
soup pizza is not good. It can be very good. Sometimes it's like, all right, this sucks,
but it's a soup pizza. It's pretty good. You'll pick up a slice and it all just starts... it's
all liquid, all really, really thin, and you have to fold it together and like keep... you can't
happen to do this shit. Hold on. Pause it. You keep having to do this shit. Can you guys even see me?
You have to... you keep having to do this, right? So you have to keep going like...
like fold, fold, fold, fold, fold, fold, fold over and over again with the cheese. He's handsome?
Yes, I am. You'll go in for a bite and everything will start to fall and you put your hand under
here and your hand's like accepting hot lava and you like fold it back up on top of the pizza
and like... and you keep folding it on top of each other and eating it and eventually you like churn
it like butter. That's sometimes... it sucks, but sometimes it's okay. Sometimes it's actually
exactly what you're looking for. Worst noise of 2020. Well, I will make sure you clip it because
you'll make sure you remember where it is. Dammit, it's not gonna hit it, is it? Yes, it is.
Do you own more than three shirts? Yes, I do. These are comfortable. You have no idea how
comfortable this... this Nightwing shirt is. You have no idea. It's ridiculous. It is the most soft,
wonderful material and it's washed. I wear it a couple times and you wash it. It's the most
comfortable... it's one of the most comfortable things I own. Plus, I like to fucking like pretend
I'm Nightwing. Not even... not as cool as Batman and I used to be Robin, remember me? But I got two
fucking batons now. Cool... it's cooler than Robin and like definitely like... definitely like sexier
than Batman. You know what I mean? Nightwing. Bruce Wayne ain't got nothing on me, okay?
What's it... what's it... Drew Carey? What's his name? Not Drew Carey. Who is Nightwing?
Who is Nightwing? Not Bruce Wayne. I'm talking about Nightwing.
Yeah, Drew Carey. Good, good. Drew Carey can be Nightwing if you want.
Did you see how fucking pogchamp that just was? That was the most pog...
put... nominate that shit. Watch this. Ready? What is that? Oh my goodness.
Fuck. It's okay. Yeah, Batman's old news. God damn it. I didn't move my hand fast enough.
Dude, he's begging for nominations. Eye roll. Uh, me and Joel are gonna play the bomb game. Yes,
we were supposed to play it today, but uh he kind of last second got uh ill. I think he was
feeling under the weather. So instead of it being... all right let's... we want... we want
Joel to be in, you know, peak health while we do that. So he wasn't feeling well. So I just was
like, you know what, fine, it's all good. I'll just do something else today and we'll do it tomorrow.
Obviously, uh, if Joel's feeling all right. Otherwise we'll do something else. There we go,
get in there. Should I do the bigger paddle? Yeah. And... no, that's fine. Joel's streaking
the bomb game right now. Now that would have actually been pretty hilarious. Um, can you
imagine if... hey, sorry, um, no, we're not doing it... and then just streaking it with somebody else.
You'd be like, oh shit. No, I can assure you that is not the case. I don't like these ice blocks.
Don't do it. Neither does... whoa! Whoa! I don't like ice blocks. Oh! And neither does...
oh! Anybody that played WoW PvP back in 2005. Fuck! I tried to stop it. I'm sorry. I fucking
couldn't stop. I couldn't stop it. I couldn't stop it. I had to say... I had... I couldn't stop.
I tried to stop. Don't worry, I'll apologize for the next, like, five days straight. Don't worry.
You're a psycho. Who said that? Okay, no. I love this game. This game's actually fun.
Uh, this is just a fun game just to sit here and just dick around. Come on, get back in there.
Is there a button I can press? But no, long story short, yeah, we'll do, uh,
keep talking and nobody explodes tomorrow. We're very prepared for it.
Like I said earlier, I think a lot of people really are underestimating just how much we're
going to be prepared for these streams. Or these stream, whatever it is. I'm going to take it dead
serious. Even if he does not take it seriously, I'm going to take it as dead serious as humanly
possible. I'm going to try as hard as I can. I'm going to be very clear with my instructions.
I'm not gonna, whoa, what if I say this and like fuck it up?
Laugh. Laugh. Uh, nope, not gonna happen. Oh dude, I'm gonna say cut like the blue wire and he's
gonna cut it. He's gonna explode and it's gonna be, nope, I'm gonna be trying as hard as I fucking can.
Whoa, he actually, he can get attacked? I'm so excited for the explode joke next stream.
That's not gonna happen. I mean, maybe, we're probably gonna lose. It's a very complicated
game. Is it dead? Jelly? What did I just get? Keep pogging and nobody explodes. Should I go back?
Yeah, let's go back and see what the town looks like now. Oh, look at this. I can go in the houses.
Oh, it's the, it's the tavern. This is cool. I guess this has opened up me. Heard that everywhere,
else in Gerudo, people turned into ghosts and vanished. Isn't that creepy? Do you sell stuff?
Can I play piano? I don't think so. Oh, a chest. Uh, I'm not sure I can do anything with this yet.
Dog? Oh, I can't take their, okay. I would have never believed that such a hideous creatures existed
if I hadn't seen them with my own eyes. She's talking about you? Can I go to the dog house?
I want to do it too. All right, I did the shop. Let's go to the shop. I already own all this stuff.
I'm out. Slow. All right. Uh, farmer? The windmill. Watermill. People are starving. 350. Yes. Thank
you. You got an extra life. Good. Uh, can I repair this or provide the entire town with milk? All
right, let's fix the farm. 350. Except this, you got an extra life. Cool. Anything else need to be
fixed? Couple houses up here. What is this for? The mayor carries more for his citizens than for
himself. I'd rebuild this house if I had the funds. 999. All right, well, I don't have that.
All right, well, let's just build this house back up then. Omega low link. I had to like double take
for a second here. Bomb game. Don't tell the German. Don't tell him. Don't tell him. Imagine
this is real. Imagine if it was real. Now that would be ridiculous. All right, this is terrible.
These monsters took away everything. Here. 250. I got a key. What about you? Do what you need.
How could those monsters destroy a statue? Boo hoo. Donate 500 for the statue. I don't have it.
All right, let's go. This buddy gave me these meatballs. One pound spaghetti ground beef.
Bread and crumbs. Finally chopped parsley. Freshly grated parmesan plus more for serving.
One egg. Two garlic cloves. That sounds gross. I'm making meatballs. They're wrong.
I mean, well, I mean. What does that thing in the middle mean? Stay up there. Get up top. Oh,
my fucking hand slipped. It's all right. I don't have any powerups anyways. Greed? Well, yeah,
I need that money to rebuild the whole town. Should have saved it. That was dumb. All right,
top five favorite superheroes or super villains. They can both be on the same list. Who are they?
That's a good question. Let's find out. Bator? That's not a superhero. That's just,
that's a word that I've said a few times. All right, I'm gonna go. I'm gonna go.
Hmm. Shit, this is tough. Who's, what's the, who's the best, coolest? It's too bad because I would
have said, I would say Deadpool. But Deadpool has been like meme-ified now. You know what I'm saying?
It's very hipster of me to say that. Deadpool is like too popular for me to say that now.
So many people were just like, what the fuck? Fuck you, man. Uh, no, all right, it's probably
Deadpool. Spider-Man, Deadpool. Lame. Stop! I'm trying to have conflicting, backtracking opinions.
Stop. Stop, stop it. Don't you understand? I'm, I'm saying something, engaging what everybody
says and then I'm just gonna go with what you are all saying and backtrack. I'm gonna make a
statement and then immediately tell you otherwise and see what you guys say and then I'm gonna,
that's what my opinion is gonna be? This guy's fucking smart. No, uh, for real though, no jokes,
no bullshit. It's probably Spider-Man. Spider-Man. Uh, it's Spider-Man. It's definitely Spider-Man.
It's Spider-Man. What's cooler than Spider-Man? Nothing's cooler than Spider-Man.
It's not Captain America. I'm sorry, I'm gonna have to put my foot down there. It's not Captain
America. It's Spider-Man. Spider-Man. Venom. Aquaman. No, no, I don't think so. Not for me.
Although he makes great t-shirts, but not for a superhero. Um, some of the X-Men too. The problem
with the X-Men is the X-Men were so cool and then they made like the last two or three movies were
just real bad. So it's kind of, they gotta get the X-Men in somebody else's hands. The actors were
fine for the X-Men, I think. Um, when I was younger it was Gambit. What is this? The Magic
Wand launches three at once. Oh, fuck yeah. Gambit was my favorite superhero when I was like 14, 15,
16. It might still be. They even put Gambit anywhere, really. Besides the cartoon. Okay,
this is, I gotta have to show you guys some skill here. Do I get three balls at once forever?
Yeah, I do. All right, I gotta be really, really good here. Bat fucked it up. Sorry. What does Bat
even do? Is it taking my health? Wait, is it taking my health? It drains your magic. Ah, that sucks.
I'm so happy you get this for every level though. This is great. Not much I could do
there. Oh, fuck, that instantly kills you. I mean, yeah, the Avengers are cool. They're,
they're all right. They're interesting. Although, is it weird that I really only like those movies
because Spider-Man's in them? Even though they're good. I love that latest Spider-Man. That Spider-Man
movies are great. I love them. All of them. They're all so good. Me hate popular thing. Me interesting.
Spider-Man is insanely popular. He's like the most popular superhero ever.
It's, it's, it's, it's the Deadpool thing that I said, isn't it? People are gonna be mad at me now.
I love, I like Deadpool. I was just fucking, I was just joshing everybody. Super villain though.
Spider-Man superhero. What's the best villain? Freeze? That's not a bad pick. That's not a bad
pick. I don't know. Who else though? I like the Riddler. The Riddler's cool because the Riddler
doesn't even have any superpowers. He's just a dick. Like the Riddler doesn't have superpowers.
He's, he's just like, he's just like a really good lawyer. All right. Get the balls again.
He was super intelligent. Yeah, but that's all right. I mean, yeah, that's fine. But
Riddler sucks. Just tells shitty puns. I, I was kind of sad when in the Christopher Nolan series,
it was Bane. I really thought it was going to be the Riddler and we were going to get a Christopher
Nolan Riddler and that would have been, that would have been awesome. Can you imagine a
Christopher Nolan Riddler? Oh, I missed it. I have to keep him alive. Weren't they in talks to maybe
do a Riddler? Long time ago. Why do I feel like it was going to be Johnny Depp? Why have I like
heard that somewhere? Am I insane? Jim Carrey? Yeah, but the only Riddler we ever got on TV was
or in the movies was the guy from the sixties and Jim Carrey. And although I love Jim Carrey's
Riddler, it was more the Joker than it was the Riddler, but he still, it was good.
Get stuck in there. How did you even get out? The Arkham Riddler was the best one.
Yeah, that's pretty good. It was. We haven't got a TV or movie Riddler besides. I mean,
the one from Gotham. I haven't really watched Gotham though. Is that a good show?
Why am I not paying attention? I'm seeing a lot of conflicting opinions here. Of course not.
Wasn't the penguin good on that show though? I heard that was the reason to watch the show
because the penguin was really good. Oh, the wind. Yeah, I'm an idiot. Yeah. All right. If we
already got a really good penguin locked down, then we got to get him in a movie. Danny DeVito
was the best penguin. I mean, that's, that's not even up for debate though. Yeah, that's
But Danny DeVito, I don't know. How old is Danny DeVito now?
That movie is so awful, even though DeVito is great. Yeah.
I don't remember much of that movie, but I, no, I can't say that. Michael Keaton,
Michael Keaton's in that movie. It's automatically a good movie. If you guys
didn't know, Michael Keaton's like my favorite actor. All right, I gotta hold on. These things
launching around. Have I seen Birdman? Yes, I have. It was fantastic. He was great as
Batman. He was great in Birdman. He was great in Spider-Man. All the other, all the man movies.
He was great in Beetlejuice. God. Fuck. It's one of those scenarios where anytime there's a
Beetlejuice ever again, it's just going to be, uh, you're not Michael Keaton. I don't like this
movie. You're not Michael Keaton. No, like we can't, it's not going to work. And it is that it's not,
it's impossible. It has to be Michael Keaton. It can't be anybody else. It can't be. What is this
one? The above deals double damage until it's lost. Um, okay. I gotta read. Wait, does that mean I
got double damage and the three balls? Yeah. Michael Keaton is great. Well, so what other actors
do I really like? What's my superhero, uh, actor list? I think Michael Keaton, Tom Holland. Yeah,
but we'll, we'll see though. Tom Holland is awesome. Got a long career ahead of him. Ask
me in 15 years. Willem Dafoe, Jim Carrey. Yeah. Oh, Woody Harrelson. Yeah. Woody Harrelson's pretty
good too. I was trying to sneak it in. It's all right. Cape Lanchette is awesome and almost
everything. Who else? Ooh, Ryan Gosling. Yeah, he's done, he's done some good work. He's done some
good work. You're right. Die. Sorry. Fuck. I needed that. No, I didn't. Uh, you know who actually
tops that list besides Michael Keaton, uh, is probably Gene Wilder. Gene Wilder was
awesome in everything, in everything. The original Willy Wonka. Yeah. And way more on an
incredibly storied career. He was just so interesting. He was so funny and fun and
everything he said was just, you carried weight. It was, it was, it was amazing.
Gene Wilder influenced a lot of people that you watch now, including me. So you're here now.
Oh, fuck. Don't touch anything. God damn it. Why am I so stupid about that? I got to be
on my way. I want to know what this means. Somebody said, I feel like I'm at a family
get together. And then they said residence sleeper. Is it, wait, you mean this is as
boring as being at a family get together? What? Get, well, go get fucking Yahtzee or Uno. What
are you doing? Why is that my fault? Go open up Monopoly and play six rounds and then everybody
has to leave. Speaking of Monopoly, do you guys, like we should play Monopoly. Do I have Uno?
I don't even, I don't remember how to play Uno, if I'm honest with you. I really don't know.
You're supposed to be the entertainer. Yeah, but I got, I got, I got, I got that by, yeah,
but I'm like stuck here. I'm like in traffic right now. I'm in really relaxing traffic
and I'm, I'm all right. You have Uno. What do you mean I have? How do you know I have Uno?
How do you know that? You have Uno. You have the box. I don't, it came with your Xbox.
It comes with your Xbox. I bought this Xbox third party guys. I don't have Uno.
The? What is this? You have, I don't have Uno. Why is me saying I don't have Uno as strange as me
saying when I turn the faucet, no water comes out. What are you talking about? You fucking turn your
faucet. What are you, what? Like, no, it's not as, what are you talking about? He doesn't have
water in his house. It's a meme. Oh, I'm getting memed on. Okay. Well, sometimes it's hard to tell.
It's hard to tell. Everyone's saying it at the same time. I can't even hit that one.
This is the end. I gotta play that too. I gotta play No More Heroes 2. I can play Rhythm, uh,
Rhythm Heaven. I'm gonna be doing both beautiful Joes. We're fully, we're fully packed. All right,
boss battle. I gotta play God Hand. That's right. I got Tony Hawk's Underground. What else we got?
I got a whole list, guys. Shit. All right. Don't be an idiot. Uh, what else we got off hand?
Oh, the Surge 2. Yeah, the Surge 2. But I'm probably only gonna, I'm probably only gonna
play that for like two hours. All the Lord of the Rings PlayStation 2 games. All of them. Um,
holy shit, am I about to beat the game? Why are we here then? Because this is, uh, come on,
this is, this is unplanned scream. I have plans for everything else. All right, let's put a statue
up. Did I do, did I rebuild everything already? Wait, what about this house? You literally won't
get past the first part of Fellowship, I guarantee it. All right, I wouldn't, all right, I'm gonna
remember your name because when I get past level one in Fellowship of the Ring, I'm going to fucking
scream your name. What was your name? It's fake what? I'm gonna write that name down. I'm gonna
literally yell your name. I'm gonna yell your name when I get, when I'm done. Fake up. All right,
fake, fake rumble. You got it. All right. Yeah. I'm, when I am done with that, I'm screaming your
name. And I'm gonna turn the gain on my mic as high as it'll go. Oh, look at the farm. Oh,
this is cute. At least my daughter now has a decent place to live. We're at the end. This is
the last level, I think. This, look at this cute little game. This is, wow. Seriously. Wow.
Ooh, can I do anything here? King of Gerudo is valiant. People never starved under his reign.
He disappears and makes everyone sad. Cool. Jump in there and get crushed. But I'm the psycho.
All right, let's rebuild the house. 9.99. Do it. You have a heart of gold. Please accept this reward.
You got an extra life. It's the mayor's house. I have enough money. What about you? I haven't
talked to you the whole thing. I've heard that you can cast special magic spells if you press
a magic button when the orb hits the magic wand. Yes, I can. All right, let's get it.
The cursed castle. Here we go. Yeah, I got all the Lord of the Rings games.
What else we got? We got all that shit too. Oh, I was gonna bring this up because,
uh, not what a dodge. Um, I was talking about cleaning games and this is like, you know,
maybe three or four days ago when I last streamed before New Year's. And it was like, oh, you,
you would love Chibi-Robo. I'm like, all right, Chibi-Robo. Let's get it. That sounds like fun.
This fucking game is $200. Is this like some extremely rare video game? It's like 200 fucking
bucks. Somebody just said, I have it. Um, well, you might be able to make like at least 180 dollars.
Time to sell it. Yeah. Yeah. All, yeah. All of you sell it. All of you sell it. Flood the market.
Flood the market. So it comes down to like fucking 80 bucks. So all of you sell. So all of you sell.
All of you sell it. Somebody said they have two copies. Holy shit. You lose a life and it bounces
back up. This could get really bad. I just lost two lives in a row. Have I thought I'm playing
control? Yeah, but control sits kind of in that weird spot. Kind of a Jedi fallen order is.
It's something I want to do and want to play, but I, I just, I'm probably not gonna. And why is
this happening? Maybe I, it's on, it's on the list. It is, but it would have to, it's kind of, okay.
Just like Breath of the Wild. I still, I might play Breath of the Wild. I mean, I got, look,
I have to come clean with you guys. I have to be completely realistic. I did put on the list of
games, the ones that I've bought. Mario and Sonic at the Olympic Games 2020. So how could I,
could I really play that without playing Breath of the Wild? I feel like that would be upsetting
to a lot of people. You're not going to get the lore of Breath of the Wild? Why not? But yeah,
also another game that I really, really want to play desperately. And this game is also
$250 for the GameCube. It's called Gotcha Force. Anybody remember that one? Game was
ridiculous. It was so much fun. Mario Sunshine is also on that list. What the fuck is this?
10,000 for the crown? Jesus. I'm, I'm not getting the crown. It's not going to happen.
I, I got distracted. So when you have this shit out, I feel the same way about multi-ball and
pinball. And so it's like, you need to have two eyes go in two different directions. Omega lol
bits. Wait, what? Hold on. Bilater just gave $250 in bits. 25,000 bits. Buy Gotcha Force,
you sweaty streamer fuck. I'm, uh, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna buy Gotcha Force. So I'm
going to buy it and I'm going to own it. And then I'm going to be the guy that owns Gotcha Force.
I'll be one of like five people on earth and then I will lock it away. It's going to be an
asset that I hold for the rest of my life. Uh, but if I like to, Jesus, that's insane amount of
money again. Let's be clear. Again. Thanks a lot, dude. Seriously. Buy it now, you fucking liar.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna buy it. Jesus. Damn it. He's going to use, he's going to use it on pizza
instead. I'm going to buy a $250 pizza. I'm going to get a special ordered 600 foot wide pizza.
Make it, make it, make it real soupy this time too. Make it real soupy.
Yeah, make, make, make, make me an old fashioned, old fashioned way. I can't, I can't see. I can't,
I can't, I can't see. He can't see. I can't see. Why am I quoting It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World?
What the fuck is going on? That's a movie from like the fucking fifties. Have I quoted it before?
I, I, wait, hold on. I've quoted It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World before. When? I do it all the time?
Do I actually do this? It's under the big W. It was Smiley Grogan and the great tuna factory robbery.
Yeah, I used to watch the movie all the time when I was younger. In fact, when I was younger,
we had that movie recorded on a blank VHS tape, but the movie is so long that we never got to
see as kids the end of the movie because it was like 90 minutes for a VHS tape or something,
60 minutes. And we would always get to the apex of the entire movie and we never got to see it
because we didn't have the second part recorded. So we just watched the first like hour and 12
minutes of whatever it was. My parents used to just describe, oh, and by the way, this is what
happens at the end and blah, blah, blah. Oh yeah, okay, that's funny. I'll give, I'll give you a
dollar. Um, three dollars, three dollars. I'm remembering the whole movie. Ray, we're gonna
have to kill him at the gas station where Jonathan Winters is like freaking the fuck out and like
beating the shit out of those two guys. Okay. Has that movie influenced more in my life than
I give it credit for? Probably. I don't know. I mean, that was one of like six VHS tapes that I
had. So when I was, I don't know, 12, 10, nine, 10, 11, 12, I probably watched the first hour
and 10 minutes of that movie 150 times. Listen to your father. He's holding the two phones up
and the mother is like yelling at the daughter. He's holding the, he's on two different phones
and he's talking to his daughter and his mother and he holds the phones up together
so they can talk to each other. I gotta watch this movie again. That movie's fucking crazy.
On stream. That movie's not public domain. No way it is.
Mama, I'm coming. Mama, I'm coming to save you. It's, it's all coming back to me. It really is.
Now that's what we call walking in there. I still, I can't afford that.
There's that one scene where the two, where the two guys are fighting outside in like the sand,
like the desert area and they do, they do the classic, I think they like came up with it maybe.
I don't know but they did, they both throw a punch at each other and they, they connect with
their fists in the air and they get hurt. It's like fucking funny. They throw a punch at the
exact same time and they fucking smash fists together. That's hilarious, boomer. Hey, some of
it, come on. It's, it's, it's a, it's a comedy movie. It seriously has some great stunts in it.
Yeah, it really was. It really was like, I don't remember. All right, we're gonna get in that right
side and then we don't. It's over. What movie? The movie's called It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World.
It's the actual title of the movie. It's public domain? No, it's not. It's public domain? Am I,
am I, wait, am I finally gonna get to see the end of this movie? Yeah, I still want to do that.
Watch public domain movies. In fact, I want to show you guys a skill called we're gonna watch
a bunch of public domain movies and we're gonna do what I do when I watch regular movies sometimes
on Netflix. And that's the, you'll get the gist of the entire movie. You watch for two minutes
and then you skip 20, watch for three minutes, skip 30 minutes, watch for five minutes, skip 10
minutes. Why would you do that? What do you mean why would I do that? I, some, guys, there are a
lot of movies that aren't very good and I just want to get the gist of them. You're a psycho,
what? And watch movies that are good. Yeah, but I sometimes, what's the last one I did it with?
I did it with Dad's Home 2? The one with John Cena and, no, yeah, the one with John, no. Will
Farrell? Will Farrell and, you've heard this before, yeah, it's the last, I'm telling you,
that's the last time I did it. Yeah, Mark Wahlberg, Will Farrell, yeah, I've seen that whole
movie. I just have to skip like 20 minutes every five minutes. You'd be surprised how many movies
you can watch and understand everything that's happening when you do this role. Can you just
get in there, please? Come here. Just read the Wikipedia. No, that's, that's way worse. Yeah,
at least I get to see some of the scenes in the movie and I only do this with movies that are
not good. Because I'm not going to do this with The Godfather. I think, like, the Sherlock Holmes
Will Farrell movie is not a movie I want to spend two fucking hours watching, so I'll watch it for
12 minutes. Plus, it means I can reference scenes so people think, you know, think I actually watched
the whole movie. I can reference specific quotes from the movie that I would, I, I wouldn't know
unless I saw it otherwise. So now at the office I can be like, remember that scene with the bees?
Hey, remember that scene in Dad and Daddy's Home 2 with the thermostat? They all freak out
and then they're like, who's changing the thermostat? And John Lithgow comes down,
it's like, it's not billions of degrees in here. See, it's not hard. All right, I, I don't want to
die here. This is like the last level. Clean it up. Clean it up. One, two. I could play Bubble
Bobble too. That's a classic game. And no, not, not Bust-A-Move. Not, ready, go! No, I'm talking
about the original Bubble Bobble. They really threw those two dragons on the bus, by the way.
Because like, where's, where's Bubble Bobble? Like, where's the other, where's the actual
Bubble Bobble game sequel? Bust-A-Move is better? That's, I don't think so. I don't think that's
correct. They took those two dragons and turned them into an iPad game. And have they even appeared
anywhere else ever? They were, they were really iconic characters. What happened to them? What
happened to those two dragons? They're public domain now. All right. But really, who owns those
characters? Are those Namco characters? No, Konami? Who owns the two dragons? Taiko? Taito? Okay.
What is, what has Taito done recently? Anything? Or did they get liquidated somewhere?
Nothing. They're under Square Enix now. Oh, okay. I'd love to see a new Bubble Bobble-inspired
video game with those two dragons. And I'm going to lose this game. Get in there. Finally. Get in
there. This was always the worst new plate breakout when you ended up with one that you needed to get
and it was just, you couldn't do it no matter what you did. Oh jeez. Square Enix owns it? No.
Now picturing the Bubble Bobble RPG. It'd probably be pretty fun. What are the characters that did,
because Taito was around right from the very beginning of the NES. They probably have a bunch
of characters. Are they, are they Snake, Rattle, and Roll? Is it Snake, Rattle, and Roll, they
Taito? Who owns Snake, Rattle, and Roll? Rare does? Why, what the hell are they doing? How have they
not done Snake, Rattle, and Roll too? I feel so bad for Rare because I really feel like they're
just like frozen in cryostasis. Like they have Rare frozen in cryostasis so Microsoft gets to
walk into the museum where they are and just look at them every once in a while and it'd be like
have a big cigar in their mouth being like, that's right, I remember, I remember Banjo-Kazooie.
Nobody else does. And then close the fucking door and lock it.
Spoilers for Star Wars, but who cares? Um, no, people, do people care about like the ones from
the 70s? Probably. Who gives a fuck? Oh no, that's right, that's not, it doesn't matter. I've already
talked about it on stream because I've already shown it on stream. You can't stop but now the
carbonite is gone. Yep, all right, that's true. How much money do you think that Raiden Solo makes
because that song exists? What do you think? It's probably a lot. Get in there. Wait, why is this
locked? Don't waste all your gold. Actually, I can, ready? This is gonna be a big moment for me.
No, it's not. I just like shook. I need more magic. I fucked it up. It's in Just Dance too.
Give me more magic. I could have done a huge line here. Do they still make Just Dance games? Yes,
yeah, they do. In fact, I think, I think they still release for the Wii. Original Wii, not Wii U.
It's accurate? Yep. Pepsi. The Wii is still going pretty strong from my understanding.
And the game cube. I love those little discs. Little game cube discs. Oh, they're so cool.
They're so cool. I can't wait to spend $500 on two discs. Door. Oh, door, door, door, yeah.
Come on, get in there. Don't. I can't. Ah, guys, it's hard to get in there.
Chibi-Robo. Look at this room. It's all treasure chests. Guys. Ooh, this is a fun game. This is a
cute little game. All right. Let me tell you. You can tell when a game is good. Guys, I've spilt
coffee on me that were more expensive than this. So come on. You. Time for the final boss. What
kind of coffee is that expensive? A, a Trenta iced Frappuccino with extra sugar, double milk,
double cream, 10 pumps of French vanilla. The drink is like $11. No, I don't owe to that.
Oh, what do I do? I do the thing. It's going fast. Things going fast. How big is the Trenta?
Anybody know? How many ounces? And how big is the super size that they like made it legal?
30 ounces. What's the super size? Super size is 80. Wait, a super size from McDonald's was 80
ounces? No. Holy shit. Wait, how many ounces is in a two liter? Was a super size as big as a two
liter? No magic allowed in the final boss. It's an instant kill. Only four lives left.
This could go to shit really quickly actually.
80 ounces is like three liters. I kind of want to look this up.
What's the, um, the biggest purchasable large drink? Big gulp from seven up.
Super size from McDonald's. Which one? What was it? Oh, fuck. There's another one. The nether world.
Wait, there's another one to build? Oh look, there it is. Is that me? There we go. All right,
this is the mayor's house. All right, so what do I talk to now? The four sacred children have the
power of summoning the forces of nature. They could help us if we could find them. I got them.
Have I ever heard of Fury? I've played Fury on stream. I think I got like halfway through it.
And then like a lot of games I've ever played on this channel years ago I sort of gave up on.
Yeah, I did. Like four years ago or something. Okay, this looks ridiculous.
We're in the nether. Go back? Go back to the map. I forgot about somebody?
There are only four lives left. Oh, my house is a real palace and now it's gone. Donate one
GP. Ha ha, gotcha. I've never had a house, but thanks. Today's a great day for Tarot.
Thanks to you this town will flourish once again. Again, once evil is vanquished. By the way,
we found this amulet piece in the debris. You got the fire amulet piece. What does that do?
All right, let's go. Oh, buy. I could buy. I'm even gonna buy stuff. I'm gonna buy hearts.
Oh, here we go. Here's the biggest big gulps. The original fountain drink from McDonald's was
seven ounces. All right, hold on. Let's see. Let's get this on stream. I want to look at this.
So, the biggest of big gulps. Kid-sized McDonald's in 2012 was 12 ounces.
Super-sized from McDonald's was 42 ounces. That's it? Great biggie from Wendy's,
the king size. They were all the same. The KFC mega jug? What is the KFC mega jug? The beast?
What is ARCO? I've never heard of ARCO. Like a gas station? The humongous come and go.
100. What the fuck? I feel like that's, is that a made up name? Is this real? No, it's a,
come and go is a convenience store. Okay. Well, why is it, why is it spelled like that? It's like,
kind of like humongous. Oh, okay. 100. Fuck it. The team gulp from 7-Eleven was 128 ounces.
What's the team gulp? This is just the thing that they dump on the coach
when people win the football game. Team gulp. Why would somebody order this? This is,
this is just a trash barrel with, you know, this is gross. This is just like a weird trash
barrel full of liquid. This is a gallon. Gross. Look at that thing. That's like the, that's the
thing that has fucking fertilizer in it in your garage. You don't want to drink out of that.
Propane tank? Yeah. Jesus. What is this? Is it a germ of gulp? This is, this is a coffee.
I hate this picture. No, I don't, I don't even want this on camera.
I don't want that on camera. That looks just, I don't like it. I do not like that picture.
I don't like it. I'm not leaving it. Oh wait, I was going to buy stuff here.
Let's refill all our magic. Let's get a bunch of health. Hey, one life. Oh, I'll do it to 10.
I think that's enough. 12. All right, I guess I need a thousand. Let's go. We want it back. We
want coffee mug back. No, it's just, I don't, that looks like a good cup of coffee though.
I love coffee. There's two things that are certain in life for me. That's pizza and coffee.
Both of them. Can I kill these things? Oh, they block. You fuckers.
Got him from behind. Oh shit. This is bad. Can you let us hear your BPM? Beats per minute,
like my heart. How would I even, how would you guys even be able to hear that?
Put the microphone off to my chest and mute everything and make everything really,
really quiet. I'm not even sure you still hear it. Get up there. Get up there. Try it. I feel
like a lot of people will leave if I do that. That's, I mean, I don't think people would want
to hear that. Can you imagine if I put my chest up here and it's like, like, holy fuck me. Jeremy,
go to the doctor. It's like, that's not normal. I got it in the mouth. Oh boy. Really could use
this right now. Damn it. I don't have any more. There it is. I don't want to die. This
reminds me of a cake. Yeah. It's kind of, it's kind of cakey. It's like a cake. Oh,
I forgot to show you guys. I got the, I got something cool. I got something cool.
Not like I forgot to show you guys. Oh yeah. I'll show you. This is tough. I don't want to lose
this. There's a lot of opportunity for me to lose and I don't want it right now. Not this. No, no.
Oh yes. This is a bonus room. I don't know. I'll show you after. Well, before I turn the stream
off, I'll show you. What level is this one? All right. I'm going to sneak it up underneath.
No, there we go. It's stuck. Get stuck. Get stuck. Get stuck. Get in there. Get stuck. Show us. I
got, you mentioned the cake thing. Oh, that instantly kills me. I just lost two lives.
Oh, I got, I got a great portrait of cake Mario. It's going up. I'm going to hang on to magic.
In fact, I actually may. Is it cake Mario though? I get a further inspection. I'll look at it in a
minute. I think it's cake. Yeah, it's cake Mario. Chat doesn't know. A lot of new viewers. Oh,
whatever. It's just cake Mario. All right. This guy's got to die. Get it. Get it. Die. What?
That hit him right in the back. How did I, how did I let it? I was going to say I ain't
fucking around anymore. Have I played Noita? Nope. I have not. Jesus. Oh, all right. Nine lives.
Play it right now. I'm about to beat this breakout game. You say Noita? How do you say it?
Noita? Noita? Noita? Shit. That was bad. All right. There can't be many more levels after this.
Hopefully I don't blow it. He's not going to ever, he's never going to play Noita.
Um, I don't know. We got a lot of stuff to do and I also have seven streams that are not video games.
That might be fun. That's right. You heard that right. Seven. Seven. Did you give up on FTK? No,
actually. I have a meeting with the people that made it because now I believe it is pretty close
to being really truly ready and that test that we did a few weeks back was very, very, very, very
helpful. Uh, yeah, I have like a meeting with those guys on, um, I think on Monday. You'll
hear more about that soon. They all unlock the puzzle card game. Oh, this is it. Oh man, that's
fast. I have five health? Oh, break the, I could break the cage. It's like playing air hockey. Get
up there. That's how you, that's the way you do it. Damn it. One more. Oh, oh, success losing against
CPU paddle. I'm fine. I got it. Damn, I got late, didn't it? Did I win? You saved the sacred child
of fire. Thank you. Save the remaining children and they will grant you with their power. That was
one. Wait, what? Talk to her in the town. Oh, demons could have used our magic to open a breach
to the nether world. That's one fourth of the game. Is it though? Where's the other, where the other
children? Are they hidden? They might be hidden in another level. I'm telling you, simple living is
the best lifestyle. He doesn't know. Go back to the nether world. Wait, what?
Oh, the 60 levels across the five worlds. Wait, so I have to find the way to get in.
Wait, didn't I go in this thing's mouth? I'm confused. Clear this level. Yeah, I'm going to
clear this level. Fuck, there's only five lives too. Shit, I'm in trouble. I should have bought
lives. That was a mistake. How the fuck did I miss all those? I'm so sad. Come on. But yeah, after
tomorrow. I'm not sure what we're doing after that. There's a ton of things on this list.
We'll just pick one. Got a lot of things to stream. All right, I don't want to get accidentally put
in there. Katana Zero. I'm going to play Katana Zero. Maybe that's what we'll do after playing
Keep Talking Nobody Explodes. Possible. Next day or the day after, whatever. It's on the list.
I would show you the list, but I don't want to spoil everything. Dude, I forgot that I played
that police game. That game was weird. I completely forgot about that game. That was like
yesterday in my brain. There it is. Is Pikmin on that list? It is not. It is not. Shit, it's not.
Yeah, it's not. Sorry. I just didn't put it on the list. Put it on. But which one? Pikmin 1,
Pikmin 2, Pikmin 3. Which one is the one that people think is good? They are all good.
1 and 2. Get them all. Mario Sunshine is on that list, though, so people can be happy about that
one. Just go in order. We could. How long are they? Are they long game? Not really. All right,
gotta be all blue. Or all whatever. All yellow. All red. All blue. All yellow. Oh my god. Yellow.
Yellow. I'm gonna beat the level before this happens. Blue. Red. Yellow. Red. All right. No.
Red. Red. Oh my god. This is fucking ridiculous. Finally. It was just for one heart.
There could be a crown in there. Have we still? All right, I get it. So you have to get them all
through different... All right. All of them are in here. Are we gonna get them all? I don't know.
I don't know if we're gonna get them all. Well, we're going up here. Oh, this will be interesting.
Three orbs. Double power. And catch them all. Let's go. It's just a shotgun that I get to catch.
Fuck! What? How? How? I'm done playing again. That just made me so sad. Like, that actually
made me so sad. I can't believe it. That's... I'm... That's actually ridiculous. I can't believe I
fucked that up. Is this gonna go down? I'm so... What the fuck? All right. I'm in trouble. If I die,
I'm a... If I die, it was a cute game. This is a really cute game. I'm done with it if it's cute.
If it's... If it's a cute game, I'm done with it. It wants... All right. I'm... Okay. I actually am
like fucking starting to freak out. I just want... I just want a pizza. No. All right. I'm not gonna
be able to... Who cares? It's... This heart's in here. Don't even get the chest. What is going on
right now, guys? What's going on? What am I doing? I just... I'm like throwing. I'm not even trying
to throw. I swear to God. Motherfucker. Yellow. All right. Bart. Bart. Bart. Your mind says game,
but your heart says pizza. Or like maybe like tacos or something. A good... A good nice like
soft shell, you know what I mean? Yeah. That's what I'm talking about. That's what I'm talking
about. Get up there. All right. Pull together here, seriously. Before I lose... Well, I got one child,
right? So that's all right. Look, I need to get the four children of power. All right. Well,
with this, I'll be able to at least turn on... Our TV's at least will work, right?
His brain is mush. Oh my God. I was looking at chat. All right. Yeah. All right. Okay. There it is.
All right. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yeah. Yep. Yep. This game's actually really fun, though.
I like this game. He's done? No, I'm... Not yet. I'll get to one more boss. He said the same thing
about Jump King. Yeah, but Jump King was... So you guys don't know this, but like two days ago,
I had this extreme urge to play the DLC. I was like, I want to play Jump King DLC right now.
And then I stopped myself. I don't want to do that. That does not sound like a good idea.
All right. This is it. No losing here. Get it up top. Nice. Good. Again. Good. Good. Good. Good.
Excellent. Excellent. Excellent. Excellent. That's just exactly what I wanted to have happen.
So there are two Jump King DLCs. I'm dead. No, we're good. We're good. I can do it again.
The second one on average is between 25 and 40 hours. Yeah, I know. I've seen a lot of the clips
of streamers and bawling. And I'm just like, that's probably going to be me. And
it's just like, damn, that's a lot. Some of these people handle that shit way better than I would.
Seriously. It takes an average of like 20 to 40 hours. Maybe. We'll see. I really know what's
going to happen. I said this to myself. I'm going to open it. I'm going to be really into it. Yeah,
let's go into the DLC. I'm going to get into it. I'm going to beat it. And after like two or three
hours, I'm going to be sitting there and you guys won't even hear about this. It'll be me internally
saying to myself, not out loud, just going fucking mistake. This was, I could have fucking played
Nancy Drew or anything. I could have played fucking no more heroes or something, but now I'm here.
Fucking idiot. Stupid fucking goddamn idiot. And now I can't leave. I will be internalizing that.
Get him. How is it not getting him? Jump in real life instead.
That would be interesting, wouldn't it? Play this game if you're a streamer or a YouTuber.
I'm just happy that I beat it. And I, look, if I never beat it again, if I never do anything,
but I did the base game and I'm like, okay. But if you start the DLC, you are accepting
the fact that you have to try to finish it. You don't start the Jump King DLC and go, man,
all right, it's the Jump King DLC. It's been an hour. No, I'm out. I'm not doing that. It's like,
you've no, you have to get, you have to stay there. You did it. You did that. Oh, I didn't.
When did I do that? Oh, you tried out both DLC. Yeah. But that was before even one of those times
is I just stumbled upon it accidentally. I thought it was another area in the game. I didn't know it
was a DLC. Yeah, of course. But I wanted to see what it looked like. I didn't start playing the
DLC. I just wanted to see what it looked like. Oh, you started it. I didn't even start it.
I did. Yeah, I did one screen. I'm playing a game that's relaxing. That's not Jump King.
The stream has been kind of interesting. This was like, I was that that emergency game was
crazy. And now I'm just like mouth open. It's pretty rare. We don't want you to relax. We
want you to play Jump King. Don't relax. Stop relaxing. Fine. Fine. I'll open it.
I'm not going to beat it. I'm going to. No, no, don't let them get to you. Don't let them feed on your
vices and your insecurities. Don't let them. I don't want to open it. I'm not going to beat it
tonight. I've been streaming for six hours. I'm not going to beat Jump King DLC tonight.
You guys just told me it takes like 50 hours to beat this thing. I'm not going to beat it now.
Me and Joel are planning to keep talking. Nobody explodes tomorrow. I'm going to play it right now.