To the left, to the right, to the behind.
Oh dude, I got killed by a parachuting man.
Wow, that guy just got destroyed.
Oh my god, there's people everywhere.
I don't even know. Guy that just parachuted in.
Didn't kill him.
It's okay. I'm pinned down here.
I'm pinned down here.
What killed me?
You're telling me that some motherfucker on the roof just killed me?
Somebody on the roof.
Except for Vibe, yes. No, I'm dead again.
He shot me again from the same spot.
He's up on the roof, he's like on the corner.
He's like fucking Spider-Man.
Get rid of that guy.
I don't know what corner you're talking about.
He's on like the roof of the building, like one of the highest buildings.
Spawn on me, then shoot at him.
Alright, fine. Spawning on you, shooting at Spider-Man.
Confirm Spider-Man, get him.
We're never gonna hit this guy.
Dude, this is the one time I spawned without a sniper rifle.
And I just got...
Oh, it was a long storm on that one fateful day.
Did I ever tell thee the story of me old bones?
Do we keep going under the water?
Yeah, we do.
Let me tell you the story of me old bones.
There was a time in a pirate's life.
When we didn't have such old bones.
And that time, well you ran out of bullets, didn't you?
So, are we defending this?
Okay.
The house just...
I did that.
Did you seriously just do that?
I spent the last minute looking for a spawn beacon that was placed there.
Couldn't find it.
Honestly, I didn't even know what just happened.
I felt like somebody just put a flash in my face.
And I teleported to the past.
How do I get a better view?
I don't know.
I need a better view of this.
I fucking jumped out.
I swear to God, dude.
Why am I floating?
I'm flying into the air.
I'm going to heaven.
I'm going to heaven. God has chosen me.
Let me tell you the story of me old bones.
Did you just never tell the story?
You just keep saying it.
Let me tell you an old story of me old bones.
I want to hear the story.
One time me old bones shot twelve people in one second.
Like you just saw right there.
And then me old bones were buried.
In the graveyard.
Behind your old bones.
Once again, I guess we're going to have another German video where you don't even play the game.
I'm kicking ass right now.
And your bones, whatever.
And then he turned the corner.
And he shot some more old bones.
And he got another kill.
And then another boat came over.
And he killed all their bones as well.
And blew up the fucking boat.
See how I was seven and ten?
I got my only seven kills in that fifteen to thirty seconds when I was doing the old bones thing at the end.
You were doing it for like eight minutes.
Blub blub blub blub blub blub blub blub blub.
You just like stumped your balls in my face.
Blub blub blub blub.
You see what I mean?
Yeah, you just did.
Did I just drown?
No, I didn't.
No, I just want to go swimming.
I just want to go swimming in grandma's lake.
No!
Grandma's lake, the ocean you mean?
No, grandma's lake. She's a rich bitch.
What am I supposed to be even shooting here?
Please don't drive us into like the dish from Cable Guy.
No, this is the ending scene from 007, Goldeneye.
Ah, this is the ending scene from Cable Guy as well.
Who's this dude with a blowtorch?
Some guy, something tells me buddy.
You're not going to hit anybody with a blowtorch.
What are you doing? Stop spinning around in circles.
You're seriously fucking up my screen.
I'm out. See you later.
Goodbye.
Look up in the air at me.
What are you doing?
You spin around in circles.
Blowtorch man, like trying to clean somebody's teeth.
Alright, let's go.
Deploy.
There he is, there he is.
Gotta land on the building and do the bros.
I'm not even close to landing on that building.
I'm like falling straight down.
Battlefield bros.
You just came out of the ground.
Now that we're in a plane.
I might as well tell you the story.
Of me old boys.
It was a dark and dreary night.
And me old boys were fucking on fire.
Sure, he's still alive.
That makes perfect sense.
I'm going.
This guy lying on the ground right here.
Why is this working?
I can't even see man.
You are messing up my camera.
It's trying to fix my camera.
My character is stuck in the I'm crawling forward animation.
I fell off.
Let me tell you a story about me old boys.