That was just so stupid looking so all all this nobody capped the point by the way leave the point uncapped
All this huntsman snipers stand over here. So follow me for the sake of just testing this out
Everybody hold your arrows out on them and on the count of three let go. We're just gonna see what happens. So ready one two
three
Isolated. All right, you got your uber and make sure heavy make sure you stand still stand completely still
Alright, so we're gonna start our ubers and then I'm gonna count to three and everybody everybody knock an arrow at him
You ready start ubers?
three two one shoot
All right, stop stop shooting
Stop shooting before you run over it. Oh
Dear okay, don't kill him. Keep my life. Everybody go back up. Everybody come back up
He's got like arrow boots on walking around a little bit heavy. Look at this. It's like
Three two one to activate uber start shooting spam Wow, dude
Keep going keep going
I'm taking damage
That's like
That's seriously insane man. All blue medics come to the back of this wall back here because I want travel time
I want them just just travel across the map
Make sure you're hitting him. Oh
Dear it looks like bugs. It looks like a bunch of bugs like flies like bees
I don't think I think he'll stay alive. I don't think he's gonna die from this. I
Really think he's gonna live forever. Oh
No, not for long. Here comes like the other team
Holy shit
Dude are the noise coming out of this right now?
I'm playing an RTS right now. This is my base right here. All right, I've got my base here with my unit
Oh, that looks good. There's the enemy base. She doesn't have shit
That's crazy looking. It looks like silly string
You're all spraying silly string at him. He's gonna die. He's gonna die. Keep alive
Wow. Oh
No medic died. All right. Oh, let's see. Let's take a look. Let's take a look
Let's see what he looks like. He was looking at the it's all in the same spot
You can see the pattern look at the pattern that's going in a line down his face to his toes
Well, all right, so now have you get him have you fight back pop over I'm gonna keep him alive
He looks like a vending machine