Hey, you, person that just landed on the channel page. What's going on? My name is Germa985.
Or you can just call me Germa. That's what most people around here call me.
I'm a gaming channel. You probably could guess that by all the different playlists and all the videos below,
which you should check out and you should go watch some of them right now and possibly subscribe.
That's the whole purpose of this video. I'm trying to get you to subscribe to my channel.
So hey, subscribe to the channel! Subscribe!
You see on this channel, I like to call myself Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Germa,
because I have two different sides. I have the very professional side where I review content.
I review packages. What? I don't review packages. I review like games. Oh, here's like, here's a cup.
This cup is good. There's a whole lot of stuff here though. I have my fun.
I have my professional side and I mold them together into sort of this lunacy that is Germa985.
So hopefully this little trailer will be able to give you an explanation of this channel and
hopefully you subscribe as well. So please subscribe, subscribe, and subscribe and I'll
subscribe you all next time. And of course, subscribe, subscribe. Bye. Okay. Yeah.
Hey, what is going on everybody? Hey, what is going on everybody? Hey, what is going on everybody?
Germa here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
Meet me at the statue at 12 o'clock, okay? I don't know what the statue is. I don't play this game.
Oh wait, I'm going to bang. No! What? Oh, what was that? You were going to bang? What?
What were you going to do? You were going to bang me? Oh, there we go.
So of course as Mario, you have to do all the dirty work because you can jump real high. I
never understood that by the way that why does Mario have to do everything? He's like the saviour
of the world because he can jump higher than Michael Jordan. Left or right? Left or right?
We're going to go left. Oh man.
I knew it. I knew what was going to happen too and it still doesn't matter.
What I'm talking about here is you'll see it. I go like me, me, me, me. Almost like I'm sweeping
the screen, not with my mouse, but with my A and D keys. And it's something I don't know why I do
this. And I think it's because I have a lot of trouble aiming with the mouse more so than I do,
which just kind of getting people in front of my crosshair. But I kill every single person almost
by doing the sway in quotes.
in the world. And I'll show you right here. Look at this. Get the fuck out of here, buddy.
And let me tell you, did I really have this in me the whole time? And the answer is yes,
everybody does. Everybody has it in them. You have it in you. You can, you can actually do it.
You just have to tell yourself it's possible and you have to act on those possibilities.
Hi guys. Today we're going to create a fucking washer, dryer, a generous channel there.
All right, fine. Right here. So he already finished it. That was it.
So thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. And hopefully you subscribe
to this channel. Hopefully I have convinced you to do that and you can be part of our little
community here, the germs. So join the germs. I hope to see you all in the comment section
and thank you for watching again. So take care, everybody. I'll see you all soon.