Hey. Yeah, we're early. Very early, actually. Almost an hour early.
Uh, I'm just, I'm ready. I'm ready. You know how sometimes I tell you guys that sometimes
I sit here and I'm just all set up. Things work. Everything's ready to go. And it's like 45 minutes
to stream time. No, no, no, no, no. We're going now. I'm ready now. I'm that kind of person where
I've had a show and I went on stage and the show was seven o'clock. People are funneling in at like
six 30 getting their seats. I, if I was ready, I would just come out and just start talking to
people. It's like, Hey, I'm, I'm ready to start my show. I was, I would be, can I have a mic?
And I would just, it'd be addressing people as they walked in to get their seats.
And then it'd be like, all right, six, it's like, it's seven o'clock. All right, now we can do the
show. It would be pissed to start the show like 40 minutes early. People walk in. It's 20 minutes
till the show's over. Oh, sorry, guys. I really just had to, I really wanted to start. Be like,
Dickhead, these tickets were $285. They're in the front row and it says there's a meet and greet
after. Is that still happening? I don't feel like doing that anymore. Dude, I got free tickets to
the Jerma string. Yeah. Well, we had to start giving them away free because I didn't really
get any money to come and pay for it. Anyways, we're gonna play Tony Hawk's Underground today.
It's all ready to go. It works. This is, if you're wondering the platform, this is X-Box,
X-Box that has been upscaled to 1080 through backwards compatibility with 360.
That's where we're at. That's why I'm playing it in 360. It should look a little crusty,
but not too crusty where it's gonna be annoying. I don't know. We'll find out.
Just say you pirated it. Just say you pirated it. No one will care.
I didn't. I got a 360 right next to me. I had to get a 360 hard drive.
I'm playing this on a 360 right now. That's what it is. But there's not much else to say besides,
here we go. By the way, I think I'm gonna keep original music. So this entire VOD is gonna be
deleted. There might be like 10 seconds of this VOD that is watchable. I'm really sorry, those of
you that are VOD watchers. But the last time we did this, we played Tony Hawk 2. No, don't,
spoilers. We played Tony Hawk 2 and I think I muted the music and it just fucked it all up.
It just didn't feel right. It felt off. Is there skateboarding in this game?
Yep. No, you didn't. Oh, so Jeremy lied about turning the music off in
Tony Hawk Pro Skater 2 for the Dreamcast. I don't think you can even make a username that long,
so don't even try it. All right, I'm ready. Let's go. So there's the story mode. I'm gonna
do the story mode because that's obviously the easiest thing to do. I need to make a skater too,
don't I? Let's create a skater to use in story mode. Stream will be chugging in just a moment.
Please up the game volume. Oh, let's see what it looks like first. All right, so
create new, create a new skater. That's like a Neversoft developer. Okay. Any unsaved changes
to your current story that don't matter. All right, pre-made skaters.
Pre-made Steve, Becky, Mike, Jim, Chad, Joey, Sheena, Josh, Andy, Liz, Jack. Are these all
game devs? These might be game devs. The suit, Tiger Swallow, Big Lion, Green Chick, Big Pimp,
Big Pimpin', Big Pimpin' Eddie. Well, I want to make a, I want to make one. All right,
head information, name, custom skater, age 16. I had sucks to do this. You know what I mean?
I remember playing games when it was on Xbox or PlayStation. It was like, yeah, all right.
I'm done. All right. That hurts. Stance. I would pick Goofy, but Goofy just means left,
lefty, right? I'm just going to regular. Push. Never Mongo. Mongo Switch. Always Mongo.
I don't know what these mean. What's just default? Never Mongo. Do not push. Always Mongo. Always
Mongo. Full Mongo. What does that mean though? What is always Mongo? What is Mongo? I don't know
what Mongo is. Tricks. Street. I like going up high, but I also like manual too. So we're going
to street. I gotta, I gotta Google what this is. What is Mongo? What is Mongo? Mongo skateboarding.
The Mongo push. A stupid way to skateboard. A person skates Mongo if they use their leading foot
in the front while riding to push. While they are pushing, the back foot stays near the rear
of the board and they push with their front foot. So Mongo is a stupid way to skateboard. This is
the official definition. Is it bad to ride Mongo on a skateboard? It's a bad habit. Okay. Never Mongo.
Goofy. Always Mongo. Okay. Never Mongo. Regular Stance. Hometown. What the fuck? Las Vegas.
Uh, yeah. I wasn't born in Las Vegas. You're right. Fuck. I was. All right. How do I do shit?
Shit. Boston. Do I have to do Boston mass? No. Where did you know where that is? Custom name.
Me? No, it's going to have to be like some fucked up like frog person.
Ernie. I think I like Ernie. Ernie is a Mongo name. Ernie. Ernie. Ernie. Ernie. Ernie. It's
Bernie. It's Ernie. All right. Ernie. I don't have a last name. I'm just Ernie. No, I'm just Ernie.
All right. Well, Ernie isn't 34. That's not even me. So I can change these. Whatever. 40 from Boston.
Ernie. Head options. Face. Can I rotate? Okay. Can I? Whoa. Gray. Gray skin. Gray. Eyes. All right.
I can't do eyes. That's going to fuck me up. Yeah. That's the... What was that game that Ubisoft came
out with? That was a fucking mess. It was like a... What was it? It was a... What's it called?
Assassin's Creed Unity. Yes. That's the one. This is every YouTuber's thumbnail for an Assassin's
Creed Unity video. I mean, I would have done it. I think I like a gray skin. Let's see what else
we can do. Hold on. Wait. Oh, that doesn't... I can just be blue.
Okay. What is Ernie? I think... I don't know if I want to just be like a wacky color or something.
You know what I mean? No. I don't want to be like orange or like blue. I don't want to be like
lime green. Let's take this set to a value. I can be like a glow stick.
All right. How about... Should I be a glow stick? I don't know. Let's force a neighbor. All right.
Fine. I'll be a glow stick. I'm going to... No, no, no. I'm going to get... I'm going to hate that
after like fucking three hours. All right. How about kind of glow stick? Like how about just sick?
Like how about just sick?
Just look back here.
It's my hair. Middle part. No, no, no.
Comb over. No, this is all too easy. It has to... It's too easy.
Medium, medium. Actually, I kind of like this one.
Spike long. No, no. I kind of like clown hair. No, I don't. Literally spikes is what I thought
that said. Pompadour. I like it. Eraser hair. I think I like the pompadour.
How do I do a hair color? Make it the same color as my skin.
I'm not sure I can even replicate it again.
Shrek 5. Zoomer Shrek.
No, I don't want it. I don't like this. How about... All right. Let's do middle part.
That's fine. I don't care. Whatever.
It's just my hair. Facial hair. Beard. Mustache. Long sideburns. Honest Abe.
Did it be honest Abe?
Just looks like he has a helmet on. Chinless Abe. Okay. Just looks like he has a weird helmet on.
It's going to be lower saturation.
It's just wearing a scarf with your own hair. Is this a... Okay. Is this a hairstyle?
Having your hair go all the way down to the bottom and come all the way to the right?
Is this like the wearing a helmet of your own hair style?
Can't get the color exact. That's close. That's good. That's good. That's all right. That looks
good. That looks fine. Hats. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. I already have a helmet on.
No. No. No. No. How about the dunce? Okay. I like that one. I like the dunce hat. I get to be the
guy that wears the dunce hat today. Hold on. Let's see the others. Viking helmet. British officer.
A British bobby. Oh, I kind of like this too. That's so stupid.
If I could wear a wizard hat. But if I do a wizard hat, then I have to be a wizard.
What about the earmuffs? Just be a wizard. But I have to do like a big long wizard beard. No,
I don't want to do that. It's too... I'm going dunce. Can you even make a long beard?
Can you even make a long beard? Let's see.
Facial hair. Let's go. Beard. No, you can't.
It's just painted on. Guys, this game came out in like 2004. 2003.
No. We're going to have to go dunce.
Or actually, I like the earmuffs. The earmuffs to me are funnier. I'm going earmuffs. Wait, paper bag.
But no, no, that sucked. That's just the eyes with more space. Dastardly Richard.
I might be able to make it pretty close.
See if I can. Damn it. I can't put glasses on the front.
Okay, we got shirt style. It could be pretty close.
There you go. You're going to think it's blue.
You sure it's not? No, it's blue.
Make it darker.
Make it a little too dark. Yeah, it's all right, though. It ended up being perfect.
It's a zipper hoodie, you fake fan. I can't. Well, you want me to go through every offer to
find the zipper hoodie? And that's not even true. Dick Dastardly Richard. That's not a zipper hoodie.
It's not a hoodie. Who's the fake fan? It's this, but long sleeve because there are no zippers.
It's not a hoodie. It's just a jacket. This is actually, it's probably pretty damn close.
Let's see. Suit coat? No. All right. Remember jogger jacket? I think jogger jacket's the one.
It's got to make it weird and light blue and splotchy. I mean, the reason why that shirt looks so
different and odd is because it's a game from 1995. I can't add a Nintendo 64 pixels.
It's a little lighter than that. It's like this. That's close. This is close enough.
All right. Now the second color. Oh, I can't even make it the second color. It's all right.
Close enough. What about gloves? Spike neck? Wristband? What do you gloves?
Wrist tape? Elbow band? No. Gloves. Here we go. Gloves. Can't wear gloves.
Does it go some green or something? I can't believe this is actually kind of working.
All right. These are, they're white, but they're pixelated and crappy and smudged with
42 kilobyte, like yellow and brown pixels. So we're going to go zebra like it is in the video.
I can't make these longer. Hmm. Suit pants. Jogger. Oh, he's just going to be in a jogging suit.
Oh, he's in white. He's got a stripe going down in his boots. He's got these red
bare feet. Oh, it's too bad. I can't make him in bare feet. If I make these red, it'll be fine.
Anything chunkier than this? He's a chunky. Well, then this guy's not Ernie anymore.
This is not Ernie. This is Dick Dastardly Richard.
All right. These are boots. There we go. What happened to Ernie? Like that's, I want Ernie.
Fuck Ernie. Head top. Wait, you can. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. We can't see any of this.
Wait, you can. What? Nope. No, the fucking head's coming off. That's coming off. Ernie can be a big
fan of Dick Dastardly Richard. This is coming off. He's just, he just dresses as him because he
likes that video. No, if you tell me I have full on scale, face scaling options. What? How big?
I don't want to be too huge. No, this is not, this is not Dick Dastardly Richard's origin story.
This is Ernie the fan. He can make a mega mine. Head top. Where's this going? Oh, okay. Let's do
it this way. At least don't make him green. We'll fix it. Hold on. Yeah, this, this is big fan Ernie.
Big fan Ernie. That's what his name is changing to. Super wide. Big head funny. His head's not that
big. His head's not even that big. But it is funny though. Why is it? His head's not even that big.
Y'all. All right, that's too extreme though. That's way too extreme. Yeah, I don't want him to have
like an orc mouth. How about, all right, that's okay. Chest. Oh, shit. Make him, make him like
an ant. All right, I like this. This big gross stomach. A tiny, tiny chest. Wink. Hold on. Big
biceps. Forearms. Yeah, I don't, I gotta take the beard off too. It just looks stupid.
Huge hands. Or small hands. We gotta make him kind of like a pear. All right. Why's the jaw look
still so strange? Without the facial hair. Okay, I think it's good. I think it's good.
Big fan Ernie, I think is good. He's an alien. All right, we got it. We're done. Scale options.
Body. That's good. You can just make him roll. Okay. I'm doing any of this stuff. Who cares?
Wait, does it matter? Helmet. No, who cares? Does big fan Ernie need to be protected?
All right. Big fan Ernie can wear knee pads. These look like metal shackles.
Not knee pads. How big are the elbow pads? I can't even wear elbow pads. He has cow legs.
I'm gonna be so safe. Okay, that's fine. I'm done. I can't unseat the cow.
I cannot unseat the cow legs now that you said that.
Information. Big fan Ernie. Well, how about bovine Ernie? That's not bad either.
I think I'm gonna go with, I'm going with bovine Ernie. Can't wait for this guy to get instantly
eliminated in the next rumble. He's gonna have zero stats. Bovine Ernie. I think he's
however late on the screen. All right. Bovine Ernie. There he is.
From whatever. He could be like my neighbor or something. I don't care. How high can this go?
45. Okay. Done. Okay. Save skater. Let's see those legs.
Bovine Ernie. All right. Here we go. Let's start a career.
He saved. Should have been Dick Dastardly Richard. Well, it's, it's bovine Ernie.
New story. Begin at normal. I'm not doing 2003 hard. No, I'm doing normal.
2003 hard is 2020 like insane impossible. Let's go.
Muska is actually coming to this dump for a skate demo. Get dressed. Let's go.
I am dressed. I'm already dressed in my shackles.
Oh, I just got my ride all set up. What? They talk sort of looks like that thing's held together
with duct tape. Let's go skate. I didn't know they actually spoke. He's fully voice acted.
Home sweet home. What a dump. At least it has some killer spots. The old pool down by the high school
scab land, the drainage ditch on the south side of town street, our own little strip of paradise
complete with drug dealers who hate skateboarders. Well, I got to turn the volume up now.
Get ready. Check this out. Oh, by the way. Yeah. Again, this whole thing's going to get muted just
in case you didn't know. It's definitely been looked at bad on Xbox 360. All right, let's talk.
What up, Eric? Hey, help me out here. I need help with. I was just skating mind in my own
and the dealers grabbed my board. They tore it apart and they threw the pieces up on the roof.
My knees wrecked. Could you grab them for me? I got to go. I got to get on the roof.
Oh, man. Yeah, I'll hold your death. Use A to jump and R to grab onto stuff and then pull yourself
up. Press A to continue. So you jump, but you hold it. R is grab on stuff. I'm actually walking
around. I forget everything about this game. The next part should be on the house across the alley.
Jump. We can grab the gutter piece. Okay. Last part is on top of your house.
Hey, well, I'm getting my right set up again. Let's see if you are a couple of things.
You can get off the board to get over terrain that would normally be hard or impossible to
skate over. So you can get off the board. Is it L? Give this a try. Get off your board,
then jump over the barriers. What button is that? What? What is that like weird moon or like cute?
What is that? What button is that? Is it LBs? Okay. Run and jump over each barrier to get on.
Okay. So that's left bumper. Good job. Now jump up while running and then grind on the barrier.
Jump and wait. There it is. Okay. Beating stat challenges will increase your skating abilities.
Pause the game and go to the view stats menu to see a list of the challenges.
I think I got those knee pads on. Wait, what's that? Oh, this is like, this is shit to do
everywhere. What's this one? What are you doing? You psyched to see Muska's demo? Yeah. Bet you
are. Hey, since you punks aren't in school, why don't you go put up some flyers? Oh, I got to
put flyers up. Try to hit all the telephone poles. Why does that name sound fake in 2020?
You know what I mean? Like Chad Muska. The audio is delayed. Shouldn't be. Is it delayed?
So what you're hearing the sound after I move. Well, it should be going click, click, click,
click, click. It's not. It's barely fine. It's good. It's a little delayed. The video is slow.
I don't know why that is. Let me try one thing. How does this change it? Yeah, just that delayed
the audio for like a hundred milliseconds. All right, let's do it. So pick up the flyers.
All right, I got to get back into the Tony Hawk spirit here.
Oh shit. Did I win? I think I won. Yeah, I'm good. I love springing together. Oh, I missed it. I
missed it. Ah, good. Get you done prancing on and off your board. Let's actually escape.
At least I'm not too gimp to prance. How's your knee? I'll show you. So you land this.
Do a melon in the drainage dish. Oh, that was fucking pathetic. Oh, there's blood.
There's blood. Do a melon. I didn't. But did I not do a melon?
I flexed way too hard. I flexed too hard. Did I not do a melon?
A melon then revert to R as you land. Yeah, revert.
That's it. Enough warming up. You can't beat my score and you know it. What's right?
You see people at the skate park or like the ice skating rinks and anywhere that there's a
skill like the white, the ground is made out of moving material. What's going on?
What's your score? Beat Eric's score. We'll give him a head start.
Ooh, a thousand points. What else can you do? Wow. Really nice, man. Oh, I can't keep,
I can't like leave the area. I'll beat him. Don't worry. I'm trying so hard.
I'm still in the lead. All right. I'm just going to play. Oh shit. Eric's going to win.
Let's go. I gave him a head start. That was stupid. That's enough warming up. All right.
Let's go. Oh, why? Why is he fucking kicking my ass?
What? Why is he doing so much better this time? And you guys wanted me to do this on sick. No
fucking way. Losing to Eric. Wait a second. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. I don't have stat points that I didn't put in. Do lip tricks. It's like holding triangle,
right? Right at the top. All right, Eric, let's fucking go.
Okay, come on. What? Whoa. He just fucking shot me into the air. Oh my God. I'm like
tilting right now. Did I win? Eric, don't you fucking dare. Eric, Eric, why are you so hard?
What the fuck, Eric? Eric, you're supposed to be in the tutorial. Eric, you haven't even taught me
how to do anything besides a melon grab. Why are you trying so hard? Imagine doing this on sick
difficulty. He probably does like 100,000 points. Fuck, I keep screwing that up. You can't just
mash. Shit. Oh my God. I'm not going to be able to beat Eric. I'm not going to be able to beat
Eric on the tutorial. I beat Eric. I can't believe I almost lost it. That was way harder than it
should have been. I can't believe it took that long to beat Eric. Did he get arrested?
Fuck. I was going to say you fucking try to do that line, Eric. Also, I have to keep in mind,
I'm at zero stats on everything. I think I'm supposed to know who this is. Mike V.
You're way nicer than fucking Eric was. You all right, kid? You seem to smash your face on the
fucking ground. All right. You know what? Can you use an Xbox one controller on 360?
Can you use an Xbox one controller on 360? God damn it. You can't. It's the Xbox controller.
They're all the same button. They're not individual buttons.
I probably should have thought about that. It's all just one axis. It's just one huge
button on their original Xbox 360 controller. You know, they're individual. God damn it.
See how these are individual buttons? See, like, you guys need to see. I can't use the analog
either. It's too hard. I'll have to. I'll get used to it. I never use the analog in any of these
games. How do I do Flamingo? Left, right, B. What? You're fucked for real. I've never used
an analog in a Tony Hawk game. I only use the defense. It's easier to press the buttons
because, like, hitting, like, left and it's... No, it's too hard. I'd rather just use the analog.
It's because of manuals. It's hard for me to do a manual than analog. I don't like it.
It's easier to go, like, tap up and down on the actual buttons than to have the analog.
That's why I learned how to play these games with the D-Pad long ago, just because manuals
is just so much easier. Tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap. Because you can go way
too far. See how I'm using the analog right now? Oh, too much. Remember, you're nuts. I saw one person
said, I agree, so I don't care. As long as one person agrees with me, what do I care? All right,
we need another... Oh, I got too greedy. Looking for... There is somebody.
Oh, I never even got the guy's skateboard back, did I? Hey, JT, not out racing today.
Hey, the kid next door. Nah, Charles needs some exercise.
I'll give you five bucks to run him around the block a couple of times for me.
Five bucks? Wait, what?
Do I have to ride the dog? This dog is fucking fast, man.
Oh, Muska's here. We got Muska's demo. Same counter. All right, so how is the voice acting
in this game, you think? Yo, check this out. Muska, chilling, chilling. Where? Australia.
That's how you hook it up. How do we get this close to Chad Muska?
Wow, Muska in Jersey? Unreal. I wonder if anyone could impress him.
He's checking out the pool by the skate shop. Eric, where is that?
Chad, Chad, Chad, Chad, are you looking? Chad, I just want to say I'm a really big fan.
What do you think about this? Chad, look at me, Chad.
Chad, just wait, I'm coming. Chad, take a look at this one.
Oh, hey, Chad. Hey, man. When we drive around, just avoid this fucking weird kid.
He's freaking me out. It looks like a good place to skate.
I didn't do it. All right. 30,000 points. Fuck. 40 year old kid. Come on. I can't.
Do you think we should call the police or something? Or is it going to be all right?
It doesn't look like the other kids. Chad, just watch. Okay, I know what I have to do.
Yo, it looks like a good place to skate. Oh, they turn this way. Fuck. 7,000. God damn it.
Yo, it looks like a good place to skate. What's this? I'm just going to finish the trick in
front of me. What? When did it finish? A place to skate. I'm so desperate for his attention.
Just give me attention, Chad. I'm dying over here. Just please look at me.
I'm going to go. I'm going to start all the way back here. I know he can't see me. It doesn't
matter. I'm going to finish the trick. Here we go. I made a good line. 6,000 points. Fuck.
Use the half pipe. 30k total. It's 30k total. Not 30k in one trick. You can bust some nice lines
there. Is it? Yes. Restart it. That looks like a good place to skate. Okay, fine. It does. Nice
turn. Okay, he saw it. Okay, good. He's not even looking. I just was in front of the car.
I was just standing in front of the car. Not bad. Not bad. That looks like a good place to skate.
Yes, it does, Chad. I'm losing my mind here. That was 10,000 points. That looks like a good
place to skate, man. Okay, I'm laughing. This is too funny. Whoa, Chad Muska. Holy shit.
I can't believe he noticed me.
I had no money, no place to stay, nothing, man, until my first shop sponsor hooked me up.
So why don't you head down to your shop, check out their riders. I thought there was a Christmas
present in his front seat. I was like, wow. And yo, Merry Christmas. It is. Thank you. Thanks.
Mr. Peralta's not here right now, but if you want to be sponsored by a skate shop,
you'll need to impress the riders on his team. If you get us to sign off on you, you're in.
Okay. All right. Bernie Ovine is doing pretty good. Chapter two, impressing the locals.
So you want to be sponsored, huh? Got to be able to put up big numbers under pressure.
Think you can handle it? Yeah, sure. No problem. Okay, then let's see what you can do using our
setup.
Why don't I have a private lane? Why don't I have a private lane? Why are you people standing here?
I'm taking out all the competition. Oh, okay. I need 20,000 points. Everyone's watching you.
Let me see. I saw the fucked up thing I just did.
All right. Did it. Jesus. Yep. I am a local. Dude, I go to school with your sister.
Then you should get stats increased. No, you'll probably need at least five tries to hit them
like I do. You Chris's best line. It took me six months to hit that line. Well, whatever.
I did it. See if you can hit this. Chris's crazy line.
It's a broken neck in two places. End it, end it, end it, end it. All right, let's go.
I got to impress all the locals. Why does it have a gas coming out of here?
I heard yo skater. Why am I a charging bull? How much do I weigh? Am I a train?
You goals. Impress Sean. Impress Joey. Impress Sean.
Let's see if you got the cojones. I can just go right to them.
Meet me on the roof. Use the quarter pipe to get up to roof height. Then hold left and jump off
your board onto the roof. That seems like a lot of it. Jump onto the roof and then get off your
board while jumping up onto the roof. Nicely done. Now I want you to transfer between the houses.
Don't live in these houses to transfer. Come down the ramp and angle yourself. So your jump
carries you across the space between the houses. Oh, and carefully you don't overshoot. I don't
want to have to scrape you off of Elm Street. Transfer over the alley. So he wants me to
feel pain. Hold on. I kind of don't understand what he wants me to do. Transfer over, get off
the board and then jump up and then get on. Oh, I know what he wants me to do. Nice. Now spine
back down and I'll tell Mr. Brompton you've got skills. So skate up the quarter pipe, catch air,
spine transfer and land in the quarter pipe below. Skate up the quarter pipe, catch air, spine
transfer and land in the quarter pipe. Spine transfer. That's not it. Where does it go?
Why is it spawning me here? I don't know. What is it? What spine? Okay, spine transfer is that.
Spine transfer is you just go forward. They're using these terms like I should know where they
are. Mongo, spine transfer, goofy. I don't know what these things are.
So just run in. I weigh like 6,000 pounds. Just run everybody over.
Where's the school? Like where's the school? What is going on in this neighborhood?
We have to like fight crack heads. Wait kid, it's too dangerous.
It's an actual stealth section. Wait kid, it's too dangerous.
Oh, get on the roof. What? I'm supposed to get by them around this way. Where is it?
Is that the Simpsons? Wait kid, it's too dangerous. I'm going to go back. No,
no. Use the wires? What do you mean the wires? What? You want me to tightrope walk on the wire?
I can't grab them. Power lines? Didn't I just grab them and fall? Just go straight on the roof.
Wait, why would I do this? This would kill somebody. You die if you do this. If I make
any connection with anything. I can get fucking hurt doing this. All lines can't kill you,
but electric lines can. If you touch any other thing, you die. Wait, Eric? Is Eric doing drugs?
Oh no, Eric is doing arson.
Oh, I'm looking for the owner, Mr. Peralta. Wait, are you the Stacy Peralta? That's me.
You the guy my skaters have been talking about? Well, I hope so. I'd like to be sponsored by your
shop. Yeah, so would everybody else. I'll tell you what. Make me a sponsor me video. Show me what
makes you different than Bobby B down the street. I can't wait to make a sponsor me video. Please
don't hand me anything from the same old spots in New Jersey, dude, because I've seen it all.
Done. No local spots and different tricks. Dude, I just gave me the go ahead and do something
dangerous. They know those gangsters know it was me. What are you talking about? When I got back
to my house last night, they were parked outside waiting for me. I've seen all the local tricks.
I haven't seen somebody put their tongue in through an outlet yet. It couldn't work for me.
Hey, Eric, are you okay? I think we lost him. Who's this guy?
We got to get out of here. If they find me, it'll be my name on this headstone.
I'm hiding here with Headstone Harry. Headstone Harry. But if we bring in some scrap metal,
he says he'll bang us out of our ramp. And if we can get it set up, the street warriors say they'll
give us a tow to get speed. Jumping the bridge is the only way to get past the cops. Quick,
drug dealers are after us. All right, I got to get the scrap metal. Press A and jump and grab.
All right, scrap metal, let's go. Or scrap, scrap, scrap. Let's probably get off the board.
Jump and grab. Where am I? Up here? On the roof? Do I need six? Filter. Big jump.
Didn't work, but it's all right. Need to get to the other side of the bridge, huh?
No problem. Those pigs can't stop us. Grab the back of my ride and I'll get you up to speed.
Clear the bridge. Okay, let's go. Don't let go until I tell you. Hit L and R if you want to
switch sides. I don't need to switch sides. Ready? Steady? All right, how do you let go?
Is it just up again? Is it down? All right, it's down. Holy shit.
No skater punks allowed in this station.
How would I land that? Do I have a parachute?
Please, man, we have to get out of town. The Elm Street dealers are after us. We're desperate.
Didn't you see us jump the bridge? Guess I was too busy stopping lions,
skate rats from sneaking into the station and spray painting, I am the king of no pants on
a phone key on. What's your problem, bacon bits? Wake up on the wrong side of your mother this
morning. Oh, holy shit. Makes Stu chase you three times around the circle. Did I kill him?
Okay, well, we killed the security guard. Yes. Keep going.
All right. Can't be on the street. Get 25,000 points. Don't touch the street.
End it. Oh, I thought I could end it. End it. Oh, it's ended. End the trick.
I can end it right there. There it is. No, it's not it. Shit. Fuck. Shit. Fuck. Shit.
No, you idiot. I was trying to do a lit trick. Turn the music up. The music is as loud as it can go.
I think it's just bad mixing. Back to the hangout. Save. Wait, they took Eric. Hold on.
Yeah, look, I think I'm pretty sure it's off as loud as it can go. Maybe it's not.
I had it in reverse.
All right, we got to chase him. Hey, Eric, look out the back window.
Eric's dead. Can I go faster? Oh, come on. What the fuck is that even there for?
Who are these people?
There's a car in this game. Okay, well, that took me back a little. There's a car. Good.
It's a full letter grade. That much is certain. All right, Brian. Imagine you jumping for him.
That was a stupid thing. It was like a Disney game. Rescue Eric. Got it.
That's one way to rescue somebody. Let's get the hell out of here.
Quick, get on the train. That's Mario Kart. We can't grind in Mario Kart. We're in Manhattan.
Big bad New York. Peralta will be pumped if we can get some footage from the program.
Are we actually going to make a video? Veterans Memorial, the Pyramid Ledges, and 78 Water Street.
I hope I get to edit the video.
Where are your parents? Well, in the lore, I am the parent. This character is 40, so
you're looking at him. Skate the Big Apple. I'll find it.
Explode the Alpha and Omega Coles with drum rolls and hoes. So we uphold and foretold the scores
of six years ago. Fast flow from G-Rap to Kool Moe. Super Celeb-O. Major to the Minimo. Every
individual bounce to the tip of your lungs. Collapse and raps you trapped in. The only way
to make it happen, George, I've been fast. I'm the hot dog. The run the hottest monologue
installed. Poetic and certain. Can I actually get up there from? Oh, wait. Get on the board.
Oh, OK. I restarted. I got one.
Found one of five. Where's your other stuff? Oh, is that what? Up there? Shit.
Come on. Why'd you have to do that?
No, I got the one up there.
I don't see anything. Oh, there's one here.
I'm going to get the hair on that.
Where? Over there. Where? Where? Where? Right there.
I'm going to get one of there, too. OK, I should get it. Wrong way.
Last one's this way.
I got to get all the way up there. OK, I know two. I got to grind on that bar.
How many cars to come down this tiny little fucking road?
They're probably saying the same thing about me, too.
Oh, I had it. I just didn't grab it. No, I had it too. Shit. No, I'm dead.
No, here we go. Number two. Here we go. All right. I'm hitting. I'm letting go of the ollie
too. Way too late, apparently. I don't know why. Song name? Pause for the song name. Hold on.
Little Lips. Grab it, can I? Can I just jump and grab the damn thing? Do this. Can I get it?
Yeah. Song is Crush Them by GBH. Crush Them. Get off the board. This one's going to be so hard for
me to get because of the angle. Tiny little lips. No, I want to grind it. No, I want to stop doing it.
I want to grind the fucking rail. Thank you. There it is. Yes. All right, who's next?
You. No, you. What song is this? It's Braggin' Rites.
Uh, hold grind combos. Up and Y and then Y. Y and then down Y.
Can you make the game louder? A smidge. There we go. What about you? Yo, let's see you try
this one. Get special on this QP to do a Muwop 5-0. It's QP. I don't know what that term is.
Get a QP on this M5-0. Oh wait, that's Chad Muska. He's just hanging out over here.
All right. Get special on this quarter pipe then do a Moonwalk 5-0.
I'm gonna die. Get special and Moonwalk 5-0 the waterfront.
Down, left, right. I died.
Still don't have a special.
All right, there we go.
Shit. Is that not it? I don't have a special anymore. Damn it.
I didn't do it. Is this it? No, it's down, left, Y. Down, left, Y. All right, slow down a little.
Down, left. Okay, here we go. Down, left, Y.
Don't fall in. Oh no, that guy. That guy was doing the same quest.
Oh, it's all right. I'll get it. That poor guy was doing the same thing.
We're all trying to impress the same guy. I'm not going fast enough. Look at how bad this is.
Hey, be careful, man. Watch out for the bodies in there.
People keep trying to impress me and they keep getting fucking killed in there. You keep killing
each other. Radical. That's not a bad deal, but I don't really want to do that.
Why destroy the competing car mission? Why is this car so low? I feel like it's not even a car.
This is freaking me out. I feel like the car's inside the ground. I didn't mean it. Okay,
I'm not sure what we're going to be doing this time. I think we're going to have a good line
here because there's seven of these. That restarted. I got time. I got time.
Ah, that arrow fucked my head. It's hit and run all over again. It's like the same driving
mechanics in hit and run. Where's the last one? I'm getting time. That's good. Wait, where is he?
How do you even have to shop in an alley? That doesn't seem like the smartest place to get
business.
Okay, entertain us by throwing 45,000 anywhere or do I have to be in here? 45,000 doesn't matter.
I'm going to do this line here.
I just grew. It's got color. That's weird. All right, Bernie Bovine, doing good so far.
I can't wait to impress the fuck out of these guys.
Wait, take your soggy mob flips back to Jersey, tweakers. Hey, let's just go skate. If we tear
up your favorite spots- Excuse me, the proper term is crackhead. All right, I'm going to impress
the locals and then they finally will have to use their video camera. Alley switch coming up.
Trying to get up on the bridge. All right, what do you got for me? Some fun?
Can you help me out? I need to get some footage of this kid and my camera's busted.
He's risking his life on this line. Can you help me? I need to get some footage of this kid.
Film the locals. Stay close. That works, but isn't somebody filming me filming him?
All right, I got to get a big drop into a switch with a transfer. Come on.
Don't fall. Hold on. That's the best part of my 20-hundreds. I can do shit like this.
You know exactly what I was trying to do there? Just pretend I did it.
Oh, shit, dude. That was fucking awesome. All right, what do you got? Check out my buddy's
sick line here in the banks. This is a line? It's a bunch of cars. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. Hit the killer line combo. Wait, why didn't it start? We're getting ready.
Oh, okay. Hold on. Start it up. What? That was- It was still in the combo.
Fuck. I need more speed than this. Do I have to start on the car? I have to end on that.
I'm so mad. I can't fucking believe it. Dude, I'm telling you, this lift thing is
fucking me so hard. It's just ruining me. It's fucking me up. Fucking me up. So bad.
They're like, I'm timing it wrong. Help me out and help me get some killer footage for Stacy.
Remember how she was building this? Okay. The guards are tough, but I heard they like hot
steaming nuts. What? Get some nuts from the vendors and bring them back to the guards
before they get cold. Here comes the meltdown. No, I just- I gotta get that lift better
because I'm doing it too early or too late. It's like that little window.
All right, let's go. Getting nuts from- I get nuts for life. What? I don't understand.
Here. No, I have to keep getting them.
Hurry. Where's this guard? Guard up here? Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
There's a security guard this way. I have to put the angle up.
What's with this place and nuts? You guys have anything else to talk about here?
Yeah, we just fucking love nuts in New York. Get special and then nut bust inside the building.
Wait. Okay, I got a special. Nut bust. Can I even get back in? Oh, it's in the building?
Sure, you can make that trick even better. It's the rocket ship.
Create a trick. Welcome. In Tony Hawk Underground, you can create your own tricks.
The trick timeline shows the components of the trick you just landed.
Tweak it or make a whole new trick and map it to your skater. Let's go. Front flip spin.
Okay. All right. Point five seconds seems pretty good. Okay. And then right after that,
I want a new trick. Slow, you go into this slow motion, more rotation. So just do like 6,000
front flips in like three seconds. In two seconds. Yeah, hold on. Get rid of this.
Uh, rotation. Roll. The spin. All right. Wait, wait, wait. Okay. No, no, no. I want it to be.
Okay. One more. Two or three more of these. This is just a Sonic the Hedgehog card.
Did you sound? Yeah.
No, I'm not doing the fart sound, guys.
Special. Okay. I can't even. What's happening in here?
This is what happens when you attach 10 thrusters to somebody in a Garry's Mod multiplayer game.
No, no, no, no, no. No, it's too much. Can't even see what's going on. No. How do I get back?
I don't delete it. I want another one of those super spins.
Well, what's happening at the end? Wait, hold on. What about this?
That's good. All right. That's good. Done. Is it saved? More sounds.
I can only have three sounds. You get what you want. Okay. Trick done. Name the trick.
Preview trick. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I've accidentally done this so many times. I can't
put it on X. It's got to be way quicker than that. How long is it? Two seconds?
Let me see if I can even do this. I don't think it's possible to land. It's got to be faster.
Holy shit, I just did it. Oh, no. This whole playthrough just got ruined. Rename it. Name
trick. Hyper flush. Hyper drain. Hyper flush. The drain. The drain.
Okay. This is on a kick flip. This replaced kick flip. The royal flush.
This whole playthrough just got destroyed because now I'm just going to make
fucked up tricks for every move and never going to be able to finish the game.
The royal flush. Save the trick. Royal flush. Okay.
It's got to be. Hold on. Back to editor. Okay. Let's try that. Use it.
Add a scream. There's no scream.
There is no scream, guys.
All right. We got it. Keep this. Create a trick. Once kept, a credit trick can be permanently
mapped to your skater from the tricks menu. Yes. Okay. Let's create a new trick.
Holdable.
Air walk. Oh, that's pretty sick.
Hold on. What else we got? All right. We're going to do air walk.
Air walk is going to be long. We're just going to stick our legs out. Make it fall three seconds.
Bang. Is it not holdable? No. So in the middle of this, boom. Right when the foot comes out,
you can do this. Flip trick. You don't have any room. What? Oh, can't do it for that long.
All right. Right when the foot comes out, boom. Boom. New part. Gotta be quicker than that.
Bang. Foot comes out into a
boom. Hold on. Wait. Check this out.
Hold on. Oh, I can't. I can't. I can't do it.
No, never mind. Not a flip trick.
Let's see. When there's a rotation, like spinning. Ooh, that's kind of cool.
That's also pretty cool. That's pretty cool too.
Ooh, that's tricky.
No, no. I don't like it. Something else. Other. Well, hand stand.
What is a Casper? Truck stand. The faction.
You just play the guitar.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Another one. Oh, I can only have three sounds. All right. Let's check it out.
What? Why is it playing?
It already has a sound effect built into it.
It already has a sound effect. Get this fucking thing out of here.
What is this? Hold the American flag. Slam bam. All right. This is a fall joke. I like this.
It's got to be a little backwards. You're going to have backwards that you bounce off. No,
you're going to bounce back. Okay. It's too long. Three seconds is a long time.
Anything more than two seconds is almost impossible without huge air.
Okay. One second should be all right. And then we'll go to other as well. What else we got?
Handstand. Handstand and then falling off the board. Do it again, but backwards. Let's cheer.
Anything ending in the fall. This is going to fuck me up because I'm going to think I fell off
the board. Slap. It's like I'm getting hit with projectiles. All right. Yeah. This is the people
are throwing objects at me trick. You got it. How does it look? I like it. That's good. A little
bit shorter. Yeah. That's a wall. I've lost control. Yep. Right there. Yeah. Okay. So somebody
throws a rock at me. Hits me right in the chest. Bang. I'm losing control. Falling off the board.
Yeah. I have to add like a, I have to add the moan because it's like,
let me edit this. Hold on.
I actually kind of like it a little longer. It's got to, it's got to flow animation wise
a little bit longer. What does it actually end if you do it back here?
Yeah. It's going to be the full fall.
Yeah. Cause then you get back up a little bit further out of the start,
a little bit further, I think. Let's see. Maybe further. No, I actually like it.
Like taking out his legs. Actually. Yeah. That's much better. Okay. Let's take a look at the slap.
What the fuck am I doing this like this? All right. That's fine.
We could pull. I like, I like how it rips his arm kind of back a little. There we go.
Okay. Now we have to add, oh, okay. So that's bang right there.
And then there has to, is it like a crashing sound?
Yeah. Okay. That actually, I don't think I want that there.
Do a fart at the land. You guys are killing me with the fart shit.
Let's test it.
I don't think it's going to work out.
Oh, my knee. What?
No, that's too, I, this has to be way shorter than that.
No, no way. It's going to be way shorter.
Hey. Oh, it's cause it's too full seconds. That's way too long.
Now that's one and a half seconds.
Okay. That's right.
Okay.
Why is the sound not playing?
Just got him shorter. It's still too long. I think I have to remove the slap.
Make it a grind. Can I do that?
Rotation grab flip special. How do I do that? How do I, I can't make it a grind.
No, I can't. Oh, well. All right. Let's try that.
Can I please get rid of the fart sound? Can I get rid of the fart? This is turning into
another crack game. Okay. Let's go.
I'm ready. Edit tricks, edit tricks, grab tricks. So right and B is indie, sniffy right now.
We're going to make it a royal flush. Is it a grab trick? Is the, wait, is the royal flush
a grab trick or is it a kickflip? Wait, I need, I need to get rid of the, I need to get rid of
Oh, I need to be, it has to be special. It doesn't matter. All right. Well then I'll,
I don't want it to be, I want indie. All right. What we got down at down, down B is going to be
the one, the royal flush. And then the other one's a kickflip. So it's a flip trick.
We'll just make that be left, left or whoops. Okay.
So now, are we just back out?
Let's see if I got it right.
I'm never going to be able to do that again.
No way. In any in-game scenario.
Music's so loud.
All right. I'm ready to get back into the game.
Working as intended. Let's view goals. What we got. Gap the burning taxi.
I did it. So, wait, did I not do it? Check out that taxi. The fire's starting to rage.
You got it. Don't show them that one. It's kind of hard to do this. Turn the fucking music up.
Louder, louder, louder. Hold on. Hold on. Just wait. No, the music is fine. Everyone,
look at all these people saying no. I can't do this nose grab. I'm doing up and B's.
Why is it not? Well, this one's a, this is a goal. Restart it. Dude, one guy, one guy, one guy,
one guy. Dude, come on, dude. One guy, one guy. This song is so good. One guy. This song is so bad.
One guy. I think this song is just right. One guy. I can't, all right, I cannot make it across.
I have to just go across and do the big one. It's too hard to jump it and do anything else.
It's bad. There you go. I can't even do it. It's not possible. I don't have enough jump right now.
I think this song is a cactus. One guy. But it's a pop puppet. Yeah.
What do you think you're doing? Hey, man. I got the video you sent me. Wow. You got style. You
are on the team. You're definitely on the team. I'm going to find a way to get you down to the
Tampa Am Contest. Tampa? What? That would be insane. But I have like three bucks to my name.
Why do I have yellow gloves on? Don't matter, man. I'll tell you what. You run some errands
for me in New York and I'll floor you my vintage bus for the trip. Now tell me what you want to
ride and I'll send you all the free gear you need for the event, dude. I got a new outfit.
Free gear from Peralta is now available in Skate Shop. You can now return to the Skate Shop from
the Edit Skater menu. Dex. Oh, hold on. Almost. All right. So I do the Almond Joy.
Baker. I think I like Almond Joy. Sorry. Yeah, I like the Almond Joy one. Grip tape.
Grip tape. Solid. This just looks like something fucked up. I like it.
Oh, like the molten lava one. Yep. Grip tape color. Green. Grip tape froze. No, I'm a pro.
Oh, it has to be black, right? All right, that's fine. That looks good. Wheel color.
That like bright blue. I just did poker table green. No, I didn't. Whatever. Astro turf green.
Bovine Ernie. That's a boomer board. Whatever. Favorites for a ride. Hello, you.
I am not going to turn it up. It's in a perfect spot.
And restaurant. Okay, no comply. Five times. How do I even pop that up? Good. You'll learn
over an obstacle. Apply this technique versus new will be delicious. No comply. Manual and then
manual and then trick out manual. No comply onto the no comply into a manual on the bench
and flick your gut. Soon we will fuse the boneless into modern music but first you must practice.
Remember, the boneless will give you extra height and distance. Boneless.
This one would be almost impossible to jump over. You can jump over with a boneless.
It's a simple task. This will be the ultimate fusion of new and old. Get some speed and
boneless off the lip of this quarter pipe. This should give you enough air to do a huge
vertric. Accomplishing this will bring boneless pizza. Boneless off the cube.
Boneless into a grind. Another grind. Manual and then off that into a royal flush.
People that are just showing up for the first time that haven't been watching the stream
are randomly going to see that trick and it's they're going to be blinking their eyes going
what how how is that in the game? Man, damn kids, I was supposed to have some new decks
delivered to the sponsors by the start of the show. I just did. You can get them back in time
it'd really save our ass. Okay, find the punks who stole the decks. It's not gonna work.
Where are the punks? Oh, I found a punk. Wink. Steal a deck and get away with it.
Where'd he go? Oh, two punks. I just went through the hoop for any three more punks.
What is that guy over here? I saw his indicator. Oh, you're out. Oh, you. Okay. I just accidentally
got one. He says we can borrow his old hippie bus and hit the road. He's accumulating wink debt.
Going to Tampa. Check. We apparently didn't make it to Tampa, I guess. I'm assuming.
One bad bumper sticker. Oh, big mistake, you punks. Oh, that was horrible.
Aren't you white meat supposed to be out fighting real crime? Like figuring out where that missing
sprinkled donut went. Oh, that's real funny, smart ass. Kiss your little roller skating contest.
Goodbye. That is unless your buddy here wants to do us some favors.
I got the two backpacks on his knees. All right, chapter seven with syrup or jelly.
Just, oh, Tampa's cool. Wait, what's this? We just got a very rare T-pose, by the way.
Hey, get special. They do a yeah right manual through the cones down the Pro Bowl.
Special and do a yeah right manual through the cones.
Uh, that's get special. Okay, let's go. Get special. I'm doing yeah, right through the cone.
What? Now that you got that down, get special, then skip this car. You suck.
Then do a yeah, right through the cone. Oh yeah, you only get one chance. I don't choke it.
One chance. Get special. Don't mess it up, you goof. Okay, now get special and then
it's the car and then yeah, right through the cones. Wait, will I just get special by doing this?
Yeah, right. It's next turn. Yeah, just rush. That's it. That's how I think that's my,
you might not be getting up from that one. Oh, that hurts. You're dead. That kills you.
That actually, I think that actually kills you. All this individual stickers everywhere.
Jump into the wall at an angle, then jump while wall riding to Wally and access hard
to reach high spots. Jump while we're on. Okay, wall ride, jump while wall riding.
Get all the stickers. Cool. There's one, here comes two. Gonna get a better line here.
Okay, I see another sticker. More back here. What's that? Wait, what the fuck was
I just looking at? I don't know. It was weird. Need more stickers. Sticker, sticker. There's two
more. Is that a sticker? No. This one. One more. What's that up there? Look at that.
Come on. Where's the final sticker? No. Where's the last sticker? Shit. I don't think I'm gonna
find it. Right over here. Rats. Anyone just come to the stream? Like, anybody just like,
just kind of show up right now? Welcome to the stream. Anyone that just showed up for Tony Hawk?
Pretty fun game. It's a pretty good game. All right, let's see. What else can we do here?
Remove all the stickers. Get the best donuts. We'll do this one.
Why don't you put yourself to some use? Go get some donuts for me and my fellow officers.
Twelve donuts. Okay, let's go like this. Grab here, up there. Not enough momentum. Two, three.
Okay, there's another one right here. Oh, there's a big line. Oh, that hurt. I'm trying to go over
it. Just grab it. Okay. Oh, look at this. Well, I didn't press the button fast enough.
All right, what do you got? A mission for me? Oh, the stickers. Okay, let's get it.
There's one up there. One behind the new girl's place. One on the wall back here.
One over here. And this one. Back here, right? No. Oh, I think it's the one I didn't get last time.
Did I get this one last time? I don't think so. I think I did. One right here. Okay, there's one more.
It has to be down here. That's it. Those aren't stickers. I have no idea where it is. This way.
Oh, I'm missing this one every time.
Okay, Lapid doesn't know. No, I don't. Every Tony Hawk game, I was always so awful with the
collect-the-thing. I just skipped every single one of them. Is there one down here? Fuck,
it's right there. Okay, right there. I didn't get that one. All right. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. Let's go. Come on, I need to get to the last two. All right, where's the script club place?
He didn't know. He doesn't know. He doesn't know. Don't tell him. Nobody tell him.
Hey, anybody just showing up for the first time? What else we got? Skateboarding bandit
and help the private eyes. Let's do skateboarding bandit. Someone has just robbed the bank and is
escaping up there through the skyway. If you follow the drop cache, it should lead you right to him.
Okay. Oh, damn. Let's do it again. Oh, I did a cool move there. Nailed. Am I not going? Oh,
I only have five seconds. Okay, right. Jesus. Holy shit. This is fast. Did I get it? Okay,
so if I jump off this, I go off to the left. I don't know why that happens. The way my thumb
is pressing on, you know what I'm saying? The way my thumb's pressing, it just always pushes me to
the top left. That's not helping either. Damn it. See what I'm talking about? Like I just like top
left because just the way that my hand naturally presses up, it just goes up to the top left.
How did I fail that?
Is he high right now? No, I just... It's hard to do that.
Jed. No! There's Jed! No! There's the other Jed sign. Jed. Jed? Jed? That's screen tearing though.
Jed. There's the Jed. Oh, I gotta... Come on.
Ditch the car. Why is there a lose the cops thing? Okay.
I want to rock and roll. All right. Wait, is this like... This is not the actual song.
It's a live version. How is driving in a circle around the same block losing the cops?
Not what happened. This is not... Why would the third guy go over? The third guy...
You just watched two of us drive into the water and you're going to do it too or whatever.
Nice driving. Now let's get out of here.
Save it. Tampa AM 2004 check in.
AKA now you're under arrest for fucking assaulting somebody. You just don't... No,
you just slapped somebody. You don't... You slapped him in the fucking face.
Dude, look, I'll sign up now. I told you the list is full.
Feel free to watch from the bleachers though. Yo Thomasville, what's up street dog? You been
shrouded in any 10 story rails with the old magic stunt wood? Yeah, I'm sorry about this. But
anyway, I gotta go skate. I mean, this could be my big break and who knows? Maybe you could
impress a pro or something to get into. This is going to be a double cross. Yeah.
He's going to be mean to me and shit and he's going to be like, you were always a loser.
You were always nothing and I'm going to have to beat him in the final.
You skate pretty well kid. There's a couple of things I want to see you do before you're ready
for the Tampa AM. First, land a trick with a spin. I'm going to be okay with this because I spin
every time I do anything. Land a trick with at least a 540 and a revert. That's cool. I need
any more pros. I like this place. Tampa's cool. Can't get in. So is there a reason why?
I guess maybe there is a reason why, but I just don't like to admit it or something.
Why has there never been another skating game like this?
Just kind of fall out of popular culture and people just didn't really care anymore or something.
All right, let's get out of here. Pretty much. Didn't Tony Hawk make a new game
this year or last year? It was like an iPad game or something.
Was it any good? Really bad. It was very bad. Let's see what we got here. Party boat skate tricks.
Welcome to Wet Beaver's party boat. Bam. This party is boring as hell.
Let's liven it up with some skating. Nail the tricks I yell out.
He'll flip. Of course, the same person is getting hurt every time.
You're leaning too far in, man. I'm hitting you in the face every time I go up.
It's like giving me anxiety. I'm the same guy. Don't stand in the way. Oh, boy. I'm telling you.
It's me hitting the people is what's freaking me out. I have to turn the volume off.
Oh, he used to cheat code. Reminding me of my past meltdowns.
All right, let's go skate some spots around Tampa. Let's see if you can beat my combos
while you're at it. Maybe. Beat Andrew's three best combos. What is that? That's pretty wild.
What combo, Andrew? Andrew, I just destroyed your combo.
Again, let's do it again, Andrew. Well, I got to do it in a row. I just didn't realize where I was.
No, stop. OK, next one. Now, this is the one on the roof. Jump over it and land.
It's going to go like this. Oh, fuck. No, fell off. Shit. All right. Fancy. What?
This is like a ball jump. It's a molding stream in the making. No, this is the nature of Tony Hawkman.
All right, let's get this one. Motherfucker. Streamer, look inside yourself. Wall plant combo.
I bet you can't wall plant off the drawbridge to wall. Here's where I learned how to do it straight
into a wall and hit this jump straight into a wall and hit this then manual all the way down
through the cones in one combo. Hurry up. There's some balance here. Oh, I got points.
Let's see if you can impress him by nailing the tricks I yell out. And for variety,
I'm going to throw in Tony Hawk. I wonder what he's going to say. Hey, man, nice work over there on
those grinds. You did such a good job. I'm going to make sure I give the word and that you can do
that. And then you can do the competition in Tampa.
Flip. 540 flip. He'll flip. He'll flip. I'm not doing it. He'll flip. He'll flip. What? He'll flip.
He'll flip. He'll flip. He'll flip. Oh, a 540. Whoops. I didn't even try to do it. I didn't even
try. No, I need to do an Indy. Why am I doing an air walk? Hey, you skate pretty well. Let's see
if you can hang with me. It's because of the Xbox buttons, the left and right. Here he is. Let's
see if you can hang with me. Beat Tony's score. I can't win this. That's the legendary Tony Hawk.
Whoa. What do you call those moves, man? Oh, I'm just destroying him.
Carrillo. Oh, this game is so fucking fun.
All right. I beat the shit out of him. He just doesn't even stand a chance.
Eric did better than Tony Hawk.
For the Tampa and talk about a surprise attack. If you stay on your board tomorrow,
you'll walk away with the contest. I can't. It's full. I worked so hard to get a sponsorship
from Stacy Peralta. Stacy Peralta? I know that dude. He was my first sponsor too, back in the 80s.
Is he still into yoga? That's one weird dude. But cool as they come. Look, I can't make any
guarantees, but I'll talk to the guys at the contest. Just show up tomorrow. This was way
better than I thought it was going to be acting wise. It was very good. That was actually just,
that was very natural. Tony Hawk, like actually naturally good actor. Well, pretty good.
By the way, if Tony Hawk can't get you into a skating competition, then no one can.
I don't think the president can like executive order get you in if Tony Hawk can't.
That was good. Got a tight street comp going on. Best two out of three runs. Stay inside on the
street course. Tight street comp going on. Best two out of three. Let's go. Oops.
91 to 88. All right. 90. Best step two out of three. That one, sorry.
43,000. What is that? 95? Yeah. All right. 90. 93. Rob. I don't like that place no more.
Now what? Talk to Afro Gym. There's some cool stuff on this here roof to trick on.
Climb up there and I'll meet you. You just have to jump up, grab on, and pull yourself up.
All the way up to the ladder. Hey, I just showed up. What is with the bar tricks?
I'm so glad. I'm so happy. That makes me so happy. Okay. Try and beat my high score. Stay on the
rooftops. Oh, that's not a roof? How's that not a rooftop? Okay. Take it easy. Too easy to get too
much momentum and fly off. I have two minutes. I know everyone's going to call me a cheeseball
for doing this, but that's fine. Oh, that's a broken arm.
9,000. All right. All right. I need like, I just need to kick flip in front like one or twice.
You fucking cheeseball.
With the lowest score gets eliminated. You're in a big combo. Don't worry. Those points count
toward your score as long as you don't fail. Last two skaters advance. Every 30 seconds,
the skater with the lowest score gets eliminated. Sorry, guys. You're dealing with a fucking pro.
Dude, I have 31. Wait, I have 31,000 points. How am I out of the competition?
What? I'm not. I mean, what? How am I not in first place?
Guys, best trick competition. I'm so confused. Well, I have 48,000 points,
but I'm not even on the list. Best trick pop to advance. All right. Well, aren't we all just in
here every 30 seconds to eliminate somebody. So why am I not on the list?
Why am I, why do I have a small brain? You see your own score. Yeah, but I mean, why wouldn't
it be on the, it told me like, oh, you're out of the competition area. I'm like, oh, I didn't know.
I'm sorry. So I have 44,000 points. I'm in first place. Okay. So I can't really lose
sloppily doubling everybody's point. 30 seconds. All right. All right. Let's go.
Get into some good here. Good line. Fuck. Sorry. Just me and Eric. Biggest score.
Trying to do the special. Choke, choke, choke.
Revert and manual. I do, I do manuals as much as I can, but like the revert into the manual,
you'd like revert manual. It's a brain kind of fucking freezes up.
Five seconds and let me talk to the damn kid. I gotta give it to you. That run was bullshit.
No, in a good way though. I'm gonna have to put you on element bottom line.
Oh, I'm on element. All the major deck companies are after you. Time to check out some videos to
see which sponsor best fits your style. The choice is yours. Birdhouse, Sean White,
and then the Olympian. What is a snowboarder? Holy shit. He's skated. Wow. Vinny Vegas.
Bam Margera. Bam Margera. Here's the thing about Bam Margera. The reason why half of
us think anything is funny is because of Bam Margera. Bam invented comedy, but that,
that like style of like alternative comedy, like Jackass. They're like Johnny Knoxville.
Those guys were just, they were nuts. That was pretty, that was horribly morbid. Holy shit.
I don't think I want to join the life sucks gang. There's no skateboard there.
All right. I like this. All right. Okay. I kind of liked that one because that was just like,
that was pretty funny. I kind of like, yeah, right. Pretty good. This game is what made me
want to be a graphics artist. I think like the thing about skateboarding, skateboarding in like
the mid nineties into the early two thousands influenced so many random other cultures that
have like counter cultures that moved in a million different places. It's spread out everywhere.
Fashion, graphic design, videos, making funny videos, videos, skateboarding groups would make
skits and shit. That's what I'm talking about. I'm talking about like Bam Margera and those guys
are some of the reasons why we have to have the shit that we think is funny. It's funny because
they like did the skits. It influenced so many things that you can't even wrap your brain around.
All right. For a second, I thought this had John Birdhouse, John Element, John Flip, John Girl,
John Zero. This is going to be tough. All right. I like the fun editing in Girl. We just had a
bunch of subs coming in though. No, we didn't. It was a ton of money. King of Troll gets 10,000
bits, a hundred bucks. Put this forward something nice to him. I will. Thanks to the huge,
ridiculous amount of money. I like the, as King of Troll, 10. Thank you. It's either going to be
Girl or, that's going to be Girl. Welcome to Girl. Gear up and then you'll be flowing out to San
Diego to meet the rest of your team. All right. Let's gear up. I like my Almond Joy. It's a real
color. I like Almond Joy. No, I can't. It's my board. I can't get rid of it. That's your sponsor.
Hey, what's up? You get in from the airport? Okay. Yeah. Are you Todd? Hey, I want to sponsor,
but I'm not going to put any of your stuff on. I got to finish this meal before I go out to eat.
So here's my skateboarding 101 spiel. The more coverage you get, the more crazy tricks you land,
the more tours and free gear for you. Okay. Just push yourself, show us your Skittles and everything
is cool. Skittles. Skills. Skittles mean skills. What are you from Idaho? Hey, look, the film is
here to shoot some other guys. Go piggyback with them and get some coverage. All right. Look at
those bit maps, spaghetti, french fries. It looks so good. All right. Prove yourself worthy.
All right. Your HUD changes too. That's cool. Rare T-pose study. We got. What do we got to do
for coverage these days? There's one that nobody will volunteer for. There's a bunch of flower boxes
up on that sketchy ledge and they want a picture of one of us grinding some of them down. Okay.
You're a newbie. You're up, newbie. All right. So grind the boxes. Did I screw it up? Did I mess
it up? Yes, I did. Oh boy. Okay. Did I get them all? Oh, that's tricky. This is tough. All right.
Oh, I missed one. I think I can get back up there. Right here. Where was it? No, you got to get it in
one go. You got to get it in one go. Oops. Floppy, but sloppy. What happened there? That was lame.
No, it's lame maybe. Not the job done. Yes. What do you mean timing? That's the guy from American
Dead. That's the boyfriend. All right. Let's do this. Let me see something basic for starters.
Yes. Yes. That's Jeff from American Dead. Double kickflip over the stairs. It needs to be faster
than that. There we go. Jeff, I did a triple kickflip. You can use it. Why can I not hit
this? Bang, bang. Bang, bang. Jeff, you got film in that camera? Double impossible over the stairs.
That was pretty cool. What's that called? Impossible? Come on. Stop doing that. Stop
doing the worst move. I don't even have special. Please wake up. You're unconscious.
Jeremy, please. Wake up. What are you doing? All right. Air out the atrium. All right. Here it is.
They want pictures of you blasting some big grab airs. Above us is a nice open gap over the front
of this atrium. It's perfect for these photos. Work up speed back and forth and do the grabs that I
tell you. Use a boneless to jump higher if you need to. Melon over the gap.
I got it, right? That wasn't it? Oh, I get it. I just felt like that was a melon. That was a melon.
Okay, I'll go out of the room. Hold on. That was a melon. How was that? That's not the gap.
I don't understand. I have to hit the gap?
How was that any different? I don't understand. Actually, let's take break number one. Let's take
a full break. I'm going to get some water. It's been three and a half hours. First break of the
night. I am back. I got myself a sprite on the rocks. Joe Otto? He's not even in the room anymore.
How's Otto after the surgery? He is fully healed. Stitches have been removed. He is back to 100%
normal. He's good to go. He's healed up very nicely. All right. Something a little tougher over the gap.
It's stiffy. I need some air. Let's get some air from here. Here we go. This will be it.
Just watch. I'm going to lose this twice.
Oh, shit. I'm so bad at this.
Oh, that was it.
That was it. I did it.
Oh, kid. You've got serious skills. How about another tough one over? Go for it.
This is rocket air over the gap.
I was not even in range of the photo. Crazy. You're unstoppable. They just want one more shot.
Let me see something really big over it. We're done here. One foot tail grab.
Six, and I still can't let them. All right, newbie. You want comfort. You gotta get creative.
Nail this run. Your picture will be in a magazine ad for sure. All right. I'll call out the tricks
and the team photographer will snap the photos. A really long spear or lance. How do you hold that?
I feel like that thing would turn. You know when we have a tape measure out too far and the thing
just goes to shit when it's out like that. I feel like that's impossible to hold and throw.
You just worry about busting them over the spine transfer on the statue.
Rock and roll, kid. Busting them over the spine transfer.
All right, I see. You get this L&R over the statue.
Cool. Bring it back. I get it. I get it. Tail grab over the statue.
Sloppy, but I did it. You want a bunch of kickflips. Sure, I can do that. No, I can't.
L, R, up, and X. It's like scratch your head, rub your face. Hold down X,
L, R, and then we let go of A, up, R. It's like a lot of my brain's processes.
Good. Try to do one at a time. Indie, then go over the statue. Melon.
Technically got it. Well, I'm going to make a joke or I'm going to drop out of high school.
Sorry, you're not going to be getting your diploma.
I don't like this one. I got to do two tricks in a row.
What do we got? Indie. Slow down, slow down, slow down. Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Okay, thank god it's a bunch of impossible in a row.
Kickflip. What the fuck was that? What? I didn't even want to do that, man.
Look at all these tricks. This might be it. I'm not going to get it. No more grab moves.
Make a joke. No, how many of you guys are going to drop out of high school if I don't make a joke
in 10 minutes? Stay in school for fuck's sake. But I graduated. Well, that's good.
Don't drop out of school because I didn't make a joke. All right. That first is just fucking with
me. Indie. No, do it again. Does that count? Not really. No grabs. No, just turn around and do it.
Okay, nose grab, heel flip. It wasn't a nose grab. Why? I just did up and B.
That's it. That one was hard. Real wink. Every day we get darker and darker.
What was the mission that the person said? If I do it within four tries, they'll give me like
a hundred dollars. It's like an impossible mission that they would like. This mission
sucks. You're going to hate it. But if you do it within four tries, I'll give you a hundred bucks.
Which one was it? It was like the spot, like the cool spot one, the cool spot or something.
Big apple spot challenge. Yeah. Okay. The big apple spot challenge. If I beat that within four
tries, they'll give me a hundred dollars. Nobody said that. Wow. Wow. Wow. Why would I even know
what that is? The cool, the apple, big apple spot. Man, we need to get some flyers thrown around
for this party. I said, I know it. Okay. I said I would throw up a cheese steak on my keyboard,
not give you a hundred dollars. I said nothing about a hundred dollars. You fucking greedy streamer.
Well, hold on a minute. Are you eating a cheese steak right now? Because that would make you a
liar if I did it within four tries. Like, did you, are you eating a cheese steak today?
Slap these flies around by doing wall plants. Okay. Cool. You'll see the spots where we want
to put up. What the fuck? I'm literally eating a cheese steak. Well, you don't, but you don't
have to throw it up onto your keyboard if I do it in four tries. Hold on a minute. He has a green
shirt on. Fuck. Nevermind. Oh, he got a friend. Don't just restart. It's fine. You don't have to
restart every time. What is he pretending? Stop pretending. There's no way this is not,
there's no way this guy's not pretending right now. There's two more. One here.
Great Marie's dumb. Great Marie's dumb. Dumb. Dumb. Dumb. Dumb. Dumb. I'm not dumb. You're dumb.
I'm not dumb. You're dumb. What do you got? The band that's playing your party. We stopped to get
some grub and while we were out some joker snaked our instruments. He's killing his streaming career.
Can you help us find him? Otherwise, we can't play for you guys.
All right, get the instruments. They're probably gonna be on a line here.
I was gonna guess. I'd be like, yeah, there's one.
Upset. Brums. I see a microphone.
I see. Let's go this way. There's a place where everyone can be happy.
Isn't the most beautiful place in the whole wide fucking world. That's the best song.
Oh, that's gonna be actually tricky to get to. Climb it. Really? The one place that hurts
is your knee. Those must be inflatable then. Get up in the chat. What's up, dude?
Grab that gardener's cart. Find a few ladies. Do whatever it takes to get them back here.
Don't be slacking. If you don't hurry up, this party's gonna be over before it really starts.
Tony, let me do some consulting work for you. I love these games and as you can see,
I get 20 to 30,000 points when I get in a line so I know the game.
Maybe if you show me how handy you are with that skateboard, I'll come to your party.
How about showing me a combo? You want to say a combo? Show me a combo. How's that?
Shit. Did you just hit my car? Stay right there. I'll do it. My face is a Jehovah.
Coming to the party. Wait, pick up girls for the party. I can only have one person in this car.
Well, she'd go anywhere. I'm not that easy. If you want me to go to your party,
you're gonna have to show me more. How about some of those neat freestyle tricks?
What do you mean freestyle tricks? Start manually and show me some tricks.
You're asking a lot in a row.
Okay, who cares? I'm just gonna go this way.
Be an X. That's a weird combo to do. It's hard. Your hands can't do that.
I have to be in front of you? Why can't you just walk with me?
I'm doing it. Look.
Damn it. This is fucking tricky.
Bill Emanuel, you motherfucker.
Are you happy? All right, let's go.
Make room and I'll come to the party.
Everybody good? I thought it was a ramp.
NA navigation.
Whoa, I just like this. What the fuck did I just do?
All right, do I have to be in front of you? Let me see. No, good. Car hop. Oh, don't reset.
No, don't flush her. What I Xbox 360.
I'm coming to your party. Even if I do have to write in that thing. Let's go.
Jerma looks like the mom from Dexter's lab. Yeah. Yeah, kind of. Kind of. Whatever.
If I flip this thing, I don't hurt anybody. All right, we got a full house.
Hey, I snuck out of the party and hooked up some real fun. What does that mean?
I snaked one of those cards from behind the epitheter. Okay. And some of the other guys
set up a little racetrack for us. See if you can beat my best lap. In the car?
It's going to take some skittles as that dork Todd likes to put it.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go, my dork. Beat Jordan's best lap. This arrow is not helping me.
It counts. Hit it.
You want to save? Yes.
SpongeBob driving test. What's wrong with me?
There you are. Hey, come on. It's two in the afternoon and you're still asleep.
You got to skate the demo at three. You know what demo? The team demo. Come on. I want you
to get the new guy. Yeah, I do. I look like, look, I look like it's Dexter. Dexter character.
You're on the team. It's like Dexter's older cousin. That's cool. I can see how busy you've been.
Oh, you guys know each other? Anyway, why don't you find the rest of the team? They scattered
after the party. I'll see you guys at the demo after I chow down. All right. So yeah,
new friend became enemy. Good thing they're all right here.
Other than you and me, the rest of the guys on the team kind of got lost or wandered off.
Mm hmm. You need to round him up. Why distract Todd? Or we're going to have to cancel the demo.
All right, the team members. Do they have an indicator or they're just lying around?
Do they have a green indicator? Good one. What? Yeah, they do have an indicator. Hey, get over here.
You're going to miss the demo, man. Come on. It's going to be some kind of record.
I'm just like skating around. Yeah, I'm just having fun. I shouldn't be doing that. I need
to go find these guys. No fun allowed. Get up there.
I got to go up and around this whole thing. Oh, shit. Do I actually have to do this?
Am I going to climb it? I don't think I can climb it anywhere.
You got to grind it. Oh, wait, there's a pipe here.
I know you want to make move, my son. You best take a second look.
You're going to get some super here.
I don't think it's going to be enough.
I got to go the other way. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Get up. All right, I got it.
I'm trying to snatch it after the laughter won't cease from the comparison. I dare you, son.
Stupid.
Stop having fun.
All right. Let me get this guy first. Oh, I went by him.
Blame, blame, blame, blame, blame, dude, blame, blame.
Blame.
I mean, this is pretty sick. I have to do it.
All right.
OK, I need three more.
I'm here. I think I'll find you.
Somebody up here, right?
Where are you?
No, but again, where are you?
No.
Damn it. Where are these other three people?
You in here?
No, nobody in here. I'm not going to do it.
Somebody there.
That's only one. You're also a fucking mess.
All right. I remember this one. Sorry.
Apparently, I got them. These other two hidden fucking people.
All right. Come on. One more. One more.
Where's the last one? I need one more guy.
Come on. 13 seconds. Oh, my God.
I never found this guy.
Hide in a bush. All right. Let's go.
Let's get him. I did find him, though.
That's true. I did. I did find him.
Two. Three is that way.
Got to get up here and grind it.
It's not what I wanted to do.
What are you, a dumb person?
Okay. Two more.
There was somebody in this building over here.
Stop. And where is the other one?
I got three minutes at most to find him.
All right. Any doctors in chat?
Are there any doctors in here?
All right. What does it mean when my entire face is itchy?
They never stop. And I don't have any allergies.
What does that mean?
Every three to four minutes, I have an itchy spot somewhere on my face.
What does that mean? My man's dry.
No, no, no. No, I'm not a moisturizer.
Looks like we got our cart back.
And there's some free skateboards on the back.
How nice of you punks to leave these here for us after you stole our cart in the first place.
Have a nice day.
What do we do?
Just hitch for 60 seconds.
Oh, that doesn't seem fair.
All right. It's like Temple Run.
That hurt. Mobile gaming streamer.
And then I played Temple Run maybe once.
But that's what this mechanic is.
This is not even me doing this.
This guy's just running over everybody he's at work with.
No, don't. I'm so close.
Just get over here.
Come here.
No, stop. Wait, wait for me.
What was that move? What was that guy doing?
Come on. I'm so close.
My God. I can't believe it.
All right. That was stupid.
I'm going so fast right now.
You got to pay attention to the bar and the ring.
I'll give you fucking 60 bucks if you can beat this first try.
Right, Gerber?
No. Will you really?
Nope. I'm just going to throw up a ham sandwich on my keyboard or something.
Get it. Don't let go.
Okay. It's coming down here, right?
Okay. View goals. The only public one or two left, right?
Breeze the crowd. Find more kids.
I love the Sonic the Hedgehog actor.
That people do.
That'll itch my fucking like rotten face.
Ready? Three, two, one. Let's go.
It's time for you guys. It's time for you to pay.
Anyway, if you're as good as they say you are,
then do whatever grind I tell you to up on that raised bar.
Sure. Grind the bar.
Nosebleed. A double nosebleed.
All right, let's do it. Can I switch it up?
Ooh. 50-50. Nice.
Re-50-50 is going to noseblunt.
He's instantly just retrying every single failure.
Yeah, that's what you do.
I thought you got it.
You got it because it's not clean in your brain and you don't want to do it.
Like for instance, I would have just restarted right there,
but I might still be able to do it.
Go faster.
Restart Randy. Restart Randy.
Faster, faster. I'm going as fast as I can.
How is that not fucking Xbox 360 controller?
I got it.
Nose brine.
Good. Good RNG.
Pop-pop.
Good RNG.
Look at that RNG. It's like playing Tetris.
I'll try.
All right, reporter. Take a look at this one.
Get a huge score to impress the media.
Oh, what? You bought that in one combo?
Is that what you wanted?
Get special and press just before the lip.
All right, what do you want to do?
Press right just before lipping on the stage lights.
Is that it? I don't think that's right.
All right, right, right, yeah, that's what I'm trying to do.
Turbo walk. I did it right.
Does that count?
There you go.
Going to Hawaii.
Can you believe it? Hawaii. You must be stoked.
The team usually doesn't bring hams on a trip this big.
And those sketches are awesome. Did you draw them?
No, some artists did. They're the graphics for my new pro model.
Hey, how long were you on the team before you turned pro?
About a year. I just threw down a couple of hammers for the last video
and the response was so crazy. They gave me a pro board.
Who knows? Do the same. Maybe they'll turn you pro in a few years.
What's wrong with your character?
It's a weird glitch that happens in the game sometimes.
This is original Xbox, by the way.
If you get more than two million points in one combo,
the game can kind of fuck up and when it loads the actual combo,
all right, you can mess up your character and shit.
We paid for your trip to Hawaii. Getting sick footage is your job.
Then we're going to premiere our video in Vancouver at the Slam City Jam.
So don't half ass it. We hook up in three days.
I need a rabbit.
Nothing says aloha like getting laid. Collect five lays.
Five lays. Let's get it. Sucks. I wonder if it's failed.
Consoles ever. Like the 360. All right, two more down here.
I took a lot from me to not restart. There's only one more after this.
Over here is the one I didn't get. Didn't get it. Too hard.
Inside that bar. Restart Robert.
Restart Andy. Restart Randy.
This is Tony Hawk. If you are not one thousand percent happy
every tenth of a second, you restart the mission.
Good footage of destruction. Pineapples explode real nice.
Let's see a smash five pineapple stance. Smash five pineapples.
Apparently it wasn't enough. Can't wait.
Popping in here. What else is here?
Jump into Tiki. Tiki. Go to the Tiki.
Jump in Tiki. Where is it?
Hey, first big trip. Paradise is pretty sweet until you smash your face on a banyan tree.
Remember, you're here to skate, not to play official bikini inspector.
Look, why don't you just show me what you got?
Get special, then do a crook's dark slide grind.
Lock on to it long enough to show me you got it.
I say it every time I stop talking. I even do that.
I intentionally jumped off the board and tried to neck myself on the ground.
You can't even do that.
All right, what does he want me to do?
Crook's dark slide. Hold it long enough so I know you're good.
You all right? That wasn't long enough?
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Stop moving me around.
Okay, here we go. Show me a crook's dark slide.
All right, I have to hold it for seven seconds.
Where the hell am I going to do it for seven seconds?
How am I going to do it for that long?
It's going to go very slow. Come on.
Three, two, one.
Oh, I did it.
Restart ready.
Restart, Randy. That's me.
Hey, by the way, anybody just open the screen?
There, there, there, there, there, there, there, there.
Where?
What do you want me to do?
Other way, other way, other way.
I am literally screaming at my fucking monitor.
Where?
God, there, right fucking there.
Oh, my God, I'm screaming.
I'm grabbing my TV and screaming at it.
Oh, that was crazy.
Oh, no, it's bugleberry.
Missed it.
I don't even know what I was supposed to be doing.
I'll try it again.
Okay, here we go.
No, I don't.
That's not me doing the voice.
It doesn't count.
Right there, right there.
I know I'm trying to.
There's like a videotape or something I can grab.
I don't think my oddly is good enough to get it.
Try it again.
Old school icon.
Congratulations.
You've unlocked an old school level.
Venice from Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2.
Okay, I can't restart.
Wedding guest.
There are lots of people getting married around here.
Why don't you try to get some footage with four sets of brides and grooms?
Perform the trick and I'll take the shot.
Some wedding footage?
But I have to do a kick flip.
Why would you want to kick flip somebody doing a kick flip behind your wedding photo?
This is the shit that you tell the guy to photoshop out of the frame.
Wrong couple.
What?
He's aiming camera over here.
Next couple?
Yeah, right.
That's so stupid.
What do they want?
Impossible.
Get it?
Be discreet.
I drowned in the pool.
Okay, where's this other couple?
From here?
Where's this other couple?
Fucking Xbox.
Fucking stupid.
Fucking shittiest console.
Fucking Xbox.
Fucking stupid.
Where's the other couple?
Getting old console bumping and stuff.
Fucking shitty thing.
Some of you new viewers.
I don't know what I'm doing right there, but some of you old viewers know.
Come on, where's the last couple?
What?
I don't have a special.
Why is that even possible?
Okay, where's the last couple?
This other one's over here.
There's one where?
Where?
Right here.
Where's the last one?
Where?
There.
Right there.
Where's the last one?
In the teak.
Oh, that would be rude.
Seriously.
Where the hell are they?
Up, are they?
Come on.
Sometimes you have to just be calm down.
Just calm down.
First wall plant the vending machine three times.
Come on.
Let me adjust my, uh, my fucking bionic boomer vest.
Come on, comfortable?
All right, first wall plant the vending machines three times.
This is some.
This is some stupid secret how to get to the DLC in Bloodborne or Dark Souls.
Here it comes.
Now, acid drop from that platform up there into the pool.
I bet it'll make a big enough splash to make the security guard drop his candy bar into the pool.
Acid drop.
Yeah, acid drop.
Jump out over the pool and press.
Press what?
Press skeezo, press what?
Is he all right?
Um, acid drop.
Jump out over the pool and press L and R for two ladders.
Okay, but I can't even get over there.
All right.
This so fucking finicky being on this legend.
What?
All that just to throw a candy bar on the pool.
I think we're at the, uh, check out this clip from wallows.
Whoa, and that's some heavy footage.
What you got going?
Um, I have some secret spot I just found.
It's pretty gnarly.
I'm going to shoot it later today.
That's cool.
Give me a ring if you need help shooting it.
It'd be like old this guy middle in an animorph into a root vegetable.
I think that's the actual description of what it is.
Lots of places on the island to get some good lip trick.
Find the four lip trick spots.
Lip trick.
And hold a lip trick at each spot long enough for me to get some footage.
Where's the lip trick up here?
Up there.
Is there a half pipe here?
This ain't a half pipe, it is.
I gotta go.
Everything's closed up.
Good.
Thank you.
That one is one over here somewhere that I saw right there.
Do a Russian bonus or riot.
There, I did a.
Invert.
Be happy.
No, you know what?
You know what?
No, you know, ban that guy.
Ban that person.
Unbelievable.
We don't take requests on this channel and I'm gonna put my foot down on that.
No, I do the lip trick.
Quick, somebody redeem a wink.
Here it is.
Nice.
How long can I hold a manual for?
I need to hold it for like 10 seconds.
There it is.
15.
Oh, everybody in the room just ran.
Ooh, the annual plus one to even get 20.
How long was that?
God, manualing is free.
This ditch here is called off the walls.
Manual to the end in one combo.
To make it harder, do a handstand while you're at it.
I know what it's gonna be.
The last one got redeemed an hour ago.
I can see it.
All right, we want to do manual down off the wall.
Hold on.
Manual off the wall and do a handstand.
My hands got sucked in.
Not it?
Manual down off the wall.
Manual down off the walls and do a handstand.
Should I bounce off the wall?
Real wink.
What do I need to hold it for?
Do the whole thing or something?
Manual down off the wall.
Down?
Maybe it wants to be like actually dropped down.
Not it?
Do I have to make it the entire way?
Am I gonna run out of steam here and not even touch the wall?
Oh, and I did it.
That was weird, okay?
I did well.
Impress the girls.
Ladies love the big combos.
See if you can impress three groups of bikini girls by landing big combos in front of each one.
All right.
No, I gotta go.
I've got more people to impress.
But I will, ladies.
I'll leave you with it.
What was that?
I put it between my legs.
Did that not count?
No.
All right, ladies.
Get away.
Don't restart.
I want to impress it.
66.
There it is.
All right.
Make it nice and easy.
Let's get out of this hole.
All right.
You know what?
I'm just gonna manual in front of you guys.
Because this is, I, here we go.
Ready?
Damn it.
Your combos are so big.
Here we go.
I almost just restarted.
I thought she was T-posing.
No, dancing.
Mahalo.
Welcome to the beautiful island of Hawaii.
Please join our skate competition.
Metal competition?
I didn't know I was starting.
That was a big one.
Here we go.
That's what we call saving at the end.
I'm trying so hard.
Fucking way.
This is skateboarding competition, you fucking idiots.
Four.
Am I just standing in the middle of the half pipe?
Having a conversation?
What is wrong with you guys?
I can't restart that.
Bullvine.
Bullvine Ernie.
Or Germer Rumble.
What are the goals?
What did I just do?
No.
View goals.
Wallows combo balls.
Or high lines.
Kill wallows.
You'll have to top trick on the houses, fences, and balconies here in wallows.
More air.
Come on.
Get up there.
It's out of bounds.
It's like trying to get on the fence.
There we go.
That would have been like 200,000.
Five.
Already got this one.
I'm trying to get on the fences and the houses, but it's hard to do it too.
What the fuck is wrong with this?
Do it again.
Yeah, okay.
I got Ollie too.
Four more.
What have I not done?
Which house?
All right.
There's a...
It's up here.
Let me go back this way.
Nope.
Ah.
I'm gonna go five.
Did that count?
Yeah.
What am I even on?
Shit.
I'm trying to find a way to...
Like while you turn...
Like I'm trying to get on the ledge here.
There we go.
That's it.
One more.
What piece of fence did I not touch?
Fence or a piece of a house or something?
Come on.
Oh, come on.
Anything.
Literally anything.
A house.
There it is.
End it.
Dude's fucking naked.
Big bits?
What do you mean big bits?
Where?
Oh, Jesus.
Freakout gave like $150 over the course of like three...
Five different things.
What?
Why?
What is this?
However, the Yanks still had to reply to the Germans.
Otherwise, they'd be wiped out by the shelling.
While trying to find proper response to the letter,
Lieutenant Colonel Kynard said that the McCallum said basically summed up the situation.
So when the Americans finished their letter and sent to the...
This is what it said.
They sent a letter.
It says to the German commander.
Nuts.
The American commander.
That's nuts, right?
I love you and all you do for this community.
But I wanted to ask, is voice acting something you still want to pursue?
Pursue with your little career.
My little career?
I think they...
I don't think they meant that in a negative way, by the way.
I've only been in like three or four different productions.
I think that's what they mean.
Not like, you're like, hey, dude, your career sucks.
It was pretty short.
Yeah, I don't think that's what they mean by that.
No, this is my focus.
And I mean, just take a look at the last four days straight.
Five days straight.
Like, this is what I do.
This is my 100% focus.
This stream, this community, is the priority.
So it's like, I can't...
I don't...
I can't like take time to do auditions and do lines.
And oh, this script has a viewer character that has 250 lines of dialogue.
I...
That's just a ton of time with a director.
And it's just not something I want to focus on.
So voice acting is cool.
It's fun.
And it's really, really interesting stuff.
But this is the focus.
Thanks for your interesting nut message.
I do appreciate the fact that this time you did not...
You did not spam a bunch of codes.
So thank you for that.
And thanks for the huge amount of fucking money.
He hates voice acting.
I want to get onto the roof of the Big Sur hotel.
Okay.
Now...
Now where?
Over...
Uh, can I go up?
Wait, oh god, I gotta get up here.
Would I ever act in a movie?
Oh, that's...
Sorry, wasn't paying attention.
Uh...
Yes.
Yes, I would.
It'd be a lot of fun.
Would you act in Spider-Man?
As, um...
As what character do you...
What character do you think?
I think you would be a good green copy.
Eric, I found it.
Get up here and bring the camera.
As the greedy grinner.
Can you believe this spot?
We're about to film somebody die on camera.
You serious?
You'll miss your ollie.
We'll be sending you back to Jersey in a coffee can.
Todd said he wanted something big.
This is it.
Todd said he wanted something big, man.
I'm gonna jump off of a building.
Without any safety equipment.
Now that you're up here,
why don't you try to gap to the top of the wavy roof hotel over there?
Get specials in Gap the Wavy Roof Hotel.
If I can do that.
Okay, specials.
Now, which...
Where does it want me to go?
This way.
Let's gap it.
Here we go.
What kind of special should I do?
I don't have enough...
I'm gonna get more of this.
Hold on.
Oops.
Gap the Wavy Roof Hotel.
Okay.
So, how am I gonna do this?
Holy shit!
There you go, man.
Forget the pink hotel.
Look, I'll shoot you getting a high score up here on the rooftop
and we'll call it a day.
Imagine getting that on camera.
You could live off the ad revenue from that video for the rest of your life.
That would get a hundred...
That would get...
That would get a million views a day.
Forever.
Get 50,000 coins on the roof.
Easy.
That was pretty cool, but I didn't know how to land it.
Again.
Oh!
No!
Sorry.
Fuck.
That was 44,000!
Spine transfer over this quarter pipe to the street below with a big spin.
I can do that.
Yeah!
Dude!
That was a spinning T-pose.
That was sick.
Vilemi just gave 5,000 bits.
Thanks for the $50 Vilemi.
Jeremiah just tuned in.
Why does your character look like Ron Weasley?
Thanks for the 50 fucking bucks Vilemi.
Because.
Because he just jumped.
A Mick Twist?
Get Special and do a Mick Twist over the helicopter.
Special and then Mick Twist.
Where's the helicopter?
I want to see how many times I can do it.
Here we go.
Mick Twist!
Oh, I can't even, man.
It's so stupid.
It's like not even...
Is that...
Oh.
Whatever.
Let's go.
That's just panic in the air.
Here we go!
I'm gonna do it!
Yeah!
You filming, man?
There we go!
Jump!
Oh my fucking God!
That's just flailing panic in the air without even a second thought.
You deleted it.
Oh.
Here's the 411 on Vancouver.
We got our video premiere all set up.
One problem.
We don't have a freaking video!
If your footage ain't done, get it.
And if it is done, help set up for the big event.
Got it?
Okay.
Sorry, Dad.
All right.
Last minute tasks.
Here we are.
I heard you guys have some killer footage cooked up for this video.
Something about a massive Hawaii gap or something?
Well, that was me.
I cleared that air.
No way!
You're not even a pro!
Yes, I am.
Goiki!
Thanks for the $50, Goiki.
5,000 bits from Goiki.
Appreciate it.
Jerma, if you won't become a voice actor, can you become a ska artist?
Ska?
Um...
Doesn't matter.
Just go with the premiere tonight and you'll see.
Uh, I mean, that's like the genre of music, isn't it?
Wouldn't miss it.
Hey, since we're here, why don't you let me shoot a little footage of you?
50,000 points.
You keepin' up?
Oh, and I landed it.
I hate that trick so much.
Okay, stop.
What?
22,000.
It's a laggy level.
Why did I do that?
I was waiting to do a revert.
Restart?
No.
It's been gone.
Oh, laggy Lenny.
What else we got here?
50 FPS.
I will say, let's be completely honest to the Xbox 360.
This?
That guy got a gun?
Okay, I thought he had a gun.
Um...
This looks really good.
Remember, this is an original Xbox game.
It's the original Xbox disc.
This looks actually pretty good for being an original Xbox.
Upscaled.
What the heck is that?
That's a leaf blower cart.
I use it to clean up these plazas.
I'll let you try it out, but you've gotta do my work for me.
I'm not even sure, this game I think is like 480p.
Or maybe even like something like that.
There was no HD on the original Xbox.
No, wait, not even close.
Was this 720 on the Xbox?
It's probably 480, wasn't it?
Leaf Blow Company.
Loud as fuck.
PlayStation 2 was the...
No.
The PS2 was not capable of 720?
I do not remember that.
No, no way.
PS2 could do 1080i.
I...
I have...
Going to have to say I do not believe you.
Come on.
Is that right?
No, more?
Broke up.
Nice.
That was cute.
That was fun.
PS2.
PS2 had some of the best games.
I will agree with you there.
Just want to get air.
See if I can get some more air points.
No?
Oh well.
Slam City.
I just turned my mic up a little.
Better or worse?
Better?
Worse?
Okay.
Failed.
Combo all...
Combo all of them.
Oh, this is going to be hard.
Actually, it wasn't that bad.
A lot of missions here.
Turn the music up.
Please don't ever turn your mic down.
I'm going to turn it down.
I'm turning it down right now.
No, please!
No!
All right.
Hit all the Flatland tricks.
Got to do manual tricks.
Oh, these are always a pain in the ass for me.
I know I don't do them all at once, but I know.
I know, I know.
But that's fun for my brain.
It scratches a niche in my brain to do them all together.
Truck stand.
Do a truck stand.
Y and X.
Y and X is truck stand.
What the fuck?
Y, X.
Oh.
Okay.
God, these manuals are going to kill me.
Look at that fucking row that we're going to clear out right now.
Fucking manual Tetris.
I have to look at the controller.
I know.
You don't understand.
Truck stand.
Why would I do a truck stand?
Y and X.
Y and X together, man.
Camera ready.
Get 5,000 points in a manual combo.
Oh, I had 29,000 points.
This guy sucks.
Whenever somebody says that, I feel like that's how it's being said.
The sucks part is slowed down.
This guy.
This guy sucks.
Hey, Bob.
What are you doing?
Bob?
I've been working on this new manual for Casper Handstand.
Want to give it a try?
Get special and see if you can pull it while hitting my line.
Get special and see if you can do the Casper Handstand.
Now hit your line with the Casper Handstand.
I mean, I did it, but what's your line?
Got the line right there, man.
Very slow.
Wait, is it not a grind?
Just do it down the stairs.
Got it.
Okay, what else is left?
We have skate, Tom's part, party drags, Ralphie got busted.
Filming a line.
Hey, bro.
I'm about to hit a line through the underground.
I need to get some footage.
Can you follow me with the camera?
Well, you didn't.
Why are you not moving?
He's gone.
Shitty footage.
What are you guys doing over here?
Is he busting some fat ones?
Those missions are so, uh, not good.
It's just so, those are so bad.
This game is like a 97.
But those are so bad.
It's terrible.
Okay, how are you guys doing over here?
Is he busting some fat ones?
Dude, look at him.
He can't skate.
The fool is still drunk from the hotel party
and I need footage of him to complete this video.
He was going to bust some Nollies here at the museum.
Can you fill in for him?
I won't film your face.
Okay.
Record five Nollies.
Hit L twice to enter Nollie state.
You broke my fucking leg, buddy.
L twice to enter Nollie state?
Get this on fucking camera instead.
That's like way cooler.
Um, I don't understand what to do.
Record five Nollies.
Hit L twice to enter Nollie state.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
Switch pressure.
Bakey?
Bakey Ollie.
Pressure.
Okay.
Switch pressure.
Nollie.
What am I doing?
Don't do drugs.
Oh, awesome.
You better stop landing those Nollies
so cleanly or no one will believe it's Tom.
Drunk bastard.
Anyhow, cruise over here and bust some pressure flips
and we should be good to go.
Pressure flips.
I don't know much about, like, skating.
So what's the difference between this and a Nollie?
Thanks.
That will make perfect filler.
Okay, one more part.
You skate this plaza and I'll film combos
starting with Nollies or pressure flips.
We'll need some serious points for some good footage.
Nollie is off the front of the board.
Okay.
Record 25,000 points incorporating Nollies and pressures.
Sure.
Alright, let's get a Nollie in here.
Bakey, switch, pressure.
Pressure.
Nollie.
A lot of good ball jokes this stream.
Yeah.
There's been a lot of good ball jokes here, right?
That wasn't one.
I know a ton of you guys are just on the edge of your seat right there.
By the way, did anybody just open the screen for the first time?
Just curious.
Hello.
If you have, welcome.
My name's German985.
I'm playing Tony Hawk.
You might think it looks a little different.
It's underground.
It's not a numbered one.
Thanks for the follow.
Appreciate that.
Welcome to the stream.
Welcome.
What's going on?
The cops nabbed me when I bailed in the museum plaza.
Couldn't find my passport.
Make another one?
Yeah, I will.
Hold on.
Where'd you bail?
You gotta find the gardener.
Maybe he found it.
Where'd you bail?
Find the leaf blower guy.
All right, you know, is he in the hotel?
Right here.
Passport.
Well, I haven't seen it, but there are quite a few leaf piles around here.
If you want to search them all quickly, you can use the leaf blower cart.
55 seconds.
They're all right here.
One, two, three, four.
I got one up top with a six one.
No, Jeremy.
There's one right here.
Okay, I got a line.
This dropped my full plate of dinner on the ground in front of my mother.
Where is it?
Huh?
Guys?
I thought it was further down.
Fuck.
My mother made an entire false spread of food.
And I dropped all of it on the floor.
Potentially a new floor, new carpet or something.
Just like, no, Jeremy, what are you doing?
It's okay.
It's all right.
Yes.
Just go.
It's all right.
Just grab some towels.
Expensive floor.
Please be more careful next time.
I'm sorry, Bob.
It's okay.
I'm in a towel ladder.
I would be in a lot of trouble by now.
Wow.
Fuck.
It's so hard to control.
All right.
Now, go.
Pitchy face.
Okay.
Tonight's my night.
Thanks, man.
Get everyone to the premiere.
What?
Why does the camera just swing?
These are all of our friends.
Why'd it happen to the color?
Yeah.
Why is the color on?
Did it go down here?
That's weird.
Get everybody to the premiere.
Come on.
Quick.
We have this many friends?
His neck was backwards.
I guess his head was on backwards.
He made it.
All right.
Let's see.
Let's take a look at my skiing footage.
This game is so shit.
Laughing my ass off.
What a funny pretend comment that is.
Hard.
You weren't even in it.
But Eric's gets rooftop gap I've ever seen.
Eric edited his face on my footage.
Forty stones.
My trick in my spot.
To introduce our newest pro, Eric's.
Eric.
Editing his face.
Eric's on his way to the last gap.
And his first pro board will become two months.
Hey, Eric.
Do that trick that you did off the roof again.
That's what I would do.
You poached my shots.
Where's my footage?
Oh, man.
I put them on the spot.
I told myself to tell you, see.
There was this thing at customs.
Hey, we go way back.
So I'm going to forget you just did that.
Now listen, I got three parties to hit.
But you better go rest up for the amateur contest tomorrow.
Dick.
Just need some basic information from you.
Budget 3D Bible show.
You're a pro?
They entered you as an amateur.
Someone made a mistake.
Here's my ride.
Destroy the slam city jam.
This is a cool park.
You guys, I think the skate park would make a big return.
It's getting so hard.
Who in this kind of shit?
I mean, obviously, this is like an arcade game.
But holy shit.
It takes so much skill to be able to do any of this shit.
Oh, my God.
That would have been fucking a lot.
This isn't real.
Yeah, but have you ever seen an actual skate video before?
That shit is insane.
I had to jump in with a board and sliding down a bar
and not like fucking instantly dying.
Like, oh, I'm just going to jump down the 30 flights of stairs on a bar.
Like, holy shit, that's so scary.
It takes so much skill, so much patience.
I'm on the list.
Destroy the street competition.
My best.
Should we show them up our special move?
OK, I got to incorporate my special move.
Oh, that felt nice.
Damn it.
I love this game.
No, Xbox.
Xbox.
Why Xbox?
That was like 180,000 points.
Xbox, what have you done to me?
Xbox, what have you done?
OK, well, I mean, I got I'm in first place.
Eric Sparrow stuff.
Let's go.
Wow.
No, no, don't do it yet.
Ooh, don't end it yet.
No, dude, I just went through it.
All right, 200,000 should be good.
Big finish, here we go.
God damn it.
Come on, big finish.
I'm still dumb.
I can literally do whatever I want.
I almost have a perfect score.
Actually, I'm going to go for a monster combo.
I like this space.
It's great.
Are you kidding me?
What the hell was that?
You seeing this shit?
Mom, get the camera.
Some half-pipe shit.
It's OK.
Oh, that was so much fun.
Just flying around and going like.
I love it.
It was 133,000 to get some practice in hip transfer these ramps by skating up the first
quarter pipe at an angle and cutting the corner in the game is so good.
It's always up to.
Yeah, it was hip hip transfer these ramps by skating up the first quarter pipe at an
angle and then cutting the corner in the air.
After you jump at an angle, press this hip transfer to the other side.
Watch this guy.
He's not very good.
Oh, again, the same hip transfer first, then continue on to the second.
Who hip transfers?
I mean, that was fucking awesome.
Way better than what you wanted me to do.
All right, let's do some more stuff.
How does it never get old?
I don't know.
It just doesn't.
Weird.
Any more quests?
I want to put some new tricks on, too, because these are getting a little stale to me.
Edit tricks.
Wrap tricks.
I want to do.
Get rid of the melon.
Let's put on fucking cannonball here to the Indy and let's do the Madonna.
Get rid of the Japan.
Let's put on.
Stale fish instead of Indy Stiffy.
Let's do a crossbar.
Let's check it out.
I got to learn how to see what it was like.
The actual part here.
Hard to land.
Yeah, that's hard to land.
Oh, whoa.
Hold on.
Christ air.
They're all kind of hard to land.
That's all right.
You're killing this guy.
He'll be fine.
Christ air.
Fine.
We're making our own Christ air.
All right.
Holdable.
Yes.
Just make him a drill.
No, we can't spin.
Just turn him into a helicopter.
I'm it's going to be another spin joke.
That's going to be fucking great.
All right.
That's good.
Somebody said just do Christ air,
but just add a fart to it.
Imagine if I actually did something like that.
That's it.
That's the only change.
What is it?
There's a toy.
There's a toy that you pull a little string
and it like spins and it's like a flower that opens up.
You know what I'm talking about?
It's like a little it's like a cheap little toy
that just like you can like open it up, open it up, open it up.
What are those things called?
They're like a dollar.
Oh, how many can I add?
That hurts my head actually.
It's one of those it's a full helicopter.
Oh, it's too much.
It needs to be shorter.
It needs to be shorter by a little bit.
Imagine holding this.
I want a quick one.
No, hold on.
It's holdable.
Make it 0.1 second.
I'm glad you think that was any different.
It's the same thing.
Just.
Okay, back to editor.
You know what?
No, no, I've got a better idea.
I want to be able to do a kickflip
but just do a backflip.
You know what I mean?
Just like, bam.
Imagine doing a backflip on landing it on a grind.
See what I mean?
That's fucking so stupid.
Here we go.
One, two, add to cart.
No, I think I've modded this.
I mean, like this just feels like it shouldn't ever be in the game.
It's a literal backflip because it's technically a kickflip.
Imagine not getting an actual 10 out of 10 for doing this.
Jesus.
All right, we're good.
It's called one, one B, one back.
No, one back.
Back one.
That's what it is.
Boring.
It means to invent a funny name.
It's a backflip.
That's it.
What do you want me to call it?
Oh, the scoopity poopity.
It's a backflip.
That's it.
It's just a backflip.
Backspace.
I like backspace.
Capitalize the flip.
Okay, let's get out of here.
Edit tricks, flip tricks.
Here we go.
I'm going to put it on to this hard flip here.
You unsubbed because no scoopity poopity.
I'm so sorry.
All right, blimp.
Crazy ass fans.
Competition won't start until they're removed from the lights.
Fans are on the lights.
I have to use a blimp.
I'm killing it.
Blimp controls.
Celebrate.
How do I go up?
I don't think I can move it.
I think I can just go left and right.
Go up.
I just hit an invisible wall.
What is that, gang?
Come on.
You're supposed to be in 97 stuff.
Oh, yeah.
These balls.
Wow.
Oh, look at that.
So good.
Just standard jumps and standard kickflips.
Safe.
Nice, but safe.
Okay.
When are you going to be done?
He's actually pretty impressive.
He's still going.
He's still got this combo going.
I'm actually a little concerned now.
I don't think I'm going to be able to do this.
This is like five laps on the course.
There's A.
Oh, shit.
Find it.
Okay.
It's actually a little distracting.
I don't know if I like this.
I would take it off.
I don't like it.
It's super distracting and it's hard.
It's very...
It's kind of ruining my runs.
I can't take it off.
No, get it off.
Get it off.
I can't stand it.
It's too fucked up.
Get it off.
Put anything else.
I don't care what it is.
Get it off.
I don't want to see it anymore.
It's not going to happen.
We'll just do a varial heel flip there.
That sounds like a good one.
You know what I mean?
Like it's not...
My whole body isn't moving around.
Fuck you.
I had that.
Fuck off, Eric.
How's that fucking taste, Eric?
I'm a pro now.
Did he say bovine balls?
Create a deck.
Now that you're a pro,
you'll need to design your own pro deck graphic.
Base graphic.
No, the bricks.
Bricks.
Rock?
Really?
What?
Oh, no.
I can only have one of these?
Move it.
Here we go.
Okay, looks good.
Okay.
Another one.
I can only...
I can only have one.
Layer three.
Okay, great.
I could use four slot emotes.
Oh, well.
All right, I'm going to do...
I don't like any of these.
Maybe the fire?
I don't really want anything.
No, I don't want any graphics.
No graphics.
Layer two.
Layer...
Layer one.
Layer two.
Let's try this one more time.
There we go.
Like that.
Looks fucking good, dude.
All right.
The pizza stain board.
That board sucks.
No, it doesn't.
Hey, way to clean up in the slam city gym.
Heard you scored a pro model, too.
Well, I would have scored it sooner if Eric had...
It's brick.
It's brick with blood and stuff.
It looks like...
Pizza board.
You're just jealous Eric gets to go to Moscow instead of you.
I got more important things to worry about than Eric.
Like maybe you could help me shop for a house.
Nice work, guys.
I'll help you shop for a tent.
Nice job.
Look around the air and it'll land on somebody.
Yeah, but I see Kostin with his crazy Hollywood house and Tony with his Lexus.
Sponsors, man.
Even my sister knows that you have to have a signature shoe to make decent living from skating.
But hey, it looks like the sponsors are all hanging around town.
Why do they all just walk around town?
Who knows?
If you get a shoe deal, maybe they'll take you on tour.
Just the random NPC sponsors that are just in your city,
just walking around waiting to give you money.
Just do a cool trick.
Does this work for magicians, too?
Ditch.
Why can I ditch the car?
I can't ditch.
I'm a pro.
I have a limo.
Learn to drive.
Why have they spawned me here?
Driving your own limo.
Half pipe.
Nice trick.
All right, let's do something.
Show off your skills.
We need to see something edgy before we'll give you a shoe.
Tell you what.
Let's see you clear all the spines of Superior Court.
Where are the spines?
One, two, and three.
What do you mean by this?
You mean that counts, right?
Come on up here.
Restart.
No.
Get off the board and walk.
All right, come on.
The shoe guys are into me.
Todd says I'm on board for the next tour.
Dude, you're going to miss that bus.
What bus?
Your team bus.
Bro, they're going to Moscow.
What?
Oh, damn.
My shoes.
And my socks.
Go, dude.
My shoes and my socks.
Why am I doing tricks?
I don't know.
I just want to.
Thanks.
Son of a.
There goes my bus.
Son of a what?
What?
I need my.
No, I need my trophy.
Get your slam city trophy.
Excuse me.
I got to.
It's the bus, right?
What?
Do I have to beat the bus to Moscow?
Stop that bus.
I can't get.
Why didn't they break?
Oh, I just didn't get to the end.
I thought stop the bus.
I'm like, stand in front of it.
I didn't know that stop the bus meant
to skate over through the level out of the level.
Mother Russia.
Home of borscht, potatoes, and the world's biggest skate demo ever.
All the press will be here looking for this year's best new pro.
Now, the demo doesn't start for a few days, OK?
So stay the hell out of trouble.
Is this emulated or is it on console?
This is actually on console.
This is an Xbox 360 slim with an official Xbox 360 hard drive in it.
You have to have one of those.
Don't make the mistake I did.
And it's just the original disc for Xbox.
Welcome to Russia.
Hey, American.
Some nosy American company installed cameras on our buildings for this contest.
Cameras.
We Russians value privacy and would like them knocked out.
Why don't you do something?
I do favor for you.
I knocked on the cameras.
Don't say that you can't comprehend.
Don't say that you don't understand.
This is California.
I'm not saying that you can't understand.
Don't say that you can't understand.
This is California.
Don't say that you can't comprehend.
How many are there?
I guess it's just got to stay on the grind.
Oh, it's up there.
Holy shit.
Damn.
How do I get up there?
Is that your wall ride?
Don't say that you don't understand.
That you don't understand.
Shit.
There it is.
But not quite.
I didn't get the other one below it.
Wait.
Did I?
Okay.
Yep.
I see it.
It's right after that.
I'm going to go up.
There it is.
There's more here.
I thought that was going to be the end.
That's not the end.
Fuck.
I got to keep going.
It's one line.
Holy shit.
Sorry.
I got to...
How do I get up from this without...
Can I just...
Hold on.
Fuck.
Just get off the board and just punch it.
This one's fucking hard.
There it is.
Got it.
There's more?
No.
Okay.
There we go.
What?
Whoa.
Where?
What?
Wait.
There's another more.
Didn't it say completed?
Wait.
What was the green?
Oh.
Okay.
I saw like the big green green.
Like, okay.
And I looked over.
I was just done.
I thought that was it.
I thought...
I just saw the big green text.
I'm like, all right.
There's the line.
Fucking kidding me.
What?
Where is it?
Holy shit, dude.
What's the transfer here?
I don't see the transfer.
Got it.
Holy fuck.
Okay.
That one was fucking hard.
Caveman grind?
Well, I'm going to lose 400 rubles
because I don't know what a caveman grind is.
That's a caveman grind.
Just jumping off?
Like with a...
I don't know.
A caveman is you just don't need to put the board back on.
Like that.
I don't know.
Stop.
Please.
Why is this the hardest thing so far?
Caveman attempt...
Oh.
Caveman attempt in a 20,000 point combo.
They said fuck this mission, by the way.
Really?
I...
What?
Fuck.
Ah.
My hands are sweating.
Nope.
I'm losing all my ruffles.
I know.
It's actually very, very hard to control the character when you're...
Standing on the tank, your movement changes.
Like I'm holding...
It's just weird.
It's almost like the character's...
See, I'm like holding the buttons down.
I'm like not running anymore.
It's kind of odd.
I'm just walking instead.
It's weird.
It's like I'm walking in quicksand right now.
20,000 points.
I can do it.
Fuck.
All right.
Now I understand what somebody said when they said fuck this mission.
Now I get what you're saying.
Did I get it?
What about the other one?
This one here.
This one's firing.
Fuck.
There's a much better line here.
There's nothing over off that one.
That was only 15.
Fuck.
Damn it.
I'm starting to become greasy again.
Can caveman any part of the tank?
Are you fucking serious?
Why am I doing the hardest part?
What?
No, I can't.
Oh, come on.
Why is my brain so strange?
Oh, I got a caveman up the nose of the tank.
Oh, my God.
What a waste of fucking time.
Good duo combo.
He's gotta get something going and then run back.
Because it keeps your combo when you run off like that.
All right, here we go.
That's it.
Why would I caveman first when I can just get off the cater?
You just have to have done a caveman at some point in the combo.
So I might as well do the combo first and then just do the caveman
because it's easier because I can just get off the fucking
scooter.
If you're in the middle of a combo and you get off the skateboard,
you have like five seconds with the combo meter still going.
Okay, that's special over here.
Why do I need special?
Get special and some speed first.
Okay, now over the wall.
Over this wall.
Behind you.
Special makes you faster for some reason.
Does it really?
All right, let me get some speed.
I'm not going forward.
I'm going to be going forward.
Are we sneaking into the Kremlin right now?
What are we doing?
Uh, Operation D's what?
Oh my god, really?
I can't believe we just got a D's nut kill.
Two more.
Hello.
That was some damn sweet kung fu.
One last thing to do.
Bam never has any clothes on.
Why?
Get up that ladder and ring those bells.
Easy.
We think the guards will run out and open the gate.
Yeah, it's a long shot.
Oh, yeah.
Don't get shot.
Ring the bell.
Ring the bells.
Um, oh god.
Caveman.
Trekkin' along.
Tanks.
A tank.
Look at these tanks.
Damn, look at these tanks.
It's probably pretty cold out here.
She's stoked by getting best new pro.
Well, it's not a done deal yet.
It's pretty close between me and Eric.
Sup, guys?
Listen, I've been thinking, we can't keep this up.
Remember how I used to torch action figures with you?
I acted like a dork.
I'm sorry, I got carried away.
No, we're going to get, we're going to get fucking double-crossed again.
Get out in front of those cameras and earn your keep.
So good.
We can't go skating right now.
Look at these tanks.
Damn.
Chapter 21.
Time to skate, comrade.
Christmas in Moscow?
Manuals for Moscovites.
Rodney Mullin.
Why are you hanging out here freezing your ass off?
I was waiting for it.
Somebody just went, what the fuck?
I know we've done that a lot tonight, but it's funny every time
because there's new people that experience it every time.
That's what makes it so much better.
Around to get more.
Manuals.
Should we be concerned about tanks pointing at us?
More.
Oh, that was broken, but okay.
I'm going to get blasted with a tank shell.
That would be, that would be, uh, Tony Hawk, what do you need?
Russia.
Cool, eh, comrade?
The locals are stoked on this chick I've been working on up here.
I'll tell you what, you give it a try.
Land tricks until you get your special meter full
and then do a 360 burial heel flip lean.
Okay, thanks, Tony.
Special move.
I'm not doing the flush.
We can't pull out the flush every five seconds.
It loses its comedic value if you do it.
So,
show me how well you know Moscow.
Oh, no, some gaps and you might get jobs later.
Too much media around here.
Find some gaps.
Find five gaps.
Three and a half minutes to do this.
Is this a gap?
That's kind of a gap.
Hey there.
Why are these reporters bugging you?
I feel like I'll be searching around for like 20 minutes.
I don't want to do that one.
Do they not have animated eyes?
Look at her eyes.
More manuals?
Get a 20,000 point manual combo.
Easy.
That's the easiest thing I've done all night.
If there were not so many reporters watching,
I'd show you some tricks too.
Bye-bye.
Oh, I like that pipe.
Let me try that.
Nice.
Pretty solid.
95,000.
For me, anything more than one to 200,000 is like,
all right, that was pretty good.
I know some of you guys are pros, but you know, I'm me.
Warm up.
Why is this guy talking like a sham?
Wow, dude.
Cool.
50,000 points.
I could do better.
Do I still have that on my bar?
Yeah, it's still on the bar.
It's still on my bar.
Yes, I'm using MMO terms right now,
but you know what I'm saying.
Where's the DPS?
I only have to do one more thing.
Ratings, stunts.
I want you to get some air time.
It should be easy with all the reporters around.
Try to score big points around them while they're broadcasting.
Unreal TV is doing a story under Lenin's statue
about him coming back to life as a robot.
NSBC is doing a corruption story near St. Basil.
I'm gonna do crazy shit over here, right?
On each one of these.
After that, Channel 9 is interviewing some actress
in front of the armory.
Now go rip it up at those spots,
and you're bound to get on TV.
Okay, all right.
State Lenin's statue.
Oh, you are on camera.
Sorry, I got 16,000.
Yes, all right.
I don't really like the scan lines all over my screen.
All right, I just destroyed that.
Is it possible that you could create a character
that looks normal?
What's the fun in that, though?
What's the fun in that?
Get 10,000 in double tricks.
This is like broke out of the glass.
Wait, does he do that, too?
All right, we just did that.
Am I holding him?
Why am I doing these?
I feel like these are...
The points are much easier to attain here.
He did not do any of that correctly.
Well, yeah, I did.
I just had to get points when he was getting points, too.
We got points together at the same time.
Double points.
Did they put a tank level in Tony Hawk?
I will be shocked if this is the case.
This is not a dude stop it scenario.
It's not like somebody throwing TP.
Like a Halloween prank.
This is driving a tank into a building.
I missed the competition, is that what happened?
God damn it, Eric.
Get the check from the parents.
The kid's off the team.
You are very lucky your embassy has freed you.
Too bad your team has left you here to rot all by yourself, eh?
Good luck finding a way home.
Okay, I'm now stuck in Moscow.
The first thing I do when I get out, I don't call my mom.
I do a manual combo.
All right, how do I get out of here?
How do I activate?
What do we got for goals?
An anonymous caller.
That was him on the phone.
Oh boy, that was bad all the way around.
I'm supposed to take it off a bar and I can't.
I think that's how you play a game like this.
You just get so, you get so perfectionist.
You just want to do everything so good and so perfect
and then you do it wrong even a little bit.
You're like, no, no, no, do it again, do it again, do it again.
I don't want to, no, do it again, do it again.
Stop doing tricks.
It's like going to McDonald's and somebody's in the backseat going,
just don't, don't eat any hamburger.
Order a salad.
The electromagnetic forces you create will disable the tower.
Spins over the roof.
All right, got to go over 15 spins.
Holy shit, I feel like this is going to be hell.
Is this the only one I have to do it to?
Or are they all over the place?
Wait, let me get off the board.
Is there more than one or is it just these two?
It's just these two, huh?
15 full spins with spine transfer.
Do the flush.
I don't think that counts.
Why did it go the other way?
See, like why is it doing that?
What are you doing?
Yeah, all right, I got to, I got to go straight because this is just
such a small disorienting area.
They, they say, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Back and forth, back and forth, straight over.
Oh, God.
Flush is going to save you.
No, it's, it's not, it's actually 360 spins.
Watch, ready?
It's not what you think.
I have to use the analog here because that's going to keep happening.
15 fucking times.
Watch, watch.
It's going to be hard to do it.
Trust me.
It's not going to do what you think it is.
Spining over and then down, down, B is actually fucking hard to do.
It's rough.
All right.
No, no, that's not even the controller.
He's spinning back.
Why is he going the other way when I go to more than 540 goes the other way?
I don't know why it's happening.
That shouldn't be happening.
See what the fuck was, what is going on there?
Why is that happening?
What is it?
Why is it doing that?
What the fuck?
That something weird is going on here.
Something weird going on here.
One more try.
I don't want to do this one.
This one.
I have to do it.
Have to do three of them all.
I'm not holding the triggers.
I have to hold the triggers to go over the.
Is that what's happening?
Because I have to hold both triggers to go over the satellites.
So I have to be holding them in the first place.
Wait, I don't have to hold them.
I just tap them.
Where's my clothes?
Why am I naked?
Pick the boss up.
Arrow freaked me out.
A lot of random car levels.
Is that him?
That was weird.
Do it again.
Boston band?
Yeah, it is.
It should be.
Where's this arrow going?
Do a royal flush with the car.
I can't.
Earn.
I, crazily enough, I didn't hit anybody.
Nobody got injured there.
I was fine.
Go get her.
Okay.
Simpsons hit and run all over again.
Even the timer is similar.
Jesus.
There's another person.
What?
Rita?
Lariska called for a ride.
Can't you guys all be in the same spot?
All right.
I'm going for this one again.
Here we go.
Hike.
Oh, God.
Okay.
Now let's try this again.
Failed when walking.
I don't know how I did that.
Here we go.
Let's go.
Okay.
Yep.
That's exactly what was happening to me.
I hate this area.
It's just, it's too, it's like so claustrophobic up here.
I'm going to do 15 oftentimes.
Why does Cookie Monster sometimes talk?
I haven't figured that out yet.
Watching this makes me sick.
Playing it also does as well.
I feel your pain.
You didn't read chat's joke.
You made your own minus two joke.
What are you talking about?
I asked a question.
Where is that Cookie Monster voice coming from?
Remember, that wasn't a very good joke.
It was a question, sir.
One of these days, Jerome is going to snap.
Why?
What do you think that?
Is there any particular reason why you think that?
Do explain.
I'd like to know what your hypothesis.
One more.
No, no, no, no.
Why?
You cannot refuse.
You're not going to complete this one?
I have to.
Perhaps you find cures for me.
And then I talk to the organization about getting you back home.
Aspirin, water, vitamin A, vitamin D, dog poop.
What was it?
Where is it?
People pink stuff.
Let's see, up there.
No, stop.
Grab it.
Get off the bike.
Skate or whatever.
Actually, just climb up is probably easier.
Feeling stronger.
Whoa.
I just got sucked into a black hole there.
Hold on.
I got to get up.
Can I jump up here?
I don't think so.
I got it.
I just looked into the wall and got it.
Here, too.
Aida Caratine.
Turn around.
Get out of here.
I can't grab that one.
Where's there a line that I can get up here from?
This way?
Oh, shit.
Hold on.
Do I have to get up there?
Not good.
Get up there.
Is there another way to get up here besides having to jump up here?
Here?
Hold on.
Let's see.
No.
I have to.
I have to just jump across it.
Shit.
No.
I'm so close.
Get off the bike.
I keep going on the bike.
It's seven hours of screaming that goes through your brain.
I'm going to have to do it again.
Stay up here.
No.
I'm trying to just jump over it.
Let's do it again.
I had it, too.
Cleaner this time.
You don't even have to touch them.
I got to get some water.
I got to drink some water.
It's blending together.
The world's blending together.
I got to get some water.
All tricks are becoming the same trick.
And all lines are the same line.
It's water time.
Remember the guy that wrote it all caps?
You're never going to beat this mission.
Okay.
All right, let's go.
Wink.
I'm in the middle of a really, really hard mission.
Just hold on a second.
Oh, my God.
Stop getting stuck on every polygon.
There it is.
No, I was on it.
Why did I have to jump?
Fuck.
No, no.
I got to go up around that again.
It's the only way to do it.
I don't like this area.
This is my least favorite level in the game so far.
I have to get on this and then I make it from I have to just jump to jump the tower.
I have to just jump over this tower.
I can get over here.
The ladder over there is seriously.
Okay.
Get me the fuck over here.
Get off the get off.
Get off.
Where is it?
Oh, my God.
I'm going to scream into this microphone and fucking blow out my vocal cords.
That was horrible.
Don't look inside.
Don't let any of the guards see you with it either.
They are on the walls and there are many more in this.
Wait, now that I can focus.
And you made it into the cave.
The cave of the greasy fucking mad streamer.
What questions do you have for me?
Alexander is near St. Basil's.
It is the pointy thing you don't remember.
Bye.
Get me out of Moscow.
I don't like that wall.
Oh, there's the ladder that everyone was talking about.
Oh, you can't like punch.
I can't like jump on them and knock them down.
What?
I can't knock them down.
I can't like run into them with my skateboard.
I've just done a stealth mission.
Oh, great.
Go around that guard.
Wink, redeem.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I can't stop.
Don't you understand?
I can't.
I'm going to be in big trouble if I fuck this up.
Is there a guard down there?
Can I skate this?
Fuck.
You are going home, but you are welcome back here anytime.
I did it.
You look horrifying.
Come on.
Give me a...
Come on, man.
As I walked into your room one day when you were sitting there playing a game
and I just like knocked on the door.
And you're in the dark and you turn and I just go, you look fucking horrible.
I gotta close the door.
I don't care how many kids are waiting.
Who's here?
I was hoping to see you.
I never got to thank you for handing me best new pro back in Russia.
You still don't get it.
No, homie.
I got it all.
My own company, six cars in my garage, a record deal in the worst company.
Russia to New Jersey.
How long is that flight?
You go ahead.
Keep telling yourself you're happy, but it ain't about the money.
I can't believe I'm wasting my time with this jackass.
He probably skates for minimum wage.
See ya.
You'll see.
I'm not going anywhere.
I still got a few real friends left.
Like Tony Hawk.
He gives me a stomach ache.
I can't believe kids will look at Eric and think that's what skating is about.
Look, you got a deal if you want to make it as a pro.
Man, I just want to skate like the old days.
It used to relax me, not stress me out.
That's your deal, man.
Skating is whatever you make it.
It didn't change.
You're the one that changed.
Now go skate.
You'll remember why you started in the first place.
Oh no, he hates, he hates skating now.
He hates skating.
He used to love skating.
Hey, good to see you again.
How's that whole life been working out for you?
Hey, Sean, going okay.
About to get a lot better.
I'm going to make a comeback.
Check out this new trick I invented.
Damn, you are shooting for a comeback.
Do I get to show him?
Let's see it.
That's the cannon one that I invented.
Oh, that's so stupid.
That's so much worse than mine.
Mine's way better.
Create a trick, welcome.
You can create, yes, I know.
Modify my trick.
Funniest fucking thing I've ever seen in my life.
But it shouldn't be.
That's like shouldn't be the funniest thing ever.
Okay, so we're back in New Jersey, ready to go.
And the first thing, what do we have to do here?
Combo the entire city.
Hell yeah, I remember you doing sweet lines way back when.
Got a new one, eh?
All right, I'll put it on film, you hit it.
Combo the whole city.
Oh man, this is going to be tricky.
I'm going to jump off.
I hate this because I was bad at this.
This is hard, this game's not easy.
Seven out of ten.
I want to get some water too, I forgot to do that.
I really need it.
Yeah, I'm starting to get a little hydration deprived.
I'll be right back.
Get some water.
Okay, fully hydrated.
I drank a full glass.
I'm ready to go.
Ready?
Oh, this is the power of hydration.
It hasn't gotten in my bloodstream yet.
Hold on.
My manual's dropping so hard.
My manual's just dumping.
I don't even need to start there.
That's a shitty line to start on.
Sorry, wait.
Oh, only five seconds, that's...
Oh god, okay.
That's kind of like a trap, I feel like that's a trap.
Oh, there we go.
There it is.
No!
All right, you just have to hold, you stay on it.
This stupid fucking flip.
Oh, that manual is going to be hard to hold.
That was almost really cool, almost.
Oops, ah, I didn't hit it.
Get off the board.
Yeah, that's true, I can do that.
Let's see if I can get it in one go though.
I'm currently addicted.
Why are you not facing me?
Look at me.
He didn't even want to look at me.
I just did the sickest combo ever.
Five community subs from...
Six.
Thanks, Pelsix.
Perfect, then all we need to do is find a great name for our team.
Name the team, okay.
Before any of these other guys are going to want to know that I'm still for real.
I'm guessing with everything that's been going on, most people have forgotten.
Well, I guess I'll just have to remind everyone.
Let's go.
That reminds her...
What?
Fell off?
I just wanted to turn around.
Flush.
This guy's made out of...
This guy's made out of rubber bands.
For the love of God.
He says I keep kicking the shit out of this guy.
I feel so bad.
All right, let's do it.
Nail all the tricks.
Come on, somebody's air-conditioning.
Wait, what?
Stop, stop, stop!
Do it again.
Is this not low house lift?
Oh, I got it, I got it.
Tony Hawk's got a game.
Yep, he's got a few of them.
Tony Hawk 1, Tony Hawk 2, Tony Hawk 3, Tony Hawk's Underground, Tony Hawk's Underground 2,
Tony Hawk's American Wasteland, Tony Hawk for the Weave,
Tony Hawk for the Weave with a skateboard...
Ruff-Roll, what else does he have?
Tony Hawk Project 8, right?
Tony Hawk 4, right.
All right, um, Burial Invert to Fakie.
Oh, how am I doing this wrong?
How am I doing this wrong?
That's just a lift trick, isn't it?
Let's switch rooms.
All right, lift tricks always are just kind of...
You know, I've played every Tony Hawk game.
I still don't really understand how a lift trick actually even works to not grind.
Like, you know what I'm saying?
Because I'm only, I'm doing up and wide, but there's other tricks that I can do.
I thought these specials, they might be.
See, I always have trouble with these plants.
I just try to do left and wide at the same time.
Here we go, more of this Invert, that's a gymnast plant.
Invert, Invert, Invert.
Isn't that what I'm doing?
Switch a room.
There it is.
One foot, okay.
Burial, I can't get this one though.
Nose butt, whatever, nose, whatever.
There it is.
All right, it's because of the analog.
One second.
It's because I wasn't, the D-pad sucks with it.
So if I need to do a plant trick, I'll just use the analog.
All right, we got one more thing to do here and then what's next?
Score a big, all right, a million points.
Big points, 200,000 points, let's go.
What?
Did I lose it?
Restart Randy, I know.
I'm like this with every one of these games though.
There's nothing I can do about it.
I feel like my balance has gotten worse.
Is that like even possible?
No way.
That just fucked me up.
I have to restart.
That was so bad.
That move, man.
I got to get that out of here.
I got to delete that move.
All right, 80,000, look at that.
Huge gift subs, just a second.
Yeah, I was trying to grab onto that.
Ow.
There we go.
That's exactly what I want to do.
It's an old secret technique.
That was a lot.
Hey, where it is you've really been tearing it up.
Here you're starting a new team as well.
This bear is getting really good at video games.
You know what?
That's the fucking like that's the comment that I like to see the most.
The answer is no, though.
They say you want to cut through all the bullshit.
Just hook up some guys that want to see how far they can take skating.
Imagine getting mad at a fart joke.
Would somebody mad here?
Wait, is somebody actually upset here?
Did somebody come in and say like, fuck, that's not fucking funny?
Shit.
Yes.
Oh, no.
You know, all right, whatever.
That means I'll do it three more times in a row.
I think that sounds pretty cool.
Pick your team members.
Bam Margera, of course.
Tony Hawk.
And who?
Tony Hawk, Bam Margera.
And this is Pup.
Chad Muska.
Hey, Chad Muska was there when we first started.
Chad Muska found us and discovered us and gave us our first gig.
Chad Muska can do more.
It's Rodney.
Rodney, Rodney, Rodney, Rodney Mullen.
And Eric.
Wait, is that the evil Eric or is Mike V?
That's not evil Eric, right?
All right, yeah, Eric.
Eric Tom.
So the name of the team is going to be the Destructors.
How about Questers?
Crunchers.
The Flush Force.
Flush Force.
Sounds good to me.
Flush Force Assemble.
You know what would be awesome?
If I could give them different moves.
Just give them all for every move.
I thought.
Okay, we gotta kill a team.
Now to spread the word.
We're gonna make an escape video.
But we're not gonna make some cookie cutter film
where everybody is skating the same stuff.
We're gonna make something bigger and better.
Totally unexpected.
Check this, dude.
I've had this for years.
I've been saving this list of secret spots
since Animal Chin.
You know, it's actually...
I'm supposed to do shit like that.
Big Apple Spot Challenge.
Here it is.
You still have your steak and cheese?
Get ready to...
Here we go.
I have four attempts to do this.
It was a cheese steak.
I just said steak and cheese.
Next part.
I want to shoot just one long take.
You know, get some smooth...
What?
Street skating to New York.
You just reversed it.
Bacon Cheese Challenge.
Here it comes.
Every object before my film runs out.
Select a teammate.
Oh, Jarrah.
It's not even my character.
What?
This is not even my character.
Why?
Why can't it be me?
I don't...
This is...
He handles differently.
You can't make me toad the whole game
and then make me play as Donkey Kong
when I've never done that before.
He doesn't have the flush.
He doesn't have it.
I can do this.
I have four attempts.
You have four attempts to do
Big Spot Challenge.
Sure.
Let's go.
Oh, I got 13?
Not even close.
It's not even close.
I don't want to be bad much yet.
Come on.
24 out of 44.
Five.
How many more times?
You got to try to get it all in one line.
Or at least a lot of it in one line.
27 out of 44.
This is definitely doable.
In four attempts.
Definitely not going to be this one.
Yeah, that's it.
All right.
This is attempt number three.
Oh, no.
Fuck.
Oh, I just like literally dropped the ball.
All right.
Okay.
Go this way.
How many more?
27.
You got to do it all in one go?
Yeah, I know.
This is that's hard.
All right.
Try it again.
You don't have to.
I don't care.
You don't have to throw up your steak and cheese.
You get to keep it inside your stomach where it belongs.
No.
Okay.
I got to go up that ramp.
All right.
Let's go.
Take this.
I mean, yeah, but I didn't really do it.
Are they all like this?
Or is this one in particular just the one that's?
Is this this?
Are they all like this?
Every single one?
Or is this the I'm going to throw up the big challenge one?
This is the one.
This is the one that's hard.
Try it again.
One line.
Not bad.
Not a terrible start.
Could be worse.
Let's put a score and I touch that to grind it.
You got to learn it.
I mean, you got to learn the entire route.
Doing that in one trick.
I'm sure it's on YouTube somewhere.
I'm not going to be able to do that.
20.
A lot of shit over here.
30 out of 44.
Is it every single one or you just have to get 44?
Or is it all of them a 44?
All of them is 44.
Well, I don't think I'll be doing this one.
I'm not getting over there.
Nope.
For this next part, I want to shoot this.
Wait.
What?
I can't leave?
Why can't I?
There we go.
Change the level.
Get me out of here.
End goal.
Few goals.
Okay.
Jersey spine trick shot.
Apples.
Big apples.
I'm not there with that one.
How about slam a jamma?
Let's try slam a jamma.
Check it.
Peralta pulled some strings and got us onto the slam city course after hours.
This setup is perfect for a real street technician.
We should be able to shoot some nice long combo lines.
I've only got enough footage for a set number of lines.
So hit as many markers in one combo as you can.
I feel like this is going to be a significant portion of the rest of this stream.
Man, you have to do 10 combos.
You have nine combos.
I don't understand.
You have nine combos?
I only have to do...
I get it.
I have to do this in that...
No.
Oh, no.
Am I not going to be able to beat Tony Hawk's Underground?
I was hoping we were going to be at the last level after eight hours.
I'm sorry, Tony.
Let me see the other ones.
These are going to be so hard for me to do.
How about Vancouver spine challenge?
Those are the two hardest ones.
Are they?
Load, land, spine series.
Okay, land, spine series.
Okay, let's just spine over this.
Okay, there's one.
I would have had it.
This doesn't seem too bad.
Well, stop.
You're killing him.
Why can't I go forward?
What the fuck?
What am I doing wrong?
I need more air.
I had no air on that one.
I'm not holding anything.
I'm just doing L and R.
L and R.
Well, I get it.
I get it.
I'm starting to understand it, but fucking L and R is killing me.
Okay, L and R.
Give off as a controller.
The height of the jump?
I mean, all right.
So why am I doing the first one pretty much every single time,
but I can't do this one once?
I'm doing it too early?
Don't jump.
Wait, don't jump?
Why would I not?
Well, all right.
What?
Why would I not jump?
Now score 100,000 points.
Does it time?
Wait a minute.
What the fuck happened?
That whole...
Wait, the whole thing has to be a combo.
The entire thing.
Like from here down.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Oh, boy.
I didn't really tacked on the fucking difficult shit
at the very end of the game, huh?
All right.
100,000.
I need a good line.
All right.
I'm not going to use Tony Hawk.
Who's got good street games?
Just do manual spam.
I'll still get off.
Hold on.
I'll try.
I'm going to try manual spam.
Oh, boy.
Here we go.
Different.
Do it with somebody else.
I don't want Tony Hawk.
Very patient car.
Tony Hawk?
I don't think has the best manual game.
The best game.
All right.
Let's get some manuals.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Start it.
Messed it up.
Same thing on the road.
All right.
Let's go.
There it is.
All right.
Jesus Christ.
Okay.
I need to do four more.
Hawaii Huge Spine Challenge.
Oh, no.
No.
Why does it have to be spine every time?
No spines.
I don't want to do spines.
The leap of faith's got nothing on this spy.
Roll off the end of the hotel
and acid drop to the quarter pipe below.
Okay.
Use that speed to spine up to the far roof
and then hit the next two spines in a row.
Who's got the nuts to try it?
You don't look like you're going fast enough to do this.
Tony Hawk.
All right.
Acid drop.
This one's kind of fun.
Do it.
Just jump over.
Got it.
Now what?
Spine?
The spine of acid drop before we move the first hotel spines
before time runs out.
Did I not do four?
Just a little one right here.
Why would that be part of it?
That's it.
Okay.
Florida Tony Hawk's Pro Skater Challenge.
500,000 points.
Cool concept for someone's part.
Let's do it video game style.
We'll shoot four sick combo lines.
First combo, you can use whatever you want.
Next, only Tony Hawk three stuff.
No spine transfers.
Then only Tony Hawk two stuff.
No reverts or spine transfer.
I don't use them anyways.
Finally, only Tony Hawk one trick.
No manuals.
All right.
How about Van Margera?
30,000.
Okay.
Well, I didn't know we were going to go right now.
Now no cat puke.
I'm just going to manual the first two.
All right.
Van Margera is not very good at manuals.
Maybe I shouldn't do that.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't want, I'm going to save him.
Van Margera.
You said like BAM sucks?
I'm trying to get over it.
BAM's not good at anything.
Why don't I pick them?
What?
There's 68,000.
All right.
Let's do that again.
Man.
All right.
I'm going to have to, I can do that.
I can do it.
I'm not going to, I'm not going to rely on manuals.
Just for the first one, I will.
And did you see what just happened?
Magnet just grabbed that.
Okay.
Let's just do tricks.
Out of bounds game.
I got to do it with BAM.
I have to.
Did I fall?
Let's try that again.
Manuals really are the way to do it.
It seriously is.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
Now.
No manuals.
Damn it.
I thought I had it.
Manuals are allowed?
Wait.
That was the third time though, right?
Was it a Tony Hawk 3, Tony Hawk 2, Tony Hawk 1?
Four of them, bro.
It's a normal Tony Hawk 3, Tony Hawk 2, Tony Hawk 1.
All right.
This is the one.
No manual, right?
This is no reverts, spine transfers, or walking.
This is the last one, right?
Can I still manual here?
Just infinite grind.
Just grind in a circle.
But where, I don't know where that line is, man.
Grind in a circle?
Oh, why did you guys even say that?
The tree thing?
The road median.
That's not good.
Right, right, right to my right.
Okay.
Forever grind.
This is fun though.
I like it.
It's hard, but it's not too hard for me to not be like,
I don't think I can do this.
All right.
I turned the wrong way.
It's fucking hard, but it's not like I can't do it.
I'll do it eventually.
Imagine this on stick.
Shit, I went off the side.
This is the least fun part of the game.
Yeah.
Yeah, it is.
It's still good though.
It's still fun.
I mean, it makes you have to play well.
Did you learn anything, you know?
Did you learn whatever the game's trying to teach you?
It's good if you're good at the game.
Yeah, sure.
Times 13?
That's not, no.
Isn't that usually the case?
To get good at something, don't you have to do it
and play it and do it for a while?
How do you get good at anything?
You don't just start good at something.
That's not how it works.
I played all the Tony Hawk games.
Yes.
Yes, I did.
20 years ago.
And we did Tony Hawk 2 on the Dreamcast a year ago.
Yes, I've played all these games before.
Oh, when I was 17.
Okay, let's go.
The tree.
That's it.
Guys, this is a bad idea.
This is a very bad idea.
With Bam Margera?
Wait, do spam tricks?
What do you mean spam tricks?
Wait, what?
Wait, while you're grinding, I can do,
I can hold like X and Y and...
Oh man, I don't know if I'm gonna be able to do that shit.
I don't know if Bam can handle that.
I guess, okay, I can.
I can do it.
All right.
All right, I can do it.
I'll do it on the next run.
I have to get there again, though.
I don't know if Bam can handle this.
Just do something!
Do something!
Here we go.
Go.
San Diego Transfer Challenge.
Fuck you.
No one's ever shot at San Diego like this before.
I've got filmers spread all across Balboa Park.
Is that how the song goes?
We just need a burly vert dog to try and hit all the transfers we've set up.
Okay.
Uh, Boston.
No.
Who has good air?
Boston versus Musco?
Probably Musco.
Neither.
Transvert transfer photoshoot.
No, I can do this.
Just hold R.
Or hit R.
Okay, there's one.
How many are there?
Over there.
He's praying for me.
Okay.
More of this way.
No, there isn't.
He's taking a picture to laugh at you.
Funny LML comedy.
Fucking comedy moment.
A little too far.
I still got it?
I got it.
Fuck you, buddy.
You're in Tony Hawk's way.
Wait.
Oh, do I have to...
Come on.
Get out of the fucking way.
Matthew McConaughey is on his way.
I got it.
Not very good, but I still got it.
Okay, let me just slow down and do this the way it should be done.
Okay.
Uh, so how bad is Causton's air again?
Somebody said.
Here?
Over here?
I don't see anything over here.
They're on the roof?
No.
Wait, what about in here?
I mean, that could be one.
Oh.
This one?
It's not up here.
Yeah, this...
Where else would it be?
Over here?
Oh, there's one over here.
Only one?
There's a corner one.
What is...
I haven't even seen what the hell I'm supposed to be doing.
You want me to go from here to here?
Wait, what does he want me to do?
Over the...
Up on the roof.
Oh.
Over the roof.
Well, shit.
Okay.
In here?
We'll just delete the cars.
Three stair ones.
Okay.
There's another one back here.
And I've skated by it.
Okay.
Now, go up on the roof.
Over back here.
Good.
Was there one?
Wait, is there one over here?
I don't think I looked over here.
What does he mean?
He misused it.
What the hell are you trying to do?
All right.
Over the roof?
Just a spine transfer?
From here to there?
Through the opening?
Ram.
Not a spine transfer.
Yeah, you're supposed to go from bird to bird.
This one?
Like, from here to here?
It's probably that one.
He's not even aiming the camera over here.
Is there one on the other side?
I don't get it.
The roof has a ramp.
What is it?
Like, here?
Oh, okay.
That.
I see.
All right, all right, all right.
So I have to go.
Now I know.
Wasn't it?
Wait.
How is that not it?
Other side?
So you want me to come up from that side?
Okay.
This side.
I know where it is now.
Well, I killed the photographer.
There's one.
That still doesn't solve the problem.
There's this two more somewhere.
Where on earth are the last two that I haven't seen?
I didn't do the first one?
That's bad.
I can go back and get it.
I'm going to call a legend.
Dominance before it gives me a warm reception.
Double war with weapons.
Give me shit.
Throw him the sword.
Dust him just as well.
That fucking car.
No, that fucked that car.
Fuck that car.
That ruined everything.
Unless I can get this one.
Eww.
How did there be a mission here?
I don't know.
I'm going to fall again.
Should I just do it?
All right.
Now go this way.
Up and in?
These guys are going to have a bad day.
I did it?
Did he get the photo?
Okay.
He got it.
Now where are the last?
I know one back there I didn't do.
But where are the last two?
Is that a photographer?
Up here?
Let's just spine up here.
Shit.
I see one there.
There's nobody here.
There's one up there though.
Where did I see that?
Isn't that like up there?
Yeah.
I gotta get up here.
So I need just a view.
Is one in there?
All right.
In there.
Wasn't I in here already?
Oh, this motherfucker is right here.
Oh, man.
They're both right here.
All right.
Let's go.
That's too bad.
There's no ramp on that side.
No ramp on that side.
Just take it slow.
I did it.
Last one.
Jersey spine trick spot challenge.
Big apple spot challenge.
Slam a jam of Moscow's lost tapes.
I'm not going to be able to do it.
No, there's no way.
I'm not capable of that.
Who wants to leave his mark on red square?
There's no way I'll do big apple.
I'm sorry.
This is not going to happen.
Those ledges are rough.
So make sure you warm up before you go.
All right, Muska.
Ten tapes.
I feel like Muska doesn't have very good grind.
Oh, boy.
What would that even happen?
Don't tell me what.
You can't come in here with that.
Don't tell him what.
Why you can't come in here with that?
What is it?
Why are you saying that?
He doesn't know.
I mean, I do.
How do I look at a character's stats?
Oh, no.
This buster.
He's not good for this.
What was slam a jam on again?
No.
What?
Jersey spine trick spot challenge.
I didn't even look at this one.
Peralta was right.
This old spine is a big ghetto,
but it'll definitely turn heads if one of you guys can get.
I mean, he is sideways tricks as you go over it
and we'll have a killer part to lead off the team video.
All right.
What do we need to do?
Hit the tricks over the train station spine.
Wait, I guess there's a secret level over there.
Look at that.
This is going to be it.
That's it.
Oh, I did it.
I did it.
I beat Tony Hawk's pro skater underground.
But that didn't work.
I can't even say, like,
I don't know how it goes that fast.
Once you do it fast enough, stop.
Let's take a look at our sick video, man.
Blush force video.
I'm Chad Muska.
Oh, sick.
And then we took that photo.
Nice, Tony.
Sick.
Oh, that was clean.
Oh, yeah.
Now do the thing where you fall forward on the front part of your neck
and your legs kick you in the back of the head.
We've got a lot of footage of that.
Did the editor put it in?
Eric Costin.
Let's see it.
That shit is so hard.
It's so difficult to do this stuff.
That's beautiful.
That was a manual all the way.
Skateboarding's fun to watch.
Yeah, it's just, it's a craft.
It's an art form.
Wow.
No fucking way.
All right, bam.
Let's see it.
Oh, there we go.
Yep.
This is where all that footage went.
It just like falls down.
Accurate replay.
Remember when I rode the ATV?
Oh, shit there.
Remember when I drove the car like that?
Nice.
You know how much that hurts your back?
Planting from that high.
Do I get one too?
You've got to be kidding me.
That was phenomenal.
How do humans do this?
All right, this dude is a video game.
Actual video game character right here.
Cardi Mullen is the greatest of all time in the street.
Holy shit, that was awesome.
I just kind of wanted to watch these.
I just want to watch skateboarding videos now.
You can just do those little transfers over.
Little railings.
This shit is so dangerous.
But completely captivating at the same time.
Uh oh.
Illegal picnic basket jump.
Here comes my video.
I saw him do a royal flush and he got arrested.
You blew every cent you own on that car.
That was a mistake.
Cigarettes?
Oh, my cassette tape.
What do you say?
One last trip around the neighborhood.
Winner takes the tape.
All right, one last trip.
I've waited a long time for this.
I'm gonna light you up.
I'm gonna light you up, homie.
Oh, boy.
Why does he have to fire?
He's throwing, like, grenades at me.
That's not fair. I don't get grenades.
Oh, shit!
He's up top.
He's got a hit. Jump over it.
Hit the line.
He's fucking schooling me right now.
I mean, but...
This is gonna be rough.
Two hours later.
I kinda hope not.
It's really just the end of the game.
I'm trying to jump through those.
It's giving me a lot of trouble.
Why does he have Molotov?
Molotov?
That's a great question.
To make this
already difficult
way more difficult.
Something like that.
I'm gonna stop getting off that.
All right, here we go.
Here we go.
Jesus Christ!
What? Oh, no!
The power lines.
I don't think I can even get up there anymore.
Hold on. Time for that one.
Not even halfway there, either.
Two minutes, too.
I'd stay up here.
Did I not get it?
Yeah, I can't get this part down.
I could jump through.
Where does he jump? He jumps right here.
He hits me like that every time.
Rhythm Heaven?
This is probably...
I would probably put this...
This is probably harder than Rhythm Heaven. Did I not get it?
I don't think I got that one.
No, I didn't.
All right, save.
I'm just gonna try to stay with him.
I could jump over it, too.
The whole screen.
As long as you're in the vicinity, you get it.
Here he goes. Didn't get it.
Oh, man.
This might...
I'm not sure a nine-hour stream Jeremy can beat this level.
I'm not sure this is gonna happen.
I don't know if a nine-hour stream Jeremy can complete this.
I'll try for another 30 minutes or so.
Let's see if I can get it.
Watch out.
Up the wall.
I think it's over.
Unless I can stay...
It's hard to see the wires.
The wires are almost just blended with the background.
I can't even see them.
Level up my stats.
Where are all my stats?
I can't even see them.
Air spin. They're all really good.
Run, flip, ray.
Actually, rail is really not that good.
Crying for 15 seconds.
Crying for 20 seconds.
Haven't done that yet.
No, I got it.
I...
I mean, I'm gonna try.
And when he abandoned you in Russia...
I do. It was bad.
Yeah.
I think nine hours straight Tony Hawk Jeremy.
I think it's time to go to bed, son.
You've been up all day playing Tony Hawk, son.
You can beat the last level another time.
No, I can do it. I can do it, dad.
Son, it's okay.
You don't have to beat it right now.
I missed.
Shut up, dad.
Are you your own dad?
It'd be odd, wouldn't it?
This is the part that I get caught up on every time.
Up, and then drive?
Drive? No.
The worst thing is if you miss it,
it's just over.
Turn the music off.
Alright, I'm gonna try it without music.
Just skateboard sounds.
I'm just trying not to do any tricks.
I'm just trying to grind and just stay...
I'm not trying to do anything fancy.
Alright, every time.
That stays on it.
I don't know.
So he just, he doesn't jump or anything.
He just stays on the line.
It just rips him to the...
I just didn't have any speed.
I was gonna fall off anyways.
Alright, 10 more attempts
and I'm gonna do this tomorrow.
I'm out of gas, man.
I just am.
I was probably out of gas like 40 minutes ago.
But I should be able to do this tomorrow.
After eating a good breakfast.
Cheats? No.
I cheat?
Why would I cheat?
You can still make it.
What about Helm's Deep?
That's a different kind of game though.
This requires
a huge amount of
concentration.
Helm's Deep was just running in circles kicking ladders.
So it's a little
different.
Just get the funny bad ending.
Funny bad ending?
Just do the
infinite grind cheat.
How far am I gonna go?
5, son.
I don't reliably get it
to be able to get up there.
It's something to do with how I'm jumping or how...
I don't understand.
Don't let the pervert skateboarder win.
Did I miss that?
Why am I reading chat right now?
I think I've clocked out.
I'm just looking over there.
What are people saying?
I'm teleporting up to the top of the building
instead of the pipe that I'm trying to grind on.
There's another ramp to the right?
I'm supposed to be doing his
line, right?
Aren't I supposed to follow him to grab these things?
Get a grind
to gutter. That's what I'm trying to do.
That keeps on going up to the top of the roof.
See what he does here?
I did it, but...
Alright, you know, I'm not gonna restart.
Let me just look at this.
I feel like I've done the same...
He rips to the right.
When he gets up there, he goes like this.
And he goes like...
Like...
What's that?
You gotta get on it?
Let me just practice.
If I just spam Y,
it takes me over here.
If I just go like...
It just snaps to the wire.
My balance is shit though.
I need to get my rail up.
Is there like a free skate
where I can just get...
My balance is really not great.
Let me try this like one or two more times.
I'm gonna use it.
I turned it off.
Ultra concentration.
Alright, same theory.
So just...
Here it is.
I'm still up here.
Now what?
He goes down.
Where'd he go? Where'd he go?
Where's he? Back?
It's alright! It's alright!
I didn't know it was gonna rip that way.
What are you talking about? What?
How does he do that?
I think I can do... How does he get up there?
Hold on, can I stay here?
Holy shit, man.
You gotta be serious.
Alright, let's try this again.
I was kinda close.
I think that's better than I've ever done.
That might've been the only one to find out.
Get this down.
I jumped over it.
I'm delayed by like 4 tenths of a second right now.
Every time that hits me.
Let your older brother do it.
Imagine this older brother scenario here.
This would suck total asshole.
Being the older brother in this scenario.
This isn't just like jump over Bowser.
Little older brother.
Can you just jump over Bowser and grab the axe?
Yeah, of course I can, little brother!
Look at me! I can do it!
I'm so good at video games.
Can you beat this for me, older brother?
Yeah!
Need me to get another axe?
From, uh, dear old Bowser there?
Nope, this!
Oh!
Let me see it!
This is the ultimate older brother scenario.
I would try it.
Here we are.
That's another wired knife.
I'm calling it at 9 hours.
Actually have to call it.
I have to call it at 9 hours.
I'll stream it tomorrow too.
Day 5 in a row coming up here.
And I don't want...
I don't want to stream like 60 hours this week.
We're like crossing like
50 something hours
as of tomorrow.
I really didn't plan on having like
4, 50 plus hour like
I had it but I lost it.
People are working more than
60 hours a week?
That's a lot of time.
That's 10 hours a day, 6 days a week.
Holy shit.
70 hours a week?
70?
I was always at like 38.
Like 35 to like
40.
7 fucking hours, holy shit.
That's a lot of time.
I overshot it.
Alright, 8, 56.
That's 8 days a week.
It depends on how many hours you work.
You work like 20 straight hours.
Like 12 straight hours.
That's a lot of time.
Yeah, I got that
9 hour a week schedule.
I can't even see the wires.
I don't even know which one I'm jumping to.
Just hold Y?
Yeah, I was.
I'm really just trying to follow him.
That's distracting in its own way.
How am I not going
far enough?
I'm waiting for the...
I don't think it's a complete disaster yet.
Fucking rail sucks.
I have 2 minutes to do this.
How was I not turned all the way?
What the fuck, man?
Having like 60%
rail is actually fucking ruining this whole thing.
Not having the rail
at 100% is actually
ruining these runs.
Without a doubt. I don't even know where he is.
I need to level up like 5
more times.
To be able to reliably probably do this.
I'm up in front of you.
Dude, why am I even...
This is where I got to last time.
He goes up and then he rides the...
No!
That's the farthest I've gone.
It was right there. I was so close.
I just didn't know what was next.
Do it in one combo. Do it in one combo!
That's the first time I've ever even seen that one.
Should have just done the flush.
I feel like I can do it now.
Let's see. I'm supposed to stop
right now.
Why even give him fucking firebombs?
This shit already sucks.
Why?
Oh, boss.
That Eric Wynn.
Why can't I just push him off the fucking balcony?
Why?
Is it there? I tried to wait to
jump on the other side of the bridge.
I feel like
transferring there is
probably not a great idea.
Slow it down.
What are you up to?
What are you two boys
up to?
That's Adam Sandler doing his grandmother.
Alright, I got plenty of time.
Oh, you motherfucker. Are you kidding me?
This sucks.
Why?
This sucks,
asshole.
This sucks.
Jump higher.
That's a good idea.
This is where it gets all fucked up.
Speaking of fucking up.
How are you going to sleep tonight
knowing Eric schooled you?
I'm not going to. I'm not done.
I'm at like 38
out of 41. I was going to throw in
the towel, but
I didn't think I was going to get past
16. So I can't throw
the towel in now because I saw the end of
the game. Quick, gas
light it. You don't need to gas
light me. I'm already
burning. This fire is hot.
Why can I not do this?
It's one of the things I can't fucking do.
It's that stupid thing.
It's like one of the only things
I can't do now. Oh my god.
Go back.
Go back. Alright, here we go.
Playground bullshit.
I was on the fucking power cord
for too long. Just get off. I have a new strategy.
I don't give a shit. Just grab him.
You stabbed me in the back.
Why did you stab me in the fucking
back? Dumb thing
to do. You keep getting to that
stupid part. And yes, I'm
just going to jump. I'm going to get off the fucking
thing. And I'm just going to grab him because
I can't. I can't
do it. I can do it while walking.
Or I'm just going to say fuck it
and just practice it.
I've gotten so far. Like what the
hell, Eric?
How did he drop you in the ocean?
Hey, just stop
sucking.
Yeah.
Maybe we should do that too.
What other phrases can I get out of you?
This streamer sucks.
Stop
pretending.
Stop stalling, idiot.
Twitch chat
comes with four phrases
and has a karate chop action.
Alright, I have
I don't do it now, I'm off.
I'm more of a molding
meltdown PlayStation
fucking 2 stream.
Who cares?
Alright, here we go. What is it? It's Xbox.
How dare you
correct me? Did you just
correct the streamer?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's corrected?
Okay.
How did I miss that?
I held Y the whole time?
I held Y and I waited so long.
His ego.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're saying it's on the Xbox
and make me look bad
in front of fucking like 400
people?
I can't.
I don't get it, I don't understand.
What the fuck did you...
I'm holding Y when I jump
too. It seems so
finicky.
Tap Y?
I mean, that's what I
was tapping Y before and I got a bunch of
people telling me that I should hold Y.
Which one is it? I was falling off.
I'm like, that's almost like
I'm not getting enough air.
What is my air even at?
Doesn't it feel like I'm not getting enough air?
Apparently, I don't know.
Breathe.
I thought I was too late
before, now I'm too early.
That's the worst jump of the whole entire run.
The other ones I could probably get if I did them enough times.
It was definitely too early, yeah.
I figured maybe because the bridge goes
up before it goes down.
Maybe. Let's see.
Plus, I have to fucking worry
about the stupid triangle on the screen.
Like that. Meltdown?
No, I don't think so.
I don't think so.
I'm alright right now.
Fucking... I'm fine. Hey, you know
what does it say? You don't have to come over for career day
anymore? Wait, what, why?
Go to bed? I'm fine.
Don't worry.
This is the end, too. And I'm not playing
Xbox tomorrow.
We're doing Diablo 2 tomorrow.
So, it's a whole other
setup. So, it's either now or
it's probably never. I didn't even
mean to jump. I let go. My hands
are sweaty. I had my hand
let go of me. I didn't mean to jump.
Let's go. Let's go. This is it.
All night, boys and girls.
You're not. Something is
wrong. What am I doing wrong?
Is it still too early?
I can't even fucking tell,
man. How far
do I have to be on this stupid
thing? You're supposed to have max
stats. Am I really
just doing this for no reason because I don't have enough stats
to do it? I mean, I've gotten pretty
damn close. Yes.
No. Why
do I feel like people saying no want
this to be a 12 hour stream?
I've waited so long.
If I wait any longer, I'm going to fall
off the damn bridge. Losing too much
momentum. You need to jump
more.
That's what I was thinking. Just like jump.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
He's going sideways.
The absolute worst
time. Plus, the guy going sideways.
That's what you guys have been
talking about. I was wondering what the fuck
you guys are talking about. Admin, he's
going sideways. That's
what you guys are on about. Okay.
I think I'm going crazy. How is
it possible? I feel like you're missing
Tony Hawk.
God damn it.
Why do you have to keep me
addicted here on this
fucking burn
into muscle memory?
This one stage.
I haven't even done a royal flush in a while
either. What a fucking mistake.
Now we're getting, alright. Now
we're getting, we're getting to this, yeah.
You know the stage of
video game madness?
When you do
the same thing so many times
that
it starts to become a dream.
I'm having a dream about this game
right now, this stage, right here.
Your skills are depleting.
Yes.
Alright, I'm calling it. I'm calling it.
That's it. I'm calling it. I've called it. Now I
have to do it. I have to call it. I've called it.
It's over. I've called it.
It's over. That's it. That's enough.
We'll be live tomorrow with Diablo 2.
I've called it.
I can't sit here and do this anymore.
This burning hole in my brain.
I can't.
I'm gonna go to the, oh here comes another
doctor bit. Oh, Derby, you go to the doctor
when something happens in a video game and you get
like mad? Yeah, you come to me every time.
I know. Let me go, let me see if I can figure
out what you're gonna say. Hmm.
You're going to say, uh,
hey doc, something's wrong. And the doctor's
gonna say, oh, did you play Tony Hawk 2?
Yes.
That was what I was about to do.
The time loop.
I don't want to do this anymore.
If I don't actually get into the next
like three attempts,
I'm out. Maybe I'll try it again tomorrow.
Clip that. Somebody clip it.
And slow it down. For the frame.
It's my stats.
I want a frame by
frame analysis. I want to hire
like an e-sports pro to do a frame
by frame analysis is why I didn't jump
higher at the end of that.
Don't grind on the ledge. What do you want me to
jump? You don't want to, wait,
walk it? I was lucky.
I didn't even mean to get that. Do you see
how fucking horrible that was? I did
not even get that. I don't have enough
stats. Somebody, I want an e-sports
pro to clip that one and
tell me what happened with that.
Sorry, I fell into it.
I fell into it. Sorry, did you get speed?
Why did I go into a manual?
The Xbox controller with the one
big fucking button. One big
ass button.
Get it! Get up, it's okay. Your
knee's gonna be fine, honey. Your
knee's gonna be fine, honey!
Slam city jammer.
You lucky little bitch. Get back here.
You ain't nothing to me.
I can't. I can't
anymore. I can't. That was fucking
terrible. That was
that was terrible.
That was unbelievably awful.
That was so bad. I don't even feel
fulfilled. Praise
water. Dude,
I almost turned the camera on.
I almost turned the camera
on and did a wink right at the end.
Because I was like, fuck it, it's over and I'm just gonna get
a wink out. Oh my god,
that was so painful. I wasn't even that big
of a deal either. I'm so sorry, everybody.
That was probably so painful.
But yeah, look at that!
That game was great. What a fun game.
Oh, that was a really fun game.
Just as good as I remember.
We got a ton of subs, too.
Boiki gave 20 community subs.
Okay, so somebody gave...
Secret level.
We got Iron Man?
Marvel Iron Man
Iron Man and Marvel characters
are... I'm not going to bed.
Not yet. I'm not going to bed
yet. I want to see Iron Man. I want to do a secret level
with Iron Man. And Gene
Simmons. God damn you,
Tony Hawk.
I want to address these bits here.
SoupGG gave a thousand bits,
but first of all, they said cheesesteak guy here. Okay,
so cheesesteak guy, the guy that said he would beat
Big Apple's challenge before 10.
So I'll throw up my cheesesteak on my keyboard. I didn't,
by the way.
I just want to say you're the worst Tony Hawk player
I've ever seen.
It's not even true. You give this controller to a baby
and they won't be able to get past level one, I guarantee you.
That being said, this is probably my favorite stream you've ever done.
Thank you, Jeremy. Love you. Thanks for playing my favorite game
ever.
Let's try that again.
SoupGG says...
SoupGG says, hey, cheesesteak
guy here.
If you don't know,
somebody told me
SoupGG said that
I can't even do it again.
SoupGG said that if
I beat Tony Hawk Pro Skater
Underground,
Big Apple spot challenge in
four attempts, he would throw up a cheesesteak on his keyboard.
I didn't, by the way,
if you're just joining us. That didn't happen.
That being said,
you're probably the worst Tony Hawk player
I've ever seen. I said that's not true.
This is probably my favorite stream you've ever done.
Thank you for playing my favorite game ever.
I'm not the worst Tony Hawk player
you've ever seen. If I was the worst Tony Hawk player
you've ever seen, I wouldn't have beaten
the game. I would have...
Guys, worst Tony Hawk player ever
means you can't even do a manual.
You don't even know what it is.
Like, you don't even know what a combo is. You just do a kickflip
over a ledge.
You don't even know...
I think that you cannot be claimed as one of the
worst Tony Hawk players ever,
if you get a hundred thousand points
on a combo. You just not.
That's impossible.
People just do a kickflip and get a hundred points
and they're done. You're the worst
player to have beaten the game.
That's like so not even true.
Even worst Tony Hawk player would beat
Eric first try. That's not even true.
That's not even true. That guy's gonna whip.
Alright. That's dangerous, mate.
That's not how you use a whip.
You crack a whip. You don't
swing a whip.
It's just in the Neversoft office.
These guys are doing this wrong. Someone's gonna get hurt.
Funny story.
For the Carnival stream,
instead of Polypolite and
Cuddles,
we were in talks
to have a different
clown on that stream.
And that clown was a
kind of one of those...
He said it was kind of like a freak show clown.
He was going to bring
a whip and I
was gonna put a cigarette in my mouth and he was going to
whip a cigarette out of my mouth.
And we were seconds
away from signing this guy.
But the reason why we didn't is in the 0.01%
chance that he like
blows up my face.
So we were like, no,
we can't. That's not a good
idea. That's a
family guy joke. I mean,
it's a sideshow act.
So he was gonna like,
hey, I'm gonna whip the thing out of your mouth.
Because he's very accurate and
that would have been legendary.
But I can't. No. We talked about it
extensively. The guy was a really nice guy too.
He's really like
interesting, really fun, smart person.
Imagine if your childhood
friends stole your jokes and got more Twitch
subscribers than you. Would you
let him win or would you beat him in a clown off?
That was a bit message.
I had to read it. Alright, that's somebody's
fucking tooth. Where's Iron Man?
Oh my god.
Are you serious?
Edit tricks.
Special tricks.
The scanner. The boot
burst and fire blaster.
Let's go to
didn't we get a new level?
We got Venice, right?
Alright, here we go.
Iron Man.
Make Iron Man
flush. Oh, that was sand.
Here we go.
His head rocked back.
Okay, I need to, I have to leave.
I have to leave. I actually have to leave.
This is too much.
I just want to try.
Let's just go to Manhattan.
He's going insane. Hotter than hell?
Oh fuck, hold on.
I will watch the second ending, I promise.
The last time you're going to see it, we might as well get it out of
our system now.
Did it get knocked down? Who pushed me over?
Holy shit.
This lady means business.
That fucking Ryan
Mancliffe is going to haunt me for like the next six hours.
Hotter than hell.
Do his
special.
Big upper special.
Down right B, left right
Y.
We need to get special up.
Oh, this is the kiss level.
Why?
It seems interesting.
Turn the music on for this stage.
I mean, I kind of have to, right?
Let's go.
Let's do down right B.
Get the letters. Get the letters.
No, that's 59,000.
This is my favorite kiss song.
Give me that thing.
All right, that's it. Flush him.
Can I get a double flush to end it?
Get the letters. Get the letters.
Let me get the letters.
Okay.
I got it.
I got this S.
Get the letters.
Guys, I'm so demanding.
So commanding and demanding.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna
I don't know where the other letters even are.
All right, if I don't get 100,000 points
right now, I'm gonna get a 10
fucking, I'm gonna give 10
I'm gonna give 10
french fries to Kim.
Go to McDonald's next.
All right, it's K. Did I get it?
K. I got it.
Okay. K. S.
Where's the other one?
I'm blind. I got that.
Oh, I thought that was just a glass panel.
Look at the other panels underneath it.
Okay. K.
I. S. Where's the last S?
In the ring.
I'm gonna pierce my mind.
I'm gonna pierce
my mind.
Why can't I get up here?
I'm gonna pierce my mind.
Transfer. I mean, it looks like I
I just know people are gonna be very
upset about that. All right, transfer.
It's in a weird spot.
Can I just grab it?
I'm the damn thing.
R to transfer. Let's do it.
Just vert transfer. Yeah, I'm just doing
vert. Just trying to do vert transfer.
Just like the
The half pipe is behind the
I'm not pressing R.
The half pipe is behind it.
Can I just spine over this?
No, just spine over that.
Why would I try to do this?
All right, now I have to just jump through those.
What?
Oh, I can do it this way.
Wait.
Guys, you have to give me
a little bit of a break here.
It's been 10 hours of Tony Hawk.
And I've peed two times.
So, yeah.
It's not going as clean as it could be.
Congratulations, you unlocked the kiss movie.
Do it again.
They put on a show for you.
You're gonna get banned from Twitch.
It's in the video game.
I'm not gonna get banned from Twitch for everything that's in the video game.
Get out of the way.
I have to get up here. Wait, that's me.
That scared the shit out of me.
I didn't even mean to do that. I just hit L.
Oh, no.
Here comes a
crazed kiss fan.
He wants to get on stage with Gene Simmons.
He just wants a selfie.
Why am I the only one
falling down?
Look, it's us. We did it.
Okay, it's funny.
Okay, time to go to bed.
That's it.
Alternate ending. Okay, we'll do
alternate ending right now.
Oh, my God.
Alternate. That was Tony Hawk Underground.
And it's a fucking fantastic game.
I highly recommend it. If you have a 360
and there's a hard drive inside of it,
get Tony Hawk's Underground. Tony Hawk's Underground 2
is behind me.
It's right there.
You can play that at some point, too.
That was a fucking really fun time.
We stepped over the
we stepped over the meltdown
area. We just put our toe over it.
It'll last like an hour and a half.
We're good. Just enough to
have an issue.
It was a lot of fun.
Seriously, these games are fucking incredible.
I had an absolute blast.
I'm so happy I got to experience this
because I played all the main ones.
Tony Hawk, Tony Hawk 2, Tony Hawk 3,
Tony Hawk 4. I never really
did this one.
I played it like here and there randomly, but
I never really played it.
But let's do the alternate ending.
This is what happens if what? What's the
scenario here?
How does this end? What's the scenario?
Why does this happen?
Somebody link it right here.
This is
Tony Hawk's Underground alternate
ending. Make sure I can
hear. Make sure you
guys can hear, too.
That's important. Alright, let's watch it.
Here we go. This is the
alternate ending to Tony Hawk Underground.
Aww.
How cute.
Two little skaters and their
ghetto shop.
Her Juvideo went over pretty good.
I guess kids dig that goofy soul skating crap.
I tell you what,
I'll buy you out for half a mil right now.
I got my checkbook.
I told you. It was never about the money.
Right, right, I forgot.
Mr. Pure,
I should have fixed you back in Tampa.
Tell it to your posse. We're through.
I've got everything I need.
Not this. Remember?
Hawaii building jump?
Helicopter? That was some sick
footage. Too bad no one ever
saw it. You backstabbing
mob flipping cockroach.
Hey, what do you say?
One last trip around the neighborhood.
Winner takes the
tape.
I wanted to do that.
That was...
Remember I was saying, like, why can't I just push
him over and get it? Why can't I throw him down
and get it? Wow.
How do you get this ending?
You got to get that scene. You have to earn it.
You beat the game a second time. Oh.
So when you get through a second time, they're just like, yeah.
You can just push him over. You don't have to do
the hard line
thing. That's funny.
Alright, that's where we're going to end it.
I'll see you guys tomorrow for Diablo 2
Hardcore. It's been a while. It's been
a week, a couple of weeks actually,
hasn't it? It's been like week and a half.
See if we can beat Diablo.
I'm looking forward to it.
See you tomorrow. Starting at the same time
so probably around two o'clock.
Somewhere, yeah, two-ish. Two.
Same time. But let's do the bits.
Let's go back earlier.
I got to get this off my screen because
it's covering up everything. Thanks for joining me.
Thanks for joining us.
Hope you had a good time. I did.
We'll see you all tomorrow. Take care. Get some sleep.
See you soon.
But let's do the bits.
It's time for slime. Thanks for 500
bits. They say thug
hype. This was
one of those streams. A lot of people were waiting for it
and it was a good one.
Jay Onzel.
Thanks for the 300 bits. Hi, Jeremiah. I was so hyped
for the stream today because I loved this game and I'm just imagining
you as the Steve Buscemi skater meme.
We had a wink too?
That's a real wink.
Alright, let's go.
What was that image? Why was that like
back here? Look,
how long have I been in darkness?
This room's not dark.
You want me to blow up your immersion right now?
The room's not dark.
Holy shit, that's pretty bad here.
The exposure was down
low because I started the stream during the
day. Sorry, guys.
You look tired. Audio
is, yeah, audio's bad because of the
uh, I wonder why.
It's past my bedtime. No, I
guess I gotta eat something. I gotta
eat something. I ate
before the stream, but as a lot of you guys
know, I don't eat on stream.
Not usually.
I don't really like it. I did wink. Yes, I did
when it was dark. Fine, you wanna
loop Honda. Thanks for the 300
bits. They say uncanny. Uncanny.
Yes, it's online. 300
bits. Never thought in my life I would hear a
Quasimodo song on a Jerma stream.
Yeah, sorry to all
the VOD watchers. You probably
won't be able to watch any of this
stream. There's probably gonna be chunks
that are watchable, but
start the video now.
It hasn't taken on yet.
Quick. Load it into cache
on your browser. Quick. Do it.
Yeah, because I'm almost, this whole stream's
gonna be gone. But this was a, uh,
this was a fun live only
stream because there was just copyright
music playing almost the entire game.
Download it.
Yeah, thanks. AtroLux
Atrox, thanks for the thousand bits.
Ten dollars. Oh, there's nothing on the screen.
Thank you AtroLux.
Dropping this because this game is in my top five ever
thanks for playing it, man.
It is really, really, really good.
I wish they would make more of these.
Sorry.
Something in the throat there.
I wish they would make more of these and not
iPad games.
But I'm not sure if there's a market for it anymore.
Let's talk sad
truths here. I don't know
if there's really a huge market for
arcade skating games anymore.
Everybody wants skate 4.
Skate 4, people
requested every single year.
But I don't know if they would
What? What's going on?
Oh, God.
Sorry.
I just don't know. There might not be a
market for it anymore. It's just
it kind of fell out of popular
culture. There's a lot
of die hard fans of these games
for very good reason.
And I would say I would be one of them.
I never played skate, though.
I heard skate 3 was good. I never played it.
But I have played all the Tony Hawk's.
Pretty much. But people love it.
People love these things.
You did, didn't you?
I did not play skate 3.
Skate 3, no.
Tony Hawk 2.
You're probably thinking of Tony Hawk 2.
Yeah. That's definitely what you're thinking of.
Yeah.
Bulbaswag, thanks for the 999
bits. 999.
I've been on vacation, so I've missed the last few streams.
They look like a blast, though.
Yeah, I think Outer Wilds
was fun and
interesting. This stream was
kind of crazy and all
over the place. A lot of different
streams this week.
We're really going to chill out tomorrow.
He did play it.
I don't know. I don't click links in my chat.
Sorry.
We started. We watched like an
action movie with Siraswrath.
And then we did
explore and do the puzzle game
and figure out the
Outer Wilds.
And then we had a stream
today, which was
I laughed like every five seconds
of this stream. And then tomorrow
we're just going to dial it back and do a chill stream tomorrow.
He liked an old Tony Hawk game
better than Outer Wilds.
That's not fair, though.
Do I have any interest in Warcraft 3
Reforged? No.
Because I heard it sucks.
I heard
it's really not that
much of a reforging
and more of a repainting.
So I don't know
if I'm going to care that much about it.
It also
it also does not give me
very much confidence in what
Diablo 4 is going to look like.
From my understanding
it's kind of
stripped a bunch of stuff from it.
The graphics really aren't that good.
They didn't really remake
very much. They kind of upped some textures
and some models, right?
Custom maps you don't own anymore.
It belongs to Blizzard. Well, you know why they're
doing that, right? You know
why they're doing the custom games or
ours? Because look what happened
to Dota. Dota was
created in one of their IPs.
And it
created one of the biggest video
game genres
on Earth. And they couldn't
take it. They couldn't control it.
So in their minds
what they're probably thinking is if another
Dota comes up in these custom
games, we will own it.
No one's going to make custom games
now. I would probably jump on
and mess around in tower defense. That was
one of my favorite things to do.
Tower defense, hero line wars.
It was a lot of fun.
But you kind of take away the incentive
to make a
game mode for us.
Make a new fun custom game.
But if anyone ever thinks
it's good, you can't
have it. It's ours.
You're ours now.
Custom game Golden Age
is long over. People just download Unity and Unreal.
But they actually have the chance to
make money. That's also another really good point.
That's a good point. That's a great point actually.
That you can just make
your own game now.
There's a lot of tools now that were sort of out of reach.
Some 15, 20 years ago.
I've played Beautiful Joe.
I have. They're amazing games.
Both of them.
Some of the best
GameCube and PS2 games.
Love them.
And they are behind me.
They're in two cases behind me. We're going to play them
very soon.
But let's keep going before it gets too late.
But thank you. That was Bulbaswag.
Thank you for the $9.99.
Rastnama, thanks for the 500 bits.
The first stream I've been able to catch.
Busy with college and life. I've been watching your stuff on YouTube for a while.
Glad I can actually catch a stream for even a small
while.
Appreciate you, Jerma. Glad to have you.
Thanks for stopping by and thanks for
$5.
One Trick Gaming, thanks for the five community subs.
Enyaz, thanks for the
$5.00. 500 bits.
Jerma, I'm a recent fan.
Since about October.
Cool. Welcome.
I'm giving you bits tonight as your Dreamcast video that just went up
was the only thing keeping me from falling into shock
because I just discovered a family member
took their life this morning.
That's horrible. I'm really sorry to hear that.
I am so sorry to hear that.
I'm in the UK studying abroad
in university. I'm away from my family
who live in the west of Ireland.
And your voice is keeping me calm.
So I needed to say thanks and keep doing you.
Enyaz, you're about to go
through, and you currently are going
through, a very, very, very, very difficult
time. Stay strong.
That's a really
terrible thing to happen.
Seek guidance if you need to.
Breathe.
Keep your head on your shoulders. That's tough.
Thank you so much for the
$500 bits.
I wish you and your family the best.
Thank you again.
We have five community subs from
Ferlitty. Thank you
Ferlitty. And just to touch on that
one more time about something.
I've been
fairly fortunate in my life
to not have somebody
potentially close to me pass away
suddenly. I can't imagine
the pain that
people could be feeling when that happens.
We joke around a lot and we fuck around
a lot on this stream
and stuff like that. I'm just
really, really, really sorry.
I cannot even imagine.
As I think about my life, you think about
what you and people
that you know that you've maybe seen
or done things with or grown up with.
I think that's why a lot of
people can feel
because you put yourself in that scenario.
Somebody said
life's unpredictable. Be safe.
Just do your best.
Do the best you can. That's all you can do.
I just wanted to kind of
say something else about that
because that's
not fun.
That's tough stuff.
The best you can is good enough. That's true.
Just do the best you can.
But SquimPST
gave 400 bits.
I've been wheel throwing this whole stream
and all I can think about is Bugleberry Pottery
ASMR, so thank you for that.
Nice.
You got a wheel? I imagine that would be
really, really relaxing just to throw on like a
TV show or a YouTube video
or stream and just wheel throw.
You can just sit there for
hours doing it.
Your viewers just plummeted to zero.
It's kind of just like a
neat little trick.
You know what I mean?
I know that I can do it.
But I can't do it as well as a lot of people
that are very, very good at it.
So it's almost just like a
neat little thing
that I can just turn on sometimes.
You look at some professional beatboxers
and you're like,
I'm going to beatbox
and I'm going to beatbox
You look at some professional beatboxers
they run circles around the stuff that I'm doing.
So capitalize
on an album. I don't
I'm not sure. It's kind of just like a hobby
thing. I just do it sometimes. I'll be in the shower
just doing it. But I
appreciate the fact that you think that it's good enough to
do that. You have the first
beatboxing gamer.
There are probably others.
I was initially a little
It was a little tough hearing my own voice in recordings
but I'm gradually getting used to it.
If you have any tips for a newcomer, I'd appreciate them.
Thanks for being you.
Something I learned a long
time ago is
do what you want to do.
It can get really, really
tricky.
You can kind of get in your own way
when you start to think about
instead of what you would want to do, what would
somebody else want to do.
Try not to compare yourself to other people.
That's also tough too because you're like oh
this person and me and this person do this
and how many people watch?
How many people sub to that person?
How many viewers do they have on YouTube?
Their videos are better than mine.
No they're not. I gotta make a better video. I gotta try
to make a better video than them. You can get
lost. Do you
do what you want to do and stock
up on baby food. The last part is
not a joke. We add
$30
Yeah 3000 bits from
Go Ike
$30 fucking dollars. It's a lot of money.
They say skate or die. Skate or die.
Thanks for the huge amount of money. That's 30
bucks. Is that a college tip?
No it's a streamer tip. That's a real
streamer tip. Alright so it's been
10 hours. You hear me out on this. This is very important.
It's been 10
hours of this stream being turned on.
I've gotten up from the chair a couple times.
I peed but I'm back here in about
2 minutes, 3 minutes each time.
10 hours and like
5 minutes of time
not on camera or not
on broadcast.
You gotta eat something. You gotta drink something.
You gotta have something available.
We've been here for 10 hours. Baby food.
Those little baby food packets
or even the little jars.
You can eat those in 5 seconds.
You know how easy it is to drink
just to slurp down one of those baby food
packets? It's got
vitamins. It's got fruits. It's
real shit. It's food. It's
just liquified. It's bananas.
Apples.
I'm not joking. No.
Stay here.
Okay.
Let me fix this. Okay.
So those of you that said this was not real.
It is. It's very real.
This is apple
banana. This is real.
Apple, banana, fruit on the go.
All natural. No spoon. You just twist
the shit off. Apple, banana,
fruit on the go. This is designed
for small children. Look at how small
this is. You give these
pouches to kids.
It's baby food. It's not baby
food. I mean,
who's gonna eat this?
Besides a baby. Who do you
know that's going to eat this besides a baby
or a toddler? Me.
Look at how simple this is. Done.
I just ate a full meal in
12 seconds.
Done. I can keep going.
A full baby meal.
Yeah, but a full baby meal is still a full
meal for somebody.
A full baby meal can keep
you going for another couple hours on live stream.
Or beef jerky.
I'm not crazy.
Everybody else is. It's really good.
And they're fucking so fast. It's easy.
You gotta find, streamer
tip, streamer
tip.
Find something that you can eat, that you can eat
quickly, that you can snack on.
Crackers. You know.
Cheese. Baby food.
Fucking go-go squeezers.
I don't think I was making this up.
You just eat an apple.
You know how long
it takes to eat a fucking apple?
It takes like 20 minutes
to eat a full apple. You have to
like, hey guys!
What do I do with the core? I got this like, fuck
my hands are all sticky. No. I just did it.
You gotta like sit there and eat it
and spin it around. The core is all
fucked up and gross.
You can eat the core. Don't eat, don't eat the-
Listen. Somebody just said that. Don't eat the fucking core
of an apple. Don't do that.
Why would you? Don't eat the core of an apple.
The core is- Don't eat the core of an apple.
Why would you don't eat the core of an apple? It's like
rawhide.
The police are coming to
take you somewhere
to get to hell.
It's fu- It's apple
sauce, guys.
The number one ingredient is apples
bananas. It's apple sauce
in a little jar.
It's not a big deal.
It's literally 70 calories.
Yeah. It's 70 fucking
calories of super
ultra hyper energy. Alright, I'm done.
I can't believe nobody wants to hear my fucking
tip. I've been doing this for a day. I've been doing this
I've been doing this for 10 years.
You don't think I've figured some secrets?
Some secrets seem strange.
I've been doing this for a decade. I think
I've learned a few secrets.
They're so good. Thank you. I'm so glad
that there's a human in here that can
back me up a little.
It's human detected.
I like these things.
They're really easy. And it's like
100 calories and then you drink
like a glass of fucking almond milk
and you've had like 200-
It's just a snack. You know something? Guys, I'm not
talking about like eating a full plate of
spaghetti. I'm talking about
just a little something to like- Oh, I need
something. A little something.
Alright, let's finish the bitch. I said
it's a full meal for a fucking child.
Okay, it's a full meal for a child. It is.
It's not- Alright, whatever. I lied.
I got it wrong. It's a full meal
for you. You lied. Stop
lying, you-
It's perfect for me. It just is. Alright, we're gonna
move on from this. You give
some secrets. You know, I gotta start
holding on to my secrets.
I can't tell everybody my secrets now.
Because then they'll- I mean, I gotta- These are my secrets.
What do you think I do when I go downstairs?
I go-
drink a glass of water and I shake around
a little. I like shake my body.
I move my back up and down. I do some stretches
for my costochondritis and I come back upstairs.
Call me weird, that's fine.
It's been 10 hours.
And I'm- I'm good. A little tired.
A little cranky. I'm good.
Maybe need a little nap. Might need a
bubble later, but I'm good.
Hey, Appleship, thanks for 250.
Appreciate it. Uh, yo, have you heard
the new Gorillaz song? I have not.
Something I will do immediately when
turning this off. It slaps.
I'll have to hear it. Dark Soul,
thanks for the 250. Gap Gaming
here to let you know this is a fake funny
ad, just to let everybody know this is not real.
Uh, Gap Gaming here to let you gappers know
we think this stream is pretty rad.
That's why we're gonna step
it up and donate these 250 bits so we can
scoop some totally epic gear from our store.
Oh, I got some- I have baby burps
coming. Use code
BAMTHEMAN for 20% off your next order
of knee pads. What does everybody
say? Everybody said something funny in here.
What did they say? I see people
tagging somebody. They said something funny. What did they
say? That was heavy info
to drop on us. The baby
thing? Holy shit, 20
pouches is only $10.
Somebody's figuring this out
in real time, and
I'm so glad that they are.
Somebody is figuring this all out,
and I'm just so happy. You know when you just
know you're right and you have a secret
and you just know what you're saying
is correct and nobody believes you?
That's not a good value.
Jar of applesauce is like $3.
This is not a jar of applesauce. This is apples,
bananas,
and lemon juice. It gives you a little
kick. You don't have that in regular applesauce.
What about granola bars? Those are
great too. You just pick the thing
that you like. And I like go-go squeezers,
apple, banana, fucking lemon juice,
little kick. Squeezers!
The Glare, thanks for 10 community subs.
Appreciate it.
Thank you, Fel6 for the 5 community subs.
Appreciate it. Both of you.
Back to back there. Oops, thanks
for 500 bits. For the record. Somebody said
for the record, Angela
Anaconda.
Holy shit. Yeah, this is like
I... What network
was this show on?
Was it on Nickelodeon?
I distinctly remember seeing this show.
This show was weird.
Yeah, it was weird picture,
real life picture, stop motion
kind of animation stuff, right?
They just used
real photos of people and animated them?
Yeah, that was a weird show. Yeah.
Thank you, Hoops.
Thanks for the 500 bits.
Drink a better
beer.
You guys are gonna fucking kill me.
I have like my boomer brace
on.
Yeah, that was fun because chat loves to antagonize
and cyber bully you.
It was meant to be nothing more than a throw away goof
you happen to notice. That said,
I'm still sifting through some old streams. What were you
saying? I'm the guy who
joked about you snapping on stream.
Yeah, and then I was like, yo, why is
that? I said, and what do you think
that is? I remember that.
Snapping his fingers.
Uh oh, he's gonna fucking snap.
You are fussy.
That was fun. I especially
like the part where I couldn't get over the wall.
When I couldn't get over the wall and everybody was screaming
mean things
at me. Everyone get down. He's about
to snap.
Baker. We always do that.
I know. I just
give it back.
I can't, I can't jab back.
I jab back.
2020 Jerma jabs back.
Gotta be careful.
Hey, 101 dominations thanks for 250.
With all the money coming in, if we don't see Danny
DeVito in one of your streams, we're going to explode.
Jokes aside, love
your streams. Keep it up.
I don't know if that will happen,
but it would be really funny if it did.
Is Jerma Merc the worst emote?
No, JermaTV is. Or JermaBald.
The bald coin one.
Keith King Crimson, your skater
looks like Angela Anaconda.
Thanks for the 250. Yeah, that is
pretty accurate. Silent Serenity
thanks for 250, Silent Serenity. Imagine if
your childhood friend stole your jokes. We got this one already,
but it's funny. Imagine if your
childhood friend stole your jokes and got more Twitch
subs than you. Would you let him win?
Um, it would be really hard
to beat that person in a clown off
because no matter what, that person's
audience would always see me as the pretender.
It would just never work.
I could give documented evidence
and it would be like, yeah, I know,
but I'm already subbed
to this guy, so
and I like him.
I don't like you. I don't even know who the fuck
you are.
But I'm the funny one. I'm the funny guy.
Yeah, but are you though?
I like him. I've been
watching him for five years.
He's gonna come in here and
blow up this whole community like this?
No. No, maybe I'll
give you a follow. Jerma sure does
seem to know how this would all play out.
That's just human nature, isn't it?
Carlos Mencio
stole everybody's jokes and
he was one of the most popular comedians ever.
Like, nobody cared.
God, he existed.
He immediately became less popular.
I don't know if it was immediate.
I think that took a long, that took a while.
That took a lot longer than I think you remember.
He still had a bunch of, he still
had his TV show. He was still touring.
Joe Rogan made him disappear.
No, he
Alright, how many seasons of
Mind of Mencio were there?
Mind of Mencio.
There were four seasons
of this show. Now, he wasn't around
for like a year. He was around for like five
plus years before
anybody really, really took it
to him to get rid of like, oh, you were
a joke stealer.
Fridl Schlintz
Thanks for the 250. Please turn the light on in your room.
You'll ruin your eyes staring at a bright screen in the dark.
I am in a bright room.
Goiki gave
Goiki gave 20 community subs.
We caught it, but that's a lot of subs.
Thank you, Goiki.
Really appreciate that.
You came out as a baby on this stream.
Say goodbye to any future sponsorships.
Unless it's from Gerber's Baby Food.
Have you ever seen a sponsorship on this stream
that wasn't a joke?
Of us pretending there was one?
Has this stream ever been sponsored once by anything?
That we're not making a pretend I'm
sponsored joke?
I don't think that's going to be an issue for me.
I think I'll be okay.
But that being said, Go Go Squeezers
are the best.
So is JetBlue. You should fly it every time you fly on an airplane.
And Ridgewallets
are good. I like it.
Out of those three, I mean if you're listening
I'm here
I talk. I like to meme and chat.
We go back. We jab back and forth.
We have like this little fun banter thing going on.
They call me short.
And I like scream at them.
It's fun. I eat baby food
in front of them and they call me a weirdo.
Don't you want to sponsor this stream?
Don't you want to like give a bunch of money to this stream?
Why wouldn't you?
Most impressive babies too.
Nah, I'm just fucking around. I'm just messing around.
Don't worry.
Isaac?
Isaac, thanks for the 5000
bits. That stupid fart special
made me laugh harder than anything else in a long time.
Thanks for the fun stream. Thanks for watching.
Thanks for spending time here.
Thanks for giving me a very large
amount of money. Glad you got some laughs.
Thank you.
Five community subs, Kip. Lazy
Purple. What's going on Lazy Purple?
Lazy Purple, you still here? It's late.
Last second bits because that was honestly the funniest
stream I ever caught. Thank you, Jeremy. I appreciate that you pushed
through and beat it. Thanks a lot, dude.
You are still here.
I should probably do this.
You got
VIP. Let's go.
Newest VIP. Lazy Purple.
Bane?
Lazy Purple is an old YouTuber.
Made a lot of TF2 content.
Funny guy.
Well, I used the term old because
we're talking like
six, seven, eight years ago.
He still does.
I'm just saying he's an old
YouTube. He didn't start his YouTube channel
three days ago. He's been around for a long
time. He's an old YouTuber.
He's an old TF2 YouTuber.
That's accurate.
Lazy Purple was making videos I think before I was.
Like in 2010 or something.
When did you start your channel?
2011? 2012?
Something like that.
That's a good question.
Oh, yeah. You really are
a baby. July
21st, 2010.
That's a year before I started
YouTube. So, yeah.
You've been around a long time.
Thanks for watching. Glad to have you.
Five community subs
from Chef SCT. Thanks for the
five subs. Aw, futz. Thanks for the
$11.
Hi, Jermis. I want to say thanks for everything.
Past year has been one of the hardest years of my
life. And the main thing keeping me afloat
and positive are your streams and the chat.
Hi, chat. Thank you
so much for everything and a fantastic stream tonight. Have
a great rest of your night. You as
well. We've got a fun group of
people here. This community is one of the
best. At its very core,
there's a lot of really, really,
really great people here.
The channel has grown
so much in the last two years.
I'm surprised it still can
stay kind of like this.
Once a channel
typically, I mean,
we've seen the kind of the growth
of a bunch of new people that are coming
in and just the chat
goes much faster. It's
harder to pay attention to what people are saying.
I mean, there's typically
nowadays there's
four to six thousand
concurrent viewers on this stream.
Even a year or two ago, there was like
two thousand, maybe.
Two years ago, this
stream was at like eighteen hundred
to like twenty five hundred concurrent.
We've grown like three times
the audience in a year
and a half. But even still, it
still is, it's
still fun. It's not getting
corrupted. Not that it would
for really any reason, but
he's viewbotting.
Why would I ever do that?
And yeah, we've had some
growing pains on this channel.
Nothing anything major, but anytime
any channel grows this
quickly, you know, even for me,
like I'm trying to find
ways to moderate the channel better,
figure out how to
have a community this large and what to do,
how to be fair.
We've seen like the bit minimum
increase, right? Like that's something
I didn't really want to do, but I did.
All this stuff
has kind of only happened within the last two
years, but I still
love it. I'm still having a great time.
I'm glad there's people here that enjoy it too.
I worry about the implications
behind gifted subs. What do you mean?
Implications behind gifted subs?
Like people, there's a
lot of gifted subs and they'll
what do you mean? Trolls become
subs. Yeah, but that's
most people that are coming here, they're
just fucking around. They're not
I don't think of maybe
a few times in
five years on Twitch
have I really thought that there was a problem
in the chat, like a real one.
Not something that could be, you know,
fixed with a spam filter or
I don't think, it's been a while
since I think that there's been a
real, I've had it like, let me just put it
this way. I'm not sure there's been
a point where I've had a real
problem with something going on in chat.
Like a real problem with somebody
or
I don't, that just doesn't really happen
that often here. What were the problems?
Sometimes the channel, sometimes it can get a little
out of control with, somebody will come
in and say something
really, really fucked up, whether it's something
just ridiculously
offensive, racist
shit. Somebody will just drop a bunch
of terrible shit and it's like, okay, we gotta
deal with this. Sometimes
the spam can get a little
out of control. But that's
not that big of a deal because
it's easily correctable.
But this community,
they all, you guys all
think usually the same things
are interesting
or funny or
there's not a whole lot of split
up groups of people in this community
that don't like each other or don't
agree with each other or think, you know what I mean?
There's not that many people.
Well, the Dru crew is less
than a hundred people. I should do a poll
one day.
He still thinks that.
Don't you see the long game
I'm playing here, guys?
Come on.
This is some serious
6,000 go go squeeze brain
IQ
long play. This is a long
con because the more
the more that we talk
about, oh, there's not that many people
in the Dru crew.
No, of course not.
No, there's like 10 people in it.
They get members and
they get members and then I can
stream Nancy Drew
whenever I want
because all of you will be in
the Dru crew and I can
stream the 250 game
catalog and everyone
will be for it. Oh, no,
not my master plan.
I'm not even sure there is that many Nancy Drew games.
You're a megalomaniac. You psycho.
You monster.
No, I love the Dru crew.
Their enthusiasm is encouraging.
Makes me happy.
It really does.
Play this like a fiddle.
We love you. Watching you play Diablo
is my favorite.
Outer Wilds was the second.
I mean, we're playing Diablo 2 tomorrow.
Get ready. Tomorrow's stream, by the way, is going to be
very, very laid back.
We're just going to
I say that, but I'm probably going to be really tense
trying to fight Diablo.
Ah, another battery fell.
Why am I covered in batteries?
Yeah, it's going to be just chill tomorrow.
If I beat Diablo and
or if I die
let's say I die
at some point during that stream.
I'm going to try not to, but it's pretty possible.
Especially Act 5 is going to be hard.
We'll just do Asura's Wrath DLC.
Like if the D2 segment
if I cannot beat Act 5
then, you know,
if two or three hours have gone by, we'll just do Asura's Wrath.
We'll see.
Let's get the credits rolling.
Roll those credits.
Thanks for sticking around, guys.
Thanks for another long one.
Ten and a half, ten and a half, ten and a half,
ten and a half, something like that.
Almost eleven, almost.
We were talking about that earlier.
About how something goes, say, in like sixty, seventy hour weeks.
That's so tough.
That's so much time.
I really hope you're either making good money
or you're making progress, you know?
Here come the credits.
Seventy hours.
We're talking about like five twelve hour days
or something, like six twelve,
ten twelve hour days.
Rarely worth it to work that much.
Just take care of yourselves.
If you really are working that much more than like fifty plus hours a week,
sixty hours a week,
I really hope you're taking care of yourself.
That's what it takes to get through residency.
Yeah, nobody should work that much.
Yeah, it's unfortunate.
It really is unfortunate.
Sometimes it's not a choice.
If you like working that much,
yeah, then, I mean,
some people really love to stay busy
and doing their job or their work
is very fulfilling and they love it.
Yeah, absolutely.
But even still, like, that's a lot.
Sixty hours,
seventy hours a week for a job.
Because you can start to burn out.
You can burn out like the sun.
Like I told you back when I was
working before
YouTube or Twitter or anything,
you know, when I was working
full time, it was
thirty, thirty five, forty,
maybe max, like thirty five.
Even then, I can't imagine
doubling that shit.
That's a lot of time.
I thought he showed that after four weeks, sixty hours
a week becomes as productive
as forty hour weeks.
It's stupid to work people like that.
Yeah, there's a lot of
research out there about
shorter. And I'm a proponent
of this as well.
You are more productive
the less you work.
Working three or four
eight hour days
is more productive than working
seven six hour days, seven five hour
days in a row. Because
this is how I feel as well. I mean, this is
getting a little existential here, I think.
But if somebody
is happy and they have
time to spend,
don't you think that they would do a better job?
Right? Don't you think that
they would do a better job if
they had three days off,
four days off a week?
Going to work and they would be like, alright, like
I'm ready, like
I'm ready to go. I'm a huge
proponent of productivity
versus time.
Effective use of time
rather than hours of time.
There are tons of studies that
confirm this. Yeah,
it's really true. I wish we would
pull back to like a four
day work week. We'd do so much
good for so many people.
We wouldn't even lose out on anything.
Ow! Oh, that hurt.
That actually hurt.
Oh! My mic just
why did, what the fuck? Hold on.
My mic just like unscrewed.
My mic just unscrewed
and I like tried, it was like gonna fall.
It was like loose or something.
I just like stubbed my fingernail.
Oh, the retch are
cutting his mic.
I don't even think it's about money though. Like you can
if you're more productive, you'll make
more money. If your workers are more
productive, you're gonna make more money.
If your workers like what they do for work
and they enjoy coming into work, they're gonna
do more work when you
ask them to. If I ever had
a company, like a real company
not like, oh, German 95, the
E-Clown dickhead. If I had a
real company with
like 50 employees or something,
none of you motherfuckers is working
more than four days a week. Like under
any circumstance. Unless of
course, if you
wanted to, like let's say you were like
can I get some more hours? I really, I'm
ready to go. I want to go like all, I want to go all
this week. Alright.
You got it. Let's go.
God, please hire me.
It'd be nice to like just run a big
company and have tons of money
and have a bunch of employees and
I would love to have like birthday parties
for people. Is it weird
that I think about this stuff? I would love to be like
the CEO and like have like a surprise
birthday party for
workers.
That would be so much fun.
And we'd bring like games in and stuff.
You'd be Michael from the office.
Gamer boss.
It would be that I, because
if you're happy and you
like where you work, then you're
going to want to work better
and harder. Not
work smarter, not harder.
Work smarter, not harder.
It's such a simple concept.
How is it so boring to so many
people that run companies?
But what about that
fifth and sixth day?
We're going to lose profits. No, you won't.
No, you won't. You'll make more money.
You'll make more money. I bet you you'll
make more money.
More money, you say? Yes, a lot
more money.
Maybe I'll think about this
all day work week.
More money, he said
more money, therefore I should probably do
it.
Make a company as a funny
bit. I would just go bankrupt.
I don't have the capital
to be able to rob
a bank. Come on, it's like midnight
man. But let's finish
the bits. I could go off on a tangent
of how work
productivity is more important
than numbers at the job
all day.
You give me like two fingers of whiskey
and sit me down.
I could talk to you about this for like
three hours.
Hey, the
point. Thanks for the
300 bits. Hey, German back. LOL, by the
way, these are a rare
those are
nevermind. Those are great. I eat
organic applesauce, squeeze things as a filler
too sometimes. They're fun, but also a lot
of plastic waste.
Anyways, I'm getting interested in what you
do. What do you listen to in music?
I really like Rush, to be honest.
You have like a top 10 bands
you listen to. Gorillaz?
Gorillaz? Gorillaz?
Whatever video game soundtrack
I think is interesting
at the time. Gorillaz?
Repeat the same
three anime intros 200
times each until I don't care anymore.
Gorillaz?
And
Mozart. I know, that's a
lie. I don't really listen to music.
We, I know, he
eats baby food and doesn't listen to music.
Okay, check box one, check box
two. He is a sociopath. I know
like if you were a doctor you'd probably be like you fucking
something wrong with you. I don't
really listen to, I don't really, I don't. I don't
listen to music that much.
He's a baby. Clip this
and show it to the doctor.
Thanks for the 300 bits, appreciate it.
Thanks for 250. Are you ever going to attempt The Royal Flush
yourself on stream after doing
some practice? Martin
had a meme thanks to 250. Hey there
Whittle Jeremy. Baby Gap
Gaming here. We're wondering if
you'd like to be sponsored by us instead of the big boy
Gap Gaming. We think our baby
products fit more in line with your mentality
and height.
Martin had a meme thanks for the pretend
we're joking around having
a good time post stream
having fun message.
Thank you.
Hey Shoesip thanks for the 300 bits.
Hey Jeremy I appreciate the content and streams helping me
through some tough times. Keep it up.
I wish you the best. Hopefully you get
through what you're going through with ease.
Hopefully it's not as hard.
Not sure whatever it is but I hope
you get through it. Thank you.
The 300 bits. And finally
let's get to the end.
This is the end.
Silent Serenity with 250.
Do you have a vent to Kim
about how chat bullies you?
No.
No I don't think so.
I think about that so well you guys
think I turn the stream off and I just like go in there and I'm like
let me fucking tell you something.
Man I'm so sick of that shit.
Like what the fuck did you see what they said
today? Were you reading when they
said that? They said like oh he's short
he's fucking stupid.
These motherfuckers
let me tell you
I don't not do that.
You know what happens when I turn the stream off
and I walk into the bedroom over there?
You know my first words to Kim are
usually every single time I turn the stream off.
What do you think it is?
It's I'm hungry.
What do you want to do for food?
Are you hungry? Have you eaten?
Do you feel like anything in particular?
Do you want to get
sushi or something? Do you want to get
Mediterranean?
Do you want pizza? I'm hungry.
It's midnight. Well yeah not tonight.
We went late tonight.
Typically the streams turn off around
9pm, 9, 10pm Pacific.
I stream for like
six and a half hours, seven hours typically.
So yeah it's like
eight, nine, nine o'clock.
You go late every night.
Only the last couple
weeks really have I been doing more than ten
hour streams.
That's a pretty recent thing.
It was very rare for me to go
over nine hours. Very rare.
But I'll see you
guys tomorrow for Diablo 2.
The streams have only been going long
when you start early. But that's, we talked about
that though. That's another big point.
Starting at like 1 to 2pm Pacific
the streams can just go longer because
it doesn't go until like 3am
Pacific.
Much easier to stay live when
it's not too late for every
single person.
But I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Much love to you. Get some rest.
If we see you tomorrow, we see you tomorrow. If not
then maybe we'll see you again soon.
Take care and bye for now.