All right, hi. We're gonna move on to another game that I have been sitting on for a while.
This is a singing game. It's called One Hand Clapping. You have to sing to play the game?
I will find out if it's any good. Checking it out Thursdays. It's down. Just give me one sec.
Well, I think I have to calibrate it too. Let's find out. It's Wednesday? Oh, it is Wednesday.
Well, okay. Hopefully this can pick up my microphone. All right, I'll be... Give me one
sec. It says a microphone is required to play, which I have. Well, what the fuck? Hello? Can
you guys hear this? Oh, okay. Use wired headphones? Oh, no. Wait a minute. I'm gonna... Should I mute
This is me muting the actual mic. I'm speech jamming myself as I hear the meter singing.
I hear everything. I hear everything. The meter should light up when you sing and turn off when
you apply. Make sure it's not activated by breathing in the background. You guys, you can't... It's
not way too damp. I'm delayed though. I think this is fine. I actually have to keep this off.
This is gonna be so stupid. What a terrible screen this is gonna be. I need to get my...
It's not like you're giving a speech. I need to delay the webcam by like a tenth of a second.
Actually, this might be... You tell me when it's matched up. Am I matched up? One, two, three.
One, two, three. Is that better? Two, three. Turn it up. I mean, it's the game. This is as long as
I can go, man. I can't turn the audio up. Maybe I can. Hold on. Two. Sorry. It's gonna... Is this
okay? This is not a stream routine. This is not a stream that... This is the game. It's too quiet still.
It's gonna go really fucking loud. It's gonna go really, really loud. Turn your fucking speakers
down right now. Turn your speakers down. How's that? Are we good? Put the music... All right.
Honestly, turn your shit down. The music might be insanely loud. It's gonna be so loud. Turn
your speakers down. I'm serious. Am I missing something? Oh, over here. Did I break the game?
Oh, new game. The game's called One Hand Clapping. Oh, I know it's due.
I can jump. My microphone's fine. It really is like an ambulance driving by.
Am I sick? Am I over here? The audio is awful. That's the game. That is the game.
I was on the key. What's going on? Hey, I thought that didn't sound like it. That was like, no way.
How was it? Do a pedigree. Hey, Lois. Let's take a show. It's like auto.
I'm so mad. See the beat? I can't break it. You have to understand. I am hearing this.
Do, do, knee, knee, two, two, go, go, two, two, the, the story story. It's fucking horrible.
Oh, hi, guys. This is what I hear. I hear this. Isn't that tough to listen to?
This does not sound better. No, it does not. This there's no way this sounds better.
It does sound better. Give me a clip. One, two, three, one, two, three. Hey, what's up, everybody?
I want to hear it. This does not sound better. No, it does not. This there's no way this sounds
better. It does sound better. Give me a clip. One, two, three, one, two, three.
That sounds like shit, guys. All right, fine. I'll keep it on. I'm turning this shit off during
important things. Okay. So what do I do? I broke it. No, I didn't. Okay.
There you go. Fuck off. What the fuck is going on?
I fucked that up. This sounds so bad. This is bad. Do the misery? No.
Okay. Are you upset? No. What's going on?
Fucking easy. Fucking easy. Fucking easy. Fucking easy. Fucking easy. Fucking easy. Fucking easy.
Fucking easy. The louder you sing, the more the meter will fill.
That sucked. That sucked. That hurt so bad.
Okay, what do I do with this one? Just ride the clock? Do a cat puke?
It was a button. I'm switching back and forth. It's going to be really loud. I could actually
just talk and it'll spin around and shit. That's fine. I have to hold the note.
What time does it have to be?
Okay, we're good. This is, wow.
Singing is fucking hard.
I'm going to be speech jammed for the next like two, three hours. I have to sing duets?
Get the fuck out of here. Get the fuck out of here. I wish I could get new lyrics.
Fucking help me.
Not even trying. I'm not going to sing an entire song to get this thing to fucking move up and down.
It's just.
What if I did like halfway like this? I can still hear it though. I think it's important.
Yeah, because I think that during the course of the game it records what I say
and plays it back. I'm 99% sure that there's two, there's cases in this game where you
you won't be able to hear it. It's important. It's got to stay.
Okay.
Use your webcam mic. Well now why I can't hear it now.
Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? What happened? Hello? It's important. I'm not going to use a webcam mic.
Oh my. Maybe I should. I'm very curious. What if I do that? We need to see what it's, I need to see.
This thing doesn't, I can't do it. That was easy.
I can go. No, Shido is worse for him.
Let's go. Rip your vocal cords. I'll be all right.
Did you warm up before this? Um, I think so. Kind of. Now what? Oh my god.
Yeah, I know it was bad. It was bad. I can't match that. That was bad. It works. It's okay.
Why was I trying to go over? I was trying to go over that for no reason.
That could have been better, but it's okay. I think I have to hit the button.
That was really loud. That's why I have them both off. We're good. I gotta.
Jerma, you look skinny. No, I'm like 170 pounds. I'm a fat fuck. What? That was close.
That was a close one. Scream into the mic.
You're making me laugh. People are, I'm skinny. I'm five, seven, 170 pounds. That's, that's not,
that's not, that's overweight. That's actually fucking overweight. I'm not six, two. I'm literally
five, seven and a half. And yes, I may be a little overweight.
God damn it. Imagine this with multiplayer. It'd be insane. Now what? Okay. This person
hasn't done anything. Okay. What does that mean? It looks like I got out of prison. Why?
Dude, you're tone deaf. I'm not.
What do you mean Bjork? I don't sound like Bjork. What do you mean?
The whole thing is fucked up now. I can't play anymore. Push your Adam's apple up.
And then somebody says Bjork and I'm like fuck. Oh, I hear like what? That's what I hear. You
fucked up the whole screen. You fucked my whole screen. I hear that. I'm so thankful
to hear that. I'm so glad I have a container to puke into. I'm so glad I have a computer to
puke into. That's so fucking funny. It's not a computer. I can't hear anything.
I didn't mean to say computer. I meant to say a fucking coffee cup. I meant to say a coffee cup.
I'm being speech jams. You don't understand.
This is a coffee cup that I just spit everything into. No, I don't. That's coffee.
It's not chewing tobacco. You fucking weirdo. I'm sorry. I don't even think of it. It's in my head.
You know, turn this shit off for a second. All I hear in my head is just Bjork and that person
ruined the whole stream. You fucking idiot. I don't even know what happened. I don't remember
what happened. I need a clip. I don't remember what just happened. I started choking. I puked
into a coffee cup. What happened? I don't even know why that happened. Did he just puke? Can you
hear it? Hold on. Do you actually hear the puke sounds? No, you don't. Wait a second. You don't
actually hear it, do you? No. It sounds like I'm inside of a fucking toilet bowl. No, I didn't
puke. I just spit what was in my mouth. Okay. No, I didn't actually puke. That does look like I
actually threw up. You don't see me. I drank another sip. What the fuck? It actually is like
I puked. All right, let's go. We lost a thousand viewers during this, by the way. I think 2,000
people left in the last 15 minutes. No, I didn't puke. I just spit what was in my mouth. Okay,
this is clean. Viewers plummeting. Somebody just said, I'm close to leaving. All right. All right.
Fucking stop. Enough. Enough. Enough. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Are you ready? I just did like a curly laugh from The Three Stooges.
Fuck you. Fucking goddamn Bjork is in my head again. All right. You ready? Let's go.
What the fuck happened? I didn't make that noise.
I said 100 gags. Stop naming musicians that aren't me. Stop naming people that aren't me.
Stop. You're not a musician. Okay. Sure about that? Yeah. You sure about that? Fuck out of here.
Ban them. Imagine raging at a game like this. I was about to punch the microphone. I was going
to punch the microphone. That was really fun. We're gonna play something else.
Let me try it without the headphones in.
Bjork is is 100,000 times more talented than I will ever be in my whole life.
I can see that. I can understand that sentiment. So where we go now?
Vampire Survivors? Go back to Wheel of Fortune. Wheel of Fortune? I could turn on Wheel of Fortune.
Yeah. Okay. We'll do Wheel of Fortune for like an hour or so. Okay. Yeah. Give me one sec.
Change in game and change in console. That was really cute. These two games are actually really
cool. Something different. Something interesting. I've actually been sitting on those games for a
little while. The coolest part about that was one-handed clapping. Oh, one-hand clapping,
by the way. That was the fact that you can see in real time. You probably could train
your voice pretty well. All right. I'll be right back. I'm going to get the Wheel of Fortune set
up because it's on the Switch. So I'm going to get that set up or be right back. Just kidding.
Now I'll be right back. I guess I don't really have to even go anywhere. Do I?
I'm trying to capture the Switch right now, which can be finicky. Give me one sec.
Where is it? Where is it? It should be capturing it. I don't know why it's not.
My capture card can be really weird, though, for some reason. It just doesn't want to capture it.
Oh, hold on. Hold on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. I know you can do it.
Come on. Come on. What do you mean no signal? Oh, I took the HDMI out of the back. All right.
Actually, BRB.