Late. I actually just walked in here, just moving some stuff around. I went to the bathroom
and saw the time. I saw it was 3 59 and I said, oh fuck, and I pressed the button.
I ain't even fucking ready, but I'm gonna press it. That was an awful little laugh. What are you
talking about? You've been doing this all week. Hey, I was live at 11 15 yesterday.
The window was 11 to 12 yesterday and I was there at 11 15. Right? Yeah, but that was
yesterday. This is today. The one time you're early. There's no, look, there is no early or
late anymore. There is between three and four. That's it. Might start at three. Might start at
four. Just gives me that window so it doesn't matter. Usually though, all jokes aside,
usually though, if you look back at the last like three or four weeks, it's usually been
like 3 40, like 350. So between three and four p.m. has averaged out somehow to like 3 45,
like 3 40 and 3 50. Well, that's the design. That's what it's there for.
Just make it 3 30 to 4 30. No, because no, no, I can't do that. Because look,
the whole point of this whole thing was to make sure that I didn't start after four.
You know what I mean? Because like if I got a three to four hour window, like what, are you
kidding me? Making it 3 30 to 4 30 is then like, oh, I got it till 4 30 now. No, no, no, no,
no. It's to make sure that I like get fucking ready and get here between three and four.
The more you push that window forward, the more it's like, wow, 5 30. All right, fine. I'll
start at 5 22. But anyways, how you doing? Make it within a 24 hour range. Well, the idea
was that, okay, I got rid of the schedule, right? So no, it is not like, oh, Tuesday, Thursday,
Friday, and that's it. It's, we'll just do whatever. Getting rid of the time schedule
was also part of the plan, but I didn't want to do that. So I kept it at like the three to
fourish sort of range because I don't want to just have it be, oh yeah, he's going to be
live at some point at some time. That doesn't make any sense. Why would I do that? All right,
guys, I'll see you streams over for today. I'll see you guys at some point at some time.
You mean tomorrow? I don't know. You mean what? You mean like this week? Yeah. Oh yeah. I'll
stream at some point this week, but at some time, it's like, it's like sitting there
waiting at the telephone. Is he going to call? Hey, that's like, can I get your number? Yeah,
yeah, sure. I'll give you my number. What's your number? Thank you. Thank you. What do you
want to like, when do you think he'll call? At some point at some time. Don't do that to
me. Tell me if you're going to call me tomorrow. Anyways, let's move on. Today is going to be Sam
and Max season two. I'm going to start, he's ghosting his chat. I've never done that.
Actually, well, I have maybe a few times, but we're going to do season two, episode one
of Sam and Max. Can you, could you already tell that will there be anything else than
Sam and Max? So I, I know. No, Sam, we're just going to do probably the first two episodes of
Sam and Max tonight. And then tomorrow, that's right, four days in a row. Tell him to get rid
of that schedule. And I have unleashed. You see, you see, it's the same thing.
Look, look, look. I know. Oops. I'm sorry. I know people are going to be like, I know,
I know we get it. Just go. But listen, removing the schedule. It's the same idea of
having the window there, right? Or giving like a perfect time. Cause if I have a three
day a week schedule, I'm only going to stream three days a week, Tuesday, Thursday, Friday.
That's it. Okay. Bye. I don't have to worry about anything. Just that's it.
See now I can, whenever I feel like it, we can just fucking keep going.
I can, I could go three, four, five straight days, whatever. Keep talking to us. No,
with no schedule, you can stream less. Oh, that's true, but that's not the case.
All right. If that was the case, is he mad? No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait, mad.
No, no, no, no. I'm just trying to give some more insight. It's some more lore for
the Wiki page. Keep stalling. All right. You think I'm stalling? It's already ready to go.
Bang. Game paused. Press space. All I have to do is press space. Oh,
fucking set. Who set him off? No, no, no. I'm not. I'm just, nobody set me off. Don't
worry. See, it's right there. I can just press it. That's a screenshot. Oh yeah. You
think that's a screenshot? Is it now, huh? What you guys don't know is I animated all
this in dreams. That's not a video. Hold on. Let me just tweet this. All right. Too long,
too long streamer stalling for fucking 10 minutes before we do anything. No schedule,
no timeframe means I stream more. I need to get more of me. I don't know if you want
that or not. Maybe you don't want that. Maybe you're like, dude, we liked it when you were
less. Get the fuck out of here. Called dentist waiting room. All right. Here we go. Season
one, uh, season two. Sorry, I'm saying Max, but I didn't even get a chance to ask you
guys how has your day been going? That's the ultimate stall question.
Because I'm talking, okay, I'm typing right now a tweet saying that I'm live. Hey,
and so by the way, how has your day been? Let's go ahead. Give me some answers here.
All right. Season two.
All right. Now it's official. I gotta go. Season two, episode one, Sam and Max.
Let's see what the intro is doing for us today. Congratulations on another successful
peace summit, Mr. President. Don't congratulate me. Congratulate the peacemaker. You crack me
up a little brain salad. Oh, that was, he just, he's been acting surly and withdrawn
even for a vice president, but I never thought it would come to this.
His lust for power has twisted him into a mockery of the goldfish. We once kind of loved
that in sushi and fin flapping that glassy malevolent stare like a sociopath or a Fox
newscaster. Mr. Spatula has become pure evil. Why would he do staging a spatula? Not on my
watch. Eliminate him. You are my idol. I didn't. Why did they do that?
Hi fellas. Hey, what's the rumpus? I'm in the middle of some sensitive PI business.
And we respect your sensitivity. Is that mechanical goon one of yours?
Secret sideburns of Isaac Asimov. My name Tron.
That's what Mr. Spatula gets for sending a hitman with lousy aim.
Max, what say we go down and administer a freelance police style beat down to that
metal monstrosity? And then dance on its smoking carcass. It's that attention to detail that
makes me glad you're still president, little buddy. Sorry, I had to, I had something, I had to
talk to you real quick. All right, so first of all, this is important. I need to make sure
this is in the right settings. Are these right? Wait, is it, is Cox coming back? Help not.
I think this is fine. I had to do this because I couldn't do full screen,
because full screen wasn't gonna work. Top titles are on, hint level. They added this
in season two. I can't turn this on, right? People would make fun of me. I think we're
good. All right, let's go see what this thing's doing. He's tearing apart the entire
building. That's fucking kind of loud though. Hold on, that's the thing. We're not dropping frames,
right? We better not be. All right, what do you say? Hello? We didn't see you at all last year,
Flint. What gives? Okay, that was weird. I had one hell of a crazy case, fellas.
Boiling a conspiracy in the movie biz, matching wits with a reanimated Grover Cleveland,
breaking up Ascension's cell phone network, and a showdown with a cult leader on Saturn's
sergeant moon. It's wall dead. Wow, come we never get to do cool stuff like that.
That really is wall dead. All right, so I don't have, what do I have? Gun? Shoot robot with
gun. Not even a gun. They just don't make bullets like they used to. Wall dead. He's
tearing apart the entire building. He's tearing apart the entire building. I'm worried, Max.
Worried that enormous black mole on your back might be malignant?
Well, I am now. I was just worried that the giant robot was going to tear down our building.
Can you hear me? Okay, the button's fucked up. How are things going with your presidency?
The winds of progress are blowing swift and juicy, Sam. I'm proudest of the new law I
just pushed through congress. I'm pretty sure he who smelt it dealt it was already established
during the Eisenhower administration, little pal. I enjoy our little chats. Anything for a
friend and registered voter. I'm excited for season fucking two. What's this? We should just
accept we'll never teach that chief to be an arts grand master. How do I stop a robot from
punching me? Banana peels are a lot better than what he used to fling at it.
All right, this is really loud. Like, too loud for comfort. We can't do anything out here.
He's tearing apart. Should we leave? Should we just leave?
What goes up must come down. The boss goes back. Just to tell you once again who's back.
He may be a mechanized engine of wanton destruction, but his taste in hideous
middle of the road pop music is impeccable dead. No, they wouldn't kill a main character like that.
I don't believe it for a second. All right, so he's lost that loving feeling.
Excuse me, Mr. ginormous wind up toy of destruction.
Yes, I don't suppose you care to start. What do you want?
Hmm. In truth, it does not matter. I exist only as a mechanized engine for destruction.
What I do is what I am, whether I care for it or not.
Oh, no, Sam, he's been to community college. It's trouble. All right.
All right, so we're not I have a question. You seem like a smart guy for a robot.
Can you explain something to us? There is no question you could have
that I could not answer immediately. Okay. No, no, no, no. Put that away.
Max, you're always screwing things up. God, I love them. Why are you doing this? What if all
this is an illusion? Why do fools fall in love? He's having love. He's saying stuff about
love. Let's ask him that. Why do fools fall in love? Why do birds sing so gay and lovers
await the break of day? All right. Well, that stopped him from doing something from
attacking the building. I wonder what that means now. Maybe we come back and we
throw a grenade at him. I don't know. We're going to go to Bosco's. He's selling a
limb tear off device and it turns out as a grenade. The car's fucked up.
I've spent too many cycles processing this query. I might as well face it. I'm addicted
to show. So that stops him. I don't think I can do anything else.
Excuse me, Mr. Manedron. He didn't go high enough. He should have went.
All right. Let's do again. I have a question. I want to ask you something. Why do birds
appear every time you're near? What if all this is an illusion? Why do birds
appear every time you're near? Why do birds suddenly appear every time you are near?
Do that. Fascinating. All right. You get him to start thinking and then.
Wait, hold on. The robot sounds like Kylo Ren. I seem to get to turn him off. Reach
out the window and turn off his thing. Pull the key up. Oh, you were trying to
destroy us and worse. You butchered every song I wish I'd forgotten. And another one
bites. And another one bites. And another one bites. I didn't kill him.
I didn't kill him. He's alive. Check the closet. Oh, that's from season one. Here's
the Whack the Rats bulletin board. Cool. Pardoned. Have you been abusing your
presidential powers again, Max? He's not. That depends on what your definition of
abuse is. He's not dead. He has a wind-up toy in his back. He cannot die. He cannot
die. He cannot live. He can merely exist. And I know what you're saying. Oh, hey,
Jeremy. What about your fucking body's electrolytes? That's the same exact
thing as pulling the key out. No, it's not. So he's just. Who is he fighting?
What's he doing in here? I'm surprised this game survived being thrown clear
at the Playland and Casino explosion. Nobody's saying that. Yeah, they are.
You're thinking it. I forget which. It's the orange. Okay, it's the orange one. I
didn't know. I forgot. I'll get that better. Hold on. Do it again. I don't
lose. I don't. I never lose. Don't say that. I don't lose. I don't lose.
Don't ever say that to me again. I don't ever lose. It's our Salvia
Hispanic of Brady culture here. Safe and fun gardening at home with no
threat of legal action due to trademark infringement.
Oh, okay. All right, let's go check on the robot.
We pressed a few buttons. Not bad, kid.
Question, Sam. How do you like me now, spatula?
I'll ignore that question, Max, in order to say, look,
holy knuckle cracking cringles on a bullet train with a sack full of head-covered cheese.
I wish Jerma played Joffrey in Game of Thrones.
We were wrong about Mr. Spatula all along. What do you mean
why?
It was sent from a bleak and desolate wasteland by the most ancient and
powerful opponent we've ever faced. A hairy, bloated, pagan god.
To Sam and Max from Santa. Why is, why would Santa be sending us, um...
Dun-unh, dun-unh, dun-unh, dun-unh-unh. Dun-unh, dun-unh, dun-unh, dun-unh-unh.
Dun-unh, dun-unh, dun-unh, dun-unh-unh. Dun-unh, dun-unh, dun-unh, dun-unh.
I missed my cue. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Goodbye, Santa. Leave the talking to me. And the hasty trial, the harsh
sentencing, and the immediate execution. I took a bite out of a sandwich.
God damn it. Don't I get to do anything?
Don't, I can't restart it. God damn, that was a perfect opportunity.
I don't know. I took a bite out of my sandwich. I have a sandwich over here.
Hold on. I was gonna, I was gonna go like this.
It's too late now, but just add it. Add it.
Somebody add it to the end of that. I know someone's gonna fucking clip it
or something, but add this. Oh, hey look, Max. It's the soda
poppers. Again. We thought you'd all gotten
taken out in the Great Dakotan Conflict.
You might be relieved to see we made it. Right.
Relieved. What are you doing here? We all got terrible presents from Santa.
So we decided to come to the North Pole and return them.
Better that than spending Christmas Eve with a shotgun aimed at the
fireplace. Kids today have no respect for
tradition, Sam. Yeah, these, these guys again.
Why don't you go inside? We were on our way in when we heard some
frightening noises. That's the end of the Cowboy Bebop intro.
It almost sounded like. I thought you guys liked that shit.
Yeah. I'll write it down. Why am I the only one who associates Christmas with
the sound of gunfire? Best not to think about it, Max.
Uh yeah, weren't they governors? Aren't you guys governors of the Dakotas?
We were, but that wasn't enough. So we annexed Nebraska. Unfortunately, there
was a bit of a disagreement. With who? 2.5 million
voters. They won. Are you going to run for reelection?
No, now we're focused on environmental issues. We've got a new respect for
nature since we got kicked out of the governor's mansion.
Can we stay with you guys? No. Are they?
Okay. Well, what did you get from Santa? What did you get from Santa?
A jar full of rhinoceros musk. Yes, another one.
I got a see-through 90. It's beautiful, but I don't have the hips for it.
I'll trade you. Why? What did you get?
Tuberculosis. That's what I gave Sam last year.
Don't do it. And that's why we no longer have secret Santa at the
office. Don't fucking do it. I know some of
you guys don't. You dare. Okay. We should be going. Christmas
isn't going to save itself. Yeah, not like that snobby self-sufficient
St. Patrick's Day. All right, so we gotta go
Santa's Workshop, the second happiest place on Earth. The first
happiest place in the Disney world. He's really let himself go.
I should make a snowman on stream. I can't do that.
I live in the desert. Oh, I forgot I don't live
in Massachusetts anymore. I can't do that. Never mind. Wait, what's this?
Yellow snow reclamation. Just make a sandman.
Bleaches it into fresh sanitary snow. Want to have a snowball fight?
Not without industrial goggles, I don't.
What do I do? Okay, I have a snowball. This is a pea snowball.
I throw it. He gonna throw this in his face? Hey, wizard.
Please forgive us for what we are about to do. Oh, crap.
You guys are gonna kill me, aren't you? Yeah, we're gonna kill you.
You need to relax. Take a deep breath. Put your guard down.
I don't know why I'm so tense all the time.
All right, let me tell you something. That sucked. You ever been hit in the
face by a snowball before? It's not fun.
Of the smell of snowballs in the morning.
It really, really fucking hurts and it's like this equal parts
numb, pain, cold. It goes down your neck into your shirt and
it's awful. All right, well, I have a snowball here
and it really depends on the snow too. You can get
packed up really, really wet snow and it's like getting punched in the face
by a fist. People don't realize that shit.
Mostly. Not him, Santa. He forced us to make all those awful hurtful toys.
We don't know what's gotten into him. Whoa.
The snow will turn red with the blood of the knot.
The cartoons always made him seem a lot more jolly.
If you have wet snow and you pack it up and throw a snowball at somebody,
you are throwing a baseball at them and then it's like it's all fun and
games. Would you throw a baseball at your
friend's face as hard as you can? Why would you do that with a snowball?
It's not, it's fake. It's made out of like fluffy water.
No, no, no. It's a baseball you're throwing at your friend's head.
We're trying to talk to Santa. You know him? Mind if I keep cowering?
I'd encourage it. Just remember to cower with your legs,
not your back. The evidence melts away.
Whoa. I would, I would track that guy. Okay, uh, see anything unusual?
Well, this morning I could have sworn I felt the presence
of an unspeakable evil. Tell us more about this.
That doesn't even look like me. Give me a break. I'd rather not speak about it.
My teeth are way better. You all know that.
All right, so unspeakable evil. Can't you tell us anything about that
unspeakable evil? No. Don't you know what unspeakable means?
Okay, what's, what is he doing? Why is he doing this? Santa went nuts.
Beat me? I'm the intern. I just came off the assembly line yesterday.
Jumping jacks and half stacks of hat racks. Are you saying elves are made in
factories? Because if you are, I want to place an
order for six million. Also, tell my army they're fired.
No, I meant I was working in a factory. Sorry, it's relevant at the moment.
What did the factory make? Elves. Okay. Merry Christmas.
It sure is. So the snowball melts. Should I throw a snowball in the elf's face?
Or should I compact up a baseball snowball, throw it into the window, and
hit Santa right in the mouth? Okay, we got a lot of things to look at
here. Hold on. Trampoline. Max, get on the trampoline.
We do? Not really. All right. We've got better things to do than jump
around on a trampoline. Okay, so the gift dispenser. This tube
spits out presents. Hey, it's just like me. I wouldn't
call those presents, Max. It's a high score. I can put it with
high score. This must be what Santa uses to send presents.
Cougar in a box. Footbath and piranha aquarium.
That's what he sent to us. Grandma's happy pills.
My first Moai head. Santa exclusive. Obsess-o-matic stopwatch.
Uh, footbath and piranha aquarium. Just scoop them out.
Oh, now we just need to attach a gift tag. Attach a gift tag?
Look. I gotta find out what people want for Christmas. Perfect.
I've had a hard time lately getting people to open packages that say
from Max on them. So who should this go to? You don't have yourself to blame for that.
It was worth it. Okay, I just wanted to take a bite of a sandwich, but I just
realized that sounded like somebody came up behind me
and like put like a fucking covered my mouth and like dragged me away.
Then I'm gone. Okay, we got the gift tags.
Let me see. Hold on. Who's it for? No one. Actually, I can't think of-
It's for me. Oops. All right, so I have gift tags. I can put them on the presents.
There's a switch too. That turns- All right, so hold on.
Let's stop it right here and then Max jump on the trampoline
and get the coin, the star, whatever it is. Go for it, Max.
Get it. What the hell? It's a toy bomber.
Or a real bomber that just takes tiny warheads.
Makes me wish we still had that box of tiny warheads.
Not me. So I can't jump on that? That was our best fishing trip ever.
All right, well, slimy crate. What is this gelatinous goo?
I don't know, but for once I don't find myself wanting to eat it.
There's a mailing label. To Santa from lower Manitoba.
And they said Santa never gets gifts. Manitoba.
Should you get chicken tenders? Absolutely, get them.
I wonder why they call this the Flounder Pounder.
So you can shoot tennis balls out. Don't get ten- Why not?
That's fine. Just don't- Just get chicken tenders and get like honey
mustard sauce. I don't know. The bop buddy pre-adolescent
aggression management system. German would never say to get
tenders. Somebody just said should I get tenders and I'm like yeah.
It's the world's simplest maze. What's the big deal?
All mazes are simple. Not everybody has your knack for lateral sinking and heavy
ordnance, Max. This is not fake. Why would you say
something like that? Am I not real enough for you?
I will try harder. Tendies, right? Okay, world's simplest maze.
So let me go talk to Santa. Will he shoot at me?
Sugar in water. More, more, more. All right, come on. Give me
some intel, Santa. I want intel.
Hi, we're collecting guns for tots. Care to make a donation?
No siree. Should I give him the kitty litter box?
All right, record player. It's Santa's record player. Do you think it still
works? Since we haven't gone near it yet,
I assume so. Wait, hold on. Double click to run.
That doesn't work. He just walks a little faster. All right, cannon. Wait, wait, wait,
wait. We're gonna have to do like a Rube Goldberg machine here.
It's one of those infinitely reloading cannons. Is it loaded?
Well, yes. It even has the easy light wick.
Toy Marie Antoinette sold separately. Okay,
so what put the other half? We're trying to talk to Santa. You know him?
Oh sure, he's the one who put me in charge here.
Was that before or after he went crazy? I'm not sure.
When someone offers me a promotion, I don't ask a lot of questions.
That's a soda popper. Santa fired them to stay competitive with the other major
holidays. We had to outsource our gift manufacturing.
How'd the elves take it? They all got together and sang a farewell song.
Oh, that's sweet. You didn't hear the song.
Let's just say it wasn't very Christmasy. No, no more songs. No more Christmas songs.
What's it like being here? What's it like living at the North Pole? I wouldn't know.
I commute. Okay, okay we'll buy. Merry Christmas. Don't remind me. If we don't
deal with Santa soon, we'll never make our shipping date.
All right, so what about Boxing Betty? It's a Boxing Betty doll.
The finest in remote control fisticops. Didn't the Mame-tron teach us
anything about the dangers of playing with violent robots?
No, I didn't learn anything. Good, I worry sometimes.
Okay, well I have Boxing Betty. Boxing Betty, simple maze,
gift tags, gun. It just wouldn't feel like Christmas without the needless
destruction of an innocent bystander. Can I put like Boxing Betty on the
trampoline and launch Boxing Betty up into the
atmosphere?
I wonder what the elves have on their office computer. Oh, let's read
their email. It's a high score list for Minesweeper.
Let's see. Prancer, Wiggles, Shambling corporate presents.
How'd that get there? Well, pretty soon it's gonna be all
max. Now how do I start a new game? Sorry, I think it's
frozen. Torture? What does that say? Icey arctic wasteland. Hold on, what does that mean?
I need to see it. There's a, there's a torture thing over here.
Torture me Elmer, product testing. It's a torture me Elmer doll. Look, he comes
with his own breakable spirit and detachable retinas. What the
fuck? Seeing all these toys kind of makes me wish I was a kid again.
If it's any consolation, I still think of you as a child.
Thanks, I wish the courts did. No, you can only do that for three
seconds before people start to leave. All right, we got uh. Hi guys. Let me
check, wait, wait, wait. See you later guys. Did we do this to him?
It's a topiary planted in a tiny clay pot.
You guys, you guys are the, I think you guys might be the villains here.
This must be Santa's sleigh. Where does he attach the flying reindeer?
There's a boiler on the back. Whoa, tough break for the reindeer.
Wait, I want to, before you don't leave yet, let me see what this
out of you as a child. Thanks, I wish the courts did.
All right, that's fucked up. All right, I'll give that to you. That's fucked up.
Santa's coal-powered sleigh. Sleigh. Where are the reindeer? Whoa, you
actually can run. You guys weren't lying. I can
snowball. Let's think about the snowball. Boxing Betty.
Gift. Tags. Snowball. Um, let's see snowball.
Again and head. Baseball throw into dude's face.
Didn't even break. The co-op Jupiters are really good today.
They tend to be. All right, what about Santa? Throw it at Santa?
It's a bot. Oh no, no, it better not be.
I don't like to hear that. No, they teach you how to dodge snowballs on
day one of elf orientation. Should I shoot back at Santa?
I feel like there's an elaborate puzzle here that I need to be thinking
of rather than throw snowballs at people. I think I'll save my gun.
North pole. Okay, all right. Well, let's just leave.
Use Max on the torture rack. No. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Can I actually shoot
the cannon? I'm not going to do that. Whoa,
because that line, I lined it up with the, what's not lined up anymore?
It should be, right? So can I put it right in front of it? Like right
here? No. I need to shoot the toy bomber.
It's very obvious. No, you can only stop it here.
I can't stop it anywhere else. How is it obvious? Well, I mean, I have to
move it and then get it right. Okay, it doesn't work.
What happened to Santa? I don't know, but if you ask me,
it was only a matter of time before he snapped.
He's always been a little crazy. He has?
Think about it. The man gives presents away for free.
I always assumed he did it for the tax write-off.
Ah, that's right, right. Oh, that's a good humor right there. Who manufactures
the toys now? It's all been moved off site, so
officially speaking, I have no idea. What about unofficially? Baby penguins.
Why on earth would you use baby penguins? The adults refuse to work
without a health plan. Santa paid more in taxes in 2018
than Amazon.
I mean, think about that. That is a funny joke. Santa is operating at such a
massive loss. Oh, the elves make the toys, but
Santa, buddy, I gotta have payroll. They're probably, and he's gotta give
toys to literally everybody on earth. That's the thing. That's the lore,
right? You just wake up and there's a bunch
of fucking shit expensive stuff under your tree to
millions and millions of families. Santa is operating at like a 40 to 50
billion dollar loss every year. I don't know, where's he getting the
money? Who is like leveraging and insuring Santa
Claus? He might not even be real. I mean, I
don't know where the presents come from. I just assumed
that they just, they just were kind of, he did it. I don't know, he might
not be real. That's kind of weird to think about.
Wait, if it's like 50 to 100 billion dollars a year and nobody pays it,
but what about the guy that's at the mall? There's a person, there's a
guy, I guess you could just, you could dress
up as that guy, but they say it's him. It could be an actor.
Merry Christmas. If you say so. Fuck. No, but then how,
then where did I get my stuff? When I was like,
parents might have done it. I gotta take a,
I gotta take a quick break after this. I'm just gonna make a couple phone
calls. Where to, Sam? On second thought, let's just stay here.
Kind of, my whole world's kind of crumbling on me right now.
Trying to figure out what the fuck is going on here. I can't leave!
Where to, Sam? On second thought, let's just stay here.
Okay, well I have to figure this out. Simplest maze. Max, come here.
Can you do this? When one of the soda poppers touches this?
Then they try to give me something I didn't want. Give me a snowball.
Let's try throwing snowballs and stuff. I didn't do shit, don't stop
saying that. Throw a snowball at me. Baby
penguins. Do penguins do good work?
Sure, if you don't mind toys that have a slightly fishy smell.
Giving them or receiving them? You can use the gift tube over there and see
for yourself. Gift tube, we already clicked on it.
Okay, we want to talk to Sam. We've already done this.
I don't think talking is going to do any good.
All he wants to do is shoot everything. That's understandable.
You gotta get his gun away from him or he's gonna make us do
bad things. Get the gun away. Merry Christmas.
Don't remind me if we don't deal with Santa.
Yep, all right. What about you? You have anything else to say?
What are you doing? So what do you do here? I'm supposed to make this tree
grow. Oh. By crying. Christmas trees love
elf tears. Heck, who doesn't? It makes them grow up big and fast.
But I'm too darn happy. I'll never be able to cry.
So we gotta make him cry. It's enough to make you cry.
I wish. Throw a snowball at his face. I bet we could make you cry.
Thanks. I've been trying to cry but I'm just too darn happy.
We can fix that. In fact, that's about the only thing we can fix.
If you want to make me cry, go ahead. We want to. We want to.
Me first. Okay, wait, wait, wait. We killed your dog. I'll feed you to a
polar bear. I'll rip your eyes out. You were adopted. Santa isn't real.
You're fired. I give up. All right, hold on. Should we drop this
absolute bombshell on him? You don't still believe in Santa Claus, do you?
Sure I do. I saw him this morning. Well, I hate to be the one to break it to you
but Santa isn't real. He's just make believe.
Like the black Easter bunny or elves. But I'm an elf.
That's what makes this so hard. Wait a second. Are you saying I don't exist?
I got him. Can you prove that you exist? Well, sure. Got him.
I mean, no, I guess I can't. Got him.
Ouch, tough break. Surprise, we were lying. Congratulations, you exist.
Nice try, but I don't believe in you either.
Grow? Excellent. Hey, my snowball melted.
All right, so now it's bigger. That's a big honking tree.
Those elf tears really work. So now,
uh, is this gonna bump into the tree?
No, I thought it could have, like, stopped at a bump into one or something. I don't know, dude.
Um, all right, cannon. But let me, hold on.
There's a demon at the top of the tree. Yeah, there it is. All right, so we can throw
snowball at, give me this. Well, I can't believe he filled up the entire can.
Yeah, we must have really terrified the poor guy. Good work, little buddy.
Oh, stop. Now you're gonna make me cry. He shat the line, little buddy.
All right, let's throw snowball at cannon.
The cannon's already loaded. No, snowball.
He's already cried. There's this thing, snowball
into this thing. I think I'll save my snowball for a more satisfying target.
Okay, snowball. No. Can I make something else grow? Can I make the
trampoline grow? Hey, my snowball. Maybe a bigger
trampoline? I can't water that. Why not? Wait, do I have any other stuff
in my office or something? Can I leave now?
There is something out here. Can we grow? I remember this thing. All right, so that's huge.
Give me the rest of those elf tears. I've got a date with an unsuspecting
metropolis. Sorry, little buddy. They only work on
plants. Only on plants. You win again, Tokyo!
Giant topiary. I know it's called a topiary.
So now we're in Santa's room. Merry Christmas!
We come bearing good cheer and high-powered pistols.
Chuck-a-bump fairies! Santa, you okay in there?
Wait, why are we coming down again?
Okay, so we have to be quiet. Now, let's see here. We've got
Boxing Betty. Simple maze. That's his aggro zone. Santa's safe.
Bookshelf photo. Exit. Santa's hat. It's Santa's hat. Do you think it's
magical? Nope. The tag says it's 100% polyester.
Wow, that's the exact opposite of magical. I'm not gonna shoot him. That's not the solution.
Okay, we've got... Grr?
All right, I'm gonna shoot him now. That was my one shot. That was my one chance.
I can't shoot Santa Claus. What if I missed?
That'd just make him even meaner. But don't miss.
Problem solved. Boxing Betty. All right, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, what's... Christmas record? Record player?
Oh, it includes the smash hit, the friendly demon song.
I can't think of anything to say right now. He'll come up.
Okay, so record player Parchment. Their exorcism instructions.
Wicked! I want to do it now! But we don't know anyone who's possessed
or doing. Possessed. How do we start? Hey kids,
want to silence those inner voices? Do I? No more messy arcane rituals.
The My Little Demon playset makes it easy. First,
signal the emergence of the demon with the Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse
action figures, sold separately. Ask your parents to help you place the
horsemen around a powerful magnetic pole.
Roman Polanski? Finally, draw the hell spawn out by singing the friendly
demon song, using personal information about your
demon. He won't be able to resist. Okay, so we need four horsemen.
We need the four horsemen. Where am I going to get the four horsemen?
Performance reviews for young children. Well, at least I have the
record. It's either a trip to the zoo or Santa's gotten remarried.
Either way, I can't tell what he sees in her.
Yeah, I think you'd need a wider lens. All right.
Well, can I put on the coat? I can't touch any of this stuff. I've never
seen Santa take his coat off before. Now that you mention it, I don't
think I've ever seen you take your coat off either.
I haven't. Reindeer? Wait, this is one of the reindeer? It's either
dasher or dancer. Well, let's just see what we can do now. We
have a way to get in. So I'm gonna assume we can
eventually hear. I got the record and exorcism instructions.
Can I play the record? There's a whole lot of random stuff in here that I
feel like I'm missing. Naruto? Why you gotta say Naruto?
Let's put on the friendly demon song.
What? What? Very scary demon. We had him. Like two ferrets and a dolphin
stapled together.
In the bathtub of 94 Honda Civic. I pull the tail off the donkey.
Hey, nameless one of his homilinkers. Hey, he has a thousand unanswered
supplies. Hey, Shambling Corporate Presence. Hey,
Shambling Corporate Presence. I don't think that's how the song goes.
So we have to, all right. We have uh, what would it,
who's on here? Who's number one? It's a high score list for Minesweeper.
Prancer, Wiggles, and the Shambling Corporate Presence.
Okay, Prancer. So these are all references to stuff in
the I.K. All right. So let me look at that again.
It's Santa's record player. It's Santa. Oh, play it.
Let me just see what those options were again.
Very scary form. IRS 1040. I mean, that's, didn't they make an IRS
gelatinous goo? Because that's what's in the box.
I'm going to say this one.
Most unholy creature that was ever born. Okay, Manitoba.
In lower Manitoba. What's on the box? It's like Minesweeper, right? Because the
computer. Shout his name. Prancer. Oh, shit.
That's not the, the Corporate Presence didn't win. Is it that?
That's no, no, no. That's the only, that's the only possible option.
Oh, the song seemed right. I guess we must not have all the
horsemen in place. Oh, fuck. I have to have to put them over here.
I have to have four horsemen. Hey, it's the North Pole,
the magnetic center of the earth. Well, magnetism.
Don't tell me you're one of those kooks. You don't believe in magnetism.
It's an interesting theory, but I'm not convinced.
Your magnetism is a cute bedtime story, but I believe in one
thing. Okay, fine. I can't believe this works.
I believe in two things, but that's my limit.
Max is a flat earther. All right, so we need four people or four things
out here. How do we, where the hell does that come into play?
Is it the soda poppers? It's only three. Who's the fourth?
Is it Max? Hi, guys. Why don't you go inside?
We're waiting for the shootout to end. I can respect that.
How? So I have to stop Santa from doing that. See you later, guys. So they go inside so I
can teleport them to hell. All right, maybe something with the gifts.
No, but I don't have it. Can I leave yet? Where to, Sam?
Okay, I can leave. Let's go back to the office. Let's head back to
civilization or what's left of it. Good thinking. We can always freeze to
death out here later. Drive from here to there because I
couldn't leave before. This is the first time I've been able
to come back to the town. All right, well hold on. Sibyl's is, is
Sibyl alive in here? Sibyl's not here. It's closed.
Open 24 hours unless I don't feel like it.
Or a giant robot tosses the entire building a city block.
Poor Sibyl. Sorry, Sibyl. We tried. All right, boss goes for the first time.
Who's this rat? It's not a clickable rat. New S&M
season. It's a shame you don't wear collars, Sam.
It says they're coming back in style. Sam back.
U.S. to Macroheart Corporation. I wondered why the stock market kept
crashing. All right, let's go in. How's Bosco
doing in season two? Welcome to Bosco's
inconvenience. Please wait while I determine whether
you are truly welcome or if I am just uttering idle pleasantries.
Nothing says inconvenience like a full body search before you can buy
your candy cigarettes and all day suckers.
You have been deemed not unacceptable. Welcome.
Bosco, your disguise. It's, it's, it's hideous. Claw my eyes out, Sam. I can't
bear to look at it. Not if I claw my own eyes out first.
He's not going to be in a costume. I'm not wearing a disguise.
I know comedy. I forgot how ugly you were without a wig or hat or something.
My package. All right, so what, uh, what, what package? Say Bosco, what's in the-
Hey guys, does my package sound like it's ticking to you?
Not your best pickup line, Bosco. Oh, I don't know.
I think my package is the bomb. Now that's
a pickup line. Okay. Keep going. Who would send you a bomb?
My mother, of course. She sends me one every year around this time.
What the? Families need traditions. So why don't you just get rid of it?
I built that bomb disposal unit for that very purpose.
So why don't you just get rid of it? Because it might be the billion dollar
plunger I just ordered. What a dilemma. Billion dollar. Just open it. Just open
your package, Bosco. What if it's the bomb? I thought I
heard ticket. Just get rid of your package, Bosco.
Forehead. But what if it's my plunger? I gotta be sure it's ticket.
Just open your package, Bosco. Just get rid of your package, Bosco.
But what- Just open your package, Bosco.
Just get rid of your package, Bosco. That's-
that's the shit I gotta deal with on a day-to-day basis.
I know what it's like. Why not disguise it?
No hilariously inadequate disguise this time? Sam, Sam, Sam, you
poor naive fool. Don't you realize the time for disguises is past?
Yeah, you poor naive fool. Don't you realize that?
Quiet, head knuckle. A disguise could never protect you from
T-H-E-M. Them. You scared me. Who's them?
That's exactly what I'm trying to figure out. I'm watching,
I'm listening, and I will find T-H-E-M.
Well, if you do, tell them- Okay, this is getting old fast.
Them. Them. That's great, I love it. Just open your package, Bosco.
What- Them. Just get rid of your package, Bosco.
But what if it- Them. Welcome to every German 985 stream.
Just open- Them. Just get rid of your package, Bosco.
But what if- Them. Oh, shit!
I don't do that, though. I don't do that. I can't do that.
What's with your store? I'm not sure if you noticed, but this ain't-
Jokes do always go wrong. I haven't noticed anything.
Look, I've got a hundred trillion dollars and a thousand faceless
enemies. I don't need to sell anything. Then why keep the place open?
I'm a people person. You would if you could. No, I would not.
I love you guys, you guys are great. You think I would ever do that?
Okay, what's the door scanner? What's with the fancy dance scanner, Bosco?
Tools are necessary. Tools are the only things that separate us from the
animals. That probably plays a little better
with the non-dog and rabbit ground. That's why I need the personal
antipathy registration annulment and non-negational
omnifunctional identification device. That's just paranoid.
Technically, yes it is. Okay, oh here we got another one of these.
Do you have any bulletproof edible underwear? I don't have
anything. This ain't a store. It's not a store anymore.
Do you have any lords of leaping and or maids of milking?
I told you this ain't a store. I'm gonna get punched.
Do you have any inflatable arms capable of being used as replacements for your
real arms? Didn't I just tell you this ain't a store
no more? Do you have any passive aggressive
payback disguised as an innocuous customer inquiry?
Punch. Do you have any- No! This ain't a store!
It's not? No! Oh, why didn't you say so?
A trillion dollars worth of detection equipment and yet he still didn't see
that one coming a mile away. Now the store looks interesting.
It ain't a store no more. And did you know people who say that-
Wow, I'm being a real asshole. Are more likely to be serial killers?
More likely than who? Than non-serial killers.
It's a fact. A fact they don't want you to know.
Who doesn't want me to know? Exactly.
Hold on. My regards to your decorator. I like this. Yeah, what's the style?
Early colonial conspiracy theorist? No, a theorist is somebody who has a theory.
I have conspiracy facts. So I guess you'd be a conspiracy factist.
He's certainly not a cluist. Conspiracy factist.
Because he doesn't have a clue. Yeah, I got it.
All right. Enough about your store. It's not a-
Oh, forget it. Just open your package, Bosco.
See ya, Bosco.
All right. Bomb be gone. Can we borrow your bomb be gone?
There's some obsolete landmines around the office we need to get rid of.
No. If I loaned my bomb disposal unit out to everyone in the
neighborhood who needed it, I'd never get it back.
You know, in this neighborhood that's actually true.
X-ray machine. So it's not a store. It really isn't.
Theory of everything. Suddenly, it all makes sense.
I can't see where we fit into all this, Sam.
Oh, I've got a couple of walls upstairs devoted to YouTube.
That's not the shit that he made. That's not the stuff that he
researched. All right, X-ray machine. Hey, an X-ray machine.
Don't fool with that. X-ray boxing bag.
Don't fool with that. X-ray... What about these?
To exorcise the demon, it says we'll need to
collect the four horsemen of the apocalypse action figures. Place the
horsemen around a magnetic pole and draw the demon out using the
friendly demon stone. We just need the four horsemen.
Enlarger. I wonder if we can enlarge anything else.
No, Max. No. Okay, if the tears make things grow,
I'm not gonna say it because that's an easy
low-hanging fruit. Fill in the blank. All right, so
I'm not, let me go check the other stuff. Wait, this is open?
Stinky's Diner is open. Stinky's Diner.
It's back in business. We're gonna, a new character? An excited neighborhood
reopens its arms and its emergency rooms. Stinky's
Diner. I'm excited for a new character. Ah, the
smell of desiccated eggs, congealing bacon fat and rye bread gone
awry. It's like Stinky's Diner never
closed. Welcome to Stinky's. We never close except when we're closed.
Who are you? Is it Stinky? I'm Stinky. The Stinky we know was a
cantankerous old man who transformed his seething hatred of humanity into a
misanthropic smorgasbord of culinary horrors.
That does sound like grandpa. Okay, we're ready for the next round of
trivia and the question is... They're alive!
They're alive!
Bangers and match. Do I get the answer?
I can't. Okay, alpha horn. Bug. Oh wait, it's a bug.
I've got two people living in there.
Why'd you play back that demon recording? I've got a case of PISD,
post insecticide stress disorder. It keeps causing these flashbacks.
How so? I get a whiff of something familiar and the memories just come
rushing back. All right, so you get a smell. Must have been some brimstone in the
air during that exorcism. Oh, was that brimstone?
This whole time I just assumed you let out a 200 pound fart.
No, it was brimstone, honest. Okay. You don't get along with your family?
Negative. Except for my dad. They're all a bunch of spineless ladybugs.
Aren't all bugs spineless? Not in my regiment.
If you didn't have a spine, by god, my dad would make you grow a pair.
A pair of spines? That's just the kind of bug he was.
Oh, I forgot about the dream. Like, I had a dream last night.
This is important. Really important. Pause this for a second.
I actually can pause this. So listen to this shit. So last night I had a
dream, and this is, it was too real. So I had a dream. You know how people
have dreams about me streaming? They say, dude, I was having this
dream, you're streaming it, you got sucked up, the gray fluid went into
your brain, and then I... So I was having a dream that I was
streaming. And I turned on the webcam. I don't
know what game I was playing, what didn't matter, but that was about, I
was gonna do like a joke that I thought was gonna be funny.
And everyone was like, oh, joke incoming, joke incoming,
webcam's on, and I was like, I didn't have anything. I had nothing.
So I was like, oh fuck, I gotta think of something funny to do quick,
because I didn't, I don't like have a joke ready. And I like did the turn on
the webcam thing. So I just started going like this. I
started punching towards the camera, and every time I would punch, I was
going, I'm gonna get you guys with some karate!
And it was like minus twos, and people would just like, I did it like
four or five times in a row. And I remember right when I stopped
doing it, I was like that, this was not even funny,
that was not even, that was horrible. And I was like, I'm just like kidding, I
turned off the webcam, and I was still asleep. And I went
through the rest of my night, walking around like eating, I just
have these vague weird flashes of me lying in my bed,
being like, fuck, that like, that really, that joke really sucked.
Ah, it's all right, like I'll come back tomorrow and like do something funny,
and then I woke up. That was yesterday.
Imagine if this actually happened.
I'm so fucked up, and like delirious, and so
scatterbrained, that I don't even remember what I did yesterday,
and I thought it was a dream. He doesn't remember it.
He's not even funny in his dreams! No, I'm not. Here we go, let's go.
I just, that makes it even funnier in my brain, that like this actually
happened. And I thought it was, I don't have any
clothes on, I can't turn my webcam on. I was like, punch, punch, punch, I call
raw tea to you guys! And people hated it. That didn't happen
yesterday. No, stop fucking with my head! No,
no, this is not like time travel, guys. I don't have to like redo the
thing that I did to keep the timeline going correctly.
What do you mean we have the clip? What are you linking?
Hold on. No, it's not the slap. What is that, what,
Effectator, what are you linking here? This, what is this?
I missed my cue! Oh, wait, you already did this?
Wait, what is this one? Wait, how did you get this already?
Oh, here comes a joke. Karate! Oh, I already hate it. Not the video, but
hold on. I missed my cue! Well, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, I took a bite out of a sandwich.
God damn it. Don't, I can't restart it. God damn, that was a perfect
opportunity. I took a bite out of my sandwich. I
have a sandwich over here. Hold on. I was gonna, I was gonna go
like this. It's too late now, but just add it.
Add it. Somebody add it to the end of that. I know something's gonna fucking
clip it or something, but add this.
That was not what I did. That was not even close to what I did.
All right, let me play the game. Recreate the karate joke!
No! I, hold on, let me put on like a blanket.
Bag on my body. I need a shirt. Hair. This is fine.
Will this cover enough? Yeah, no, this is fine. This, this will cover it up.
This is essentially wearing a shirt. Is it? I need to look.
I need to see where the camera is, because this, I, this is a, this
functions as a t-shirt. Yeah, we're good. Oh, we're good.
Okay. Yeah, this functions as a t-shirt. Okay.
So I said, hey, it's time for some karate!
That's what I did. And that's like a SpongeBob thing, right?
Oh no, I'm looking over it. I'm seeing it. You know, here's the really fucked
up part about this whole thing. I'm living right now the dream that I
had last night. That's, I had to correct, there's some
weird like time thing where I had to do that. I just
probably, I just like saved all the, all the whole universe by doing
what I just did. For some reason I had to do that. I
had to help, somehow. I don't know how. Is it the same armor from the day the,
yes it is. It was just in the closet and I knew I could use it as a shirt.
Sometimes you gotta think about that. Like, why did I have that dream in the
first place? It was because they, like they knew
that I was gonna have to do this. And I, that second, somebody was
watching the stream and like I had to stall here for a second for some
reason. Because that made them pay attention
for some reason. Because they're gonna go on to be like a
scientist. And they, right after fucking watching that clip they,
they thought of something to write down or at that moment they picked up their
career path. And then you go on and you like cure
every illness. Because of just the way that the time
that had that had happened for a reason. Santa isn't fucking real.
Figure it out. All right, when did you start, where are we?
I gotta get a good career.
I gotta get a good career so I'm not a guy in my 30s
punching into a camera with a child's hockey chest pad on. You know,
however we do it, we do it. However we do it, we do it guys.
Right?
It's D.
We think it's D. Wait, what was, oh fuck, wait.
Hey, you okay? Hey, you okay, man? Was it D?
Yeah, the D. All right. Hey, Sybil. Oh, hey there, Sam and Max.
What was all that commotion outside? Just a little urban renewal project that
got out of hand. By the way, didn't you tell us that you
wished your office was closer to a good restaurant?
That's right. Why? No reason. All right, what are you doing here? What
brings you here? I thought it would be fun to play this
trivia quiz. But instead we're stuck watching
Stinky make a mockery of the word knowledge.
Sounds like fun to me. Yeah, Max and I always have a blast making a mockery of
the word justice. How Stinky rooting for trivia.
No, I'm sure my answers are right. But Stinky says otherwise.
I'm sure you're right too, dear. If this is too aggravating.
Oh no, this is fine, Abe. I'm just enjoying being here with you.
If I weren't trying to impress Abe, I thought I saw that
lying witch's eyes out. She doesn't want to be here. Get her out quick.
Otherwise your entire relationship is based on a lie.
Why are you giving out relationship advice, Max? I just want to see a good
cat fight. Anytime somebody says on a date,
no, no, no, I just like being here with you.
Out. Because that means, no, I hate everything that's happening here, but
I like you. So it's like, oh shit. When you're the most interesting thing
in the laser tag area, I think, yeah, at least come on. She probably doesn't
like laser tag. And why did you pick that in the
first place? You gotta go somewhere you're both
gonna like. You kids be like, oh I like laser, let's go play laser tag.
Go see a movie. Having fun yet? I know she's cheating, but I don't want to
ruin my date. Laser tag? Yeah, you decided to take her to
laser tag or take him to laser tag, doesn't matter.
And you thought it was a good idea. Yeah, I love laser tag. It's awesome. I'm so,
I love, it's my favorite thing. Oh, this is cool. Yeah, pick you up at
eight. Okay, cool. And you go there and you're moving,
you go here all the time and you fucking lighten up the scoreboard.
You do so many more points than them. That's not, that's, why, why is that
fun? Don't do that. He's speaking from
experience. It's too specific to be a random joke.
Let me help you here. By the way, I used the name cloud9
long time ago for my laser tag days. This is before that company even existed.
I was like 12. I swear to god this is real.
Are you and Abe on a date? Well, if you want to call it that. I did that
when I took a girl bowling. What if I wanted to call it
the unspeakable obscenity from beyond space cackling on the threshold of
utter madness. I think I'd prefer date. What, do you get like a bunch of
strikes when she was on her like phone?
Okay, so let's let's figure the trivia thing.
Yeah, that's uh red flag number one. If you're having a great time and she's on
her phone. Hiya, stinky. If that is your real
name. Uh, who are you two again? Sam and Max,
freelance police. The real stinky's favorite customers.
It says so right on our frequent diner cards. Which conveniently double as
organ donor cards. Oh yeah, Sam and Max.
Grandpa warned me about you two when he left the restaurant to me.
Something about frequent threats of violence and refusal to pay your bill.
He remembered us. Okay, why are all these people? What's going on? There's a lot
of people here. Two. It's a trivia contest.
It's fun. People get to show off how little they know
and I get to show off how much I know.
That doesn't sound like much incentive to play. Shows what you know.
Oh, and there's a big prize too. What's the prize? What's the prize for the
trivia contest? If anyone wins, they get my ancient heirloom.
Sickly man on a horse. Famine. Pestilence. Not that anyone's come close to winning yet.
My sophisticated questions are just too esoteric for these
booth monkeys. Booth monkeys? Where? It's just an expression.
No, not wrath. They think of the seven horses of sins.
Not the four horsemen of the apocalypse. Okay, what can we play? How do you play?
It's easy. Just grab a trivia pad. I'll read a question.
You write down the answer. I'll review the answers.
Eleven horses of evil. And then you'll see how much smarter I am than everyone else.
You can choose a team if you want. Oh, oh, Sam! Kick me! Kick me!
Okay, we could order food. We'd like to order something.
We're all out. Of what? Whatever you're going to order.
That's okay. We just want to order it anyway.
All right. The daily special. Poached eggs with tinfoil. Tuna sandwich with
peppers and pop rocks. Ooh. We'd like the tuna sandwich, extra
peppers and pop rocks on white bread. That sounds kind of cool.
I need an al gore and mariachi pans writing a disco ball.
Sweet and sour salt water. That sounds good too. Sweet and sour salt
water taffy. Sal? Julia Roberts. Put a bullet in her brain and kiss her
with Andy Rooney. It's like my secret dreams made
audible. Two yogurts and a turkey sandwich.
We'll have two yogurts and an open-faced turkey sandwich. Sal?
Hubeless times two with a side of Brady culture.
Uh, poached eggs with tinfoil. We'll have the poached eggs with tinfoil.
Sal, give me the Norse god Thor in a terrarium and spank him.
Double biscuit burger no clams. I'd like the double burger baked in
biscuit dough. Hold the clams. Half a doppelganger in tight
pants singing solo. Precious special with hash browns.
Can I get the precious special with hash browns?
Sal, two limini snickets in a Mexican standoff with a prairie dog.
What's the daily special? I'd like the daily special. Sal, condi rice, kickboxing
the buddha, Thai style. What's in it? What do you mean what's in it?
On second thought, I'm on a diet. All right, what was that about trivia?
What's happening again? A trivia contest. Just grab a pad and try
around. Okay, so let's go try around.
But how's business? Exhaust all actions. Well, it's no Italian villa rendezvous with
George Clooney, but reopening a family restaurant is
very fulfilling. Bringing people closer to obesity-induced
ischemic heart disease is its own reward.
On the other hand, George is much easier on the eyes
and the feet. My dogs are barking louder than you, Fido.
Standing up all day getting you down? And how?
I was made for sending beachside and capri, not slinging hash
counter side for a pack of ingrates. The forbidden word.
So long. All right, well let's sit down.
Let's give this trivia question a try. It's D.
Okay, let's hear everyone's answers. We'll start with you,
Sybil. I chose A. Of course you did, dear.
Because you're wrong. I also chose A.
And that's very sweet, Mr. President. But also
very wrong. The answer is D. D. Wait. Oh, I'm sorry. That is wrong.
We also chose D. Really? Hilarious. And again wrong. The correct
answer was actually B. B? Liar. All right, next question.
This day of the week comes between Tuesday and Thursday.
What is it? A. Doomsday. B. Wednesday. C. Doris Day. D.
Menachem Begin. Doomsday. Okay, let's hear everyone's answers.
I think we have to make them choose the wrong answers. I love how you keep
playing even though you're always wrong.
Never lose that. I also chose B. We all have to choose the right answer. Oh, how cute.
You two are like identical twins or something with your enormous foreheads
and your matching wrong answers. The answer is D. D.
No, it is not. Not. How could you be bad at this?
What are you talking about? Oh, too bad. Wrong. Only one answer
wasn't guessed, so it was obviously the correct one.
I get it. I understand now. That's just not true. I know what you gotta do.
Next. Here's the plan. Which of the following women's names
is also the name of an herb? You gotta make everybody somebody has to win. C.
Rosemary. D. The pyloric sphincter. None of this matters.
So convince everybody to choose a different answer and then choose the
one that was not picked. So somebody has to be right. 23
Skadoo, Mr. Lincoln. What's shaking, Mr. X, president?
Hmm? Oh, it's you two. I also chose D. Wanna compare notes on the trivia
contest? That's not necessary. Abe and I know
what we're doing. That's right. We're doing fine.
Help me out here, guys. We think it's A. We think it's A.
Okay. All right. Bye. See you, A.L. Represent. We think it's B.
Do you know the answer to the trivia question? I'd rather not say.
I'm kind of competitive. That's okay. We're not.
Why? What do you think the answer is? B.
We think it's B. Hmm. Good to know. Okay. See ya, Sybil. Then have you pick C.
Hello, sir. Oh, I thought you were my family.
They always try to surprise me on my birthday. Someone's gonna win the prize and then I just...
What day? What the fuck was that? That was weird.
Okay. Wanna compare notes on the trivia contest?
What do you think the answer is? C. We think it's C. And then we're gonna pick D.
That's the best I can expect from civilians.
Sir, so long. We have five community subs coming in. Thanks for the five community
subs, Tour T. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Five community subs.
I chose C. Oh, only C was an option. Wrong.
I chose A. Scratch it off.
Sadly, you're wrong. The answer is D. D. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. What?
What? We also chose D. Oh, he chooses D.
The correct answer was B. He chooses D every time. Time for a new...
Who is buried in Grant's tomb? No matter what.
A. Grant. B. C. Abbott and Costello.
All right. All right. It's C. D. Spam.
C. We pick C. He's gonna pick D. You pick A.
Let's talk trivia. Wanna compare notes on the trivia contest?
Yes. Hook a brother up. We think it's A.
Got it. See you, A.L. Wanna compare notes?
Why? What do you... We think it's B.
Okay. See ya, Sybil. He always picks D.
What's the actual... Wait. What's the actual fucking answer here? Hold on.
Who is buried in Grant's tomb? Grant. So, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
She's gonna answer Grant. So, Sybil is going to do Grant.
So, that means we have to give A to B and we have to do C.
Wanna compare notes on the trivia contest? She always gets pissed off.
Yes. Hook a brother up. So, you do B.
We think it's B. We're gonna do C. Thanks for the tip. See you, A.L.
Refres... Okay. So, then we're gonna do C. He's gonna do D.
Bingo. Problem solved. So, we do C.
Okay. Let's hear everyone's answers. He read chapters.
Of course you did, dear. Because you're wrong.
I chose B. Come on. I appreciate a man
unafraid to flaunt his ignorance. Wrong. You think I'd read chat?
The answer is D. D. I look over here and I
say random answers to random questions. I don't have chat open.
I've never had chat open. We chose C. No, that's wrong.
I guess it must be right. Well, congratulations.
I know you guys always say, nobody said that. I really enjoyed that you won, but I'm far too
magnanimous to let it bother me. Cheaters.
It's the limited edition pestilence maquette with super detailed open
sores. Oh, see how he slumps in this saddle.
Do you have any cool action features? I'm surprised I've been able to go four
years of doing this without people knowing. What's the worst a toy could do?
Choke a toddler? Blind a toddler? Eviscerate?
Well, it looks like nothing happened anyway. Let's go.
One guy is fake. One guy is just alternate accounts.
I have to find a way to reply to somebody. All right. So, we got
one horseman of the apocalypse. It is pestilence. I knew it. I knew it.
Still need to do something. Can I do anything over here? What about down here?
Whoa, wait a minute. Jimmy Tootie. Hey, my missing boxing glove. Whoa, he's got one.
That's my lucky glove cut. Jimmy Tootie, what are you and your
unsavory pals doing in the burned out husk of this robot?
The first rule is we don't talk about what goes on in the burned out
husk of this robot. Hey, eat horse. Give it to me. Nothing. Do it. That's my
championship trophy and I want it bearing square.
That's my trophy. I could probably get it if I tried.
They're giving out trophies now? Boxing championship, wise guy.
See ya, suckers. Okay, so how do we get him a boxing championship?
Well, isn't that funny? Boxing Betty. Do with this.
Do I have to play this or are they going to do it on their own?
Gabby J. Yay, yay, yay.
Okay, hold on. We got five community subs from PilotGuy. Thank you to the
five sub PilotGuy. Appreciate it. Thank you. Coming in with subs.
What do we got? Move your mouse left and right to dodge and click either mouse
button to punch or use the keyboard. I'm going to use the keyboard. Use the
left and right arrow keys to dodge and then use A or D to punch.
So it really is punch out. It is punch out.
Yo.
More punch out? Uh oh. Bald Bull. Do I have to actually do the Bald Bull
mechanic? He like runs in.
Who's left? Final opponent? The Giant Rad. He's got a huge glove.
Can I not dodge that glove? And maybe I can't dodge that side.
We'll find out. Oh, he can. Oh, that was quick.
Left jab. Left hook, go left. Right hook, put him away. One more.
Right hook, and Jimmy goes down. It's the super exclusive,
more action figure with extra, hmm, there are pieces missing.
I don't see the weapons of mass destruction. Eh, who needs them?
How could I lose? I'm no expert, Jimmy, but I bet being a loser helped.
Four.
I think they kind of need to update the four horsemen, don't you think?
Like, where's the horseman of identity theft?
That's a huge problem right now. Where's the horseman of,
you know, like a pestilence? Famine? No, where's the horseman of low Instagram likes?
That's what we care about now. Suicide isn't the answer. Things will turn up. Think of your loved
ones. I stuck a nerve on that one. People are getting defensive here. Wait, what did he say
about me? What did he say? I'll bite him. All right, uh, I have a big question.
I think like a millennial like zoomer joke. How many times have you wrote boomer jokes in here?
What, I'm allowed to just take them, but I can't dish it out? What's up with that?
Sometimes you guys gotta play defense. It's not all offense.
Try to land. Oh, my God. Which one's the incontinent one again? I couldn't tell you.
Boy, you really are useless. Aren't you?
It's not funny when you're making fun of me.
Uh, think of your loved ones. You know, your wife's going to give you hell if you kill
yourself. You're overreacting, Jimmy. You think? Sure. Your wife probably never really
loved you in the first place. Jesus Christ, that's fucking awful.
It's always darkest before the dawn, Jimmy. What the hell does that even mean?
Give it up, Sam. Oh, you're right. If somebody as dim as you can tell I'm
just phoning it in, why bother? Thank God. Um, I don't know.
Max, I don't think this is helping. I disagree, Sam. I feel much better about
myself already. Uh, well, do I have any items? Maze? Jimmy, care to try out a maze?
No way. I ain't falling for that. I'm not gonna shoot him. That's not
gonna do anything. No, Jimmy's gonna have to do this for himself. Oh, God.
Nobody's home. I love, I love that. So I love, I love just how I make like a, like a zoomer
reference and all of a sudden it's just like, boom, chat explodes. Right? Oh, that's so
fucking funny. I love it. Can I talk to, I can't talk to the other rat, I don't think.
Throw a snowball at him. It's gonna melt. It's like a 16 hour car ride.
But can I maybe, where is he on the left? Where's my office? Here's the window. Hold on. Wait a
minute. I can't reach Jimmy from here. No, we'll have to talk to him from downstairs.
Nope. Well, let's listen to the answering machine. What does that sound? Oh.
I mean, this is IP Freeway. Stick Charmer in the closet. Then you should see a doctor
about that. No way. Crank calls only work when you call someone besides us. This is
the only phone number I can remember, Sam. Can I like, I want to, you know when you
get like rewind and relive moments? I want to relive that one. Oh, I love it. This is,
I love it. I love this. It's so much fun. All right, let's go.
Let's go back to the North Pole. I need a snowball. We're off to the North Pole.
A new, okay. So I have two horsemen. I have the record. Hmm. Can I, nothing can be done
with these two. I have to, what do I do with the snowball? Can I bring the snowball back
and throw it at him? Let's see. There's a time limit on it, so let's go. Where to, Sam?
Let's head back to civilization or what's left of it. Why would I do that? To throw the
snowball at the rat to stop him from jumping off the ledge? Wouldn't this knock him off the ledge?
That's not how it works. Ah, Bosco's maybe.
I don't know. Let's try, maybe go, let's try Bosco's again.
Do you ever look at your subreddit all the time?
Being hit with a bleached snowball at this range could cause permanent blindness.
And usually draw the line at temporary blindness. Microwave, microwave the snowball. I don't know.
Does he have one? But we have something with the gifts. Save, Bosco. We'll take that package
off your hands for you. Step back, boy. That's mine. Get away from me. I can't like occupy
his brain with a maze. Maybe I probably have to send him. Wait, hold on, gift tags? Maybe
make him think it's not. I don't think I can send that in the mail.
X-ray machine. It's probably something to do with sending him a present. Hey, an x-ray machine.
Don't fool with that. Even dark rooms need popsicles. What's going on in the refrigerator?
Stay away from my cryogenic freezer. Yeah, but what reddit? They said your reddit.
If it's a cryogenic freezer, why are there still mustard-covered snow cones in there?
Just because I'll be in suspended animation doesn't mean I don't want a snack.
All right, this is the bathroom. Something to do with the gift. X-ray viewer. Oh,
it's in there. All right, we have to send Bosco a present. We're going to send Bosco
a present and then we're going to take this one. So we got to get a package sent to him
and it's going to be green and it's going to be a clock. Clock. Send him a clock. Got it. I win.
Sometimes it's just so easy. I get headaches all the time. Like my brain is so fucking huge it
can barely be in the skull. It's just like I want to just let it come out. You know what
I mean? That's what my mother used to tell me. Mom, I have a really bad headache. That's
because you got such a big brain, sweetie. Off to the North Pole. That's not true.
Your mom lied. Jesus, guys. Oh my god. Yeah, Neanderthals have big brains too.
Yeah, but they didn't know how to use them. Okay, so now I get a gift. Bingo.
Sessomatic stopwatch. It's going to Bosco. With a constant reminder that they're always
running late. You can hear the precious moments of your life passing with every second. Now we
just need to attach a gift tag. Gift tag to Bosco. What unlucky person should we mail this to?
You know. Bosco might like that. It's not green though. Does that matter? I don't think
that matters. Brain spickness does not equal smartness. For example, blue whales. You're
talking about not a human. Let's go get it. Where to, Sam? Let's head back to civilization
or what's left of it. Good thinking. But how do you know? We can always freeze to death
out here later. How do you know how smart a blue whale is? Have you talked to a blue
whale before? No, scientists have like dropped cameras down to the deep sea and taken a few
pictures and put it on like Instagram trying to get a bunch of likes. Dude, what is with
okay. We're going to talk after this.
So where's the other one?
We're good at waiting to open presents, a little buddy. Wait, where's my package? Dear God,
they took it and they took Sam and Max too. There ain't no place safe.
All right. So listen, the word Instagram has the immediate, innate,
complete opposite reaction of the word speed. Think about that. When I say, oh, an
Instagram, I'm going to fuck up you guys right now. You ready? Instagram likes speed,
Instagram likes Instagram speed speed. What do I do? What do I do? I need one more.
Let's just stay here. You never take me anywhere. I just took you to the North Pole.
That's how I beat the villain at the end of the movie. I used that tactic. That's all they had
to do. I beat the robot villain at the end of the movie. I went, you are the villain.
Sometimes the villain wins. I better be careful though, because the villain,
only temporary, no, the villain can like, and we gotta be careful because like the villain
somehow always in every form of media is like, wait, I'm not a bad guy as I can't win.
But sometimes they do. Sometimes they do, guys. I need one more. Can I go in here?
There's actually been like quite a few movies and TV shows where the bad guy did win.
I can name you a few very recent ones. Uh-huh. Like, wait, what? Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, what? Like, I'm not going to say, I don't even know what you mean by this,
but hold on. I'm trying to piece that together in my brain. Megamind. Does that, does,
does Megamind win? But at the end of the movie, does Megamind lose? You know what I mean? Like
I'm saying, like I love when they, when they skirt around tropes like that. I'm spoiling
Megamind. No, what? I didn't spoil, I just said that's a trope in movies, like the bad
guy doesn't win. I didn't mean, I didn't spoil Megamind. You just spoiled every single movie.
That's not how that works, okay? Just because somebody says the bad guy doesn't always win.
The bad guy wins, but the bad guy doesn't always win. I just explained to you every
piece of fucking media that's ever, and guess what? There's a bad guy in this one too.
Sometimes a bad guy, the bad guy won in episode three. Bad guy didn't win in episode five.
I, what do you mean? I'm spoiling every fucking movie. Every single piece of media.
That's not, come on. Megamind, who cares? So long. Megamind was like a fucking Will
Farrell movie that came out between like two other Will Farrell movies. That was like a Will
Farrell 1.4 in the middle of like a 1.0 Will Farrell and 2.0 Will Farrell. You don't care
about Mega, I didn't spoil Megamind. I just asked a question. What do you mean Will Farrell's
not even in it? Will Farrell is Megamind. I don't even need to, I just watched the first
five seconds of the trailer of Will Farrell. I can't believe you spoiled Megamind.
You said the bad guy doesn't win in movies. Oh no, I could never play Super Mario Brothers
ever again. I could never play any. Streamer says it's okay to spoil movies if you don't
care. That's not, all right, we're done with this. Oh no, wait, the bad guy doesn't always,
the bad guy doesn't win in movies. I like when the bad guy wins, but the bad guy doesn't win.
You mean to tell me that Bowser is not gonna win? I thought this time when he captured the
princess it was gonna work. Can we start the exorcism now? No, we still need three more
horsemen. Let's hurry, I've got a sudden inexplicable craving for pea soup. I hope
this demon appreciates all the work we're going through. I just hope he doesn't rip our lungs out
and eat them in front of us. Bowser does win in one of the games, but that's what I'm saying.
What, what are you talking about? Bowser is like a, wins sometimes, but he loses all the time.
You'll have to, we still need one more horseman. Okay, I gotta get one more horseman.
It's definitely not here. It's something to do with this shit, but it's not here.
How does he win sometimes if he loses all the time? I don't know.
No, one snowball is probably more than enough.
So basically what you're saying is sometimes different things happen in movies.
Sure, and everybody lost their mind. I don't even know where Megamind came from.
Or what's left of it. Where the fuck did Megamind come from? I don't even know what
happened. Garage. Oh, it was the Villains Win movies. No, because you guys called me a villain
and I said, Hey, does Villain win sometimes, doesn't he? And then all of a sudden.
All right, well these guys, there it is. There it is. How do I get this?
Autobot is here before you open this body shop. A string of unsuccessful body shops.
What makes you think you will have better luck? A recent influx of road debris will
result in the projected six four percent increase in revenue. Route debris from the main
track.
Okay, you don't like Torture Me Elmer. What have you got against Torture Me Elmer?
Show us. My associates were once the most popular toys available, but no more.
Beating up a doll cannot compare with the wonder and excitement of arithmetic and grammar.
Uh oh, Max. I think the cops may have been educational toys. I knew there was a reason
I didn't like them. You know how to fix cars. So do you know anything about cars?
If we didn't, why would we open a car shop? Because you're lonely,
forgotten machines who do anything to feel useful. Processing. Oh dear. Import appears
valid. I just had a breakthrough. This is all about my dad.
All right, we want a hybrid. You guys turned the DeSoto into a hybrid.
Damn hippies. We are not. I just wanted to be able to use the carpool lane.
Since when do you stay in the lanes anyway, Sam? Okay. Torture Me Elmer is the hottest
toy this season. Elmer appeals to the lowest common denominator. He's a solo!
We'd like to pimp our car. Please make a selection from the following menu.
If you'd like the exclusive Death Horseman hood ornament, press one nine.
And what else? That is all we have. There was an ordering malfunction. Totally not my fault!
Actually, we also offer a wide range of completely worthless decorative decals.
We want that horseman. We'll take that Death Horseman hood ornament.
Excellent. First, however, you must complete the Pimplica driving challenge. Oh no.
I'll just give us the horse. Video game challenge. Where is this on the net?
We've pooled together our years of experience in designing the most advanced computer games
to bring you the ultimate augmented reality driving experience. Augmented reality? Yes.
While you were cooking, we placed a pair of our patented augmented reality goggles in your
vehicle. Okay. You did? Through the miracle of augmented reality, your driving experience
will be five to ten times more satisfying than ever before. Would you like to try the
driving challenge now? Yes. And how? Eat my dust. Initiating augmented reality driving secrets.
So I have to just win this driving challenge? Elmer's hit. I have to run over Elmer's.
Pimplica driving challenge. Thanks to advanced technology and the darkroom, you can now drive using a computer keyboard in addition to your mouse.
I'm really excited. How many do I have to hit? 30. Your mission is to have the displayed number of torture meal medals.
I can get that. And you must do it in the allotted time.
Well, let's go. Just go. That's right. I'm not non-efficient.
Fuck not. Once they put the pressure on, I can't do it. I got it.
I win. I don't. Got them all.
Look, Max. It's the sudden unexpected death figurine with super reaping action.
Now wherever we drive, pedestrians will feel the icy chill of death. More so than usual.
I didn't skip that. It was over. I didn't skip it. I didn't skip that. Hi guys. What's this about
decorative decals? We can outfit your ride with a wide assortment of decorative embellishments
created by our in-house auto detailing artist. How does he do that? I didn't skip it. His
mother was your label maker. Simply hit the street and obliterate rare objects. If we deem them
suitably interesting, we will reward you with a decal to commemorate such joyous destruction.
Now that's my kind of game. What should we be obliterating? That is for you to determine.
Okay, so no decals. All right, give me the horseman. Do I just have it in my inventory?
I don't. I don't. I don't. He's giving me horseman of death. It's icy cold. Complete
the exorcism. Where to, Sam? It's time to make a horror movie. It's time to have first and
last name and then the bad thing that happened to them as the title of the movie. Off to the
North Pole. The exorcism is definitely rose. Jenny Stevenson goes to hell. That's the last
one. Now we just have to sing the incantation. The haunting of Will Ferrell. Possibly the entire
earth as we know it, yes. It still hardly seems worth it. I feel like that could be a real
movie. All right, here we go. Let's do it. Let's put on the friendly demon song.
Here's some demon.
It was a gelatinous
mantle.
Mime sweeper.
Corporate presence.
Poor horseman. Suck him up. Roy G. Pitt.
The power of Christmas compels you. Any second now, Santa's gonna walk out that door demon free
and show us with gifts like absentee dad and guilty conscience. Did it work?
Wait, but he, you mean, but I thought, no. I quit. I'm gonna be a dentist. Is he dead?
Finish Navidad, baby. What? Nothing? Didn't you guys read the back of the instructions?
There's a back? Feeling hungry? My five dollar fill up box will do. I'm sorry.
Very important. Make sure you have the spirits of Christmas to contain the beast or you're
screwed. Shaman Max, it's up to you to save Christmas. Yep, we're screwed.
Sorry, I had to just ruin that. I'm sorry. I'm having too much fun today. You know what
I mean? I gotta like stop having fun. I gotta like shut up and have not have fun, right?
All right, so let's investigate. Can we just go in the room now? I just got 45 dollars for that
joke. Juno Upsetto, that joke deserved these bits. Thanks for the 45 dollar joke. That was
just for you. Thank you. That's a lot of money. Christmas pass, present and future.
You know us? We know all those who have ever ruined Christmas, especially the repeat offenders.
It's only supposed to be five dollars. Spirit of Christmas past, brothers. I am the spirit
of Christmas present. And that cat's the spirit of Christmas yet to come. He's shy.
What's your 20, good buddies? We could use some help saving Christmas. We're not bad
people. We've just had bad luck with major holidays and automobiles and federal statutes.
It is your own selfish actions that have brought this to pass. Selfish? We're freelance police.
We save the world, sometimes on purpose. You got no clue the bad karma you've built up, man.
You will need the combined help of all three of us to defeat the demon. We will show you
three Christmases you've ruined. Set them right and we will consent to help you.
Where are you going? I have to get some air. I'm gonna talk shit right now.
Pause it for a second. Somebody said when the game is funnier than the streamer.
Well I'm sorry. I'm talking in real time here by myself over a video game that I'm just saying
time. Of course the game's gonna, they had like years to make this game with a team of writers
who every day for months came up with jokes. What? Of course there's gonna be better humor
in here. They had like a year and a half to write the jokes. You gave me 10 seconds. Sorry
I spoiled Megamind. That's what this is about. I know it is. That's what this is about. They're
mad because I spoiled fucking Megamind on them. Hey Sam, what time is it? Let's see. The
little hand is on the freckle and the corn cob pipe is on the right eyeball. Ready? Where does
the time go? Look at this. It's Santa's magical stocking stuffer. It fills the sock with whatever
gift the owner deserves. Oh let's try it. I think we'd need to have socks first. I was gonna
see them theaters after the stream. It's a record of what people got. You know how they
Jenny A. Nice kid. Sock full of toys. I know we're still on this but. Means well.
Sock full of candy. Steven G. Liar. Sock full of coal. Wow. Santa must really hate liars.
You know when they bring back movies for a limited run in the theaters? What if they
brought Megamind back for a new another run in the theaters for some reason? If they break
to IMAX or something or 3D for a couple months? Oh man. That would be fucking hilarious. But
why would they ever do that? That's such a forgettable movie. Not that it was a bad movie,
right? Listen, it's just not a movie you would bring back. Didn't win the Academy Awards.
That's my son's favorite movie. That's fine. I didn't say it was a bad movie.
No, one snowball is probably more than enough. A concrete car thanks for the five community
subs. There's a lot in this one. There's like a bunch of different things to do.
You cats ready to take a freaky trip to the past? Thanks for the five subs. You bet!
A team of writers spent months writing Megamind. Of course it's going to be better than this stream.
The game crashed. Uh oh. I didn't save it once. Is there an autosave here? No,
okay. I think we're fine. I just had my stomach just hurt for a second. I was like,
that was two hours. Gone. Oh boy, I hope so. Come on. What is this? Where is this?
Okay, I'm fucking having a little panic attack here because this is the first image of the
beginning of the game. Oh, thank god. Okay. Oh. All right, well let's go to the future.
The future. Oh no, we're spoiling our future.
Change our snackless fate. Surely we can alter these shadows before us perhaps with a larger
economy size bag of pork rinds or chips. You know, Max, we could find a way to get our future
selves out of this place. Yeah, I guess that'd work. So, uh, what's the scenario here? We need
to get snacks or something. We probably have to change the past. Why did you bring us here,
spirit? What do we do? Who wins the SEC? We probably have to bounce around between. I got
money riding on it. Yes, our future selves are trapped to die on a tiny outcropping of ash
surrounded by roiling magma. But what is it we're here to fix? Hold on, hold on before everybody
screams. I thought you can't talk to yourself. Don't I crack you up now, Sam? Sorry pal,
his material just seems fresher somehow. Hey, future me, would it hurt you to hit the treadmill
once in a while? Did you say something, Max? You mean after we're gonna die, it burns, it burns?
Topical. What do you mean? Anything else in here? No, just lava. All right, let's go to the past.
Game saved. I'm so glad they added that run. It really is great. Portals of the present.
Are we already in the present? How does that make any sense? You cats ready to take a freaky
trip to the past? You bet. I want to rub my body all over Mary Curie and see if you'll glow in the
dark. That'd be neat too. Wow, man. We ain't going back that far though. Jump in. All right,
don't crash. Oh, we're back here. Here we are in your office in a not too distant past.
I remember this. This is when we had to retrieve the toy mafia's meatball sandwich
that Leonard tried to fence to Jimmy. Do we get to beat up Leonard some more?
No way, Max. These cats can't sense your presence in any way. Dick, you are here to
right a terrible wrong you once committed. We have to stop ourselves from doing yo mama jokes.
Just watch. See you around, sucker. Stop ourselves from doing karate jokes. Hello, guys?
Jimmy, anybody? Well, Jimmy, where's this big score that's going to change everything?
Where's all the money that's going to save our dear tiny Timmy? Yes, daddy,
where the **** is it? Oh, it's hopeless. The doctors say his Tourette syndrome will kill him
if they don't operate soon. Don't cry, mommy. I'll get the **** with the **** angels.
It's all a bust, Mary. Every time I try to make an honest living,
Sam and Max smack me down. Oh, ****. Jimmy, we were all counting on you.
I know, Mary, I know. If only I'd have stuck to boxing, I could have been somebody.
All right, so we got to be in a wreck, which is what I am.
Stop him from boxing? So get your lucky boxing glove and go fight.
I don't have it no more. Sam and Max took it. Again with Sam and Max. If you spend more
time boxing and this time sitting around watching TV, you'll be champ. They said,
Jimmy, you're a washout. Please don't fight mommy and daddy. Daddy's my hero.
This is bad. This is not good. Poor Jimmy.
Oh my God. I'll go call the doctor to ease his suffering.
Just get that glove, Jimmy. A baby doesn't have much time to live.
I can't say all that on TV. That's probably a $400,000 FCC fine.
You see what you gotta do. Beat up Leonard some more?
All right, so we have to. Jimmy, stop sitting around and get that glove.
We have to get the box. He has to be a boxer and boxer.
I gotta get the glove. So I have to give him the glove.
We can't interact with anybody, can we?
We've come back from the grave to haunt you.
He can't hear us, Max. Also, we're not dead yet.
Being hit with a bleak snowball at this range could cause permanent blindness.
I usually draw the line at temporary blindness.
We need to get the glove from Jimmy in the present to give to Jimmy in the past.
So we have to get Jimmy to not jump off the ledge to get the glove to bring to here.
The street looks a lot less destroyed.
All right, so how do I get the glove from Jimmy?
That's the real question. Hold on, can you tell me?
So what do we have to do?
Can't you brock the signal these cats are sending you, man?
The ailing child, the nagging old lady, the boxer who lost his mojo.
I have to go back and lose?
Trap traps? No, you gotta get him back in the ring.
Okay, get him a glove.
I know I have to stop him from suiciding, I know.
But the question is how?
You don't gotta all caps me.
I just said I knew that's what I had to do.
All right, so what does the present do?
Prepare yourselves for a journey beyond imagination as we enter the present.
Sam and Max, witness how your reckless carelessness hurts those in...
Hey, wait a second. This isn't the present.
You took us to the past.
Past us are standing right there.
Yeah, this is the past.
I know that.
Just give it a minute to catch up.
What?
That's the limited edition pestilence maquette with super detailed open sores.
Aw, see how he slumps in his saddle.
Does he have any cool action features?
Cut it out, Max. You don't know what that'll do.
What's the worst a toy could do?
Choke a toddler? Blind a toddler?
Inviscerate?
Well, it looks like nothing happened anyway.
Let's go.
Oh, no.
Seriously, we had a totally boss bug summoning toy and we wasted it on a stupid exorcism.
Teen hut!
That too, sergeant.
What?
How did you stink bugs find me?
This place is great.
Beaty brother too good to share with his family?
Too good to birth radio silent to cause this problem.
Another family problem.
Been on a work mission, ma'am.
Been hanging out with those filthy dungies more like me.
They don't even speak our language.
As long as my family's together again, I'm never leaving.
Mayday! Mayday!
Request immediate evac.
Immediate evac!
So what?
We have to rekindle the bugs' love for his family?
Teach them what they really mean to him?
Oh, my.
No fair.
Have you seen them?
They're awful.
You have to get rid of them.
Oh, boy.
I'll go get my stomping boots.
Non-violently.
All right.
Let me see.
We've got gift tags, simplest maze, and spirit bottle.
The maze has definitely put something here.
Can I like do something with the maze?
Not happening.
What do I do with the maze?
I've had it for a long time.
Hello, sir.
He can't hear us, Sam.
What is that?
It smells like wet ghost dog.
Maybe can I do the maze to the rats?
Well, I didn't think it was that funny.
But whatever turns you on.
I didn't say that.
The bug did.
What else is in here?
Hey, Sybil.
Oh, she can't hear us.
Hey, Abe.
Oh, he can't hear us.
Think it'd scare anyone if we started playing the jukebox?
Probably.
Your taste in music scares even me.
Can't change the channel.
Anything else over here?
Hey, Stinky.
Oh, she can't hear us.
All right.
Well, bug family.
Anybody else feel that?
Sure did.
Some kind of angry, violent presence.
And strangely familiar.
Is that you, Dad?
We haven't seen him since the attack of the cleaners.
Give us a sign, Father.
Okay.
So the idea here is, what if I just go back?
Maybe press the button on the...
No, but I don't have it there.
Let's go out of here.
Let me try the maze on the rat.
Why would that do anything, though?
The future doesn't...
There's nothing there.
I mean, I'm in the...
I can still do stuff now.
Let me just see what this does.
Look alive, Cheek.
Lead on, brother.
I'm gonna try just the maze here and see if I can put it down.
Jimmy, stop sitting around and get that glove.
Most rats would love a maze for Christmas.
No.
But this rat only wants his boxing glove.
Nope.
I gotta get him off the ledge.
The booze?
Maybe, like, how do I get him...
That's how I get the glove.
I need to get...
Go back to the reality here.
The real reality.
Can I give him, like, the booze?
Well, what is this thing?
Oh, that's the corporate presence.
Freelance police help spawn.
You're under arrest.
You have the right to remain viscous.
I mean, yeah.
You'd think the rat maze would do it, but...
I was clicking on Jimmy.
Can I click on the kid?
Jimmy.
Timmy this...
Here we go.
Hold on.
Timmy two teeth.
Rats do love mazes, but giving a dying kid
a cunningly disguised trap seems cruel.
Merry Christmas, Mrs. Two Teeth.
Come on.
We've got you the one gift every rat loves.
Really?
An impossible maze.
Yeah, I'm gonna get it.
So now in the...
I hope Mrs. Two Teeth appreciates the finest...
So now if I go into the present, is she gonna be in there?
And she's gonna come out and I'm gonna make her talk him off the ledge.
Let's see.
Hold on.
Where to, sir?
Let's head back to civilization, or what's left of it.
Good thing!
Let's see if she's in there.
Okay.
Now is this here?
It's not there!
We never should have let that deadbeat...
Wait, is he on the window?
I can't read...
We'll have to talk...
Wait a minute.
Wait, hold on a second.
Is he...
Was he on the window?
Fuck.
Didn't do it.
Wait, let me try to give him the...
What I was gonna try before.
Give him the booze.
You want this?
Nothing doing.
No.
It's the guy that did something through the maze and the boxing club.
The wife and the...
Where to, Sam?
Can I just...
Wait, hold on.
Let me talk to him.
Because I did place it.
Oh, that was a big one.
I'm gonna do it!
I'll jump, I tell ya!
Hang on a second, Jimmy.
Smile, Jimmy.
What about...
Smile, Jimmy?
What is it?
Look on the...
Turn that frown upside down.
That nonsense ain't helping.
Sorry, Jimmy.
It's just that suicide is too horrible for me to even contemplate.
Even though we'd all be happier if you were dead.
So there's no, like...
What about your wife?
No wife, no family, no job.
What right side?
Well, with all the brain damage you got from boxing,
you'd make a great bacon-eyed janitor.
Nuts.
My boxing career didn't even last long enough
to give me a decent case of brain damage.
You know your wife's gonna give you hell if you kill yourself.
Mary!
She left me!
You're overreacting, Jimmy.
You think?
Sure.
Your wife probably never really loved you in the first place.
I gotta get the glove.
It's...
We're in a paradox.
I have to get the glove to give him a pass so he boxes,
but I need to keep the wife there
so he doesn't end up going down the path.
Max, I don't think this is helping.
I disagree.
We gotta break the loop here.
How do I get his wife to...
What is the point of the trap?
Hold on.
We're off to the North Pole.
Am I missing something here?
Because at present, the trap is that I have this alcohol.
I have a snowball.
The family is just out there.
How do I get the wife to go into the maze?
How are we doing on fuel?
It's running low on coal.
I can't take anything from that.
All right, hold on.
Let's go back in here.
Let's exhaust some options in here.
She's talking.
Take the coat.
It's always the coat hanger.
Is that really it?
What?
That is...
We can work it out.
I just took his wife.
She left me.
Now I'll never see her again.
I know, son.
I know.
Okay.
So now we go to the present.
We put the wife down.
We show them that we let the wife out.
Okay.
I guess we're just gonna hold her up and be like,
here she is.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
This is how she left.
Oh, shit.
I told you this is time travel.
We took her.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
Here we go.
Look.
Oh.
I hope he takes the glove off and it's a huge fucking human hand.
Got it.
Oh, my God.
That was awful.
Why did you do that?
Give him the glove.
Why not?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Here you go.
Now be the best boxer ever.
And then we're gonna lose to him.
Probably not.
This is probably just as simple as clicking on you and then we win.
Excuse me.
Makes.
Get out of the way.
Thank you, makes.
What?
Could it be true?
Timmy, look, it's your pa's lucky boxing glove.
Where the fuck did that come from, daddy?
I don't know, son.
All I know is I finally got a second chance.
It's a fucking Christmas miracle.
Stop that.
I ain't never gonna get anything out of my sight again.
Now, come on, son.
No squares are allowed on Twitch.
And get you that operation.
Way to go, dudes.
You saved Christmas past.
So let's move on back to the present.
The rats made you and the rats will destroy you.
Sam and Max, you made up for your past and helped Jimmy find his way.
Now for your reward.
Your eternal reward.
I'm just gonna chill in this bottle until you're ready to unleash all three of us
cats on that fascist demon.
Nope.
Okay, so we have done that.
We now have one spirit in the bottle.
We now have to figure out this shit.
Which is we've got the future, which is just standing there.
That didn't really do anything for us.
That just closed up that little port of the present.
Let's go back to the future and see.
Ready to hit the future again, Max?
Go ahead without me.
I'll catch up.
Just get in here.
Bottle of spirits.
I get it because alcohol is scary.
Why are you capsing me right now?
We still haven't escaped yet?
I'm disappointed.
It's people like us that give people like us a bad name.
There's nothing else in here.
Jimmy didn't do something different.
I'd better start dieting now if I want to be in shape for my inevitable death.
Can I throw a snowball at myself?
Hey there, sexy.
I'll be back to pick you up later.
Being hit with a bleached snowball at this time.
I don't think I can do anything.
I need an item or something.
What happens if you kill yourself in the future?
Can you tell us what to do in charades?
Is that it?
Nothing.
Okay, okay.
One word sounds like fiery death.
I'm skipping the text we've heard three times already.
I better start dieting.
Are you mad that you don't get to hear that an eighth time?
What if I didn't hear that one?
Yeah, I did.
Skipping the fight.
It was the shooting one.
Oh, well, whatever.
Santa's coal powered sleigh.
Santa's coal.
Coal?
It's running low on coal.
I need coal.
Can I dump this guy's energy in here?
Coal?
Where do I get coal?
I gotta get from the stockings.
Wait a minute.
Get out of my way.
Let me go over here.
So you're telling me this was for nothing?
This trampoline cannon toy bomber thing?
I don't have to even use right now?
It was for nothing.
They set this up.
I took like 30 to 40 minutes in the beginning of this stream
trying to figure out how to do this.
I can't be right.
It was just for fun.
Well, whatever.
Okay, that's cool.
All right, where is it?
Stocking stuffer.
Look at this.
It's Santa's magical stocking stuffer.
So the sock.
With whatever gift the owner deserves.
Oh, let's try it.
I think we need to have socks first.
So we have to get a pair of socks.
Where can I get socks?
I need a pair of socks.
Santa doesn't have socks lying around here somewhere.
Okay.
Are the Curly Larry and Moe still out there?
Whatever they are.
No, no socks here.
No.
Are these little weirdos over here still?
No, they're gone.
Socks.
We're gonna get a pair of socks.
Let us return to the present.
Off topic, but how much?
Never mind.
That's very off topic.
That's so off topic.
That's not even like I'm not.
Why would I would never would read that?
Okay.
Just what we need.
I mean, there was a feet command here.
Hey, stinky.
Oh, she can't hear us.
No, it's in the other.
No, I gotta go back.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's the only.
Is she even wearing socks?
Why would I go to them?
Why would I go up to her and be like,
Hey, can I have your socks?
No.
They're for a quest.
Okay.
It's adorable.
I think it might be a warning, Sam.
Still adorable.
Hold on.
Where to, Sam?
Is that really what it is?
Let's head back to.
Good thinking.
I thought about the bugs.
Bug family.
Come here.
Let's let's talk about this.
Standing up all day, getting you down.
And how I was made for sunning beach sunning.
Not slinging hashed counter side for a pack of ingrates.
This doesn't mean anything.
Any tips on dealing with cockroaches?
That depends.
If they're in the soup, just scoop them out.
If they're on the pizza, it's easier just to eat around them.
Um, okay.
So long.
Bug family.
Hello, sir.
What happened to your dad?
You really want to know?
No, not really.
It was our toughest battle yet.
We secured our positions in a heavily fortified dumpster.
When suddenly they came out of nowhere.
Who?
The cleaning crew.
Cleaning crew.
Attacking with sanitation.
That's just plain dirty.
Get stinky socks.
Overpowering.
We all would have gotten.
I don't.
I think I'm getting, like, baited.
I still remember his last words.
Move out, maggots.
God, he was concise.
Cleaning.
Every time.
Every time?
I know what to do.
Can't you get your family to leave?
This sorry regiment never listens to me.
These half-wits would only listen to my father.
God rest his exoskeleton.
Goodbye.
Keep them dead.
Being hit with a bleached snowball at this rate.
No.
And?
That was so clever.
Really?
I think I'll save my snowball for a more satisfying target.
No.
That's not it?
But where's the, where's the watering can?
Can I throw it at the different time period?
In the, at the.
Where to, Sam?
We're off to the North Pole.
Let's see if I can do it in the other presence.
Okay, so now.
To containment.
No, no, no, I know, I know, I know.
Got it.
Whoa!
Cleaning crews on all sides.
Father, it is you.
The butterflies are pinned down!
Move out, maggots!
Sir, yes, sir!
Company, march!
What in tarnation?
My family!
Imagine taking this long to beat a putt-putt spinoff?
Well done.
Now, let us return.
Get over it.
To the present.
I must admit your obedience was acceptable.
I suppose I can help you after all.
Forget that!
You gotta send me back!
I wasn't done haunting people yet!
Oh, Max.
You and Sam will be dead soon enough.
I'll wait in the-
What is this? What are you linking?
I've saw, I've seen that already.
Hold until you're prepared to release all three of us to smite the demon.
Alright, socks.
We need a pair of socks.
I'm excited, disappointed, over-socialized, and more than a little gassy.
Get me back to the sock machine.
It was a bunch of bullshit.
You guys just wanted me to say the word, like, feet and stinky.
Together.
And it worked.
You did a very good job.
You did a great, great work.
Here, print out.
Candle hell.
Deceased.
Sock full of flowers.
Richard N.
Liar.
Sock full of coal.
Richard.
Jason B.
Liar.
Sock full of coal.
Patches.
Good boy.
Sock full of chew toys.
Dr. Catherine D.
Upstanding citizen.
Sock full of toys.
George W.
Liar.
Sock full of coal.
Annabelle L.
Deceased.
Okay.
Richard N.
I don't think that matters.
Ahhhh, god.
Damn it.
It's a torture me Elmer doll.
Look, he comes with his own breakable spirit and detachable retinas.
It couldn't have been that easy, right?
I need socks.
I need to find a sock to put the coal in so I can power the sleigh so I can...
I'm just gonna go back to the real world.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can you get socks from...
Hold on.
There's actual toys in here.
Computer.
Foot bath and piranha query.
Too bad the piranha are sold separately.
Let's attach a gift tag.
Who's it for?
Stinky might like that.
Quick, run!
Joke's on you.
The chat wasn't being creepy.
Well, they were.
They were.
Very much so.
But I thought I was getting...
I thought it was like a defeat meme on Switch.
Apparently not.
Let's head back to civilization.
Or what's left of it.
I was trying so hard to think of another solution around that.
But it actually was the solution.
Because I thought everybody was just doing like,
Yeah, she's got feet.
She's...
It's this way.
That's gonna be like on the counter.
Oh, that foot bath was heavy.
My feet haven't felt that good since that hot oil massage from Barack Obama.
It smells like you've got a new item on the menu, too.
Now I can find the strength to keep serving these poor sweet spoiled imbeciles.
This smelly old sock could come in handy.
That was the thing that I thought was never gonna happen
because everyone was saying it was gonna happen.
Where to, Sam?
I was trying to just subvert it so much.
Oh well.
We're off to the North Pole.
See you guys.
Chad is becoming the voice in Jerma's head
that is always right that he never believes.
Always right.
Okay.
Hang back on the extreme backpack there.
Always right.
At least one guy is right in Chad.
At all times.
Yeah, I mean that's...
But you're just talking about like a sample statistic here.
There's 3,000 people here.
Somebody's gonna be right.
At least 10 of you.
100 of you, maybe.
What do you mean?
If you get a thousand people in a room
and you ask them all a hard question,
at least a dozen of them will get it right.
So Chad is...
No, some of Chad is always right.
Most of Chad is always wrong.
That's true.
Some of Chad is right
and most of Chad is wrong.
Right?
I'm not...
Think about how many times you've said something
that it was correct.
You're one of like the 20 to 30 percent
that gets it right.
We need more research for that conclusion.
What an unexpected stroke of luck.
Is this another mastermind thing?
Well, you're talking mega-line.
An effort to save Christmas
and drove it recklessly into a hellish vision of the future
very much like the one we're standing in now.
I stopped paying attention halfway through that sentence.
I wonder if our ghosts are here guiding us right now.
Hey, past me!
Check this out!
Shake that thing!
Classy as always, little pal.
Now let's get out of here.
We get it.
I have closed all outlying portals.
Hey, you could stand to lose a few yourself, smart guy.
Chad is always right.
Right, if you could say that.
We saved Christmas for our future selves.
Chad collectively is...
Some of them will be right, so Chad would be right.
But that's not how it works.
That means he'll help us take care of our demon problem.
What's he gonna do?
Give him the silent treatment?
Oh, stop!
Hey!
Never underestimate the power of passive aggression.
But that would also make Chad wrong, too.
Yes, Chad is right and wrong at the same time.
By the way, opinions are not facts.
Let's just get that.
So, Jerma is short.
Oh, we can all agree on that.
That's an opinion of yours.
If somebody was like 5'5", or like 5'2",
I would be taller than them
and they wouldn't think I was short.
So, that's an...
If I went to like a village of people that were like 2' tall at some point,
I don't know, I would be tall.
That would be their opinion.
Oh, you're kind of tall.
So, that's an opinion of yours.
That's not a fact.
So, I have all the Christmas spirits.
Hey, demon!
Cut that out!
I was supposed to take the spirits and...
What was I supposed to do with them?
Give them to Santa?
What are you doing?
I just...
We were talking about...
We were talking about shitting.
What are you doing in the game?
Yeah, we were talking.
I wasn't like...
I was focusing on speaking about opinions.
What size shoe do you wear?
14.
Happy New Year, everybody.
Well, I hope you boys have learned your lesson.
It was a series of honest mistakes.
Keep us on the nice list and nobody has to see this videotape of you
wetting yourself and screaming like a campfire girl.
You rapscallions!
Rattle on to bed, both of you!
Ready for visions of sugar plums to dance in your head, little buddy?
It'd be better than the night terrace.
I got a size 10.
Ho, ho, ho!
Jello!
Sinful.
Santa!
No!
Uh-oh.
Eat the jello!
That feels so good.
So wait, that was all for nothing?
The whole episode was for no reason?
All right, this is where it comes in play here.
Okay, yep, we planned for this.
So we've got to move this over there.
And then we've got to move this.
We've got to move that.
Shoot that.
Drop it on his head.
Trampoline.
We've got to get that.
We've got to move this over here.
Stop it over the trampoline.
And then shoot it with a cannon.
And the cannon's going to break that.
It's going to bounce and hit him in the head.
No, it's not.
What we've got to do here is we've got to shoot this.
Shoot the, uh, I've got to, how do I move the cannon?
Gift.
Christmas present.
We've got to shoot.
Oops.
Shoot the present.
Onto the trampoline.
Oh, fuck.
Shoot the, shoot the cannon.
Shoot the present.
Present.
Explodes.
Shoot the cannon.
Hits the present.
Present.
Onto the backboard.
Backboard.
Goes over here.
Dump it.
Yeah, we finally did it at the time.
Oh.
Okay.
Wow.
Everybody.
It's almost dawn.
What are you standing around for?
We don't get to pull together and save Christmas for the kids of the world.
When have I ever done like a change the letters around joke to make another word?
That's never happened.
I can do the urinating.
It's opinion, not a fact.
And who could possibly deliver all the toys in time?
Read seven.
Merry Christmas.
Good luck.
Drink water.
So that was the Christmas episode.
Say Max, do you think we should have waited for them to load the presents
before we drove off?
What's the rush, Sam?
It's the middle of November.
Oh.
Ice Station Santa.
Cool.
That was fun.
We're gonna take a pee break while the ending plays out
and then we're gonna go on to episode two.
Next episode when?
Right now.
You're about to see it.
All right.
I'll be right back.
This will just play out.
We'll see you in like two, three minutes.
Why is it taking so long to pee?
But I gotta get water, too.
Come on.
I gotta pee.
I gotta get water.
I gotta like stand up and shake around and move around a little.
Takes a few minutes.
Everyone always screams.
You're not hydrated enough.
You're gonna die.
Where the fuck is he?
Get back here now.
I was gonna get a water.
No.
Now.
Okay.
But drink some water.
For God's sakes.
You're shriveling up.
Sorry.
All right.
Let's do episode two.
You guys are like a grandma.
Dear, dear.
Please come in.
Yes.
You have no idea.
Look at you.
You haven't eaten in forever.
Get in here.
Let me get you some cookies.
Oh, yes.
You love cookies.
No, have a steak, too.
Let grandma will take care of you.
You know, you look a little fat today.
Hey, I think you need to go outside more often and get some exercise.
There's the Adam Sandler voice again.
That's the guy.
That's probably an Adam Sandler joke.
I definitely didn't make that up.
Somebody else did.
That's been a thing for a long time.
Adam Sandler probably made that up, too.
Adam Sandler was funny, you know,
before he started doing a Netflix movie every three months.
He was funny like 10, 20 years ago.
What do you mean he wasn't funny ever?
He was funny on Saturday Night Live.
Happy Gilmore, Billy Madison.
Those movies were actually pretty funny.
Just because his movies are not good now.
Like his like mid to late 90s movies were pretty good.
That was like the heyday I said that Chris Farley, Adam Sandler,
Dana Carvey, David Spade, Chris Rock.
Come on.
That was like the golden years.
All not particularly funny people.
Holy shit.
I'm too old for this.
Who's funny now?
Who would you compare to Chris Rock that's funnier now?
Somebody just, Ninja.
Bill Burr is hilarious,
but Bill Burr has also been around for a long time.
All right.
Okay, before I have a meltdown, anyone you don't like.
All right, let me.
Okay, here we go.
Quit this episode two.
Give me a moment.
It's actually kind of opening these old games.
They require a lot of care and attention.
So I'm going to mute the audio so I don't hurt anybody.
I have to change the title too, to make it episode two.
Which is uh, Moi Better Blues.
Here we go.
I have to do all the settings again.
Why is it not?
There we go.
Do I drink tap water?
Technically, yes.
I mean, it comes out of the tap.
I don't drink it right from the tap though.
It's filtered.
Hold on.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Wait, wait, wait.
Pause.
No, I have a water filter.
So the tap water goes through the water filter,
and then I drank it.
It's a good filter.
Don't worry.
Let's get this on here.
There we go.
The audio seems to be okay though.
I hope it is.
That's such an American thing to do,
to filter your water.
There's a lot of fucked up shit that is in water.
How is it American to filter your water?
EU stream was yesterday.
You may have missed it.
Let me make sure that's all set.
Now I'm going to change the title.
Episode two.
Oh, two.
There it is.
Let me update it.
All right.
We're officially ready to play episode two.
Good time coming back from the North Pole, Amax.
If you say so, Miss Daisy.
If I'd been driving,
it wouldn't have taken us a whole month to get home.
Well, I've got to go drain the DeSoto.
You should have taken care of that before we left.
Somebody insisted that we drive through
the Hudson Bay with the top down.
What the hell was that all about?
That's what I said.
Unless I miss my guess,
Sybil's being pursued by some kind of rogue,
semi-sentient, interdimensional portal.
Think we should try to help her?
Can't think of anything better to do.
All right.
So at its peak,
how much was the Max's head in United States dollars?
No matter how many fires we cause,
this baby keeps 70 to 80 bucks.
Yeah.
And without complaining about it,
not like all those uppity firefighters.
Is it still worth some money, isn't it?
Have to do anything with the robot?
Well, well.
We were wondering where you'd scampered off to.
What are you doing just standing there?
Stop that thing.
What do you want me to do?
You already sucked up Big Otis and T-Bone.
It's some kind of semi-sentient,
interdimensional portal.
Okay.
Don't have to shoot it.
When it comes back around,
I'm just gonna shoot it.
Well, I would have stopped it,
wouldn't it?
Throw a parking meter.
Make it the water.
Have water shoot out.
It's some kind of...
Okay.
What about Bosco's?
Hey, Bosco.
What do you know about suddenly appearing
interdimensional portals?
I hear a lot of things.
What does it look like?
Three sides, reddish, chasing Sybil.
Oh, what you've got there is a Bermuda Triangle.
Bermuda Triangle.
Why didn't we think of that?
Wait, chasing Sybil?
You mean it's here?
Oh, that ain't good.
That ain't good at all.
Uh, shouldn't the Bermuda Triangle be in Bermuda?
What's the Bermuda Triangle doing all the way up here?
Sometimes they just like to wander.
Unless it was summoned by T-H-E-M.
This thing again.
Okay.
Who controls the Triangle?
Who's controlling the Triangle here?
I told you.
T-H-E-M.
I really hope you're talking about the giant ants this time.
Giant ants?
That's crazy.
I'm talking about the mysterious cabal of controllers
who summon the Triangle's Ascension portals
to do their dark bidding.
Well, that makes sense.
If there's a Triangle in our neighborhood,
that means they're coming.
All right.
Oh, how do we stop this Triangle?
Once a Triangle gets imprinted on you,
it's tough to shake it.
But they say you can train them
if you can figure out how to communicate with them.
Okay.
How do we communicate with the Triangle?
They're very attracted to Symbols and Sigils.
Symbols and Sigils.
Those two.
They're not real picky.
They're driven by shapes and colors.
A pink rhombus makes it nostalgic for the people.
Pink rhombus.
Red octagon.
Makes it stop whatever it's doing.
I need a red octagon.
A blue icosahedron makes it sit in its mom's basement
and draw maps of dungeons.
And they can't see or hear.
So you've got to feed them a symbol of what you want them to do.
Okay, so we need an octagon.
We'd like to buy something.
I told you, fools, last time.
The store is closed.
But I've been craving a pack of beef tarts for weeks now.
It's the delicious tangy candy that makes its own gravy.
Help us out, Bosko.
That sounds pretty good.
Stop wasting my time.
I'll never get the bunker ready if you two keep chatting.
Some of these comedy foods I would love to eat.
You can't close the store, Bosko.
Everything we value is bought or shoplifted from here.
Don't you see?
The end is nigh!
Nigh?
Yes, nigh!
Wandering Bermuda Triangles.
Strange radio transmission.
Don't you see?
It's T-H-E-M!
They're coming!
I have to relocate before it's too late!
When your life is such a joke that you want to eat comedy food.
But like you didn't, like you've never wanted to have
like a donut from The Simpsons?
Like specifically from The Simpsons?
Come on.
Donuts are real.
That's a real food, though.
Oh, yeah.
Um, what about a, uh, everlasting gobstopper?
Those aren't real.
That's a fucking comedy food.
Those are real.
No, they're not.
Those aren't real.
Wonka was bought out by one company and they, uh, they do, they still,
only thing they do is nerds.
They don't do anything else anymore.
They don't have like Wonka bars anymore.
They don't, the Wonka the company went under.
They don't really exist anymore.
Look it up.
Why does the Bermuda Triangle have such a grudge against all those boats and planes?
Oh, the Triangle got a bad rap for that.
Scientists say those accidents were caused by sudden explosive outbursts of methane gas.
Speaking of which.
Max, don't.
What, Sam?
I was going to point out that many phenomena long believed to have paranormal causes
have actually turned out to be far more mundane in origin.
Only one phenomenon's tremendous power continues to baffle scientists.
Why do you always bring negative energy?
What's that?
All right, so let's, we need to get out here.
I'm gonna get a red, I'm gonna get octagon.
I wasn't laughing at that.
I was laughing at something, the thing that somebody said.
All right, we need, what do you, let's go to order.
Into Stanky's.
What about the toys?
Howdy, cops.
How's the auto body business?
How does it feel knowing you're the only person on Twitch streaming this game?
Doesn't surprise me.
All right, so we have to stop this.
We need an octagon.
Can we go into symbols?
Sibyl's office is closed.
What does she do now, anyway?
I don't know, but whatever it is, she's doing even less of it than usual.
Number one Sam and Max scream, screamer, streamer.
Oh, damn it, stupid spot.
Red.
Hi, you stinky.
Oh, it's you guys.
Hank and Jethro, was it?
Red, toaster.
Sam and Max, actually.
What are you doing?
What? I was just taking care of some cleaning.
Red, stoplight.
If that's a blood stain, you should be sure to use bleach.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Sadly, I think my days of pillaging coastal villages are now behind me.
Give me, give me.
Can we borrow your sign, stinky?
It's kind of important.
Well, okay.
But bring it back.
It's a national heirloom.
You made an octagon.
That will stop sign that would have prevented the Kennedy assassination
if Connolly hadn't run it.
He's blind.
What?
Yeah, they can't do everything instantly.
Oh my god.
Instantly.
I need to instantly do it in a second.
Look, Max.
It's our neighbor, Flint Paper.
Hiya, fellas.
Keep it on the down low, would ya?
I'm doing surveillance.
Oh boy, real detective work.
Who are you spying on?
Some bug, the name of Bosco.
Oh, so, wait, is this a, somebody's, okay.
Stinky's has no smoking unless you're Flint policy.
Sounds a lot like their policy on homicides.
Kitty litter, somebody gave a lot of money.
The Bala Koala, 50 bucks.
Thank you for the 50 dollars, 5,000 bits, 5,000 bits.
Thank you.
Bala Koala, huge cast drop, bit explosion there.
And they say, don't listen to chat.
They suck.
Thank you for the 50 dollars.
I mean, that's, that's the opinion.
No problem, the jukebox only takes 20s.
That's your opinion.
But I like him here for a second.
Yeah, yeah, no, come here.
Yep, nailed it, man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no, they can't hear us.
No, that was fucking the livers.
Of course that's what I fucking think.
Get the fuck right in there, man.
Fucking thank you for that.
All right, thanks for coming out.
See you later.
Hey, there we go.
Now thanks for the 50 bucks.
Just wanted to, I wanted to just say thanks in person.
A little, you know, bring them up and just puddle up a little bit and just,
you know, like what dad does at the wedding when he leans in and just,
I just wanted to tell him a couple things.
Appreciate that.
All right, so we have, let's go stop it.
What are you talking about?
I just had a moment with somebody.
Come on, cross over here so I can stop you.
Got it.
Doink.
Don't suck up Abe Lincoln's head.
No!
Oh, not Abe Lincoln.
Casualties.
What do you think's on the other side, Sam?
Oh, I don't know.
Probably some horrible alternate dimension ruled by incomprehensibly
horrific ancient gods seeking to bring chaos to this plane.
Do you want to jump in?
You can read my mind, Sam.
Oh, we're going a new dimension.
I hope not.
It's my opportunity.
I can do it.
They're more difficult than I imagined a horrific alternate dimension to be.
Help.
Help me.
Help!
Oh, you big baby.
But my nose sunburns so easily.
I'll get it for you later.
Oh, hi, StamaMax.
Are you guys on vacation too?
Yeah, we're on vacation.
We came here to rescue you from unimaginable horrors beyond the portal of mystery
You could have at least had the courtesy to be impaled on spikes or something step aside
Well, thanks for the thought guys, but this place is great. What was the name of it again? Hey
What scab are you guys eating in that pot activity in the South Pacific?
Commonly known as Easter Island because once you leave three days later
You can't wait to come back Abe and I thought this would be a great chance to get some alone time
emphasis on alone
Finally someone has come to rescue us from the ancient prophecy
Talk oh Sam ancient prophecies can only mean two things
Tedious backstories and work we don't get paid for let's hear them out little buddy. Well, all right
Maybe these giant stone heads have something interesting stone heads. What's all this about a prophecy?
The ancient ones said this was going to happen. It's the end of our civilization
But you can stop the prophecy and save us all
Okay
What what is the prophecy? What exactly does this prophecy say is going to happen?
The carvers were told of golden age of one thousand years of peace
Cataclysm the great volcano god Rana how would
Reawaken and rain fiery death upon the island our noble civilization would come to an end
Sounds like we picked the coolest time to come
What do you want us to do you must stop Ron a cow from the
Legend speak of a hidden cave beneath the island where the ancient carvers built a means to pacify
Dribble Venus eyes in the mood for a little spelunking and volcano god pacifying a little buddy
If by pacifying you mean squeezing the magma out of him like toothpaste from a savagely beaten tube and by spelunking you mean
Spelunking and yes
Okay, we'll do it. We'll take the case your honor. What does that mean like the Hawaiian word aloha?
It can mean many things like hello. Goodbye or as in this case
We're not going to pay you
Really is the universal language
Not even a couple of bits
Anything else in that prophecy who are you guys? Who are you guys? Anyway, we are the moai
Guardians of the island spirit keepers of the elemental power
Sounds like either a good prog rock album or a bad animated series. I
control the power of wind
Well, I used to control the wind now there's not much point to it
Okay
So where's the cave? Where is this ancient hidden underground cave? It's hidden. Cool it rocky
We were asking the middle one
Unfortunately, he is correct. The entrance to the cave is shrouded in mystery. It's gonna be in one of their mouths
with peril
Brought with peril or just right with peril. This is the kind of thing we need to know going in it doesn't matter
You'll never find it
Okay, cheer up max and I will find a way to stop that volcano
Oh good, then we'll be able to go back to our important work of sitting motionless and staring
We have something to look forward to that's a really really good Queen of thorns
Impression I feel like the Queen of thought feel like that was watching game from
portal triangle triangle
Gone and lost and found they don't even know that
That's not a joke. I just think that that sounds just like all this junk
I'm gonna ring the triangle anything good want to read the second half of the 20 commandments
Nah, I only support omnipotent deities when I'm the deity
Okay
fountain of youth
Gong light preserver the only thing that survived from the SS minnow
Did they ever find all those irritating castaways? Nobody ever looked
It's the fountain of youth
All right, so there was a deadly piranha swimming in it
I never wished that about anything
Get rid of the piranhas somehow triangle pong. What are these?
Check this out max. It's even the same color scheme this portal
When did this come out? It's a gong with a silver triangle on it. Check this out max
All right, so
This is the portal out anything else in here. There's the picnic. They're doing a picnic over here
Gong there's like this gongs all over the place. It's a silver gong. Oh, we're salmon max freelance bro. The cake is a lie
I can do this one
Still can't understand you speak a little more clearly
What's left of Noah's Ark? So the legends are true
Someone really was crazy enough to save mosquitoes from extinction and humans live and learn
I know where to go. How did you find picnic stuff on a desolate island? Easy. It was on the picnic basket
So I drank all the coffee out of this coffee mug. It's been sitting here empty with just a little coffee stain on the bottom
That it's this smells so bad, I don't know why
When coffee dries out, that's why I never spill coffee in your fucking car
When coffee dries it smells it like shit
like actual shit
I've ever one time my mother dumped a whole coffee in the car accidentally
And it smelled like my little ass
Five years, but something tells me this just might be the ancient entrance to the secret underground lair of the volcano god
Where do you think you're going?
Try not to get imprinted or shot max we still don't know who this little type belongs to
Jimmy Hoffa belongs to nobody
Okay, so
You can't be Jimmy Hoffa Jimmy Hoffa was a ruthless union organizer and head of the teamsters in the 50s and 60s
Known for his ties to organized crime and his mysterious disappearance good recap Sam
Also, Jimmy Hoffa wasn't a diaper wearing baby. I'm not a baby
No
People always showing me disrespect you should never have started drinking from that fountain of youth. No, it makes sense
What fountain of youth are you talking about? We're gonna be babies fountain right there brainiac
You expect us to believe the fountain of youth is on Easter Island
I can't believe it. I can't believe how perfect he is
Okay, you came here for the mountain water a little hard haven't you I do but take on occasion. Yes. That's my business
Well, why'd you drink so much of infancy look I ain't got no problem, so don't go saying that I do
It's just a little discretion is required
Drink too little you have to go through puberty again too much and bada bing
but as
Just take a small sip every day and stay the same age, you know
Well, just take put an eye droplet in there and like drop one droplet into your eye and you'll stay like 40 forever
I don't see where the big deal is
Step aside sport we grown-ups have to take care of a great big mean old volcano gone
You and your companion will be one thing to take a step back
Not now max then when Sam my biological clock is ticking and I'm not getting any younger
If you spit into the fountain, do you get older?
Know your spit would the whatever the DNA that's in the saliva would would transmute whatever it does
No, it would have to come in contact with you
Okay, so we need to obviously
His baby getting fussy. Is it his bedtime? I'm gonna speak. Yeah, that's it gets younger
How can we find out it's baby gassy this baby need to be birthed that's weird to hear that
It's baby gassy
That's the first time we've heard. I think him change the way that he speaks
This is very weird
We'll give you a nice big rattle for that dumb old gun of yours. You two are seriously trying my patients
We're going bye-bye now, bye-bye you'll stay gone if you know what's good for you
To get him to get out of the way
We can't go in bye. Bye. So we need to okay. Tiny Tiki is this way
Looks like we've stumbled into some primitive Tiki bar. How it's going
Pipe down chucklehead. No, I was hoping to get into a lagomorphs gone wild video
Howdy boys haven't seen you around before
Sam they're all babies stay calm max. They're more frightened of you than you are of them
All right, so this is called wipeout
Hey max, want to see how I won all those surfing trophies back in school
No, I don't want to see you cry to the PE teacher and then beg me to club your competitors in the knees
Why? Oh, you're just jealous of my more plausible center of gravity. Watch this
It's surfing time as the surfboard bucks back and forth use your mouse for the arrow keys to dodge flying bottles
He's like up or down
Two surfers don't lose pal. We just bide our time on the next way
I thought I'd press left all their arms and shriek like startled raccoons either. I'm pretty sure you lost
Try to have your socks knocked off little pal. I don't wear socks and socks feet humor me socks
You'll better pretending that you're not naked. Okay
Hold on. It's not it's not instant. The Sun was in my eyes. I'm gonna take another crack
The call
Why is it doing that
So, what do I get a baby bottle? Well, that was entirely point baby bottle pop a baby bottle pop. I
Hope so. So it was pointless
Purely decorative. Hey fellas, what brings you to our little slice of paradise?
Salmon max freelance police man, and we're here to stop a volcano you babies are in danger. Shut up. We're not babies
He's right pleased to meet you boys babies
My name's Amelia a hot you've already met. Mr. Charles Lindbergh, Jr
Whatever and that other fella is one. Mr. Dan Cooper. Hey
Call me DB everybody does
You've been missing forever. You guys have been missing for decades. That's the funny thing about this island
It's easy to lose track of time. They just keep drinking baby
You don't write you had conspiracy theorists and documentary filmmakers. Baby fountain youth drink. You can't tell us what to do
They keep drinking from the fountain of youth
You look younger than in your pictures
It's that damn fountain
Once you start drinking from it, you can't stop
We had to put the fountain off limits
From it, you can't stop we had to put the fountain off limits or we would have drunk ourselves out of existence
Ironic ain't it? I made my reputation being a woman. I'm afraid to wear pants and now I'm wearing rubber pants
It must have been a big adjustment going back to wearing diapers
Well, not for me when you're in my line of work
It helps to have some extra protection if you know what I'm saying
I ever tell y'all about how I dive them feds and jumped out of a jumbo only like a million times
Okay, what's the do around here you guys do come on around here
We used to ride the bucking surfboard until we drank ourselves under the hot limit
Give me a few more years and I'll beat your record Amelia
Why don't you just leave why haven't you gone home and ruin a clean getaway? No, they don't understand me at home
My parents are so stupid
And I'm not leaving until I get some service
Who is this one? Who's this guy?
How'd you manage to all regress to exactly the same age?
It was a very carefully planned and executed drinking game. You take a drink every time DB says the word parachute
Okay, see you around kids
We have to fill up with a drink. I'm gonna get a small max here
Well
It's an empty tea kettle tempest not included. Okay. Hold on a minute if we boil the water from
the Fountain of youth then it maybe will be the fountain of aging. Maybe the boiling the water gets rid of the aging germs and
It's cartoon logic guys. It's possible. I'm gonna boil the water
It's a swing town inferno. It's gonna reverse them
Where did you find so many femurs my old thorn section say hello to Jack Don and
Rochester that's awesome animals. Tell me about these guys still can't hold the high notes
steel pins go
Alas Gene Krupa. I knew him
Thank you. Thank you
Hiya boys. You're new here, right?
Salmon max freelance volcano stoppers. Well gosh, I'm glad to meet you. I'm Glenn Miller
Maybe you boys can help me out
Everyone here is missing
You're a missing person. We thought you were dead. Yeah, I get that a lot
I was here 20 years before I believed I wasn't really dead
Hated to break it to you Glenn, but all that hot playing was getting annoying. I
Don't know who any of these people are I
Don't I know I I don't know what the references I mean, this is not like
Chris Rock Adam Sandler David Spade those people were up here. I would know who they were
What's Benny Goodman like in person Benny could do things with a clarinet that nobody else could
Thank God a one night after a show in New York
I'll just tell you it was the damnedest thing I ever saw and and leave it at that
I know who they are my god. I don't know who they are. I know who two of them are
But honestly, I got this could be dawn nuts. I don't know from the Andy Griffith show
I don't know who that is. Was count Basie really a vampire a golem actually
But we never held that against it. That was we simply time
How'd you end up here? I was on a mission for the Air Force and I flew here
You mean your plane was sucked through a portal into an alternate dimension and deposited here
No, just got kind of lost and crashed on Easter. I
You ever get a song stuck in your head and can't get it out. It's downright distracting
All right, so song
What do you need help with? I'm trying to find just that perfect sound for my next big hit
Oh
That's it
Well, gee, thanks, but I don't want to just put out a repeat of my early stuff. It's got to be new and fresh
But I'm stuck on on two things
I need a catchy melody and I need a good train sound a train sound
You need a melody and a train
You need a melody and a train whistle for your song cool
You but I'm pulling out all the stops this song's gonna be about all the things the kids are into these days
Train the song is gonna be perfect swing dancing in methamphetamines
But how are we gonna find a new melody?
You've been here 60 years and have been able to give my show you guys I'm teething
Baby, Lindbergh, baby is what I got so far
electronic music
Do you like it you think it'll be good with the kids keep on rockin plan word if I had a hammer
Oh, you can take that mallet if you want. I was going to use it for percussion
Any direction that doesn't involve hitting things with hammers is no direction. I want to go. Thank you and good day, sir
That's it
Okay, I got the I can hit the gongs so we need a train sound
What oh stop so what do these gongs do
Portal just showed I can't reach it
Okay
The ancients use them to transport the sacred stones and to travel all
Throughout the world and for practical jokes, which weren't funny
Okay
If you control the wind, let's see a demonstration
I'm not really in the mood not in the mood. Come on. Blow us up a typhoon
I guess I've just got a case of the Blas. I don't know
sacred stones
God is okay. So I'm gonna make you happy so you blow
All right, don't do it. Have you heard the good news about rhinoplasty? What are you in flying? Oh
Nothing. It's good. You're not bound by the conventions of traditional beauty. I'm just the way the Carver's made me
All right, keep up the good work
Make them happy, but so did this causes the triangles to appear can more than one appear
Or can just one appear does it is just one that shows up and teleports over this way
Okay, so that I guess I can read maybe do it on this one and I can reach into it
Maybe I could see what's in it
Check this out max. Where does it go?
All right, so oh
That's the book. Hey, that's this one kiss and now
For some reason I thought they would these were okay. So can I reach in and like grab his head?
See what happens goldfish memory
You know, I'm getting up. Let me tell you something. I'm getting real sick and tired of people questioning
Yeah, no, no, cut it cut the music cut the music. Let me tell you something
Like the back of the head. Wait, there's a gong over here
So I okay. Here's where this I don't understand. I can't reach in why why would this matter?
I'm assuming there's an item that I need to do all these things check this out max
Like yeah, all I can do is put my hand in there. But if I had something else I could
Transfer it around but what?
Well, I could go back to the real world. I think I have exhaust all the options here besides of the picnic
Let me go over here. Don't you think it's amazing that you found that picnic basket full of food?
Not really. It was sitting right there. You couldn't miss it
How's the vacation going? Oh
The weather's perfect and there's so much history and culture
The best part is that Abe and I finally get some time all to ourselves. Let's talk there. No distractions
Abe what? Oh, yeah, right culture
The volcano is gonna explode volcano is going to erupt in a deadly rain of fiery magma. Aren't you worried?
Are you sure you're a dog? Did you sound like a big chicken?
Be nice Abe. Well, if it looks like the volcano is going to blow we'll just hop back through the triangle
Just between the four of us those moai statues are real jerks now you just shut your mouth
Trouble in paradise have fun kids. Don't wait up
So long you two
Talk to you talk to you. What about you? This is the one that doesn't like me
Why the long face? It's just that we've been here for so long and there's so little for us to do
I have to question the soul-crushing bleakness of our existence and oh
Wait, you're making fun of me aren't you took him long enough to catch on and the way that sob story was going
I thought he was about to show us baby pictures and have his sign his yearbook. Not cool
All right
One here Joe. Hey, how many volcano gods does it take to screw in a light bulb hackneyed and blasphemous?
Sheesh up island
Okay, what do you?
How about this problem you believe in all this prophecy of destruction mumbo-jumbo? Of course I do
I can feel run a cow's anger rumbling. Even now me too, Sam
I think those tamales from stinky's are repeating on me. Ah
It's got a logical humor very classy
Don't worry
Your civilization is coming to a fiery cataclysm again. Don't sweat it. I'm glad you can joke about the end of our civilization
I don't find it particularly funny
Okay
What's your story if you must know I am the keeper of the power of earth
Why don't you give us a demonstration? I'm not going to unleash the tremendous power of the earth God on just a whim
Shake the earth. Okay, so shake with your volcano problem. At least you could do is shake things up and win
This isn't some game. I wasn't granted elemental powers just to amuse you
Are we gonna have to dig this guy up to get the stick out of his butt? He wasn't always like this
Double dig that guy out trees ago when the ground would shake with his laughter
And there was a time when you didn't need a sandblaster to fit in your ceremonial dress
That was uncalled for
Okay, got to make this one laugh this one happy
Hmm. What's the problem man? Stop being so uptight and give us a demonstration. I'm not in the mood get lost
All right. So how do we make you laugh?
Don't go anywhere. We'll be back. Is that supposed to be funny?
Hmm
so comedy
funny something
happy I
don't know about you though
All right, let's go back to earth and explore a little bit
Like I have an idea of what's going on here. Can I shoot the fish?
Sometimes the simplest answer is the easiest one
So what about the diner anything in here?
Oh, I can talk to the I remember that they said they wouldn't talk until the I stopped the time
Howdy cops anything new in the out-of-body business
Naturally
Oh, it's a captivating melody composed by a resident musical maestro
All right enough with the sales pitch how much it is not for sale
All right, there's a new tell us about the new game
That is correct
We are sorry, did we just blow your mind
I don't like to brag but my prowess at banjo legend extreme is pretty renowned throughout the tri-state area
And i've been banned from 27 local arcades for playing forbidden dance insurrection in ways the designers never intended
Does not compute you are saying that music video games already exist
We play the new game how do we play this game of yours
Well, here's the melody for the
You know the guy in there that I don't remember his name the right time earning more points the closer
We get to being in rhythm with the soundtrack
Obligated calculating that would require processing power far beyond error not a number
Just destroy all the to win our exclusive new car horn
Would you like to play our game let's do it so we have to run stuff over again
Hello and welcome to the pimp the car music challenge
Your goal is to drive over the bagpipes and own me the bagpipes don't hit the courty
Thanks to advance of the nanotechnology at the dark car you can now try using a computer keyboard in addition to your mouth
Ready go
Where are the bagpipes you see any bagpipes I do I see them
Okay
Okay, get them
What is that you see that thing rolling at the end
So is it a train
Be sure to come back soon and play again
Don't worry max. I'll put it back before we go cruising again
So what is the sound is like the melody right? How does it go?
I want to hear it. I just want to make max happy for a second
Just for I needed to do it just for one second. I know he's
It's okay
All right, so I have the musical maker
From these guys, let's go in the diner. Hi stinky. What? Oh
Nothing doing
Anything else I need in here?
specials
Camp david granite. What is it camp david granite grinder little tykes grinder with
this I
That's okay
Anything I can do palm tree. Wait, can I get a coconut or it doesn't need a gardener? It needs a plastic surgeon
Napoleon not pictured his right hand
Is one of those people on the island gene shallot kaplan? Whatever happened to him? He's been masquerading as gene shallot apparently
Why are you checking out bosco flint for a client samo said she was the poor chumps mom
She was a real no-nonsense dame with legs up to here hairy legs, but still
And then there's jesus
Okay, they have these little passwords under here
Airhorn
This your pipe stinky. Yes. I looted it from the corpse of a 50-foot sherlock holmes
Can we have it?
No
I come on. That's your pipe stinky. Yes. I know but what about these things?
Where's the band? I keep hiring drummers, but they keep combusting and not slowly over time either
spontaneously
I can't like take that for his music shop
All right. Well, I have I can bring the horn back. Let's try that
Maybe in boscos that I didn't do what about the office?
Hey moscow
What do you know about easter island?
Who told you to ask me that just some guy outside in a black suit and sunglasses
Seem to know a lot about you bosco
They're getting closer
Bosco has the water been tasting funny to you
Why am I doing this to him ever since we saw those government guys working on the pipes down the street
It tastes like control and makes me want to pay taxes good thing. I distill sanitize and recycle my own water
He he gets it about those black helicopters hovering outside
Stop trying to freak me out fools. I'm busy
Hey bosco. Did you know you're being watched? Do you guys even know me? Of course, I know that
No, we mean right now from inside stinkies
Y'all just trying to make me paranoid
You think I don't have a camera inside stinkies. I'd know if I was being watched. Where's the camera?
It's genius
Hidden inside the pie that nobody ever eats oops, by the way
Tell stinky her place would look a lot better if she didn't have that big black lump in the booth
That looks like a small intestine
Where you planning to go? Oh, you'd like me to tell you where my emergency bunker is
No chance you'll have to stop goofing off and bill jones
It's just like the fable of the grasshopper and the ant if the ant were a paranoid lunatic and the grasshoppers too come to think of it
All right. Where's the emergency bunker in it? But uh, where's your emergency bunker bosco for the last time?
My secret bunker's secret location is a secret
Do you have any honey bunches of pumice brand cereal? Yes
It's good and it's good for you and it's all for the bunker. We're gonna find the bunker
Do you have any stem packs and radiation cams fall out? Sure do cool. It wouldn't be a good emergency bunker without them
Unfortunately, they had to pay
I think the settlement was
Four to five million dollars out of court
Bethesda did not like that at all
That's kind of sad. Do you have any zombie repellent? Get out of here. There's no such thing as zombies
That's just what they want you to think
Do you have any powdered drink mix cases of it in every flavor you can think of?
Three day old rigatoni stuffed with marshmallow peeps in an orange soda reduction with a hint of cilantro
Every flavor a normal person can think of
Is that it? Do you have any high glass repair kits?
Not much worse than being stuck in the apocalypse with all the time in the world to read and then have your glasses break
Y'all think i'm an amateur this bunker is going to be 100 irony proof
Do you have any look for the last time? It's all for the bunker. Give it a rest already
All right. See you bosco. That's not for long
It's a combination microwave and x-ray machine perfect. Now we can see what's living inside the burrito and then watch it die
I don't think there's anything left I can do in here
I do know about an emergency bunker, which is probably the bathroom
And it's definitely the bathroom
Do the grandpa voice
for what
Just right now
Just because nothing else down here
Let me go into the office
Wait, wait, wait, was there anything else over here I could do?
Chew chew teeth miss me already chumps. Well, I ain't coming back no matter how much you beg
The place just isn't the same without your persistent funk and wheezy starting. Yeah. Well, i'm done with that rat hole
Happy birthday mega agro
We're gonna do it up. I have a wonderful birthday party and all your friends come and they have all kinds of toys for you
Because that's all that fucking matters in your birthday party is if somebody brings you something to eat and brings you toys
That's all that I that's all I get
Happy birthday. There you go. That's free birthday. No
God there's nothing we can do to torture me elmer that hasn't been done to him already torture. Yeah, we were pretty thorough last night
What oh god
Check the closet always check the closet
There they are
finest in remote control fisticuffs
Leonard looks surprisingly healthy for someone who's been in the closet for six months
I've been feeding him. Oh you old softy. I've been feeding some way to get rid of all those spiders
This is a fucked up inhumane shit going on in the closet here
Just like max this desk is full of handy secret compartments
Okay desk line. I don't think I think I just gotta keep going
I think we just have to go back
And do the music thing. That's all I have
Let's go see if I can blow the horn in his head
Let's try this
So we've got the horn
Hey glen listen to this action
That that's fantastic you like it who wrote it bring him with you so I can work with him full time
I don't think he'd like it here. No outlets
Well, in any case, that's the perfect melody for my new hit now. Just find me a good train sound and we're all set
me sound
Why is there a train?
Is there a a whistle or something I can find?
What this glass?
Well, okay
diaper rash dispenser the diaper rash
Ingredients bourbon wava juice mint and talcum powder. Whoa
the pacifier
Ingredients kerosene pepper spray dihydro capsaicin and wasabi. No, okay, which one sounds the best water ingredients
Artificial colors flavors preservatives and water. I mean, that's just a gatorade. I would drink this one
All right. Well, I have the cup now. Can I
Put this in the fountain youth the piranhas are in there though. What's left of Noah's ark?
Can I have some of that?
Maybe something with the portal. Can I like put the
Cup in the portal or
They're gonna jump out at me
Did I get it? Is this fast enough?
No, I gotta stop them
Let me just see what happens if I do this
I'm just curious if I can put things inside
No, siree
So how do I take care of this?
Nope
Can I actually use the cup on anything that can I fill the cup?
Hold on. Can I drink one of these or put one in?
The diaper rash ingredients bourbon guava juice mint and talcum powder
The only thing that you can't really the talcum powder is the only thing that's not good there. Like can I use it?
Oh, actually I can I can fill it up
They've already got their drink
Viper rat hold on. Let's see other one the passive fire kerosene pepper spray wasabi
Pepper spray the hydro capsaicin and wasabi
Not happening. No siree. No just just dump it
No, don't get more
Get the one that hurts
So is there somebody I can feed this to but I don't think that would work. We just dump it in the piranha pool
I feel like that's too easy. Does somebody
try
you
Want a drink mr. Hoffa?
Jimmy hoffa cannot accept a drink from none. Do you want it in your sippy car?
I didn't mean to do that. I want it served by a dues paying member of the waitresses union
How do we get into the waitresses union? Fortunately for you, I am the union leader and also dues collector
Yeah. Yeah, I know a setup when I see one
I suppose you want a favor to let us in the union the game has too many jimmies from spilling on the paying customers
Take a tray of drinks and ride the bucking surfboard without dropping anything
What?
Oh god
Now I have to ride the surfboard
Let me just see if I can I just dump this poison in here
No, no, dump the poison in there
Poison the fish
I guess I can't we gotta just keep this going
Hold this don't drop anything
All right. Here we go waitress tray wipe out
Max check this out. I'm gonna fuck this up for like an hour straight
Oh, yeah, i'm gonna screw this up for like a fucking full hour
I'll see you guys when I never compete
The sun was in my eyes
Straight up straight up. Oh, yeah
How much time has it been the hearse castle now do it with me on your head
Not unless one of the babies let you borrow his diaper. You're too easily startled
Third time's charm so I did it
Now, excuse me, sir
Wait, hold on can
German never loses I did what you wanted me to do. So let's talk
How about that harper didn't drop a single bottle
Impressive. I must admit. All right. All right, you're in you're lucky. I'm very thirsty now. Get me a drink
How about this one?
Thank you our little man's going to need you like that try it and i'll shoot off both your paws
How do you like that didn't even flinch?
um, okay
well
Can I?
Wait a minute. Can I?
Kerosene can I burn it? Can I can I give him like a fire drink?
That's what this is for
There's nothing in it
It's an empty tea kettle. Okay now put it
now put
What what what in there which one the same one diaper rash?
Or the same one?
Oh, it's the train with simulacrum of a train listen we constructed out of everyday household items
Don't say simulacrum. Well, that's perfect. That's just the sound I need for my big hit
Let's get started making musical history boys
Uh, there's a demo on that conch shell this is gonna be you
Are we going to get a producer credit?
Talk to my agent
So
Where do we do this?
Can we do it now do it here or what do we do with it?
Who needs this?
No, he's already
I need to get him a drink though. I'm sure they've already heard it
I know what that is
Put this through play it will make you happy
But yes, it's down like toe tapping
Oh, no whistling sound
Abe
Are you even listening to me?
Unfaithful, Abe
Okay. So wait a minute. Hold on
Do we put
Abe hold on so long you two
What's left of Noah's arm change a
I wonder if there's a way
not happening
Whistle so what is this is does she whistle into this? No, he needs to come up
I'm gonna put something what Abe wants to go over there
Come on blow us. You know how to whistle. Don't you just put your stone slabs together and blow
I think I need something else really in the mood. Well, you're not in the mood fine. Keep up. All right
So how do I get you to move now?
Will you move?
Playtime is over son. We've got important work to do
I'm expanding my enterprises back here and I'd hate for either of you to get hurt in the construction
I have to I definitely have to give him another drink of
freelancers family worse than scabs
He's gonna take a drink of the font newth he's gonna turn into an amoeba that's what's gonna happen
Going bye. Bye now. Bye. Bye. You'll stay gone if you know what's good for you
Sam look how his little eyes and the barrel of his gun follow us. I could squeal
Drink he tried this one. This one has actual alcohol in it
Drunk, baby. This is not this is illegal
Oh, Abe, isn't it beautiful that gentle breeze and that melody in the air?
Abe
That look you haven't heard one thing monkey ass, right?
What? Oh, I mean, did they talk? I hadn't noticed
So anyway for our next vacation
Hey windy sybil, I mean sybil have you ever thought about getting some surgery done?
What I was thinking if you had your nose stretched out, so maybe you sweared off the head a little you'd look fantastic
Not that you don't look nice now, of course
That is it. You've done nothing but stare at her this entire time
Come on. I'm a man. I'm not made of stone. Well, you know what I mean
Oh, I know what you mean. All right, you're just in a mood
No, i'm not
I will long remember what you said here and I will never forget what you did here
I just can't believe you'd insult me like this
And on my birthday happy birthday sybil
I said birthday today makes you have a good one to have a picnic and have some toys. That's what I want
That's it that free birthday
Well
And again, I forget to bring my video camera
Okay
Well that happened but we have an important task to do it's give alcohol to a baby
Say bye now
Let's try some water
Bourbon is not going to do it artificial preservatives is
I was thinking
give him the
fountain of youth
You just don't want water? Thank you. I've
It's probably the I've got to get the piranhas out of there
I don't think we've ever tried to stop a volcano before not unless you count that time in the philippines
Let's take in some sites or vice versa
It's definitely the fountain of youth and you feed it to him
but
We have another scenario over here things didn't go so well with sybil, huh? Yeah, she was cramping my style. Anyway
So miss moai
How you doing get bent beauty?
Fair enough
Okay
What's left of noah's art?
So, uh to put in a good word for you with sybil. Nah, i've still got a shot with the locals
Not even after another thousand years. Wow. I haven't seen rejection on that scale since I walked you in the last election
Don't you think it's amazing that you found that picnic basket full of food. I've got more important things
Should I go talk to sybil maybe I should go talk to sybil
What's back there what's left of noah's art?
They're gong back here
Looks like another gold gong
What?
There's no way I could reach that how do I get over there?
Now we have five community subs from splarg
Thank you splarg
For your five subs. Thank you
That has to mean something. I don't think I can reach that. I don't think I can shoot it from here
Are you serious? I don't need the gong
Well, what am I supposed to put over there?
Check this out max. What happens?
Is there anything over here?
I don't think this will uh
Nothing doing damn. All right. Well, that's probably for that's the volcano
here
Hold on and blow the whistle into here. She's gonna blow and it's gonna come out the other side
Watch this ready
No, it's not what you'd probably make more friends if you'd just denunciate more clearly
What would that that line that wouldn't accomplish anything but what do I get to do with that? It's a silver gong. Can I
No way
No, no, that's not gonna do it. Is it?
No, it's not
Something has to come out of here. Wait, hold on
You seem irritable
Want to talk about it?
I got it. I know what to do. I know what to do. I got it. I got it. I got it. Here we go
It's a silver gong
I gotta be quick
This is this is gonna be a
Pleat yeah, because now i'm gonna get the water and then i'm gonna go give it to hoffa and then i'm gonna get in
All right, let's go
I want to do this fast
Not fast enough
No
Hold on. I can I can shoot wait. Hold on. I guess
here
this
and um
so
Do the conk
and then
shoot
over here
And then just run over there
Let's see. Okay. Here we go. Ready? Three two one
Put the plan into play
All right. All right
Ah
Oh, what's happening to me?
I still have to get him angry
No, that's I gotta do this a different way. Hold on. Wait, can I listen to this?
I don't even have to use the portals
Okay
that
That changes everything
Great
So let's just have it set up
Yeah, gg
Here we go
All right start it keep up the get him mad blow it in there strike the lightning
Get mad
How's that dirt bingo anybody have any malt vinegar?
Thank you everybody
Thank you the three heads
Here you go, jimmy
Time for you to drink heat into oblivion
Take it
You're gonna turn into a single-celled organism
Thank you. Hmm
This tastes familiar
I can't place exactly where
Oh wait
I remember
Sorry max, I know you were getting attached to the little guy but it's for the good of not what I thought was gonna catch the who
All right. Did he leave his gun?
I thought he's gonna turn into
Like a amiibo or cell or something. It would have been fun. I just shrunk him and popped him anybody home
We're here to fix your volcano god interloper
Dare violate our most sacred sanctuary. You're all in danger. The volcano is going to erupt
I don't like how their tentacles move. You treacherous defeat. You must answer to our leader
Oh my god, um who framed roger rabbit, right?
Is that what movie is it mighty kamehameha doing donuts in a square paddle boat kissing max?
It's the spectral form of mr. Spatula. That's just our dead goldfish
From
What be the punishment
High priest has spoken you to be executed
Now hang on what you have say for self
Um, you can't kill us we're famous
Be reasonable seahorse monkeys, but your spatula is evil
Your high priest is a false prophet that very serious claim to make
Could make us lose tax exempt status. How are you back it up with a filet knife and some sushi rice
kill them
Uh, you can't kill us. We're famous. You can't execute us
We're the freelance police killing us would bring down the wrath of legions of fans and licensors
Not to mention the aspca
We know like killing speak for self
But we must act on wheel of high priest
He our only can do it to mighty feet
Okay
Think about what you're doing. You seem like a fairly reasonable group of uh,
What are you anyway?
We are the underfoot protectors of the sacred home of ranakao the volcano god
The airbreathers call us ocean chimps
We know like that name
Okay enough of these we know that imposter is lying because max is the true high priest
He does have feet maybe shulu's dog speaks the truth
Look, we ancient civilization that worship giant feet who speak to us through ghost fish high priest
We're not gullible if white one with mouth truly is high priest
He prove it by fulfilling the ancient prophecies
I bet there are three of them. He knows our ancient traditions. Maybe he really is the chosen one
Ancient say that an outsider will be anointed by the feet the feet will recognize him
And he will perform great miracle to feed his people
He was feeding these water becomes delicious treats
And the island itself will show us the face of the true high priest
He appears before us in the living rock
Ah
How does max get anointed by the whole anointed by the feet business the great feet speak to us through the high priest
The outsiders stand under the great feet. They move to show they accept him
Okay
What kind of miracle are you guys looking for prophecy say
The high priest feed us by turning water by turning water to banang so I mean water
Banang eat delicious banana flavor drink that fortified with essential vitamins and minerals
That's the fake water
with banana flavoring
What do you mean about the island showing his true face prophecy say image of true high priest
Will appear to us in the cavern
That prove our high priest is the one look
You mean that image of max?
what
You crazy that no look anything like box max have two ears. That's just a seashell
Rock next to it look exactly like high priest though. It's miracle
All right, so we have to put his ears down
All that is max in a nutshell
We believe it when we see it we fair people we give you until soon down
You prove white one is high priest and we know kill you
Okay
So we need to make max we're going to take max's head
We got to cut his ears off
or fold him down with blue or
I don't know
Oil or something. We'll just slick him back
And then we need to feed them a banana flavored water and then we have to go get worshipped by the feet
All right. We want to get max anointed up
Okay, we humor you
Almighty feet give us a sign
Do you recognize this white stranger as your servant whose feet are these though?
Give it a minute. The feet just don't recognize me without the mustache
You waste our time
Say you not high priest we killed him now. No, we must wait for sundown
So, okay
This all right
Three
Okay, so what all right?
We got a gong here
Ceremonial earn some kind of ceremonial earn we eat ritual food from there like still beating hearts of victims
or party mix
All right. So this is
Yeah, this is buried guy. Hello champs the song lady and then mean mad guy got to make him happy
So, let me get this straight you worship feet. Yes
The great feet that hang over us always
The first to go into the world to bring food to his people
Yeah, it's just feet and watch over his people always season one was like a hypnosis
thing
Second game is feet bounty of nature. What's the third season gonna be teachers purity of the fast?
And when the end times come the fifth to return to deliver his people home to paradise
We
Okay
Can I play the song under here?
So portal down here. Why is it down here? I'm gonna have to bring something over here
Machine pod it's the entrance to the lava machine that only used by high priest
We're in his entourage show
What do you think I can open magic
No
What have you done
What have you done?
Okay portal
Stalactite that precariously hanging stalactite looks awfully familiar. What is it?
Our guns don't work underwater reason 976 to get me that harpoon gun
Is that a portal axe
I was hungry
Let's check everything else
Wow, we really are off course vanished set adrift and disoriented. But what does it all mean sam?
I don't feel like waiting around for years to find out
Now what no
Jeremy you're playing fetish games
This all started with mr. Mosquito and all of a sudden it's like do I play anything else interesting seaside reading
Is it piloting for imbeciles? Nope the desperately lonely traveler's guide to easter island
For the most relaxing trip on easter island bring plenty of basalt
It's a mind-altering substance for the moai that helps them tune in turn on and drop out
All right. Well, I just grabbed that this is
the travel guide
radio
Hmm, the plane's radio still seems to be working
Um, it's wizard
Observing your earth and we'd like to make a contact with you, baby
Baby
You're listening to get the let out weekend on 107.7. Ks am ks am easter island
Attention charlie india oscar 1017
2006 and a frequency
Bingo
Uh tora tora tora
We are observing your earth and we'd like to make a contact with you, baby
Uh, and we're back for max and s-dog in the morning
Let's skip the small talk sam and get straight to the pranks and racial slayers
Uh, let's not do that. We should not do that
We should probably uh, absolutely not
uh
over and out
Frequency, let's see
You're listening to get the let out weekend on 107.7. Ks am ks am easter island
Is anybody there attention charlie india oscar 1017
Observing your earth and we'd like to make a contact with you, baby
so
tora tora tora
How many frequencies are there?
Oh, it's bosco
Observing your earth
We have come at last prepare to meet your doom
We heard that bosco. We are not amused
Uh attention charlie india oscar 1017
Over and out what else is on here?
Tora tora tora
And we're back for max and s-dog in the morning
Let's skip the small talk sam and get straight to the pranks. No, no, it's not let's not do that
No, we're not gonna do that over
Look, it's this one but
Crate crates full of video games
All right, so let's go back over here the maxish clam
Another one of nature's horrifying wonders. I gotta agree with the chimp sam. That looks nothing like me
So we need to have we need to change his nose. What? Okay. Wait, hold on
So we've got
Can I do anything with this?
All right, I can put that in here
It's the desperate for the most relaxing trip on easter island bring plenty of basalt
It's a mind-altering substance for the moai that helps them tune in turn on and drop out
Can I shoot that?
And turn it on don't work underwater guns. Don't work underwater. Is it one next to his hairiously hanging stalactite?
Let me go just look at it for a second
Here's this one. The water cooler is one of the most often repeated forms appearing in nature
So the something right next to his head
He has one right next to him, right?
It's this one
Go back down because it's one two three, right?
Maybe not that way. Wait, what do you mean wrong?
It's the middle one. Isn't it isn't it right next to the third feet right here?
What do you mean? No
No
What?
It's the middle one
No, i'm trying to activate the stalagmite next to him
Because there's three
I mean, I know I can do the the singing thing now
I thought this was gonna open and I could I was gonna go this way first
The music doesn't do anything to the third one
Now that this this is a portal right and this is the one next to him if I activate that I can like reach
In right?
All right, so max get up there. Let's get max anointed again
Does it look like a portal?
Mighty feet give us a sign
Do you recognize this white stranger as your servant?
I thought it would look like a portal. It could be like a portal
look
He must be high priest. Uh-huh. That's right. Bring the love good to see you too mighty feet
Sign is clear mighty feet anoint you as high priest give blessing
But you still not satisfy all three prophecies
Who's very explicit on this show us two more and we're convinced
Because he oh that looks very familiar it doesn't that that precariously hanging stalactite looks awfully familiar
Just let me humor myself for a second
Can I shoot it down? I can't think I shoot it down
He's gonna like them. Okay, he's gonna laugh and this is gonna drop
Just need to make him laugh
And then I stick that on the other all right, I don't know I i'm over thinking it
I thought I had to like turn that into a portal left of noah's art
Okay, so
I've got i've been anointed
Travel guide is gonna make you laugh desperately lonely travelers guide to easter island
1963 edition for the most relaxing trip on easter island bring plenty of basalt
I can't shoot now. I can't shoot mind-altering substance for the moai that helps them tune in turn on and drop out
All right, let me see
Nothing else over here. Can I drink this? Let's see if I can
Drink it all little buddy all the good. No, I wanted me to do it
Oh, we both did it
Well, did it work? I guess so. I think your music sucks and I want to stay out all night
You already do that chowder head now. Let's hurry up before our voices start changing
I can keep going. Oh, this is awesome
So what's the point of this?
My best friend max has something very important to say to you boobies
Whatever. Oh, you don't think that's funny
But i'm all my stuff
This makes me want to go potty
All right. Well, can we leave like this?
Are we gonna be little?
I guess i'm just little now
Let's freak out bosco
No kids allowed. Oh what?
What happens? I feel a sudden urge to vote republican. We're not as young as we used to be max
The fountains effects well off quickly
Well now I know where they drink so much of it
Are you stinky? What? Oh
Okay
jackalope buddha
shipwheel shark
Palm tree
Um, is there anything I can get from here?
Gong it's a gong with no gonger. Where's jp morgan when you need her
Come on
Do it
Portal why doesn't stinky's gong work like the ones on easter island?
What can we do? Is that a blood stain? I don't think we even talked to her. Are you cleaning up?
Is that a blood stain? Don't be ridiculous blood
You act like I killed stinky or something grandpa grandpa stinky. You killed stinky
Oh, this is just cherry marinara sauce for the meatball
Bananas banana pie italiano. Can I have some banana? That does sound tasty
Whatever happened to the original stinky anyway banana flavoring retired went on an around the world cruise
Stinky hated traveling and water and the world. Yeah. Well, he must have changed his mind
So are you two going to order anything?
um
Next time you hear from him tell grandpa stinky. We said hello
Oh, I don't think we'll be hearing from him ever again because you sent him on a
Permanent vacation
No, because he was a cheapskate and I refuse to collect calls. What is it with you guys?
I don't ever go to easter. I ever been to easter island. Oh, sure
I lived there for a few years when I was growing up
My opera was surfing legend. Miki dora taught me everything. I know
Really, what can you tell us about easter island? It's kind of boring. Actually
There used to be a tiki bar near the fountain. That was pretty good
terrible service though
What's the special today?
Oh, it's just a sandwich. I whipped up for the camp david middle east peace summit in 2000
Roast beef monster cheese on a slab of granite on sliced sourdough. Nothing special
Slap a granite slab of granite. Yeah, you know for texture on the kids menu. I substitute a slab of a salt
It's easier for the little ones to digest
We're ready to order
We'd like the special sure granite sandwich coming right up
I
Wanted the other special oh, sorry, that's for kids only fda regulations
I'm coming as a kid and I get it max would like the kid special. That's for kids only
Hey, I don't make the rules
We're gonna go quick
Okay, so we got i'm not that hungry if you say so
Bye stinky
There's a sandwich
I gotta come back as a kid. Can I bring it out of the portal? I can bring it on the floor. Okay
How's bosco doing?
Can we go into bosco is inconvenient?
Not here
He's always in the bunker. What's this? I think i'll wait to use that until I figure out how to launch the torpedoes
He went into his bunker because we called him
That would be a good way to lose a hand
Scared him into the bunker
Because we need to come pre-jerk it's gotta be he's gone now there's got something I can fucking do in here freezer
Bosco tech cryogenic chamber and ice cube maker
steal everything
Amazing. There's a perfectly preserved squirrel and a bunch of imperfectly preserved popsicles
Bosco seismograph steal the seismograph to measure earthquakes and giant robot attacks. Have we missed any giant robot attacks?
No, I think we actually caused all of them
The microscope radio is the radio we call them on noise seven one seven five there it is
Larger we thought enlargers would be smaller
Think bosco would mind if we helped ourselves to somebody good question another good question one can or two
One should be plenty
Founded
I'm looking around. I can't see look. Okay. I can't see that from back here. I can see like a can
It's like okay a little bit when I got close enough I could see it I was gonna look around
You can't read that from from back here. There's i'm looking at like the grand scheme here the grand space. Uh,
I moused over it. I wasn't reading it. I was mousing. How far away are you? I don't know 40 feet
30 feet maybe
Okay, so
I've got some banang and i've got a sandwich
I'm ready
To go complete some stuff here back into the portal
so
Hey, look at this
I've got something for you
Would you like it? You know what would cheer you up a granite sandwich a granite sandwich?
That's the best you can do apparently your taste in cuisine is as refined as your sense of humor
No, is it? I don't know about you sam, but i'm ready to chisel this guy a new one
You know that that's funny
Why don't you think that's fine? Let's go do the water
and then
No, no, no, no, no
Can I combine these here?
No, I can put it in the I can put it in like the jug
What what what? Whoa? Whoa, what what what didn't they say they wanted water with like vital nutrients in it?
Why is everybody freaking out? I was gonna pour this in and put the banana in there and then
they
What this isn't spongebob
They're underwater
Uh, it what do you mean? This isn't spongebob. This is a goddamn cartoon
You want me to use cartoon logic? We're in a cartoon right now
It is spongebob
I thought I had to like add like a sprinkle of banana flavoring watch as high priest max performs a great miracle
Oh hear my command what was once waterless make yellow impressive
What was once without sustenance make enriched with calcium, which is something our bodies need anyway
Just get on with it max
See it's like a powder
Eat like a party in the boat. I thought I had to add it like a crystal light packet
Sorry
But you're still not high priest yet
Most satisfying final prophecy
Yeah, I know about the final goddamn
final prophecy is it's
Uh-huh again in the sandwich
It's the desperately lonely traveler's guide to easter island
1963 edition for the most relaxing trip on easter island bring plenty of basalt
It's a mind-altering substance for the moai that helps them tune in turn on and drop out. Yeah
fountain of beverage
Give me the fountain beverage. Give it to me
But he can relax
Your buddy relax
Two steps forward 15 steps back you
You are making me so angry right now, you know, hold on cut the music for a second. Let me tell you something
I now that's an odd feeling. Hey, what gives the fountain of youth water is gone
What have you been sneaking into my inventory again max?
Don't blame me if you're having trouble holding your water
Why is it going water evaporates if it gets too far away from the fountain. That's damn inconvenient
Really? I can't just uh
so
So I can't we I cannot drink it and sprint. No, it's not gonna work
I have to drink it outside. It's gonna it's gonna happen
Watch this
Try it stupid
Give me a break
Try it. This is stupid
Okay. All right. Let's try it
dumb dummy
Oh to use
I couldn't have known that was gonna happen. Thanks for trying it. Dummy
all right, so very obviously we have to be small and we have to get in there and
I need to somehow
gotta
Gotta um, I gotta do something in here. What do I have to do in here?
Are you stinky? What? Oh
I mean you've got a gong in here. You've got a gong in here. This is not here for no reason
Nothing happened. Why doesn't stinky's gong work?
Like the ones is this the germa told the truth about taking forever to over complicate every scenario and the simplest one's always the right answer
I don't think you can have an account name that long. What about the ashtray? Can I let's say eat them?
Stinky's has a no smoking unless you're flint policy sounds a lot like their policy on homicides
Stop, but what if I don't feel like stopping then our insurance rates go up again
Let's think of the facts. I've got the sandwich. I've got to make him laugh
I've got the basalt
I need to be young inside of here and get the kid's menu the kid's meal. How do I become small?
In here
I can't bring the water here. There's a gong. That's up here. It might just be there for a comedy purpose
If germa you okay, you sound irritated. No, i'm fine
Put the gong in the cup
Should I can I fill it with like other liquids? Can I bring any other liquid out?
Boil the gong
Drink and then rush to stinky. I already tried that
All right
um
The passive fire ingredients kerosene pepper spray the hydro capsaicin and wasabi
How do I make you small?
Can I can you eat something?
Can I like cover it? Uh
Max has got to be small
And what the hell is that for?
I still don't know what that's for
What is that for?
smoke
No, I know I can activate it by shooting it, but I don't know what I need to do with it something
I don't even know why I still have this
I'm i'm stuck. I'm kind of stuck. I am but
Let me just get this in here
The gong the gong in sybil's is like this. No, it's not. It's like
If this is stupid enough to work
I'll be surprised but hold on a minute
No
Come on. I can't like take some of that goo and throw it on the gong
The red like portal goo
Stupid magic water evaporates if it gets too far away from the fountain inconvenient
Shit, hold on. Are you stinky? What?
Oh, give me that
I can't like squeeze the mustard on it and turn it orange
Looks like somebody already had a slice that explains all those ambulances this morning and the screaming
I can't I gotta be able to squeeze mustard on that shit
Damn it. All right. Well, let me go
Uh-oh
Well, that was a long one. That was a very very long one
I hope are we still hopefully live still?
Well, this would make three days in a row
of
Bad fucked up internet. So it's time to it is time to make another phone call
But I cannot do that tomorrow. So we're gonna have to deal with it tomorrow, too
Sorry
We have ten thousand five hundred drop frames
Not bad enough to turn the stream off but annoying enough where it happens, right?
It's definitely manageable
But now it's not good enough. You're fixing it again cocks
Is there something in here that I didn't do?
Can I take something out of can I take the banana out?
I drink something ceremonial feeding her
Not happening. Damn it. What about this? I can't open this thing
It's the entrance to the lava machine only used by a high priest
Oh for the love of god
What the fuck?
There's enough this another portal in here
There's a whole side of the cave. I didn't see snail trail. It's that sea snails disgusting red residue
Well, that's red sea snail. I hope that's red ink and not
Something else the world beneath the sea is both wondrous and completely disgusting
Okay
That gong doesn't need to be painted
I've got to paint a gong. I've got to paint the gong but red it's it's orange. It's not red
Do I have to go paint that gong?
Yeah, but like this I have to paint the gong red
No, siree. Let's go see what it does
All right, let's go paint it
That one's not red
That one this one's red. That's red, right? This is red
That's red
Oh, it's red. That's the bits of huge and it's red. It's a big red
That's the biggest red thing we've seen. It's a huge and red
Hi, stinky. What? Oh is doing red improves digestion. Don't try to argue with feng shui stinky
It's science. We can now activate and deactivate red
activate red
Really expected that to work. Ah
It pulls the biggest reddest thing here. How was I gonna connect those two? That's I what what?
It's huge and red. I what
That was a tough one that was tricky
It's obvious. What? No, it's not
It's not that obvious
It's tricky
Colors. Yeah, but I didn't know this one was connected to a gong. How would I know that?
All right, let's do it
And I gotta go find like a snail with blood coming out of its ass or whatever it was
Give us the kid's special, please. Hello, miss stinky. What do you boys want? Do you have money to pay?
Drop the attitude lady. I'm the president max
President's adorable nephew here for a visit. Well since I know the president personally, I guess it's okay
kids meal
We like the special
We like the special you're in luck boys. I've got one already made one basalt sandwich coming up
But we also want the kids meal, too
Aren't you gonna cut the crust off? I've um misplaced my knife
You probably left it in the real stinky's body. It's an honest mistake. Oh, that's silly you little rascals
Now running long and play before I call child services
That is the kid's meal. I thought they were different things
Hey, look, we got you a mouth-watering basalt sandwich basalt
Hmm. It's been a while
What about the rabbity guy? Is he cool more or less?
All right quick before my carvers get back
This is such a drug oh man, that is some kind basalt dude don't bogart the sandwich. Oh
man
It's like I can taste colors get a lot of cheech over here max
He's lit up like an arsonist birthday cake. No way sam. It's been like five seconds
He can't be that much of a lightweight. Oh, yeah watch
Sorry, sir. We just accidentally killed your puppy
You cracked me up little dude
Oh, whoa
Hey, you guys want to order a pizza really loud laugh
Well, what if we're like all dreaming now and what we think is a dream is really reality
That would explain why i'm always showing up at places with no laughs two or three times just to make sure
Dude
Hello
That's a pretty great lawnmower laugh starting them up
Later dude
Let's go get that stalag
tight
Stalagmites are the ones on the ground so like tights are from the ceiling and you can remember that because stalactite has to hold
That's to stay on the ceiling stalactite
It finally shook loose
Wow, it's like an eight again
How old are you now?
Make sure you get my good side sam. Do you have a good side?
Look over here. It's an image of the true high priest max
How'd that get there?
I win
Defeat show us this of true high priest
Prophecies are fulfilled defeat have spoken true high priest has returned people of the feet
All shall love me and despair
No time for that now little buddy high priest take rightful place on altar
So go in here
Save the day
We've got to get up there and stop that volcano
So wait
We still get to kill them now. Yes. No now we deal with imposter
that's
sad
Funny so-called high priest. What have you to say for yourself?
I thought we were pals. He said
Then he spit derisively
Me
Now he say
Me welcome death
Better than suffer tyranny of imprisonment on stale beach flakes. I knew I should have taken him for more walks
I blame myself. I blame you
Now he say you think you won sam and max you really just step in trap
I send triangle to summon you here and your stupid primitives to waste your time
We not primitive we have cell phones they say the betrayal you're too late to stop volcano
fascist oppressor sam and max get herbal tea and foot rubs once and for all that doesn't sound so bad
Is this thing going faster? Now? He's saying that not what I said at all
Me confused not herbal tea and foot rubs rain or fire and drowning magma
I always
Should have taken the express part now. He's taking a long time
Sam and max come to your doom
In my spectral form
Press the in case of emergency button
What uh now he say my medallion no
Cannot be what world what world he's gonna be fine
The dude's underwater you're gonna be all right no time max you're too late to stop the volcano. What do we do?
What do we do?
We press this emergency button. It says in case of emergency press it sam press it
I suppose now is as good a time as any
Uh
That did nothing more we can do here max. Let's go up top and check out the situation what?
Turn off the volcano like this. It's too late. The volcano's already going to a rock. All right
Well, we just okay get it done. Let's go go go come on. Hurry
With some pep in your step
Hey, look, I had the parking brake on that whole time. Whoops
All right, what did that do up here we need to see what's going on outside
Bloody-nosed euclid doing the eucarist on a nitro-burning catamaran. That's the second biggest bermuda triangle
I've ever seen seems to be spinning out of control, too
Now this one's getting up
That one is it went inside the only way home. I fail to see how this is helpful in an emergency
This is it. The volcano is about to explode
Help us sam and max
I'll try
But hold on. I forgot to get the thing that fell
run this thing
High priest medallion. It's the official signet of the ocean chimp's high priest
Don't I get to wear it? We don't have a chain long enough to fit around your enormous head chump
Okay, anything else sock crown?
You look right
Any more snail trail? It's that sea snail's disgusting red residue
All right, so I got
coin
Conk well, I did that. So now let's see so I have
All right, hold on
Cup of the snail trail. I maybe let's see
This one's pink
So we got that's I can act definitely have to do something with the one in the back
What do I have to do with this?
May I make pink maybe?
Can I scoop it up? I mean I need to make pink
No way. Nah
I still have to use it. Okay
Well, I have a red coin
red and blue makes pink red and green
red and
Red makes red and white
Well, i'm just going by previous logic that we had to paint the gong a different color
Maybe I have to paint the gong a different color now
Now it's a fucking call back to the beginning of the game
Hold on
Watch this
He's gonna stop what did that not work?
Uh, I hope there's nobody on the other side of that triangle. I thought I had to do way more than that
You said it dude, bro
You've done it. You've broken the prophecy. You've saved our ancient civilization from destruction
So sweet thing now that's over with let's say you and I find somewhere private to get
Sedimentary so accomplishment is something we've been screaming for 10 minutes time apart your loss
Can I get a ride with you guys? You guys like think i'm just sitting with my face into the other monitor going
Just where's the answer?
Mr. Lincoln only one way to find out I have to like click on the screen
But and I have to look at the screen. No, no, I have to look over here the whole time. Yes. I got it
Thank god. I guess we just sit here for another few thousand years. That's what I do
That sucks
Where's the music?
Imagine talking over the ending I could hear it just fine. No, I didn't mute anything
Is this supposed to be playing music?
It's all right. Don't worry. I'll I'll show it again. Yeah, maybe we lost the uh, the window is
Yeah, the window is on the music stops if you take too long take too long doing what the episode
I took like, I don't know. What was that like an hour and 20 minutes?
Isn't the general time for these like an hour to two hours? All right, shut up. Sorry. I had to stop talking
Here we go, you guys want to see the ending no see you guys in five minutes
I hope there's nobody on the other side of that triangle. I don't care. Uh
You said it dude, bro. You've done it. You've broken the prophecy
You've saved our ancient civilization from destruction
So sweet thing now that's over with let's say you and I find somewhere private to get
Sedimentary. Yeah
I think we should spend some time apart your loss. Can I get a ride with you guys? Our portal back home is gone
We're gonna have to swim
Do you float mr? Lincoln only one way to find out I get to ride on his do-lap
You can only call that once we get in the water
I guess we just sit here for another few thousand years
That sucks
Okay, so
Everyone was so upset that I spoke over the last four sentences of the game. Let's see what we have to do it again
Again with the music it's to say you i'll put it on youtube here now
I gotta do it again because the music's not there. Can I get it?
No, this is that's this is this is the rick and morty's ending credits. All right, that's it
That is it for tonight sam and max episode two season two
I will be back tomorrow tomorrow. We're gonna do something different
Probably should put this up right when you play
Blood fresh what's blood fresh supply. Am I gonna finish season two? Oh, yeah, definitely
Just not tomorrow tomorrow. We're gonna do something different remaster. Oh, okay
This is now a sam and max only stream. I think it's great
But tomorrow we're gonna do ms dos games
We're gonna do
uh
archive.org
Is sim earth in there? I don't know. There's like
4500 games
There's a lot to be honest. That sounds like shit. Well, you don't have to go
You don't have to watch tomorrow. You know, there's a thing in the top right corner of your screen
You can just click it
It's not that hard
But i'm gonna pee i'll be right back
And we will do the credits the good old credits after I piss so technically we'll be right back
See you very soon
Hello, why was this closed did my stream labs update it's odd
This feels incomplete
Maybe it's not which what chat is pissed. Why why is chat mad at me?
Why what do you mean chats mad? But why why why but what?
What did I do? What happened?
You know
What what what are you talking about? What are we mad about tonight lads?
It's not funny when you're mean to chat with mean to the person that mean to the one person that told me that they said
My stream was gonna be shit tomorrow
What?
That's one guy
Who was rude so I was rude back
What?
What are you talking about?
This is this is copypasta bullshit
What would jesus do he'd say hey cut it out asshole
That's what he would say. I don't think jesus would know english. He might
They're copypasting but when I said it I meant it
What?
That what are you talking about?
No, this is this is just bullshit
That one guy has a now permanent bias
Yeah, i'm i'm permanently getting t
One guy has so much power
When I look over here and I say here's what for the fourth stream in a row this week
Hey, I had this idea of playing like ms dos games
Now that's gonna suck that stream sucks
Like what like what what do you want me to do be like, yes, of course it will suck. You've got a great great idea
Good. Thank you
what
What do you what?
Don't acknowledge the one guy. I mean i'm i'm partially
Kidding when I acknowledge that
But I am gonna i'm gonna fight back
I'm a fighter
I lost in the first round when I got in that fight in high school
First round got KO'd I got the wrong thing up here
And then after that I took a vow to never ever fight anybody ever again
Back in 86
That was that was the smartest thing i've ever done. But anyways, yes, I will see you tomorrow
What games are we gonna play that's for up to you to decide
Because i'm gonna turn on smart clicks
So you'll be able to decide that I know there's a lot of things on there that I might not be able to stream
so
Gonna have to be careful with that one. You gotta get it right
But uh, let's go back to earlier. We are where are we here?
We had five dollars from the english alphabet. Thank you for the five dollars. Appreciate it
And right now uh sci ntf 2 5
community subs
Really appreciate that. Thank you right at the end here. Uh, germa k my mom get a shout out from mother's day
Her name is kim
Yeah, happy mother's day
to kim
The english alphabet's mother
There you go. Uh, happy mother's day
Happy mother's day to
You know all the mothers, right? But thank you. Thank you to jack
Jack gave 14 bucks earlier in the stream. Thank you jack adventure mf dan five community subs. Thank you dan two very
Generous back-to-back community subs. Thanks guys
Thank you sci and thank you adventure mf dan
Uh, but jack, uh jack the mac
Gave 14 bucks anyone thinks germa looks like the golden company
leader in game of thrones
uh
I feel like people say I look like a lot of people but I don't know about that one
He's a little more full in the face than I am but thank you for the
15 bucks here
Really appreciate it jack. Thank you
And now mr. Comcast coming in with three bucks
What do you got first today? Mr. Comcast?
Thanks with three dollars. Hey germa john comcast here. Just letting you know
that I saw you at
Nando's last night. I wanted to come say hi, but you were shouting profanities at the 16 year old busboy
Because kim only let you use the kids menu
I found it awkward when you dd teed the chef through table and then started harassing an elderly couple about how you kicked their ass
in the germa rumble
It got so bad that the police showed up but you escaped through the back door while carrying a box of cheeses
Why do I always have to like be?
This like insane person that's hurting people and breaking things
there's nowhere like a copy pasta here of like
I saw germa out at
Wendy's and he high-fived the guy in the window and gave him a
$100 tip and then turned around and winked at me
And in the back was a bunch of puppies that he was saving. It's never that it's always like I break shit and hurt people
Because they're telling the true stories. Yeah, there you go
That's unrealistic
You would do those things
Uh, thank you
I
zek
I zek
I x e k isaac
Thanks for the five bucks bit late, but here's five dollars for the tendies bit
Got a good laugh out of me on an otherwise depressing birthday. Well, happy birthday. That's
Well, there's the coffee foster. There it is
But thank you the five dollars
I
We kind of were just talking about a random bunch of bullshit
Hope you thought it was funny glad you did
Hope you have a better. Uh, hope you have a better birthday
Sorry to hear that. It wasn't very good. Happy birthday though
Combine thanks for the three bucks. Here you are clown
Uh honk honk honk honk, right?
I didn't even do it right
But thank you. Thank you zack or zake again for the 250
Well, pretty cool that you have a black belt in karate. I didn't know that they use hockey pads in karate, too
PS have you ever thought about doing morning streams for eu boys?
Uh after yesterday
I thought this one might have been a little like an hour or two early, but no, I just wasn't able to do it
But not really planned on it. Unfortunately, I know there's a lot of people that want it but I have to be
Ready to stream and in a streaming mood and doesn't really happen that often in the morning
And for me to do an eu friendly stream, I have to start at at least you know, nine ten o'clock in the morning
It is not
That highly energetic
in the morning
But they will happen randomly from time to time like you see them already a couple times
Uh, thank you ranzor for the three bucks. No messages. Just three dollars. Thank you ranzor
Bimber ten. Thanks for the five dollars. Hey jeremy. I would eat my toes if you played no one lives forever, too
A spy in harm's way. It's a classic game that I think you would love it'd be entertaining to watch
um
I've never heard of it
But I admit maybe if I think it's something that's fun and worth streaming
I don't know. We had a lot of feet on stream today
Yeah, there was
German lied about taco bell. Thanks for the 250 mega mind for germa rumble
Good old mega mind
No mega minds
I'll get in trouble. Somebody will sue me. You never played it. It's
Look at the tricycle mine level
Bought 50 from bala koala earlier. Thank you so much bala koala
We touched upon it already, but that's a lot. Thank you
Ferotian weapon. Thanks for the 250 since the easter island heads aren't paying up. I will in their stead. Happy friday. Happy friday
Thank you. Thank you
C4g
Thanks to 250. I don't know what message you include. So here's a picture of my cat. Let's see that. Oh, that's a great cat
What's on the collar? Is it a flower?
That's a pretty great cat
Uh, somebody said you ever just sniff your monitor. No never
that was um earlier it was a bit message, but I
I've never done that before
Freudian weapon. Thanks for the 250 don't listen to the rude guys. Your streams are always fun
I'm gonna fight back
No, I know people were fucking around 95 percent of the time
But i'm yeah, i'm dead if we're gonna if we're gonna have a back and forth scenario here. I'm gonna fight back
You can hear him flex. You just like fucking muscles are just exploding
I'm serious
Chat rumble
You want to hear me flex?
Just popped up
Try it again
Oh
That one that one was that one hit the ceiling
Most of the time you guys realize that
Whenever somebody if I say something where i'm like, oh fucking ray, what the fuck fuck you
i'm usually just fucking around
we have all kinds of
in
channel kind of back and forth
that
are
Fun, right?
But i'm i'm what you what do you want me to say?
I I can't like pretend
You hurt my feelings. What about my feelings?
You you took it too far
What?
I spent the whole last 10 minutes of the stream. I mean people tell me how stupid I was
How dumb of a person I am
That was that was like the last 20 minutes of that was like actually the about six hours of the stream
So wait, i'm allowed to take the harassment here
huh
When I say one thing
In like a joking manner all of a sudden i'm like the joker from batman
I get to be the one guy sometimes come on
You gotta give me a little bit. I like you gotta give me a little bit of slack
We fuck around here a lot but half the shit that is said in this stream would get you banned somewhere else
And you know it come on. So we have a pretty light atmosphere here
I say a lot of shit and get banned for it be the bigger person in any room
Oh, I get it. See? All right. So, all right. All right. Look at that. Look it's being spanned right now
Look, do you see this? You see like what?
What that shit's
Uh, and i'm at zero we're in the middle of talking about like shit talking
And I look over and I see a shit talk
Coffee pasta you guys are on point. I'll give you that joke was so good. It fucking killed him
But anyways, let us move on the coffee pasta is so elaborate because
People can come up with some crazy shit
But we had let's uh, almost at the end here. We had ten dollars from all mu for thank you all mu
Hey, germa was out with my girlfriend the other night at a bar. We were pleasantly surprised to see you
Kim and shito there, but you seemed a little off
I saw that you ordered enough pbr to make yourself almost pass out and even be sick
we didn't want to go up and say anything because we saw shito and kim carrying you home as you stumbled and
a drunk fit
I just want to ask what's the deal with you lying so much. I really want you to be a better person
Thank you for the ten dollars. I appreciate i'm gonna i'm drinking pbr tomorrow
Mark my words, I will drink that gross liquid
Germa lied about taco bell. Thanks for the 250
I saw germa out at a wendy's he high-fived the cashier and then winked at me
He was super nice to everyone right up until he pulled his pants down and shit on the floor
Son of jenova, thanks for the three dollars. Hi. I love you. Watch this, please
It's probably what's gonna happen to you tomorrow
Hey, don't tell him penis
I'm not allowed to do that. Come on
Nobody said you can't
It probably is what's gonna happen, but i'll be i'll be on top of it. Don't worry
I'm gonna flex my fucking tiny muscles
Why are you so mean to us? I'm not i'm not what?
I know this is just a die. No, everyone just fucking with me now
Where's the sour place? Come on. I was there it is. That's what I was waiting for
Thank you, though. I will be on top of it. Don't worry. Hey, uh shinoda. Thanks for the 250
Hey germa, are you going to join the vine sauce charity stream?
It'd be good time for vine wrestle versus germa rumble with joe
I don't know
That's a really good question
i'll have to
I don't really have an answer for you
But it's a great charity. They do awesome stuff
They do it every year, right? So I mean, I maybe we'll see I I can't give you an answer
I don't want to tell you that's gonna happen and then it doesn't right so
But thank you for the 250 definitely something to look into right?
Mr. Comcast. Thanks for the three dollars and
Let's run the credits on stream
We had a lot of community subs today
Like at least 20 to 30 probably community subs. Thank you guys
And why don't we run them here they come all the new subs all the other subs. You guys are awesome
Thank you so much
Reload the page the fix the music. I hear that all the time. I don't I don't
I've never picked up on that
Maybe it's when the internet kicks out and it calls it to fuck up. That's weird
But thank you everybody
German lied about minecraft vr. There's the original one original
Minecraft vr lie
But it did play
Uh, mr. Comcast go thank you. Thanks for three dollars. Comcast a germ of john comcast
You're just letting you know that I saw you last night six flags
Okay
You were screaming and shouting at the 16 year old ride attendant for not letting you on the teacups because you were under the height limit
Found it awkward when you didn't
When you ddt the park supervisor threw a hot dog stand and stole some candy off a five-year-old child that was sitting on a park bench
It got so bad that police showed up, but you stole a captain crunch mascot outfit and escaped
I'm glad I got away
In this fake story, it's not real but I can the good thing I hit manned out of there in the captain crunched uniform
Finally the sand witch thank you the sandwich for 250
German I want to say that I hope you know that at least 98 percent of us love you and we know that you're messing around
Have a good night. Thanks for helping me get through the semester with your kind personality
I know i'm messing around but people think i'm not messing around and then they get mad at me for messing around
But then people mess around with me all the time then like uh, it's a it's a circle. I gotta close
I don't think anyone actually gets mad people do though. They do
We can't you can't tell that we're joking is easy. Yeah, but you can you can tell I know
Shit is just a joke and I know when people are actually irritated about something
Start to tell if someone is angry through text. Yeah, but you can
You can tell
I ban them. No, you don't get banned in this channel for like making fun of the streamer
That's what I was referring to
There are a lot of scenarios where it you
Talk shit to the person streaming. They'll just be like bye
We have like a joke kind of here about it
But the streamer can't get banned for making fun of the chat. No because you're in this this is they're in this is the streamer's house
You're in my house. You're in my house
He's gonna get evicted. No one's getting evicted
Refusing to show Otto's feet
You've seen him already. You've seen it already
But finally before the stream ends, I got those tendies with the honey mustard sauce good
I hope it's fucking delish
As always, thanks for watching everybody. See you tomorrow
Where's your restroom? I don't have one
We pee outside
That was a lot of fun. I'd say I've access great. It's I've had a lot of fun tonight
Can you do you crack me up little buddy as Elmo Thanos doing a Sam impression?
I don't think I can do that
Am I gonna do season three? I I don't know
I don't know once season two is over. I'll see if I'd want to keep going
After season two, I might stop salmon max for a little while just to do some other things
Because it's been taken up. Um
You know at least one or two streams a week the last couple weeks have been
Sam and max so maybe i'll put it uh in the
On the shelf for a few weeks
But we're gonna do at least season two completely
And we'll see after that we'll go from there
I'll see you tomorrow
Have a wonderful rest of your night
good night
Goodbye, and i'm gonna feed everybody in stream legends. Hope you're ready
Take care everybody. See you real soon
Like tomorrow
Good night guys
Bye. Bye