Is that somebody bat-chested my title?
You don't like LeBron dunking?
Multi versus open beta?
Let's go!
That's what you're gonna, that's what I'm gonna be doing, I'll tell ya.
Hehehehe.
Alright, let me open the game.
Okay, lookin' good.
I'm so excited to play it!
You need some LeBron tips?
Nn, may, I don't know, maybe.
I've been playing a lot off stream, so...
I have to be honest with you. Let me be honest.
Alright, one more second, we'll get started.
I need to pee too, yeah. I'm gonna piss. You're back.
Okay. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
See? Oh, oops.
That's not the right game. Why is this still open?
Oh, because I never closed it.
Let's go. Can I get some Let's Freakin' Go in the chat, please?
Can I get a few Let's Freakin' Go in the chat, please?
Oh, we're gonna eff here for a second.
Yeah, don't worry. We are effing.
Currently, it's okay. I know, I know.
It's, uh, don't worry. It's gonna be fine.
I'm ready to relax.
First of all, let me tell ya, ladies and gentlemen...
Multiverses is currently in open beta.
You can go get it right now.
It's on everything. And you know what else is cool?
It's cross-platform.
You can play it on your Xbox.
You can play it on your Steam.
You can play- you- go do it wherever you want.
I've been playing LeBron.
You're gonna see some LeBron gameplay here.
Loud. I'll fix it. I don't want it to be too loud.
This is a sponsored segment of the stream, yes.
And it's fucking awesome.
Okay, hold on.
I gotta get it correct.
You guys are gonna be surprised at just how well I'm gonna be playing today.
And that, you know, obviously people think like,
Oh my god, Jerma sucks, right? Right?
That's fine. Keep in mind, though. I've been playing.
Let's go! Alright, so yeah.
If you- let's do some 1v1s.
To warm up a little. And take a look.
LeBron James is in the game.
And he's fun as fuck.
I've already played it. I've- I- look.
I've been messing around in the Xbox version.
And I'm ready. LeBron James
has this dunk move that you
just need to touch somebody with it.
And it's over. Let's fucking kick some ass.
You ready? Thank you, obviously Warner Bros.
for sponsoring the stream.
I mean, I love this game. I genuinely do.
You guys all know that. You already know that at this point.
You're gonna blame your controller now.
No, watch this. Watch- I'll show you in the lab.
It's so surreal.
Watch this. Oh, what's that? Oh, excuse me.
Okay, whatever. I'll show you- I'll show you how you play.
You're gonna blame chat?
Yeah, I'm level one.
But we'll go up.
We'll go up.
Instant loss incoming.
Well, now I gave myself an opportunity
for failure, which was a bad idea.
Here we go.
Don't get in my head already. I haven't even started playing.
Don't get in my head.
Let's go. Oh, what's that?
Oh, excuse me. Oh, get dunked on.
That's what I'm talking about.
That move is sick. Good dodge.
It's alright.
Come on.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, easy.
Oh, you piece of sh-
Relax.
Bad, bad move.
Damn it.
It's alright, it's alright. It's a warm-up.
It's a warm-up, it's a warm-up, it's a warm-up.
It's alright, it's a warm-up. It's a warm-up.
I haven't played, it's a warm-up.
I fucked up in that first part.
again again again let's go you get beat by bugs bugs is awesome what are you talking about
okay i thought you were practicing no this isn't a bot this is a person that's copium it's match
number one out of like 60 today i'm gonna be fine we're going lebron again game time baby i gotta
just like get the i gotta like shake it out of me did you see though did you see how good i was
playing i was through up when's rick and morty coming out i don't know i have no idea i just
know what's here now i don't know what any other characters that could be in the game
i don't have any perks look i gotta just get it out of my system look here we go
all right let's go prepare yourself yeah it's open beta you can literally go get it right now
open beta progress stays by the way all your progress stays by the way all right let's go
no more fucking around what are you doing what are you doing what are you all right you can get
good i'll get get me to 19 get me to 19 go on give me a 19 that's all right a little bit
a bit more no no no get that get that shit out of here get that shit out of here no excuse me
get that shit out of here this is going to be x it's going to be extra damage it's going to be
more than 19 all right game on literally game on i didn't want to do that move what the fuck
what the fuck point red team
fuck you what are you talking about
excuse me tell me what you think what the fuck just happened there huh i was i was on top of bugs and
did my doubt excuse me i was on top i was i was the one on top that was a good warm-up don't run
that clip back i'm up top and i go down and he goes down and i'm the one that goes down all right
let's go no time like the present it's okay maybe video games aren't your thing quiet you snooze
you lose nobody said mario tennis meltdown incoming i'm not look i finally got my first perk no all
right we're gonna we that was a warm-up i had i gotta get look i gotta get my blood pumping
when does the beta end that's a really good question i don't i don't know it's just an open
beta now i wonder what they'll do i think it's going through august right we'll find out all
right is what we've been trained i didn't want to do that move i need that ball oh my god just hit
the person oh it's not the move i wanted to do finally jesus i need that ball you're so
just useless without it in your hand i knew you were gonna do that night just pull together
didn't want to do that move that's it that's it that's not it oh damn it that's it
you cannot escape that's it
stupid oh my god oh it's so hard
shit that was a good match that was a good match good match good match we'll do it again
there's a lot of whiffs yeah i think with lebron is if you if you don't hit the basketball
you lose that's just the way it is but i like the way he plays it's funny why are you throwing
throwing i came back i was down by 80 points i came back i was down by 80 points i came back
just old man reactions do the air neutral more with uh with or without the ball from one to ten
how do you rate yourself as a gamer eight and a half super mario two dark souls games eight
and then it averages out after that oh my god i'm getting fucking annihilated oh my god i can't
even play the game how do i let him do that and does that move not go through anything
i feel like it doesn't that move doesn't go through anything
holy shit i can't get i can't get two out here jesus okay maybe it's not lebron
holy shit this guy's level one it doesn't make any sense it's this guy level one shaggy
i still would have no way that's not the level one shaggy that's a level 60 shaggy all right
we're gonna go back to bugs he was level 14 oh i thought he was level one i thought he was level
one okay back to bugs for a little while if you say so can you wish my dog a happy birthday we're
oh that's horrible happy birthday i'm sorry you're going through that to your dog you have to use an
s tier character everybody else is how much have you spent on skins i don't want to talk about it
uh none it's so nice he keeps letting his opponents win stop it i'm gonna just wait watch this one
here watch this one here watch this one here check this one out that is the question god damn it wrong
way sorry yes yes good fight good fight good fight good fight good fight very good fight
don't talk about how bad my lebron is ever again well you can because it was not very good
i feel like it just went cross-eyed into the camera did i go cross-eyed don't ever play lebron ever
again i like lebron it's in my title lebron's fun with the projectile but if you miss the ball you're
just you're just gonna lose i just gotta not miss the ball remember that was their first game you
don't know that dude you went green and your eyes bugged out wait what like the hulk how to train
your perks all right oh right you can buy ones can't you this one's good 20 reduction to ground
and ball bounce velocity all right let's go i got money four percent reduced incoming damage
15 percent increase base knockback influence that's kind of big that's actually really big
you should wear lebron jersey while you play as lebron yeah but if i'm gonna get destroyed i
can't uh air acceleration a little more offense i think that's fine for now that's cool though you
can do that all right this is what i get at level 10 that's kind of a big deal don't disappoint i
gotta try a few more games let me try lebron again we'll go in teams i'm gonna try lebron again i'm
telling you he's fun he's funny he's just kind of hard to play what's up doc no i voted already
this is teams this is gonna i'll be all right all right jake is really good projectile speed all
right let's go come on i'm telling you i know how to play lebron i promise that's a different
character whatever that's finn what i thought jake and finn from adventure time what's this
all right he's gonna eat the basketball isn't it a bunch it's gonna be bad jake the human and
in the dog i know all right here we go i'm going for it and we're gonna it's gonna be a good match
check it out i promise i promise it's gonna be a good match don't flip these cats in the bag
i've already fucked it up i must have spilled off the fucking stage what how did he eat me what's
going on here what just happened not bad that's how you drink whoa i went across the map in a
second something's going on here uh something's going on here what the hit that taz no where are
we we did it that was messy but we did it okay nice job good fight good fight continue
i got the kills that's all that matters all that matters is the uh the number at top
nothing else does choose your character hey dude just tuning in is this guy pro lebron
what's up doc you tested me today and i understand has his spin is op i think they nerfed it they uh
they made it way way less powerful in the last batch it's still really good but not as nearly
as good as it was it seems like they're really on top of patching the game every week or two
so that's good that's good every uh every week or two i see a new patch with nerfs and buffs and
stuff so it's good they're gonna make it a cool down move that makes sense it's only been one
week it's a lot of fun though be really honest with me how many you guys have ones in the chat
if you guys have actually downloaded this and went like this on the couch fuck it's good
wait be honest actually be honest that's what i did
oh all right oh my goodness i just got absolutely double teamed that move has no priority though
i mean i i get why it's so powerful but you got to catch people really off guard with it
you can pass the ball to your teammate too which is really cool oops i didn't want to do that
all right oh my god i thought it was over
i tried my hardest it's all right jump into it shit
oh you got so lucky there you go sir remember because you went in a fight against a grizzly bear
yep i think so when it just feels right i think enough like
you know like the every beat-em-up sound you've ever heard if the bear comes up with the claws
all i have to do is just go go go go go go go go go and i'll be able to knock him down
guys i would die instantly i would die in one hit the bear would swipe me across the face and my
face would come off of course i can't fight a bear i think i'm kidding it's a joke i would
get up with my hands like this and then my whole head would be gone but you can dodge an axe yeah
an axe is not a grizzly bear there of axe is not a a person has to swing the axe all right i want
to do all right lebron or or bugs you want to see more lebron gameplay he's so fun to play he
really is i just not very good with them lebron means you'll lose i just wanted to enroll lebron
on the team i'll do lebron again no time like the present tom and jerry i tried to play tom and jerry
they were kind of weird they remind me the ice climbers but you need to pay attention essentially
to both ice climbers at the same time it's like both it's like if you put the ice climbers away
from each other and they both have different moves it's uh if my brain just has trouble doing it
they're cool though should you purchase multiverses well multiverses is free an open beta right now
which by the way you have a moment or two this is a sponsored stream for multiverses
the game is uh is very good i don't need to tell you that twice it's currently an open beta cross
platform cross progression all that good stuff you know you understand come on you have their
drops i don't think there's any drops right now they did that a couple weeks ago rain dog is cute
i tried to play rain dog a little bit i still don't understand how it works all right i'm warming up
i'm getting into it i'm warming up we'll go back to one of you ones in a minute
batman got nerfed too right batman's uh batarang got nerfed oh that thing is weird oh how did you
get under that go over it i mean we're getting beat pretty bad here got some payback to a name
did i hit him what it's not good it's not good we're in trouble
we got destroyed
did my mic just break i feel like my microphone just turned off apologize to your teammate
hey i thought we were doing okay in the second half there it's okay we got it we got it we got
it all right we're going back i'm going back let me claim some of these uh i have some prizes
right oh prizes gold and oh i definitely want to put that on that okay this is when somebody gets
uh ringed out don't ever play lebron again how are you supposed to get better at something if
you don't do it that one's cool i yeah i definitely want this one what's my banner
should i do deluxe founder so people but then people will think i'm like good at the game or
something that's fine okay wait what about announcer what should i have for announcer
i i can afford it i do lebron oh okay i thought it was 700 all right let's go taz would be funny
too i think too okay let's do it here comes the heat okay hey taz i'll buy taz and maybe use it
later what does taz sound like what was it again last week people said that taz doesn't talk
there he is talking here comes the heat all right we're gonna do lebron first
here comes the heat is that all he says i'm gonna laugh so hard if that's if that's it you know
what you're doing please say here comes the heat again can we go to the next thing i hope so look
he's so look he's so theoretically fun you know what i mean he's so theoretically fun here comes
the heat that's that's pretty funny he's theoretically really fun show him what we got
i'm probably gonna get destroyed here again all right i'm telling you right now if you're
if you're voting and you're betting on me right now don't i'm gonna try i don't eat tom and jerry
he's got to get rid of uh jerry let's settle this on the court god he's got no priority come on man
didn't want to do that fucking move no i didn't want to do that not that way
hey we're good we're good good good match good match was there ever any doubt did you just drown
i just like came up with air from the water here comes the heat no that was like my my brain just
got scrambled more lebron let's go see the only thing that was missing was they needed to be
another me superimposed at half transparency looking around going right what do you mean
no show them what we got how do you guys know you don't understand what i'm talking about
get on that editors you don't you don't tell the editors what to do all right let's go like
this control smells you and the king's court now yeah listen get me the fuck away from you
oh my god i can't even do a single god darn move oh my god
like a charm oh you can't guard me too late excuse me the fucking computer
huh oh my god dude i can't do any moves without the basketball
holy shit man you gotta be fucking kidding me oh my god i know i this isn't an episode of the
office i don't know why i keep like going looking into the camera it's like what the fuck you know
never mind accidental skill here comes the heat all right no more lebron for now let's do a new
character let's do bug prepare for my dectifying exploits hey you technically lost sorry everyone
thought i was getting destroyed i was getting absolutely annihilated that round but you bet on
the wrong card there sorry all right i promise after two matches with bugs i will play another
character that i haven't played before you so badly want to be jim from the office i've seen
maybe four episodes of the office total i've never seen that show in fact i just watched a
full episode of the office one day when ed helms was the guy that was in charge of everything and
i was like okay this is one full episode i watched that was a mistake i think the problem that i
have with the office is hold on steven universe's theme song is here turn it up wait let me turn it
up let me turn it up don't hit me yet let me turn up the sound don't hurt me yet i want to turn the
volume up all right we're good we're good we're go go go go go go go go go fight fight fight fight
what the fuck this hair over my fucking mouth i swear to god look can you see that why did
so much hair stick in my mouth it doesn't make any sense this like i like i went to the barber
and they cut the hair in my mouth i swear to god i have to i have to take a break after this
and spit it out okay that was a major fucking distraction how would it this many hairs in the
fucking room it doesn't even make any sense all right this one doesn't count this one doesn't count
actually
all right if i didn't have a handful of hair in my mouth and take a hundred points of damage in the
first 30 seconds i would have been way more closer somebody somebody watch what happened
how did six hairs get in my mouth how is it possible what did i do did i put my hand in my mouth
when did my fingers go in my mouth ever what happened does anybody know what happened
did i go like did i like put my fingers in my mouth when that never happened what happens
i yeah i turned the volume up but why would that put hair in my mouth here comes the heat
let's go let's get it go i don't get it new character i will i promise you're playing the
worst character in the game well hey lebron's not been up that long you don't know that yet
it was on the chapstick wasn't it yep sure was because this is covered in hair does that mean
it was just sitting on my lip the whole time until i like went like this show them what we got you
put the chapstick in your armpit by the way multiverses an open beta right now go get it
the game is phenomenal it's actually the best fighting game i've played in a long time i don't
even like fighting games i really don't i genuinely like this game i've been playing it like a
week while i was sick i gen it's a great game it's this is a sponsored stream let's go you
want to throw the ball that way you dodged that perfectly nice job you where's my ball what's
going on what the hell's happening it's like i have a ball in my hand why am i not using it
what what happened what where's my fucking ball um something wrong with that
that
don't say this guy sucks you only been here for five minutes you don't know you haven't seen my
bug's bunny why are you moving like you're on adderall i don't know because i what do you mean
here comes the heat what are you talking about now we talk time that person up for 15 minutes
total what do you use for shampoo i use uh actually it's changed recently what's it it's
got shea butter in it what's it called i don't remember what everyone has shea butter in it
that's the one new character i need to level up lebron james show them what we got
why are you the xbox players so bad they're not most of the i i was playing on xbox and
they were really good all right i'm going in for this one i'm gonna be quiet i'm not gonna do any
like youtuber reactions where i go like i'm just gonna play let's go let's i'll show it to you let's
go this won't last long don't do that
all right all right all right we got this what do you have for breakfast green tea
and a burrito that wasn't bad i think that was a good match here comes the heat all right i got i'm
gonna have to stick with lebron for this one right game time baby is it a breakfast burrito
it was a made-up burrito because i didn't have one show them what we got
i had a piece of bread that was some butter coffee and half of an avocado
you didn't know that it bounces back oh jake is so fucking good
oh my god i almost just caught him shake it up we only get stuck jake esther i feel like he should
be all of jake's moves are like a hundred feet around him
that's an easy 30k well don't bet against me again i'll tell you here comes the heat
operation rabbit begin which which character should you pick uh whoever you whatever tv show
you like the most because that's how you get the power to play well see if you play as a
character which tv show you don't like you don't care if you win or lose but if you if it's a tv
show you really like you want bugs bunny to win because you love the looney tunes that's why i
always win with buggy's money all right let's go you're about to have a bad head what's going on
that's weird god damn it
perfect plan the perfect plan damn it these moves are all mine god damn it
oh what a battle what a battle
you don't why did that happen three times
good fight good fight excellent battle excellent battle excellent battle
again just said someone just wrote in all lowercase steven universe fucking sucks
okay have you ever seen the show have you ever seen that television show
you probably haven't even seen it here comes the heat let's go i don't even know what he does
excuse me he's fucking cracked up are you serious is he what where is he on the tier list you know
who cares about tier lists actually at least so far i feel like a lot of characters are viable
that's what it feels like show them what we got except the characters i play right i play i play
them because they're lower tier characters and that's why i lose like half the games
all right let's go oh and he eats cookies dude you can skateboard don't get too greedy here
and hit somebody man wait have a shield what's going on with the internet
like this okay i'm thinking it's a party who's in continue
he's actually kind of fun i think he's pretty good let me go look at the uh
hold on everybody relax let me go into the um lab put on tabs if i put on tabs we're gonna lose
here comes the heat and that's i don't know if i want to do that all right one more lebron
excellent choice is your is your username the name of your persona
here comes the heat that's a good one actually good one all right we got a mirror here lebron
versus lebron no complaining this time is just who's the better lebron that's all that matters
right now show them what we got okay let's go back on steven universe all right uh
just like on tv come on fucking hit him oh my god dude spin spin spin all right
don't fucking tilt here just fucking wait come on easy too oh that would have been it
i told you we got this that was tricky that was tricky i got a couple of lucky uh bounces
with the ball you look really waxy today okay this game is so gosh darn fun we kind of we got
to do lebron lebron again right that worked pretty much our work yeah i got this can you do mouse
and keyboard i think you can but i would not recommend it at all show them what we got i
will learn a new character after this i will all right this is a good player i gotta be careful
let's play good play good play
oh careful oh that was a bad move oh come on we got this goodbye good fight good fight good match
are you using a fight stick no hey to a fellow lebron player good match see i just needed to
warm up a little every time you talk i grow more warts on my body sounds like a problem that you i
don't know what are you doing go to the doctor that's got nothing to do with me all right i
promise one more game with lebron and that's it and then i'm gonna go in the lab with another
character and it'll be chat's choice i promise i promise it'll be done after this 100 promise
here comes the heat stop giving that guy warts so is it is it syllables is it the my human voice
with syllables because in that case good luck they're all over your whole body now
all right let's go hope we all meet under better circumstances someday
i have not very much experience playing against superman i'll be honest
you can't guard me wrong way i hate when that happens it's so annoying hello what the hell is
that oh god we got this his hands are sweaty yes they are very sweaty superman seems fun
have you ever watched adventure time oh yeah it was on cartoon ever call the time
i was a fan i thought it was a good show time like the present that sounded dry what do you mean like
name your favorite adventure time episode um one where they have to go uh show them what we got
there's a dungeon they have to go through that lemon grab put them in or lemon grab was there
first and they get to the end of the dungeon um i did honestly i just have flashes of animated
sequences from that show i don't remember episodes three two good job good job shit
i could do this all night try me
yes drink some water i told you we got this this stage is broken for lebron yeah it is
just throwing the ball and not even caring about getting it back this is this is the lebron stage
without a doubt without a doubt also the um the scooby-doo stage is really good for lebron too
all right new character i will do a new character i promise i will here we go by the way multiverses
is in open beta right now and go get it steam xbox wait what is this here comes the heat
yeah thanks one of brothers again for sponsoring the stream and honestly at this is i'm really
happy because i actually genuinely love this game i think it's awesome i am so happy to be playing
this game because it's very good all right who do you who do you want to see me play let's put it
out there all right i'll get let's do a poll i'll give you guys a top four who i would actually
like to learn uh belma superman bin or batman let's get a poll up who do you want me to play
with i will unlock any of them in the meantime yeah i'll put the uh announcer on oh what's this
a sticker i can't even see who's winning who's winning i love this song in particular you know
the music in this game especially the main menu it reminds me of being at like six flags right and
you hear that music just playing everywhere you get a corn dog it feels very amusement parkish
i love it i feel like i'm at the in the line for the superman ride you know what i mean
i love it let's get a new emote wonder woman weightlifting all right i've got an 80 recent
win rate this is pretty good i'm only two million one hundred eighty nine thousand look at your
bugs bunny rank how do you do that all right because it looks like it's velma how do i see
the one v one all right let's take velma into the lab all right so velma's got a couple of cool
moves her basic attack is ranged so you have to target somebody and then you can just kind of pop
pop pop pop and then that's on cooldown all right let's see velma shouts a word bubble projectile
that seeks out her ally if the bubble hits any fighter ally or enemy they become targeted and
additional bubbles will lock on to their target their location allies who become targeted will
also briefly gain hastened all right so that's a support move so it's a heal all right so the
ammo which is replenished itself uh side x is a combo of quips yeah that move is good too this
one here that's what that could that i honestly think that's the best uh combo in the game it's
got such insane range look at the range on this like that's insane you can't get away from this
it takes a long time to charge up that shit so i'm not going to do it too much okay what about
down yeah this is the whack okay and the idea bubble you know what you really can do to screw
with somebody so you get them in the air and then just start throwing these out there and
just pop pop pop pop boom okay cool i like the combos what about the air moves whoa that's pretty
good that's just okay cool this one's like a dive it's got a lot of bounce to it and you can charge
this too that is a stuff move if you got somebody going around the corner here and you just stuff
right there okay what about specials so that i've said because you got to collect these things right
what does it do motivational speech beam projectile that repeatedly hits enemies and heals allies all
right the final hit of the beam applies targeted if the final hit lands on an ally it will fire
an additional beam okay or if it hits the full stack they get weakened okay you can aim the beam
up or down so it's just like a okay is this one too was this okay here we go yep is there a cool
down on that there is no cool down on that so dude all right target watch this well i screwed it up
you know what i mean that's i think that'd be pretty cool uh cool combo maybe not flashlight
okay cool so that's what that does you carry them over to the edge allies can hop into the arms to
increasing attack power all right toxic goop on the ground and jumps upward enemies standing in
the goop will receive continuous stacks of ice all right or it's you snap a picture
melma snaps a picture downward with a camera that sends her and enemies upward breaking armor applies
weak really that seems what's the range on it all right that seems insane that's a kill move
okay so that throws ice on the ground if you don't if you're not in the air so that i gotta
remember that down is spread the knowledge projectile that homes over an ally you get
educated if the book hits them reducing the duration of their cooldowns okay so when everything's on
cooldown you just kind of throw the book down all right i think i'm ready give it a try i think i'm
good to go wait is there anything else to look at all right during the match evidence will appear
and some of velma's moves spawn evidence so you can pick it up you fill the evidence meter so when
the meter is full velma can call a police car the police will seek out the nearest enemy disable
them and drive off the map and do it do this while crouching how do you activate that though
that seems insane all right let's do it do some velma gameplay she calls the cops yeah we'll do
one v one here comes the heat i forgot about taz come on pick character there's velma's here
also again if you play the game all your progress is kept through open beta stop doing your funny
voice i didn't do anything okay let's see if i can make anything happen here headphones going in
gaming time gaming time oh shit i forgot i had that move what the fuck are you going all right
let's go what the fuck is happening why can't i leave the stage i can't get off the stage man
i almost got him i think i almost got him all right seriously what the hell is going on
what's actually happening why do i have so much dude you could go buy a boat with the amount of
money you have right now jump off i wanted to get to a thousand and i'll jump off what you can't go
more than a thousand what we good i think that was a little um out of the ordinary i don't think that
one counts i don't think that's possible okay come on pick character i don't have enough the
king now sure i'll take it what do you mean votes immediately started to go to no after you picked
lebron fine let him do it let him vote that way that's fine let him vote that way the believers
oh he didn't even dodge he didn't even dodge what was that
should have shut up oh my god vin you are fucking disgusting dude he could just what the hell
you can block that shit oh no you know it's wicked funny when i play a game like this happened in
smash brothers 2 whenever i played against somebody that like destroyed me and i thought
was like potentially powerful character it made me hate their fucking tv show or their game this
happened in smash too i would get like dominated by an olomar and i'd be like fuck that game that
game sucks or it even likes that game it would make me genuinely not like the media that it came
from so right now i like am never watching adventure time ever i'm gonna skip it every time it's on tv
come on pick character prepare for my dectifying exploits it's so good i know but you know what i
mean okay if if i was getting destroyed by a bug's bunny i'd be like loony tunes i'm watching that
show but see all right here we go all right this is this is a jake and is this going to solidify
the bow i'm never going to watch adventure time because of this oh shit i completely forgot i was
going to go get a bunch of big carrots and every time i won with bugs i was going to take a huge
bite of a big carrot that was a mistake i fucked up i completely forgot to go to the grocery store
and get it where did that go all right okay come on man how many goddamn moves do you have
fuck this show i've never watched this on netflix what i'm a show nobody fucking watches
i'm kidding it's a great show
game time baby yeah i'm it's a great television show you're gonna do an apology video i actually
do like adventure time it's just okay so i could tell you if i play play play a fighting game and
i get destroyed it makes me hate that piece of media you need to apologize to finn and jake
directly start you're gonna hate batman no i don't hate batman uh-oh well it depends how badly do i
get beaten this match we'll find out that cave security system must be compromised
oh shit that was so stupid that was so stupid i did not expect him to get hit by the goddamn ball
we're good we're good we're good we're good we're good we're good we're good
fucking batman superman's way cooler anyways god damn it my my mind's not in the game
it's coming in hot my head wasn't in the game my head was not in the game
i made a lot of mistakes at the end there
i'm here to fight for truth and justice what he sounds like was that superman talking was that
who was that all right i thought i thought that was batman talking i was like that's not the same
voice i don't know why i thought that was batman i was like that's he doesn't start time okay now
the voice is completely makes sense i just i don't know why batman was the one talking and
i'm like this doesn't really sound like me i'll beat you without oh they actually talk shit to each
other
should have gone up should have gone up what an idiot oh what a colossal fucking battle what a
colossal battle shit what the hell is going on here ah i could have went down stop talking
shit to me feel like you're in my chat that was your character i whatever i keep thinking it's
batman this is a fun game i'm telling you i'm so sweaty superman's really tanky very heavy
come on pick character let's do it again let's all fight fair and this should be fun how come you
look like you made it a soap i don't know i don't know do i it's kind of weird i gotta stop okay my
biggest problem with these games is panic dodging i get up there we get in the air and i just go oh
my god oh my god oh my god and i gotta stop doing that the panic dodges are what's getting me killed
are you gonna play anything else tonight probably not probably not we'll come back with uh we'll
come back with sorcery in a couple days maybe on uh monday i completely forgot i played the hitman
map that's weird walked away stay back oh i thought i got him really powerful actually powerful the
move his moves just hit so hard with those powers shaggy someone could get hurt play again
go ahead how come you went live when i went to the movies
because we were trying to get a stream in before you showed up
that was rude i'm just messing around of course i want everyone that's here to be here
it's me making a joke as long as i'm standing you can count on me oh when's green okay green
screen part two movie night is going to be on next weekend uh we're probably going to go on
friday or saturday so the fifth the sixth right let me see check the date it'll be the fifth of
the sixth we'll come back with another probably one to 200 videos gonna be insane and then sorcery
we'll do some more of uh kare that'll be on monday maybe we'll do monday tuesday well maybe we'll do
monday tuesday friday or monday tuesday saturday that makes sense to me you have a face filter on
no i've not seen a harley quinn in a long time
oh almost i'm goner i'm a goner
oh shit nice dodge damn i got outplayed too i really did i actually got outplayed that whole
entire game i just got a couple of uh good smashes that's it for someone without powers
you still pack quite the punch okay come on pick character he seems like he's pre-recorded
we'll do taz didn't i own taz did i not own taz before i have level three here comes the heat
oh is the free character rotation right that makes sense i think you might be stupid enough
to be a taz main show him what we got funny guy taz is low tier now i don't think so
how did i fuck that up holy shit what happened i told you we got this that was ridiculous what
happened just went flying that was insane i don't think i did that much damage dude it's you know
what it's fun to sit here and just play a video game and just try to play it well i feel like it's
been forever since i've tried to do this i feel like it's been ages since i've cared to play a
game and try to play it well does that make sense does anybody feel that way or am i just getting
old here comes the heat elden ring yeah i mean multiplayer though playing against somebody else
i'll do it again i'm not gonna play this game competitively ever i never will but i can't wait
to watch the people that do especially the teams there's no way they're not going to do some kind
of interesting stuff with the game right there's no way i'm looking forward to watching this game
oh all right i hope it's successful it's really great game i do too i hope it's successful as
well i mean it's gonna come down to how much support the game has in the next you know six
to twelve months looks like it has a lot i mean wasn't this one of the most played fighting games
ever on steam isn't i've never seen this like a screenshot am i wrong
all right all right
good combo good combo oh you're almost a snack you're almost the turkey turkey
oh shit i'm almost a turkey we got this and the turkey attack nope you can just run around
tasmanian andy i thought that was a good match i did i thought that was a good fight
here comes the heat adventure time i move around a lot i do i know when i play games like this i have
to move around it's the game the game is inside of me batman feels low tier to me is that wrong
to say like batman doesn't have very many moves doesn't feel high tier am i wrong he has trouble
killing at least in one v ones show them what we got batman is top you are ass you don't even
want you to give the screen turned off i think you're the toughest i've gone up against i try
to get it
i got i was getting juggled a lot too is there a campaign mode i don't think there is a campaign
mode nothing i'm aware of prepare for my debt defying exploits how can we always look so upset
i mean i i'm walking in gamer wise is that what it is you know holly said this to me too
she's like no seriously like if you watch you play a game that you're really really focusing on
it looks like you're going to headbutt the screen i'm just like what i just sit there like i have to
focus why is your chat so weird shall we dance i don't think they're that weird i mean some of
them are i wanted it so bad press the button we're even man we're even we both want the same
thing man it's not gonna happen to either one of us damn oh i'm in trouble i'm in trouble i'm in
trouble oh i almost got it no no no no no no no no that was a huge hitbox yeah it was
i'm having more fun watching you hop around in your seat i get i get really into this
shit man i'm sorry i really just do but it feels it feels good to play fighting games always play
like such ass online it's just i've never even cared i've never cared to even play one because
i'll jump into online and it's like why would i ever do this this sucks it doesn't feel like
that this game does not feel like that at all it just doesn't i have to be up front let's be
honest i'm here to defend justice the netcode yeah it's really hard to do it i mean look there's
been some times where the game's been a little laggy teleporting around and weird shit happening
but i would say 90 probably like 80 to 90 percent of all the games that i've played in this game
i've played pretty normally as if i was sitting next to the person that i was playing against
so that's encouraging and honestly the servers are are getting hammered right now
this just went into open beta there are a ton of people playing this game so it's
holding up pretty well let's go all right all right okay all right okay oh shit did i hit it
back at him damn it anti-superman land b yikes oh nice kick nice that was a good play that was
a good play it was what are we doing all right all right pull it together pull together that
freak down we got this oh my god that was so scary bugs is getting nerfed in a week that's all right
he's really strong bugs is very strong yeah i get fin on that nerf too play tom and jerry
actually fin is probably in a good place i would i would imagine they probably just need to they
need to bring a few people up i think genuinely i can't think of a character that i think is not
worth playing i don't think so i mean maybe lebron feels a little weak but his brand new character
who is genuinely terrible i don't think there's anybody that's genuinely awful rain dog is this
character not great wonder woman sucks really on team teams though rain dog is probably really
good aria feels really interesting too i want to try aria i was trained by the greatest swordsman
who ever lived cereal laurel oh here comes the heat steve is not uh good either it's fun to play
she's busted if you know what you're doing show him what we got steve i asked steve okay
i just let you do that all right what did that do what's my head hurts from that what happened
that's hurt my brain holy shit they look cool i don't know what they do though
i don't know what i'm doing okay shake it up we only get started
these powers like i'm unstoppable continue she seems fun here comes the heat excellent choice
all right i could do some team games i've been doing all one v ones i'm obsessed with one v one
oh i guess i'm unlockables hold on a new banner all right this is a good harley quinn
i gotta prepare myself this is a good harley quinn show them what we got you guys are fucking
hilarious jesus
no no no no no i need that really come on man really it broke the shield oh my god
it's not impossible it's not impossible it's not impossible it is it's impossible
shake it up we only get started i felt a little laggy did you even try rematch do it again okay
here comes the heat i'm here to fight for truth and justice did you even try
no i just i literally just like was trying to touch my tongue my nose and uh i focused on that
more than the game because that was my mistake i shouldn't have done that
so i'll focus this time i'll try this guy i'm warning you i don't have an easy mode
damn all right all right be by surprise harley careful let's go let's go i told you we got this
let's go that's a good fight good fight change it up on the harley change it up
this one okay are we gonna get a character switch or am i gonna get dunked on by harley
i wonder here comes the heat i'm gonna say superman should you fall i'll catch you okay
do you think this game will have the three stooges does warner even own the three stooges i don't
think so but i mean it would be all right this is this is it this is for the marvels
watch yourself watch this all right all right whoa that was weird make me do this
oh i'm good i'm good i'm good i'm good yeah i told you we got this superman's
launch moves are unbelievable gave me quite the work out there they're so good they're
actually cracked out man oh good fight though good match that was that was intense i can feel it i'm
like nervous it's that that gamer feeling you know what i mean here comes the heat you were popping
off you should probably main superman you think so right choice only choice god superman's moves
just feel great to do when you're in the air and you just go like what you just do that huge right
handed punch what's the last game that i played off stream fall guys i played it for like 10
minutes all right let's see if i can do some work here show them what we got why because it was free
and it was on xbox so i just downloaded it for no reason and speaking of downloading a video game
vaulty versus is an open beta right now if you want to do gaming skills like this oh check it out
for real actually you actually check it out it's a great game actually phenomenal fucking game
i don't even know what that does went over his head didn't catch it come on wrong way
oh that back already added man i love winning you look thirsty dude
okay dude you you look thirsty here comes the heat oh no i can't afford it as long as i'm standing
you can count on me get the mustache hair again probably i didn't he peed his chair i did not feed
my chair he for sure peed his chair did you get a haircut no i didn't a while ago i did
oh it's jake got so greedy that was like unbelievable
what the hell keeps happening here what the hell dude he went off the goddamn screen
he went into the skybox for god's sake every time he does that does that move the whole game turns
off i'm so confused that was so stupid dude my dub why is my double jump something's not funky
shake it off we only get stuck i've never watched this show ever again
here comes the heat what this life nothing but simulation the show dude the show ended
years ago i've never watched it on tv when it comes on tv ever again can you please stop
shitting in my garden i don't care if you're fertilizing the crops it got to take out that
message got removed so enjoy your five minute time out all right here we go dude i told you we got
this get stretchy dog not stretchy enough nice what happened that was weird here comes the heat
open beta cross progression cross platform lebron's in the game you can get it right now go
download it multi-versus you can look up pretty much anywhere where if you can get it why do i
keep going back to lebron i don't know why i keep seeing the potential of playing with lebron and
it always is and we're going against a fin i'm literally snapping all my adventure time dvds
in half after this show them what we got all right come on i guess this is a map for lebron by the
way actually a map for lebron okay here comes the heat i'll do my best that's the first time
i've seen that happen it's been pretty rock solid so far dude bro is flabbergasted dude bro is
flabbergasted i do look like it's sweaty don't i it's the same person no show them what we got
madam to sew wax statue version of germa it's hot in here man
i think i'm hitting gamer fatigue
i guess it's time to increase my power levels on you
that gamer fatigue is settling in am i still on the stage oh my goodness
all right superman is amazing superheroes but i'm definitely hitting gamer fatigue
we're gonna do some team fights rematch okay the next stream monday or tuesday next
stream is gonna be monday here comes the heat the wax is dripping off what if i just started
going like one day hold me to this because i will do this one day i'm gonna put a layer of
wax clay all of my do a full face have a professional makeup artist do this
and just be slowly kind of pushing it and moving it around and smearing it around and shit
i swear to god i'm gonna do it and i'm not gonna say a single word about it
all right let's just do one more box and then i'll do a couple team fights
that's good same person when is baseball baseball is august 19th you're gonna start to see a lot of
marketing i would say well don't worry we're gonna hype it up you'll see some marketing for it
marketing in quotes right pr andy that's right august 19th you don't have enough money
i promise i'm trying to do the other boobs all right come on wait
yeah we got this oh bones bones what a performance
all right let's do a few relaxed team ones maybe some free for all there was some good games i got
absolutely diarrhea on in the first um the first like half hour plan i got into it though we played
some really good players though looking forward to putting on the director's commentary for
adventure time season 3 dvd special 10 toasts that's cool all right let's do some stuff let's
do some cool stuff let's do some free for all some teams here comes the heat let me say superman
genuinely superman is awesome uh before i forget though like i play this game and i think it's fun
and warner brothers actually is just like yeah we'll sponsor you that's just cool i'm really happy
about it so i'm glad that it's a game that i really like to play i actually enjoy it so thanks
again for sponsoring the stream seriously really really cool can you jump six times yeah sure uh
oh oh we'll go we got it we got a perkless steven universe and a almost perkless superman
we're in trouble now or maybe not my voice is like so dry you're right who said that earlier
somebody said dude your voice is wicked dry they were right it sounds like kind of terrible
i'm like hey what's happening why does it sound like this
all right let's do it come on stephen watch out for that smoke
i didn't grab him what get out of here this isn't over yet
oh i almost had it i almost had it again that would have been so sick and i'm terrible
here it is sorry superman
how did i not hit you what the fuck sorry superman get the fuck oh my goodness
just like the gems got me
i forgot where i was on the screen this fucking harley quinn oh my god dude i get out of here
not today what just fucking happened i flew in the air we only get stuck
i've lost count how many times have i beaten you now all right let's do it again let's do that
again that got all messed up i couldn't even do anything i messed with every single goddamn
swing all right we're going fucking lebron i'm pissed visually overwhelmed yeah that's it when
you play these games for long enough uh just colors just start to i just i can't tell the
difference anymore after about three to four hours my brain just kind of like all right i need to do
i need to like look at a wall or something they switched up their mains did they oh they went
garnet it was steven universe before all right let's make it happen let's go show them what we
got we can make it happen let's do it all right i'm gonna i'm gonna let's let's go for it okay
oh come on where's the priority on that move i didn't hit come on man i'm so confused
well i didn't do that whoa
oh
watch that zone watch that zone oh all right sorry sorry
oh that would have ended it oh you bastard
we got this good fight good game good game seriously hold that good game well it's not over
we got one more we gotta go for the real deal right here comes the heat do you know who lebron
is in real life yeah no i have no idea i have no idea who one of the greatest basketball players
to ever live is i don't know who that is i've never heard of the guy do i stay lebron i don't
know yeah the king now all right you know who steven universe is in real life show them what
we got all right we got it we gotta win this one oh we don't have to do anything right we're gonna
try no oh that's so anticlimactic that was it that was the client that was the climactic part
oh that's unfortunate unfortunate here comes the heat all right we'll do one more we'll do one more
one more and that's it just do a free for all uh i'll do a free for all after this if it doesn't
get picked right uh a rain dog yeah my kryptonite in this game is finn and jake from adventure time
i can handle the bugs i can handle a batman i can handle harley quinn and i'll handle
and jake they're killing me i wonder what my record is against fins and jakes it's probably
pretty low back to the lab i gotta figure out why all right come on rain dog let's do it
oh that was a double
oh i almost had it you got two of those whatever what nobody wants to go near each other we're
good what the fuck is happening okay
oh dude how come he's got two of those what is up with that w i told you we got this
good match good fight play again it's a bug you know i've lost
nice i think i've only lost maybe what five times total six or seven times i've won probably 10 to
20 games what's with what's the record today i feel like this has been pretty good the game's
been great so far here comes the heat let's all fight fair and this should be fun you can check
i'll go check in a minute let's be the last one check your profile 83 win rate oh thanks for the
perks definitely that one i want that one i want all defense no no we want yeah so after uh
multiverses uh well not aftermath but on monday we'll go back to sorcery on monday and then tuesday
maybe we'll do that again friday we're gonna do green screen movie night part two definitely
want to show up for that one it's like another 150 plus videos to watch so that should be fun
and then baseball's august 19th we got a lot of shit going on august 19th all right let's go
when you look aren't you you got caught in that damn oh my goodness he almost just eliminated me
out of that not hit dude this guy seriously keeps throwing us up
no dude he's just throwing him around all right get this rain dog get the rain dog oh shit
oh we only get stuck crap of all the rain dogs you're the rain doggiest
it's all good it's all good let's go that superman just kept on grabbing the fin and just
tossing him he got me once with it too sneaky that's sneaky stuff you just kind of grab and then
blink good choice all right this is it after this i'll see you guys on monday i've had a lot of fun
though and sponsored or not i'm probably gonna keep playing this i don't know why i would stop
i think this is a good thing just to you know kill a couple of hours show them what we got
just jumping here for an hour or two every so often i think it'd be fun especially when they
start adding new characters i'm gonna want to play them not all the time but i mean whatever i
if i get into it i get into it right let's get it bro i have no more escapes
all delivery oh one of us is going down there man oh come on
can't keep a good farm boy down all right we gotta tie it up go go go go go
make me do this oh that didn't hit sorry it's good one for blue
big one for red don't let them i freaked myself out i freaked myself off i freaked
myself i freaked myself out i freaked myself out why did i do that i freaked out i freaked out
oh my god i freaked out we were we were winning i just oh i freaked out i had a shitload of damage
i i freaked out i freaked out it's like jumping in mario when you jump to a ledge and then you
You jump again when you made the ledge and you just fall to your death.
Ah!
Here comes the heat!
Okay, I'm not going to end on a loss.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't know why I did that.
I just...
I threw the ball and the ball was gone.
You look pale because this webcam is a piece of crap and it's like the most expensive webcam
you can possibly buy and it's worse than the one I had before and it overexposes you and
you can't do anything about it.
It's literally the worst webcam I've ever used.
It's a skill issue.
There's a DSLR.
I don't...
I don't care.
I don't want to set up a big camera pointed over here and have the room heat up even more.
Alright, let's go.
Bro, I'm serious.
What is going on with my guy?
I'll do it again.
Don't do it again.
I almost had it again.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, this guy's just spamming his down smash move and it's
freaking me out.
Look, and he's just doing the down move and it's freaking us both out.
We can't do anything with him.
He's just going shrug, he almost did it too.
Oh my god, that was so close.
Oh my goodness, that's a good strategy.
That was seriously ridiculous.
Alright, this is it, this is the end.
Alright, we good?
Final one.
This is it.
I'm going to try as hard as I can and I'm going to try to win.
Don't throw, don't throw.
It's asking a lot.
You know what channel you're on.
The channel where we do that stuff.
Please be on Steven Universe.
Oh, okay.
My, I don't know what happened.
I'm serious.
I think I lagged out of the screen.
I didn't press that button.
Sorry.
We're fine.
Fine.
Relax.
It's a really bad start for both of us.
I don't know.
I get my game fucked up.
Oh, no.
This was a disaster.
Wait, that was an absolute disaster.
I don't even know what happened, man.
We just, there's the same players.
What happened?
What even just happened?
More like world's greatest everything.
Alright, this is, I mean, come on, man.
This is the final round.
What the hell happened?
I'm seriously shook up over this.
Here comes the heat.
Who I should have taken that left toy and alpha koi ki?
I slam dunked off the screen.
Oops.
Okay.
Let's go.
I'm going as hard as I can.
I'm going full volume.
I'm warning you.
I'm not going to look at chat.
And it's Steven Universe's theme song.
It's Steven Universe's map.
It's the best map in the game.
We're good.
Good match.
That's a good one to go out on.
Good work.
Oh yeah.
No.
Good battles.
Alright.
That was a lot of fun.
When you get into a rhythm, the game becomes just like fluid, you know, like water.
It's just like boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, down, boom, up, down, down, down, down.
The game's great.
This stream was sponsored by Warner Brothers.
Thanks again.
It's an open beta.
Go check it out.
I highly encourage you do.
I really genuinely think this game has what it takes to be played for a long time.
It's very fun.
Huge thanks to Warner Brothers.
Seriously, of course I'm going to take this sponsor.
That was awesome.
I will see you guys later.
See you on Monday.
Have a fantastic rest of your night.
Thanks for watching.
We'll see you for Sorcery.
And those of you that, check out Sorcery.
Sorcery is a really fun game.
Really chill.
It's kind of just like a book.
We'll see you on Monday.
Thanks again.
Good night.
Goodbye.
Good games tonight.
Good games tonight, right?
Thanks for all the subs.
All of you.
Now, this time I gotta remember to take this off.
And I love Adventure Time.
I'm just kidding around.
I don't hate that show.
I was kidding.
It was a joke.
I've seen all those episodes on TV.
Good night, guys.
See you soon.
Call your mother.