Welcome to 2020. I know it's been, it's been four days, but you know, it's 2020 nonetheless.
How are you? God, shut up already. What? I just turned it on. What are you talking about?
Hey, hey. Oh God. First comment I read in 2020 is that great. It was a good start. Anyways,
starting a little late today. The plan originally was we were going to do
keep talking and everybody will be whatever. Keep talking and nobody explodes with Joel,
but Joel's not feeling well. He kind of last second was like, I'm sorry to do that. I feel
like shit right now. And I'm like, don't, it's all good. Don't fucking worry about it. It's all good.
We're just going to do it tomorrow. So today, today we're going to do something else.
And what we're going to do is I've got a lot of games to play. I've got a huge list over the
last couple of days, at least I've been compiling at least what I want to start to do in 2020.
Derma falls on the street. Yeah. And I also, I've looked at the images.
I've seen the images of the, everyone that like weird mutant face that I have when I'm in the
chair. I know it looks doctored, but it isn't, but it, it looks bad. I know, I know I've seen it.
Anyways, we don't have the idea because we're starting really late. So I want to kind of get
right into this. So here comes the game. This is, this is flashing lights is the game. This
actually was requested more than once. This is a requested video game. This is a game we play as
police, ambulance and fire. No, not like not actual flashing lights. You know, you're not
going to get like flashed. This was requested twice. I don't, I have no, I saw the screenshots. I saw
like a few seconds of the trailer and I'm like, okay, fine. All right. I'll give it a try.
I'll give it a try. If this game is not, if we, I got two other like last minute additions,
that should be fun. Uh, we did a poll earlier and this is what was voted for. Again, 2020 is going
to be no different. I'm going to make this really, really clear. The power of the pre-stream chat.
This got like 70% of the vote. And if you want to know what it beat out, it beat out Katana Zero
and Wizorb. Just say it. The power of the pre-stream chat. Don't think you don't have power.
Somebody just wrote seriously? Seriously? Anyway, let's go. I don't know. Let's play.
This is called flashing lights. Uh, max vehicle traffic. Why don't we make this, um,
why do I have to do this? Max pedestrians. Yeah, you know, I want 99 vehicles. Sorry,
it's 20. Uh, okay. How about 12? Parked vehicle density, medium high, medium time,
day fuel consumption, medium, I guess. Is this like a simulator? Do I, is it like a tutorial?
There's 12 people in the whole city. All right. Is it, do I, this is really low volume too. Hold on.
This is going to be really high volume in about five seconds. Guarantee it. Let's find out.
I'm not looking forward to this. I'm scared. This is really, really, it's going to be really
fucking loud. Is this the same image? Wait, what? Is that a tank? Why is there a tank? Oh, hold on.
Can you hear this? And now you can. All right. Police firefighter or medic. Which one do you
want to start with? Uh, I feel like the title of the stream is doctor officer fireman. So we're
going to start as doctor. Let's do medic. And this, I can't hear anything. Medic. Done. Uh, male.
Okay. Uh, three bodies. Okay. You can either, you can wear a Christmas hat,
um, and sunglasses. At what point do you just not have a character creator? I'm just going to be
completely honest. Like just, do you really need sunglasses? There's three options. Like,
do you really need sunglasses? This is the EMT from the rumble. Holy shit. It actually is.
Oh my God. That's fucked up. That's really what it is. Uh, we had huge bits come in from
bilateral lich. Thank you for electric for the 5,000 bits. They say Jeremy is the police monkey.
S well, not yet. I'm the medic. All right. We're going to go with this. This is fine.
So I have to go help people, but seriously, thank you for the fucking $50 by luxury
starting 2020 off with huge money already. Thank you. I got to turn this up. This is really low.
Okay. Emergency medical service. It's like, it's like an open world. All right. Let me turn this
up. 75, 70, 77, 78, 79. Unconscious person at address green tag. What? Hold on. Address unconscious
person at address green tag. Call ID respond. Okay. Except unconscious person at green tag.
How do I get in a car? David too is responding to unconscious person. All right. I get in.
I don't even get a tutorial. Engine on. Okay. Lights sign. How do I drive right now? This is
fucking loud. Now we, of course it is. It's one of those loud and soft games. All right. 65 sounds
all right to me. All right. Here we go. Unconscious person over at green. Do I turn my siren on?
What? I got minus points because I bumped a stop sign. Really? Okay. How long do I have?
Do you have to follow the rule? I feel like I'm explaining Grand Theft Auto. All right. Hold on.
Unconscious person. See, I'm not making any, there's no damage. I just, I skimmed that person.
Inspect the person. Check if they can be transported to the hospital.
Interact using med bag. Where's my med bag? Why can you punch as a medic? Why? Why can you punch
as a medic? Okay. Med bag. Interact using med bag or other items from your vehicle trunk.
Okay. Let's get it out. Items. Okay. Stretcher. I got to put this guy on the stretcher.
Uh, what the fuck is going on? All right. How do I put them on? I put you on the stretcher.
Don't run them over. I'm not going to run them over. Oh, wait, here we go. Okay.
Wait, why is there an indicator over his head? Um, I don't know what the fuck I'm doing. Hold on.
Can I go back in here? You got a nerd neck. All right. What do we got? Technical defibrillator.
This is my first day. I'm sorry. Okay. Shock pads. Remove top part of clothing. What? What do you
mean? What do you mean remove top part of cloth? How do I, how, what? All right. Well, this doesn't
work. Um, items. Fracture kit. Medic bag. All right. Medic bag. I got it. Inspect patient. Here we go.
All right. What's wrong? You hit your head? Breathing. He has pulse. Unconscious. Uh, what
about his stomach? Inspect it. He has a pulse. You can feel a pulse from somebody's stomach?
It has pulse. Okay. You have a pulse. You have a pulse. You have a pulse. All right. I've,
you, I do have to use the defibrillator. All right. Where's that? Where's the, oh shit. Um,
okay. No, no, no, no, no. That, I think that's correct. Where's the defib? All right. I got it.
Okay. Um, what? Okay. Uh, grab the stretcher from the ambulance and load the patient
to deliver to the hospital. Wait, his friend's leaving. I'm not done. You, you might, can you,
uh, okay. His friend's leaving. How do I, he has a pulse. He's good. Did I really knock a car over?
All right. But how do I put him on the stretcher? I need a second EMT for this. How do you put him
on the stretcher? Using med bag. Can I lower the stretcher? Is there any other buttons I can press?
Inspect you. Wait, let me give him the med bag. Give me the med bag. Okay. Let's try that. So
perform CPR. Neck collar. Uh, okay. I got a call. I got him in a neck collar. His neck was injured.
Okay. Um, now transport. Request transport. Wait, I am the ambulance. Unconscious person. Dispatch
received. Aren't I the ambulance? So why did an ambulance just call an ambulance?
I can't get him on the stretcher. Why would I call the ambulance?
Well, are they coming? Oh, there they are. Oh, don't worry. We'll take it from here.
Wait, there's a vehicle incident. Vehicle incident. Respond. Code three. Wait, I'm not yet. I want to
see what happens here. Well, you just kind of scooped him up. All right, let's go. Vehicle
incident. I got to load this stuff back onto the car. How do you put people on? That does a weird
indicator there and I'm not sure what it is. Excuse me. Thank you. Thank you for putting it in.
You helped me put it back in the trunk. Good job. Oh, gunshot. Oh, hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I got
to put my, I got to put my stereos back in. Just get out of the way. Get out of the way. Out of the
way. Okay. Can I not pick this up? Pick it up. I, there's nobody, there's nobody on the ground.
Why is it, why am I getting this? Remove all. Okay. All right, let's go. All right, vehicle incident.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Why can't I drive? Am I driving the car in front of me? Oh, shit,
I'm in the wrong seat. Hold on. Okay, let's go. Where was it? Oh, it's all the way up here.
That's so far away. Filactory. Again, another $50. Holy shit, dude. 5,000 bits from file. I need you,
I need you to find out how many ambulances you can call at once. I was thinking about doing that,
but I think no, not quite. We're not quite there yet. We're not there yet. But yeah, I feel you.
Yeah, I want to call every single emergency service. Vehicle incident. Is there a handbrake?
Shit. Is this pre-recorded? Uh, no, it is not. Those of you that just trickled in,
Joel and I were going to play keep talking to nobody explodes today, but Joel was not feeling
well. Uh, he kind of just, uh, right at the, right before we were about to start, he was just like,
I fucking feel like shit right now. He just, it just jumped on him. So we're going to do it tomorrow.
Joel's health is more important. Defusing fake bombs. Seriously, this is, why do I have to go
all the way around here? This is no better way for me to go. This is just trying to hit me.
This is the worst emergency route ever. Why is it not an emergency route? Multi-lane driving. No,
shouldn't, shouldn't it be like an off road that's, wait, this is the wrong way.
All right. What's the other siren? Is there no other siren? Wait, I can turn my blinkers on?
Why, for what? Whoa. Okay. I'm fine. That was actually scary because I have to call an ambulance.
I have to call an ambulance.
All right. I gotta call an ambulance. Hey, where's my medic bag? Okay. Need an ambulance.
How do I call an ambulance? I can run there. I can run there. I can run there.
It's right there. I got my medic bag. I can, I can call the, I can call for another ambulance.
What the fuck was that? Okay. Imagine, imagine you got in a car accident and you look down,
you got like a broken leg and you look down the, all the way down here and you see the medic
and EMT running up the hill with a bag. How disappointed would you be?
And you look even further down, you see that he drove into a ditch. All right. I'm here. I'm here.
I'm here. I'm here. I'm here. How's the patient? Inspect the person. Okay. There's the tank.
All right. What happened here? Leg, broken leg? No. Wait, what did it say? Not breathing, no pulse.
Okay. Um, perform CPR. Uh, what? How do you do CPR? How do you CPR? Does this get dead? Okay. Um,
I need the defib. I need the defib. All right. I'll be right back. Wait, wait. Can I have your car?
Can I borrow your car? Can I take this car? Okay. Let me request an ambulance. Let me request an
ambulance. Okay. Request transport. Patients not ready for transport. God damn it. You can't get
hurt. Can you, can you reset the car? I don't think so. Not that I'm aware of.
Can I get the car? I think I can get the car out of the ditch. I can, I think I can move it.
Yeah. I think somebody just mentioned it. Why is there a jump even programmed into the game?
Just for fun? I mean, I guess that's just kind of for fun. You can reset the car.
How? All right. If I get out and move like this. Okay. Here we go. I got it. Why didn't I do it?
I should have just done this in the first place. God damn it. Okay. Whatever. It's fine.
Do I need gas? I think I need gas. I need the stretcher. Do you need the stretcher?
No, I don't. I need the defib. How did that even fall out? The doors are closed. What the
fuck are they talking about? All right. I'm here. No, thanks to you two officers. Thanks a lot.
All right. Give me my, look, stretcher. Items. Stretcher. Items. Um, was it defib?
Technical. Defib. Let's go. Okay. Let's put it on. Here we go. I'm here. What does that mean?
What does that mean? What does that mean? What does that mean? What does that mean?
What does that mean? Does anybody know what that means? How many times do you have to do this?
Okay. Is he alive? He's alive. Right? All right. Let's go. Give me my med bag.
Uh, hold on. Is he alive? No pulse. I killed him. The patient's not ready for transportation.
Didn't, didn't he just have a pulse? Look, see? Patient's not ready for transportation.
Do I have to have the stretcher? Where is the stretcher? Back here? It's not that far.
You have to put his clothes back on. Why is it so hard for me to drive over this road?
Where's the stretcher? Isn't it right here? It was right here. Another $50 from Phylactery?
Holy shit, Phylactery. Really? Oh my God. Get boots. All right. Put that in. Let's go.
All right. Get over here. I'm just learning. I'm learning how to play. Please don't do this again.
Move. Bro, you need to learn how to read. No, I don't. Speaking of reading, five community subs.
I can read that from Flinzenberg. Thank you Flinzenberg for the five subs and Vilemi for
there's more money coming in. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. There's a shitload of money coming in.
You guys didn't stop from New Year's Eve. Oh my goodness. He can only read Greed. It's not true.
Vilemi, 5,000 fucking bits from Vilemi. If I'm ever dying, I hope to God you're not the EMT
that responds to my 911 call. Well, I wouldn't because I'm not an EMT. I'm an internet clown.
And now that would be odd if an internet clown had to come and take care of you.
How do I fill up gas? Another five community subs from Adventure MF Dan. Where's the,
in an emergency vehicle, where's the gas? Wrong side? Shit, it's the wrong side. Whatever,
whatever. I don't need it right now. There's a guy lying on the ground dying. I'm going.
Had his hest. 2,045 cents for gas. That's pretty cheap. He's not dead. He's going to be fine.
Flutter is 10 community subs. Holy shit, guys. Thank you. More subs. All right, I'm here.
Look, there was no real tutorial. I'm trying to figure it out as we go.
Drive on the roads. I did too much Grand Theft Auto in my blood. Okay, I have the stretcher now.
Stretcher. Let's get it. All right, I just like causing injury to somebody else.
Phylactery, what on earth are you doing, man? Phylactery, 60 fucking nine subs. What are you
doing? Holy fuck, dude. Hundreds and hundreds of dollars. Hundreds. All right, I get a, that's a
lot of subs. 69 fucking community subs. All right, how do I put you on the stretcher? I have an
indicator, but I can't do anything about it. Jeremy, you need to buy phylactery dinner at
this point. Phylactery's bought me dinner like 6,000 times. So, I mean, all right, hold on.
This is an indicator right here. Request transport. Not ready for transport. No pulse.
CPR again? Do the defib again. Okay. All right, stop doing that. Get up. What is additional?
Traffic cones? What? Why do I have this? I'm just like playing. What a dick. Okay, all right,
all right, all right. Defib, let's go. Defib, okay. Put them back on. You've got a pulse. Why
does it say no pulse? Grab the stretcher. I already did this. Load the patient and deliver
to the hospital. Okay, okay, okay. How do I load the patient? Oh, cannot do this while the, oh,
I have to undo the connections. All right, undo these connections. All right, put this down.
So, you do have to kind of go over them. Okay, pick up. Got him. All right, let's go. Into the car.
Let's go. Into the car. Okay, let's go. Let's go. He's going. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Not into the
river. Not into the river. Okay, get in. All right, door's closed. Let's get you to the hospital.
Where's the hospital? Yeah, I know, I know. I, yes, I'm aware that we just did like a 90s comedy
routine. Yes. That, I think that happens in every single Leslie Nielsen movie. And, I mean, those
movies are legendary, but that does happen. All right, let's go back. Get your bag. I don't need
my bag. I'll get a new, I'll get a new bag. Can I skip this? Hold on. All right, that guy just hit
the ceiling of the ambulance. He went like, boom, boom. I'm not going down that stupid thing again.
I'm so glad there's no time limit because this would be so stupid. I'm not driving down that
bullshit again. There's no cars on the road. Why would I even need to have the siren? Hopefully,
this guy's bolted to the ground. All right. Where do I go? Just drop off at the front.
Okay. Get them out. Let's go in. All right. Where? Into the here. I did it. Patient delivered. All
right. That was pretty fun. Okay. See, and I got a new medical bag too. You guys were so concerned
about that. Did I miss any of the calls? All right. I have two patients hospital. Here we go. Another
vehicle incident. Uh, skip this one. All right. I'm going to fill it. I'm going to get gas.
You're wasting tax dollars. I mean, am I though? It's like seven ambulances. This is not how you
pull into a gas station. What the fuck am I doing? Where's the, um, it's right there. Okay.
Skip. I don't drive big cars guys. I'm so used to being on the, it's on my car. It's on the
right side. Okay. So that's why I, and it's like that every time. And yes, I know you have to look
every time that you have to look at your gas meter on your dashboard every time. Yeah. You do
too. Even if you've owned the car for 10 years. Okay. I got to turn the engine off. What vehicle
incident? Nah. All right. Fuel. How do I feel? Is it fueling? Is it fueling? I have to pay that
due to pay money. Vehicle incident. Nah. What was this? I've got a currency. Hey, I don't know. I'm
not sure. I do have, okay. You just, you just click it and it fills instantly. All right. I just need
to see. I'm just curious. Can I make my own incident to then bring this person to the hospital?
Don't worry. I got you. I'll take care of you. What's, what happened? What? Uh, where are you
going? You're going the wrong way. Where are you going? Hold on. You're going the wrong way. This
way. Did you fuck? Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Wait. They can't get over here. All right. Hold on. Wait.
I have to cause a couple more injuries. This is where we test it out. This is where we test the
theory. Can steal the other ambulance. Hold on. I will. Or I'll try. All right. Ambulance on route.
Ambulance on route. Okay. Move. Move. Get out of the way. How many ambulances can I have at the same
time? Oh God. Here we go. Come here. I got you. Damn it. That's the plan. Okay. We got a new plan
here. Yeah. When the EMT gets out, run over the EMT and then call an ambulance for the EMT.
Fuck. They're immune. Damn it. They're immune to damage. No, they're immune to damage. It's not
fair. Not fair. That guy's pissed. You keep yourself in business, but they can't go anywhere.
All right. Vehicle incident. Where's the vehicle incident? It's all the way back there.
Turn your blinker off. Oh shit. You're right. I'm sorry. Another vehicle incident hit a ton. Yeah.
All right. All right. All right. We gotta, we gotta get to, we gotta get to a spawn area
because what I'm going to do is I'm going to run over like 10 people and then I'm going to get out
and I'm going to go bang, bang, bang, boom, boom, boom, boom, bum, bum, bum, calling me as ambulance,
ambulance, ambulance, ambulance, and roll. Why is my blinker still on? Turn it off. It's a guy's,
my blinker's off. Deep. I can't turn it off. It's odd. Now the other one's on. They're going to go
all the way up here again. Turn off blinker. Oh my God. It's driving me crazy now that you mentioned
it. I can't fucking believe I have to go up here again. I'm just gonna skip this one. Skip it. I
don't even want to do this one. Is it too late? You blinker fluid is too low. How do I D? How do
I like turn? I'm gonna get out of the car. Turn the engine off. Turn the engine on. Ready? Okay.
I can't turn it off. Just unplug the battery. Yeah. I know. Don't worry. That's the plan. The
plan is we're going to, we're going to hit at least 10 people and I'm going to run around and
call an ambulance for every single one of them and watch the chaos. Press three. Yeah. I mean that
look, look at the bottom of the, look at the bottom of the screen. Press the left arrow key.
That's turn. Okay. Save a little bit of time there. That noise is going to drive me fucking crazy.
It's going to drive me crazy. It really is. You're right. It's driving me crazy right now.
All right. I'm here. What happened? What an entrance. Oh, look, someone's lying on the ground.
Okay. I need the damn med bag. Just get it all out of here. All right. What's wrong? Inspect.
Head. No pulse. Okay. There's no pulse. Let's get the, uh, defib. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
What are you doing? Oh, right click. Uh, hook it up. Okay. Uh, I have to, wait, what? Oh, um, hold
on. Wait, hold on. Okay. No, this is bathing suit. Okay. This is a bathing suit. All right. Um,
let's, uh, where's the, where's the, where's the, where's the, where's the defib, where's the defib,
where's the defib, defib, defib, defib. I just did. Let me inspect. I didn't, I just do that.
I gotta go. Hurry up. Where's my med bag? I just teleported it. All right. Inspect. I have to
inspect every single point here. I know the possible bone fracture. Oh shit. Okay. Perform
CPR. Okay. Here we go. How do I fix the bone fracture? What do I do? Okay. Use defib. All
right. Let's go. Let's go. Come on. Come on. Come on. All right. One, two, three. Um, that,
that just looks like a wavelength in audacity. Uh, shock pads. Okay. Here we go. Did it work?
Do I need a fracture kit? What's a fracture kit? All right. Fracture kit. Uh, technical items,
fracture kit. Okay. Here we go. That's it. All right. Grab the stretcher for the, and uh,
deliver it. Okay. Let's go. Wait. I have to take all this stuff off. All right. Give, I needed to
get this off. Give me this. Okay. Remove. I fixed it. I'm good. Oh, I need to put cones in the road.
Oh, I got a fracture. I got a left leg fracture too. We're the same now. You and me. All right.
Here we go. Okay. No, I can't. I can't. I can't just into the water. Oh, no. Please. No.
Don't worry. I'll get you. I think she's okay. Wait, can I, I can't just go into the ocean,
right? Why can't I go? Wait. Oh, shit. Wait, wait. Contact with water? What do you mean
contact with water? Is that a tube? I think I got fired. I think the game doesn't know what to do
with me. Is a new, is a new person. Wait, she's still there? Vehicle incident. Sure. She's still
there? All right. Do you think that she is still there? Yes or no? What do you think? And can I
get her? No, no, it's definitely gonna reset. Okay. Whatever. Uh, oh yeah. Hey, this is not
a, we have two more departments to go through. Wait, what? Open. What do you want me to do?
Why do I always get stuck like this in every game? Open chat window to, to respond. What?
What do I do? Slash car 100. Is that bullshit? Type car 100 to create tonic traffic.
That didn't do anything. Slash car 100. I'm not doing it. Is it car space 100? No, it's not.
You have to get out and do it. All right. Well, good. Nice. Good one. Got me. Baited. It's not
gonna, it's not working. Oh, I think we have a fire situation here. Inspect who? What is that?
All right. What happened? Inspect. Breathing has pulse conscious possible neck injury. I know what
to do. See? Give me. Give me. Into the water you go. No, this one's not going to the water.
All right. Excuse me. That's my fucking medical bag in the way. All right. Let's go.
The ocean, the ocean. I'm not putting them in the ocean. I don't think you can actually
go in this way. All right. You're in. Close. I don't think you can fall out that way. So who cares?
I really don't think you can. Speaking of which, I'm not sure I can get back in the car.
He definitely cannot fall out that way. All right. I think we may have seen all there is to see with
the EMT. I think it's time to switch to a firefighter. Yep. It's time. It's firefighter time.
Yeah. I'm going to try. I'm going to try my bullshit one time. I've done so much weird shit
and how do I only have a... That's not that big of a deal. Minus one. All right. Let's go.
Out. Into the hospital. Let's go. Aha. Good. All right. If there's... If we have one more
opportunity here, I'm going to skip a couple and I want to get like a person fell off a tree or
something. A person fell down a hole. Is there any of those? You can choose the next mission
with a command. Oh, I left a stretcher. I don't get a new one on a new mission. I thought that
happened last time. What did I do? I just pressed N. I just skipped something. Cheat codes? All right.
Hold on. What is this? Change role. Oh, I can change role. It's that easy. Officer next.
So how much... How different is everything? Reputation, fire calls, rescue calls.
Do I have to pick up this stuff? No. What is... Select vehicle. Fire department car, ladder truck,
fire department, pumper truck. I mean, I want this one. Why would I not use that one? Building.
Okay. There's a fire. Let's go. Where's my car? Let's go. I got to put out 10 fires. All right.
Open this up. How do I open this? Uh, open the garage? Open. Oh, shit. I have to go down here.
Okay. Let's go. Uh, how do I get out of the garage? And by the way, what is this bullshit on the front?
What is this cartoon thing? They don't have that. That would be so bad for people in the...
coming the other direction, wouldn't it? Like, just... That would be ridiculous.
On top I'd just stay, but like, that's crazy. All right. Let's go. Siren doesn't do anything.
The siren doesn't do anything. All right. Here we go. Uh, the diner. How do I put out the fire?
How do I put the fire out? Oh, fire extinguisher. Right. Oh, no. Hose. Hose?
Do I have like a mask on? Uh, what do I do? Attach hose to the fire truck. Okay. Now,
is this what you do? Oh, there it is. Go in the... I gotta go in. Uh, this...
Is this... Am I doing this right? Oh, there's people. There's people in here. Where's the...
Where's the hose? Am I dead? What? What happened? Is this an ambulance coming?
How are they gonna get in here? Play as the EMT and save yourself.
Is he an EMT? Is he gonna come in the front door?
Oh, shit. Wait, what? You brought me back to life. I did it!
There comes another ambulance. I have to run out of here. The second... I have to run the fuck out
immediately. What about this person? Is this person right here okay? I have to run out. Is
the second... The second that he gets in here. There he comes. All right. Get me up. And we both
have to run out. Get... Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Okay. Good. Now, where... Is my hose still in there or not?
Okay. I need another hose. Oh, shit. I need... I don't have a hose. Uh...
Don't worry. I'm here to save the day. Oh, that's so stupid. All right. Get off.
Sneaking. Oh, wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. That's dumb. How fast can I sneak?
Go on the roof. Okay. I don't think I can get on the roof. Can I get on the roof? I can get on the
roof. Holy shit. No. I need the ladder to get up there. No. No, I don't. I think I can jump over
this. I'm almost there. Come on. Okay. I'm on the roof. I've made it to the roof. What does this do
for me? Not much. Okay. Well, there's a fire. It's not just smoke. There's a fire up here.
Can the EMT get on the roof is a question that we'll have to ask. I soft-locked it? All right. I'll...
Is there a better camera? All right. Come on. Get up here. No, he doesn't get it. He doesn't get it.
Does he get it? He gets it. Hold on. I just went in the building.
I don't see him coming up. Somebody help me. Wait. What? You actually... He got me?
Holy shit. What a hero. He did it. All right. I need to... Okay. Here we go. Now put this down. I need
a... I need like a fan. All right. Give me a fan. How do I use this? How do you put the fan down?
All right. Did I put it down? I need like a mask or something. Where's like a mask?
Traffic cones. Is this thing? Okay. I got it. It's on. All right. The scuba? Okay. Now I need the...
All right. Give me a fan. Where the hell's the fan? There it is. All right. Fan is in use. Let's blow
the smoke out the... Out here. Here we go. Watch out. Move. All right. Where's the last one? Right
up here, right? Isn't it somewhere right here? It's on the outside. It's outside. Outside.
Is this working? No. This is not working. I have to get on... I might have to get on the roof. I have
to use the ladder on the roof. I gotta use the ladder on the roof. Hold on just a minute.
All right. Did you guys ever... Did your parents on Easter ever do this shit where...
For my family, each kid got a string that went around the whole house. And at the end of the
string that went all over the place was your Easter basket. That's what this was. That's what
this is. How long is this? Can I spell my name? Oh, not quite. I was trying to spell Jeremy.
I'm writing an incursive. All right. Fine. I won't write an incursive. I'll do it regular.
It's... I thought it was gonna be easier to write an incursive. All right. I won't write an incursive.
Whoa. Okay. Here's the J. Right? That's done. Now I need E. So I need to go...
It has to be connected. So we'll go to like here. It's a J. Like it's gotta be a big loop, right? E.
No. Fuck. How do you make an E? Just we do... I do all capitals. Yeah. Okay. That makes sense.
Don't fuck this up. Get out of the way. Why is this so long? Why can I do this? I don't even
want to do this, but like it's available. So I'm going to do it. Fuck. Almost done. Almost done.
Relax. Relax. I have to see what it looks like. Okay. M. M is... Okay. Hold on. I gotta fix that.
That looks like shit, but it's okay. And then just Y and I'm done. And I'll go back and I'm
just going to underline it. Okay. Y needs to be straight line up and then split it right here.
Come back. Split it this way. Ah! Ah! Ah! No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's a little messy, but it's fine. We did it. All right. There
it is. I wish I could get a big view. There's Jeremy. Okay. Cool. This thing's still going.
How can water even go through this? Ladder. Press E. What? What do you mean press E? Press E?
Why press E? I don't get it. Why press E? Press E for ladder. This is fucking ridiculous.
Imagine just driving out. This is fucking crazy. Like this is ridiculous. I don't know why you can
do this. All right. E for ladder. E. Press E. What? I can't move. Oh no. Oh, what happened?
What happened? Why is it turning into rabbit food? Oh Jesus. Why can I do this? Use ladder.
No, I can't. I don't want to. I can't. I need to move it. How do I move the ladder up and down?
The game was suffering. Is it in a trunk or something? Like fire. Fan. No. Additional.
Okay. I'm just going to spell my name real quick. J. E. I'm fucking kidding. Relax. All right. How
do I put this down? Okay. So rescue ladder. Here we go. Wait. No, no. This is like a regular ladder.
Hold on. How do I put it down? I have a huge ladder. Why would I need to put the...
All right. I made it. No, I didn't. Honestly, I don't know how to move this big ladder up and
down. Is it inside the car? Like is it in the truck? Like I have to be inside? See? No. Is it
actually on top? No, it's not. Is it? I have to actually be on it. Oh, all right. What the fuck is
this? How far can this go? Q is... Okay. Q E is up. All right. Holy shit. This is high. A little to
the right. All right. A little to the left. All right. That's where I can go. Let's go
down with it. Right here. Okay. Looks good. Press to, press to lock in the ladder. Okay.
Lock in the ladder. All right. Now I'm going to get off and I'm going to get the hose. Lock in. Okay.
Don't worry. I'm fine. All right. Let's go. I'm actually excited for this. I can't. What do you
mean I can't use this tool? Why not? How was that? What am I supposed to... Fuck. Okay. I have to
use regular ladders. Put it, put this away. Put this away. Use the other ladder to get... Oh god
dammit. Don't give me stupid ideas. Okay. That's fine. Is this thing in water? I don't understand.
No shit. How do I spin it? Mouse scroll wheel? Wait, what? Middle mouse button change adjustment.
Okay. Here we go. Good. Right there. All right. It's in perfect position. Give me the hose.
Attach it. Climb the ladder. Use the ladder. All right. Let's fucking go. I can't jump.
Hose on ladder. Put the hose on the ladder. Hose on the ladder. Hose on... Wait. I don't know what
you mean. There's a hose on the ladder. Wait. What do you mean there's a hose on the ladder?
Bring up a fire extinguisher. There's a hose on the ladder. What? What are you talking about?
There's a hose on the ladder? What do you mean apparently? It's built in. Am I even going to make
it from here? Oh my god. There is a hose on the fucking ladder. How do I use the hose? All right.
I'm gonna pull this back. Oh. Oh. Oh. I'm just a giant shower. Did I do it? All right. I'm almost...
This is the stupidest thing.
So much impractical bullshit. You know what? I feel a little dirty today. I think I'm just
time for a shower. I have to get fucking rid of this. Oh no. I don't have to climb all the
way back up. I can make it. No. It's gonna have a stupid... I have a stupid fucking hose in my hands.
Just get off. Get off and fucking go up the hole. Just put this away. It's not soft locked. Put the
hose away. Put the hose... How do I just put the fucking hose away? I just want to put it away.
I want to put the hose away. Okay. Let's go. Get off. The truck is on two wheels? Is it really?
All right. All right. All right. I've had enough. Yes, I have. I've had enough. You're right. I've
had enough. It's over. It's just time to get this done. Wherever this fire is. Where is it?
There it is. Okay. There's more? Is there more? Oh, easy. Easy, easy, easy, easy, easy.
I'm just spraying the street now. Where's this other fire? Pull it back. It's gonna go up. That's
the problem. It has to go up. People are trying to drive. Okay. Seriously. Stop driving. Somebody's
in control of the actual car. Pull it back. There's a fire right there. I see it. I almost got it
right here. Yeah. There it is. There's four more fires here. Where the fuck are these other fires?
Seriously. Where are they? Are they still on the roof? Right here? There's one right there,
I think. The car is just driving without me. There's so many cars. It's all the same car.
All the same car. There's too many white vans in this universe. All right. Here we go. Am I
hitting it? No. There it is. Okay. I got it. Increased traffic. Well, how do I do it? Somebody
give me the data. One more here. Do 100 times traffic. What is it? What is it? Do slash cam
one. It was just car 100. You already did it. Yeah. That's a link with all the commands. Hold on.
All right. Commands list. Resets the vehicle. TP car. I think I have to put it in brackets.
Okay. So, yeah. So, I'm missing the bracket then. All right. Let's try it.
All right. I got to... I don't think I can open up that menu right now. Okay. Slash car 100. Slash car
five. No, guys. I don't think some of these work. Pedestrian number. Example command.
Ped five. No. I don't think these work. Maybe the console commands have to be turned on. I'm
not sure there's a thing in the menu for that. All right. Let me just do this.
Where is this? Right there. Get it. All right. Ped 100. It goes in a line one at a time.
There's only one more left. Where is it? Oh, God. Hold on. All right. We're good. We're good.
There's one more right here somewhere. We're in the edge. There it is. Jeremy, you're going to
drown people. They're going to... All the fires are out. All right. Turn this off.
What? Fire department dispatch. Did I do it? I think I did it. What happens if I collide with
myself here? All right. That's fine. All right. Get off. Get off. Container fire. Let's go.
How do I get off of this? How am I going to get out of here? Are those commands in effect right
now? They might be. Because there's a shitload of cars here right now. Can't use this. I have to
put the mask away. I put this away. Additional. I mean, get rid of my mask. Okay. It's up.
God damn it. Do ped 100. All right. Slash ped 100. I just did it. I did it. I don't know
what's going to happen, but I did it. Okay. Let's go. Where's this water even coming from?
What am I... Right. Fuck. All right. Right. Right. Right. That makes sense. That makes sense.
I just drove in a perfect spot to get stuck. I have to drive as if that's the front of the car.
Pedestrian 100. I don't see that many more pedestrians. Do you? I don't see any more
pedestrians. You're watering people. There's nobody even on the roof here.
Pedestrian 1000. I don't think that shit works. I really don't think that works.
All right. I got this one. All right. Good. Easy. All right. What's next? Anything else?
I don't know why I'm trying to chase this person to carwash them. No, this is just how they make
every Hollywood movie, guys. When it's raining out and there's a big chase scene. Give me another
call. What's going on here? All right. Building fire. You got it. It's right here. In fact,
I'm going to change this up a little bit. Give me one sec. I'm going to make this a little easier.
I have to aim the ladder in a little bit higher. So we're going to pull it up.
It's got to be like a cannon. I will do all these missions instantly. Ready? Watch this.
Okay. Then put it up and we go. Maybe a little bit higher like that. That should be good. Maybe
a little bit right there. All right. We're good. Lock it. Let's go. And then stupid blinker is on
again. Don't go under an overpass. That's right. Don't go under an overpass. Uh-huh. That's a good
call, chat. Uh-huh. Good, good call. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Body, let's get out of here. Okay, Fred. I'll fix
it. Uh, I'm just going to staple this thing. Uh-oh. Oh dear. There we go. Not so hard, is it?
Not so hard. Not so hard. All right. Now I just have to turn it a little bit more like this and
then up. Okay. Bring it down actually a little bit. Don't drive under an overpass. Don't be a
fucking idiot. I can't... Why would you have punching? All right. No overpass. I gotta go this
way. Don't... No emotion for two minutes. Why would I do that right now? I'm full of emotion at the
moment. This is a very... This is... I'm full of... I'm full of it. All right. Let's go. No overpass.
No overpass. Oh no. Overpass. Wait. I got... Okay. I guess I got miraged. I thought that was two
next to each other. I really thought there was two right next to each other. Okay. God damn it. What
the fuck? I thought they were... Look. Look. Look. Look. Look. Look. This is where I was.
It was... The perspective was like this. Like... I was like right here. Look. I thought they were
both the same part of the road. Look. See how they're connected? Ah. So I'm like, oh shit. I
have to go all the way around. I have to go around this. He was blind as a bat. No. That's... No.
That's real. Because I actually do... If I have... If I have sound available, I can hear better.
I would get... Fucking idiot. I can see better if I can hear what's happening.
I think... Okay. I'm... I might be fucked here. Can I push it back on? I think I'm fucked. Yep.
All right. We're going to do something drastic. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. I feel
like I'm not even trying to do this. You know what I mean? Like I'm... I can't... You get stuck on a
curve. Ugh. All right. Here we go. Okay. Done. Pull it in. All right. I don't know if it's just me,
but it's like the running water is starting to give me anxiety. Is anyone getting anxiety
from this water being on the whole time? I kind of am. All right. Let's go. All right. See? Look.
Ugh. All right. We're good. Right there. The diner is on fire again. It's the same diner.
All right. Are we in the right spot? Kind of. I don't want to do this... I don't want to put
this out again. This is... This is the same one. I don't want to do this one again. Why is there a
chainsaw? Okay. Water hose. Let's go attach it. Here we go. Get in. Fires. Where are they?
And I... What? I want to rescue these people this time. Actually rescue.
Is it just the top of the building that's on fire? Oh, come on. Really? What about this side? All
right. This right here. You're cleaning the windows. No, I'm trying... It is outside. I was right.
I was right. I was right. I was right. I was right. So what the fuck? Let me know water supply.
Did I use it all? Dude, get out of the way. Move. Oh my God. You drive me fucking crazy. Get out of
the way. Move. Chainsaw. Hydrant. All right. Hydrant. That's not how this works. Water supply
hose. Okay. Now water hose. All right. Let's go. All right. Is there any of the jobs to do besides
just spray the same building over and over again? Forspawn them with cheats. Cheats don't really
work. I haven't been able to get them to work. These fires are in like some strange places.
Drive. What? Yeah. What does someone have the cheats? That's not that. Where is this fire?
Where's this fire? I can see it, but I can't hit it. Right there. I'm... I know it's right here,
but what the hell is going on? All right. Let me look at the cheats. I want to spawn... I want
to spawn a different mission. Okay. So a command to force the next mission is set. It does not
force the call. It will appear still at random. Cannot be the same twice in a row. Okay. So next
mission underscore ID equals... Oh, no. Underscore ID. Next mission underscore ID. No, no. Just
next mission underscore aggressive driver. This is police. Okay. Fire. Container fire. Building
fire. Vehicle fire. Driver trap. Driver trapped. Cat in a tree. Cat in a tree? Okay. That's kind
of cool. Let's try to do that. Cat in a tree is 2,000. I wonder if it's going to work. Try M
cancel. M... What was it? M cancel? Dash cancel? Oh, shit. It does work. All right. So the cheats do
kind of work. Vehicle fire. No, skip. All right. Let's do cat. Cat. I want a new one of these. I
don't want this anymore. What else we got? Oh, cat stuck in a tree. There it is. Boys and girls,
cat stuck in a tree. Freddy Dredd just dropped a fucking hundred subs. What? Freddy. Holy fuck,
Freddy. Freddy coming in hot again with 100. And they're... They are... Oh, boy. That's a...
That is 100 tier 2 subs. That's tier 2. That's a lot. That's a lot of money.
Tier 2. And the thing is, I don't even have any tier 2 stuff. Holy shit, Freddy. That is
even more to the ridiculous amount of fucking money that you've given this stream. Post the
golden beer. I'm not even sure... Is that still for 10 bucks? Where's my... I'm trapped. Hold on.
I need to get in that building. So I do have... No, I don't. Isn't that... That's a regular one,
isn't it? All right. How do I get into the fire department? Time for you to upgrade. There it is.
Okay. Cat stuck in a tree. I want to spawn just a regular vehicle. Nothing insane. We're going to
heal. $1,000 in one draw. Yeah, that's fucking crazy. Freddy, I can't thank you enough. That's
ridiculous. All right. We're just going to do fire department carb one. Or... No, let's do the...
Should we do every children's toy? Yeah. Honestly, the cat was up in that tree the whole time.
Phylactery. And not to be overshadowed. Phylactery with another 75. So... 75. 69. 75 stuck in my brain.
You guys. Seriously. Holy fuck. All right. Let me put... Phylactery. Thanks for the 69 fucking subs.
Let's go save a cat. We're going to start to be compound subbing. People are going to be
subbed two different times. People are going to get tier... Can you get tier one and tier two at
the same time? Holy shit. But seriously, both of you and anybody that subs this channel. We
talked about it on the New Year's Eve stream, but there's been so much support on this channel.
I just... I'm fucking flabbergasted. All right. How do I get the cat out of the tree? Do I have to
climb the tree with my hands? Where is the cat? I don't see a cat. No cat to return. Ladder. Climb
to... Okay. Cut the tree down. Wait. What? Hold on. Cut the tree down. They don't do this. Don't they
go up? What? What do you mean cut the tree down? Okay. Here's your... Thank you for calling the
fire department. Appreciate it. Have a good rest of your day. Oh my God. Okay. Can we do... I want
to do the cat. I want to do the cat stuck in the tree again. These are fun. These ones are good.
Okay. I want to actually fire... Building fire. No. Skip. I want to actually go climb the tree. I
didn't know you could even do that. He's stalling? What? Who's... Oh, this person's in the way.
He's stalling. No, I want to see the rest of the... I want to see the... You want to see stalling? I'll
show you fucking stalling. You really want to see what stalling looks like? Sure. What happened?
We should go... Oh, never mind. All right. Cat a tree. Let's go. Oh, I'm not doing it right. Cat
stuck in a tree. Okay. Is it her? Let's just... This time just run the tree over with your truck.
Oh, that's so loud. Stop. Get away from me. You're putting on a siren for a cat. Yeah, this is an
emergency. What if the cat like fell? But what if somebody cut the tree down with the chainsaw?
I gotta be prepared. I gotta be ready. I think I can do it. No. No. No. Don't. Don't. Don't. I think
I can do it. I really think it's possible. I do. All right. So it's not possible. Fuck it. Whatever.
You were right. I was wrong. I was wrong. You were right. I was wrong. You were right. And I will
admit that. That's fine. I thought that it was possible that I could go up and over. I might be
able to, but okay. Fine. No, you're right. You're right. You're right. You're right. It's good to
try. You gotta try at least once. I hate going up here. Oh, that's right. There is still police
missions to do. What is that? Why do you have the Hollywood Hills place from GTA 5 here? And there's
always missions over here. All right. There's the tree. Let's go. Enough bullshit. I'm climbing up
there and I'm going to get the cat myself. There we are. All right. No, no, no, no, no, no. I have
to go all the way around. Don't even think about it. You're going to get stuck. Okay. I'm here.
Cat's stuck in a tree. All right. What seems to be the problem? Found the cat. All right. Cat right
here. Give me the ladder. All right. Rescue. Ladder. Looks good. I'm going up. Come here.
There you are. Got you. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Shit. I was going to...
You were going to be my partner. No, I was going to put you in like the front seat and it was
going to be like a funny movie, like a Disney movie. Stop. Come here. Save. I saved the cat.
Who cares? That's two failed cats. That's two rescued cats, actually. There's another cat?
Why is there another cat in the tree? You have two cats. Okay. Well, you have two cats.
Probably you're doing business with you. All right. Let's go. You didn't have clearance to do that?
It was violating... She was violating her neighbor's yard. Vehicle fire. No. All right.
What's any other good ones for fire? Driver trapped? All right. How about driver trapped?
We'll try this one. I don't know. 18. Oh, here comes the cliff joke. All right. Okay. Let's
do... I want to see driver trapped and then we'll do police. I promise. Vehicle incident. No. That's
not it. 18. I'm going to stay up here for a second because just in case it's up here.
I'm not doing this again. Wait, that was it? I thought that was a... Oh, that was it. You monster.
All right. I thought it was vehicle. I thought it was like vehicle incident, not like driver.
I don't know. We've seen like a bunch of vehicle incidents in the same thing. Building fire. No.
Okay. Let's do it. And then it was 18. Come on. Drive that guy off the road. I'm not going to do
that. Come on. Let's go. All right. Driver trapped. Yes. Where is it? I knew I should have stayed
here. Right? See? I told you. Wait, where is that? No, that's really far away. Is this a beach in
this game? This place... Why is everything in this same... This is a huge map. Jesus. This is actually
a giant map. Like that was not meant to be a joke. I'm serious. Like that was just quicker to get
down here. That's not... Oh, look at me. I'm jumping off a cliff. No, that's... I'm just trying
to get here fast. Minus one. Yeah, I know. That's fine. You can do that. Explaining the joke doesn't
make it funny. It would have taken me so much time. Wrong way. I know. I... This is how I drive in
I'm telling you. I'm sorry. It happens every single time I play any game. I drive on the other side
of the road. Something about it is easier for my brain to understand. In a video game. Like I drive
my car every fucking day. Let's be realistic here. I don't... I don't know why. And I missed the turn
because I'm sitting here just yapping. I can't even go over the medium. I have to turn around.
I have to turn around. God damn it. I gotta spin this car around. Admit it. You have a butler drive
you places. I don't have a butler. Get the fuck over here. I gotta go... Who put these cones in?
There's not even any construction. Fuck. No. Why does this have to keep happening to me?
I can't even... Why does this have to happen to me? This keeps happening to me.
When things like this keep happening to you, you're the problem. You know what I mean? Like
I'm the problem here. This... Oh wait. Why did I get stuck here? When it happens every time,
the problem I think is probably you. You know? It's me. All right. Fuck off with this. He's driving
on the wrong side of the road and he finally... He says maybe I'm the problem. Not right there.
I was driving normally there. Is this a Sim City highway? And these carriages all over the place,
aren't they? All right. Vehicle... Vehicle incident. Here we are. What's the problem?
I don't know. Somebody's... Who's trapped? Oh, okay. What is it called? A spreader? This just looks
like a camel spider. Okay. How do I get it in? Now what? Okay. Got it. How do I put this... All right.
Now get him out. What? Do I have to pull him out? Why do I have to pull him out? Aren't you an EMT?
Where'd you get that cool EMT outfit? Interact using medbag. That's you. That's this person's
job. I don't have a medbag. What? Yeah. Wait. Hold on. I have to do this? Breathing. Conscious.
Possible neck injury. Yeah. I got you. Wait. What did that say? Okay. Do CPR? I don't think I can do
CPR while he's inside of the car. You can't perform CPR on this person. Can't use this.
How do I do CPR? What's this guy doing? Why is he doing like mime work? Tree blocking road. I'll take
it. I can't move. Okay. There we go. All right. No, no, no. Time to... I want to be a police officer.
Did you just get in my car? What the fuck? No. All right. I want to be a police officer. Let's go.
And then we can move on. I'm interested though. How do I TP? TP slash HQ. Here we go. All right.
Let's go to the police department. He's cheating? Yes. Sorry. I'm cheating in flashing lights. Is
there a single game that you don't cheat in? Wait. Why is everybody so concerned about me teleporting?
I'm just TP. I'm not using cheats right now. All right. Here we go. Wait. Okay. Change to police.
Okay. Let's do tall guy. Hat. And shades. No. Wait. I'm going to get VAC banned. Office of Jecks.
This isn't supposed to be a fantasy game. Yes it is. Because it's something I'm not doing in real
life. All right. What's here? What's going on here? Register suspect. All right. Select vehicle. What
do I want for a car? Police car. Police car. This one. Get the tank. Oh, there it goes. Armed robbery
in progress. Let's go. It's in progress right now. Like right here. This car is fast. Really fast
actually. All right. Armed robbery. Here we go. How do you arrest people? Oh no. Armed robbery at
the diner. This diner. It would suck to be somebody that worked. They're shooting at me? It's the same
dot. How do I use a gun? All right. Wait. Wait. Trunk. Weapon two. What? I don't know. People are
running at me. I don't know. Why do you have a fan in here? What? Wait. Can I get revived by a BMT?
Wait. Suspect on foot. Suspect on foot. Suspect on foot. Quick. Get me. Get me. Get me. Get me. Get
me. Get me up. Up. Up. Up. Up. Up. Revive me. Come on. Don't let her get away. Don't let her get away.
She's not getting away. She ain't getting away. Revive me. Why is there a fan in here? What are
they doing? Let's go. Come on. They're gonna get away. I have to arrest them. How do I say like
you're under arrest? Am I not gonna be... Am I dead? Permanently. What just happened? Come on.
Give me like ten. I think they're fucked up. All right. I have to respawn at the station.
I can't. The whole thing is fucked up actually. Yeah. It's all fucked up. I can't. R is not doing
anything anymore. I'm gonna TP. All right. TP. TP HQ. The suspect is coming back. What?
Dead body TP. Is the suspect gonna come back into the diner? Shit. Okay. How do I like... Is there
any like force... They're coming back down here. Somebody stop that person. Okay. I'm dead. Oh,
it's over. Is there like a force reset or something? What is it? How do I like force
reset? There's gotta be something here. Car. Reset. The resets vehicle. Cancels mission.
All right. So M cancel. Let's try M cancel. Okay. And then V reset. Can I fucking come back to life?
There's a fight going on in progress. No. God damn it. Come on. Wait. Where's the fight? There's a
fight in progress? Where's the fight? All right. Come on. Robot. Oh boy. All right. All right. I
gotta... I can't even hit escape. I'm gonna reset the game. I'm just gonna reset the game. Give me
a sec. Let's get an alt F4. I'm gonna spawn as a cop. It's fine. Yeah. I can press R and do anything.
It's all good. I'm coming right back. That was only one mission. That's not fair.
Coming back. Here we are. Why is my car flipped? It's because I spawned it in front of me or
something weird. I have no idea. Okay. Let's go. You want this as high as possible. 99.
99. Don't matter. Parked vehicle density. Medium. Time of day. Fuel consumption. Who cares?
Don't read this. I don't know. I'm not gonna. I'm not gonna read the rest of that. Whatever it was.
Have I ever played city skylines? I have never played city skylines and I've never played sim
city. I have no idea. I've seen random stuff. I feel like I'm too stupid to play it.
You're not. I feel like it's too. I have to learn a lot and I'm not. I'm too
all over the place to be able to learn it correctly. He played sim city on DOS and it was a disaster
and I played it for like 15 minutes and realized I was not going to be able to. I was incapable.
City skylines is easy. All right. Well, put it on the list. I have 60 PC games and Wii games and
and GameCube games and PS2 games. I've got so many games. You have no idea. All right. Let's go.
Aggressive driver in red vehicle. Ram or pit? All right. Let's go. Aggressive driver.
Use spike strips? We're gonna have to try that. All right. Where are they? All the way down there.
Give me a break. Do I really have to go all the way down there? Is this game one of them? This game
was one of them. This is one of like 62 games. Wait. Open the map. Where is it? All right. Down
this way. Oh, this was recommended. I pulled a lot of these from the recommended channel. So
this was on there more than once. I'm going 120. All right. Where are you at? Aggressive driver.
Block the car. Ram it or use spike strips? Am I supposed to use spike? I think I could go in front
of them. I could go in front of them and do spike strips. Where are they? This person wasn't even
aggressive. They were driving normally. You were driving normal. All right. Get out of the car.
Out. Get out of the car. All right. Out. Get out of the car. Driving recklessly. Get out of the car.
Suspect compliance. Okay. What do you mean suspect compliance? Arrest? You got on ran.
All right. Come here. How do I interact? Wait. Okay. Arrest? How do you arrest?
Ask? Wait. Hold on. Alcohol test. Blow into this. All right. Okay. Let's. Hold on. Interact.
You're under arrest. No, I can't. Come here. Ask for your ID. What was it? Brandy Alvarez. Okay.
Wait here. Okay. Handcuffs. You're under arrest. Okay. Let's go.
I don't know. Not in the trunk. No. No. No. Hold on. I need to be standing out of the way.
Oh, come on. Oh, well. Wait. What am I actually? No, I'm not. What? What? What you? Why can you do
that? Why can you do that? Why can you do that? You should not be able to do that
as a police officer. Why are they in the trunk? Okay. What? Why is this still on the list?
Block the car? Oh my god. Why? Hold on a minute. I am so confused. I can't believe you can do this.
Why? There's no reason for that. No, no. I'm taken. I'm under arrest. Why is it still happening?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Seriously. I need to ask a real question. Why is it still happening?
She's under arrest. Why is there green blip still on the screen? Oh, request a tow. Okay. All right.
All right, let's go. That's gonna be done, right? This car fucking screams. Not into the ocean. Not
into the ocean. Not into the ocean. Locate and stop. I did it. Suspect neutralized.
The car. The car is gonna arrest yourself. Transport to courthouse.
You got it. Who? Oh, get out of the car. Get out. Out. Out. Quick. I'm fine. Who needs to go to the
courthouse? Pick up at police station at the back entrance. Do we have a car? Oh, okay.
Transport suspect. There he is. Come here. You got anything on you? I don't know. You got nothing
up your nose? Okay, that's good to know. Cool. All right. Handcuff this fucking guy. All right.
Breathe into this. Okay, fine. Return your item. Okay, let's go. Commands. Follow me.
Don't try anything fucking crazy. Wait. What do I have to bring him? Transport to... Oh, I'm... Okay,
wait, wait, wait, wait. I need to... Okay, I need a car. All right. Here. Yeah, I'll take off those
handcuffs. Now you... Okay. Wait here. Don't go anywhere. Don't do anything. Okay. I need a car.
All right. Get in the car. Come with me. Let's go. Yeah, I got this guy's ready for his court date.
Open up the fucking trunk. It'd be like, what the fuck are you doing, dude? Ah, you know,
I was transporting. All right. Shit. No, no, it's all right. Don't worry. I poked like six
air holes in the trunk. Where is this? Wait, what? Okay. Wait, do we have to watch this guy's trial?
All right. Let's go. What is going on? I don't... I don't think that's such a good idea.
That's not a great idea. You go out a little bit. You go out a little. You go out. Guy's out of
bullets. He's out of bullets. He's out of bullets. He's out of bullets. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Give
me the... Wait. Get back in the trunk. Get back in the trunk. Come here. Ah, you shit me up.
Yeah, we'll see, motherfucker. You and your friends. What is going on? Speed radar? Wait,
what is going on? Why am I... Wait, who has a... Why am I... Radar? Which one is the suspect?
Wait, wait, wait. How do I... You guys are all a bald guy with a tank top.
Wait, stop. Get this off. Shut this down. Hey, don't move. Freeze. Come here. Get up. Get up.
Give me your ID. Eddie Scott. Okay. Eddie Scott, wait here for a second.
Eddie, you fucker. Eddie. Eddie. Eddie. Where'd he go? There he is. He ain't gonna get fucking far
from me. Eddie. Eddie. That's right. He ain't going anywhere. Stop moving. Stop. Eddie,
get over here. You're under arrest. I mean, wrong guy. What the fuck are you talking about?
This is Eddie Scott. Let's go, Eddie. Get in here. Aw. Get in there. Wait, who the fuck are you,
then? Who are you? Are you... No, okay, this is Andrew. All right, all right. Okay. Wait a minute.
What do you got on you? Okay. Are you drinking? Okay. All right, let's go. Okay, I got like... I'm
gonna have... I'm gonna fill my car with this bald guy. I have room for one more. One of them
would be correct. Transport subject to the... Didn't I already do that? Wait. All of you just
follow me. Come here. One of them will be right. Okay. Everybody follow me. Follow. You too. And
you as well. And... And I'm no longer gonna play the game. I'm gonna have as many bald
guy with a tank top as I possibly can follow me. Maybe up to 100 to 200 of them. God damn it.
This is not good. Uh, fuck. Don't you dare run away. They're not... Okay, they're no longer
following me. Where are they going? Where are they going? You're supposed to be following me
and instead you're trying to run away? No. Okay. Remember, if you see a bald guy, they have to join
the group. I'm gonna Agent Smith the fuck out of this. All right, let's go. I think they're too
stupid. All right, whatever. They don't move that fast. Can I even punch anybody? Punching doesn't
even do anything. All right, get over here. Register. It's not you. Where is it? It's you.
It's one of the three of yous. Come here. Register. There it is. Okay. Now the two of you.
Why is it sub only? Uh, I don't know. I think there was a bunch of spam or something. I don't know.
Uh, you know what? Like you guys can just stay here. I don't care.
Oh, it was bad. Okay. Yeah, that makes sense. Yeah. I'm just dropping them off. They can stay there.
Possible drunk driver. Where? Reports of erratic driver to pull over any suspected
drivers and check alcohol levels. What? Follow vehicle plus left control? Wait, somebody's drunk driving?
He's gonna get away. He's gonna get away. No.
All right. What about this person? Pull over. Follow vehicle and then plus left control. All
right. You pulled over. Pull over. All right. You pulled over. Pull over. Follow until the
driver stops the vehicle. All right. Get out. Excuse me, sir. Uh, as you were. As you were.
Uh, I think. Well, you're free to go because ain't nobody in here. Oh, you're definitely drunk.
All right. Okay. Get out. You drunk fucking ghost. Pull over. Excuse me, sir. Okay. I'm gonna have to
license registration, please. Oh, it looks like in before you were a ghost, you were a bald guy with
a tank top. Interesting. Hmm. You have any alcohol recently? You do any drugs? Why can I do these?
Illegal items? Um, get out of the car. Okay. You've been drinking? All right. Okay. All right. Fine.
Fine. Go ahead. Have a nice rest of your day. I need to. Is there so many parked cars on the street?
Hey, have you been drinking, ma'am? Okay. Uh, license registration, please. Chris. Uh, Rochelle
Christensen. Okay. All right. Here's your fucking ticket, please. You were speeding.
Uh, you were going fucking. I don't need to give you a reading. You're on this row. There's your name.
Uh, driver's name. License plate number. There it is. Uh, I don't know. Fucking A, B, C, D, E, F, G.
Fine amount. Uh, $70. Date and time issued by officer David two. Have a nice day.
Oh, well I gotta get this right. M six four five two E. Okay. What? What do you mean? That's wrong?
How is that wrong? M, M six four five. What was that? All three of you were drunk. Hold on. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Details. No reading. All right. Well,
fucking whatever. Just so, Hey, I'll let you off of the, I'll let you have a warning this time.
Get out of here. All right. I got to catch that guy. Dude. The problem is everybody is driving
like a fucking idiot. So how am I supposed to tell who's drunk driving? You know what I'm saying?
Like everyone's bumping. How am I supposed to tell? It's definitely this guy. It's this guy
right here. Like it's this dude. Okay. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. It's you.
All right. I have a license registration please. Okay. Um, any alcohol? Why can I say this? Tests.
Uh, I want to do an alcohol test on you please. Result zero. How is that possible? What? What?
Did you see, you saw how she was driving, right? Look at this shit. Did I just get
the gay baited by the game? She was going left, right, left, right, left, right, left, right.
I'm never going to find this person. Am I? Wait, did I, what did I say? Be gated, get baited?
What? What? Wait, what did I say? Get baited. I said you baited. Clip it. I want to hear it. What?
You said gay baited. Wow. Get baited. I need to hear it. That's fucking crazy.
I said it as two words. I get baited. I need to hear it. That's not you guys. That's incorrect.
No, that's me saying Eddie. I should, I'm going to have to skip this one because this,
I don't think I'm going to be able to do this. I'm so, I'm so confused.
Baited by the game? I say game. All right. All right. Let's go. I was going to say,
why would I say that? Why would I say it like that? That's odd.
All right. I'm going to follow this person. Turn off the sirens. I'm not even in the area anymore.
Am I even going to be able to find this person? I don't think I'm going to be able to find this
person. I'm going to have to skip this one. 0.0. All right. Have, goodbye. Free to go. Goodbye.
I'm never going to find this. I have to skip this one. Yeah. Oh, you, yeah. You can play
this game online. Yeah, I know. I wasn't sure how stable it was. What about that person?
Respond code one with your police radio. Wait, how do I do that? How do I open up that thing
that I had? No, not that. What was that? How did I get that menu? Come here. Pull over. Pull over.
Catch the fleeing suspect. I knew something was up. That didn't take very long. God damn it. Come
on. Really? Is somebody still in my trunk? Get in the car. All right. You're under, stay flipped
over. You're under arrest. He's going to keep, motherfucker. You're in fucking, you're in deep
shit. Okay. Into the trunk. Always into the trunk. Like this guy. I thought about it, but there's a
barrier. Nope. I'm going to do, what are some of the other police missions that I could just have
set up? Let's see. There's, I want to fight. I want to, see, I want to see the one that's a fight.
It's the fire department. Get out. Get out. You're going to fucking jail. Let's go. I just want to see
what they do. All right. This guy, book him. Book this guy. Oh, come on. Do I really have to go all
the way around? I just want to see what it does. I'm just going to test it on myself. Here we go.
Book him. Frisk the suspect. All right. What do you got on you? You got a weapon on you?
Oh, this is an ID card. That's it. All right. Book him. First name, Jonathan. Last name,
signature. David too. You got it. All right. Let's go. All right. I want to do fight.
What is it? Uh, M N M M N. Oh, let's do fight. And I'm going to take a pee break
and I'll come back and see what we're going to do. Let's test these strips. They don't work on me.
Fight in progress. Okay. Where, where's this fight in progress? Oh, it's all the way down here.
It's hard to turn. It's just the GTA five map. Is it really? No, it's not.
Is it? I'm confused. Is it really? All right. Is it, was this fight fight in progress? All right.
Um, oh, she's not shooting at me. Okay. Herman, you're in trouble. Weapon. What's the weapon?
What's the weapon? Actions. Get weapon. How do I get the weapon? Give me the weapon.
Let's give it back. Hold on. Stop. Stop. Stop. Just, okay. Come here. Stop. Oh, I can actually say
stop. Stop. Oh, I can wait. Stop. No, I fucking pulled you over. Breathe into this place. All
right. You're under rest. You, you got a weapon. You fighting. Let's go. Wait, it's right here.
Breathe into his remote. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. This is all right. All
right. Okay. Okay. Officer needs. I'm all right. I'm going to go pee and then we're going to see.
I've been playing this for three hours. I'm still enjoying it though, for some reason. I don't know
why I still, what is this? What the hell is this? What is this? Oh, it's a taser. It's a remote
person with a gun. All right. I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to tase this person.
I didn't know I had all these weapons. All right. Tase the last game blue time for Nancy Drew. No,
no, no, no, no, no. Don't piss yourself. I'll be fine. No, no, Nancy Drew. Not today. Not today.
All right. Tase. How far does it go? This is that person with a gun. Okay. There's a person with
gun. Yup. They sure, it sure is. It's kind of person of parking ticket. Okay. Stop. Stop. All
right. I don't want to have to do this. Traffic cop.
I got one last parking ticket down before I went. Okay. The person has a dozen bullet holes in their
car and they come back to a parking ticket. Oh, that's fucked up. All right. This guy's mine.
Where'd you go? Wait, he's across this way. Hold on. Here he comes. All right. Very easy.
Can I say stop? Stop. What's the range on this thing? He's running right to the police station.
I missed. God damn it. It's, you gotta be real close. What? How long is it? All right. Come here.
How do I, you're under arrest. Weapon. All right. Uh, requesting a transport. He's, he's trying to
get away. Quest transport please. Oh, we're right there. Okay. Nevermind. Uh, sorry. Someone will
get you. I don't even know I had this. All right. Let's go. Oh shit. No, no, no, no, no. I'm just
go on your way. It's a bald guy. That's how you know he's a criminal. They can't get over here.
I think the game's broken. Oh, here they go. Here we go. You know what? Whatever. Just,
there we go. Here you go. Good. Very good.
Okay. Nobody gets like scared. Okay. All right. That's it. I'm going to move on. That's it.
Interact with who? Wait, what? Oh, he's running over the body over and over again. He's stuck on the
guy's body. This is fucked up. Hey. All right. All right. Okay. All right. That's enough. Stop.
Stop. Stop this right now. Stop. Stop the car. Get out of the car. Out of the car. Get out of the car.
Out of the car. Get out of the car. Get out of the car. Get out of the car. I don't think this even
does anything. No, this doesn't do anything. This doesn't do anything. The glass doesn't break.
Watch out. All right. I think I've seen everything I can see in this game. This is pretty,
pretty interesting. Has to be from the other side. No, it does not. No. See, it's not doing anything.
All right. Let me go to the bathroom. I'll figure out what we're going to do. Some nice cars.
Wait, what? Oh. Take out all the tires. All right. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out.
I'll be back in a minute. I'm going to go pee and we'll come back and do something else.
I'm trying to exit the game. Okay. I'll be right back.