Your tail is my favorite game ever made. Hey guys, how you doing? Hopefully things are going well.
That is banana. That is peanut butter. And that is almond milk. One, two, three. The trifecta.
Jeremy, what's the latest smoothie that you're drinking right now? Because every six months
you talk about a smoothie. Well, hold on a minute here. Banana. One banana. Two scoops of
peanut butter. Almond milk. Into a glass. Slurp it up. I got coffee here too. I got a peanut
butter banana smoothie and I got a coffee. That was a blender, yeah. Am I doing well? I'm
doing well. I'm doing good. I'm doing good. So tonight we're going to play a game called
The Quiet Man, which is a Square Enix game. Kind of flew under the radar here for me,
but it's an FMV game that is also not an FMV game. It's like an action game with choices and
you play the main character is deaf. So I don't, you can't like hear. I don't know.
It is apparently awful, but it looked pretty, it looked like I had to play it. We'll just put
it that way. This game isn't fun bad. It's bad bad. Well, we'll have to, I'm gonna stomach
through it. I don't think it's more than, I think it's only three or four hours long.
That's, let's just do it, right? Should I, am I going to be able to do this?
Or will I give up? The game isn't fun at all.
Here's something about, let's get out of here. Let's take a look at this.
Here's the menu. All right. So this is, this is one of the menus. Look at this menu.
Any idea what this shit is? When I, when I first loaded the game, it said,
this is subtitles and that's, they're on. This is supposed to be difficulty. So I think this is
mom yelling at little kid who's scared, but then this is normal mode. This is hard mode
where a little kid gets a Mario mushroom and screams at mom. I don't know how this means
it's harder. Like, is this, is that supposed to be me in this scenario? And this is the game.
Shouldn't it be the other way around? Or is this supposed to be me and this is the game?
Well, anyway, I don't, I have no idea what this is. They didn't tell me what this was.
It's just, this is a group of people that are highlighted now. I don't know what this is.
Door? What do you mean door? Just hit play? What do you mean by door? Hold on. Kim,
Kim is like texting me. Hold on a second. It was very, I ran down there and she,
she kept saying door. She's pointing at the door. I was like, okay, I opened the door
and then there's nothing there. Anyways, let's play. This is the quiet man. I think it's in
the right settings. I'm just going to press play. Door bottom right. All right. All right.
Let's go. Seattle, 1998, New York. I mean, is this Spider-Man? Spider-Man full motion video
experience. That's me. I got, I've got the black Spider-Man suit on. I've got the venom suit on.
Wait, isn't this how infamous starts a prototype? I like that hair. That's good hair.
He's got great hair. This is a Square Enix game by the way. They, I don't know what they had
to do with this, but they apparently published it or maybe they made it. I don't know.
Do I get to control the character? Why is the guy not talking? Why is he just putting his
sandwich in a bag? I didn't even order anything. This guy is just getting his lunch ready.
It's the sound. Does it make it quiet? Oh shit. I'll turn it up. I'll turn it up.
I'll turn it up. Oh, peanut butter and jelly again. Dad, can I at least get some
tuna fish next time? Remember that? Write that down. That's a map.
Now this guy steps to my lady and says, wait,
I'm not reading it.
Where'd the subtitles go? Why, why am I walking down this alley right now?
Is there a reason why I'm doing this?
Am I like a crime fighter? I don't understand. What am I doing?
Am I like trying to find back alleyways of people doing things wrong?
These guys are just sitting around talking. Okay, here we go.
What do I do? Do I have to press a button? Do I press a button?
Am I supposed to punch? I didn't do any of that.
Am I a robot? I'm a robot built by someone to patrol or something.
Now we're no longer a full motion video game. Now we're CG. How do I throw punches?
Who do I target? What? Oh, I'm being electrocuted. This is immersion. What?
No, it's got the controller. It's got the controller.
How am I? What am I? How do I punch?
It didn't even tell me how to play the game. Okay, that's it. I did it.
Where is my tutorial? Where am I?
Weren't we just in full motion video? Why did we downgrade?
Is there a reason why the graphics is downgraded?
Well, wouldn't this be, this would cost more money doing full CG animations.
This costs more money than getting actors to act in front of the camera.
Options. Why does it give me the options, man? Why are they watching
a TV channel with options, man? Were they just playing Call of Duty and had to stop
because I came in? I don't understand. I think I lost.
This is, I don't like this. This is weird. Great stock footage.
What? Okay, so they have stock footage like hello, baby. I'm like kissing you. Hi, baby.
I'm a baby in a crib. Okay, this is a dodge. It's not very useful.
At least I have like a super dash. Is there anything else I can do?
At least a grab. Can I lock? What the fuck is happening?
Okay, left trigger activates quiet mode or something.
Oh, that's right. It is on hard. This is not, I didn't, this,
this lower frame rate is proving to you that I'm not playing the game anymore.
This is a rendered, uh, full rendered motion. What the fuck are you showing me?
Oh, this is, I can't, I get it. It's the controls. I see. Okay.
So the X is punch. A is dodge. Wait, what was that? If you dodge perfectly,
then you get to punch him. B is also punch, somehow.
Why is kick? But why was grab? This is super mode. This is sprint.
Oh, no, that's not what I wanted to do. How do I get out of this? No.
Okay. The end. You beat it. So there's a sprint.
I don't know where I'm supposed to be going. Here we are. Back in time, I guess.
That me? That's supposed to be me. That guy did a pretty good green screen. That guy did.
You know, I mean, I mean, you stand in front of a green screen and you make a bunch of
all of a sudden, like now everybody wants to do it. Is there a lock on? I don't think there is.
I'm pretty sure there's no lock on. This has to be getting to a point where I can do something
else, right? Why are you watching me crying? Why? Why is it super imposing this shit on the
screen? What's going on? I don't even know what to say. I have nothing to say. I thought
we might have some stuff to talk about here, but we don't. We just don't. I'm beating the whole game,
by the way. Can you please play something else? Not yet. Nice. I got him in the tub. I did that.
I just got an achievement that says, Oh, what to say. I don't know what to say.
I'm not. I don't know who we are. I don't know why we're doing this. I don't know. All
I know is we got lunch in a bag. That's it. I was given a bag lunch club, club normies.
No, we're good. Jeremy, can you turn the game up? I can't hear it. I can't hear it either.
How am I supposed to make the decision? Should I make decisions?
You can't. I can't make any decisions. Well, that's mine now. Dub it. Okay. Yeah.
I can't think of anything. Hold on. I gotta take this.
I was just like a lip matching it. Now here we go.
20. Let's see. 40. 60. $100. There it is in the case.
Oh, you made it here. Finally. Didn't think you were going to show up.
Did you get lost out there somewhere? 25. 50. Yeah. $50. So here, here's all the money we took
in from. Oh, briefcase. Is that new? Wow. And you were the only person to remember my birthday.
And I love Coke. I'm really glad you got this for me. Anyone watch you bring this in? I mean,
right on the chin. Me and you are going to do it together right now. Right. Anyways.
Let me take a look. Well, I know them. Yeah.
I actually was there when he drew it. I told him it looked like shit, but
he didn't want to correct it. I told him it should look more like a
Jackson Pollock painting than anything else, but he didn't want to listen.
What a weird, what a fucking idiot. You know what I mean? But you,
you could do a much. Hey, what's up? I'm trying to help you here. If you have run
to the chin, we're supposed to be doing this Coke right now and you are going to
rip the phone out of my hand. That's unbelievable. My fucking birthday, man.
Anyway, I have to, you know, if you want to go on a date with me, and how's the time to say it?
The body, mother of Christ compels us. Remember when we were kids, I've got your shoes.
Give me my shoes back. No, they're mine. Oh, I gotta help someone. Hold on.
I gotta help someone. Hold on. Hey. All right. Yeah, those shoes, they were expensive,
very expensive. And I'm glad that you came over there and screamed at them,
but it didn't really help that much. Oh, I just broke my finger. Oh, it's all right.
These motherfuckers are strong. Yeah. Yeah. To you, to us. I'll meet you outside. Five
million. This is way harder. This is hard. Have a look. What do you think?
I was thinking of sending it to her. You know, okay, sure. If I wanted to see her,
see her kids again, you know, what do you think? Is it too much? Yeah, I think it might be.
Took me a long time to make it though. I am the business of ransom. It's just,
you know, not easy. Maybe you could go there and convince them. Yeah. Well, you,
you don't have the superpowers. I don't have any superpowers. Come on.
I just wanted to make a couple extra dollars, make some more millions.
Press one for refund. Play for one hour and then refund.
Oh, I wish I had like other items here. How long do they get to hold it here before
I burn my hand? I'm going to say probably 10 seconds. And that's why I say,
I burnt my hand already. Were you thinking about something?
I just can't even imagine, you know, it's really, let me tell you something,
you know, it really pisses me off lately. The whole, it's, I mean, it's not even Thanksgiving
and I mean, I see, I see. Hold on. Words with friends just popped up. I am the pretty much
number one in the region of words with friends. So sorry, I'm going to take an extra minute
here. Christmas decorations. You know what I'm saying? I want to punch them. I'd love,
I'd love to punch a Christmas decoration in the face. You know what I'm saying? Like
right in the face. Oh, with a shovel or a rock. Not even Thanksgiving yet.
Like, you know, a rope maybe. Sprangle. Yeah. You and me. We're going to go vandalize
Christmas decoration. Why is this? Oh, King's words. I want you to imagine this. If this,
if there wasn't a dub here. It's a five minute silent cut scene. What does it want me to do?
I have, oh, go over to the flowers. Am I going to eat them? Is this actually supposed
to be muted? Yeah. What is this? Turn up the volume. There is no volume. That's like the
point of the whole game. There is no sound. I don't, it's not that I have the volume
turned down. There is no volume. Turn on subtitles. They're already on, but there's a splash screen
at the beginning of the game that says, hey, subtitles are on, but you're not going to see
them unless it's in a specific situation where you can actually hear them. Wow. The iPhone sure
did get fucking good. That was the best photo I think I've ever seen. That's like iPhone
16. Again, I'm going to reiterate this point one more time. Go to a stock footage site and
type in like woman smiling in bed or makeup commercial or toothpaste commercial.
One of those three will do. I was, I was specifically told before the stream started,
do not play this game. It's not funny. It's just, it's just not even good. But I,
well, we can, we're going over for free. What if I just don't move?
All right. Those are the moves you make when your cat's going crazy and you're like a
afraid of what it's going to do next. That's somebody that there's like a, there's a cat or
a dog in the room and they're like, oh, oh, hold on. Those are the moves you made during
the green screen. Well, you guys know what to do. Hey, you got to pay for that. Grab,
throw. That was a pretty nice knee. This won the golden joystick award over red dead.
No, it did not. It did not. I'm sorry to say it's the same two moves.
What? You got back up. Why is he getting back up? Oh, now he has a saw. Oh wait,
I thought this was still in the subway. I'm not dubbing this scene. Okay. Lazy streamer. No,
I can't. Lame. What? Are you serious? Are you serious? Well, I get to be the only person
that's ever beaten this game on stream. Do you think that's a 100% guarantee? Maybe I'll
get invited to Square Enix's next launch party. That was pretty nice. Dude, this is just a
wrestling game. He's gotten four sweet chin musics in a row. He should be done. No,
he has a knife. Can I pick up the machete? What? Just now all of a sudden you can block.
These are identical to my green screen kicks. The boss, this is a boss, isn't it?
Now we got to wait for the train. Skip to the next game. It's only been 30. I
feel like I've been here for two hours. It's been 30 minutes. No, no, this is lame. No.
Get off me. Yeah. My son, I think. I can't do a dog. Hold on. Yes, I can.
I can't do a dog. Hello. My phone just actually rang. She's calling me. You had
that ready? I swear to God. No, I just got a phone call right now. I did not have that ready,
but you told me to freeze. Was it a dead bird? This is not CG. This is, instead of FMV dad,
this is CG dad. Right this way? Hey, thanks. Yeah, you can close it. Nervous. I'm so
nervous about this. I mean, we had our troubles, but it's worth a shot to see.
Funny you to show up. Well, got the flowers. Oh, I forgot you're allergic. Sorry. You want?
Hey, shut up. You just look handsome and light here. Do I? Maybe we could potentially
work things out tonight. It's hard. Oh, uh, you know, I tough to come out here like this
and try to, you know what I'm saying? I know what you're saying. Hey, uh, hold on. Will you?
No, he's already school. He's with me. I don't know who the fuck this guy is.
Just thinks you're gonna walk in here. Hey, uh, sorry. Um, fuck are you doing? You know,
I'm trying to fucking fix this here to get that fucking out of here. You brought a dead bird.
What do you bring a dead bird over to me and my ex? Fucking idiot. Don't look. I know we play
the pretend detective game together and we try to find the criminals, but this is not the
time of the place, dude. Go home. Call mom. Okay, uh, we're back here. He just got lost.
This guy, I don't really know him. He got lost. But, um, anyways, so dinner tomorrow night,
potentially, if you, if you could have me. Hey, what the, why did you just do that? Oh,
no, no, you can't get. So, uh, I get how my, my little brother is going to come with
us. And, um, that's ain't fucking awkward at all. Is it? Your little brother sucks.
Just be easy on him. He's kind of a weirdo. He's a dead bird in the car. It just might
stink a little bit. It probably smells like a dead animal, but just,
he's a little weird. Just let him, let him be.
He went from potential boyfriend to little brother. Mike is muted.
So, um, can I see the bird? I love birds. Is it a sparrow or maybe a chickadee or something
like that? You don't have to be shy. I was going to say it's a blue Jay. Please voice
the main character. Please stop playing this. I can't, I can't. Do you understand? Hey,
let's try something here. I mean, I need to compose myself. Hold on. You know, I,
I like to collect birds. This is not good. I know I'm trying. You decide if you want to
play this crap or not. All right. The achievement I just got is called Stargazer
storm chaser. Everyone's just going on dates. Sorry. Club normies.
Welcome to club normies. Come on in. This is where the joke's so good. You made it twice.
No, I have this too many people here. I can't, I can't keep this up with like a hundred
people. This wine's delicious. Oh, that's a good Scott.
Important. This is really important. I don't fucking care. It is important.
So you guys have to deal with this. I can't receive a phone call right now. This is too
important. Okay, here we go. The song goes out to my, one of my closest friends in the
audience right now, dedicated to them because they mean so much to me. Nice.
It's time. Yeah. Oh, no, no, I'm not supposed to pull the fire on quick. Get like a
chair. Oh, wait. Hey, hey, hey. Oh, it's electric. That guy sneezed. No.
If you want to see her again and you'll be in trouble.
Come here.
Now there really is no sound. Did I break it? Make punching noises.
I need more sounds to do that. Um, is this guy going to go down?
Oh, so, so long ago, the bird kid long. I've waited for this moment.
Maybe we'll see what you have boss fight boss fight. This is the
flamest fucking boss fight I've ever seen. This guy sucks. No, no, no. Don't let him do it.
I'm just absolutely ratatatatting this guy's head. He's still going.
You can't match my strength. You didn't even say that. Somebody dubbing over it did.
No, my sniper rod.
No, don't. Yeah, that was my plan. Get. Oh, get me that car. Somebody call the police on
that car. Somebody call the police. It's so unnecessary. You just did that for the cameras
that are obviously there. What's this? Oh, more fighting. Gas station. We're fighting
in front of the gas station right now. Dodge. I feel like that's how I would dodge in a fight.
Nice. Broke his concentration. That was a pretty good combo over the car. Okay. Um, I
think like I really like people probably work hard on this. There's probably a lot of
talented people with talented coders and stuff. But if I'm the executive producer at Square Enix
and you showed me that last, this last hole, maybe five minutes, 10 minutes here,
I'd probably be like, okay, yeah, that's uh, okay. And I would, I would turn around
and I would do the bite my finger thing. Like, Oh fuck. Did I lose? That's a great
thumbnail. That's a really good thumbnail. I told you I was a baby. Everybody talked shit.
What do you mean baby? Question marks, baby. I'm the baby there. And she's looking at me going,
Oh, look, there's my little baby. The camera shaking so much. I mean, like the actual
full motion video scenes that look like a lot went into them. How old am I? This character?
Um, well, if I was a baby, then I don't know, like seven or eight years have gone by.
I'm probably nine. Nice. How, why, how would I have caught up with this car?
That is like an extraordinary amount of non-damage. You get out of that car. For a second,
I thought that guy was not going to notice I did that. Oh, come on. No, I want to run behind
the car. That guy was just doing laundry or something. What the fuck? We have to see this
through. You understand? The game is apparently over in like an hour. I'm going to see this
whole thing through. You don't, you really don't, but don't you want to know what happened?
I need to know what happens. That's a pretty good strategy until I get fucking murdered.
See, I'm very clearly lying on my back as a baby. Just wait until you see the diaper
go into frame. She's going to hold up like a big poopy diaper and be like, Oh,
I'm just going to spam. Who cares about actual inputs here? That was the hardest
punch I've ever seen. Why is the salad muffled? That's part of the game. It's part of the
experience. I just lost again. I lost again. This guy punched me twice and I died. All right,
come on. Oh yeah. That's poopy. Nevermind. Just wait till it fucking happens, man.
You guys will say whatever you want to say now. All right. I'm not going to fucking
lose again. The game is on hard. Just remember that it's on hard. Why do I have this on hard?
I'm already dead. I think, I think that guy's character, I think that guy's broken.
That's the only guy. Why am I waiting for this? Why am I waiting for the diaper? It's
not going to happen. It's not going to happen. All right. Who cares? Put it on like the
baby mode. The targeting doesn't make any sense either. It just randomly goes at a
sir. I can't like target anybody. Like the guy behind me. Like I can't, what am I supposed to do?
Just press B? I mean you really feel like Batman. Ah, he's trying to sneak up on me.
There we go. There we go. There we go. There we go. I thought he was going to disappear.
Yeah, come on. Of course. Wilds. See that took a lot of planning. That was, that was in
what? All right. Okay. Tyler Durden. No, don't hold on. Don't do it yet.
Oh, here's the other group. Why do they become wild birds that just fly away? I don't understand.
Was this like the next tier up? Oh, it's my friends. Refund the game. Should I keep playing?
No, no, man. I mean, really what you should do is just, this is the point of the story
where we're giving you a chance to refund. So if you want to just go ahead and you can
hit escape, right? No, no way, man. Hold on though. Hold on. Remember after two hours,
it's not going to, I don't want to. I am going to keep playing this game until I finish it.
You understand? Dude. All right. Well, that was your last opportunity.
Fuck it. Who cares? I'm going for the end. See you later. Oh, did you break that? That
was my fucking car. That's actually what he probably said. What's up next? Dump it.
He bought. The game is three hours long. Well, we're 33% of the way through it.
Stop, please. Two more hours. Hold on. Somebody confirmed that for me. Is this game
over? Okay. That was interesting. It's four hours. All right. Well, how about this?
After it gets to the point where I can't refund the game anymore, I'll stop.
I mean, it's either this or we're going back to Hitman.
Average is two hours and 40 minutes. I'll get it done. Hitman. Yeah, it's either this or Hitman
because I want to play a couple of the other missions. I think I'm almost, I think it's over.
I went by so, I did it so quickly. Please God play this over Hitman.
I don't know why part of me thinks this is funny. One guy said that. Yeah. Yeah. So what's,
what's the point? What's the point? Nobody said that. Yes, they did. Go look at the chat.
That's a Blavo keyboard. Don't you know, there's probably like two more piano scenes.
Break the keyboard. No, that Blavo keyboard was already grinded up in a meat grinder somewhere.
Now, whatever they do, I've recycled it. Low viewers, low donation, bad stream, not funny,
still watching. Hey, hold on. Listen, that's all right. That's, that's all right. That's
fine. Look, I'm going to, I'm going to beat this game. Come on. It's not all right. It's
not fine. Everyone has a bad stream now and again. Bad stream. I'm having a great time.
I'm having fun. I'm having a good time. I wonder how many times I have to say that
to myself before it becomes true. Okay. I am getting a little tired of just like the enemies
in the room. All right. All right. It's about to stop. I'm about to turn it off.
All right. Hold on. I'm about to turn it off. I'm about to turn it off. Okay.
I'm not going to refund it. Keep playing. It's like, I can't, I'm wedged inside of a giant vice
right now. And on one side of the, one of the wedges are people saying, continue to play.
And the other wedge are people screaming at me to play something else. I'm going to get
crushed. I'm going to get squished every 10 minutes. It gets closer. Like my hands are
up and the two wedges are coming in and I'm like, Oh shit, this is getting serious.
Squish him. Somebody said fucking squish him. Squish him. Kill him.
Wait, what? Cut scene, fight scene, cut scene, fight scene, cut scene, fight scene.
Make him into a puree. All right. We're going to do a poll. Okay.
We will let democracy reign. I'm going to do a poll and we're going to see what you guys
want me to do. Okay. By the way, that poll is in 45 minutes. Oh, got a little closer.
Crush it. Doing a poll later will reduce the range of votes.
I was getting a piano ready, but I don't think we need it. You guys didn't think it was mom.
Look, terrible, terrible, terrible.
Uh, we're about to get to the story climax. Come on. This is where we get to. Here's the big
reveal. I hear you with my blood. Here we go. Big like story reveal. Who's the skeleton?
Why can I not hurt you? What's going on? What? This is just like, I feel like I'm
just shooting me with a fucking gun. What the fuck was that? I just got taunt killed.
I really, I honestly, ah, he's getting close. He's getting close. He's getting close to run away.
Ah, damn it. I need to know who this is under there. I'm invested in the hour and 45 minutes
story. All right. I just, I just kicked the shit out of you. You're going to do some combos
and it's going to be the mom. It has to be right. And then I'll delete the game.
Well, all right. Here's a scenario. If it's mom under there, I delete the game and refund it.
If it's me under there, if I take the mask off and it's my face and it's been me the whole time,
then I play for another four hours. Okay. And I've just been beating my like self up in
my bedroom. We got our room with the mask. Take off that mask. Here it comes. Here comes a
Scooby Doo reveal. How did we turn just from here to where did the bird go? What? Where did
the bird go? Delete game. No, that wasn't one of the options. Please delete game. No,
I'm going to write an entire review. I'm going to get hired by IGN. I'm going to write a
review of this game because I need to complete it. And then I'm going to put my two weeks
notice in it. Okay. So now this isn't wirehead. I thought it was going to be a game like that
from the trailer. It looked like it was going to be a FMV kind of game. I was misled by the
trailer. Next time I die, I have to make a poll. Okay. That's fair. Why did you choose this
game? I don't know because we've had fun with FMV games before. I thought this could have been
another one, but it's just walk from room to room and fight enemy. And then, and they've
also paused. This is the same room I was in before. Did the game reset? I'm confused here.
This is the same room I was in. The game didn't reset, did it? Did I lose my save file?
It's the same room, same TV. Didn't the same thing happen? What? The police are here now.
Everybody freeze. Where there was a disturbance. I've been able to open all these doors.
This is a disturbance. This is the police. Put your hands up. Put a poll in chat.
Here's what I don't get about this. I understand the whole, well, there's no sound
because the main character is hearing impaired, right? But he's, he's not here right now.
He's not currently here. I mean, he's over here. Why couldn't we just hear that? Ah, the old two
people holding a guy pretending to struggle bit and they're just barely putting their hands on
him. Yeah, get in there. Oh, this is so tough. He's wild. Oh, all right. Oh, I got a,
I got a wild one here too. Oh, that was hard. If I'm a director, I'm gonna be like,
I'm gonna go like, I'm gonna take, you know, the actors to the side and be like,
hey, listen, like you, like you can bite that guy for real and like try to bite him. And you
want like really want, I would be, I would, I would direct my actors. I don't understand what,
this is like the main selling point of the game is we just didn't add an audio track.
That's, that's the only thing that's, that's it. And you want to play it. I don't
want to play it, but, but we see things through on this channel, maybe like 30 or 40% of the time,
like, but we, we see three, we see things through on this channel, maybe like three
out of 10 times. So, sorry, I just kind of had to piss back here, but sorry, I startled you.
He'll finish this, but not LA D'more. LA D'more is like 60 hours. This is three.
This is punishment for the dab. I can't tell. Is this CG? No, this is, this is real,
right? Yeah. Okay. This is real. All right. We're almost ready for the pole. If he breaks the lamp,
I'll give a pull. Throw the lamp across the room and you get a pull. Uh, one of these tropes is
going to happen. He's going to notice something ridiculous. Turn around, grab, throw, shatter
against the wall. Then you get your pull. Wait, what did I say? If it was me, if it was me
doing this, that I had to finish it, right? Oh no. I did it. So I have to finish it.
Oh, he screams again. I'm remembering everything that happened. I broke that guy's arm.
I smashed a bottle. I got yelled at. I made direct awkward eye contact with another actor on
him. What am I done? What the hell are you doing? He's the bird. He's the bird. I have to beat the
game. He's the bird. I knew it. Yep. He's the bird. Okay. Well, no pole. Oh, it's over guys.
All right. No. Okay. All right. Here. Let me like, let me go back and like
rewrite this rule. That was just a dream. That might not be real. All right. If it was
just a dream, then rules are rules. See, it's okay. It was just a dream. That wasn't actually
real. Just because it was on camera doesn't mean it was real. Still get your pull.
Dream rules don't count. That's yeah, that's real. That's true. No, that's fine. Just because
it showed up in the game doesn't mean it actually happened. Face on. What do you mean
face on? Did he throw that out the window? Those are expensive. All of his personal data
is on there. He's punching the driver's seat. Yeah. He's going to fuck up his driver.
How long has it been? Have I been streaming for like five hours? No, not even two hours. Not
even an hour and a half. I feel like I'm sitting in this chair for a month. The game
actually has no sound. Oh yeah. That's not my configuration being wrong. You have 40 minutes
left to refund this. No, I want to be one of their only sales. What's the story again?
Good luck. I have no idea. Something about a guy. His mom was killed when he was younger
and it might have just been him that did it. And now he's, I don't know. I have no idea
what's happening because we weren't able to see. I can't, there's no subtitles and you
can't hear anything. So we're just supposed to be led to believe his dad is a cop. His dad
may have killed the mother and I have a friend that they got the sneakers stolen
by this guy. And then this guy went to jail and then, and then this, I don't know. Why would
you want to be one of the idiots that bought this and didn't refund it? I don't know. Part of
me thinks that's funny. I kind of think that's funny. Is it? It might be. I could, I could
look at my Steam library and be like, oh yeah, I remember that. This isn't $30. This is 15.
He's running away. Okay. It's not worth it. Well, I got, I have up until,
why would you want to remember that you played this for the Steam trading cards? Yeah. You'll
see in like five years, this will be worth like at least one or two Hearthstone packs.
You know what I mean? Trading the Quiet Man two main character cards for two refined metal.
No, that's going to be worth a lot of fucking money. Quiet Man was critically panned. What,
what are you guys doing with the complaints? Uh oh. Uh oh. They're copy pasting a review of
the game. This game is 39 gigs. Holy shit. It was, I was wondering why it took so long to
download. Why? Why is this game 40 gigs? What? Is it because of all the, the cut scenes? No
way. Yeah, it did take a long time to download. That's true. It has uncompressed audio. Come on
H.264, man. You ever like, I know this is, I'm speaking at it like total like arm chair here,
like arm chair dev. Like, you know, it's the Viad. But sometimes I really do think if I had
like $10 million or like $5 million, I think I could probably actually put a team together and
make something pretty good. I don't, maybe that's just me being an idiot and like lying.
I don't know. You ever, sometimes you feel that way? Everyone, everyone thinks that. Yeah,
I know. But like, sometimes I think it's real, but it's not because that's speaking from total
ignorance. If I had $5 million, I had to make a fun game. It's like, oh, would you? No,
I'd come up with, I would make, this is what I would make that. But that would, at least
I would put that in the game and I'd be proud of the spinning roundhouse kick. But then
you have to like bring yourself back to reality and be like, I, uh, I have no idea
what the fuck I'm doing. And there's no way it would be even remotely close to probably
as good as this game. Technically, like I would, it would be like a stick figure game,
but I would hire people. I bring in very talented people and I would, I would just
sit in a giant chair that oversaw the whole development team. And I'd have a big horn,
like a big bullhorn. And I'd be like, you're doing a good job down there.
You over at programming, excellent work. Like I would look over, I would see on the other
side, they'd be the, you know, the, the grass, the grass people, the grass team. Yeah,
I'd have a dedicated team of grass. You know, I took a tackle. Did I lose? No, I'm still alive.
Like the grass looks good over there. Good work. Maybe 2% longer blades.
And people would love me as their boss. Yeah, I would be so, I would be such a good boss.
I would throw parties. Like I would invite clowns to be birthday parties and I would
always have like fresh muffins and cookies for everybody. Oh, I died. Shit. And anytime
there was something I didn't like that was happening in the studio. Like if I looked over
at the team of, of, of grass blade designers and I was like, oh, that didn't look that good. I'd
be like, you're doing your best and I appreciate it. Take the next three days off. And then I
would just like get down off my giant chair and I'd sit at the computer and try to do it.
All right. Here's a fucking pole. Next three days off is fired. No, it's not. That's go
take a break and come back fresh. I would have fresh sandwiches every day. I would go,
I would go person to person, like seat to seat. And I would take a, Hey, what's your favorite?
What's your favorite sandwich? No, actually, uh, I really like a tomato basil mozzarella.
Is that like weird? No, no, no, that's fine. You're going to have it every day.
Okay. Hold on. Uh, finish this game. Come back fresh or don't come back at all. That's not
what I said. That's not what I said. All right. Here's your pole. I died. Take a look.
There you go. Come back. So you can design grass. Yeah. They would, they would be,
there'd be 2000 people on the dev team. And by this point I would have had,
I would have already been making, you know, I mean, my Twitch career is,
I mean, doing real good. So I'm saying probably another year or two, I'll have like
six or $700 million in the bank account. So I would just, I would have 2000 employees
each. There would be 10 employees dedicated to grass, 10 employees dedicated to the sky,
10 employees dedicated to food items that like modeling food items to put around.
New game plus has sound. This is difficult. Look at this split here. Fucking sandwiches.
Oh, the boss, like that, you have to scream at me though, because I'm,
I'm so high up in the, I'm in like a huge chair with a horn like boss.
Yeah. Tim, what is it? Tim valued employee, Tim, how are you? What can I get for you?
Hey, uh, can I have a lasagna? Absolutely. And I would fucking call like the nearest lasagna
company and would get it catered for him. Uh, it looks like, okay, whoa, this is still close.
Bankrupt in a week. And if somebody had a problem with like me or the company, I'd,
I would get off the chair and I'd be like, all right, uh, uh, Mike Davidson.
I, I know you've had it. You have a problem with something here. I, it's, I want you,
you, you get a day in the big chair. Then he gets to go up there and like sit up there
and like yell down about lasagnas to people and shit for 10 minutes. No, no, no, 10 minutes.
And then when he comes down, we've been like high five and they're like,
I would shake his hand and they'd be like $400. Like just 400 just in that handshake.
All right. I, I'm going to close this in like 60 seconds because this is so,
this is too close, but I'm going to close it because it has to happen.
This is the longest 60 seconds of my life. And the people that are making the grass,
let's bring this last point up before I close the poll. You know, uh, uh, Mr. Albertson.
Yeah, yes. Uh, I don't, I don't, I'm trying to get a feel for, I never like made grass
before. I've never really, I came from like a different team and I'd be like, absolutely.
Hold on a minute. I'd come down and I, we would eat grass together. I'd be like,
you want to try some? And like, we would eat it. I would eat it mostly. Uh, I'm a big, I love it.
So I would be, I would eat the grass in front of them and I would explain exactly how it tasted.
And I would be like, if you want to try, go for it. And I've given them microscopes.
They ever more, every single desk would have a microscope by the way.
So in case there was something you need more detail on, look through the
microscope for the blade grass. If you want to eat it, it'd be fine. Um,
all right. The poll is closed. I'm done. I'm out. Poll is closed. That's it. Nah,
it's over. By the way, guys, this is a telltale game. Choices don't matter.
I can't believe this got voted off. I can't believe it. What the hell? Everyone that said,
yes, keep playing. Fuck chat. No, I, uh, I can't do that. No, just one more guy,
one more enemy. Look, I told you I was going to stop. I didn't tell you when,
in like a minute. I would, okay. Can I play this like in the corner while we figure out
what else we're going to do? Like I may not have done what you wanted here,
but it's anybody down here wanted a lasagna. Anybody want a lasagna?
I'm willing to call. I'll get one. Me, me. What if everybody wants a lasagna? Well,
then I'm going to get a big lasagna. I'll get a big kiddie pool and they'll put it,
they'll just make a giant lasagna in the kiddie pool. It'll be lasagna day
and I'll jump in it and like roll around in it with like swimmies on.
All right. I'm leaving. I'm gone. I'm leaving. I'm leaving. I'm almost gone.
Damn it. Hold on. Let me open up. I was going to,
I'm going to plan a couple of hitman missions that we have didn't do.
And this is going to take a second. I'm not going to break my computer.
If I crashed my computer, I'm going to be so sad. All right. Here it comes.
Let's get another game capture on here. What the fuck? The controller. I don't want rumble.
Nobody wants rumble. Nobody. This was a gimmick back in like the Nintendo 64 era.
Does anybody get immersed with rumble at this point? The controller shakes. That was cool.
Back in 2002. I mean, I like it. It's fun. Sometimes. Don't you wish food had a rumble
feature? So when you eat lasagna, it would like rumble to going down.
This is impossible. So I'm just going to delete.