Hey, what's going on, everybody? Jerma here with just a little update vlog telling you where I've been the last couple of days.
While you haven't seen really any videos in a couple days here. I just got back from North Carolina.
I actually just landed. The plane landed like 30 seconds ago. That's not true. It landed like 40 minutes ago
because it takes a while to get off the plane and then get in a car and drive to my house.
But I just got back from the baby's house. Well, my sister's house in North Carolina.
And it was a great trip. It was awesome. And those of you guys that have become uncles or have had, even if you've had kids on your own,
you know that holding a baby and seeing like a baby, it's a lot different when you actually get to have your hands on them
and like cuddle them and rock them and stuff. It's really, really cool. And it's quite a humbling experience as you're watching me here
with the baby right now. I never like have held a baby before. And this is like kind of probably going to sound odd to some of you guys.
But I've never held a baby before. Ever. Never in my entire life. This is the first time I've ever done it because I'm kind of,
I'm kind of afraid to do it. Like I've always been kind of scared to, oh, let me hold my baby for me.
Like I don't, I don't want to do that. Like for some reason I've just never wanted to do it.
But when you have a connection with a kid, when you have a direct blood relation, it's like a sister's,
your sister's kid, your brother's kid or something, it's a lot different. And you really want to just like
hold the baby. Like the one thing I wanted to do that, right when I got on the house, I was like, I want to hold that baby immediately.
And of course, everybody wanted to, because I mean, the baby gets passed around to all the family members,
because there was a lot of us there. There was my brother-in-law's side and me and my brother and my sister,
obviously. My sister's the one that had the baby. And my parents, there was just a lot of people there, friends there.
So everybody, the baby kind of got like passed around. It was pretty ridiculous. But when it was my turn, oh my God,
I like sat there and just stared at the baby and just wanted to see like, what is this baby thinking?
And I mean, I'm going off on kind of a tangent here and I wanted to make this video kind of less than
like two or three minutes just to let you know where I've been. But it's a really humbling experience.
It's a really almost life-changing experience, if I can really say that. And all I can really say is I feel great.
I feel awesome. I'm glad that I was able to be a part of that. I was at the baptism. I was standing there.
I did a reading for the baptism. I mean, I'm not like a really highly religious guy, but it still was cool to do that
and be part of that. But before this video kind of gets longer than I wanted it to, I'm going to wrap it up here, guys.
Just hope you enjoy the little clips in the background while I talked about life and babies and spies.
Well, that wasn't technically a baby spie. That was a baby harper. And I can't wait to see her again,
probably Christmas time or Thanksgiving. And I'm going to let the video play out, guys.
I'm going to talk to you guys all next time. Thank you all so much for watching. Really do appreciate it.
I'm back in action tomorrow. I got a lot of stuff planned for the next couple days.
I got a lot of stuff planned in general. Just stay tuned, baby. Just stay tuned.
All right, guys. I'll see you all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.