How the heck are you? Hey, you sleeping? Hey, wake up. Hi guys.
Oops. Welcome to another stream. Just saw you last night potentially.
Or maybe I didn't. Maybe you weren't here yesterday.
And in that regard, how are you today? A loud streamer wakes up innocent viewers.
Innocent viewers. What about that one time you called me an idiot?
Guilty! Now I hope you guys are doing well. We're going to start today.
Sort of where we left off yesterday. And that is...
I almost puked. What is going on? What's with this fucking like earthquake?
Like the choppers closing in? Listen to this. You good?
Okay, what is... Is everyone just hovering here?
That was a long time. That was almost a full
10 to 15 second straight. Longer than that.
But no, we're going to play Clock Tower 3. It is a classic PlayStation 2
game. I don't know how much of it I'm going to
play, but I'm going to give it at least a solid attempt. And then from there
we're going to move on to probably 25 to life.
I still need to find a place to play this game that requires 12 hours.
Maybe we'll do that today too. Should I start? No, I can't start with that
one. That game probably sucks ass. I thought Clock Tower 3 was the bad
one. Oh, I thought it was the good one. Did I
get the bad one? Is Clock Tower 3 the bad one?
Three is the bad one. So what's the good one?
Two is the bad one. Clock Tower 3 is the good one.
He doesn't know. One and two. Three is just weird.
It's not scary. Well, good thing I've got
a little bit of a list here to play today and tomorrow.
And then we're going to close the book on retro for a while.
I've said that like so many times. I have so many old games.
I keep saying, yeah, we've done like three streams in a row
of Dreamcast. Yeah, we're going to close the book a
little while and like the old retro stuff and then like a week and a
half later I'm playing PlayStation 2 again.
I was gonna say Dark Souls, but I don't know why that was going to
happen. It's not just the game that's old,
but I love it though. I love like playing these old games, especially the old
strange, obscure ones that just don't make any sense.
It scratches an itch in my brain, so I love it.
But we're going to go back to VR after tomorrow.
So if you're wondering, wait, when are you going to go back to that VR stuff?
I just needed a break from it. VR is going to come back next week.
We're going to do Mind Show and then I kind of want to go back to
Jet Island and keep playing that, but it
should be fun. That should be at some point in the
middle or late of next week. No one liked Jet Island? I did.
I did. What's your overall opinion on VR so far? I wish I could just play it
every day. We would be playing it. I'd be doing
it right now. I'd be streaming VR today and yesterday,
but I can't do it. My fucking old man brain can't do it.
I just want to live in VR. All right, let's get going. I'm going to play
the good one. Incoming Clock Tower 3. Let's just have some fun. No, let's just
relax. You got to build up a tolerance to it.
Yeah, if I do that for more than three, four, five straight days,
two days in a row, three days in a row, if I wasn't even streaming it,
I would still have to take a break from it for a couple days. I would
start getting headaches. It's like wearing glasses for the first time.
This game includes disturbing content and scenes of graphic violence. Does
it? It's a PlayStation 2, though. It don't
count. The graphics aren't good enough for it to be, like, actually a
problem. Produced by Capcom. Directed by...
I didn't see it. Not seeing. Quiet.
It is Mr. X.
This is a Capcom game. Mr. X drops a nuke somewhere.
Clock Tower 3! All right, make sure we're right here.
Only type. I can't type and play the game at the same time.
That wouldn't make any sense. This is not the technical screen, too, although I
kind of wish it was sometimes. That was so much fun.
I'm just in the right spot. This is not correct.
Wow, hold on, hold on, hold on. It's pre-recorded. You can type.
This is not pre-recorded. I feel like I'm gonna get Phantom of
the Opera memed here. No, no, I need that back. Give me that
back so I can see what I'm doing. All right, that looks good. A little bit
of bars on the sides, but it's cinematic, okay? Well, get those
bars off. No, that makes it a 16 by 8.
That makes it 15 by 9. You guys, that's
cinematic. Is this a movie? I don't know.
Dearest Alyssa, how have you been? I think of you every day.
It seems such a long time since you started your life at boarding school.
It was after your beloved grandfather went missing while traveling three
years ago that I sent you away to boarding
school and told you not to come back for at least six years
without giving you any explanation. It must have been very painful for you
and I'm sorry, but it was for your own protection.
Now your 15th birthday is approaching and I fear your life may be in danger
more than ever before. Please go into hiding until your 15th
birthday has passed. I know that what I am saying will make
no sense to you, but please do as I tell you and hide as
quickly as you can. Your loving mother, Nancy.
Mum. Alyssa, you're wanted on the telephone. It's your mother.
Hello? Mum? Hello? Are you there? Put on to me. Hello?
Am I playing yet? Mum, I'm back. Margeants.
What? Are we already starting? All right, I should pay attention and not
write like fucking tongue-in-cheek scripts on my video
page. By the way, that was the, I think
that was the actual garage band default sound you can make for a
jumpscare. Does Mr. X talk? Is he a tail?
Yes, I am. Oh, I'm Alyssa, Nancy's daughter.
Daughter? Do you know where my mother is? Your mother has gone out.
That was early yesterday morning. Huh? She mentioned that she would not be
coming back for some time. What? She was wrong. She won't be
coming back. At all. And he's gonna bring the
scissors up and start snapping at me. You are all in this world, little girl.
See? Here he comes. My sweet Alyssa. All right, I don't like this. I've been
waiting so long for this moment. Get away from me. I don't like this
version of Lemony Snickett's A Series of Unfortunate Events.
Is that supposed to be, uh, Snood? What's his name? Olaf.
Count Snood. All right, let's go. So I just...
What the fuck was that? My shadow. I thought the shadow was an alien.
What am I supposed to do? The light from the fire casts a reddish glow.
Okay. Play Snood or pre-record it. Snood is the original virus game.
Don't you guys know? The clock keeps perfect time. And the
chair that strange gentleman was sitting in,
a terrible smell is emanating. His unwashed smelly body
had been sitting there for at least three or four hours.
And you find it absolutely revolting that a smell could linger for that
long. Okay, so this was a save point. A diary
lies open with an incomplete entry. You can save game data here.
Sure. Bootleg smelly Mr. X.
Just leave and call the police. Something wrong? One minute and 20
seconds. Guest wing first floor. All right.
Yeah, I'm just gonna leave. There's no need to go out now. I have to
find Mum. All right, let's go find Mum. This
is bright. A strange pattern adorns the jar.
It is brimming with fresh water. Okay. Do I have any other menu? Okay, is
there a menu or something I can look at?
There's a map. So it looks like I can go
through. Okay, let's go there. Mr. X is just Sir Topham Hatt.
Go this way. Nothing of interest here. You don't want to open the door?
Do I hide in this game? I have to hide from Mr. X, right?
It's filled with art and antiques. Grandfather used to collect that kind of
thing. This is Capcom, so those of you saying
that this is a copy of Resident Evil, you mean you're probably right, but they
made the other one too. All guest rooms from this point forward.
Everyone's out. It's locked. All guest rooms from this
point forth. Everyone's out. Okay. Grandfather's room. He's not here now.
It's been three years since he left. When is he coming back?
Ooh, I don't know if he's gonna come back.
I don't know how to tell you that. He left.
He took off three years ago. No one decided to tell her.
All right, upstairs now. Let's check this one. Let me look at the map.
I need to have complete map knowledge. Where am I standing?
Right there. So we're gonna go into the corner here. All right, this one
has a spell on it.
Okay, so it turns the lights off. That's a pretty weird place for a
light switch. The panic meter. Whenever Alyssa is
feeling physically or emotionally threatened, the panic meter rises.
When the panic meter reaches max, Alyssa falls into a state of panic.
While in a state of panic, Alyssa's movements are restricted
and if attacked while in a state of panic, she will die.
The panic meter reading will go down slowly if Alyssa
relaxes in a safe place. Always keep an eye on the panic meter
and try to minimize stress whenever possible.
All right, so we have to manage a panic meter.
Or you could call it the P meter. For short, we could
simplify that as the Peter. Sounds good.
So don't touch that. First jump scare of the game. Fire!
That's really bad. You found it, Django.
All right, let's see what it is. The wall behind the fireplace is falling apart.
Who would have thought there was a hidden room in there? We'll get in
there. Oh well, circle is crouch apparently.
Do I get any weapons or anything? No, the whole point of clock tower is you're
just walking. Okay, grandpa had a weird graphic imagery. That's graphic.
See? What's that? Let me see. That looks like a bottle and a letter down
there. It's a bottle of sacred bottle
and a letter. Let's read the letter in a good accent here.
Nancy's letter. No, I'm not going to do that again.
Dearest Alyssa, I wanted nothing more than for you to live
peacefully, but if you are reading this now you must have come back to the
house. For your protection, I am giving you
some advice, as well as instructions on how to use
this bottle of holy water. How to use it. If you ever are
threatened, sprinkle some holy water on your asylum. It will cause them to
halt temporarily. And to break the soup. No, I'm gonna,
I have to fucking take this knowledge in because I'm gonna read. People get
mad when I play games like this and I act like a dickhead and I don't
pay attention to what this says. Because right now I'm not paying any
attention at all to what this says. I'm just reading it. Here we go.
Exorcism. If you ever are threatened, sprinkles, if you ever are threatened,
sprinkle some holy water on your assailant. It will cause them to halt
temporarily. So splash holy water like that.
Okay. Destroying sigils. To break the seals that prevent access to certain
places, sprinkle holy water on them. So those
seals, I sprinkle holy water. I'm paying attention.
I'm paying attention. See? So sprinkle, sprinkle.
Replenishing holy water. Always remember that the holy water you
have is not in limitless supply. You can refill your bottle from either
sacred jars or from lion drinking fountains.
Sacred jars or lion drinking fountains. So the jars, the jar.
Okay, my mouth. I gotta like, yeah, so those jars.
Sentimental items and spirits. A person who has died of unnatural causes
has unfinished business in the living world.
In order to protect yourself, you must work to heal their wounds. To do
so, you must find their sentimental item. Lastly, this is all my fault,
but I will do my best to protect you. Please remember that I love you more
than anything else in the world and I always will. So I have to find
sentimental items to let the spirits go free.
Replenish the holy water from jars and drinking fountains.
Sigils can be destroyed with the holy water sprinkle
and the bad guy that chases you in the game can be temporarily stopped
with the sprinkle of the holy water. I'm reading. See?
I'm trying. I'm turning over a new leaf in 2019.
It's paying attention to tutorial messages and really focusing.
I'm not gonna do any buff accents. It's the
patron saint of the Hamilton house. I can't even do it now.
What is it doing in here though? But the like the fucking dumb shit comedy
part of my brain is just fighting me inside my head right. There's a battle
going on. I'm gonna save the game. All right,
so I got the bottle of holy water. Is it mapped already? How do I use it?
Three? So I have three uses of it. How do I use it though?
How do I stand up? Circle? Let me go to the controls first.
Items, files, key items, options. Let's just look.
This is back when games didn't have tutorials. The tutorial for games back
like 20 years ago, they had instructional booklets that
you read before you put the disk in. All right, search is
x, duck is circle, walk is square, attack is triangle. That's very
important. No vibration because it'll just ruin
everything. Look, it always does. Special arrow is r1. Well, it's triangle.
You read the booklets on the way back from the game story. Yeah, don't you
guys wish that it was like that still?
They should have a timer when you download a video game. This should be
you open it up and there's a 30 minute timer
and it gives you a little book to read about how the game works.
And the game doesn't physically unlock until 30 minutes after you open it.
All right, so I can open this now with the holy water.
So let's try it. Did it work? Yep. I need to save the game. Is there
is there a safe point going to be in here?
Let's just go save it because I know this is one of those games where
I have to save it constantly. There's gonna be monsters, there's
gonna be aliens and shit. Save the game after all that hard
work. The game looks cool. Yeah, I thought you guys said this was
the bad one. I did my research. I did my research on
which one was the best one, aka which one was the cheapest and
currently available for me to buy. I did a lot of research on it. I have
a question though. If I refill this here, does it get
rid of this? Should I not refill this till I have
zero? He didn't read the manual for 30 minutes.
The cheapest one. I'm just kidding. This wasn't the cheapest one. I did
save. Refill the holy water. Yeah, I did just
save it. Let's see if it disappears. No, okay good. So I can refill it
whenever I want there. Who reads anymore? Now that's the
problem with this generation is nobody's reading books anymore.
You know what I'm saying? Like, that's a problem. People aren't reading anymore.
You should be reading a book a week. It's actually
it's offensive to me that people are not reading at least one to two books
a week. All right, can I get rid of this one?
I just got a sigil on it. Name one book you've read this year.
It's 2019. Look, this is what I do.
So yeah, we have to read one book per week, right, is what I just said.
That's fine. What I do is I wait till the end of the year
and then the last like six weeks of the year I read a book every day.
So it still counts. This is Nancy's room.
Well, hold on, that's not, wait a minute. I did read how to
reinstall the filter in my air purifier. That was
actually really long. It was probably like 15 pages
of how to like do maintenance and care on my humidifier.
Is that me moment up? Archie comics don't count as a book. Yes they do.
I read all of the Attack on Titan manga.
I'll prove it to you. You gotta read it right to left. Huh?
I told you that I did that. I know you told me not to but I couldn't
help it. I'm so worried about you. Where are you?
Those pillows suck. Those are pillows you'd find as a
throw pillow on a dirty couch. That's what you sleep on?
Is that Mum? Did he replace himself in all the family photos?
Who's playing the piano? Who's playing that?
Where's the sound coming from? Who's doing that?
You should have stabbed the photo. You had an opportunity. This is the way to
kill him. This is his heart right here and you had a chance and that's what
we're gonna find out at the very end of the game.
You could have just stabbed the book and blood will come out of that book
and you kill him. More shit like that in movies. I'm so
sick of like the doll that comes to life.
I'm so sick of like that we got lost in the woods. No no no. Where's
the book that is the heart or that is the
monster? And the book is just a spell book.
It's like Merlin's fucking tomb. You know what I mean?
And the family is so terrified of all this shit going on in the house.
It could be werewolves. They could be fucking Loch Ness monsters. It could be
aliens like crashing down into the house and like killing people and eating
people. But it's the book that's doing it. It's
the Merlin's fucking magic tomb that's on their bookshelf and they
didn't even realize it and they flip through at the end of the movie
and it's every page is all the fucked up shit that's been going on
in the house. And they fucking stab through the book and like the book
bleeds and that's the end of the movie.
Door's sealed. That's literally happened. That happened in Goosebumps.
Well make it. Okay was that just a Goosebumps book?
For that? These mo-capped explosion jumps.
Actor in a studio with like a bunch of wires off.
This is way too expensive for us to not know what the hell's happening.
She's desperately trying to find the piano. Each key on the piano is a
different monster on it and like he's... I'm sorry never mind.
So where am I supposed to go? I thought this was Clock Tower 3.
This dude's flying in flight in a bumblebee.
Something's holding the door. What's it gonna be? A monster in here?
Elsa. Uh-oh. Monster sequence. I'm ready. Oh shit.
Oh shit. That was a great reaction. The ring. Give me back my ring.
Here comes the piano. Can I get the ring? Ring. What about it? Is it in here?
Okay. Engagement ring. I got a ring.
Spiritual healing. When you find a sentimental item
that belongs to a person who died of unnatural causes, return it to its
rightful owner. If it is a ring, put it in its case. If it's a half heart pendant,
put it together with the other half by returning the sentimental item. Spirits are
healed and Elissa may obtain another item or value the information in return.
When you find a sentimental...
Some people are getting probably very angry at this.
Let me just like swirl around my fucking whiskey.
When you find a sentimental item that belongs to a person who died of
unnatural causes, return it to its rightful owner. If it's a ring, put it in its case.
If it is a half heart pendant, put it together with the other half.
By returning these sentimental items, spirits are healed
and Elissa may obtain another item or valuable information in return.
Put the ring in the box. Put the pendant together.
You got it. The box is literally right here.
How do I put the ring in the box? I kind of have to get you a...
Should I throw holy water at this lady? Put the ring in the box.
An empty ring box. Did someone steal the ring from him?
Do I actually have to select it?
What's inventory? Does it start? Okay, do I actually have to use it?
Drop it. Okay.
Yeah, I know what you're gonna do. Use item, yes.
My ring! You found my ring! Thank you.
Here, I left you some humanity. Thanks, hacker.
Sigil stone. Sigil stone. Let's get some info on that.
We'll take an attack on your behalf once.
So it's just... it's just a shield.
So it's an armor. It's one armor.
Oh, I can refill this. Good thing I paid attention.
Uh, it's a very fun... You can save and refill. That's cool.
How the hell do you do that on a piano?
How could you be that fast? Listen to this guy.
How the fuck can you even do that shit?
If you don't play the piano, well...
Seriously, that's... that's a skill. That's an incredible skill.
Congress? What's that? I can hear a piano. Is it coming from Congress?
Jerma, do the invisible guitar joke. Ha ha ha.
He starts... he starts and stops playing.
It's almost like he forgets how to play the song
and then he just goes completely wild and knows exactly...
See? Wait, is it this key? Yeah, I know, I got it again.
Stop playing this game to force another joke?
Wait, you want me to like put another PlayStation game in?
No, I want to play this game.
What? You want me to like... you want to put in like a...
You want to put in like fucking Stuntman and then reach for content?
What's wrong with this?
No, we're doing this for a little while. I'm playing this for a while.
All right, I gotta find a ring.
You're constantly stopping to make jokes.
Do you know what stream you're on?
I'm pretty sure that's what we do every time we play a game.
All right, I guess I got a pen. Is this this lady's pen?
Looks like you shoved it up your ass.
I thought this guy was a serious gamer.
All right, but that's not a... just a gold fountain pen.
Okay, it's covered in blood stains of victim's belongings.
The entry begins, my darling must be addressed to her fiance.
Did you pen come out of here?
All right, return pen.
That means I get one of those shards, right?
Invisibility band.
All right, this game's starting to get really, really bad.
It's like not fun.
And I should go force a joke on another game.
Ring worn for temporary invisibility.
No, I'm just kidding. I fucking think this is fun.
Hey, you can just relax.
What else is over here?
Do another Scottish accent.
No, what is with you guys lately?
This is like the guy yesterday that said,
all right, you can't take a break for a day
and then come back and play Ed, Ed and Eddie.
You have to dare you take a day off
and then play Ed, Ed and Eddie.
He was right.
All right, I made it into a new house.
Lavender water, what's the difference?
Cordial distilled from beautiful purple flower alleviates panic.
Okay, make some smell nice.
There's gonna be something in here scary.
This is a letter from dad.
Here comes a joke.
How are you?
I'm now in France in a region known as Champagne.
Ooh, that is a beautiful place with vineyards as far as the eye can see.
When the war is over, we must come here together for a holiday.
I hear that they have organized for blackouts in London now.
I'm sure that you are fine during the day as Jane is there.
But I worry about your being alone at night.
You'll be all right, won't you, darling?
Keep warm.
With love, Orson.
Did I miss something?
No, that was a classic reference.
Classic joke.
That's a huge telephone.
It's way too big for anybody to hold.
All right, that's just you because you're a short streamer.
Good evening, sir.
This is my first stream.
I want serious gameplay.
I'm sorry that you probably won't get that here.
Bring back Orson.
The desk is clean and well organized.
That just depends on who's got control of the controller today.
You know what I mean?
Some days, you get me.
Other days, you get a guy that beats Jebel first try.
I don't know who you're going to be talking to.
Remember that movie with Professor X, the young Professor X?
It's kind of like that.
Whatever his name is.
This must be the owner of the house.
There's a key.
There's a key next to it.
Yes, there is.
Red draw key.
There's probably a red draw in this building.
Fireplace.
The poker is still stuck in the pile of firewood.
Somebody must have just been here.
These records look quite old.
I wonder how many people screamed at that one.
That wouldn't even go.
That was just a rat.
There's some mouse in here.
Or a snake.
It could be a snake.
More than enough books on the classics here.
We've got Jermacraft.
We've got Otto's Big Adventure.
We've got Orson Welles.
Oh, the classics in there.
I want more water though.
Rat movie.
I'm looking for a red draw.
Is the one down here?
No.
Why am I so interested in this game?
I just am.
Lock from the other side.
Shit.
On the other side, the key's not going to work.
Will it just use it automatically?
No, it's for a draw.
Have you ever played any good games?
I played super hot VR like three days ago.
It was great.
Beat it on stream too.
That's a really slow inventory.
Red draw.
Do we go in here?
He said good.
Is that a red draw?
The desk is clean.
No, we were already in here.
There's no red draw.
Red draw.
Okay, now you dropped it again.
Like you were going to get me again somehow.
Let me look at the map.
Is this some...
Okay, I haven't been over here.
What do you mean?
What am I saying wrong?
Unimaginative ghost puts jumpscare back in same place.
That is pretty funny.
This way, okay.
Red draw.
Blood.
There's blood everywhere.
It's locked.
I'm gonna let it open.
I only have one.
There it is.
Drawer.
Yeah, but you gotta remember,
I have the remnants of a Boston accent.
I still say like car, car, car, draw, drawer.
What are you guys on about?
Christmas tragedy.
Young pianist brutally murdered.
Christmas day.
Mae Norton was found murdered in Norton's The Taylor.
She was discovered by Norton family member Jane Stride.
Returned home to find the victim unconscious.
An autopsy revealed that it was an instantaneous death
caused by a blow to the skull with a heavy blunt object.
No suspects have been named.
The victim had taken part in the 15th Annual Piano Concord
at the Victoria Hall in Kensington the previous day.
A consummate pianist, Miss Norton,
was widely tipped for first prize.
But an unfortunate error in her performance
prevented her from taking the crown.
May have been living at home alone since her father,
William Norton, serving officer,
returned to the front in July.
Okay.
It's pianist.
Something going on upstairs.
What the hell is going on up here?
What?
Where was this happening?
Why did I miss this upstairs?
What the fuck?
Oh my fucking god.
That's insanity.
Are you serious?
I don't have a save point.
What do I have to do?
Evade points and hide points.
When Alyssa is fleeing from an enemy,
certain predetermined areas may start to glow.
These are evade points and hide points.
Approach the area and press the search button
to make Alyssa take evasive action
and repel her attacker.
Most evade points can only be used once.
Press the search button when in front of a hide point
and Alyssa can take refuge there.
The camera will switch to a first-person view
while in hiding.
Hide points can usually be used repeatedly.
But if the panic meter reaches max while in hiding,
Alyssa will run out from her hiding place.
Always keep an eye on the panic meter.
Because evade points and hide points,
and they glow and you have to hit X on them.
Well, let's go.
Whatever.
Hold on.
First of all, let's open this first.
There's something in here.
It is Maze Room Key.
Man.
What?
I can't open this.
He's seeing off my name?
Can I get some evade points?
Oh!
It's too slow.
It's happening too slow.
Where does he go?
I have Maze Key.
I have Maze Room Key.
What are you doing?
Hide?
I can't get in there?
How can I not get in there?
Maybe I can scare you now.
Fire poker.
Fire poker in the head.
Sorry, ghost.
There's something way scarier here.
What do I do?
I gotta get out of here now.
How do I get out?
Anything else I can do?
He's gonna get up, right?
These records look old.
No, no, no.
Get out of the room.
Can I do anything else?
Go, go, go.
Out, out, out.
Smash his head with a hammer.
That's what I would do.
If that was me,
I would smash that guy's head with a sludge hammer.
Like a watermelon.
And then I would just like,
I would burn him.
I would drag him to the fire.
Where's this?
And I would sit there and watch
and just make sure it was gone.
Psycho?
M?
Oh, really?
The guy chasing you with a sludge hammer
that just killed like a little girl?
Are you sure?
I'm the psycho?
The key to Maze Room on the second floor.
I need to get up there.
I can't just leave.
There's a locked door on the second floor.
I've seen every horror movie in the book.
Okay, after that guy's burnt,
you put his ashes in a box
and like mail it to the fucking store,
like North Pole or something.
And then you pay a guy.
You pay a guy like 25 grand to eat the ashes.
And you want like a private YouTube link
of the guy doing it.
Just so you know.
Because it's a diary.
But then the guy that eats the ashes becomes the guy.
Today I darn daddy sucks and sewed a button on his shirt.
He calls himself a tailor,
but he can't even mend his own clothes.
Please dad, I'm not your wife.
A few more days until the button
I still can't play perfectly.
What am I gonna do?
I thought this was a game
where a guy in a tower chases you with scissors.
That's the first game.
Yeah, we played the first game for like 10 minutes.
It was an invitation.
Uh oh.
I told you we should have burnt him.
I told you we should have smashed his head
like an egg and burnt his body.
What did I tell you?
Hit him with a chair in the head.
Oh my god.
What are you doing?
In the head.
Okay, this guy is really, really not that strong.
Like that was pretty big.
Come on man, really.
That was bad.
He did a really cool Star Wars block the bullet.
He hit the chair with a sledgehammer.
But then that's like getting one of those in a game
where you're doing really well
and you do something fucking awesome.
Like you headshot a guy from across the whole map
in Apex Legends, right?
So you're playing Apex Legends
and you're across the map and you snipe some guy
and it's fucking like put it on the front page of every Reddit
and then you like fall off the cliff and die.
That's what happens.
That's what that was.
All right, I need to get out of here.
Can I go?
All right, that's not even a sledgehammer.
That's a broom.
This guy sucks.
Hi, idiot.
Use holy water on him?
That's not a bad idea.
No, it's just a guy.
This is just a weird guy.
All right, I have the invitation to the piano hall.
I need to save the game.
Where's there a save point around here?
Somewhere outside maybe?
Is there no save point in this house?
What?
He's serious.
I need to get down there.
Oh, dude, this is this is stuff.
This reminds me of Apex Legends.
When you like when you shoot the guy from across the map
and then you squat up and you land somewhere
and then like some guy comes out of nowhere and like kills you.
I actually don't want to die here.
This guy sucks.
He really isn't even scary.
He just sucks.
Where am I?
What?
He teleported.
Why did he teleport away?
Oh, here comes the piano again.
I can refill, right?
I can't refill my water here?
Dynamite?
You're the one playing the piano.
Lissa!
That's how it reminds me of it.
You know when you're fucking and having a fun time with your friends in Apex Legends
and somebody over the mic is just like talking shit
and they make a funny voice.
It's so funny.
I'm gonna have to learn how to play the piano.
Watch this.
What's that?
Oh, a diary.
Save the game.
Yep.
What am I doing the next Apex Legends stream?
Bunker S.
This is a stream sponsored by Respawn Legends.
Apex Entertainment.
It looks fun.
It does.
It looks like a fun game.
I need some more holy water.
It stopped.
Wait, is this it?
I don't have any holy water here.
Did she stop because I'm in the hall?
The concert hall?
Jesus.
Do I have to play this piano?
The mocap really is the best part of this whole thing.
Just the over actor in front of the screen.
Oh my god, noob just gave 10 community subs.
Thank you, oh my god, noob.
Is it us she's looking at?
Oh.
Thank you for the 10 community subs.
Oh, she's missing the- I get it, right?
Well, maybe if you cleaned off the-
I know why you can't play the piano
because it's covered in fucking red liquid.
Wipe it off.
Get some Lysol wipes and wipe the damn thing.
Okay, I couldn't move.
What the fuck am I supposed to do?
Do I have to play the piano?
The piano is dripping with blood.
No.
God damn it.
Oh, I'm too pa- I have- I can't control the game.
I need a special key.
What are you doing?
I can't move.
I'm panicking.
I look at this run.
I look like a bird.
This is what a bird does right before it panic takes off.
Move!
What does that say?
It's right out here.
There's a seagull on the beach.
Use the essential oil.
It's the Chad stride.
The panic Chad.
That's pretty cool.
Hold on.
I could drink that, but I got hit.
That's why it happened.
What's the goal here?
Do I even have a goal?
Wait, hold on.
Let me look what else is down here
because I don't even have a goal right now.
It's just run away from guy in the piano place.
What is this?
Some more lavender water.
Let me just see.
Okay, this wraps around.
So I take him out there and run around.
That's the only door I can go in.
Derm, what's your favorite meme?
Oh, definitely the Naruto mirror run.
Now we're gonna have to do this again.
Yeah, dude, mine too.
Basic streamer.
Come on.
I'm just kidding around.
You know what my favorite meme is.
He does a panic special move.
How do I go from here?
I don't have any other direction.
I need a key now.
Oh, God.
See, that's the panic move.
I'm right in front of you.
They could have made this guy so much better
if he was like.
Oh, what's this do?
This lever must raise and lower the stage device.
Yes, I'm gonna crash a head.
I'm gonna crush his head.
That is spawn another enemy.
Sounds like I'm a mannequin.
Don't itch your hair.
It looks fine.
Don't do that.
He just dropped a bunch of quarters.
Oh, shit.
That was for my laundry.
Fuck.
I win.
The torso has been crushed.
What a horrible death.
He's holding something.
I know it's scribbled on a tiny piece of paper.
Safe combination equals bad.
1014 is babe, 3403 is dead.
Bad.
Babe.
So I need to do 103, right?
103.
I got it.
Where's the safe that they're talking about though?
Bad because babe.
Bad because bad.
Why is that even a puzzle?
I don't know.
Strangely enough.
The piano is drippings with goo.
First person to get what that reference is to.
I will give you pretend $100.
A pretend like.
Oh, yeah.
Whoa, what the heck?
Like, not real.
Like, pretend.
Like, I put my hand out and it's like, I pretend to give you my.
Uh-oh.
You're mine now.
I should have guess kept moving, shouldn't I?
No, he's regenerating.
He must have taken a nap out there.
What the hell?
All right, I need a safe.
Duck.
He doesn't know.
Fuck.
That was pretty boss.
He doesn't know.
Yeah, let's all like fucking laugh about that guy.
He can't hear us.
He's wearing AirPods.
Yeah, don't tell him.
Don't tell him.
So he just opened this door.
Why can he open this door?
And where's I'm trapped in here.
I need a safe.
He has the key then.
So I need to I get to crush his head like a goddamn watermelon.
Slow down.
What an asshole.
They're all off limits.
I can't open any of this door.
Is it maybe in the concert hall itself?
Was it in?
He's going to get peace back.
He's back in.
No, he was just in there.
This is a safe.
Oh, this is a safe right here.
Okay.
Cloak room lockers with combination locks.
That memo might be helpful.
103.
Thank you.
Master key.
Now I can go back in there.
But oh, let's save it first though.
Don't like I don't want to get soft locked.
He like breaks in the door the second I press this.
I can leave.
Yeah, but there's a door in the concert hall that I want to open.
German stocks are in.
Go buy.
Are they?
Really?
I think he's in this room.
He's actually just in here, isn't he?
Special key.
Use the master key.
Yeah, this is why I wanted to come here.
Wait.
Well, this is too.
I can go scary way or I can go not scary way.
Oh, I don't like that angle.
It doesn't seem to be anything strange here.
But there is a glowy in the corner.
Lavender water.
Nice.
Anything else in this room?
Don't even think about doing it.
Yeah, I know you can speed by.
Don't even think about it.
It's taunting me.
The hell am I?
Some sort of stage device has been lowered.
I can't get through if it's not raced.
God damn it.
I have to go down and press that button again.
There's something sitting right there.
Joop sightings more frequent.
We got storm signs.
It's just a candle.
I don't know what the heck that could be.
It could be something that I need.
I don't know.
It's one of those survival horror video games from the 90s.
I'm just going to come out 90s.
When Chad is bored, they spend Jupiter.
I'm glad they can find a good use of their time.
Hey, what you should be doing is when you get bored
and you don't get bored with the game,
open up a tab and get some physicist shit.
Do like physicist 101.
Hold on.
Let me check what's over here.
Why have I not created a space agency?
What the heck were you talking about, man?
Get up.
Panic?
Don't think so.
I'm going to be drinking one of these.
Isn't that supposed to alleviate panic?
Did I miss something here?
Why is he faster than me on the stairs?
Oh, where am I going?
Oh, great.
A dead end with lockers.
Wait a minute.
Wait, no, no, no.
I thought...
Okay, wait.
Hold on.
No.
Does he know I'm in here?
We'll try a different place.
That's not a way to go.
This is though, right?
That's great.
Try attacking?
I don't have...
I don't have anything.
I have an empty bottle of like liquor in my safe spot.
It works every time.
Are you kidding me?
I almost choked.
Hold on.
I spilled.
I was taking a sip.
Hold on.
It's all right.
It's not that bad.
It's just a little coffee.
Thank you for that cool original spill joke.
I didn't...
I didn't buy it.
This time I'm going to start...
I'm going to know that I just raised the thing.
I hate this fucking bird chat run so much.
Really?
Come on.
Why is he not seeing me?
Can I raise this when he's on it maybe?
Maybe I can like fuck him up.
Do it.
Press the button.
He has no idea.
This is the same spot for real.
I don't want to just die though and restart.
Because I just have to raise that and go upstairs again.
All right, he's gone.
He's gone, right?
Yep, okay.
I used my magic item though.
I used like the Frodo chainmail thing.
You only get to use that once for a plot device in a movie.
I don't have another one.
Half-Life 2 game sounds.
Just cross the bridge.
Get out of here and continue your let's play of Clock Tower 3.
He's going to show up again here.
He has to, right?
The lantern is not lit.
Told you I was going to need that fucking candle.
I told you.
Everybody was like it's just a candle.
It's just a candle, dummy.
It's not just a candle.
It's too dark to cross.
Where's the other candle?
I can't pick that up.
Why?
Do you get why we said this is a bad game?
Not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet.
This way?
I didn't know.
Am I right behind the counter?
That didn't work last time.
Can I just leave?
I have the key, right?
I can just leave and go out the front door.
I'm trying to find elaborate ways to get out of here.
Oh god, it's a fountain.
It's not a holy water fountain.
Candle or something out here?
Is there a light out here?
Candle?
A light source?
A way to light the way?
Don't panic, please.
Don't panic, don't panic, don't panic, don't panic.
Out, out, out, out.
Leave me alone.
Get away from me.
No.
Stop panicking.
Stop.
Why?
Okay, I don't, I don't want to soft lock myself.
Where the, why the fuck am I supposed to go?
Not that way either.
People.
You use the water and the water doesn't work, does it?
I'm actually glad that happened.
You know why I'm glad that happened?
Because going up stairs was a waste of time
and I used a couple of items for no reason.
So I'm just gonna walk out the front goddamn door.
This is right before I raised the thing.
No, it's not.
It auto saved.
It was a sigil,
there was a sigil on one of the doors, wasn't there?
Just trying to lose them.
I'm trying to find like a good place where I can like lose them out here.
Give me some holy water.
Holy water is about to be achieved.
Got it.
Let's just save it here anyways.
Zero, zero, zero.
Oh, there it is.
I'm gonna go YouTube the ending
because Jerma's never going to beat this game.
Am I nice to expect it to?
All right, holy water.
Where is he?
He lost me.
Up here there's a door, there's a sigil on one of the doors.
He's already back.
It'd be impossible for him to know that I was here.
There's no way he would know I was here.
Now he's sniffing the air.
God damn it.
I'm like a pie on a windowsill.
No, don't come in here.
Let's get a save point with two dashes of holy water.
So now it was upstairs, not...
It was back where the lockers were.
I forgot how to get there.
So it was up here.
What the fuck are you guys doing?
Other side.
Are you playing the piano again?
Are you back?
Hey, can we talk?
She's playing the piano so earnestly.
What is she trying to express?
Good thing I have one still.
That's scary.
Of course I'm gonna throw holy water at the scary thing of the piano.
I didn't know if she was gonna like turn and jump scare me
or try to eat me or bite me or something.
I don't know.
God damn it.
Where is he?
You're mine.
Really could have used that second splash of holy water.
Couldn't you, Jeremy?
Instead of throwing it at the little ghost girl.
Where is it?
Where's the door?
Right there?
Go!
Get in the door!
What are you doing?
Oh yeah.
Okay.
This is the stadium seating.
These are the less expensive seats.
Check all the corners.
Okay, there's a door here.
I don't know what this is gonna lead to.
It's locked from the other side.
We need a light source.
This is just open.
This is pretty disheveled.
I wonder who invented this instrument anyway.
The harp?
I don't know.
The harp is a really kind of fucked up item, isn't it?
Map.
There we go.
Matches.
The harp is like a gigantic underwater guitar.
It's huge and strange and looks like it belongs
like a Disney movie.
Sounds beautiful though.
It's a beautiful instrument.
All right.
I got what I needed.
The nut's down here.
How am I gonna beat rid of this guy?
Is he gonna give me a chance out of the cutscene?
I gotta drink that laughing potion right now
before I go into a panic drink.
Okay.
Hold on here.
It's a high quality bait right there.
Can I go underneath this?
Oh my god.
Thank god.
Is he stuck?
Was I supposed to do that?
Invisibility bench.
Should I use this?
Oh shit.
Can I get through?
I can't.
Good.
Fuck this guy.
All right.
Let's go light the torch.
Can't find me.
Should I just sit in one of the seats?
Hi.
There's like a chest over there.
I can't even do anything.
I have to just leave.
Hiding.
There is no hiding.
It's one of those tank control games
where you can't even see the...
They'll give you one camera angle.
There is one.
We are in a...
Fight that thing.
He's already on me.
All right.
I need to...
And can I do the invisibility band?
Take.
I'm gonna do it here.
I'm invisible now.
Just enough to...
Light.
The light from the lantern illuminates the room.
Fuck.
I don't want to screw this up.
How do I stop that from happening?
How am I...
Why am I doing that?
I didn't read the manual about
walking across the board.
At this point just fall forward.
Okay?
Flyers.
The door with the barbed wire on it.
Where was that door though?
There was that barbed wire door.
Which one was that?
Where was that?
Bottom floor?
Start of the game.
It was in the house.
No, I know.
I know I saw it somewhere.
Don't fall off and make me start over.
Should I put on the Harry Potter invisibility cloak?
Please.
Fall joke incoming.
I'm not going to do that.
Not in a game like this.
That requires backtracking
and then I have a save point from...
Oh, here we go again.
I think that's my mother.
That's gonna be my mom.
Backtracking but with a secret door?
Um...
What do I...
What do I do about this?
Mom, help me!
Mom, like get...
Okay, you didn't...
I got put in...
I got...
Out of the cut scene.
Okay.
I couldn't move.
It worked!
Come on!
Come on, come on, come on!
Out, out, out, out, out!
Okay, I gotta get...
I just gotta leave.
Where am I going?
Oh, no!
I had to go the other way.
Shit!
Leave!
Okay, I'm fine.
Leave.
I'm stuck on shit.
Oh, hey, mom!
Oh, you could like fly in his face
and like sprinkle dust in his eyes.
I have to do it.
Hey, Jerma.
I'm back from YouTubing the ending
and this game is fucking whack.
Thanks.
Okay, I...
I hate this guy.
Splash in eyes.
Refill.
No, no, no.
I don't want to save it right here.
Refill.
Oh, refill.
Run.
Come on, mom!
What the fuck are you doing, mom?
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
Why did you do that to me?
You're supposed to be guiding me.
Do that to him.
They made that...
They...
You don't introduce a character like that.
The floating purple glittery butterfly.
Oh, I'm guiding you.
Look, I'm here and it's a bad guy.
That was great.
That's not your mom or an ally.
I don't know what...
Butterflies in...
It's a video game.
No, I want the save point that I had.
No, I didn't have it.
How am I supposed to think?
It's a horror game
and there's a shiny, beautiful butterfly
that has been shown a few times during the game.
I need to...
I'm dead.
Watch out for the butterfly.
The sonar stingray thing that just flies around.
The bat.
Lake.
Thank you, Lake Drinker, for the five community subs.
All right, where's that room?
It's like down here?
I don't even...
I have no idea.
In here?
Not down here, is it?
There it is.
The suppliers go indoor.
They lose the sky.
Okay, I think I'm safe.
Am I safe?
I think so.
A carved wooden box.
Open it.
Yes.
Is this supposed to be me?
Oh, you're doing a very good job playing the piano, Lissa.
That's the big reveal.
Like, what the fuck?
It's that guy's voice.
You're the most precious thing to me in the whole world.
But don't worry.
Daddy, don't forget the piano concourse is on Christmas Eve.
The winner will have their performance aired on the radio.
I'll practice really hard and win the contest
so that you can hear me when you're out in the war.
That would be wonderful.
The competition will be stiff,
but if you go to your lessons and practice properly,
I'm sure you can do it.
I'll practice every day.
I've already chosen the piece I'm going to play.
Listen, you told me this watch was a present from mommy
before you got married, remember?
Is this like the narrator from Peppa Pig?
So you can think of mommy and me.
Then it'll be like we're all together again.
She sounds like she's like 50.
What a weird piano.
Wait, what the fuck?
It's fucking horrible.
Why would they do this?
What the fuck?
That was too-
That was too fast.
Oh my god, that was awful.
Holy shit.
I didn't even have any time to fucking process
what I just looked at.
It was just, all of a sudden the guy flies.
Oh my god.
All right, the hammer killer.
Robert Morris, 32, the man known as the hammer killer,
has been hanged.
Rumors regarding Morris's death are widespread.
One witness reported he was hanging for a very long time,
pulling on the straps and making unearthly noises.
And blood was oozing through the black cap.
The stench was terrible.
Some witnesses fainted and were carried out.
This is too many things.
Can we just go back to when they were playing the piano?
Too many things happened in a row here.
Morris's first victim was Tony Flanagan,
a fellow employee at the Banbury stone cutting factory.
On June 6th, Morris suddenly struck Flanagan on the head with a hammer.
Sensory overload, I'm sorry guys.
None of this is like comedic.
It's just like too much sensory overload.
Killing him instantly, all five workers present were killed in the same manner.
Morris disappeared thereafter.
A string of similar crimes occurred until the time of Morris's arrest
on the 6th of March.
Morris's victim is numbered 12 and no clear motive has been determined.
Specialists continue to be baffled by the seemingly abrupt change in his behavior,
as well as the extreme violence of his crime.
Kind of like the last five minutes of the game.
An extreme abrupt change in tone.
Maybe I can save May if I get her father's pocket watch to her.
Okay, I have to take the pocket watch to the concert hall.
Okay, is that guy still here?
The stream will pause suddenly for no...
I got no drop frames.
I have zero drop frames so far.
Is the stream having a problem?
It was muting you.
Oh, that's weird.
I don't know why.
All right, so I get the pocket watch back to mom.
I have to take the pocket watch to the concert hall.
Your voice is bad.
Like sound quality coming through,
or you just think you don't like how I sound, you hate my accent or something.
All right, here he comes.
Back to the concert hall.
Extreme.
No butterflies?
No... what is that?
There's a glowing thing down there.
Is there a way I can get down here?
Yes, there is.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, cool.
Lavender water.
Stop calling them butterflies.
They're moths.
What does it say?
He, he, he, he, lamp.
He, he, what does that mean?
Am I mad?
He doesn't know.
Yeah, I've been waiting for you.
You figured me out, little girl.
It's like it's the Hammer Killer.
They thought they got rid of me that day,
and they got us because it was only the beginning, next.
A lot of random...
All right, boss battles.
This is an actual boss battle.
Control...
Duck shoot arrow.
We have arrows.
Shoot arrow, charge arrow, super attack.
Hold down triangle button,
or hold down triangle button with enemy transfixed.
R1 is special.
Battle strategy.
In order to defeat the enemy,
Alyssa must first transfix it.
By hitting the enemy with a charged arrow,
it is possible to fix them to the spot.
Several strategically placed chains
will transfix the target.
Aim so that the chains fan out from the target
who should be in the center.
While the enemy is transfixed,
Alyssa is able to carry out a super attack.
It is no easy task, however,
to hit the target with the arrow.
Watch the enemy's movements closely
and wait for your chance.
Duck can be used to avoid attack by certain enemies.
It may also cause them to become
careless and vulnerable to attack.
Press the R1 button to use special arrows
such as the repellent arrow
in order in which they were obtained.
It is wise to save these weapons
for special occasions.
So let me get this straight.
So shoot arrow is triangle.
You want to charge the arrow
and then shoot them with a charged arrow
to transfix them.
So you lock them in a spot
and then there will be chains
that are placed around the map here
that will transfix them.
So the chains fan out from the target
should be in the center of the target.
Let's just...
I have no fucking idea what's going on.
Am I actually getting...
Am I gonna do a transformation sequence here?
I am.
Now don't come out in the superhero outfit, please.
Here comes the transform sequence.
Hopefully we get some like pop music behind.
No, it's just a staple gun.
Somehow she knows how to use it.
Uh, if you're done, I'd like to begin.
Sledgehammer.
Victims 26.
Sentenced to 486 years in prison.
I have to...
Wait, I'm the judge?
Judgment.
This is a different video game.
Okay.
Get up, Alyssa.
So there's also evade too.
I can evade attacks.
I can't even pause it because I'm gonna go off on a fucking rant right now.
I gotta go off on a rant.
Okay, I can pause it.
Let me...
Okay.
I understand like driving around like cars is cool
and like it's fun to drive around a car.
But are you just driving around in a circle?
You know, like what are you doing?
Like, do you...
Okay, drive fast here.
But are you just driving around in a circle?
Like, what are you doing?
Like, do you...
Okay, drive fast here.
In like a four-mile circle.
Over and over again.
How many times can you do that before it's like,
oh, this is like I'm kind of just doing this over and over again.
Stand in the road.
Excuse me!
It's almost like that this is like on an NPC route.
That's an AI doing that.
Like that's like a GTA NPC.
It's just driving around in a circle.
It's just that picture of the guy standing in front of the...
Wait, what?
That's Vegas for you.
I understand what the fuck is happening.
Imagine if every five minutes I just went...
Hey!
Every day.
You know how irritating that would be for people that live in this house?
Okay, what's for dinner?
Well, we're gonna have carrots and meatloaf.
Hey!
Okay, thanks Jeremy.
We're gonna have carrots and meatloaf and...
All right, is that a chain over there?
No, I just...
I run around the house and I scream when I pass people's doors.
All right, this looks like a chain.
Got it right?
No?
Shoot the chain?
He's blocking.
What about duck?
That didn't work.
Pin him to the wall?
This is three of them, right?
I mean, it's hurting him.
Aaron needs to be charged more.
He has a seismic wave.
So let's see if I can get it.
One, two, three, four.
All right, but there it is.
Okay.
One, two, three.
How far can he move with that?
Okay, again.
One, two, three, four, five.
All right, now he's held in place.
I can just shoot him.
How long is he in that for?
Keep charging.
How?
Really?
One, two, three, four, five.
That's a max arrow.
Is this Mega Man X?
No, I knew like the charge and how it worked,
but I didn't know that it had like seven levels of charge.
R1?
R1.
What the hell am I doing?
Okay.
I call upon Zeus himself to draw the lightning.
This game makes no sense.
That was a limit break.
Your sentence?
Eternity.
Clover of Love.
All right, now we're gonna go lock it back to bomb.
Let's save the game.
Just in case something really bad happens.
Hey, do you guys know that there's like 12 more seasons of Rick and Morty
that are gonna come on the way?
And you know that?
There's gonna be like 15 seasons of Rick and Morty.
They've already been ordered.
At least like nine more seasons have already been ordered.
So all you guys that are like,
I don't like Rick and Morty.
Got like 10 more years of this shit.
The bad show.
Auto voice.
Mom, I've got something for you.
Journal confirmed Rick and Morty.
I'm not like a fan of Rick and Morty.
Hydrate.
I refuse.
How do I know this?
How do I know that?
What?
Isn't she dead?
This person's not rea- what?
Yeah, this person's a ghost.
Why would I say that?
Yes, just keep playing the piano forever.
By the way, your father's dead.
Oh, so she can move on.
Oh, I get it.
So was he the serial killer?
No, no, no, no, no.
No, he was in the war.
Okay.
Right.
No, that looks-
I'm not-
This is not fun.
The subject matter is not funny.
Okay?
Let me just be very clear about something.
The subject-
It's the presentation that is kind of all over the place.
As you can plainly see.
The subject matter is not like funny.
But the way that he was like floating up,
like a Teletubbies episode,
like what the hell was that?
No, it's the serial killer back again.
What the fuck is going on?
What is he-
Help him!
Help this guy!
He's looking at this weird animation.
Where's Harry?
Why is he rolling around like he's coming in bees or ants?
You can't go that fast.
That's like extreme pantomime.
What is happening?
This reminds me of like bad theater.
They blocked out and choreographed the scene.
It's just a terrible theater production.
It's a bad play.
This is fucking so stupid.
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna take a piss.
I'll be back in fucking two minutes.
Okay.
Let us continue.
This game is ridiculous.
So I have the key to Dick's room.
Is this my house?
I'm very confused.
Do I have a map of this place?
Wrong button.
I just got here.
When does he play Apex Legends?
Apex Legends.
The door has been boarded up.
Wait, why do I still need to do this?
Why would you put a spell on the bathroom?
That's next level.
Don't go in there.
You took like such a big dump in here.
That you really don't want somebody to go in.
The dead body in here.
One of the lodges view.
What a stink.
Get off me, please.
Nancy.
I'm gonna go to Dick's room.
The three-way mirror has been folded up.
What else you got here?
What a dumb painting.
What was wrong with the first one?
All right.
So there's another painting stuck under the first one.
This one has a clock on it.
And it is at 3 p.m.
Throw that one in the trash.
Why is this here?
All right.
3 p.m.
Is that 3 p.m.
Or is that 12 15?
Well, it's either 3 or 12 15.
This is Mum's bed.
All right.
Well, now we have a...
Well, here you go.
The clock has stopped ticking.
You'll need a special winding key to get it working again.
Of course I do.
Mom had a lot of shit, huh?
This desk is in such a dumb place.
What is the feng shui in here?
You might have a desk in the middle of your room.
Two desks.
What a sloppy...
Look at this nightstand.
Why is a bed here?
I would appreciate it if you didn't change the camera on me.
There's a computer on the desk.
I wish I had one too.
What's this?
I'm gonna sneeze.
Oh, I couldn't get it.
I'm sorry.
It just happens sometimes.
I couldn't do it.
Okay.
Nothing else.
I have Dick's key.
Mum must know what's going on.
Where is Mum?
Must have left in a hurry.
The wardrobe is still open.
Why is there a ghost?
Is that Mum in the bathtub?
I don't know who is that.
Why is it just a ghost in the house?
All right, we need to find Dick's room.
Let me look at the map again.
Do I have a legend or anything?
Is there a way I can get to the appendix of this legend?
Of this map?
Get to the legend.
Looking for the append...
Oh, apex legend is what I'm looking for.
Don't.
Don't do it.
Couldn't I crawl through here before?
Don't.
This is Alyssa's room.
Is he still in here?
It's as if that nightmare never took place.
Wait, what's across the way?
Is that Dick?
Is this going to be a clock tower stream?
Nothing of interest here.
Who is it?
Philip?
Damn it.
I don't know.
I'm just kind of playing it.
I knew I was going to play this for at least a couple hours.
I knew it just by the first 20 minutes.
Well, let's just save it at least.
And as it happens, sometimes you get locked in one.
I was promised 12 hours.
No, one of these games has a 12-hour timer on it.
And I don't know what to do with it.
I have no idea what I'm supposed to do with it.
I need to find the right moment to play that game.
Where's Dick's room?
Filled with art and antiques.
Grandpa used to collect these things.
Right.
It's locked.
The lodges won't be coming back.
All right.
I need to find this room.
Well, that was a random find.
He didn't even have a label on his door.
Your room is really, really weird too.
All these old books.
What was he studying?
Dog magics.
All right.
If you got this many books, it might be time to donate some of them.
There is a scribbled note.
The keys to the mystery of time lie behind you.
What a stupid note.
Book of Entities 1.
Entities have existed in the human realm since Roman days.
These beings have been known to possess innocent humans, imbuing them with
utter ruthlessness and cruelty and often driving the possessed to vicious acts of murder.
In such cases, executing the murderer does not break the circle of evil.
The possessed is resurrected to continue its bloodthirsty mission.
Those who are thus controlled by entities are known as
sub, uh, apex legends.
When a subordinate kills a human, they take nourishment from the victim's soul
and their power grows.
Subordinates may acquire an infinite amount of power in this manner.
It follows then that subordinates are sustained by human misery and suffering.
Only certain humans are equipped to fight entities and their subordinates,
the Rooters, who are always young women in their teens,
have been battling against these shadowy enemies for hundreds of years.
Their war is likely to continue for many centuries to come.
Yes it does.
Yes it will.
Considering the amount of 500 years in the future after this game takes place,
animes with the same exact plot as this game.
Serpents!
Dude I'm thinking about getting that as like a tat like the serpent eating its own serpent.
Why the fuck are you dressed like Freddy Krueger?
Is this our new contact?
There they are again.
Yep, has it been 10 minutes?
All of a sudden a bunch of like fucking Chili's employees come out and they're like
happy birthday to you happy birthday and they bring a shitty cupcake with one candle in it.
He went out really fast, loony tunes fast.
Okay a scribbled note yeah the keys to the mystery of time lie behind you so
over here these old books what was he studying something in the chair in his chair I went to
a place that charged us for the birthday thing see what you have to do is you go with you know
you want you want to do like oh hey like oh funny prank get like 15 people to go as groups
of like two in different places in the restaurant and it's everybody's birthday today
so they have to go around and do the birthday thing to like 15 different parties
and like you tip them a fucking you tip them like fucking 500 bucks after that by the way
I would fucking hate you if you did that you don't do that money does not forgive your sins
if you tipped me 150 dollars I would spill boiling soup on your lap why wait hold on
so if at the end of the meal it was like I wrote it oh yeah that was like a 42
dollars for like the food all right that's fine here's 150 dollars for a tip
you're gonna take that receipt you're gonna look at it you're gonna go oh 150 dollars
I'm gonna drop boiling soup on him what is the where's the disconnect happened there
I'm trying to figure that out so don't tip at that person all right what do I need to do
I need to find the magic what's did I get anything in my inventory it was behind you
the whole time uh jewel saved like a clove leaf has strange powers no I tip I I tip at least
every time I go out to eat or pretty much anytime I have the the slip that has a slot
for gratuity I it's I any it doesn't matter what it is it's always uh as long as you
know like it was the service was was decent it was a friendly atmosphere I give at least 25
percent sure liar what Mr. Moneybags yeah take a hundred take one he's a liar
you know this guy's loaded uh what no oh I give at least 45 percent I believe it you seem like
the type to make a real pain for waiters what no I'm like so so accommodating and so easy
I'm not those you guys know me come on like I'm not I know like the oh I bet I'm at a grocery
store and he went like coffee Cheetos and like snapped in my face and like burped and then I
threw his plate on the ground I know what those like memes are out there don't believe them
they're all fake I'm very easy okay I need to figure out where the hell I need to go
I need to it's the things actually said look behind you so I need to go back there don't I
I didn't really progress I got that cut scene that didn't know where to go after that
it's the clock yeah but I need the thing I need the I need to do the clock stop ticking I need
the winding keys yes yawning and pretending not to hear the cashier those those coffee
past is so stupid I'm just walking in circles I gotta go back to dad's room yawning loudly
my room I don't know the fuck I'm going we started talking about like tipping and I forgot
where I was I wish I could see on the map where I was standing is there like a where you are now
this upstairs it's right there Germans I gotta sneaks vodka into no I don't what do you what
I do not do that right there why did I start talking about like tips and shit I had this in
the bag I was going fine down I got too heavily distracted nothing of interest here
why don't you just go in god you're unbearable wait this wasn't locked before who could have
locked it I just get so frustrated stupid I said a lot of spit stuck in my throat there I'm sorry
all right where is there a paint this is gonna drop this painting is gonna drop
oh my fucking god of course there is behind the painting of dear old dad Napoleon dynamite
oh god oh pulling dynamite they made like five different pieces of media from that one movie
there was a cartoon there was a movie there were t-shirts there was a comic book it was out of
control there's something on the wall next to the desk oh god idiot looks like a mask used
to hang here okay so it was a scribbled note yeah chat is really weird tonight why
I think they're fine we're just having a good time wait what about this one look at every painting
put your stuff your face in the lampshade I don't think there's anything else in here I got
what I need I got the keys no you're weird like how am I going to defend how am I going to
fight that there are things that I said yesterday on stream that I could tell you I'm that I'm
not I'm there's nothing wrong with me and you clip me something that I said that I don't
even remember saying and I would be it'd be not possible for me to defend it all right put the
clock put the keys in the clock oh wait that's the get off me is it in Nancy's room yes it is
finally oh all right windy keys might just work on this clock use them uh which key will
you turn turn the right one oh fuck oh this is not gonna be okay hold on a minute here
how far does it move it moves let's see it was one two three four five six seven eight spaces
when you move left what is it when you go right one two three did it game over I went
I just need to see how many accounted and there's a secret door oh god there's
all kinds of there's a giant black book portal squares drawing the portal
square as instructed is only the beginning remember the portal square must be thoroughly
purified with holy water until it has been sufficiently charged with energy for full effect
only when the square is infused with light may the practitioner expect any ground-breaking
results so you need to do holy water and charge it portal squares need to be purified
with holy water I have four slices of holy water pie what's in here strange medicine
stand in a line there's a window nothing out there well it's is that sufficiently charged
that's it right so what do I do now go in where the hell is this gonna take me time
to get human transmutation freight transport oh it's like every time travel movie and
every time travel tv show I don't have enough to go back no it's impossible I don't have
enough to go back and they figure it out they find save it here every time travel movie is
Scottish yeah find me somebody that went back in time that didn't have an English or Scottish
accent can you do it doc from back in the future oh great scott great scott really oh he
didn't have he didn't say anything he wasn't like a great scott interesting try again
Arnold Schwarzenegger no sorry he has an accent he is a European accent Bill and Ted
but wait Keanu Reeves is where's Keanu Reeves from he's fake in an American accent where was
he born early life hey guess what uh Keanu Reeves was born in Beirut uh sorry guys
try again they time travel in the simpsons that's not a real character that's a that's not real
all right I'm doing the thing again ghost town dog uh this is a red phantom teddy bear do I have
to give the teddy bear to the red phantom oh I can hardly bear to look there's a heart
shaped pendant in its hand so get it so pick it up seems to be locking the other side
coming back in time I love people who pick it out so many random obscure time travel sequences
oh easy lock me at the side I have a bear what do I do with a bear
a blind guy pickle rick did at that time yeah you're right you're right pickle rick did
travel back in time you're right is this guy gonna be the new person I have to avoid here
yeah it is I'm gonna hear the bell new pursuer can't open these the reason why we have a cut
scene right now is it got back is there another person in the house
why are they all missing their eyes I'm gonna get ironed in the face
what the fuck I tripped the alarm sorry I didn't know you had like a home security system
merlin's home security that's what would actually happen in merlin's house you know
that they're like oh everything's flying around that's what actually would happen
people would die so where do I have to go now no no more this shit it's the ghost from the
beginning of the game the one that dropped the pot didn't give you very much time do they
blocked what is that what's on the wall a painting has hung been hung here it's all
crooked though maybe I should straighten it up so straighten the photo and any door please
move you're fine calm down still panicking all right not panicking anymore we have another case
to open albert's diary percy from the bakery gave me the name of a good optometrist in
london it's been seven years now since mum lost her sight and though she tries to appear
cheerful it's difficult to watch her grow old perhaps the doctor can do something to help
her it would be expensive I wonder if my saves would be enough so the doctor is doing this
relative ars name of john ha came asking if he could stay with us he's very cordial but I
can't help thinking there's something calculated about him I said as much to mother who scolded
me for judging a book by its cover I suppose she's right blood is thicker than water as they
say I've been hearing strange noises late at night for the last three days or so I heard
that a team of burglars have been striking homes in the area I must remember to lock
all the doors and windows at night okay it looks like a toolbox it's locked and will not open
do I have any keys this stuff the teddy bear a badly burnt teddy was it a person was it a
present to somebody do I have a guy got key in here don't I master key how did it get burnt
that's a great question probably from fire anything else in here the vase holds a moon
flower it looks like it's been turned turn it yeah I turned it out no I turned up see
well there's a new way to go the ladder goes down climb down yes
I made it down through the chimney that's an lol moments voice yeah it is where
kitchen key can I give this person back their teddy bear so they can leave me the fuck along
half heart pendant is another pendant outside all right let's complete that pendant
get away from me fire extinguisher they had fire extinguishers pack then
I wonder if I could use it for something I don't know maybe outside
let's go complete that pen the door won't open even when it is pushed it won't budge
great get the hell out of here into the kitchen plates that's it please sit in a
plate sit in a neat row finally teddy bear news reporter memo uh found v very important clue
to rand's murder we'll go back to house to investigate and gather info got a feeling about
this it'll be the biggest scoop in fleet street a newspaper clipping a sandwich between the
pages of the notepad serial killer ha meets grizzly end john ha the serial killer on the
run since early last year has been found dead at a metal plating works ha is held responsible
for the cold-blooded murder of several pensioners whom he robbed before placing the bodies in a
container of sulfuric acid thus disposing of the evidence what a sicko the acid used in
the crimes was stolen leading the police to place factories in the area with stocks of
sulfuric acid under surveillance the suspect appeared at a plating factory in horsham and
a struggle ensued ha lost his balance and fell from a platform into a vat of acid
ironically meeting the same end as his victims strangely enough months later he returned
with white face paint and clown makeup on leaving cards out of a deck and calling
himself the yoker a corpse it looks like it's been burned by something all right let's put
teddy bear film has been ripped out of the camera if i had some film maybe i could purge
the spirits didn't i just say i took it so what about the teddy bear put the teddy bear down
the burnt teddy bear no use for it now it's fatal frame yeah get the fuck away from me
why are you in here power is off probably best not to open that is there anything else
here the washing up is piled in the sink scary ghost i gotta complete that pendant outside
right here have tended to use item thank you thanks a lot spyro i'll teach you a new special
move i've never played that game i don't know what that means that's it that's all i get for
that an invisibility band are you kidding me shit you need to put these ghosts in the rumble
well let's keep going this car what's in the back of the trunk the inside of the car is scorched
and blackened a crushed box in the boot was it a present being delivered teddy bear come on
yep cool now you'll leave me the hell alone there's a sigil stone pretty good rest in peace
now the question is what the hell am i supposed to do the door won't open even when it's
pushed it won't budge don't kill the ghosts i'm not killing the ghosts i'm setting them free
did i miss anything else back here i got the pendant what else do i have for items
i got like a key got the kitchen key i was in the kitchen i still don't know what the hell
to do with this let me just take a quick gander this way can go down nope please god
next please god next not yet not yet i need film for that camera
i didn't examine any of this shit hold on no i'm missing something there was something
i didn't explore i didn't see the bed sleep in the bed the vase is facing north
let's say go down this i have the box here i need a tool kit i need a tool key
no nothing in any of these i need a key to this shed box use your bow and arrow why did i just
fucking listen to that one person i just press triangle triangles the bow and arrow why did
i listen to you why did i just look and press the button let's go back out here
are we down jump with the ghost here's this lady down here again i can't go in there
this is locked it won't open the picture frame needs to be changed i can't move it
what the dude that was walking around here shit fire extinguisher can i use a fire extinguisher
for something use that i i did use the kitchen key already you just get kind of it's just a way
to get out i think i missed something else though the fireplace has a lot now this is
what i am now i'm in the kitchen right now i'm in the kitchen this is the kitchen no it's
not the kitchen's upstairs no this is the way to go down and then the kid was that the
kitchen no nobody has a fireplace in the kitchen let's look at the map where's the kitchen so
where i'm right there i think out in the back around the corner there's something to do with
the fireplace something to do with the picture on the wall something to do there's no way i can
get out of this way right i can't leave so i got to figure out what to do here there's no
way out this kitchen which is here i opened that kitchen door this is the kitchen now what's
in this kitchen that's worth me looking at rubbish bin there's nothing in there
boxes nothing over there power is off nothing there this is the film camera film camera nothing
i can do with the film camera nothing dining table light switch i can go out what do i do
shit clover of love i don't know what this does go back to the main hall i guess i could
just teleport back to where it was right maybe i have to maybe i do just have to leave i feel
like i've gone through all the options which is activate the portal again oh my fucking really
come on i just had to walk back here huh she should have just done a pee we're hermine like
this face i would love that he drops up mom dick's desk key well now we do have to go
back thanks mom yeah talk about large marge one of the best characters ever made it's
unfortunate large marge never got her own tv show her own spinoff no i'm not gonna fill
it up again just in case i need it might as well save the game too why not tell them large
marge sent ya okay see the pee we made another like netflix special right and they cgi'd his
face to make him not look 68 years old imagine how painstaking that would be to frame by frame
cgi a guy's face to make him look 20 30 years younger pianos playing again all right so
bashing on the door i got the key i'm this is actually kind of nerve-wracking i don't want
to go out there hello no scary people right uh-oh i gotta go downstairs friends reboot
with cgi oh i gotta get back to the stairs friends reboot none of them are even that old
why would you have to do a reboot like that where the hell am i going cgi frame by frame
to make it a good show can you imagine having to do that shit they were what seven friends
and they're all on screen in the same time you have to do seven cgi frame by frame face
manipulations per second per 60 frames a second 60 frame manipulations on like the wrinkles
on jennifer aniston's head and what was the other guy's name uh i got ross perot that's
seven that's 420 face manipulations that dude that man even if you had 60 people if you
had 100 people on staff they would take them all day to do one frame of cgi make them
young again friends that's a full-time job for like 200 people all right we go dad's uh
dad's inventory whatever it is down here right so no one told you life was gonna be this way
you wanna go for broke and ride that fucking wave it's like you're always stuck in second
gear but hasn't been your day your week your month or even your year
put the dick in the key put the key in the deck whatever it's called book of entities too
in order to defeat a subordinate the murdered soul which acts as its energy source must be
healed to investigate the healing process a sentimental item belonging to that person
must be obtained if it would be able to and when this item has been found
the router power is boosted temporarily when we find that router we'll find the portal square
it appears what do i do a person must be a tow for a thief uh bomb just it's happening
again must be obtained if when the item has been found the router power is boosted
and this oh grandpa was the guy in the mask the guy in the beginning of the game
nothing else but what on the other side i knew it an order form from the camera shop
somebody bought lots of film you own it uh well if only grandfather were here i could
ask him what happened oh the mask the god the mask put it up here look at that one in the
top left now we got the secret laboratory it's up here grandfather mummy look at all these
old photos no there's a spike over there repellent arrow i got the special arrow
then this thing only uses for special occasions it's probably film right here yes of course there
is that's film give it to me give it to me it's right in front of me what are you
doing camera film now we just go back and put it in the camera is that grandfather's writing
1978 february 2nd
entities are scattered all over europe we the hamiltons are also of this lineage i am proud
rudablood is passed down to pete francesca was a group of my naive youth entities preferring
to believe that it was all just an old wife's tale i found the book and she began to sharpen
her wound finally opened my eyes to the truth began this is the kingdom hearts three
scenario right kingdom hearts one comes out king hearts two comes out and then they the
story just goes fucking crazy and they have to tie up a million lucents clock tower one
you were just scared getting chased by a guy why do we have to progressively get fucking weirder
disappearing in time generations spent their team duration coming of which well is a responsibility
that must be taken very seriously sadly another ruder have been hamilton household
first grandchild i chose for her the name alice she is bright and light perhaps even a little
strong will yet appears somehow wide beyond the praise she will grow strong and help will
fulfill her obligation as a noble sorry grandpa i don't think i want to do that i'm going home
a ruder family that's me so i am a ruder it's in my blood now maybe you should start not being
such a panicking little wuss when a guy with a sledgehammer shows up you're a goddamn ruder
start acting like one have the same rudestrain in my blood as my mother maybe i shouldn't be
flapping my fucking arms around like a seagull when somebody scares me i have magical powers
you're a ruder you're a ruder a ruder always pays his debts that's bad all right what do
you want me to do now yes i know that i'm a magical person and i have magical powers i have
a magical bow now i gotta go take the film yeah let's go deliver the film out save up
you've been on this game for three hours i'm interested well not not anymore but i was
up until we got to the plot of 48 of every animated show it was interesting
probably more than that remember there's nothing to be interested about flush it i can't yet not
yet wait once we put the film in the canister that is my like last will and testament as a
router how much did i spend on this one is this 200 no this wasn't 200 this one doesn't
have price tag on it i don't know why did i just walk right into that yeah i'm not done yet
into the secret room to splash the water on the thing go deliver the mail and let's get out
of here when i was supposed to play a 12-hour game yeah but that's that's the whole routine
though you know what i mean i can't start the 12-hour game now that like this i'm not gonna
do that now that doesn't be his own specific day it's gonna mess with my routine we were
promised 12 hours of ed ed and eddie and the game is probably terrible it's not like simpson's
hit and run well that's a game that i wanted to beat even though i hated every second of
it it still was an enjoyable sort of experience kind of now let's put the film in the
canister can you get away from me use the film there we go now you'll leave me alone
have some photos here first photo yeah okay somebody dumping a body in the dumpster
who took this photo you can't really see the suspect in it i wonder if the person
who took the photograph ended up a victim as well let's check the other one it's a
photograph of an open door with a hidden switch it's the painting is that one of
the doors in this house yes so the painting is the hidden switch just go move the painting
okay i would have done that earlier it's down here right when do we when do we actually get
to the clock tower i don't think we do must be around here oh what a hidden switch the clock
tower is just the name of the series guys it doesn't have to be a clock tower in every
clock tower game yes it has to how come there's no silent hill in silent hill yeah silent hill
with the first game was about like a misty silent weird transmission radio frequency mountain
second third one fourth one didn't even have a hill in it the fourth one you were stuck in a
room in an apartment there was no hill there it wasn't it was just a metaphor for the games
game's name give it a rest
dicky eyes
it's lovely so warm and soft thank you so much
why is this guy in here why is this like exterminator in here you're not gonna dump him
in the ass you're not gonna
jesus christ
want to join me in the acid
that was fucking terrible why is there so much terrible as shit
he sprays what is this this acid ass fight fire with fire throw it in his face
there was stuff in there
that guy was just on bath salts that wasn't even like a mur- i like
all right is that dorothy shawl how do i get that turn off the fan that was fucked up that
was fucked up it was i didn't know what to say about it if i could turn the bolt if i had
the night tools i didn't laugh at it it's shocking i told you this game's not funny
the presentation is insane it's no god damn it we all laughed at it
i'm funny you can't laugh at a comedy game it's not a comedy game it's
i need to find a way he's already down here what am i doing in the bathroom oh great
when i flush myself down the toilet is this like what's that what's that movie
get out of here i'm trying to use no that's not even funny you tell me i can't laugh
no laughing right you can't laugh at the fucking bugs bunny cartoon daffy duck guy got hit with
the door routine and i'm not allowed to laugh at this game are you just really give me a little
bit of the slack here what do i what was anything in this room there was like something
on the ground in here right invisibility band okay all right where do i go now five minutes
no laughing challenge again no i can't do that shit maybe i should try the door this is where
he came from right there's something else in here maybe something else here a key okay
toolbox there it is there's the toolbox key now i'm just trying i don't remember where that
toolbox was backtrack toolbox there he is again i hear him in down in the original of that house
jesus what the fuck he's much faster than the other guy burns it all right
leave
it's the way out it is okay toolbox is in where the hell is it
come on come on come on come on come on come on
come on open it it is a it's a night tool okay back down out and then back through the
picture frame where are you where are you where are you where are you where are you camera
where are you who are you what are you doing
i realized something that was wrong our place was infested with zombies he's too fat to go
through the chimney he is play the resident evil 2 dlc's i mean that is my current game
of the year and i can't believe i've only played through one time how could i say something
like that that how could i say that resident evil 2 is my favorite experience of the year
without but where are you i knew it and you that's not fair that you came through that way
because
the remix is so i'd love to hear it right behind we're all through now
the fan has stopped i should be able to get fruit get fucking destroyed idiot
he somehow got over them seriously yikes he's not yet invisible
what the fuck are you doing here what what's wrong with people
that ghost just snapped my back in half well that's the first time a ghost has done that to me
let's let me get to the end of this section here
dude this is to keep moving i think no button i can press no activation
doesn't go through watch out for this ghost steel door i can't hide in that why
why can i not hide in there there's a safe point right there wait what's this
electrocute him this guy have a name too he's a serial killer john the scorcher or something
lavender water it's a note on the table daughter's letter daughter's letter i don't feel
comfortable saving it when he's on the ground in the room oh it's john huh okay that makes
sense all right now at least i have a second to take a look at anything in this room
he's going to get up any second though nothing else in here at all nothing cable is sitting in
the puddle that is just asking for electrocution why don't i just go stand in it okay let's get
out of this i did pick up a new letter letter from a girl to her father must have been
read many times okay what keys no i just have that letter i wonder what i do with it
well you're here again across the way maybe then lock me the side uh not exactly what i wanted
to do maybe a secret back here germa stocks are tanking please make a joke uh it's all
right this is going to be a correction at some point it has to be which one is the
correct one there's two boards probably this one time to play the guessing game which one's
gonna break they got guessed right get off of it it's gonna break it oh it was scripted
it's scripted so in the water gas mask i was gonna be in the water wait did i not get it
maybe that wasn't scripted so is every roblox optical obstacle course do people
really do people play roblox is it is it a game that people actually play
there he is a constant reminder of the guy the guy that did it before you i actually did
guess it right the first time it's free and it's good no it's not that i forgot i just i was
trying to make sure i'm trying to clarify that that was correct so roblox is a combination of
it's like isn't it like garry's mod for kids it's like minecraft garry's mod and legos all
came together right you can make your own video games and stuff all right here we go
let us go across fast got it so i picked up there the shawl this is it this must be
the shawl that is what do i do with do i put it in the like acid
i found you
why is my meter not going down my heart is gonna beat out of my chest
um he's not even here meter i don't have to take a potion come on uh it's just a crouch
you can hear him breathing but where is he can you beat the game quicker i don't know
if there is a beat the game quicker haha funny jerma what are you talking about i didn't do
anything i'm not making any joke to references that was him right there somebody did he just
show up in the corner up there in the top right he did didn't he i just saw his acid spray
fuck you it was this lady it wasn't even him do you have to electrocute him again let's
zap him again okay so what did i i got the shawl so i need to go up back into where do i
bring the shawl i don't know where the shawl is supposed to go
oh
well i think i figured it out just walk back
it's pretty quick but wait
the power is granted to you young elisa as a rude let's see how many years in prison this guy had
corroder victims 31 sentence to 605 years in prison begin there she is
oh
oh he actually has a projectile i get it i'm gonna attach him here
two three four five
oh damn it i thought i could get away from it there she is fuck that has a huge hitbox of shit
there she is that's an attach gamer you playing come on get the projectile
three four five one two three
get it two two three four five got it it's time for you to die
what do you do how did you get out of that i thought it's three and then you can do the
magic move right
right here
three four five
okay you got one
don't do it don't do it don't do it don't do it there she is
it's hard because he's his moves stay stay stay stay stay back up
there's two what the fuck did you get people all the way back there what are you talking
come on go three bounce oh you suck try aiming there is no there is no aiming
i cannot move this around there is no aiming i just have to dive into the exact spot i had it too
this should take two fucking what's the what's my special arrow i have a special arrow don't i
she is that shit takes too long that's like six goddamn sides one two three four
five there she is it's too many years nobody even lives that life judgment go here we go
there she is there she is
so when he says damn it that's when you gotta do it
my goodness no no no damn it no come on stay there you son of a bitch
how do i shoot the special one how many times do i need before i can do it that's a good question
oh
let's try it there she is
this is this is stupid there she is
do it one more one more get it get it get it get it get it get it this is it this is it
kill him he's on three right three three do it why couldn't i do it r1 don't do anything
r1 i can't do it r1 r1 what's that there she is there she is you need more than three
you need six no i didn't i do it with three last time
full charge when he has enough tethers yeah in four no you 100 need six tutorial said six
six i have one special arrow but it's like the repellent arrow just that range you get it
right after the other one three don't don't do it
oh it's three according to the wiki i got three on them right now
it's three according to the wiki what happened is let me see what happens when i do this
i can't even cancel this what does this do there she is
oh yeah so that's what i thought you do one in each corner and then
it's the manual that's what i was thinking too somebody said that i didn't have to do that
though i was like yeah there's one there now there's like one over here right in each corner
over here
he's tethered now right r1 fully charged r1 r1 r1 he's got four on him
r1 cover it covered his fucking hair r1 game over i win it is r1 you have to do it had to be four on
the wiki live somebody edit that page to make sure it's correct it must be the amount of years
maybe something like that this is stupid he dropped what did you drop a crystallized
what is it clover of courage i have two of these now i have the triforce of wisdom
triforce courage did you drop anything else i don't think so now we have to return the shawl
and see the cutscene of them floating up right the second gem for the gauntlet it's now it's
time to quit the game how do i get out of here i have to climb back through i guess so we are
now too invested it has to be finished i don't i don't know if i can do that finish it you
might as well just beat it floygan brothers all right i don't even have the dreamcast hooked up
cutscene or something really weird angle floygan brothers are they in here
where were they where did he dump them like there what do i return the shawl to i'm not
sure kitchen was there another level down here you think it'd be right here is this
pre-recorded he's not talking to us i've been what we've been talking the whole time
there's one of the barrels yeah maybe i just have to go back or something it wasn't this
barrel what the heck use maybe uh hold on i use the shawl uh i don't think i think it's just a
random key item hand knitted shawl must give it to dorothy well wait maybe back down okay
hold on wouldn't she in oh the okay no no no wait wait wait wait wait wait wait the the room that
was the merlin room i gotta go back down and out of here back into the house does germa make
chat messages up to respond to in order to make jokes i don't think so and make up chat
messages now that was a really good one from uh mr steven 22 we should get a cut scene in
here because this is the room that she was in yeah here we go here's your shawl
i can see albert albert what about albert we don't have an item for albert
i waited so long for you remember this is the winter show you knitted for me
oh mother i can see i can see too there we go very much dorothy albert goodbye
he said they're being abducted by aliens easy yeah destroying two subordinates it's me
we have to run away from him now this game is an emotional roller coaster
that's what i was saying i can't help it if i have an outburst every now and then because
the game is out of control no not thunder two i only know thunder one uh here's the clock tower
took him three and a half hours of four hours of the game before we got to see it
yeah that was the fucking porn music
see those two spirits were stopping the clock tower from being rebuilt and now the two of
the spirits are dead it's is he's strong enough now this is no longer your home
this is the dark realm where i rule into your 15th birthday will arrive
when that happens you and i will become one and together we will obtain eternal life
my my 15th birthday are you looking forward to it so am i my dear so am i i can't wait
soon we too will be united forever alissa you might have defeated two of our number
but your mother was killed by a subordinate long ago the dramatic spinning was a little too
much for me how's she fine she's float down uh well let me uh let me go take one more pee
break and we're gonna find out what we're gonna do i'll be right back mic not muted that's
whatever that's fine yeah we both uh talax and i both took a break at the exact same time
somehow and we just did a unpause did you pee together no all right so here's the question
i have how much is left does anybody have any idea 12 uh hold on what time to beat
clock tower three how long is clock tower three five and a half hours to beat the whole thing
i'm like six hours or so more to beat the whole thing halfway through it it's like five it's like
five and a half to eight hours ah damn it damn it if there was like another hour and a half
do it you sound mad snap the disc in half no let me just let me i want to see what else
let me see what's out here let's just see what's outside you know i'm not gonna keep i'm not
gonna keep i'm not gonna beat it i'm just gonna see well that's lavender water new face game
for this i can't i don't have any clothes on i don't okay look i could tell you that this
game sucks right and you probably all be like yeah it sucks but he ran into his house without
closing um yes i don't wear shirts he already knows this he's very he was very much aware
but already uh but no but i'm like having fun light is filtering through i can crawl through
here these ps2 streams were never meant to oh you know what i'm gonna play this one for
six hours but i i don't know sometimes it just kind of happens right lantern has been left behind
with someone here the ghost hit and run was 12 hours yeah i don't maybe no i'm just gonna keep
going until i kind of don't care anymore and maybe that'll be like another 10 minutes maybe
that'll be like another hour i don't know i still have a lot of other things over here
to to check out but this has been very interesting and fun i'm at chapter three out
of five so i'm like at the halfway point okay put the drill away it's locked i find the key
i just want to see the new scary man yeah what what's the new scary thing
new weirdo if you consider playing alan wake i've already played alan wake
unfortunately i've already got i've already seen it i have never beaten alan wake but i did
get to like the final chapter in the game bubbles we're ever gonna see the egg again
um i don't know that's a good question i would not gonna rule it out the egg is the next boss
worker's key that opens the door back there fish eel there's an electric eel just no why
what oh god damn it are you kidding me how is that even i wish now i wish the webcam was on
hold on all right so i picked up my drink i just have a glass there's coffee in it right
and i don't know what happened i moved it like too fast and it like
like shot up out of the glass like t-rex style and got all over my mic like splashed
into my mic i don't know how that happened that was so dumb that again that was seriously a
physics puzzle picked up the glass and moved it towards my mouth and must have shimmied a little
it's gonna stink like coffee in here can't wait i bought sippy cups too for this very
fucking reason i haven't even used them because i'm too embarrassed i have to use them your
voice sounds so much more rich and full-bodied now well actually i didn't buy the sippy cups
you guys did well no i did but you guys made me buy them right yes that's what happened
this guy's fast kratos can i steam him
you can't get away splash him what are you doing girl
splash him with your stuff oh i'm fucking dead please don't i was trying to splash
when you can't splash when you're panicking apparently wow you suck no i didn't i'm trying
to splash him to stop him the streamer has a very dicky brain this guy sucks this guy
fucking sucks
forget about the fish all right work is key forget about it i get i mean i could throw the
just door on the other side here here he comes
what does it not work on this guy is it just a human
away fish tank nice trick fish tank nice trick
thank you fish
all right let me wait till my sanity comes back
this guy's just twitch jay and that initial like that was just forehead all right let's go
i don't know why i just thought of and uh donkey kong country every boss
anyways never mind nice trick nice trick please get out of here
nice trick i didn't even know how you could do that so okay in donkey kong country every boss
when you hit them you do like a dodge roll thing you jump on their head they do that
that's what it reminds me of sans no no that's every boss okay are you gonna come
through the door again or can i just can i leave through the workers door you use the workers
chew yes it's gonna show up right here he's gonna be in the ceiling or something you can't
get away yep yep yep yep b3 go in i don't know i don't know touch it go uh b2 patches
yeah it kind of does b2 basement two this guy has no backstory there's no what the hell how did
you even get behind me that was so not cool oh nice trick this game is so fucking dumb
um but it's something about it is it's fun
so there's a box here with a crowbar i'll take it so i have a crowbar now was there something
i could do with this i think that a sub sound i guess we're gonna go back up so we're gonna
go to b1 i guess we need a new one rip it from here somehow first floor b1 this is where
i was before but wait there might be something i can do with this this idiot came okay check down
here oh we need to do this again gloves okay you got the rubber gloves he's getting close
a circuit breaker the power's been turned off turn it on doesn't seem to be doing anything
you can't get away
well maybe we can stop dancing all right i have rubber gloves and a crowbar he's fast
he's fast don't come in here with me close the door close close be free
he doesn't need to get in the elevator he just shows up all right so i have gloves and a
crowbar of course i hate this guy anything else i need to do i need to save right now
i haven't saved it in a while i might take the invisibility thing
oh i'm gonna do it no no i'm good ah there's an item over there what the
fuck is that a gun there's something inside the wooden box distribution plan b1 b2 b3 a1 a2 a3
so you can get to a2 from b1 b2 you can get to a3 is this a puzzle i don't this is bad
it works now didn't work last time and now it's here i got a lot of random items
i'm not sure what to do with wow why are you so fast
fast
nope please stop falling and moving in random directions that truly was a nice trick
that's a b no b2 item b2 i'm gonna hang out here for a second though i want this to go down
on it because he'll this is not gonna go down i mean i'm pretty hidden that's annoying
that's not going down go down what are you waiting for go down i can hear him running
all right what's this item item he just handled me in the head
where did you actually just hit me with that fuck wrong floor move now look at that hitbox
give me a break what floor was it will you stop this nonsense
there's b1 nonsense meter here i gotta take another one of those potions
gotta use it somewhere okay b1 let me see there's an item somewhere that i missed
to the right of the elevator that was to that was to the elevators right that was
the right of the elevator god damn it you meant literal like my like i don't
like the right of the like the elevator right i can't even get this just
an invisible leave it's just an invisibility van it's not even an item let me look at my
items thick rubber workman's gloves useful for electrical work standard chikrow bar looks as
if it may be useful at some point so i have gloves okay i'm gonna go back there's probably
something there was he had to walk right by him nice trick need to lose this fucking guy
the electronic door lock the power gonna get her lamp is off oh god i'm gonna lose
do i have to put the gloves on and do the breaker no no no no no duck
so crowbar electrical gloves i tried where is this breaker
shit the main electrical cable cut rubber gloves might help you use it which wires
you want to connect all right so can i look at my menu to see the thing i can't look at
it was like i can't look at the map i kept it canceled and he's gonna be right here
not my map my inventory so bottom left connects to middle top so bottom left to top middle
bottom middle to top right so it goes when it started bottom left to top just
top ah bottom left middle just okay bottom bottom left middle bottom middle right bottom right
left so it just goes two bottoms of one two three so it goes two three one two three one
so i want to move this one to the middle it's okay it's doing top to bottom fuck i was doing
bottom to top so okay so we're gonna middle middle left right to the middle
i'm gonna do left to the right right is this the switch down here
get up why does it take you so long away oh where's the staircase get up the staircase
don't go panicking yet i hate you i'll i have to take the invisibility thing
please just get in there please just get in there open the door just be ready open it go in
okay be be be be touch it why can i touch it he's not gonna come here right
stop panicking really why am i still panicking we're gonna get out of this he's right there
b2 right oh i want you to be able to cheese the game all right but i need to okay which
way do i go from here turn on the do this whole thing again just to get it right
i was the last save point i don't need there's not i don't have a save point
fuck oh where's the power level i'm dead wrong floor everybody said b2
i there was at least 10 b2s oh no use the holy i should get a good continue here use the holy
water i i know but my brain the first time it didn't work and now my brain thinks it's not
gonna work b2 oh bad that's a long that's a very long segment there's a long ass segment
from no saves or anything you can't get away but now i know like it kind of what to do
so i have to get the gloves i gotta just kind of wrap around i'm not gonna use that
unless i need it again these gloves so let me like to put this into memory forever
is it okay here they are here we go is the i think i might have to get this to open the box
this okay let's stop them so okay that can remember this level this is what which b is this
the asshole give me one this is b3 this is not b1 we're gonna go to b2 so b3 has the console
b3 has box b2 has some other shit what does b2 have b2 has
watch out buddies this is the crowbar i'm not gonna use this yet until i need it
this girl is so fucking awkward like really you just come on
i have three of them i don't want to use it right now though
oh two has dog shit nothing here b1 you can't blame a 14 year old girl for falling over when
hit by an axe where is he i don't think he spawns until you take a step out there
i'm gonna sit here for as long as it's necessary he doesn't spawn until you take a step out
i'm not stalling i'm trying to make it so i don't have to use a potion
stalling or trying to play correctly which one let's keep going i need the gloves and then b3
here he comes see told you this guy needs to fuck off
b3 is boss anything else over here need to check make sure don't miss anything there
could be something over here there okay okay yep yep yep yep yep uh what i'd say about that
yep if you could just stand up
stop panicking stop panicking don't do it again
move i wasted so many items there for no reason b3 we are on b1 b3 do the box b1 power
somebody just wrote b2 get the fuck out of here with that
oh we sure it's gonna be two b3 box so it is uh remember this
and it's left left in the middle it's the middle of the left and then give him a chance
b1 stand from the next room over and you shut the fuck up for two minutes it's almost
two a.m and i can still hear you i had a hard day doing real work for 13 hours and i just
want a little bit of peace and quiet although just kidding it's tanner from high school again
enjoy having you playing your kids games that just threw me off i don't know what i'm doing
oh yeah okay power the way down flip the switch now i have to go back key card reader
which is where i don't remember i think the power is flowing
same floor i need chat to confirm that would be right now same floor it worked i think the
power is flowing yes so go so open the door uh oh where's the key card
maybe i don't have to activate something here maybe i have to do the thing where i
burn them something else in here i guess i should activate this i'm just gonna catch
oh nice trick we know how this is
so i have an opportunity just to not have to worry about him now
my question is is there anything else in b2 that i can do i need a key card which i don't have i
have a crowbar does he have a card he doesn't have a card maybe i have to go back and use
the crowbar upstairs somewhere nothing else in the boxes nothing right no i'm just gonna go
back i'm just gonna get the hell out of here save save i'm going going going going going
going going going where do i go from here uh can i leave i don't think i can get out of here
how do i get out of here is this the way out this is the way out right yeah yeah yeah yeah
refill the holy water okay nice you're doing a great job keep up the good work hey thanks
thank you all right so what is there i have a crowbar can i use the crowbar on the fish
i don't think there's nothing in here i can do maybe a different direction but either way
oh really like there's no escape
crowbar this looks like i can fuck it i'll need i'll never be able to lift that lid
yes i will there's no handle open so i can't get back excuse me i have crowbar what
bro the crowbar and i could go down wow yes please poor guy what do you have what is that
doing here couldn't have been locked in here it's holding a note a message is scratched on the
paper how many days have passed since he locked me up in here i can barely write anymore i came
in to rescue you but now i have too been made a prisoner i've been broken my promise
to protect you soon i'll be unable to even record these feeble thoughts i have lost the spectacles
which you gave me is it too much to ask for any remnant of you in my last hours it's pretty
terrible but what do you got a pocket knife there swiss army knife empty spectacle case
i need to i gotta find the guy's glasses right there they are they were right in front
of you the whole time man i got it i got it i have your glasses look i'm trying to put
them in there do you not see me with them in my hand what was he said rest in peace
what were you what egg were you sitting on is above the hatch key card there it is
progress so that was b1 right is he gonna be sitting right in front of me save the game
okay
nice trick you really you want to be teleported because even he can come right back in
music music stopped save it holy water refill save the game nice i just have a short question
for you i know you're streaming so i'll keep the question fast and simple i don't want to
be a bother although the larger spectrum of things this is time is quite minimal universe
took 13.7 billion years to form after over here i offer you uh 30 seconds of human communication
regardless thanks for answering ahead of time what are you talking about maybe one day i can
ask a more in-depth personal human question for my good friends i don't these don't make any
sense like 60 000 years ago the guy a guy who like wrote the bible you know what we're
gonna leave behind hey it's jeff from psychology 101 that's gonna be our generation's bible i hope
so oh it's been just been five hours and i've been i've been driving in circles for five hours
god this is the same guy here he is he's here car key inside super special arrow
you got a repellent arrow and holy water refill and a save point and super special
and the end of the fucking game not yet oh mosquito speaking of mosquitoes i have to get
mr mosquito it's another game that i have i don't have it liar but i'm gonna get it
it's so dusty nobody has used it in a while did i miss something so dusty nobody
yeah that's another expensive one though i feel like this is the boss fight they did just give
us a repellent arrow that's one of the bunnies from castle griffinstein so it's kind of odd
to see that here that's actually pretty terrifying uh brand new toy railway i can't be the one
i was given when i was a child where did i just end up mom gave me that statue it should
be in my room why is it here nothing of interest here it's locked don't max pain me
here please not yet i can't get it it's locked hmm nancy what is mom's name doing there
this is the same it's the same audio file all right fine baby the baby is probably gonna be me
and i'm gonna watch the harry potter sequence where i get the scar that baby
sure did figure out how to talk and sing very quickly
mom is that you where are you we're gonna get another merlin room the whole thing's gonna
swirl around elisa my sweet baby this necklace has been handed down in the hamilton family
for generations there are four leaves one each for love friendship i need the other one i
almost get piece number three four leaves together lead the wearer to true happiness
i'll give it to you elisa when you're older oh you're laughing isn't friendship just weaker
love darling father elisa has laughed for the first time that should be a half piece
oh
going over the edge
why didn't you have to marry a man like you a man with no spy no spirit to axe turning
it's not funny but you've seen that truth it was your beloved grandfather who murdered
your father that's impossible it's not true
here we go boss fight i don't even know this guy's name it's time
you know if i was smarter and more prepared i would have already queued up like the sailor
moon transformation song just been playing it right now just imagine i did that just you do
it this is the we're almost done with the game here we go chopper 44 victims how many years in
prison 921 years sentenced your health bar is enormous judgment begin welcome he's doing some
cool tricks speaking of nice trick you can't get away
oh
you can't get away
so
that sucks the other guy was way harder oh wait you are going to suffer the same fate as all the
rest on magical bow no that was weird we didn't get the piece just an excuse to reuse him in
the next chapter that's probably what it is you'd be correct i would assume hey nice trick devs
the scroll that i just picked up 1998 may 12 my sweet elisa my sweet elisa you do a small
hands have grasped my heart and will not let go to think of the frizz it is more than i
can bear i consented to the marriage so as to protect the rudder bloodline i realize now that
was a foolish mistake and lacks class and has not a shred of dignity he loses no opportunity
to exhibit his stupidity and weakness of character even nancy has been affected by his
rubbish saying that she does not want to raise elisa to be a rudder of course the existence
of a rudder is fraught with danger but given the gravity of the situation and the great
responsibility of a rudder family the obligation cannot be shirked any attempt to avoid such a
duty is indeed shameful as long as i am the head of this house that man will never be accepted
as one of us no date finally philip went too far i could no longer allow him to large gap
there that headstrong act has turned me into a vile murder my secret to the cannot allow
Hamilton legacy to be disrupted there is nothing to be done but handle the police carefully
and tread with the utmost caution there's police in this universe i feel like they don't
there isn't now the cops are involved there's my magical rudder bloodline and monsters and
kratos's and all the fucked up magic that we have in this world bow and arrows made out of jewels
police yeah just dialed 911 to see if we could get them to come investigate is this one of
those things it's the magical police no it's not the magical police it's going to be like
the nypd what else in here yes germa your t is ready why inside the bracelet the necklace
this is this is gonna be four quadrants this way there's one that way he's going back and forth
it's this sound in my ear i'm sorry it's causing me so many problems good thing i found
this shito this is like shito prove she does a lot prove she does live no it's fine boss fight
phase two or what is this my entire lady there's all these witches is this the fucking
belemonts i don't understand yes i made a reference to the castlevania netflix show
it's pretty good i was killed by an entity and have been trapped in the darkness ever since
it's too dark to see anything where am i tell me where i am those cursed entities
i wish i just wish i could be resurrected to fight them what a shame a subordinate stole my heart
from me and the entities used it to perform the ritual of engagement wait what is the ritual
of engagement tell me tell me what's going on this game sucks
yes but it is good because i'm still playing it and i've done too invested so i'm gonna beat it
i gotta be getting close i probably only have like another 30 or 40 minutes in this game
i have to turn the game volume down yeah i'm sorry i'm probably killing everybody
was it nothing what about the letter i guess we're just gonna turn around
so four hours four hours i don't believe that but for real what uh there we go all right so now
they did turn into one of these where does this one take me back to the house maybe please
change the song this song is still there i'm sorry same thing what the hell is that letters
engraved in the wall read the engraving a curse upon any who would desecrate our sanctuary
only she of rudder blood may heal our wounded spirits i was trying to hit that but now i can't
walk over there again hello the noise is somehow worse when it is quieter there's not i can't do
anything about i have to hear it too remove see rudder stone is that not desecration
see rudder letters are engraved in the wall read the engraving tomb of the rudder warrior
protector of the earth a painting of soldiers riding black horses so i gotta put the earth
cube in here the c cube goes in the other ones this is gonna be a pain in the ass
oh yeah there's gonna be a pain in the ass this is the c cube american rudder warrior
okay rudder stone cannot be removed only one may be carried oh god damn it
a tomb of the rudder warrior captain of the seas so i have to put this one down and take
that one out somewhere else oh my god get off me get off me you take that that much panic
use it i i can't use the stone wait i thought use it use it use it use it use it use it use
it what i there's already one in there i can't use it guys now i've wasted i've wasted two
jiggles of liquid well what's down the front hallway hopefully another one i'm gonna run
into this stuff okay what's in here yeah yep yep all right easy cannot be removing one may be
carried this is the air so how the fuck am i supposed to do this if i can only carry one
and i can't put it anywhere else what about maybe the other side is it gonna be one that's
empty there's only three places so i'm gonna go i'm gonna go to the other side
okay well there's the little holding place so now i got this is a pain now you tell i gotta
go down here go get the warrior one go put the warrior one where it belongs wait where's
the warrior one is over where the hell is it over here i don't know is this the warrior
one is the air one sky router no i need the warrior one he doesn't remember oh no i don't
remember on this one which hallway was it in no there it is i'll take that please earth router
yep and put it over there this game sucks so much
this goes in here get off of me earth insert the earth router stone thank you now i will
cleanse your spirit take this as a token of my gratitude i'm going back to luigi's mansion
okay didn't give me anything now i gotta get the water one and put it in the straight up there
stolen joke was it from where where did i steal that from oh no air air air give me air
i had it you saw it you stole it from luigi thank you for releasing me from this terrible
game i'm now going to go to a better game luigi's mansion i gotta watch out because this
thing's gonna kill me luigi's mansion was trash jesus now i gotta refill ban that guy
that guy i tried don't panic how do you remove somebody else's sub um i'm sorry you can't
it's not something you can do is there no music in this game or is it muted it's currently
muted because it's it's a piercing ear sound that is at a very high frequency
it's causing people a lot of stress by the way there are two of these so i'm gonna have to do
this again on the other side bet you a dollar double or nothing double or nothing yeah this is
the c1 this is the c1 this is the c1 right that's the earth one fuck not like this it's
the one on the right there's only three rooms it shouldn't be that hard to remember the
thing is when i get like bored i start to not pay attention and i'm sitting here like
look at the chat and talking to you guys and hanging out and having a good time having
a fun time having a good time the world record for this game is an hour and 19 minutes
interesting what is that a disc it's not having a good time if you're bored
this is supposed to be i knew we were going to play this for longer than an hour
i knew it and we did and now this whole stream has been clock tower three
tomorrow we're going to continue playing playstation games playstation 2 compass of light
just put it in here so we have another side to do one ps2 game at a time that's not usually
how it happens but the cutscenes in this game the game mechanics were just i had to see it
through it's just too much had to do it what's on the other side uh i knew it we're gonna do
it again watch it's gonna happen again this time it'll be five rooms instead of three
right one two three four i see five rooms through the graveyard there's a car here
all right the music's gone you can't get away uh so you're back now that's it you just hear
you don't want to get away can somebody just snipe them
ritual engagement will begin again oh god again what no i'm not you're right it's mom's handwriting
22 out of three two weeks until alice's birthday i'm so worried that i don't know what to do with
myself i sent her to boarding schools that she wouldn't have to fight as a router but will the
enemies let alice's heart go so easily they say a router heart is necessary in the ritual of
engagement a router heart taken from the body of one who has reached her 15th birthday i only
hope that she can elude them until her birthday is passed are you done reading
well here's this thing now now where do i go the shed nice trick i already fought this guy
why do i have to fight this guy again axe um wouldn't want to sleep in that bed
is he not on here oh this is a hiding spot why are you screaming what's he doing here
it's probably an item in here that i need to get hiding behind a see-through curtain
that doesn't work just bring the whole jar i know right mummy are you really dead
no you asshole game i'm gonna go and just my head my head's gonna start spinning here
why am i going back i'm just trying to get away from this guy temporarily
so i don't panic so now i can just chill and let it dissolve and then i'm gonna go back in
relax back to the mosquito music so that the shed is probably the item in the bed
i wonder if he's here too i don't think he is though where can i refill this
is there now let's see what happens when i go down there no no fountain over here is there
fun this way i mean i could go over here but i don't have enough to teleport no i can't even
go over here anymore fountain fountain no fountain as well there's one back here and it's a safe
point abort this game look we'll be live tomorrow with more playstation 2 i'm still
getting enjoyment from it so don't worry four hours out of five okay so let me look at the map
so i am currently standing where the fuck am i standing i just came out of what the top left
so if i go down there's a book in there a save point and all right i'm gonna go all the
way down back to the shed back to the shed damn it really did i miss you can't get away
oh man these dumb fucking butterflies are all over me now
get off me get the fuck off me too many swears
bad save point when he comes in the door i'm gonna splash maybe he's not even gonna come in
here all right i didn't get a chance to look in here so there's there's a book all right
i had to get this probably book of entities three no dad i don't want you to read this
a woodcutter by the name of harold was born in wales hideously deformed he suffered taunts at
17 he proposed marriage to emily dickens he was uh rejected in tallies and he said he had uh
okay this is the person we're talking about here for years out following the gruesome event
he went from village to village and butchering people two years later he was caught by villages
and killed however powell was possessed by an entity and arrived to hunt and it's this guy
all right good desk is old i'm gonna just hide in here item on the bed i'm gonna wait for that
music to stop that face when he won't see my message i just did he's currently in the house
place yeah psiops i have psiops right here i will absolutely be playing that tomorrow
for sure come on get out of there item on the bed what is it lavender water
so i gotta where the hell am i supposed to go interesting down here
no that's just the save point you know the other two circles
fuck it i'm going to sleep and it is getting fairly late you guys are going to bed uh have
a great night maybe i'll see you tomorrow anything else over here midnight well it's not
late really for me but it's almost three a.m eastern that's very late i can understand
if you want to skedad statue of a two-eyed lion there is a switch inside its mouth
okay so there's two more switches to press it's 12 eastern what time is it right now
oh it's 9 15 i thought i don't know why i thought it was midnight i thought it was like
12 15 i don't know why it's got so lost there okay there's the one in the middle
what about that's probably blocked pressed oh fuck off going downstairs is so hard for this
girl just go down the stairs something is written along the outer frame purify thyself
with holy water and awaken the lions in order awaken the lions in order i hope i did this
right it's got three that one has three on his head i'm going to assume that means
that that's the third one to press let's just see if i may let's see if it works
does this one have two or one it's almost got one damn eye one two three
uh one what what what what what what the fuck are you talking about is it already done
stop panicking you can't get away so holy water is going to reset them
from my understanding do we have to have this dickhead just following me
nothing happened all right so here we go this is two right this is two i need to do
the one on that's three one two three i'm gonna run out wrong one one two three i know it's not
the one over here i know it's the one in the middle but like i currently have to run away
and i'm gonna get hit in the head and i'm gonna lose so i have to take this too
you really have to come this way why would you follow me up here i'm invisible i'm
invisible all right entry and then flash the holy water on the damn thing
i have to like bait this guy around he's gonna block them you're gonna block my exit
double tap i love that not having control of my damn character it's it's really fun
and compass of shadows now no i have to see this through all right so i have the compass
of shadow so i have two items now compass of light compass of shadow i still have these
dumb gloves i have to go refill my shit too i gotta move just get out of my way
fucking come on get away from me i'm gonna panic
ah
he turns around i swear to god he wouldn't even need to teleport out of here please
thank god oh all right so now that i have the two compasses i'm gonna save the game
where do i bring the two compasses back to the courtyard the front courtyard there
that was a nice trick so the two compasses they don't really have a description
i'm gonna go i'm gonna leave hopefully he's not just standing here he definitely will be
and here's the butterflies again get away from me you're gonna do the stupid thing you're gonna
get all right
what are these things eating for what are they for no this way
all right just no stop i can't i can't even do anything oh i'm gonna die and whatever we
have to restart just walk into it let me ask for something where's your bow why don't you
just have your bow and arrow out at all fucking times you have to like get blessed and ask
permission to use the bow just use the bow just have it you have to like sprinkle fucking
candy at people there's a circular indentation it's gonna be one on the other side too
okay can i be out of this hellhole she's in the shadow realm please somebody can get out of the
shadow realm we got meltdown brewing only when mummy said so well i already have a refill
that i can save it here okay i'm getting real tired of like reusing the same chapter three
enemy for the rest of the game can't we get like the the mayor from nightmare before
christmas to come back i made it up maybe something scary something scary something scary
something scary something scary something scary i think so maybe that was an interesting angle
to not have anything scary this is a binding arrow i don't have they didn't teach me how to
use that the only clock tower in the game is in the save menu i think technically we're inside
of the clock tower
what that's why they're talking about my heart
but who who wants to drink my blood to become an entity who would do this
what the hell is this
a new arrow a new super arrow old rudder arrow so did i get an arrow upgrade
that's how ocarina of time ended now we'll get sighted what do you mean so now i can actually
hurt this guy what's gonna happen there's a guy the wicked witch of the west laugh
and i'm gonna arrow of light him right in his sternum got to hurry back all right
it's that easy oh you're back i wonder did you happen to get a new power i just noticed his hair
what chance does a pathetic little girl like you have to bring salvation to the dead ruders none
all right new power let's use it we already know this guy this guy's 900 years in prison
we're just doing it again do i have to equip them or is it auto equipped
you guys tell me i was in the shadow realm and i couldn't use my powerful light bow
what's this chopper we already know 44 victims that's to 921 years
there we go i wasn't fast enough you are fast i'm gonna have to bind him come on two three
now he's taunting that's a good time to do it
okay come on one two three four five get it again again come on again again again again
again don't get hit by the boomerang thing take a step over here step over here
fuck you have to do it again god damn it i'll tell you all these boss fights really just
feels like luck anything just catch it
that was a gigantic collision on that thing
i stopped it hit me in the face no that's not okay stick stick him stick him duck duck duck
that didn't hit him
fuck this game oh it's the god
you can't get away
am i gonna just can i whittle him down like a bar of soap
all right i'm gonna do i'm one i'm one away i wanted to beat this
um i at least beat this guy i gotta beat this guy and then we'll play like a goofy one
like no i don't have what do i even have that will take no none of these are all gonna
take too long why can't i just aim with the control stick is there a reason why you left
that out of the game you can't get away fuck you one more one more bingo uh that didn't
how did you not get i feel like something broke here i'm supposed to get like an
ending cutscene that i beat it something's not right here something's not right
you can't get hey what the fuck give me a second to do anything
fuck get out of my please oh oh my fucking god he has a a sliver of health
that was an anti-climactic he was supposed to die from the big one this is the last one
no he okay i was gonna say if this is like i'm the enemy in the next chapter too
too third piece of the puzzle clover of hope i killed that guy yeah i know i did now will
they know that i did this
bye did i bring her back no the merlin
now you're in my domain here's the clock tower we made it we made it to the clock tower
that's the weird guy you're running really fast
all four leaves elissa it'll be okay i'm here i'll do anything to help you
well you don't understand tennis i'm gonna have to eat your heart
and save mom from the entities that's the spirit don't forget you can count on me if
there's anything i can do just ask just one thing i'd like to know
where the places are we is this place close yeah dennis is going to get fucking eviscerated
why do you think that that's so terrible we're a team now i gotta check something okay just i
gotta make sure that you know i get a test to see if you're a monster or not i've got a
companion now wait you're not coming with me elissa wait for me now it's just a giant
escort mission this is gonna be hell we're gonna have two health bars aren't we
dennis where are you sis what but you said she wouldn't be back for another six months
where are we but that's her no mistake i'm sure of it oh no oh no he's gonna get eviscerated
isn't he i couldn't leave you in that house alone any longer no missed you so much
he's gonna get eviscerated hey look it's helena bonham carter in every tim burton movie
and okay never a bunch of other people nice to meet you elissa you have some remarkable
powers but no one is powerful enough to defeat us if you want to do oh god
does she what just do you have him but what is she is she having by the neck what
is that through him i thought that was through his neck uh okay well we got a picture of
photo of mother that's great there's a body here who would do something like this
dennis letter to linda hey sis how's africa have you seen any elephants i'm not too bad
living alone is really hard though don't know how you managed to raise me i'll never say this
to your face but i do appreciate that you know when you get back i'll find a job and do
my share just another six months oh it'll go by in a blink i'll write again take care says
dennis is there a door this music is the worst so far that door won't open that door
won't open it's ultra clown music it's the worst kind of clown music door won't open
bathroom is there a safe point i can get uh okay okay that is a hiding spot
sucks all right we got it uh there's a sturdy lock on it it won't open
is that a portal square if only i could open this door this music's so bad we really have
to listen to this the whole time stand up looking glass what's that do i wonder why the cupboard
doors don't open they're not broken there must be another way to open them strange motif on it
definitely not a normal mirror i still have these gloves somebody just said something really
funny king's quest level of midi it really is this song really actually is in king's quest
that was absolutely perfect well i have a mirror now chair can i take the steel chair
i'm gonna start driving people fucking crazy do i have to look in mirrors
oh great i need the bathroom into the bathroom into the bathroom
don't open that door i'm almost about to panic get thank you jesus
oh that's a hiding spot so we do examine the mirror again maybe i should hold the mirror up
to the mirror the looking glass is reacting to the mirror let's see what happens all right uh
sure i need a save point so desperately that's a release form what does it say uh hum
horrible the can i use the mirror i can't use the mirror for this red rum it is the mirror
realm that's you're right what's this save point give me a holy water refill and a save point
and here maybe let's it's just the same thing mirrored let's look there's nothing in here
stand up why does it take you so long to stand up well let's open up this
and here they come again uh it's just lavender water good thing i just aggroed
the bad guy yeah good i aggroed oh back it up all the way all the way back up back back go this
way you still in here are you still in here coming back gone shit keep going down no there's
no save point down here i'm shit out of luck i have to no keep stupid things oh come on
not fair how far is that fair you show me the fairness that's in that i can't what the fuck are
you supposed to do about this do i have any visibility again no i'm in a lot of trouble
get the fuck off of me move why are you even in here the door is not going to open
what about this one that door is not going to open either oh god leave me alone leave me alone
this is a photo of a child that door's not gonna open either do any of these doors actually open
bathroom no i can't hide here they know i'm here go in there you took it so long to get in here
with the haste with a sense of urgency refill with toilet water
they won't know the difference you just really just do the hulk hogan entrance
give me a save point i need items too why would you you were just you were gone you were gone
you were gone you were gone this door is not gonna open either how i can't believe it i am
actually shocked right now shocked beyond belief there's no way that that's fair
i have no items i have no save point i have nothing i have to go through the mirror again
is there a save point here there's not even anything it's a key that's required i don't
have it and there's no point to save the game so what am i supposed to do and you're already here
i have like the letter and shit i can hear your jowls shaking i'm gonna pee again no items
no nothing thank god stop drinking soda i'm not drinking soda i'm drinking water
drinking water stop drinking soda i'm not just slamming diet cokes here guys
ah key key b i think i know what that is i need a save point there's a locked door out here
i'm gonna piss my pants how did i miss that before because it was locked by the magical
spell from the mirror world i had to go into the mirror world and when i did it in the mirror
world i did the i released it it opened it in the real world as well funny how that works
now where is it's over here key b if i like it open this door you can i have key b don't i
let me see key b a gold key with a label on it uh what the hell is this is it a locked
door there's a ton of locked doors there's a shitload of locked doors um wait wait wait this
person must also have been a victim there's a corpse holding on to something a fiercely
scribbled journal how many bloody months have passed since they locked me in this excuse for
a clinic those idiot doctors still find a reason for me to be here i demand to be released
every time i get a hospital release form it is gone by morning get me out please please let
me out of here i feel i will i got that i got you right here take it and please give me an
item that will keep me alive there's a release form and it is nice that's very necessary right
now considering let me fucking god damn that turn that stupid turn but anything else in here
through the mirror wait key b key b it was not going to open that door is not going to open
i need to key b that's not the right one key b no this is not correct key b key b no this is
with the bugs no this level is this level is absolute dog shit i can't even leave
i'm gonna lose here i can't go in any doors just try to run he's gonna stop
he's gonna fall down the stairs come on come on come on come on come on come on one two three
it's no panic stop keep me where is this door is the door here down here the door of the
city i tried the door with the circle behind it maybe go activate the portal with the mirror
that's not a bad idea can i go in that portal room though i don't think i can
and that's not going to open none of these are going to do it so let me try to go in
that room and sprinkle on the ground i have no idea so it's this door here which one is it
that door is not going to open but it would be this room right that's the one i'm in right now
no just pee in the bottle this one is this like the portal room hey hi you're back
there's a safe point at the front desk front desk so i'm just gonna go all the way back down
can you please leave me alone leave me alone i have to go through the door and then go back all the
way down just get out of here that door won't open she can't get in here oh my god there she
is snippety step i have to get out of the mirror realm and then go all the way downstairs
done enough teleport out please let me go back in the mirror okay this level sucks it
really does through the mirror and then from the mirror we're going to go all the way down
just avoid avoid everybody just go down i have five splashes should be enough
i think hey hon definitely okay get back out of here on this like can i put something here
there's like a photo i have a letter from letter how about the photo of a of a woman
how about a photo of a child bingo give me something i can use this item is stupid
i would have rathered one of those lavender juices let's get back out what's this thing
the phone line's been cut who is slimer's coming over here all right all right i'm almost
there can i give anything to wait a minute lavender water sculpture of a woman fetching
water nothing out of the ordinary key a yes before anything bad happens just i have another
photo i'm gonna give over there thank god for the save point a huge weight has just been lifted
off my shoulders all right what about this guy over here patient on crutches even the sick and
wounded can i give you this photo or something photo mom yeah yeah that was 30 in-game minutes
without a save that would have been terrible all right i've got some items here let's get a
good save point i can't believe i'm gonna probably complete this game today i'm surprised
as hell all right it's time for the final p of the night last p break of the night
i'll be right back final hey okay so i got two keys plenty of water can i even go out here
i have to find dennis so i have key a and key b don't ask me where and what i'm supposed
to do now but i is that enough to open that door i wonder if that's enough thank god it's
a safe point anything else down here that i missed you were playing apex instead of peeing
yeah i got another computer downstairs and all my breaks i i squat up i just don't pull my parachute
out i just land on the ground and die and then i come back up here he's got a computer in the
bathroom all right so now where am i supposed to go i have this is coming back this way
double doors probably double doors i haven't gone in here have i no they won't open
neither will that i hear you i can hear you really in in in in so i need a third key you
guys are saying third key oh let me crunch on something for a second don't open that door
no i need another key that's ridiculous well let's go through and check it again what am i
eating uh these are the keibler club and cheddar sandwiches they're like those little
club crackers with the cheese they're really good um bathroom everyone's telling me to go to
the bathroom bathroom bathroom bathroom it's all the way down isn't it what's that bathroom
all the way down not as good as the peanut butter ones i don't like the peanut butter
ones as much the peanut butter ones well i mean i do like cheese more than i like
peanut butter come on in come find me sure these are the two by far worst enemies in this
leave all right last cracker going in oh that's not good i got your teeth i got your teeth
let's get the fuck out of here you didn't wash hands uh living is more important goodbye
no no wait a minute i need i don't have enough of that i need the refill i need a refill
i just used it on his face bad news that's really bad news damn door these two suck
these two suck go back down and save not a bad idea leave go let's go back down refill save
and then come back this is too stressful to watch it's very stressful to play as well wait
open the door no save it first there's no more ghosts down here i cleared them
just have to save it feel relaxed again i just love feeling relaxed watch this this is gonna
just my muscles are gonna just melt taking a hot bath i'm gonna hurry up and beat the game
i'm going i'm on it i'm on it i got it under control use the keys i have five splashes
hopefully this will get me out of here this could be a door lock the labeled key may work
use them all thank god anything else in here is that nothing else what about in the sink
nothing all right let's see where this takes us get the fuck off this game and play red
dead redemption 2 i already beat red dead redemption 2 i didn't beat it on stream i
beat it off stream play red dead 2 get out of this game i've used that exact lightning
sound effect actually i've used it on christmas the train and the train goes over the tracks and
gets the lightning strike thing what the hell is this that's grandpa right
play every game ever on stream very hard to do we're gonna get a narration here i think
today is yep i knew it the powers will become visible see you guys when you
wake up in like 10 minutes lisa is growing up into a lovely young lady she is everything to me
and i wish for nothing more than to watch over her every step she takes towards adulthood
is a step away from you i want so much to be with her i can't mute the music it's impossible
i have stumbled across an account of a ceremony called the ritual of engagement
it is written the bio didn't we already hear this
on her 15th birthday and drinking her blood person can be transformed into an entity
and receive the gift of immortality disgusted by this ritual of course at the same time there
is a part of me that cannot resist its allure i tore out alice's heart with these hands and
partook of her blood her for all eternity capable of such a monstrosity
must i desecrate my beloved in order to save myself so he's yeah he's gonna do it
yet another amazing discovery the legend of lord boris in the document is a mysterious
triangular crest it is said that the one who is able to decipher the secrets of the crest
will be able to become an entity i suspect that this too is related to the ritual of engagement
i can't skip this
uh alissa dennis and uh nancy whatever our names are
let's figure out the end of the game non-disclosure agreement i don't understand
he's just reading off like a concept for an rpg he like got invited to the blizzard
headquarters or something same point the nda i don't understand what it means i just see all
this weird shit about demons and monsters and drinking people's blood
and also somehow down here mentioned something called loot boxes which is surprising to me but
i've never really seen that term before in a 60 dollar game it's very interesting
what are you doing here what are you doing here what the fuck
uh good thing i just saved it she's mocking me i couldn't move i couldn't fucking move
i hope she's okay okay it's a good thing i saved really
that would have been pretty bad seriously jerma i could beat that
let's take care of that right off the bat because now we can predict it
watch you'll be right up my ass in a second here i told you no how did you you got in
front of me come on open hurry get in the door now i'm in the center of the clock tower
the piano segment everybody plays the piano in these games yeah no everyone's gonna correct
me that's an organ an organ is just a giant piano made out of tubes i thought that was
a sexual thing right there i thought these are all i all these good i
no wait wait wait wait wait wait just look around there's probably items there is this
guy's in the middle of a guitar solo and won't stop all right all right so settle down slash
there's another arrow over here what notes
the amount of dexterity it takes to do what this person is doing
that's the hardest beat saber level i think i've ever seen i don't know if this is the
right way but i'm just gonna do it oh hi hi again it's on the ground here another
narration by grandpa employee memo i've received orders from ralph and jemima to kill still more
i cannot continue in this fashion i killed 10 last week and this week they won 20 when will
it stop soon there will not be a person left in the entire village i must do something
about this there to be imprisoned in the kitchen one of the steel bars on the window
can be removed i do hope that they are able to see that before it's too late
and once they escape i pray that they will tell the world of the atrocities that go on behind
these walls that's not christopher walking all right so one of the steel bars on the window
can be removed got it let's uh make this guy fall i had there was a little thing there what
happened to the thing that was there there was a green indicator there and i couldn't do it
can't wait to hear that again god
so come on lisa's right man i don't give a shit about these arrows they haven't done anything
for me the whole game listen just falls down all right let's let me go up how do i throw an
axe at the person playing the piano don't walk this whole thing i have to go around the entire
core i hope this is not a waste of time as if it is i have to go back down
all right we look at that it was a waste of time back down
worst stream of the year wait why i've been having fun
wait what do you think so i don't think so that's not true uh there's another door i can try
are you having fun though i mean well was i having fun of the simpsons hit and run stream
near the end debatable but i got sucked in and i had to complete it that's what we're
doing now let's try this side i may have been possessed by the devil during that stream
my soul got torn out of my body probably three times i don't think i can cross here
i cannot cross here uh item on the other side is currently the best germa stream online at the
moment i guess so please please mute the game i can't
please be the game for five minutes uh oh shit can i throw i didn't deal with you
good thing you didn't see me that lady's coming in fish can i climb over this um i don't
know what to do about this we're good okay made it made it made it made it made it go
now what is there an item here it's locked right thanks for telling me to come over here
can i sneak in the bars one of the bars can be removed right i can't get in from here
oh shut up uh get away from me i need the bars info read the thing again
i need to read the note about the bars what do you mean then what do you mean in the files
files uh dot when i died so what i did because i didn't read the note i can't be used i can't
climb through this is trying my patience now didn't know about the bar
so i have to go back around and where was the note god i have no idea
if you're losing people well it is getting late it's getting really late and i am blowing out
people's eardrums with the same spam on an organ so i it doesn't surprise me all right
i'm gonna be ready for this guy i'm just gonna run to the end and you caught me still
oh ready there's gonna be an indicator here you explain to me why how did i i don't there's no
reason for it there's no reason for it thank you thank you okay we're gonna read the note
hey uh i must do something about this there to be imprisoned in the kitchen one of the
steel bars on the window can be removed i do hope that they're able to see that
isn't that just wonderful no don't you dare don't make me panic all right do it again wrap
around and then start playing again so please let's go
for your sanity i'm leaving fuck you god what i'm sorry look i'll turn it down i turn it down
see if i turn it off i turn it down okay that doesn't work i have to wrap around here
all right you can escape there must be the steel bars remove the loose one yeah there'll
be a tight squeeze go in there yes all right i'm in the kitchen don't fuck this up i don't
want to do that whole stupid sequence again who's in the oven what's in it no don't open it
yet thank god i didn't open it oh i didn't open it i didn't open it and it was the right
decision thank god i didn't just immediately open that if you wish to open the other path
calm the flames uh guys i don't know if the game is trying to tell me this here but do i
have to go get the fire extinguisher from four and a half hours ago is that what i have to
do there are mounds of ash brushed into a pile i heard that they used ash to extinguish
fires back then uh can i have some do i need a shovel fire in the stove is flaring i think i
see something back there can i pick up one of these kitchen knife maybe i unlocked the door
i guess that's a good thing to do yeah there is a shovel there so why can i just use it
there's a shovel just actually sitting in here and you're giving me the opportunity now the
fire has died out you collected the a crest you collected a crest she's gone nope she's dead
that's what's left of her i don't like the suit of armor thank god come here come here come
here save it quickly turn on smart click should have a car emote holy water fountain no
this should be found in here okay i'm glad to see that you've regenerated your scope
it's really wonderful you grew your head back real quick shut up oh i'm just realizing
something right now i have to fight two people at the same time uh that's gonna be impossible
large painting there is a title on it n loving mother suffers in place of daughter a
okay this is i did that that's the same thing which door did she come out of this one
no this is the one i'm going the wrong way just wait for good what happened there
what's that oh and then i realized and i can't believe that the entity if you could believe
that i've been around the globe a thousand years and my shoes were all dirty and they
fucked it all up and there was i couldn't believe that my own daughter is the one
that i have to sacrifice these are unskippable
yeah uh all right uh thanks grandpa good luck all these books are about torture and
slaughter who would collect such horrible books yeah i think that's grampy grampy is the one
lavender water yeah uh-huh i knew you're here i don't think i was stupid
another area here too i don't know where this is gonna end up
wait wait a minute wait it's what's happening here wait a second what wait wait wait wait a
minute did this go up did i just go back up okay so hold on what am i supposed to do now
what does this crest mean a crest you beat it time to shut it up a crest no that's the n crest
i need a d crest do i put another crest in here she can't get over here i guess i'm gonna
get out of here so i need i have a i have n i need d what's the d crest is the guy's dead
body across the way here this is this it has to be this ghost right can i go this way now
i have to jump i can't jump i've got to go all the way back around where the hell is she
anything else in here that i missed anything these things are going to come alive i know it
here they come can i let me just save it everyone's saying wrong wrong wrong
and loving mother suffers in place of daughter a wrong wrong you're wrong wrong wrong
she's gone jerma you're safe except with the lady in the room right now
what magical plant are you smoking right come back over here can i can i put you inside that
again what the hell am i doing she's not gonna come over here right let me just put the skull
on this guy's head jump off the balcony yeah can't you move a little faster all right now
is this guy lying on the ground here can i give him the skull when there's somebody lying
down shit uh wait god damn it i need to i need to put the swap the crests i couldn't activate
the other one before though i couldn't activate the thing on the wall this is the worst stream
how is this any different than the other what are you talking about
don't i could go back where the fountains were the fountains are here
this way right somebody said to go to the fountains fuck this dumb game yeah it is a
fountain get out of my way gamer license revoked it doesn't matter i just want to get out of this
area examine the fountains did the wikipedia page give me bullshit what a beautiful candlestick
it's been moved return it yes no nobody edited the wikipedia page the wikipedia page did not get
edited it's correct how are you supposed to know that i guess because of the cat scratches
on the table i just checked the change logs chat fuck with you just now no they how there's no way
i'm so close i can tell i can taste it okay so let's let me just say what this says
so this says and the loving mother suffers in place of daughter a so
would you go home please insert the end crest i don't have an option you're not
gonna have any eyes left by the time we're done here it just please there we go get away from me
i have six bosses left now that is an edited wikipedia chat article i'm certain he's still
gonna be following me someone's gonna the one of the nights it can start moving weird
statue i wonder if it's a device of some sort i don't know weird statue is this a device
lady leave me the fuck alone i'll be the most irritating person ever
okay uh does that mean she's gone i believe so this is grand grandpa's room
and that's a cool painting okay actually was just dumbfounded by that painting i got the
decrest i'm skimming it despite his harsh reputation lord boros loved his daughter dearly
gave her all of his land when he's 50 he was afraid of his life he learned about the entities
and the rituals uh his daughter was turning almost 15 years old he made the fateful decision
to perform the ritual he ate her heart something's happened right before her 15th birthday
she died uh we're in a carriage she was enrolled into its side shocked that she died
by his beloved daughter as well as the inability to realize the ritual fell into a deep
depression uh he was replaced with raging anger he's really mad though he had both the coachman
and the maid who were with annabelle time of her death killed it did little to a sausage's
anger the massacre of his staff continued even extending to the villages and lands
the his wife did what she could to convince him to cut it out don't do that but only
succeeded in inflaming him further and she too was actually killed as well uh lord darcy
borough eventually he died he got his head crushed with two logs two logs squished his head
uh in the clock tower of the castle as he escaped from mobs of angry farmers according to
legend he was he had died he was gonna put a plague on the world and then the clock tower
is still there something is trapped between the volumes this no no you don't can't bait me
with that i'm not gonna get baited with this
finally solved the mystery or darcy boroughs had a daughter also a son william from his first
marriage though boroughs himself was killed william escaped and lived out the rest of
his days in peace under the pseudonym that's so his head was squished between two large
logs home alone two style
dick oh it's a tv screen it's just his peewee hermit this is the bike scene
how do we get out there should i open up this like clam chair all right i have d crest
is there anywhere i need to put this in particular now you'll be fine a hidden switch is illuminated
yes the d crest goes but i need to save it where was the safe point back it was back here
right was there one back here i'm trapped well just put it in i was looking for an item
so that just opened the door but i just came in oh what a twist
fuck
why am i going in the iron maiden did i just die i like this music the skulls wait a minute
really so these are all fudged up that's too bad seven hours later still gone still driving
around
it's getting louder i'll turn it down
there's nothing here so i don't have anything to get out of here this is just
just going the other iron maiden i guess yeah
i mean i have to there's there's no way i'm not gonna go through the gauntlet here
i didn't know he came across like that i thought he they all go up and down
i don't know where i am i don't know how far away this is thank god
where is this new visibility ban this one's now open okay so i have a way to get back
through the second one the door prevents entry there's another one right there
you missed a key near the maiden in the top right corner i did it doesn't even backswing
does he what's this there's a lever on the wall pull it okay i open that now i gotta go
and get this door open this game is a torture device no don't do that i have to do it in that
order i gotta go go to the second one shit no oh that sucks all right so i have to
um i have to go and open that door and then i don't he's gonna swing
and then you're gonna swing when do you swing
i couldn't have timed that perfectly even if i tried that was an inhuman timing
oh i'm just gonna do it in order i'm so close all right it's which one is it it's the one
i don't even know it's this one right here open up the door click here we go open it
it's open this shit's open now okay now we just gotta gotta gotta gotta gotta gotta
go down here i don't remember
when does it happen swing why is one in the middle not swinging fucking no i can't
i swear to fucking god man let's put this shit in the game they put this crap in the
game is what this is this crap is crap it is he swings side but if i crawl that i'm running
at a time to get past the next guy oh it's crap i was gonna see what happens okay you have to be
crawling you have to be crawling first of all not as needed to test it to see you have to be
crawling if you're crawling it goes over you if you're just crouching it does not hypothesis
has been shown and been done and i'm ready i had it that first time fucking god damn oh
it's gotta be the end of the game i'm bad at the end of the game game the game is ending
very soon here i just have to get to the end just open this door i can't believe i've
this is supposed to be like playstation 2 we're gonna have play like four or five
games tonight no i've been playing this one for seven and a half hours
so this one comes down then you can cross crawl underneath it no i can i can make it by
i could go right now no i'm gonna wait so it's bang this one comes down and then he comes across
then watch it he throws the other way i don't know i'm sorry god damn it i had it i'm so
i'm so it's so slow but i know i'm gonna get hit by it little lever let's get the
hell out of here why is this this is at the there's the other door in the middle here
no it's not i wouldn't need shit game just give me a save point somewhere
doing what are they doing
they actually did it they oh i can't believe they did i can't believe they did it oh do it
they do it again
keep the chip keep the head down run head on the back of the table
suck in your stomach do i have to make a choice well he's dead anyway you're still playing this
shitty game
yeah hey ralph and jemima yep the siblings were horrendously cruel by nature and said that they
were the torturers and executioners during lord borough's bloody campaign so these are the two
serial killers fascination for blades and in particular scissors they found endless enjoyment
in gutting or dismembering people when lord borough's was killed ralph and jemima
were stoned to death by the crowds they resurrected together and they continued to wreck havoc
hopefully a save point and then the climax of the game would be great looks like
just like grandfather's room what's it doing in here i'm losing viewers rapidly well it's like
it's it's like fucking one or two o'clock in the morning and i've been screaming for
seven and a half hours it's not out of the ordinary it's like two thirty a.m eastern
what else is even in here is there really nothing else in here i can't go through there
yeah i'm i'm in it to win it now i need i need the closure somebody just said it i need closure
everything looks just like grandfather's looks like grandfather's okay well apparently i picked
up something well this is drawings for grampy today i read a book with pretty pictures a
wolf pretended to be grandma and ate up a girl it was scary so i went to grampy's room
because grampy would save me grampy is really strong and he can kill a wolf
i love my grampy i'm going to stay with him forever and ever i said that that was the password
who would have thought all right grampy it's time to like pull the wizard of osville
and see who the fuck is really behind this a ladder where does it go back in the projector
room now what well you did that i didn't do that you did that on your own free will
oh my sweet grandpa i'm not even gonna attempt to do a joke it's too late for that maybe like six
hours ago lord borrows ancestor hear me i know of your pain and anger when you lost your
beloved daughter annabelle just before the ritual of engagement my love for elissa led
me to kill her father philip entity was everything you're doing is it all because
of you do you want me to resurrect lord borrows after 400 he's just practicing his lines
never mind is that what you want the local theater in the community is doing a jakes
granddaughter in the chest that doesn't sound bad once the deed is done i'll be with elissa
forever return to this earth lord borrows join with me and we will complete the ritual of
engagement enter my body and let our flesh be fused this is all a great kind of climactic
ending here but um ron's still downstairs getting chopped up by a pendulum with the two clowns
we're gonna get an uh an ending to that sequence because i'm the oogie boogie man
make more tim burton references why not well that was easy i didn't have to do anything
he wanted too much power oh no vego came out of the painting now we're
fucked to you well okay any more secret buttons any more things i can do i have to press a little
button or something go down leave last time i pressed a button on the door why i'm like
back in this room i don't get it not this shit again how did i get down there before
help me out here the bottom right one is it the bottom right one
that i can take any of them can i wholly water the knights
no i already i already opened the door you're right just go down
shit put it again oh i have to actually throw the switch again don't i oh fuck okay come on
jeremy you can do this it's getting late come on
you can do it just do it don't even think about just go i can do it i know i can just go
put the switch let's do this let's do this no okay jerma finish this game i have a project
well that's more important that's more important e3 demo voice let's do this okay you got enough
supplies yeah how you on med kits radical yeah me too let's do this do we get a exposition on you
yeah we do now julia murderer rank seven a minus in social studies she's killed 495 people
she belongs in jail for a very long time scissor woman victims 22
wow not even that impressive the first boss killed more people than you
not even good so watch out for the wind how far does it go out through the wall
kind of teleport around there she is okay what's with the
jim has tim burton music oh now you're fucked bingo that did a lot of damage though
with the wind coming from corner just spinning in the corner bingo right in the head
oh i connected where are you bitch you were pathetic they're gonna combine
listen man shows up and they combine into like quad scissor
here we go again put your hand out grab it all right scissor man
37 victims you guys are really not that impressive you have a little bit more of a health
bar though okay what do you got the moves well you know i wish you could just run faster
that's like at what point do you like stop jogging and run as fast as you fucking can
you do oh that hurt oh this is gonna suck i could already tell this is like the fight
look at how slow then shitty this one is there's not another button i can press
us then run like a goddamn fucking four-year-old
that's the opportunity right here and then you gotta duck no well ducking doesn't work
get it no i'm gonna die did you get it no come on combo combo combo combo
do it yes i don't think this is gonna kill him though i'm gonna be in deep shit that's not gonna
kill him he's gonna be at like five percent health if it's anything like last time i gotta
be ready what the hell did he do that's all right i thought i was in the middle of it
i was assuming it was you know going left and right don't make me fight scissor woman
okay good you gotta catch him when he's doing his super move and you gotta hit him
so it's when he goes here it comes whatever the hell it is i have a present for you
again a little bit of trouble
attach attach attach attach attach do it yes all right i've got full health try to get it
out again again good night last one three two one bye bye
now you can dodge i thought he just was cutting his arm off
you could have waited a half second before running through the blade
i'm so glad we will never see those two characters ever again in any form of media
thank you thank you but you saved me something special
oh no i'm spurlin that was like tim and eric
but you still have to destroy me if you want to save your mother
come up to the top of the clock tower can you repair the spiral first
you stay here wait a second don't treat me like a dentist you may be a man but you're not a ruder
what's a ruder final boss save let's get i hope you know i usually don't want this
i usually don't like this but i hope this final boss is just a single arrow cutscene i hope so
you're gonna go up 16 floors you didn't fix it you didn't fix them okay good
up we go to the final sequence of the game special arrow i'm calling it right now you're
gonna rage quit when you get to this boss it's been so long it's been too long it's been an
eight hour experience i'm not gonna leave now why would i stop now lady that works too that's
fine that's not how i would have done it but that's how you're gonna do it item or
item or something nothing no items no all right here we go i don't want to make another ocarina
of time reference but this is the ganon fight i'm gonna go on fighting with a roof ocarina
what am i how am i saying it wrong it's the it's the ocarina ocarina ocarina no it's the
ocarina ocarina ocarina ocarina ocarina aquafina can i not pull that
can you do this can i pull there's a strain i tried to i pressed it every second
here's the sequence we're gonna go all the way up i just lived my entire life and died
in germans still playing clock tower uh you you're i welcome the first ever mosquito
to watching germa 985 or fucking crane fly whatever you are
this game sucks by the way
next game there is no next game tonight you can go for eight hours
there's gonna be a next game tomorrow what happened it is tomorrow well i mean later
today fuck it is tomorrow no it's not it's 11 47 12 hours of ed ed and eddie no i've been
waiting for you grandpa your ass is on fire what oh shit oh it's burning i searched and
searched for three hours castle used to stand in exactly the same spot where the hamilton
house is now it's not a coincidence it's all the entities doing this is our destiny
don't look so sad once the ritual of engagement is complete you and i will become a new entity
we'll be engaged together for this is just creepy grandpa wants to marry the granddaughter
come to your senses and give me my mom back i've got a ring for you too we have vows to say
grandpa you're fucked oh no she's stone betrayed me more than she married that weak
lily-livered good-for-nothing then she tried to prevent me from becoming one with my most
precious granddaughter that's why she's there there was no other way alissa damn you
you're not my grandfather i don't know who you are anymore but i know that i'm a ruder i'll
destroy you and save my mother fool fool he just he does ipad rpg evolved three times he's
like a five star now it only took six thousand dollars and two thousand hours of play time to
have it happen
it's wrong
dennis get up here you dope what are you dope final piece dennis get it
get it before captain hook kills me he looks like a serial mascot
oh the captain's crumbles
we're almost done i'm so glad captain morgan dennis get up here
what what happened that was way too fast oops
uh always a good to sit there ron's dead see you later final one shot arrow come on i turned
into kid icarus lord burrows only 115 people you've ruled for like 50 000 years that's
impossible he's 2200 years and he's only that's more years than people all right he has like a
slime oh he's he's doing the same thing we're both doing the same move he's doing my own move
on me he got a nuke well it was uh we had some fun just step to the left dennis eviscerated
what dennis what about me all right so i can't get three i've this is gonna be weird i'm gonna
have to shoot him with something he's got two health bars this is gonna suck
uh
he's getting closer damn it shoot that i'm dead what's wrong with him good thing i just dodged
that accidentally all right i'm good here we go my turn fucking let it go come on super hit
him with the whole thing the whole thing bingo come here do it yes oh that's gonna take it
down to one full bar how do you fast forward a stream uh you can't live content man it's live
that's my turn um what is i didn't know he had that move he's gonna do it again
fuck move oh no he's gonna do it again how many times did he do that shit
shit no come on oh no this is bad what are you falling down for why did i fall down
twice why did i fall down twice in a row that was ridiculous fell down twice in a row the
girl that can't stand on her two goddamn feet for the entire video game oh i fell over i fell
over again count how many times i fell over this game i probably fell down just walking two miles
per hour 685 times damn it it's such a klutz it's like her shoes she's wearing tap shoes
with oil on the bottoms of them what happens if he gets that close i didn't dodge it
okay so he gets that close okay can i please get away from you now he's powered up
he's throwing two balls at the same time can i get fucking dennis back can he throw me like a
second ring this one died hey dennis go into your cereal box and get me another ring
because this one ain't going anywhere just kill me
just do it just do it i'm standing here waiting for you to do it why don't you get
new attacks because this is the third game of the clock tower series and running away from
scary monsters they had to add some other stuff and they added a bow and arrow that shoots magical
bow i can't even i'm i here we go i'm beating it right now you had to fucking do that this is
so dumb i feel like i'm playing space channel again cheese strat discovered i'm gonna use it
all day all right i got another health bar to deal with keep him all the way back there
you idiot no no no no he's gonna do it again i can't i'm tethered thank god thank you
you dumb game i seriously hate that i hate it what does that mean ah no i'm not
don't even think about it you bastard i've been hurting them i gotta move out of the way
other side walk in front of it come on
not gonna have enough time shit didn't hit him he's walking he's walking oh please
damn it bad angle i gotta move
escape i gotta move this way back around oh the stupid casket not yet no no i went too far
please be despond as there is you oh this is insanity come on i can't look at how slow she
runs you're killing me with this bullshit can you stop doing that shit yes god do it
that didn't hit him in what world what fucking reality did that not hit
see you in hell see you in hell that was fucking horrible oh that was horrible
it was the fight's not hard it just lasts so long it's like a world of
warcraft boss you just have to do everything over and over again for like 10 minutes
who did you have to look what was it picture for
what's the matter does that mean remembering a photo of him he's right in front of me
oh my god elissa takes strikes from me phase two
is the game broken why are we getting the opening cut scene in the game
won't allow the ritual to happen never we're gonna have to sword fight now in phase three
passes denis on the way down and so ends clock towers is there another clock tower game
after this it can't be right the whole tower comes down who cares there are some spiritual
successors okay we didn't have time to mourn ron it was all a dream how satisfied are you
right now i'm pretty satisfied i stuck to my guns and i completed clock tower three i didn't
think i was gonna do that after the second boss i was about to stop but i feel accomplished
in a not at all sort of way mom we did it we did it mom am i dead what did we do
we did it i think we're in all we all made it to heaven
he got one out of 18 endings where would the other endings come from ron didn't make it
to heaven that's actually kind of unfortunate that's really bad
that's so wrong the main character of the next game she didn't really seem to miss him she
didn't even know he was gone ron was the reason why we were able to even win in the first
place he threw the magical lucky charm up at me without ron there is no win you don't win
i was supposed to get sacrificed to take the demon god library program all right let's see is
there a after credit scene original concept movie product what movie why didn't you just
leave in the beginning and he wouldn't have been able to become the entity either way
since you would not be there for the sacrifice yeah clock tower three received mixed or average
reviews with an aggregate score of 69 out of 100 it was still enjoyable all right look the game
was all over the place but it was still it was a it was messy fun it was messy fun no it was
not yeah it was i wouldn't give it a positive rating i'd say it was messy fun but uh those of
you that are leaving we're gonna kind of wind it down here and i will see you tomorrow
four oh yeah what's what's that oh um a bunch of other playstation 2 games that i didn't do today
that i was supposed to do instead of eight and a half hours of clock tower three so i'll see
you tomorrow why did you do this like i had fun i just had to do it i had to so i'll see you
tomorrow starting probably around the same time between like three and four gonna do ps2 games
for a month at this rate no we're gonna go back to like we'll play some jokey ones
i don't know how much longer i can be in some of these and then we're gonna go back to vr next
week we're almost there but this game was a joke yeah but it turned into a thing that uh not a
you know you got me there but i it's still i had i had i enjoyed myself to a point where
i was able to i wanted to beat it started as a joke turned into an ordeal that's right
we could barely hear you over the game the whole stream is that true
how was it that loud what the and what the fuck was that noise
routers points 40 000 a new element has been unlocked we have to see what it is so what was
the element that i unlocked this game includes disturbing content and scenes of graphic violence
yes it does 40 000 points out of a possible 20 billion okay produced by capcom right
what's this what's the new element theater just watch the cutscenes again that the new
element yeah it's just a gallery okay what some weird way to transition to that okay here's
some concept art cool is the house 3d model of the house uh that didn't happen they must
have got rid of that part the art of clock tower three bye all right that's gonna be it
i'll see you guys tomorrow we're gonna go over the bits thanks for sticking around as
long as some of you did uh we went pretty late with this one but that's okay let us move on to
the bits i'm gonna move this change that see you tomorrow if you're leaving we'll do some
more ps2 stuff and then we're gonna take break for a couple days come back with vr but we'll
talk about that tomorrow starting back a while ago we had nine hours ago it seems like an
entire day which it kind of is uh some guy gave fifteen dollars thank you for the fifteen bucks
some guy uh been a while since i last donated but that's most because i'd otherwise have
fucked up my sleep rhythm due to non-eu friendly times jerma pluto anyway here's a
meme video okay it's gonna be phantom of the opera three two one actually it's called ring
a ding i'm gonna change this ring a ding i'm gonna skip see if this fan of the opera
oh god oh jesus christ oh god what is going on in this video it's like the guy
i don't know if that is there's a guy running around with like a bell well thank you for
the fifteen dollars some guy and that was very very loud thank you though thank you divas for
the 250 thank you uh s kink for the uh i'm supposed to be doing 250 what am i doing
but thank you thank you dork you for the four dollars didn't even watch the video i'm too
lazy to click on it what's the point of that video i don't know uh dork you thanks for the
four dollars so my brother wasn't able to propose to his girlfriend last week due to
some complications but he got it today and it went swimmingly and didn't mix up the ring with
his sunflower seed holder you gotta be careful not to do that i was told a few months ago
that i need to be more careful with the things that i say to people and the the objects that
i carry around with me i didn't i i gotta talk i i don't know what the problem is but
uh good to hear congratulations to them by the way thank you for the four dollars really
appreciated door cube 700 000 games uh oh my god new but gave 10 community subs thank you
what are you guys doing what's everybody doing like question marks was question marks he doesn't
know what oh i don't know i don't know what you guys doing but thank you the four dollars
door cube uh thank you flug boy for the three dollars hope you're doing well tonight i wanted
to ask since i strive to be able to do some of the voices you can do uh can you do a snake voice
well and also while watching this my friend said he sounds like he's really trying to
entertain himself playing this game i can't i cannot do a solid snake it's one of the
many things i cannot do but i mean yeah i i the game was fun snake from harry potter
no that's snake but thank you flug boy i cannot do a snake uh thank you nate for the
six dollars streamer fails to finish and beat cartoon game i did i beat it clock tower three
uh thank you though for the six dollars name neon thank you thank you also thank you to
uh mad faro mad faro for the nine dollars no music shit thank you thank you for telling
me that thank you mad faro for nine bucks no message here just nine dollars thank you
it's a lot of money flank tank thanks for 10 bucks sorry i've missed the last couple of streams
but catching up watching the bods and you said you might go back to newer games this week
uh sorry to do this again i know i've been beating a dead horse with a broken record telling
you to play near automata but since the new complete version comes out tuesday hearing you
might play new games made me omega germa venus uh i don't i probably won't be playing it
anytime soon so i will not be playing near automata anytime soon maybe some of the time
i don't know i have no plan i have no plan to play it let's put it that way
but i am going to be going back to some newer stuff and by newer i mean
uh stuff that at least is thing the things that have come out in the last year or two
because we're gonna go back to vive and i want to do mine show but i would assume
we're gonna spend more than one stream in mine show because i kind of want to make a bunch of
random shit we'll see launch day sekiro probably i can't imagine why i wouldn't
by new he means game boy but thank you flank tank for the 10 bucks
dr dubris thanks for the 250 nate thanks for the 250 uh germa so if you love half
life answer me this question and half life too who the rebels and gordon freeman fighting
the combine that's it hopefully i i that made you happy uh ludus thanks with five dollars and
fifty cents are you a voice actor for the engineer in the game gunhead i am i am the voice
of the engineer in that game gunhead no way no no that's a lie no no no no crypt arc
crypt arc is it the way no no that's the same thing right isn't gun hit this like they did
they made like another version of it right they did like a like a essentially a first person
version of crypt arc right doesn't even know his own damn role version it's been eight and a half
hours come on give us give us slack forgets the hundreds of roles he's had in games no not
hundreds who hired this idiot uh but i'm the engineer in crypt arc which also i'm assuming
they took the lines from crypt arc and put it in gunhead i didn't play gunhead maybe have to
look at it but thank you ludus oak for the five dollars and fifty cents did i finish the
game i did i beat clock tower three in one sitting hey frody and weapon thanks for the four dollars
and 31 cents i don't mean to be a tattletale but i think shido's up to no good again he's
got this mischievous look on his face calvin calvin and hobs that's like on the back of
people's cars isn't it yeah that that's like one of the ones that's on the back of people's
windshields they had a pinging one that you know that's not even from hey calvin somebody
made that up like that calvin doesn't like take a piss on a wall somewhere in any of those comics
somebody like did that that's not an officially licensed piece of merchandise
but thank you frody and weapon for the four dollars 31 cents uh thank you nate for the
five dollars here you're gonna finish ed ed and eddie i'm not going to i will not be
finishing ed ed and eddie it was an interesting game but we had to move on thank you thank
you d jack thank you uh we had 250 coming from nate again when i played the orange box on my
ps3 i don't even think it works does does tf2 still even have servers on the orange box
for like playstation the server is still up isn't this still like a crit bug in the game
that hasn't been patched since like 2008 can't you charge up a melee crit in the
orange box version on the console there's still a bunch of old vanilla bugs
but i played thousands and thousands and thousands of hours of the orange box
i will probably not be going back and playing it anytime soon or probably you know probably
never again unless there's some reason why i would play portal again i've beat that game
like three times half-life 2 i've that that game i'm not going to go back to tf2 i mean
it's still there it's still available i don't have like a reason to go back and play it
but if they do something cool or bigger or larger add some interesting things i played it like a
year and a half ago but i don't really have a reason to play them like i've already done all
these things more than once so going back and doing it again is just like hey i'm doing it
again because i don't really have a reason to do it especially something like portal or half
life so would not be playing those games probably again uh thank you the other us for
the two bucks uh-oh i'm just gonna take some getting used to but thank you i need that story
what are you talking about tell me story i need a story stop stalling what what's story of my
talk what are you talking about i'm supposed to tell the story i have no idea what you're
talking about all right i got a story for you go to bed the end that's a pretty good one
okay good night i didn't like that story how am i supposed to sleep after that but thank
you the other us uh thank you nate again for three bucks so in germa rumple can you feature
one of the eds they're all going to be one character it's going to be a monstrosity it's
going to be all three of their faces so they don't take up three slots thank you nate
again for the 250 guess who's back back again tele frankus is back uh case is back
you're gonna get copyrighted by m&m i don't think i will probably not i don't think so
but thank you nate for the 250 uh peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 even though games
like this suck in quotes they're somehow oddly lovable and hard to put down because
you just want to complete the game yeah it's bad but you just can't help yourself
anyways here's a little of my tax return money hope you did your taxes have a good
night germa and chat now my taxes are good taxes are good to go thank you and thanks
to the 250 and yes there is something to be said it's just the cutscenes were just so
out of control there was so much weird shit going on you can't i just needed to know what else
there was tuck me into bed all right now you're just getting weird i don't have a response to
that one uh but thank you nate for the three four five six seven eight dollars and 50 cents
uh now this looks like a job for me so chat follow me all right it's more m&m and they
say when the cutscenes are better than the gameplay uh by the way that man is why is that
man guard wearing a shirt wait what are you talking about oh no it's i don't know
ban the guy with the m&m lyrics which one uh nate another like another like eight dollars
from nate with more slim shady uh m&m lyrics wonderful great thank you for the m&m lyrics
and then they say well germa two clowns do exist it's the joker and harley quinn
those two have a lot of fan art they're pretty popular the joker and harley quinn i mean yeah
they are very popular characters what if but imagine if i was like nah joker ain't that
popular joker and harley quinn aren't popular at all uh but thank you thank you again for
the 250 nate well there's my proof germa can't suck it up and beat the cartoon
network game the easiest game of all time i mean you're probably gonna do the same with
spongebob is really is that really that big of a deal but i'm not gonna play through ed ed and eddy
what the hell is going on i'm not gonna play through all of ed and eddy the misadventures
i played it for like three hours why would i need to do that all right for the amount
of people that are telling me yes i should do you see how many people during that stream
were telling me please god do anything else i was fighting off animals during that stream
i had like my broomstick and i'm just like in the corner like fucking god damn they're
coming after me but no i i will not be finishing ed ed and eddy but i am going to finish the
uh clock tower because that was something i just wanted to do but thank you to nate for the
slim shady lyrics and three dollars bro luck thanks for five dollars uh hey mate here's five
dollars sorry for not donating them well you don't have to be you don't have to apologize
for not donating man that's something i i really hope you do not feel sorry for do not feel
sorry for that you giving me five dollars is is more than enough that i could ever ask anyone
to ever give me from money on a stream don't ever apologize for it please thank you for
the five dollars thanks for hanging on thank you something or other for the 250 oh nice stream
and they do they laugh really really hard let me show you how many times they laugh look at
this no that's the wrong link hold on i can just type it wait they said they said nice stream
than that that's a lot of ha ha ha but thank you nate for the two three four five six seven
eight more nine more dollars thank you nate uh i'm not gonna beat ed ed netty off stream
it's gonna be i'll give it a shiito shiito will you play it you'll probably love it
what's the giant three legged alien that the combine use remember i remember the brains the
floating like egg sacks it's been a while since i played it and then they say go on offer up
and sell me the game for two cents i'm not gonna snow i'm gonna i'm not gonna get rid of
it i'm gonna hold on to it for a while i'll probably donate it that's what i typically do
once once a year or so a lot of the games that i buy and play i donate so that's what will
probably happen but thank you for the 10 bucks here nate and finally here at the end we had
dingus town 15 from dingus town sorry for donating uh sorry for 15 dollars thank you
dingus town and then jack thank you jack for the 250 play fusion fall retro i don't really i don't
think i really know what it is i'll definitely give it a look though fusion fall retro where
do you donate games there are a lot of places that take uh video games a lot of the there's
a lot of donation pickups that take them that's usually where i do i put them all in i get
them all nice and neat get them in a box and do a drop off or pick up uh then right at the end
here nate for three dollars this is the half life two beta boss show it on stream all right can
i like ban half life the word from my stream can i is that always like a phrase i can ban
donate the vive i mean i'm still using the vive uh bro look thanks for the five dollars
have money make me feel bad no i'm not even gonna say anything i'm gonna say thank you bro
look for the five dollars thank you appreciate it but thank you bro look let's run the credits
these are all the new subs and the resubs thank you guys see you tomorrow i might get started a
tad later than usual no i'm not why would i even say that that's not even true i got the
wind i forgot i got the window now i got like the three to four window i've just got to get
in there i'll be good i need to eat something he's a lying stream well i just i'm thinking
about how late it is and like oh well i'm gonna eat and then i'll be able to get up
i'll be fine and tomorrow is technically today that's later today damn it's almost one a.m
sometimes we go long you know don't get some mcdonald's no this food in the fridge
that's gotta make it heat it up the story has to be great for me to sub
i don't have a story tell you got a story i'm my brain is like scrambled fucking eggs
right now i can't you know it's been nine straight hours you want to come up with a
story and one day there was a prince and the prince what's the entire plot just pretend i
just did that voice and gave you the whole plot for the prince and the pauper from disney when
mickey mouse the two mickey mouses what by the way what the hell what was that bullshit
first time when there was two mickey mouses in that movie when have they ever done that
again down the clock tower story hey nate thanks in three bucks nate they just say
half-life with a smiley face i appreciate your enthusiasm for that series thank you
not good enough try again tomorrow sorry idiot hey will you relax you got you gotta relax
i won't be able to sleep because of you hey well my sleep schedule is going to be screwed
up too isn't it it's 1 a.m i'll probably get to bed around i'm gonna eat still want uh
i still want what the fuck is this what on earth is this uh nate just linked me this this
i don't even know what this is it's still in the chat it's right there
it's three dollars 50 cents i made this for you please look and laugh are you putting
ed ed and eddie misadventures in the trash is that what they're doing i didn't do that i
didn't say that i had nothing to do with me and we we did just cross the nine hour mark so
i'm gonna get out of here i gotta go five bucks from nate that's what you're currently doing
thank you for the five dollars nate and what i it's i'm gonna have it for a little while and
then i'm gonna donate it and someone is gonna get to love that game that experience they're
gonna get to play it remember when nine hour streams were a rarity they still are
they still are typically i'm usually done around what six to eight hours usually now
before it was about four to six now it's about six to eight going over eight and a half to nine
is still pretty rare go raid uh go raid vinny is vinny streaming right now what's he doing what
are you doing right now vinny are you live is he still going he's ending the stream oh okay
he's wrapping up all right well if we caught him a little earlier i would have just sent
everybody there but nate thanks for the six dollars nate you've been giving a lot of
money we gotta get you on like the the money cool down here you give you a shitload of money
that's like 40 or 50 dollars tonight thank you so much ban him from donating and there he is
again thanks with three bucks nate much love love trolling you oh by the way oh by the way
half life three is coming out soon can't wait bye well i've got some bad news for you half
life three is probably never going to release i don't i would be very surprised if it did i
would be so happy if it did but i don't think it's gonna happen you'll be probably waiting a
while but thank you all see you all later today somewhere around three to four ish pm
pacific fans are gonna make it well they would get sued all right see you guys tomorrow
today later today for almost all of you take care see you soon more playstation 2 on the way
i we i promise we're not gonna get stuck on one the first one take care everybody
have a great like 12 hours until i see you again