Hello ladies and gentlemen, this is Anthony Wimbleton coming at you with a first shoutcast on German 95's channel.
Never done a shoutcast before, but that's okay, we're gonna change that right now.
Coming at you with a heavy gameplay. Rocket at new school with the gloves of running urgently, the family business, and the Tommy Slav.
Germa is in a really, really crazy mood right now. He's gonna try and do a shoutcast for the first time. He's gonna do it right now as a heavy...
Here we go!
Spy coming around the corner trying to get a backstab on somebody, maybe snap the sentry as well, but Germa does not let that happen.
Jumps around the corner with the Tommy Slav and starts unloading a massive amount of damage on everybody that's coming up to the side here.
A lot of things going on right now, a lot of chaos, a lot of damage going on.
Sentry looks like it might be going down, but that's not a concern to Germa because he's not an engineer.
Pyro kinda hides around the corner trying to find a way to get somebody with a spray.
Germa backs off for a second with his Chinese or Japanese friend that's a medic.
Not really sure too much about that right now, but I'll get back to that in a minute.
Germa right now hogging the cart like it's one of his favorite toys when he was five years old, trying to find a way to stop this team from pushing all the way to the middle here.
Spy gets back out here, tries to get the sap on the engineer, but he gets the stab actually, and he does not get the sap.
Unfortunately though, these two dispensers are going to go down, which is going to stop our team from healing a lot.
Look at this Pyro spraying into nowhere, and here comes the first Uber of the game.
Germa comes around the corner here, loses the medic for the first time, but he finds a way to get to the medic again.
Absolute perfect push here, got a Spy on the side here, trying to get a backstab on one of our teammates.
He does not get the stab, instead he goes down, down to Chinatown, whipping off the gloves of running urgently,
and he sees an opportunity to get this engineer in his building, but now he's kind of hiding on the right side of the bridge,
and he gets this engineer and this Pyro and that Demoman.
I did not say engineer, I meant to say Demoman, I'm sorry about that.
Red Engineer now has the teleporter built up to level two, I believe, so now our team can come right back into the front lines when they die.
Medic goes down, I believe he had about 25% Uber, which is a good thing, because now he cannot charge that on a teammate.
Soldier gets around, and Germa realizes this, so he swiftly and methodically goes over into the courtyard area and towards this house into the building.
He finds that there is a Soldier and a Demoman and a Pyro here, ready to be shot, but he doesn't want to get himself killed,
so he walks out of the back door trying to find his Medic friend.
Turns around and sees that the Medic is obviously preoccupied with something else, so instead of saying over voice chat,
hey can you heal me? He just turns around and goes the other way like an idiot.
Picks up this health pack on the ground here, and he knows that there's another health pack over on this side as well, near the engineer.
Doesn't want to take the ammo, because he doesn't want to be a jerk and take the metal from the engineer,
so he comes out here with a shotgun, shooting a few times into this Demoman's face.
Gets the final kill right there on that Demoman, and now they're trying to back up,
trying not to get themselves killed, because Jerma knows that this could be very, very detrimental to his health.
So he turns the corner, Crit Rocket gets him right in the body, and he tries to find a way backwards,
because he doesn't want to get himself killed. That Crit Rocket really shook him.
Nerves are high right now, nerves are skyrocketing.
Blue Team is inches from the cart being capped. Inches, I mean absolute inches.
Jerma coming around the corner, this Soldier is still on the cart, they need to find a way to do this.
Another Heavy coming around to support Jerma and his Medic.
The cart is getting closer to completion, Demoman is right here,
Demoman is going to try and cap the point, Soldier is on the point, Pyro coming around the side here,
Jerma just gets barely the kill on him, Medic goes down.
Now the cart is simply inches away from being capped, Jerma trying to think of a solution.
There just is none at this point, he's going to come around here trying to get this done himself.
Here comes the Cavalry, Jerma comes around here, Uber is right at the right particular moment,
he gets a great Uber charge, absolute fantastic placement.
Turns out to be quite a bad idea though, because as you will see, he gets quite a few kills,
but that doesn't matter because take a look at the bottom of your screen,
the cart is inches away from being capped, the dreaded Soldier is now getting onto the cart,
take a look down at the bottom, it's going to be a close one guys, here it comes,
here comes the Soldier, what's going to happen, is he going to cap the cart?
He caps the cart, oh my goodness gracious, what an absolutely insane turn of events right there for the Red Team.
Absolutely depressing, crushing defeat right there,
Jerma is probably going to go listen to one of his favorite emo songs and cry himself to sleep tonight,
but we've got more important things to talk about like the cart coming through the corner.
This is the part where they, this is where they charge an Uber for a second, I guess.
Anyways, coming around here, Jerma sees a Soldier on the top right,
two medics healing him at this point right now, two medics count him, one and two.
Focusing right now on complete and total area denial, this is a great strategy,
especially a double-heeled Heavy that's impossible to get by, no chance in hell or in heaven to get by him.
Uber charge is almost at 95%, pretty much getting close to completion,
he's going to try and do something, try to make something happen, pulls out the gloves and running urgently,
here we go, pop the Uber baby!
Jerma comes around here, gets the first Demoman with a shot in his mouth,
second Demoman has no chance in hell, third Demoman is right around the corner here,
Jerma lights him up full of lead and then there's a Spy too, what's going to happen?
Is this Spy going to be able to backstab any of these people?
Potentially yes, because he got away, unfortunately.
Jerma and his medic are now in very dire straits right now, behind the cart,
no teammates to back them up, no one to secure their position,
and now the Spy is getting away again.
Here comes a Soldier, oh my goodness gracious, is the medic going to go down?
Can he get the final shots on that Soldier? He cannot!
The Soldier is still spamming another Soldier now, the medic is going to go down,
Jerma has nowhere to go, the medic is now down and now Jerma comes out here, kills both the Soldiers!
Unbelievable performance, I can't believe it, and he just barely gets to hell too, unprecedented.
I hope you guys enjoyed this video, it took a little while to do this,
so thank you so much for watching, I get backstabbed right here in a second,
so I come around this corner, I get around to the side here,
but thank you so much for watching and I will see you next time,
and I hope you enjoyed this, take care everybody.