Hello there, ladies and gentlemen. It's Grandpa here, and today I'm going to show you how to play Surgeon Simulator 2016 the way you're supposed to play it, like a fucking pro.
So if you want some tips and strategies on this game, then you're going to have to send me money, because I'm not telling you the secrets.
But here we go, let's get started. It's pretty easy. I'm going to do this in less than one minute. That's how good I am. I'll show you. Let's go.
So first things first, you want to pick up this hammer, and just start sliding it up and down his head like this. It's okay, he's not awake, he can't feel a thing.
Oh shit, you might. Don't knock him around like that, because he might get screwed.
But anyways, you take the brain clear out of his socket, and this is where it gets a little bit tricky. Some of you morons might not be able to do this, but whatever, this is why I'm here.
So you just start stabbing like this until you find the right spot in the head. Actually, I don't think this is even the right fucking tool. Get that out of here.
This is the right tool, right here. And you just rear back and slice the fucking thing off, just like that. Just as easy as that, ladies and gentlemen.
That's how you do it. And if you don't get it right the first time, then you're just bad, and you're not as good as me.
So then you take the brain out of the goo, and you put it in here. And ladies and gentlemen, that's how you get 53 seconds, I think. Yes, it is. And a D.
How did I get a D? How the fuck did I get a D? That was a perfect surgery. But that's it. That's your whole video. I beat the devils in 53 seconds, and that's it. Bye.
What more do you want from me? I just beat the fucking game in 50 seconds. Get out of here.