Oh, so you guys are the type to talk through the previews of the movie, huh?
Oh, okay. I mean, don't you want to see what happens in the trailer for the haunting of first name last name?
That's coming out this year. Oh, no. No
All right. Fine. I'll be right back. All right. I got uh,
I got milk duds
I got an extra large soda
I got those uh, those things they only seem to sell at movie theaters. They got snow caps
It's like a little chocolate with the crunchy sugary snow on the on the side. They're disgusting but they only sell them here
Okay, I got that. I got my drink. I got my large popcorn. Okay, that was 64
And I think we're ready to go. Welcome everybody. We're not going yet though. Hold on
Don't move everybody stay where stay in your seats. Nobody get up. I'm I'm standing up right now buttered popcorn extra cost
yeah, we're gonna stall here for a minute just because
Uh, I don't know how long this stream is gonna be there are three hundred
three hundred and sixty four
videos
So some of them are ranging from 10 seconds to two minutes. It's pretty much like a 40, you know, 40 40 10
50 50 ish
Of videos that are really really short and videos that are long. So just know that
Uh, we may be here for a while. It might be a three hour stream
It might be it's like a four to five hour stream. I don't know
We might get halfway through and need a break because this is this is just like shit post sunday today
If your submission did not make it into this movie night
Do not think that the submission was bad or sucked or wasn't good enough. It just didn't fit the criteria for tonight, you know
There were a lot of submissions and some of them may you know may have been
All of them were screened, right? So some of them may have been too loud or
Just blasting music or too copyright or maybe maybe not copyright enough on some of them. I'm kidding on that last one
Uh, but there was some small, you know, I I we had to keep this one
Clean and some shit may have gotten through. I don't know. It's very possible
The playlist is going. Yes right now. This is on a um, it's a private playlist
so after this
We can assume we'll just you know, mind everybody just have it not a big deal
But there was a lot of work that went into this especially
for the mods
uh a lot of time
Hundreds of submissions i've seen a bunch of them because I had to obviously
You know veto certain ones and be involved in the process
but a brunt of the actual
Screening here was done by the mods and I want to I want to point out one mod in particular grump clump
Everybody had its contributions, but grump
Fucking fantastic. We're talking like spreadsheets and
Yeah, it was very very very well done
anyways
Uh, I don't know how this is gonna go. We we may we we're gonna this i've never done anything like this before so
Thank you everybody for participating. You guys are a fucking hilarious
Ridiculous community and I couldn't ask for anything better. So
I am looking forward to seeing what you guys came up with
submissions
Let's go
Let's go. You ready to go. Are we ready to go? Are we ready to go?
Did you guys get your all right? Everyone quiet then everybody you have to quiet down. All right, we got shit starting
It's gonna start
Turn your phones off turn your phones off
Here it comes
thq enjoy
I know i'm going to hopefully so I think the thing about um, I think eating going on a diet. It's not a bad idea
Oh shit. Hold on. Wait, wait, hold on
Is germa the b lands wait till he lands. Okay, he landed
You see that look at these pog champs look at those this is terrible that's dumb shit. Yeah
Here comes we've picked up a new group germa the x-wing pilot
You get us uh, maybe you get us a few rounds and we're done with this, you know
Here they come
Watch out tight fighters tight fighters coming in
Left side right side. I'm not even moving watch your tail there. I'm right behind you
No, i'm going this is this is fighter one i'm going down fighter one going down. Oh
Am I going down
Hold on the best part about that last one
Was the whole the background wasn't moving
I was just I was watching star wars and pretending like I was in the movie
This one's called killer germ and started at the beginning face cam. No, I can't i'm naked. I don't have any clothes on
I can't put a face cam on plus I would ruin the movie and quiet everyone quiet
Fuck is happening. Hold on. Let me turn it up. That was called killer germ
Jerebus got talent why am I disgraced?
Hold on I should have won that competition. I just fall asleep
This was this much. Oh my god. We're not even 10 minutes into this. I'm gonna fucking die already
This is the kill me stream, by the way
We're not even fucking five not even two percent of the way through this
Okay, I knew I was gonna have to take a break after every couple of uh, but you know what I mean?
Holy shit
All right, this is called that was that was uh, that was jerma's got talent here comes mortal germ path
See how this one is here we go
Wow
Let me see
Oh, no
Hold on. Hey, no, hold on. That's what you're gonna hear. Hold on like 15 fucking times
I let but that was my finishing move
It was the dab
God damn it, man
Look at me
Oh, what a rick and borty fin. All right. This is this next one's called. Uh, jerma doesn't see it come
Like a bag of groceries or something and he just
Just full on fucking clocked her
What what what am I talking about?
Holy shit, there's a buck. There's a bee in here. Oh, fuck me. Goodbye
That was nice
Jerma's passion dance
My mind
It's a reference i'll never understand
I don't even understand
What is this one's called coming to nintendo switch everyone is here oh god
Mario
That's cool
Oh, it's pac-man pac-man confirmed
Wow
That was wonderful
uh
Some of these are so good like you guys seriously
Talented motherfuckers men, I swear to god
This next one coming up is called
Uh, i'm not sure yet. It's called
Remix 10 but with jerma and also shitty what?
What do you mean also shitty?
Uh, it's rhythm heaven
Nice
That's sweaty
Oh soccer changing
I'm done. Whoa. Hold on. Wait, wait, you can't be done. Yeah, that was fucking amazing
That was beautiful
Thank you
Now this one's called uh
So wait, what was that? Was that rhythm heaven?
That was rhythm heaven. Wow, what a detail in that one. Excellent job
Absolutely fucking excellent
Uh jerma follows jerma follows
No, it's me
Everything's okay
No, no nothing short of amazing but it could be a stranger in a crowd
Whatever helps to get close to you
It doesn't feel
It doesn't think
It's jerma
Jerma bandicoot two comcast strikes back walkthrough
What did you do to my body?
Try to be a good police officer god gamer
What a god of a gamer what is this?
Jerma quest
Oh god, mr. Jesus. I love the aisles. They're very large
Basically, that's my thoughts on the cloverfield trilogy
Huh? Well, then who are you?
What is happening? I don't understand
Okay
We need to stop after this one
All right, got me out now what?
What the hell is this? What game is this doom? What are you doing out of yourself? All right
Do it
I don't need rings anymore
Looks like this ship is mine
Oh my god
I i'm processing the last three that we just watched
Jerma saves crusty
Who's is this crusty? That's crusty
All right
I don't know where that's that's the hallway
from doom three
or uh
dead space
All right. I think we're good. I think we're good. That was a nice little breathing breather
I'd like the jerma quest
Going through the I like the end is the internet connection dropping out. That's that's pretty uh,
That's pretty good. Good pretty good bit there
Here we go. Next one coming up
anthro con truth up
It's another judge showcase because well our judges, uh,
They earned their spot up here and a lot of them you've seen the past performances as well
So our second judge showcase, please help me. Welcome to the stage
Jerma
No, don't be the raptor. No, it's the fucking raptor
How do I how do I delete a post?
How do I delete what's that meme?
This is so awkward
Uh, this is called wasp. That's pretty good echo. It's not a bad idea
Oh shit. Hold on. Wait, wait, hold on. There's wait till he lands wait till he lands
Okay, he landed the added echo was a good touch
Oh, fuck you god
Jerma combat final render and i'm pixelated. I got 16 bit graphics in this one
That was that was done that was done well here come batter up
Wait, what this is called? Hello
What you did we just do this one we already did this one
Why did I write drive through on the tricycle
Oh
All right, hold on hold on a second
It's not even 25 minutes
I've already the energy that's come out of my body. It's it's as if it's been going for four hours
Fucking hilarious
You know, I wasn't I I had some thoughts about was this a good idea or not?
Should I should I not do that? Maybe that's not a good. Oh this you guys have proven that this was a fucking amazing
Amazing thing to do
On an off-handed comment in the fucking chat. I'm so this is fucking so much fun
Here we go. Let's go. Jerma saves the day remastered
This is the remastered edition. Forget about the uh
Forget about the one that came before it pull back to the beginning. I don't know what this game is
I don't know what this game is
What game was that?
smoke
Broly versus goku and jerma life is pain
Here I come
You are occurring hired by the mojave express short streamer makes lost last delivery
What seemed like a simple delivery job has taken a turn?
That was fucking funny. You got what you were after so pay up
You're crying in the rain, pali
Guess who's waking up over here?
Good use good use of the uh cleft time to cash out
You get it over with
Maybe cons kill people without looking them in the face
But I ain't a think
dig
I'm awake though. You've made your life
Sorry, you got twisted up in this scene
From where you're kneeling must seem like an 18 carat run of bad luck
truth is
The game was rigged from the start
You got me you got that was good
Good use
I'm coming up ex jerma automata automa. Oh, it's this
Your house quadrant come in to be here. All units have penetrated the stratosphere autopilot systems green across the board
I'm gonna be one of these ships
Oh
Jerma destroys gaming coming up next that was jerma automata
Oh, okay, i'm on me on the bed i'm half off the bed
I don't know what the punch line is
Oh what's with the sands
Oh jesus
I'm still trying to get over it. All right. I'm fine. Here we go. This is called jerma adventures two
Jerma strip to the moon safe travels jerma
Great great choice of track to vegas to vegas
What was I made out of absolute perfection
No ifs ands or buts. Oh absolute perfection
Uh, that one was great for I mean you get the moon theme there from
Uh duck tales the video game
And when does scrooge mcduck come into smash brothers is that's what i'm wondering
You know
And we got all these dlc carriages dlc scrooge mcduck belongs there. He was one of the best nes games ever made
He's got the springboard. He's got the cane
Why I don't understand he should be there. But anyways, that was uh jerma's trip to the moon and he's got the money
You know, he's got the money. You're right
Because disney I know. All right next one coming up. This is germa nearly dies in a mosh pit
Okay
Okay, germa hold on wait germa craft live action germa craft live action
Hello ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of germa craft
The series where I play minecraft. This is going to be a single player. Let's play
And when I say let's play I use that term
pretty loosely because
I'm an idiot in this game. You're gonna see a lot of fails. You're gonna see lots of
Triumphs at least i'm hoping you're gonna go grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee hot cup of cocoa
I got apple cider right here freshly brewed. Let me take a sip
Please ah, that's good cider. Oh my god
All right, so let's get this started creating
I agree. I agree. Fuck that guy
germa craft
Streamer having a meal streamer having a meal
No fucking god. Okay. Why is this so low?
I'm fighting the urge to skip this one. It's mean
What is this look it's germa
face
Get that like youtube or thumbnail face off the screen
This is pretty fucking good
This is like this is good
nice musical interlude
Oh, I hate this face
How do I get a new face?
Down there at the bottom right
So sweaty
This is actually very well made
Yeah, the bottom right dances is really good too
uncle at a wedding
Yeah, like three drinks and he became
extraordinarily intoxicated
Well, that was that was fantastic. Let's get the next one germa germs bond. Okay, here we go
Jesus
He looks like he's in the back seat, that's why this that's how this is good i'm just his driver
Thank you guys on the scenic route
Loser loser
What?
Ball
Somebody used it. This is terrible. This is by far
This is the best absolutely terrible. This is my favorite part. Nothing about this is good. This is the best part
Not one thing stop talking. This is the best part turn it up
Get to shut this off shut them all off turn your lights on your house off, too
That's great
Oh here comes here comes another like jojo's bizarre adventure
When you've played half-life at least three times hd remaster enhanced edition
okay, uh, but as what i'm saying the best part about the last one was
When you key somebody into a scene and there's a car that guy looked like he was in the back seat
So it was fine. It didn't look like I was superimposed over him. That's well well done. All right, here we go
Do not attempt to open the doors until the train has come to a complete halt at the station platform
Passengers are
Where's professor you'll just have to wait until where's professor barnsworth
Welcome ah
Morning mr freeman looks like you're running late
Me
No, don't fucking dab me here. Come on, man. Oh my god
This is it is more there's another one this is part two
Is this metal gear?
Nothing about this is good. Not one thing i'm gonna dream right now. I'm dreaming this whole thing
I gotta wake up man. I gotta wake up
I gotta wake up
So was that all from
Look at this fucking face. Look at this
Look at that crazed look my god
This is not this guy. You know what I mean? Like look at this guy right here. I look like woody harrelson's son
This is not the same person
All right
Was that all from half life?
Grindelwald
I don't even i haven't seen that movie and it's making me laugh. All right, this is called germa tv metal gear solid 2
Here we go. So I think the thing I think eating going on a diet. It's not a bad idea. Holy shit
That's interesting wait till he lands wait till he lands, okay he landed
Whoo up and smoke
I don't like this part a little bit further
Okay
I would I am
I I would if I could I can't turn it off. This is called who who don't you fuck i'll skip it
I'm gonna skip it if it doesn't
All right, all right, all right, all right fine fine
This is germa super germa 64
That's my favorite game
I'm just walking back. Can I make the jump? Come on I can make this jump wrong way mom. I see it
Wow
That was great
Just pointing to it and touching it
That was amazing
That's it
Come on next we got germa. Yes who runs into a window
It's called watch out germa
When did I do this wait hold on a second, when did I do this I don't remember doing this
When the fuck did I do this?
This is really good
What this is fucking fantastic, when did I do that?
Wait, what dave right? I don't understand. No, i've been um
Yeah, i've been driving for like probably a couple years now on that right
I say we're led to believe that I moonwalked out of the stadium and
All right. So here we are. We're at persona 985. Here's this next one. I don't understand. I don't have ever played this
Is that auto
Holy shit
Auto leveled up. Well, is that my that's my persona
33 year old germa 95 defeats high school student in dance-off. Oh man
That guy tagged in his absolute form wait, what is this
I've told you guys this before absolute perfection
I know ifs ands or buts
This right here
Is absolute perfection
Perfection
Whoa, easy
easy
Oh
Gerva teaches karate
What is it karate?
Oh god, no
Oh my god, oh my god. Oh my god
Holy shit
That was fucking insane
by the way, like I was muted that whole time just laughing my ass off because
Like i'm teaching karate right teaching karate. That's me teaching karate
What is this like energy shit that i'm doing with my hands?
I'm like that guy that no I will be able to stop you with energy
And the guy got like punched in the face or something whatever it was
Oh my god
Don't mute. I had to I was gonna ruin the video. I had to mute it was going to ruin everything
I would have just like been screaming over that whole thing
That was so fucking insane. All right, this one's called germa meme. Okay
I don't like ruin all these videos germa meme
Okay, we go to youtube.com on search
searching for
sword
art
online
Episode one, okay
I don't understand
God
He just was searching for sword art online what's what I don't understand
Now, what are you doing now? You look at is you're gonna listen
What is this?
Do I just skip this one
Oh my god, okay. Well, whatever I don't know what it is
Hey, look at germa germa bizarre and well, that's love
Germa germa bizarre adventure
I wonder out of the 300 plus submissions how many of them were jojo related
75 percent
A lot of work went into this one. This is a lot of work
That was out of the binocular I mean this was not just thrown together this is like some real work here
It was the intro. Hey, here's what I have to say about this. Well, that's 76. See this bullshit
All the single drone
Oh god, what happens?
What is happening
Fashion
The next one's called birthday birthday the next one's birthday
Yeah, why would you look over and smile good for me, okay birthday
It's getting closer another jojo's
Sorry
Hey, what's going on everybody germa here with god damn sort of a different video today
I'm apologize if I sound a little nervous because I am I just found
a wild spay nest
On dust bowl and this is they pop up from time to time
But I gotta be really careful here guys. This is the middle of mating season blue spays and red spays are god
Gotta be very very quiet here
Oh shit, oh shit, does he see me?
That would have been very bad he's saying it he's saying the word like how they're reacting to this though
I don't like how oh god. Oh god. Just run. I gotta get out of here. Oh, no, that's a bit they're killing each other
I'm gonna fucking die here
Hi, hi, my name is hey the jerva perry is this
Wow, no term it goes west
You're a scientist
What is it with will of elvin?
Which chat has
Nuclear war has nearly destroyed our planet now evil presence seeks to enslave what's
What is this fucking video
I don't know if this video is
All right going for the low hanging fruit
Glow hanging fruit
Wait, hold on did this did this get through the meme shit?
No, I I didn't want anything to be too me me tonight
Is this a what was this a meme?
Was this a meme?
Did a meme get through?
Hold on. Did a meme just get through?
Oh god. Damn it a me
Whatever
All right. This is called. I don't know what that is
I don't know what that meme is
Everyone keeps saying it. I'm too i'm too much of an old man. All right, here we go
Welcome to lift dave right?
Welcome to lift so you're from here. I grew up here. I know all the secrets. Don't like turn off your gps
I know where i'm going
This is a pretty good car
Was that yeah?
No, i've been uh
Yeah, i've been driving for like probably a couple of years now on lift
right
Yeah, yeah, well I moved uh, I moved here when I was probably 19 or so
Yeah
Oh shit, sorry. Yeah
It's a great place. Oh up next. Wait, what is this?
What the hell is that?
fast purple versus germ
purple alien
Purple alien
What the fuck is this flying battle chapstick?
Okay, they arrive at the alien's home planet
awesome battle takes place
It is unsettling
Okay, wait a second
You know when there's like so much stimulation
That I I don't know. It's real anymore
All right. Hold on. We've been doing this for an hour. Let's take let's take just like a two minute
Uh state of the channel here, okay
Food break. No, no, no, no, we're just gonna chill for a second. We'll do i'm curious as to so we're about
Probably like we're probably like 20 to 10 to 20 percent of the way through this
Oh
I'm still i'm loving this though. I'm happy. This is fucking fun
All right. I just needed a second. So for us to
Flush all the memories flush all the shit that we just saw into the brain toilet and and
Put one of those coal rocks toilet cleaners in it's a fresh toilet and here it comes here comes more like video poo
I don't know why I just made that what the fuck am I talking about?
I don't I don't know why I said that look my brain is scrambled right now. This is okay
Have a good germa in an ape odyssey. This is from the movies. That's not me laughing. I'm not laughing. It's
Jeremy boston cia
Hey, how are you? How you doing? Gotcha. What is this? Well, the car is sentient. What am I being followed by?
Oh, i'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. Why am I going back and shit?
It's fucking mr. Bean
Oh
What the fuck
Next
Yeah, uh german versus the loading screen
crash bandicoot
John travolta confused by two german
Oh
He goes over with with the cowbell
Oh, okay. This is called late streamer late streamer
Fake laugh. Oh not tonight. Not any night. Wait, not any night. What I don't fucking fake laugh. What?
Oh, yeah, not tonight. But tomorrow i'll be fake fucking laughing
All right
Hey viewer, what's up nervous late? Do you have an emotes?
Uh here do you want the german mustard or german fireman? Oh, you don't want to spam emotes
What are you going to do while you wait?
You want to spam copypasta? That's a great idea
I'll ask the mods if we can if you're sure not yet. Yes ask
Okay, i'll ask uh mods. Is it okay if we spam copypasta while we wait?
Hey, what? No, I do not approve of that. But viewer doesn't have
Uh, well, what were you saying? She was just saying we're fine spamming emo
Actually, I just wanted to know
Can you please speak up?
I'm gonna be playing team this is called they move in herds. Oh my god. It's already that's auto
That's very accurate. Well it is but look
Sometimes i'm late. It's okay
Probably every other time
they move in herds
I'm gonna be playing team fortress 2 as
dinosaur
Oh, give us a wiley coyote here
That was really 1940 is a boomer that was very that was cute i'll give that one a cute
So you made it to the youtube homepage. How are you? My name's brett. I'm your digital guy
As you see here
Here's your viewing screen
This screen right here is going to show you some of your favorite videos from gondom style all the way to your grandma
outer fishing trip
This is right here. This is your space down here
You've got the like button if you like a piece of content go ahead and press it if you don't like a piece of content
Stums down that's over here too on this side
Here folks you can keep up with me here
Here's the subscribe button and if you like a content enough to want to subscribe like a content potentially lose
Their videos on your feed because we don't do that anymore. You have to click a bell the bell's over here
Click that bell right there and then maybe you'll be able to see the content you subscribe to
This is your space
This is it right here
What's happening?
Okay, uh, this is called back to formula back to formula
Uh, peter may introduce my father norman. I was born
Great honor to meet you, sir. You're a scientist. I'm something to the scientist myself
Jerma watches his favorite show. Hi. I'm jerma 985 and you're watching the disney channel
This is by far
This is my favorite part, this is the best part
Green screen trio suspect is acting extremely erratic
This is the worst thing i've ever seen in my life
I will destroy you. I have an army of 60 million subscribers. Look at my muscles
Oh, no
I don't want to fight you man. I don't big dog. We got a situation here. I'm gonna need some backup
We got a 10 22 in progress. I'm gonna need you bringing the big gun
Get on the ground
Get on the ground right now. You haters have nothing on me fine
Am I even in this video prepare to be epically owned new for I am the powerfulest
Is
All right, i'm back i'm back i'm back here, uh, that was that was um
Um
That was fun, that was a fun one that was a very uh fun one
Let's start at the beginning of this one. This is called jerma stellar
Close start not good. That's it. All right, that's it. This is called shooting
I made it I made it wherever I was going. All right friend. Oh, here's another one of these
I didn't even run anything over. Oh shit. Sorry. Yeah, sorry
Oh
I'm in my living room right now his germa craft
I do got a pretty sweet house way better than your minecraft house, dude
The gym carry I forgot about the gym carry germa versus germa. This is called short. I wonder what's gonna happen
It's time for you to pay
Ah
Casting a spell it's casting zap
I think I popped a blood vessel in my eye
When he when the transition to mortal combat
Uh, hold on. I need a break. I need a break
Because I really think I just hurt myself that that smooth transition into the fucking jost destruction from mortal combat
Oh
Holy shit, there are 9,700 people here. I didn't even look
That last video was called uh germa
That's quite the thumbnail germa versus germa short
Damn. All right
Uh, i'm gonna grab a drink. I suggest you all do the same. Let's take a little quick break
That was fucking these are these are so fun
You guys have severely severely just crushed my expectations for how this was gonna go
I'll be right back grab a drink. All right
I'm back. Welcome back. All right, let's uh, let me just take a quick look at something here. All right, we're going good
We're about we are just about like 33 percent of the way through and it's been an hour
So I think I think we can do the whole thing tonight
We almost got to 10 000 years
It's all right. I'm not looking to that's if you're here you're here and i'm fucking glad you are
Yeah, I got a drink because uh the i'm supposed to drink wine but the wine went bad
Here we go. This next one coming up
Is called uh germa snap. I believe
I believe uh infinity war spoilers coming up here just in case you did the next minute here is gonna just be careful
If you haven't seen the movie where thanos is gonna be his main character and there's a problem. All right, just be careful
Here we go. Welcome back. Welcome back to movie night germa snap
You should have gone for the head
because of this
I'm gonna do it with two hands
And everyone dies
That means me too no wait wait wait, no, that means me
I didn't
I'm so glad somebody used it
I'm, so glad somebody used it. That was great initial j. That's my new car. Yeah
It's beauty, isn't she?
Yeah, I I souped her up too
v6 engine
Anyways, great. Let me get back. Let me get to this this little thing over here. You know what I mean?
That's sweat mark
That's not even the same car. That's a different car taking you guys on the scenic route
Careful
Oh my god
This is visiting my dad
What the fuck you painted shit all over the wall
No, that's not good. I thought you were making progress in here. Stop calling me diane. My name's daniel
I know you've always wanted a daughter, but that doesn't mean you can treat me like one. That's just a big old son, ain't it?
How can you say that god?
You know i'm trying my best
Oh, no, it's raining outside
You're a fucking monster. Holy shit. You know what fine
I hope one day you get to have that stupid ugly daughter. You've always wanted
Uh, i'm not so sure about that one. I'm gonna be a hot boy. That's right
What the fuck is wrong with you? What is that? Why you've always wanted a daughter. What the fuck
Oh my god, you belong in a mental institute. You belong on death row. I mean you're beyond saving at this point
I'm sick of putting up with this. This is the thanks I get for visiting you and why are you walking towards me?
What are you gonna do step back?
Holy shit
Oh my god, that was that was crazy
Jerma and you're watching the disney channel jerma clues
Turbastic park. Oh god
Holy god, here's another one. There's another one from uh, that movie
Spoiler
Come on come on come on you had it there
And oh my god, this one is called attack of the beers. Oh, yes
The fucking undertale one
Very good job with the prompts by the way
Shut up
Wait, why why did I come in here as a different person?
That was good this jerma becomes a furry this fucking raptor man, I swear to god I never should have done the raptor
I
Compact hobbit, holy fuck. It's a stupendous. Do you think flattery will keep you alive? No, no
No, indeed
Oh, it's the the archons
Buy or rent on youtube, by the way
If you'd like to buy a rent
I'm so small there. Come on. I guessed his foul purpose some time ago
10 000 viewers will fail. Holy shit
Hold on 10 000 10 000 viewers
That's uh
That's fucking insane
Thanks for coming
Hope you're having fun
Give a speech
I don't have I don't really have a speech man
10 000 or a hundred. Thanks for being here. You guys are fucking amazing. Thanks a lot. Let's keep going
Uh, we we've got gifted subs
Uh jake lazer. Thanks for the five community subs. Thanks a lot
It's not showing on screen because uh notifications are turned off. I turned them off
So no notifications tonight because obviously, you know, i'd rather keep this
No, uh, all the audio or their video on top. So, all right, let's go
Holy fuck people are giving up tvasi just gave out 10 community subs. Let's hey, let's let's review fallout 76 in celebration
Here we go. Thank you so much tvasi
In vault 76
our future
begins
This is terrible
Absolutely terrible filling details
Nothing about this is good
Not one thing
God, I hate this
I hate this. This is terrible god
But there is one big difference
With this game what's with the kazoos in the background each of those characters is a god of a gamer seriously
It just works. It just works metal gear solid cheese and eater
I don't know why what's with the points. I like have to overact every single scene. You know what I mean? Like i'm not gonna point
Came over
Nice check it during this great screen golden eye intro, but when I play golden eye, they're like, whoa
Billy germ
Rip bod the bod was deleted probably like an hour ago
Fucking weirdo
Jesus christ get fucking x-factor what I was hitting you you have hit
Wow mortal combat dude, some of these are so
Oh
Is that the only one i'm gonna watch twice it is all right, let's go
That was so funny. I'm glad somebody used the baseball. I did like fucking 30 minutes of baseball shit
Ooh
What germa's favorite dark souls 3 video?
What this is the thing i've told you guys this before
Absolute perfection. What is this like giant dad? It's answer button
This right here
Is absolute perfection
All right, this is terrible
What is the best part right here? What am I? We are watching a video. We're just watching a youtube video. This is my favorite part
This is the best part
We're just watching somebody's youtube video
Oh my god, it's almost over a gamer. What a god of a gamer seriously
It's like a channel plug
Life is pain not tiny i'm compact germa circulation. I just got 18 sick
That that sneak into the frame was great
That's right
Of course the earth exploding
That was well made saw this guy at the market today
I know what this is already
Yep
That's a little too high for me
Sure, what what what was the point of me putting the ladder in like I knew it was gonna happen
Going again
Am I go i'm going again?
I actually almost fell off for real though
Quizny dvd hey, it's me germa and you're watching the disney channel
I hate this channel. No
Brush your teeth if you want not go to fucking jail kids
Germa ends telltale
Trouble in the mountains, what are we zooming into? Oh god
Oh
Derma takes flight another moon theme. I see you guys got good taste. That's a good thing, right?
Get him
Nice out of the lightsaber
I love the lightsaber ones. They're my favorites just because I have a lightsaber
That was a what? Oh
Streamer lost within a game realm is this one?
Is this is this is the whole video
I thought I didn't know
That was fucking great
Uh, we had a hundred dollars came in a hundred bucks came in from mostly lost
10k bits for 10k viewers germa heart. Thanks a lot
Uh, another hundred dollars just came in right now from kyra toby 100 bucks 200 just came in
Uh, congrats you 10k concurrent viewer streamer
That's fucking wild man
Holy shit
Thanks a lot guys. Thank you kyra toby. Thank you mostly lost
Huge money. Thank you. Let's keep the ball rolling. This is uh, meet the real scout v2
v2
Hey, somebody keep track of my head
God gamer, come on
This is the pinwheel fight
No, no, no, no, this is not that's not real though
That's not real. I didn't somebody did somebody did that on their own. This is not me. That's not from my fucking dark soul stream
It's not that's a fake video. Don't believe that that was a fake video people are giving out community subs job joy
Thank you for the five community subs jamie five community subs. Thanks a lot guys
I didn't do that. I and I said it was me but it was not me
I didn't have that same outfit on I was not using an axe. I used a sword
Whatever germ germ bizarre adventure height is immeasurable
The jojo ones are so well made
They took like days to make
Dedication even do that pose, right?
I wish I understood any of this
I wish I understood even one second of that, but that was very well made. Thanks a lot. Uh new sports car
That's just my new car. Yeah
It's beauty, isn't she?
Yeah, I I souped her up too
V6 fucking 1998 toyota camry. What do you got back there? Ooh
Not as good as mine, but still still worth having in your garage
Anyways, great. That's great that you're doing so well
Yeah, you know, I know you gotta go. I just find I just caught you
Let me get bad. Let me get into this this little thing over here. You know what I mean?
Good to see you. Yeah, take care of yourself. Do I actually get inside this?
Oh jesus
Where is this? This is a real tunnel. Are you guys on the scenic route?
What the fuck
What what did what was that? What was that? What was that?
This is called germa league
Real life science footage of local handsome streamer pogs in chat, please
Shut up
Do I at least fight the dinosaur?
Jeremy's house pretty sweet house way better than your bike house, dude
This house the house is better
I'm a driver. Oh jesus. Why is the camera on the ground? I think you guys are on the scenic route
Flying to the car
It's from naked gun careful naked gun
What the fuck? Whoa
Whoa
A car song
I don't either. I love that you guys found these dashboards though. What?
Uh
Those of you that don't know
Uh naked gun was a series of movies starring leslie neilson
And that's how they opened every single movie pretty good reference. Nice job
Another hundred dollars just came in. Hey germa been a while. It's from edgemont. Thanks for the hundred bucks
Lots of money tonight
Uh, I want to make a green screen vid, but i've been incredibly busy. So here's ten thousand bits instead
Thank you
Edgemont for the ten thousand bits hundred bucks. It's incredibly fucking generous of you. Thank you so much a lot of money
Bro, you're rich tonight. I I don't even know what to say
Thank you. This is uh, germa craft the adventure returns
You even got me in the right places too you had to go in here and fill this
Got him nice
Do I get the other two diamonds? That's the most important thing, right? That was really well done. Germa is dead
Hold on. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. It's uh infinity war
Spoilers just in case you're curious. This is another one of those infinity war videos. Here it comes
Close your eyes and block your ears
That's it is that it
You took the all right
You took the clip of me during the during the green scream stream the green scream
I you scream we scream raw scream for ice cream scream that stream
That was the i'm kidding around before I do the actual reference. Uh, germa loves auto
Oh god, damn it. No, no, no, no, no, no, no i'll hard skip this one
This is the worst video i've ever made and I made it like seven years ago and I hate it
But I love it and I hate it at the same time. Well, whatever there's like 11 000 fucking people here. Let's go
Hi everybody. My name is otto. This is my video. I made this all by myself. Hi
Yummy
Okay, let's go outside. Let's have some fun
Come follow me down the stairs. This is the thing i'm talking about right here. This is how I did the whole I told you guys
Absolute perfection
No ifs ands or buts. Oh, yes. Thank you. This right here
Is absolute perfect. I hope it's almost over
No, I hope it's over. This is how I attack my friend
It's just the video you just made me play this video. It's not even over. It's just the whole video
Oh, I can't show a dog shitting. I can't show a dog shitting on twitch. I had to skip it
How do you find someone who has spent a lifetime covering his tracks?
For some he was a guardian angel
Others a ghost who never quite fit in
You will give the people of earth an ideal to strive towards
They'll race behind you they will stumble what fall but in time when the sun
Superman in time you will help them
Wow
What harry believed if the world found out who I really was
He'd reject me
He was convinced that the world wasn't ready
Fucking harry potter. Hey, what's going on? It's jeremy from germa 985 and you're watching germa 985
No, don't give me a bunny. Oh my head is gonna explode
Okay, I can work with this
Hold on we have to stop. Oh, I have to stop for a second at least like 10 seconds
Uh
Did you even get that image?
Where would you get that image?
How did you come up with why would you come up with that? Why would you want me to fight a fucking baby?
uh
Okay, this is called hotel germa. Here we go
Are you seeing this fuck you
Uh, uh, hey germa, you're tiny. Oh bowser
Uh, thank you. Thank you for that. Jurassic is another one of these
Who are you
Some psychos in my back. What are you doing? This isn't your house. This is my bathroom
Who are you dude get out get out of my house, who is this guy?
Who is there's just some guy in my bathroom. No b movie five. I didn't it's not a real annotation. This is called germa combo
Oh my fuck is god
Oh
Okay, let's go let's go to the next one
Another one of these another one of these
I fucking hate this. I hate that walk. I love this video, but I hate that walk
Drop it santa returns with a vengeance
Fucking two by four. Is that what you want to see?
Before the street this tree is already done. So hey, very fucking christmas everybody
Fuck out of here santa
Merry fucking christmas
Hey, it's time. It's timely. It's relevant here
I am
and a jojo's bizarre adventure clip
Really wish I watched episode 29 season three for me to understand this
You got me you got me you got me oh shit german knight, this is supposed to be fortnight. This is a fortnight clip
zombie
No, forget about the zombies
What is this? This is not even
What you just?
All right, whatever. It's fine
All right, it's some of them. It's all right
scariest moment in gaming history
What oh my god
Battle with k compact for um delta room. That's chest not chest
Eat bow you and ralsey bowed. Oh, that's actually pretty good creative use
You get points for creativity on this one. I don't even eat cheetos anymore
I can't
The crown is 60 percent
It's because I have weird organs
There's the jacks right there. Oh, I turned to little germa
Germa's bad time and right after that we've got a we've got an undertale
I do like the audio editing very well done. All right a lot of work went into this one. Come on. I lost
All right, hold on give me a break come on
What I don't give a shit about the view count
Look, we've transitioned from youtube to twitch
And i'm still still doing things
Oh, whatever
derma versus boulder
Oh classic from resonator 4
Holy shit, it worked
All right charlie boot it up turn it on boot up the time machine we're going back didn't there it is we're going back
To 2007 let's go. What do you mean? You can't go. No, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Wait, don't don't hey
Where did we end up reverend clergy?
Fellow citizens we observe today. What is going on?
Where am I going? I'm going through time
What is going on? What is this? What is
This
That's from a fucking movie from the 90s
Okay
All right. This is a jojo's bizarre adventure episode clip on this channel clip on this stream number 14
Uh stand master jeremy someone's platinum started to beat himself up. Okay, let's see how it works
Yes, oh my god fucking help guys help, please help me somebody help me. I don't ready somebody help help
Help calm down. You don't have to worry, but i'm gonna kill you
Santa's in town
And just like that he was never heard from again, well, yeah, that was good day's work
Tom and jeremy classic cartoon
Snake up on him. What is this guys this before? Absolute perfection. No, it's halo. What is this? This right here?
Is absolute perfection
Which halo is this? I don't even play halo
halo three
Okay
I hope it was a good game
Jerma saves christmas
Oh shit zombies, what the hell is this? Yeah. All right, you destroyed that guy without even touching it
This is fucking great this is fucking great it's only coming out of one side
That's like number five for the earth exploding from the uh rat movie jerma joins the payday gang
Hey, man, come to the stream. My name is jerma. Nice to meet you right there bingo right there
That's the follow button if you click that every so often you're getting notified that i'm streaming
So what do we got here?
We know what they say
two
He's more than one
What the fuck you got something to say?
Oh
Oh shit zombies
Oh my god, this I can't even I can't even think right now
I don't even get a mask
Where the nunchucks come from payday character pack, no, it would get like 200 sales. Oh god
Yes, all right. Wow
Whoa, I never thought that I would be winning this award
Unbelievable. Let me just say
Thank you
for all of your support
And for all of your wonderful contributions
Award say it's been quite a year
Quite a year. In fact
That i've got two more games to announce
What?
Still that any of our developers have ever done
It was my pleasure
To announce our latest title
So all over the place where did I go? I just disappeared
Oh my fucking god
Ruse of gunplay amazing boss battles
Castle griffin steve the game as soon as monday
Gerber rubble fury road
No one should ever put cigarettes out on their penis. No god. No, they shouldn't
This is a booger eating stream
I'm just eating boogers
When the webcam isn't on I just dig up there and I eat the boogers. That's what I do
When did I fucking say that what why would I do that?
They coming what the fuck? This is this is very well made. He's gone out of their mind
All right, you ever see what we gremlin's to a world without hope
Wow my butthole out here everything hurts you want to get through this
Why am I here
Fire fire fire fire
Hey, give me the fucking secret recipe for coca-cola
Oh my goodness that was though. That was a whole trailer. No, no derma saves the world turn it up. Turn it up
Turn it up
Do it
Thank you
I saved the world right here. I just saved the world. Oh my god. All right, let's talk about this for a second
um
Why didn't you guys like edit out my disgusting sweat marks?
Do you know what I mean?
You could have gone in there with paint tool and just made it so it didn't look like disgusting
Okay
Sweat check. I don't i'm not wearing any clothes. I'm naked. I made sure to wear no clothes today
Uh, but that that that last one was fucking perfect
Uh, man
All right. Let me see where we are movie night. We are pretty much at the halfway point as you can see
Another we're like at 40 percent. It's over 11 000 people here. Holy shit
Another another couple hours of this. Let's just do the whole thing tonight. Fuck it. You know what i'm saying?
And we were here might as well do it right so it's been another hour
I think uh, I think it's time to take another small break
Just for like two minutes. I'm gonna grab another drink and I suggest you do the same
Because you need you need to collect your thoughts after like an hour straight of these fucking crazy videos
So two minutes i'll be right back. He fell into the toilet. No, i'm here
Oh
Oh, yeah. Yeah. All right. So here comes act
three of four
Right that makes sense, right here comes act three. Here we go. Welcome back. Let's go
65 million year old joke
Oh another here comes jojo's bizarre adventure
I don't understand. I don't I don't understand
What are you doing here? All right, germa teaches manners
After you nicked his car dean says you're fair game. Oh, by the way, i'm not like five two
Everybody thinks i'm like fucking five feet tall. No, I was like crouching down. I'm like five eight
It's true
You should get out of white granddaddy. You'll get hurt. I know he ain't joking. You should go
If you're looking for another rent boy, they're on the corner of smith street
Yeah, interesting thought process
Please oh my god
Fucking god terrible. I don't want to get up there and fight. I just want to leech xp
You missed that one
I'm going to try as hard as I i'm going to be
The sweatiest fucking try hard in this server. I'm going to kill you
I'm going to be a silent but deadly smelly fart in your face. Hope you're ready
Hey
Ha ha ha glasses suck a thought out of my ass
Uh, no, I just
I wonder what's next
Great. Okay. Kerbang crash boom the movie starring jeremy elbertson kerbang boom crash
Starring me is me
So you better bundle up out there make sure you have anti tornado clothing on and anti tornado hats because they might blow away
dying
I was supposed to be dying in what am I doing?
What am I what am I doing?
What the fuck am I doing? Why am I doing this? Why am I doing this?
I shouldn't be doing
I'm just like peeking on people. All right
Never done that
What does this have to do with a movie absolutely terrible I mean nothing about this is good
Not one thing I I I would I mean
I hate this
I hate this. I don't have to say anything. I don't say anything about my sentiments. Oh, Jojo's
Bizarre adventure
Knock knock who's there? Aren't you glad I didn't say banana my fucking god put this guy in a body bag. He's dead
This is terrible so many good uses for that one
Nothing about this is good
Not one thing
Are like 500 million people fans of this show
Judging by how many there's 11 000 people here, right? Is it like 600 million fans?
only in america
Jermario 64
This is gonna be good I can already tell this is gonna be good so this is the virtual world
It's not nobody used that one yet. Surprisingly
High quality
Yeah, the minecraft wait did the minecraft one use that so it's like a four hour
Haha
Waiting for the train
Is this just me waiting for a train?
Look at the key. Look at you can still see
That's it, okay, juror what
Say some gangster is this in your fly girl
Whoa, whoa, what the fuck
Somebody once told me the world
Oh my goodness, what is this me talking?
That's it, okay that
The the germ the germanites face worse fear
We might have a spoiler here for a various anime show just to let you know if you watch anime be careful
Because there might be a spoiler in this video
Okay
It's not very nice I wouldn't do this
Terma pulls a lever from dark souls
Okay, speed with one punch
Just in case anyone's um curious
I beat that guy first try in one hit so you can't say I didn't know
Uh when a germa stream starts
Derma saves waifu director's cut the fuck is a gamer. What a god of a gamer. Seriously. Why do you have subtitles here?
Never mind, okay
What the hell is happening right now
If you watch various anime shows there could be a spoiler here
I want to make sure you understand that if you watch animated television shows that have been abbreviated to anime
It's for animated show. Just be aware. There could be a spoiler in this video. Okay
What the fuck is even happening
All right, we're trying to get out of the exit here
Just to let everybody know if you sat me down in a chair and said, uh, sir
I will pay you
100 million dollars
to tell me what this is
I've and I don't have access to google or
Uh seri, you know, I wouldn't be able to do it 100 million dollars. I don't know
Hey
Here's what I have to say about this
This tetris
There's like seven different games going on in here
I saved the world right here. I just saved the world
And so what I didn't that's not even real
Uh germa hunter playstation 2 opening
Good use of superimposing there. I told you guys this before
Oh
Am I out of bullets
Was that the whole opening to monster hunter 2 nice job just meet the germa you knew it was coming at some point
Ah got it. All right. Wow
Right ball one streamer on twitch
And i am go fuck yourself
There it is
I do lots of fun things on this stream like coffee
Cheetos chicken nobody
Jeremy yeah
Are you a furry?
Aren't you glad I didn't say banana put this guy in a body bag. He's dead. That was fucking good
That was great. That was a meat germa
I don't know what that was
Episode 15
It's detected by this garfield
Is it joe joe's bizarre adventure that is that no there's more
Bethesda game studios
presents
What exactly?
x-men
Woohoo. Hey, it's me. That's right. Diane. We got the wacky weather report coming up here
Uh, that was my nose. So as you see here, it's gonna be
It's gonna be breezy all right
So make sure you stay indoors 60 mile per hour gusts. Be careful out there
Whoa
Easy next up. Oh, of course. It's gotta tell you the local pumpkin festival is gonna be cancelled because
Oh, no, it's raining outside
Back to you diane
What
What the fuck
What am I what's happening? What's going on?
What is what's happening?
Yes, certainly yes
I blend in with the crowd. It's okay. That's it. Is it? Yes. That's it. Yes. Mm-hmm
It's not particularly city is it?
The meme funeral too
The man who made them must destroy them sony santa monica presents meme funeral, too
What is that?
It must be this tall to all meme atlas keep contact bodies. Oh
What the fuck is that old mean to prospector life of the unsteady arm
He can miss that one
4k graphics improve facial capture
Bring photos to life with a pc compatible
Uh, that was a he will fight the worst joke of them all what's the worst joke
He's overload
That is the worst of them all
Cast docs germ of sabotage is the fellowship
That key
This is the best part
This is terrible did did I do that absolutely terrible
Oh, this one's called germ is lament
Somebody good somebody's in the pajamas sleeping we've been seeing very many of these in the bed
No, it's pretty good car jobs
You liar
Is that implying that mayor mcgee's cheated on me with chuck norris yes apparently great what the what the hell was that
German rumble moment 36 comes another one of those guy at tournaments
That wasn't jojo that was naruto
Same thing another piece of meat
It's time for you to pay
Uh, rest in peace jeremy the hot dog elbertson no, welcome this one's gerba in indiana jones
I already know what this is gonna be
Different clothes
No, not another one of these i don't want to see this one
Hi
One day ago today one day ago today he's going by up on the train tracks
What's the context here
It's a broken mom when you can't stop choosing to sleep to me
I don't know what that is. That's kirby with hair. What kirby's doing here
What's a broken mom when you can't stop choosing to sleep through your
I like the racecar bet
Why is elsa and anna here? That's the end. All right. Well, that was that was that was a video
We just watched gerba speaks on ted ted talk
Ideas where it's spring
To do what i'm doing if you were falling you would be going like this you'd just be like
Why do we why what is this
Hey scotty seriously germa craft
Absolute perfection
No, it was too fast. That one was too fast. I don't even know what they were trying to say
Uh, this is detective germa to rhyme city a celebration of the harmony between humans and pokemon
Tim your dad was a legend in this project
If you want anything like your dad, you wanted to be a pokemon trainer when you were young
Yeah, that didn't really work out
someone there
Pulling into the editing software
That gets a clap for me nothing about this is good
Excellent job
Germa greenscreen germacraft fireplace germa's house. That's apparently my house that we're going to
It's on fire
Good use of the water no one's used the water yet
Oh, I didn't know you could do that. I didn't know you could do that
What is this? Oh
now
This is show business
Into the spider verse
Looks a little weird. What?
What?
Sweat park germa fool fights the rats
Well, if you haven't seen the movie deadpool, uh, mr
Spoiler for the movie coming out here in about five seconds five four three two
Under the stream. My name's germa
What is that?
Here we go
That king
Which one is supposed to be me
This piss on me kisses piss in my face
Kiss in my face
Oh suggested once upon a deadpool
No, I apologize for this
Welcome to shit post sunday
Come on
Bingo
There's too much going on to even react to this having a cigarette is this one having a cigarette
Yeah, sometimes I like to smoke down here
I haven't seen that in a long time germa's nap. I don't know what that
You do it you do it i'm sleeping
You didn't put the covers in
Hey just trust me no, oh my god, that was it
The weather channel very smart media did not die
Ten million
That's right diane it's gonna be a cold one this weekend as you can see here
We've got some low pressure coming up for the mountains here going all the way down over southern new hampshire
That's right. It's gonna make its way down here. There it is new hampshire across
The nile river there and then it's gonna wrap back around and come back towards massachusetts, which then
Unfortunately your saturday football game is gonna get potentially rained out as you see
Two that's right two cold fronts coming from here and from here
And it's gonna be a breezy one. They're gonna collide together and they may be a gosh darn tornado
So you better bundle up out there make sure you have anti-tornado clothing on and anti-tornado hats because they might blow away
diane
I'm not so sure about that one. It's gonna be a hot one. That's right
It's gonna be a hot one over there diane as you can see look at how big that sun is
Look at how big that is. I don't even need to tell you temperature numbers. That's just a big old sun ain't it there?
And it's gonna be shining across the entire u.s of a that's right sun here sunshine over here and even sunshine down here
Where you don't typically get it if you know what i'm saying
So uh bundle up out there. It's gonna be a cold one every day is a cold one with the sun out there
What the fuck diane go fuck yourself what the hell am I talking about
I'm being forced to type these against my will what?
Yeah, it's gonna be it's gonna get cold with the sun out there derma hates memes
Hate all his goddamn memes
Not against the truth there how to kill me now. I can just kill
That's making me dizzy and i'm not even doing it derma finally plays far cry one
He's got like a steam notification
Yeah taking you guys on the scenic route
You had to play far cry for this
You actually had to go into far cry
and record this
props to that
bar song
Oh derma unlocks a power to rival the gods
Is this jojo better not be the jojo's bizarre adventure. Oh, that was fucking loud
Fuck
People have used that catch it line
Do you remember when he gets cutscene controls
Check it out
Spartan for real. You better not be no man. He's here. We're gonna be where did you find him?
nappin
I'll bet
It's good to see you chief likewise, ma'am. Let's get you up to speed
The prophet of truth ships breached the lunar perimeter
Smashed what was left of the home fleet terrestrial casualties from the subsequent bombardment were
extreme
Truth could have landed anywhere, but he committed all his forces here east africa the ruins of new mombasa
Then they started digging
What about halo we stopped it but only temporarily
Now the prophet of truth is looking for something called the arc where he'll be able to fire all the halo rings
If he succeeds
Every sentient being in the galaxy the rings will kill us all
Hell not again emergency generators now shielding failed
They're down and charging as soon as they're up reestablished contact with lordhood. Let him know
all of you vermin
Carrying the dirt thinking what I wonder that you might escape the coming fire
No
Your world will burn until its surface is but just fucking annoying
I'm just really annoying will live to instrument bastard. Just love to run his mouth
This is germa wars the meme awakens
Gonna have to take another break here in a minute
There has been an awakening
I can't even prepare felt it
Like
Yeah, I need to take a second man like I couldn't hear what I was saying god
All right. Hold on. Give me one second. Let me see where we are
We got about
We have less than 200 more
That's supposed to be a small number
We got less than 200
Oh, you know guys don't worry. We got like, you know, 20 30. No, we got less than 200 left. It's all right
We're almost there
Oh
All right
I'll be right back. I got a fist every hour. We have to take a second to collect our brains
See you in like two minutes