Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as the Heavy on Badwater on Offense.
Gonna be using the default minigun, the strange shen, which that's not true.
The regular sandwich. I don't think there is a strange sandwich.
And the gloves of running urgently, as you see right here.
So this commentary is gonna be a little bit different, gonna be a little more strange, a little more weird.
You see what I did there?
I just drank like five coffees and I decided, what if I drop all my conventional wisdoms of commentary
and just hit record after having a bunch of caffeine and just let loose and see what I say and see what happens.
I'll talk about what happens on the screen, I'm gonna talk about random stuff, but you know, whatever, let's just go.
So this is gonna be called, The Coffee Commentary of Justice and Doom.
Rated R.
As you can see, this is already going off to a great start.
So what am I gonna talk about? Let's talk about of course what's going on on the screen and what am I doing here?
Well, it's Team Fortress 2 for one thing, one of my favorite games.
Okay, that really just scared the crap out of me.
I forgot that happened and that just, I felt like I was in the game.
Will you get out of my face? I'm trying to talk to my friends.
Thank you, he's gone.
But I forgot that happened and I actually couldn't believe I was still alive at this point.
A soldier comes around the corner, right here I think it is, and he starts shooting at me and I don't die.
I couldn't believe I was still alive. I was praying I wasn't gonna die because obviously I wanted to keep this run going.
And this run does go for a pretty long damn time and that is a spy, you're dead twice.
So talking about Badwater for a minute here, I want to bring up, don't get me wrong, I love Badwater.
Badwater is probably my second or third favorite map in this game.
But while you're attacking, it is the most frustrating thing if they have a good defense on the last point.
And hold on a second, I shit you, yeah, that was the noise he made.
So attacking on Badwater the last point is almost impossible if they have a good defense.
It is almost impossible and it's the most frustrating thing.
Because you'll see, once we get up to this second or last checkpoint and we start turning the corner and we start going around,
it stops to a snail's pace, like a legit slug. We are slugs when we get around this corner.
And look at how fast we've been going. We have been absolutely rolling this whole entire time.
And what stops us is a couple of level three sentries down the bottom.
And nobody can really get down there because of course it's on an incline and everyone's kind of down in the pit,
just tossing up grenades and like throwing fire bombs and firecrackers on your front lawn.
And it can be very frustrating. So I mean, I had to cut like four minutes off of this gameplay,
specifically because it was just me jumping down to my death, getting slaughtered by the sentry guns every two seconds.
And it was just failed push after failed push after failed push.
So I figured chew the fat off a little bit, get you the good stuff, get you the real milk and cookies of the gameplay,
and you get to see the ending too. So don't worry.
So now I got a less than 150 health. This is not a good position to be in. Run away from that cart.
I shoot this soldier right in his spinal cavity, right where it hurts the absolute goddamn most.
And now I want to talk about this hat. A lot of people ask me, Jermo, what the hell is that thing on your head?
Wait, is that the Eiffel Tower? What the hell is that goddamn thing?
And I will explain. I got that hat from a gift from the Kritz cast guys.
They give away, I think every week they do a show when they give away a hat.
And that's the hat they give away. It's the vintage lo-fi long wave, I think it's called.
And you can only get it if you get Player of the Week. And that sniper.
Oh, I was so mad at that guy. I was my hand buried down into my keyboard.
I was so pissed about that because I thought I could stay alive and get a full game one life, but it didn't happen.
But yeah, I got that from the Kritz cast guys. They're really cool dudes.
I may in fact be on the Kritz cast at some point. I don't know when.
I mean, we kind of went back and forth about maybe doing something, but I'm not sure.
Maybe in the future you'll see me on that podcast.
But anyways, let's return to the gameplay.
Seeing this sentry right here, I know I can outrange it because the engineer is kaput. He is dead.
And the lower right, a spy just sapped that one as well.
So right now we have like a little tea party going on in this cart now. We are going to win this.
There's no reason why we can lose. I can't think of one reason. We're going to win. We won the game, right?
You fucking sniper. We were going to win right there, man. Come on. Why'd you do that?
All right, we got over it. We're good now.
So I bump into a dead ringer spy right here. Either that or it was lag.
And I feel like that happens more often than it should.
Where you got to, what the hell did I bump into somebody? But it turns out you didn't.
But anyways, this is the end of the gameplay. We win the game right here.
Top fragging as House Targaryen.
If you watch Game of Thrones, you'll understand that reference.
It's a very good show. I could go on for hours about that show, but I'll do that a different time.
So let me know if you guys like this new style of commentary. Not going to do it every single time.
But just trying something a little different.
So I'll see you guys all soon. That wraps up the video.
And I'll catch you guys all next time.
So take care, everybody.