See, I'm here. I turned it on. I turned it on.
Yeah, we were troubleshooting. We were making sure we could get in the party,
and that we could get everything ready, and yeah. I'm here.
Hi. I'm gonna go. I'm gonna leave. I'll be right back. I forgot to make a coffee.
Everyone's just starting their streams now, or we're getting ready.
Let me go over what's happening today.
Hi. We're gonna be playing some Man vs Machine.
Team Fortress. Something I've been kind of wanting to do for a few months,
I feel like, at least six or seven weeks.
We've got a crew. This is the crew that we've been
kind of communicating for the last month or so about this.
Sans one person, but we have Dug Dug, Ludwig, Poke, Stir, and Vinny Vinesauce.
Quite the crew. And me!
Yeah, should be fun. Looking forward to it.
I have not... I tested this last night, but I've not really gone completely into
Man vs Machine in years. It's been at least five years.
So I'm excited to at least play it, fill out a party, have some fun.
Yeah, give me one second. I'm gonna be right back.
I'm gonna just make my coffee, and I'm gonna be the last one that comes back, probably.
So when everyone's making fun of me and calling me all kinds of names,
just remember I'm getting a coffee, and you can communicate that.
All right, I'll be right back.
I am back. Check on everybody else.
Is anybody here?
Forgot there's only six guests. Oh, hello!
Hey! Oh, perfect timing.
How you doing?
Good.
What's happening? How you doing?
I'm nervous.
Don't be. We'll be fine.
I've never played before.
Okay.
Hello.
Let's help Ludwig out.
Okay.
What if I'm bad, Jerma?
You won't be bad. I promise.
What if I get the team killed?
Well, that's gonna... people are gonna do that on purpose to you anyways.
What?
It's gonna be like a funny ha-ha.
Funny we got you.
I'm already stressed out. Don't do that.
That's not a funny ha-ha for me.
It's a stressful ha-ha.
Okay, so the Scout.
He's the first class.
He runs really fast.
He has Bonk Atomic Punch.
When he drinks it, he becomes invincible.
Very important to know.
The Soldier.
Can I ask you a question?
Yeah.
Without... because I don't need to know the classes.
I just want to know what you think I am.
Just, like, soak me in.
Hmm.
Interesting.
He's the first member of the DK crew.
So I would go Lanky Kong.
Okay?
Okay.
I know I'm being helpful right now, but...
People are saying Pyro.
People are saying that you're probably a Pyro.
Well, I'm a Pyro, so...
Or a Heavy.
Heavy Weapon Guy could be good.
Why are we talking about this like it's...
like astrology?
It feels like a sorting hat.
Like Harry Potter.
Like, oh, are you a Virgo?
Wait, I'm gonna do a BuzzFeed quiz.
Really?
Yeah, BuzzFeed.
What TF2 character are you?
All right, well, let's see.
Let's hear it.
Are there more than five questions on that list?
Which...
There are 14 questions.
It is quite thorough.
Yeah.
I'll link the one I'm looking at here.
Um, okay.
I'm gonna go through this.
I'll tell you what agent I get in a bit.
I kind of feel like you're kind of a spy too, though.
Don't you think?
Mission begins in 30 seconds.
The first round of a payload map is starting.
You loaded late and everyone else has picked a team.
The game is 8v8.
Which team do you choose?
These are really detailed questions.
Yeah, these are a lot of answers.
These questions are also based on TF2 gameplay.
Okay, also, I don't want to make anybody upset or anything,
but while we're hanging out, I've got a few crates to open.
I'll get off of some crates just while we're just sitting,
we're just hanging out.
We're just hanging out.
I know why you live in Vegas now.
Yeah.
Makes sense.
Yeah, it makes sense.
Okay, so I do need help while we wait for the other three to be ready.
I have a ton of cases in crates.
I opened up some before.
Should I even open these?
Or are these dog shit?
I don't know.
I have no idea what's in these.
Are these stupid?
Should I not open these?
Open them.
Yeah, but which one?
Because I know that some of the crate series are terrible, right?
83 is good.
If you guys have no idea what I'm talking about in the call,
TF2 invented the idea of opening boxes for items.
And the world has been worse ever since.
It's all their fault.
But hey, kind of fun.
Let's do it.
All right, 83.
All right, I'm going for it.
Let's go 83.
Unusual right now.
All right, I already have one of these.
We opening boxes?
Just to kill some time.
I only have a few.
Not just to kill some time.
Just fucking throwing some keys in these crates.
All right, is it weird that I want the strange flog item?
I want to open that one.
Strange flog, come on.
Oh, holy shit.
But why do you have evil villain hair?
I told you I'm trying to be as gross as possible.
I'm trying to grow my hair up like a long and just be fucking disgusting.
Just one crate.
They want me to open crates now.
I'm not.
I don't want to do not do not.
There's no don't.
It's just.
Oh, look, I mean, it's kind of cool.
I've got a lot of items, Jerma.
But a lot of this is like classic stuff or stuff people gave to me.
So I'm good.
Is that OK?
And Ludwig has literally all the stock items.
Yeah, it'll be fine.
He'll get some while we're playing.
No, that's true.
All right.
What about this one here?
This like spider one.
I'm going to open this one.
Yeah.
And I was a little I wanted to make it nice looking.
I matched it.
Chad, this is not a great little mask.
That's pretty.
Oh, OK.
That's pretty cool.
All right.
Are we am I like just wasting time?
Are we OK?
Are we like just still hanging out?
Everyone's doing an intro still, I think.
All right.
I'm just making sure that I'm not like everyone's like, what the fuck is he doing?
I thought we went to play man versus machine.
He's opening crates.
Now they're all doing their own thing.
Yeah.
Give me an unusual.
What is that?
Cabinet man is like a little game.
Do I have to buy keys now?
God damn it.
I was just going to double.
Wait, what did I get?
Oh, it's Halloween only.
OK.
Who's this for?
Engineer.
No, check.
It's going to be great.
Give me give me a minute here.
Let me buy a couple of keys.
That's actually fucking awesome.
I wish I could have this on right now, but I can't.
Are you?
Oh, yeah.
I mean, just make sure you don't do that on camera.
Oh, I know.
I know.
Yeah.
Don't don't show them how much how much you're buying.
Make it a mystery.
That's amazing.
I love it.
Yeah.
What's going on?
We're buying cases.
I just had a few left over while people were doing intros.
What's a what's a rare case that I wish I knew?
There's like there's like 200 of them at this point.
It won't let me.
I bought the keys.
It won't let me open the case.
Did you buy the right keys for the right case?
Oh, you may have not.
Oh, fuck.
You may have bought incorrect keys.
Oh, no.
I knew I knew I was going to do something wrong.
Oopsie.
Yeah, there's there's a million different keys.
Yeah, they did.
Why did they do that, by the way?
Uh, I don't know.
I wish they did.
They're like not even in my inventory with the keys.
What happened?
All right.
Whatever.
This is silly.
This is all silly business.
I have a pending item alert.
If you bought them from the market, then you would have to, like, accept the alert.
Uh, you might need to restart your game.
It's possible, you know, also possible.
I don't want to leave the party.
So, oh, Doug just went offline.
If you leave the game, you don't leave the party.
OK, I'll try.
I'll give it one shot.
Let's see if I get a good item here, because, you know, my chat is like desperate for me
to like open items now.
What the summer of September?
Yes, that's when the event is over.
Oh, I like that.
I already have this.
I already have that.
No, I don't chat.
I got the keys.
I think I hope these are the right ones.
Fuck.
They're still not the right ones.
Is this just like Twitch streamers?
They get together for a fun night of games, and then everyone just sits around and gambles
for like an hour.
Like, but not even gambling, like, appropriately.
Like, I'm failing at gambling.
And then we all go to bed at eight.
Can you imagine, like, going to Vegas, going to the blackjack table and like, sorry, you
don't have the right key.
You have to go get the Australian keys from over there.
Yeah, it's like a bunch of different currencies.
How many barriers to entry of like, I just want to give you money.
It's like, oh, cool, blackjack.
Oh, there's five open seats.
This is fucking perfect.
Oh, everybody.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Everybody got your drink.
Yeah, sit down.
Let's go.
It's like, I'm sorry, sir.
This is yen.
Oh, this is a yen.
This is a yen table.
Oh, I see that one requires a different key, even though there's five of them.
Not seat is for the summer crates.
You have to be wearing like swim trunks to sit here.
I can open this chat.
It's a man co supply crate number 43.
Dude, that's an old one that actually might be worth something.
Some of the old ones.
The reason the burning captains and stuff are worth so much is
because the crates don't drop anymore.
I got a rare germ.
I got a Berliner's bucket helm.
Oh, what do you got?
Oh, you opening crates?
This is the stream now.
Hey, it's actually.
Look, here's the thing about this, though.
Like technical difficulties.
We can just open crates until we're ready.
This is perfect.
This is actually.
Honestly, I think we should just open crates for four hours.
We just open which is great opening.
That's like fun for me, too.
Like that.
I'm fine with that.
I had the highest viewership that I've ever had last week when I opened crates,
like by far the least creative and worst stream I've ever done.
It was peak viewership for a non collab stream.
What if I watch you open crates?
Oh, that's good.
That will get I think that would do really well.
All right, what about we if we get the five of us to pour all of our audiences
into one crate opening stream?
I think that would be a victory.
And we all we all just sit around one person opening and we all just we all get a bunch
of crates like 5000 and we all just sit around just screaming every time one opens.
I know you're joking, but I would 100% pivot to that right now.
Well, I'm opening a 2013 crate right now.
This crate was from 2013 and I got the bald eagle.
I don't know what that is.
Now, chat, I can't right click the crate and get a key because I have the steam overlay
off and I have to restart the game again.
But I mean, who are we waiting for?
Is everyone still like, what are we doing?
They're doing their stream intro still.
I think Doug had some audio problems.
So we're just waiting for.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, are you good?
But I'm all good now.
Yeah.
And then what about Ludd?
Is Ludd doing all right?
Oh, Ludd was still doing the BuzzFeed quiz.
What do you think he's going to?
I think he's going to get spy.
Hello, I've gotten my role.
Oh, OK.
So is it what is it?
I am a sniper.
Oh, oh, OK.
What you guys said that like I'm gay and you're conservative.
All right.
That's good, man.
I'm proud of you no matter what you play, Ludwig.
Thank you, honey.
Just going to unlock the jar of piss or mom.
Well, I said, honey, which wouldn't make sense if I was coming out.
What is wrong with sniper?
Be real.
No, sniper is great.
Sniper is my favorite class.
It's great class.
It's tough in man versus machine because we're fighting hordes of robots and it's better at
single target, but it is useful when we're fighting big guys in this mode.
So it's not bad.
It's just like more situational, whereas Demoman is just going to rip ass the whole time, you know?
Well, what are your classes?
Are you I bet you guys got some great classes then.
I, uh, I think I have a sniper with piss and a bow and arrow.
Wait, what is that called?
It's called Sniper Sniper.
Oh, you're you're a sniper, too.
I like to play sniper.
Usually I just shoot people with a bow and arrow and I throw piss bottles at them.
I'm the scout.
Hey, welcome.
Okay.
Jerma's a scout.
What's your class poke?
I'll do whatever.
Maybe soldier, but like, you know, everyone has a class.
Is this what is your personality or what are you playing?
Because I think some people are confused.
What's what are you playing?
I guess more importantly.
Okay.
We're all playing sniper.
Wait.
Yeah, I'll play sniper.
I'll play sniper.
Is this like the scene in dead poet society?
I'm the sniper.
I'll be sniper, too.
I haven't seen that movie in a while.
I got a strange equalizer.
Is that good or bad?
It's pretty good.
Oh, you can strange a hat.
That's weird.
All right.
So here's how it's going to work.
Thanks for coming, everybody.
Thanks for having us.
It's going to be a fun time.
We're going to be playing some man versus machine.
If you never played before, it's a PVE mode.
We're not going to be playing as other players.
We're going to be working together to fight against robots.
So as we're talking about our roles and what we're going to be doing here,
I think it's probably good just to kind of get us in.
We don't have to start the round.
We can just kind of get in and you can kind of move around.
You can pick different classes and walk around, shoot the wall for all we need to.
I do want to make it very clear that we are going to be playing on...
We had a debate if we were going to do the easy missions or the really hard ones.
And we've decided we are going to be doing the hard ones.
So sorry, those of you that may not have much experience.
It's time to step up.
Yeah, step up, wussies, right?
I don't use gendered language.
But if I did, ooh, would I rip you a new one?
Just give me an unusual right now so I can put it on
and just absolutely dunk on these fucking plebs that are in the goddamn call.
Wait, girls don't have buttholes?
What? No.
Keyless immediately.
Keyless right now.
Wait.
OK, we're ready.
Hold up.
Hold on.
I'm doing it.
I'm getting there.
Hold on.
We'll do an advanced one.
And we'll just mess around and walk around and take a look at stuff.
I think I'm going to be the spy.
I changed my mind.
I told you.
I told you he was a spy.
I have a really good turtleneck for it.
Yeah, we're going to have a drip contest, too, at the very beginning.
So make sure you put on your best outfit.
All right.
We're doing advanced.
Yes?
Yes.
So we're going to be very happy or very sad about this.
Chad, I'm going to be Duncan, the big gorilla dude that shoots.
What's his name?
Winston?
Duncan?
What's his name?
You mean Winston from Overwatch?
Oh, I thought it was Duncan.
Duncan.
Yeah.
Duncan is actually meeting right now.
Like Dunstan checks in.
That's what I was thinking of.
Never mind.
I'm sorry, German.
I ruined your stream.
I'm sorry.
You come on.
He already gave us performance reviews and told me that jokes were not OK for the stream
before we started.
Well, man up, man up, man up, man up.
All right.
Everyone pull up your bootstraps.
OK, so here's how it's going to work.
What's going to happen is we're going to get into this into this game and we're going to
be playing game for you.
I find it hilarious that you guys are taking advice on TF2 from Jerma.
So let's take it from you then.
Yeah.
I would.
Lead me then.
No.
Yeah.
Poke.
Fuck this guy.
You know what I mean?
This game's for children.
You'll figure it out.
Hey, Vinny.
Put your shoes on.
Pull them up.
Pull up the shoes.
Am I crazy to say it's the opposite of for children?
Oh, my God.
Vinny, don't listen.
Watch this movie or no?
I'm not listening to anyone.
I'm listening to my heart.
Vinny, don't listen to Sturr.
Fuck this guy.
Ludwig, don't listen to him.
He thinks he knows TF2.
I made the TF2 class tutorials back in the day.
Not him.
Yeah, we'll see about that.
I mean, I was playing Team Fortress Classic back in the day.
So I was I was how I spent most of my high school years.
Just saying a little different.
Spamming grenades.
But I was doing it was making it happen.
OK, so what do we actually want to play as?
Because we I'll do whatever.
I know we're all playing sniper.
Shit.
All going to do sniper.
We actually do have three snipers, don't we?
This is not a random pub.
We're supposed to be strategizing.
I'll go heavy.
How would you if you wanted to change the class?
Change it.
OK, you would press the comma button and that brings a sniper.
No, this is my role.
I'm actually never allied.
Are we all going to be sniper?
Can we just do it and just laugh for a minute and then go back?
Look, I did a 30 question quiz.
It'd be crazy to not follow up on it.
Yeah, that's true.
Let me change.
I don't have the piss.
Oh, here it is.
Oh, if you want to change your loadout, it is M.
I should make my sniper look cool.
We have three snipers on the squad.
Oh, yeah, that's what we were doing.
I think we were doing a little a little goofiness.
We're getting goofy.
All right.
So members, let's I know I'm explaining Andy.
But listen, there is a counter over here.
You have money.
We collect money each wave.
We get a certain amount of money.
You use that money to upgrade your character.
Be careful because everything you do is permanent.
It is not.
Actually, that was a lie.
You can refund all your upgrades in the bottom left.
I just I forgot.
OK, so you can refund your upgrades.
But these are important.
And everything in your inventory can be upgraded.
Including your heads only.
I'm not worried about all this explanation.
It's just lights out for me.
Honestly, I like that straight line and you're going to shoot them.
We're playing machine.
This is 20 year old AI.
They can't be that good.
You know, I like that.
I like that.
I actually like that confidence.
So we do.
We're doing five snipers, huh?
I guess that's what we're doing.
Can someone build a dispenser?
We can't.
No, no, no, no.
On sniper, build a dispenser.
Someone in my chat said kick the heavy.
Well, actually, no poke you.
We could have one heavy that would that would be actually perfect.
We can do five medics and one heavy and just see what does.
You want to just all just just heal poke.
That's kind of fun.
I'll do it.
We have no scout either.
All right, let's look.
OK, let's get out there.
Do your upgrades.
Put me in, coach.
Put me in.
And look at the top.
That is the classes that are coming out there.
Scout.
It's a fast class.
The first class in the slot.
Number one can move pretty quickly.
Has bonk atomic punch.
I find it strange that people standing in spawn have toggled ready.
Start my countdown timer.
Wait, so should I be sniper?
What's wrong with spawn?
I'm a sniper.
We have to be out there.
There's a wave of it.
I'm the only person out here.
I'm the only person here.
I'll be out here in the front there.
All the bots are coming from one place.
They come from one direction.
They see the track.
See these little these little dollops on the ground.
This is the path that they take.
How do you use the canteen?
The second class.
Didn't you guys study for this?
He has four rockets, but that's not always the case because he might have a couple of
rocket launchers that have different amounts of ammunition, different amounts of rockets
quantities.
Chat, I give it.
I give it like 10 seconds before we lose the round and have to reset.
No, no, no, no, no.
I got a bow and arrow.
We're already got an amazing shot.
We're fine.
Taking all the money, man.
You're not sharing at all.
Wait, does it split?
Does it split it?
Oh, sorry.
We'll talk later.
My chest hurts.
You take it all the fucking money.
I can't see.
I can't see through us because we're all snipers.
They've been pissed.
Why did I pick the classic?
This is like the worst item for man versus machine.
Not having a teleporter is awful, by the way.
Yeah, well, maybe you should have played engineer.
Oh, I definitely would not recommend bow and arrow for this mode.
Game mode.
Hell no.
Hey, they shoot back.
Yep.
They do shoot back.
Certainly can.
They do exist.
Somebody build.
Guys, they're getting real close to our base and whatnot.
It's okay.
I got arrows, a barrage of arrows and back in here.
Oh, they're behind us.
Oh, you ammo.
Ammo?
Yeah, we don't have any ammo.
Where's our engineer?
I think we're going to be all right.
I am shocked we've lived this long.
I'm going to be honest.
Oh, poke doing work.
I saw that.
By the way, if they get the bomb in, we lose.
What happens if you die?
Oh, that's what happens.
You come back, but yeah, it's a cool down.
Yeah, he's getting the bomb.
Oh, Lord.
Did we survive?
Yeah.
All right, let's let's wait with this.
$14 we're missing.
If we don't get all the money, we don't get a bonus.
All right.
Are we playing on like baby easy mode?
There's more.
There's there's soldiers.
It's wave one out of seven.
Oh, boogers just flew out of that's going to be somebody's going to get a clip of that.
Boogers just flew out of my nose.
They're at the bomb.
They went down the left.
They're at that thing.
We're losing wave.
I'm coming.
We're going to lose.
We lost.
Sorry.
No, we didn't.
We're good.
Not yet, germ.
Not yet, buddy.
I'm shooting as many as I can.
Get the scout.
Get scout.
Okay.
Not yet, buddy.
We lost $14 and I am fucking mad about it.
Clutch or kick.
We're not going to get the achievement.
I know.
Oh, we need an explosive headshot.
That sounds good.
Yeah, 100% get that.
I need to be able to hit a headshot because I don't think it's happened once.
It is one.
How is that not a headshot?
Oh, I died.
Oh, no.
Bunch of heavies incoming.
Shoot them.
What the heck?
I'm shooting them.
I don't shoot fast enough is the problem.
That's right.
It has to be fully charged.
This is the worst weapon in the game.
How the hell did we survive?
Good job, everybody.
We did it.
You got an A on your first test.
Rage against the machine.
That's a good one.
Not bad.
I get it.
Now's the fun part.
Can you change classes midway through or no?
Yes, you can.
We want to like take this seriously now or are we good to just
snipe?
Um, I'm taking it pretty serious.
Are we taking it serious now?
Oh, I don't tell y'all I've been sweating.
Yeah, let's take it seriously.
If we're going to take it seriously, then we need somebody needs to be engineer.
I could be medic.
Medic works for me.
I really I'm not sure I'm good with a lot of classes anymore.
Make sure you refund.
Are we actually swapping now?
Yeah, refund before you swap, though.
Refund before you swap.
You get the money.
Vinny, stay sniper.
You're a good sniper.
If there's double sniper, I won't be a sniper.
Someone said someone said there you can charge a sniper.
What does that mean?
OK, so the more damage it does.
Really?
Yeah.
Like Widowmaker.
Just like Widowmaker.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
I mean, I was a Widowmaker main, so it should be not.
Yeah, you played Overwatch.
Then, you know, every single thing that's in this game, you know, everything about this
game.
Oh, great.
All right, Chris Krieg.
I think Chris Krieg is probably the one.
Um, what do you prefer?
Sniper if you want.
I could swap off.
You know, I can do spy if you prefer some.
I'm good with Demoman.
OK, you guys, I mean, all jokes aside, just play whatever you want.
Yeah.
Rotate out as well.
The hell is going on?
Wait, what is that?
Who did that?
Is it weird?
OK, come on.
Was that was that real?
He switched off sniper.
Oh, yeah, elbow kick.
No, no, no.
I actually will get booted from the game.
Don't do that.
This will like ruin everything.
Well, then you should have done it.
Don't do that.
All right.
Who who wants the crits?
And if you want to know what the crits are, the me.
Go stock sniper with explosive headshots.
The seventh class in the game is the medic.
That's what I am doing.
Is that dumb?
No, that's good.
That's good.
That's what my chat saying.
That's a good thing.
All right.
I'm not doing it to you.
Oh, all right.
Vinny.
All right.
We're all on the roof on the roof.
I'm up here.
Yeah, look at Jerma stream.
He got the slick back here.
Looking like he's trying to.
I mean, are we a drip contest or no?
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, we'll do drip contest after this.
All right.
Tank is in this very where we're doing it right now.
Stock grenade launcher is better.
Use Scottish resistance.
Oh, man, I'm getting so many suggestions.
All right.
When you're ready, just unload on that thing.
I'm going to give you crits.
Now I missed all.
I forgot this even existed.
Guys, my gun is really loud.
I forgot.
Turn it down.
Ding.
I'm getting it.
Watch out.
By the way, there are spies now.
So if you see somebody that looks like you, it's not you.
If you see something, say something.
Is that not me?
That's not you.
I thought that was me.
Okay, I'm going to shoot the bomb.
You guys keep shooting the car.
Yeah, we're not.
It's priority is the car to be shot.
Drop this right here.
Not me.
Oh, by the way, if you need health, press E so I can see.
Oh, that is a lot of soldiers.
I got you.
They can't be headshot.
I'm in trouble.
I'll stay on the tank.
Me and poke should be able to get a tank if I do it.
All right, I'll try to take the soldiers with the century.
Where's the ammo?
Oh, it's down here.
There's a spice.
Yes, it's over.
It's to the right, basically the right pathway.
I'm not liking where this tank is at fellas.
Tank is almost there.
I will move my century towards it.
It's going to run me over.
Oh, yeah, it can run you over.
It actually can kill you instantly.
Guys, it's getting close.
It's mine.
It's the tank, guys, it's the tank, it's the tank.
It's in my century.
The tank.
It's got to get in.
All eyes on tank, all DPS, all DPS on tank, all DPS.
I'm trying.
I can't do it fast enough, buddy.
I can't do it fast enough.
We actually might be able to do it.
We can do it.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Bomb, bomb, bomb, bomb.
Oh, we're dead.
It's over.
No, no, we can do this.
Gang, we thought we saved it for a minute.
Okay, we're good.
All right, I gotta stop saying it's over.
I'm died.
I'm coming to come, we're good.
You can press H to respawn instantly.
It costs money, but I can revive you.
I can revive you if I get you.
No, I missed the shot.
Oh, sorry, it's okay.
All right, we needed more snipers.
I don't know.
Yeah, we needed more snipers.
It was way easier when we were all sniper
Who's restarting what's going on?
Wait, are we not returning? We are right? No, no, no, we know we're good
We just get essentially we just go back to where we were at the beginning of that round
It's not like oh we lost we got a rekey. Yeah, you get your money back and you get to try again
Just pick pyro
Special key I'm switching I'm not sniper dude. I'm a spy
I might go pyro should I just go flog pyro? Just say who cares?
I mean, I mean what pyro would wreck the tank Vinny. Do you have the log?
Let me check because I can always switch out of pyro. I don't have the flog
You want why don't you do pyro and I'll I'll do I'll continue with demo but with better weapon, okay
Yeah, I'll let me let me refund and I'll go what should I use for my upgrades as a spy?
Mm-hmm. So you're a Scottish resistance and pin the sapper is incredible in man vs machine because the sapper
Disables the robots when you have enough upgrades in it
You can do a huge AOE and turn they go
And they power down for like five to ten straight seconds a huge group of them. So it's really really good
Why'd you want me to put the pan on chat? It's just a power copy
Blood blood, you know, I'll backstab work in the game you stab in the back and they die instantly
Yeah, yeah, so if you can get behind him, then that will do a lot
I'll just increase my jump height and then I'll be able to jump over them. This is really fun
I actually like this a lot. I do have a big problem though
Unfortunately, I might not be able to play flog because I'm not high
I'll have to take a five-minute break
All damage
We lose this I'm out. Oh, we don't wait. How do I use sappers and cloaks?
Okay, so right click to cloak sapper. You have to pull it out and then you just left click to put it on a thing
Like any trick your sniper still has four to pull out the sapper or two
Yeah, this is I spy. I'm Pat. This is fun. I like this a lot
Did this require a coupon I'm a spy right now it requires it requires one $1 coupon there
Also, I was reminded queuing for us. There's a squad surplus where you'd like one ticket pays for everybody. Oh shit
We probably should have done wait. No squad surplus. All that does it just makes us we get more items in the end
Oh, nevermind. Yeah, everybody has to still buy it. I mean everyone ready at four. Oh, yeah. Sorry, but this time
I'm ready to rock and roll flog pyro. Oh
Passer this thing is amazing in members machine, by the way
This guy's been looking up the strats. No, I I've we've been talking about playing this like two months
Wait, really?
Prepared a little bit better. The knife does not work on the tank heads up
So you can shoot with your gun because there's no guys coming yet
Where's the I get a better headshot sound cuz my
I
Got one of me going spin. Oh, that's the one most. No, I'll get that to you. I'll send you that wave. Don't worry
I need a minute
I'm gonna get face down
Did you get spied by a spy as a spy? Yes, I did. I
Didn't know that was a thing. Oh, we're doing way better now with this composition. This is really way
You do
Yes proximity does matter
right
Going in for the kill the bombs going, right?
All right. I need help with the tank
Yeah, I bet you do
Yeah, I do. That's why I said it my century. I'll get it. You guys can go back to the robots
Oh, nice. Nice. Nice. That's right. Trying to I'm gonna get the
bomb carriers I
Died Oh
Alright bombs over here. Oh, there's a lot of money on the ground. We got to get this. Oh
They got me
I'm collecting money. I'm like money's I'm trying to I'm trying oh
We got lots of snipers and spies by spawn shit, I try to jump over it. Oh, never mind. They're dead
I think we're watch out for spies spies me spies me poke. Watch out turn on
That's a spy
Save the century how about it? We're gonna we're okay. We're doing fine. We're doing good. Not bad and chat
I have not played much man versus man. This is like man versus machine. What are we doing Ludwig? Do you know you can disguise?
You can so they don't shoot you when you're disguised. You don't have to be invisible. I love
They don't I don't I can't hit them when I'm disguised
Yeah, but they won't shoot you and you could just walk up to him and sap him. Hey, we're good
Oh, you sap you can sap on visible. Yeah. No, I'll disguise. That's what I meant. Wait. Yes
What's the difference between disguise and invisible?
Invisible is they can't no one can see but it's basically in man versus machine disguise is better than being invisible
You want some here you want coffee you want a sip which would be pressing for I think yeah, I think I'll
Get more penetration
It's what we're all trying to do in life, isn't it? That's right. All right. Now this thing is powered up gonna be awesome
All right. So we have if it's you see the red background that means that it is guaranteed crits every single shot
And it's the infinite symbol means that they have infinite ammo and they just BAM and there's a hundred and twenty-eight scouts
We're fucked just shoot them. Wait chat. Should I do all sticky upgrades? What do you guys think in here?
Sticky bomb is good for a demo for this mode sticky
It's been a long time, but you can have a ton of stickies out right if you are good for slow targets
Yeah, it just does so much damage versus tanks
If you have a tank is coming out and you get crits you get a crits canteen and you just put out an entire
Just magazine of learning know what it's called. Whatever people gonna make fun of me
You put you just do the whole clip out and you'll do
Thousands of damage to the tank. Okay. Yeah, I'm gonna try that. I see what that's like find a button for a canteen
What is what does the canteen do?
So the canteen at the last tab in the shop allows you to buy personal little power-ups for yourself
One of them is invincibility, which is uber charge. So you become invincible for five seconds
The other one is crits, which is obviously you get it times three damage. Where is that? How much it is?
I don't know
Really doesn't care
Technical with it. I don't give a shit about it. Crikey fucking losers in my chat correcting me
You guys are doing a really good job here. I'm just waiting to come in
Get closer and then I'll detonate. Oh
What it's a germa ADHD special interest stream
Wasn't visible I thought I'd play that well
Like a hitbox like a lobbyist big paying me to do this. What does that even mean?
All right, we have a lot of money we need to get big TF2
They're they're moving on the left the bomb. I got it
No, not your my left. I got him. I got my left your left. I just took care. Are they dead?
Yeah, I took care of it. He's making a bomb down over here
Freaking out with my sentry here. I big soldier big soldier
Nice, I'm trying not to whip the stickies chat
which is a really specific and weird sentence, but
You get it
I just taunted
Whoa, oh centers down
What is
It was a very my thing is so loud my head shots elected. Oh, yeah
You're uh, guys you can change the hit songs the bomb is at the thing lower the bomb is that thing I'm whiffing chat
I'm whiffing
Okay, it's good. Oh shit bomb. Is that the thing?
I'll drop the center over there
Sorry, we're good. We're okay. We got we got further that time. I don't even want to see that from your point of view
I let him go by me. I
Gross I'm so sorry. I don't want to be around anymore. No, it's all right. We're doing fine. This is advanced
This is not this is hard. You guys are doing great
Yes, I'm switching. I'm not the spy anymore. Make sure you refund if you refund you get all the money back
Yeah, but make you have to do it before you switch classes
Then he did it before right? You did it after you'd be screwed her
I you might have to just go back and yeah, you just swap back and then you go to the thing and refund
I will be
Who's this dude, honestly soldier gun soldier heavy
I'm what I'm older. I mean, they just they just do so much pot. They have so much power. This guy seems cool
Demo, man. Oh, it's someone already demo man. Yeah, we have one
I'm gonna try the more than one demo. I can be we have that poke is that hey engineer soldier
You go you go heavy
Load, you might like it. You want less reload speed? Hey engineer. Come over here. I really should stay on medic
Where or a scout? No, this is where I should set up over here entry goes here. Okay, I'll do it
I learned my lesson a long time ago. Never believe ha ha ha ha. Oh, they're talking about channel points
I get it gotta move that gear up
Ideally at the corner wait like here. Yeah, so that you can hide behind the wall and still repair it
Oh, I thought I would get hit from here
But yeah, I guess you're right or at this corner
So you have to still have the dispenser in the ammo we could always just do six engineers and say who cares and just go
That'd be kind of fun. Do you know what I care ready up? Are we good to go? Yeah. Oh
Yeah, almost I'm putting on these things Chad. Do not question my sticky placement. It's great
So the question minigun, oh cool. I couldn't overwatch just do this
Well, they don't get an overwatch. Yeah, why couldn't they have Duncan do this in overwatch?
Duncan Idaho, I don't feel like I'm hitting them. Oh right when they land they're invincible for like a half a second
Damn, this pyro fronts doing really well
Yep, pick up that money. I'm trying to drop left
Big soldier got me
There you go big soldiers getting destroyed nice
Nice, that was way cleaner than last time
There's a lot of my century in an actual good spot is probably helping him
What do you while I'm not down there? Can one of you go grab that money work goes away?
Yeah, you don't get the money if you don't pick it up and it go it disappears the money for upgrading. I got it
Century buster, where's it at Jesus? Yeah, so a scout actually is the money collector
Gaming a bomb approaching on a scout hook. I got a great view of that, by the way
You saw that? Yeah
Yeah, I'm not gonna know the meta like I'm doing my best but like it's gonna take a while to learn meta
I'm just gonna listen to Jerma
Well, listen to me for don't I just got killed from behind by a sniper bitch killed me
All right
Where are you at big rounds?
It was a 30 kill round for me. Is that like not bad? That's pretty desperate damn good
I'm still going. Yeah, we go bomb is here. Guess. Don't get too cocky. Yeah, I
See how it works. No, if you see money grab it
Shit. Hey, why didn't overwatch do this? This is crazy. Listen
Isn't this like the most fun you've ever had in a video game? Like how come why didn't they just do this?
Oh, I have never been happier
Okay, I got some stickies by the bomb here snipers
Take on the tower defense games
Not one of you okay, I was gonna say overwatch has the
The workshop which allows you to adjust all the attack speed and everything like they could
Up in MBO. I hear where
Now they're gone, but yeah, we need to keep an eye on I'll be back here to keep an eye on the bomb
We're good. We're good. We're good one scout going right one scout. There's literally one scout
I'm not fast enough to get him. He's at the bottom right now. Nice and
That is a successful wave completed. Yeah
Our scout should be picking that up
Hey, it's a bit of a scout. Oh
All right chat. Let's see. What am I upgrading here now that I have all my damage up?
This is where I really shine as a vlog pyro find canteens. Okay, I will but
Wait, I lost upgrades of you switch guns. Oh
Yes, you because you all the upgrade is there's so many different weapons in the game it's individual to each item Oh
Burn damage sucks, dude. What really? What do you mean burn damage is useless here? Why I understand
Wait had the wrong one to mine. It's it's already H. Okay, like H Judd Benjamin. It's only after burn. Oh
Okay, I thought it was all right. That makes sense. Yep. Yep. That's true
Resistances in the character menu Oh fire and create and all that stuff. Okay, dude, this germans. This is your fourth tour. Is it nice?
Yeah, apparently you're a little bit of a pro health on kill is important. Yeah, so I need crit resistance for this wave
It's good to have anyways
For this wave no, but not for this particular wave eyes this wave don't get backstabbed. Yes. All right
I'm good. Put it into jump height. Why would you ever put it into jump height? What is that? What would that do?
Someone said Vinnie. I thought you were a pan lover zero upgrades sad face
People do some goofy shit in members machine. It's like oh, yeah
I'm gonna put on a like the fish and fully upgraded and then do jump height and movement speed
It's like okay. Well, we're gonna lose but you're gonna have a good time. Yeah, pretty much
Alright, where should I post up as a machine gun enthusiast?
So it's distance matter with me is good because then you're near the dispenser. Yeah, so you see
Up here. Oh where you guys are. Yes. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, cuz I coming the box like the refrigerator next to me will heal you if you stand near it
I'll get this money in a second. I've made sure I took the most fall damage possible. That's good. Good job. Excellent
Mark, Jeremy, I'm really happy with your performance
Whoa, I see I should have stood closer to the refrigerator. We're good
Spies are here. If you think I can somebody it might be somebody else. Yeah, we need that money
I'm gonna get some of it. There's a lot still there
Vinnie you blew yourself
All right, and you're surprised by that watch out for the sentry buster coming up the stairs right now. Okay, how'd you bust her on the stairs?
I'm trying to kill it. Okay, we're good
Huge Scout big very big Scout
Wait, how far is no they made him that big is he dead? I don't do another
Such a buzzer on the stairs
Okay, that's fine. I gotta get this fucking money
They got snipers
To the streets. Let's go. Oh my god. He's going to get weak. He's going the bomb real fast. No
We got a problem on the left side
Oh
All right, we need that money we got oh we got the money we're good. Oh, we're good. All those were spies. Okay
I'm I took buster took out the spies. I'm not moving
What bunch people ran by me? You gotta move. I'm holding up the front you guys can keep the back alive
That's a lot of money sentry buster coming in. I don't know from where oh shit scouts a scout
You don't know where from where Jerma I don't I got distracted a scout was right here
I'm real. I'm real. I'm real same place. Oh god
If I wasn't looking
And they always go to the century
Just stop
Shining a microscope onto how stupid I am
Free to be honest that way
Alright
Where's our scout at I want to yell at them it could be me. I'm supposed to be getting the money
I got it. Yeah soldiers Opie. So do you guys think that owning a microscope is a really terrible idea?
I want to get in real life
Yeah in real life like buying a microscope and again, and I'll give you the thesis here. How much is the microscope?
I got a hundred bucks like guys. No idea. That's great. Yeah, like ten bucks. What doesn't matter like it's not about how much it costs
It's about what you would do when you had it and what I'm talking about here is I'm talking about I would get I would
Put a drop of water on that look at it from my sink or something and be like I'm never drinking water from here ever
Again, oh, yeah. Well, I just realize a microscope is different than a telescope
It's the opposite. Yeah
There's actually this thing that went around recently like an article about how New York City
Water fountains have like little shrimps in them. So like when you're drinking out of a water fountain
There's like microscopic shrimps in water and I live in New York City. I will never touch that again unless I need protein
I'm it's flavor right? You don't like free flavoring. It is free flavor. It's like drinking sea monkeys
Without having to pay though. It's free sea monkeys free sea monkeys
There you go this economy. You're gonna give that up. Yeah
The same roof it can be but it's a tank again. So we're gonna need to be forward
Copy you need big damage this round in position feeling good ready for a battle
We ready to battle
Want to be over here cuz they can heal off the refrigerator, but no, thank you, sir. All right
Be careful fall damage does hurt. Hey, whoa
Are you telling us cuz you've learned from experience or you just know about it?
I'm just telling you because I've taken 20% of my health off every round because I just keep jumping off of the roof
It's a disaster. I don't know if you know this sometimes you're close to push me off. Oh, here we go. Okay, I'm activating my crits
All right, let's go for it. We can melt this thing quick
Well, that wasn't quick crit canteen. Yeah
Okay, we are fucking all right stop on the way
that was perfect placement of
You know, I bet our heavies the medics can't move her. Yeah, I this is I can't
Scout I got it. I got it. I'm going to go. I got him. I'm going to going
All right. I got it. All I got it all. We're good. Watch me kill this heavy in fucking 10 seconds
Dude look at that. So good. You guys got the tank, right? Yep. Thank you. I got this guy tank
Tank down good shit. Good shit. Wow a little bit money left
Yeah, sentry buster coming up. Yep. Yep. Yep. Those things are so fucking loud. Oh
Where is he? Oh
Big heavy right around the corner. Oh
Doing a lot of
Shit. All right. He's over. He's over folks on the tank. I
Was trying to kill the medics break they could do it. Yeah focus the medics always because they will uber I
I accidentally made them uber. All right, we got to focus on the tank too. I'm gonna move that gear up
That's a good idea. I
Should get his tank
Or I will move that gear directly into a bunch pyro. Yeah tank is a tank should be fine. I think we're good
Where's the bottom graphic
Hi, that's a good point. What is the bottom graphic beam? I think the health of a certain the heavies walking the bomb back
He's been walking the bomb back. I focus on heavy. He's he's around the right tank is down. Oh
God, he's right there. Nice. That was good
We didn't collect a lot of money though that we're about to get it. We're about to see a big bump. Nice
huge bomb
I mean you give me a tank and I and I say how high
Does this run also have tanks it does and it also has permacrit soldiers
So this is the time to buy that crit resistance crit resistance purchased
Is this a blast resistant group a fire group?
This would be a blast resistant group as well as a bullet resistant group. Let me go. Let me do this
Let me do this. Ooh
There are no there are no tanks this round there are only
Myself a tank drama to be honest
That's like you got a notification. I think I find piss
This is the final round or penultimate. I
Think this is wave what wave?
Way the seven waves in this one. This feels penultimate, but my math has never been good. It's got a penultimate vibe to it
Let's get it. How we feel how we feel feel good. I'm feeling
Good yeah, I'm feeling good dog dog sentry turret. Can your turret shoot me dog dog dog? Oh god, damn it
I just haunted and I had to I was trying to rock paper scissors you and I just ruined everything
All right. I didn't mean like as a request more so concerned
But good to know that's a teaching moment
All right, I'm ready
All right, you know I missed don't ever say crank in that sticky launchers hog ever again chat member supposed to be me
Me doing that. Oh
Nice dog. I
Love engineer on my MVM stuff on
Trolling all right big a soldier a big one
Check this out. Yeah, I'll take
Ignore medic request money money money. I
Heavy moves fast the sniper got there. Who are those beans Wow
Hmm these beans right?
What's G do? What does G? Why would you tell me to press G? Oh, geez taunt?
My freaking gun for a half hour
All right. I got the money. Yeah
Let's get back into position. I'm starting to think that they're noobs. All right heavy's coming in Oh
Ridge gives you mini crits
Sniper on the on the side there. Yeah, we got a problem coming on the left side. Oh
Oh
Whoa medic went flying. Why is this guy invincible because the medics are ubering him
Yeah, there's always money. I'm target. I'm dead right now
He'll medic medic. I'm dead. Wait, so you're all that three hours earlier. I was right there. Okay, I'm going for this money round
Nice got such a buster
Fucking hell big heavy big heavy waste this other money that I didn't get coming in hot
century buster
Buster coming up. Oh
Shit, it's my pervert our huge huge
Soldier with medics. Oh, I'm gonna try to kill medics. Yeah left side soldier
They all over oh my god
Yeah, I got yeeted
Up until then it's going pretty good. We're doing it's going great. I think we're champions
Century buster and then that's it
Big heavy
All right, so you guys are coming up. Yep. I'm gonna lose this war
I think it's just this big heavy big heavy has the bomb and it's coming up like the left side said press Emma
Chat bomb is down. They said M for medic
It's a good guess oh
Come on. I got it. I got him. I got him. Good. All right, just the
Soldier and that's it. I think there's like a few dollars and hanging out somewhere. Yeah
There's 50 bucks, there we go 24 what I mean who even needs money anymore
Yeah, we I need the better you die here jump speed. So this is this is this is it? This is the big one
three tanks
Tanks, so just all right
So us just to let everybody know that hasn't not really played MVM
The scout is the money collector class and it's usually required somebody is almost required to do it
You get healed when you pick the money up as a scout
He also has like a big radius around him that picks it up for free, but we're at the last round
I don't we're doing just fine
What should I get as an upgrade for the last round any any resistances like crit resistance?
Maybe there's one big crit soldier. The rest are all just big
I think our biggest problem is gonna be the tanks. I agree. This is a lot of last and bullet damage
I'm just gonna go resistance. I'm just gonna just max myself out. Are you having a smashing good time?
I am actually I'm actually
Usually aren't so let me get a play a seven days a die. I
Played oh, I played a lot of that one should do this question. They got a huge update question
What should I avoid here? Should I like avoid?
Penetration or should I get some resistances?
Resistance is a big deal now
Because these are all pretty much everything we're fighting is big. So they'll kill you in two seconds
You can never go wrong with move speed and jump speed move speed. Oh, yes, we're actually insanely important
I don't have any of it though. Are there crits in this one? There is one
Giant crit soldier. So yeah, we should be able to get rid of it pretty quickly though
Okay
What about fire resistance?
no pyros, so fire is
not necessary
The only thing that we have is bullet and blast and crit use crits before shooting stickies got it
Thanks chat also to after we do this
Everyone's gonna the reason why you use that that for duty ticket is because we're all gonna get an item after this and it could
Be something cool
If anyone gets an Australian those sell for like one hundred thousand dollars
What's an Australian it's like it like a human weapon. No, not an Australian. It's really young. It's an Australian. Oh
All right. I'm ready like a person. Yeah, I got a question like an actual person find the Australian. Oh
All right. What do we got first?
Probably tank. What does that mean?
I'm big Scout
I'm gonna slow them. I'm gonna slow these scouts. I didn't do it
Oh my god, oh my god, he's they don't seem very slow. He's gonna go all the way. Oh, he's going literally all the way
This one's on me. He's going to go all the ways. He's going for speed. Oh
He's going all the way, isn't he? Oops. Oh
Save whoa, holy shit. That's what another one. That was my bad
Wait, so it's not over. No, we're good. Yeah, we're okay. Oh, I just died for some reason. That's fine
I didn't I need it to get me right on somebody should probably hang back in the kind of area
Do you what do you think as a demo? Should I hang back or yeah, I need it against the tank
Cover that thing with stickies your bitch bomb for the bomb. All right
Big heavy on the right side. He's like pretty low though. He should be dead
Why'd you walk in a straight line at the heavy
Yeah, that's a big gun heavy dead heavy dead giant charge shoulder walking over three three three homies
Oh boy
Out of that tank
Did you forget what I was playing oh, I don't know I thought I guess it just takes over your brain
Don't kill me, please
Good. Oh
Now the tank coming up. No, I reckon I can melt this. I don't know what to do chat
I'm confused. Oh shit. Oh god, I
Get you up. I don't know how to
Scout's going left side
All right. Yeah, I have a single scout makes it past. We're in trouble
All right, it's okay. One's okay now on it speaking which nice
Actually help. Oh, please don't kill me
Nice. Okay, we're okay. I
Was the back right now?
I'm keeping an eye on the on the back with bombs right now. I can't help with the tank though
I got a century, but there's like four scouts going on the point. Let's shoot
Century back here should come to the point. I belong on this character. It's just cuz the shoes alone
As a reminder, you can press H when you die to respawn instantly. Oh
Yeah for this round that sounds like a good idea. Oh, yeah, there's no
Okay, tank tank is coming. We gotta kill that tank like now
What happened? There's a hole by the way heads up
There sure is there yeah, there is a hole that's right. I
Completely forgot about the one health
soldier on the right
He's gonna stick on the tank with
All right. What's down? I'm down. I'm down
I'm gonna respond immediately, but we got a problem with that bomb. That bomb is scaring me. I'll get the bomb
I got the bomb. Don't worry about the bomb focus on
Tank is down. Thank you. Thank is down. Okay down soldier on the coming up the other side. Excellent work
Loony tunes right there by crit canteens. We can't hear in there
Good. Okay. Okay. We got a second here where we can kind of relax. Yeah, we
Snipers got this we got this. Oh
Watch it with a sniper scout. Nice. All right, huge soldier coming in with a bunch of scouts. He's very hurt
What side right or left? Uh, they come in the right butts. Oh, right. Yeah, it's weird
Teleporter that's not good. Whoa, what happened? What fuck what happened? Just one get through
It's the moment chat you could it was like a continue or vote restart no, we're good. Okay continue continue
Yeah, just go restart resets from round one. Oh, okay
Cat you saw that could upgrade your character. You heard the trigger. Wait, how do you upgrade a character?
Wait, click your character icon you get movement speed and stuff. Yeah
Bullet resides a very important
Is there a lot of blasts in this one
This is very heavy on
blast a lot of
Infinite soldiers a big crit soldier, although there are a lot of bullet scouts
So we would that we did fine that time. I think we were good
I think once the bomb gets that close
I'll just leave the level three back there and then and then you guys hold forward
Yep, I had that alert was on screen for like a second and then I yeah, it was just too much too
It was too close
Then you would have won if you use the frying pan. I get drunk back rage. That's the one
Um knock back is really good. It's it's actually insanely powerful especially versus century busters
Because you can just hold the
Just track them and they'll fly across the map
And that's very helpful for me because then I don't have to move my century around
I know a lot of people right now are gonna say hey, don't listen to Jerma. That's a terrible strategy, but hey
They instantly said knock back halves your damage. He's so dumb. Don't get it. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Yeah
They're really upset at you. Why are robots attacking the Old West ghost town? Are we in it?
We're in it, we're in it to win it let's go I want to hear at least some enthusiasm from us. Okay, buddy. Yeah
Enthusiasm on three one. Oh, yeah, two three. Yeah
It's going all the way again
You're gonna go the distance is going for speed I am so hurt right now I was too busy doing a stupid fucking voice. Oh
What oh, oh boy, okay. All right
Oh God, I did not want to drop down. Oh
Okay, left ubers left heavies ubered. I don't even know what to do about that right now chat. Oh, that was my fault
I was supposed to kill the medics. That's my fault
All right, what have he's done? We just need left one. This is a huge pyro. Oh god
Sorry, no over
Someone keeps making them pop uber
Back to a back to square one. Oh shit. Okay. There come the tanks
I'm just getting bullied. Oh
I have a lot of
I'm gonna go focus on the soldier is pretty low, but I'm gonna focus on the tank in the money
Century buster is right here careful careful. I can focus tank
Give us all crits. I think bunch of people coming up. Oh, what?
We're good, I can I can handle the scout guy this time
I'm ready. I can slow him. I can knock him back at the start to I should do that
I can also just leave my level three at the spawn for the start. That might just be the best
Yeah, this is a lot of scouts. It's just a ton of yeah
It's that beginning segment is a nightmare. I
Doubters are winning. Yeah, we'll get it. Are they? Okay. Are the initial scouts running down the left or right path switch, right?
Um for faster damage in a pinch use your grenades. My grenades are weak
If they haven't been upgraded by this point, they're not as good as this. Yeah
So what's that firing speed is glitched. You say you can't do a pass one. Is that true? Is this fake news?
I don't know that might be fair. Is that real? Mm-hmm chat. Is that real true? It's true
It's actually true only the second only the second tier is glitched
So if you do three, it'll fix it. Here's three and beyond are fine apparently, so you'd have to do with two points in it
What's the sticky it's 14 stickies at a time, I mean we could try all sniper here if it doesn't work
Well, yeah, that'll that'll definitely work. Yeah, we will find a way to beat this
I could also go scout or medic and we're totally fine. I mean, I don't know
I could also go scout or medic and we're totally fine. Everything we did was good
Let's ready up and we'll just kill the scouts. Amen. Amen. I agree
Why do you want is your Torian Lord hair and that person for at least a month? Oh
Shucks frankly, you almost had it the first time we just yeah, we were really close like we could have done that
That was that rage Luke. I think right-click. It's this whatever the special
Right better middle mouse, it's possible that it's not bound you might have to find it
Let's do it, let's do it. All right. All right. This one's for real. I miss every hit
Okay, I wish I had put my sentry closer
Great start great killer smart better
Don't shoot him. Don't shoot him. No shoot him. I got the thing on the medic
That's what I was supposed to do last time and I failed miserably that's that's sniper job because I could just kill all
The medics with one shot. Oh money doesn't matter anymore, by the way. So well, it does
What this guy just destroyed capitalism with one comment
Kind of quiet I went around this side and see if I can oh shit
Up is a sniper. Where'd they even come from?
Snuck in
sniper down the road
Thank him in he dodged. All right, two tanks back to back here. I'm gonna just focus on the scouts
I think I got them all nice good shit on the real well done. That was fast. Wow guys
Wow, the character progression was really inside you the whole time or someone activated their hacks
All right, don't get cocky
I'm raging this guy. I back him up all the way
Okay
Sniper on the left and soldier coming in that soldier. I can't see I don't even know. Yeah, I can't see shit too
smoky too smoky
Nice use that. All right
Oscar
Yeah. Oh nice. We're killing him
On the way up. Oh, we killed the
Oh, that was awesome
Well played. I mean we have him so stun lucked
Yeah, this is going way way better I don't know why
That's sticky debt. That's sticky death
Gonna eat this. He's taunting. Hmm. Yeah, the weapon I have when I build a meter I taunt and I get a hundred percent crit
Hell, yeah
There's a great weapon, but don't let don't tell anybody I said that though
It is the single most hated weapon in this game, which one?
Yeah, I don't have that one
Are there medics on though? Oh, I have a lot of scouts a lot of scouts sentry buster as well
Wait, is he alive though? Oh, he's lost
Nice rocket jump out of there
Thank you
Fuck. Oh scout. Yeah scouts fast. Shoot him. Yeah scouts, but it's hard to detonate these sticky back so soon
No, we're good. Now. We're good now was
It's weird. This is this is the this is it here. I
Gotta say guys
Great work. It's just an amazing time to be a gamer
With all the great games we have in the year 2023
F2 a library
All right, one more thing. We're good
We might get scouts that might be trickling out to be careful. This is it
Is the sentry buster alive?
Nope, my rage does not work against this tank
Yeah, unfortunately, I pop the pop the bottles here. This is I'm celebrate
What another one they just keep coming?
I don't know any better. Hopefully somebody gets the
$100,000 item
Hell, yeah, okay. Oh
I gots the the oh wait
It's switching. Oh, yeah, it goes through. It's the screens gray
Exiting to main menu in 160 seconds
Yeah, do I get all of these? I just got my overlay. I got a hat. Well, you just got a hat. Yeah
I'm like eight of the shields. What is this?
You got to get the good stuff
Is this good?
That is that's so funny. I have a robot running man. Yeah, that was fun. Yeah, that was great
That was actually say resume game. Yeah, how do you how do you guys feel you guys want to do?
Yeah, I'll do I would do oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
You could you could sway me to do a Mario for sure. You could do that. Yeah, it's a badge
Rare but worthless
Jay, I just was Jay and it's so loud like hemorrhoids. What?
All right. Thanks for playing man vs. Machine man up for more. See you guys next week. Okay, so
Blood you gotta put that hat on. Yeah, I'm ready for a swag off
So if we have time to do one more maybe maybe another. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah one more. This is this is good
It's good going. So I should be Scout. We miss this like I feel like that's what we needed last time, right?
I could scout I want I got it this time. I'd love to snipe. It would be so beautiful. So
I enjoyed soldier before I can really determine what I want to do. I think I'm gonna have to open a crate to determine
What that is
Yeah, I just opened a handful. Let's see. How does how how does this how does this affect?
Society, how do you get a crate? This is a affected society greatly over the years
There's many studies have been done on it. They drop but you can go to the steam community market comm and buy like in bulk
Which will actually do this
Yeah, don't don't do it. Don't do it on stream. Whatever you do. I don't need to buy this. I'm buying two keys chat
I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna open the summer crates that I have. I don't believe in gambling
You know, I'm gonna I want a strange a flog stranger fire. I might have one actually look I'm opening something we get
This is the dopamine chat. See we get come on poke. I'm good. I'm getting killstreak vaccinator kit. Nice
Cool. Nobody else said nice
GG
It was just crickets chat. Did I not buy the right key again? Oh
It's the cosmetic. I just got the exact same thing twice. I'm done gambling is crazy. Oh, wait, you know what? That's fine
That's what I want. No. No, it's good. It's good. I got this watch chat look open with key
No, no. No, it's not wasted. I actually really wanted this. I'm serious. I want I got a cow mangler stranger fire
I'm playing with it. I'm bleeding so hard. I'm doing cow mangler cargo constructor
Oh a cow mangler can't hurt buildings in the robots and they're technically buildings. Are they wrong? Wait, it doesn't work
Somebody just told me the spy from TF2 is French. Is that true? Yes. Yeah. Yeah, we we
Frenchman and he goes I murdered your toys as well. Don't is that your French Jerma? That's my spy
French give me your French. Yeah, give me something to say
And have it make sure it's not like oh you poop poop with his pants. That's what he's gonna
Yeah, I would like to for you to say in a French accent
Is is this really it? Is this all you have on the menu? How do I say that with a French accent?
Oh, I thought you wanted me to say it in French. Oh
Is
This it is this all you have on the menu is this all of you have on your menu
Phenomenal this all you have on your menu
His use are insane
So what is this explosive explosive headshots? What sniper rifle is good for this game mode any wrecks?
I was at the default the hitman hit maker. So apparently is good. What do you think jarate as well?
Maybe throw some bizarre bargain would be really good. I do have that
Heatmaker would be pretty good bizarre bargain. I know my chance answering you heat maker. Yeah, everyone's spamming it and just
I'll do hit me hitman. I can you want me to go heavy?
I can go back I can go back to my old ways cuz I can go
Medic instead of engineer this round and then actually heal people
but we probably want a heavy or
Soldier y'all need to carry. I got it. You know, it's not you can't also go engineer super fun. Is it the same map?
Nope, this is different. Whoa, this is much shorter. This map is a is very short
So this one is this one could be hard two soldiers bad any crits in this round. No, we could do two soldiers cool
crits
Wave one we should be. Alright, I don't think we need to buy too much. The cheaters lament is like the rarest items in the game
Why do I even have the cheaters lament, what does that mean?
You see what I think it means. You have a back then. No, it's just old. It's an exploit item
Everyone has that. Alright. Well, thanks for making me feel special chat. Everybody. Everybody has that dude
All right, so they
This one is kind of annoying right because they can actually go up top up here
All right, they can go through these now me standing here. They can't sure who's our engineer. We do not have one
So that could be that's not good too alarming could disable issue
One sec, we do have a scout and we do have a medic. So I think we'd be alright
I'm gonna purchase a crits Krieg because apparently I threw mine out. Give me just a sec. I love this thing
I don't know. Everybody hates when I play with this and you go. I do this weapon fucking sucks
Like take it off. I'm just like no which one cow made that
This is punch heavies
What is man up mode? That means we use the ticket to play the game sick. Okay. All right, poke
Let's do this double soldier. All right, no NG. Ooh
big balls
Like that AC DC song big balls. Yeah, who's this guy flying around the map?
Somebody's flying. Yeah, one of us
Who's scouting? Oh
The scout. Yep. I'm gonna have a money you guys like money. I heard get off this character though
Anytime you hear the whoo, that means you're gonna get healed every time you heard something. He's going through big Scout. Oh
Oh
Come on come on in right here
Because so old
Okay, I'm gonna switch off a soldier here, but I that was fast
What's wrong? Is that impressive chat? Oh
Shit, that was bad. No, let me try sniper one more time. Who's gonna engineer cuz I don't know how I'm too stupid
I could I could go NG. All right, this is better. I could do NG if you poke if you wanna play something else
I'll play in you
NG oh I can do
Okay, hey take a look at my wrench everybody this one is just but you know what it's possible I get from this game mode
Yeah, take a look at my wrench was a disturbing sentence I didn't think that's what you meant oh
The Sydney sleeper also increases piss cooldown, I understand
Yeah, we need more piss right now. I want the frontier justice. I'm ready. I am almost ready and headshot though
Ready to deliver justice. All right, I have crits Creek
Which means I'll give you 10 seconds of crips where you will just annihilate everything
So I'll give you the heads up when you do that, but then yeah, can we get a code word?
I mean, I would have thought the word crits, but maybe
Bagels was a safe place the old teleporter in here probably right? It was the word bagel plus bagel. Yes bagel
Okay. All right, if I hear that I know to shoot I will not shoot until then
Scream as loud as you can when you need it. It's the only way
Unless you do it Spencer's going right here
Which is protected enough from the enemies, but oh, why is my health booming?
Medic medic does overheal gives you a little whoa
Pretty sick. Why is he going away?
Unless I'm healing you
Ludwig, I don't need upgrades
$100
Rock-paper-scissors right now. You know, I rock-paper-scissors. Oh, yeah, that's G. Let's see it
I'm the tf2 player here. It's bullshit. Yeah, if your chat was playing maybe
It was funny on my screen
We have a battle siren, there's somebody else's microwave going off. Oh
God, I gotta go get my hot pockets. Can we pause?
God this isn't going so great
What are you talking about? We're doing awesome. Oh, you guys are doing awesome
What's wrong? I'm working through some things. Hold on a minute. I'm out of ammo. I know that was impossible
Why did I go that far?
Damn
I'm entering your bagel. Pussy. Go bagel. Plus bagel. Plus you should save that for the big scouts
Yeah, I thought he was about to die
yeah, I
Can see how I would have been nice to have that right now
You're gonna come back to life in a second. I am I am walking right now. We're gonna be just fine
cool
Bow for this mode. Honestly, you're not wrong. Check your bus center buster. Oh
Nice good shit
No
Wow, that was useless of me
They were like getting stuck on this defense, sir. How do you accidentally press G? Was it a good thing? Cuz H is close
Scout
Don't let them do it
Got no ammo. I can't know where I got the world to go. Oh
Oh my gosh, okay, we're good. Oh my god
A plus I helped. Hey, well done everybody
Excellent job. Wait, how do you get the bonus?
Are you get all the money? Oh, yeah, let's do this
Lector pyros
Two-way teleporter. Oh, you have to get the refill thing every round to one time use. Let me try this again. Yep
R with rifle to use your charge buff on the sniper. Oh, right, right. Okay teleporter
We'll take you both ways now if you want to go back
Full reload speeds probably broken. I don't know. Yeah
I'm ready
Okay. Mm-hmm. Uh, hold on we get the take your time
Get high ground. So you're not shooting team problem with that chat is it's easier to shoot headshots down here
Who is this person? You look cool
Third century speed upgrade is bugged. Hmm. I like your hat you thank you. It's on brand it is
alright
Can you see we got a big boy? I can see
those medics
Only shoot those medics because they will just keep this heavy ubered for a full two to three minutes
If you headshot the heavy and you have the explosive headshots, you'll usually get the medics
That is so many
Bus I'm mega bus. Yeah, just keep going
Good
Nice you you please
Who's grabbing that money? Yeah. Thank you. Yo hit hit E in the future and then I'll show I forgot about that
There you go. That's so fast. The game's just not even ready to load the next enemy. I
Do love this doctor
Curious where he got his license from but more of a doctor same deal. Oh
No, just just headshot him. No one else shoot him just headshot him
Look, I don't need a license to plunge my crits into your bagel. That's all Vinny
Spies, yep spies are going by his medic. Oh, I got spied. I got I got stabbed
Die oh my god, this is spy medic just wrong. Oh, that was that was a problem
Okay, I'm fine medic can I get a res whoa, nope, I don't
Chat if I didn't get that shot I would have been so disappointed. Oh
Around oh
There's no tank. Just that guy
Tank. Oh wait is now. Oh shit. Okay tank is now
Penetration you think chat? Yeah penetrator for sure. I
Got a lot of crits now. Wow. I have to go back and buy shit. What am I doing? What?
What's your deal man? Are you serious right now? I honestly I just was like, oh
Goodness
Max out explosive headshot. That'll be next. Okay. I got a second century now. That's fun explosive upgrade increases its range
That sounds awesome. All right, they're gonna be going pretty much both directions. So it doesn't matter
Someone said what the fuck is wrong with his fov
It's wrong with my fov. You want I can't see your screen if you want to change your fov you can do so
It's maxed out chat. It should be not I think 90s of max. Yeah, I maxed it out
Usually people when they say your fov for some reason they forget what fov actually isn't they're talking about your view model
Go. Oh, yeah, if you might have the weapons real small if you want if you're gonna change your view model in like the console
Just make sure you do that off-camera
Like hitting Tildo, you know, I mean, mm-hmm where you're century next to the dispenser, but then I can't do this medic. Are you okay?
I see you in great distress Doug
Just a little scared. I have a tank phobia. Can we destroy this tank right now for real? No cap
There are nights and I'm like, yeah for real. No cappy. No cappy Barra
Okay, I'm gonna get down. I want to use my Chris sturdy get overheal by picking up cash
I do I need to do that. All right, cuz you you always are at overheal. I can't tell if I'm
Over healed more than I should be able to I think you do. Yeah, okay. Oh
Shit oh
Man, that was awesome. This is an arrow through my fucking head. Oh, yeah
God damn it. I had 40 fucking crits in that gun. I had I didn't know nobody even laughed at it. Oh shit
Wait, what are we supposed to be laughing at nothing? I'd be coming. I'd be coming. I
Exhaled Oh sharply through my nose if that helps
That's good enough for me. Oh, I love this. Oh god still have a bagel push, dude
I don't know. We're just so well oiled machine. I'll hold your bagel pussy
Dude I'm so sorry. We have become such a a
Synchronized unit that we're gonna beat this in like 20 minutes. Are we capable of doing the real ones?
This is not a real one
This feels real to me. I don't know the harder difficulty. That's much harder. There is
What is this difficulty called?
Bagel pussy
There's an advanced and there's expert. I'd like guys for introducing that word into this game
That being said I am going to pop it right now
Big dem on the right. I got big guy. Nice. Very good. I'm just gonna throw piss at the tank
I don't think it worked. I don't I don't think I'm the most qualified to handle this tank
As a sniper also the dispenser I upgraded Spencer. So there's a big trail on it. Yeah, I've not I've never not had ammo
Yeah, I think this might also be one of the easier maps because half the enemies like have melee right tank. What do you got?
All right, let's decide for handle it. Let's sniper handle. Let's leave
The tank can't even carry the bomb. What's the risk of letting it through?
It is a bomb is a bomb. It is a giant
A plus credit rate. Look at that
Wow
Ready for hard mode. Yeah, to be honest. It's a bit of light work true. They don't know how hard hard is. Oh
The real game starts now
Two tanks this time. I believe it's two. Yeah. Oh this metal region. Is this other crits in this one?
Is this a crit one? This is yeah, these are punch
Holiday heavies, which they if they punch you you are going to just start laughing. Did you essentially just go?
Oh, thanks for explaining what laughing is I
Was unsure oh
Fuck it up for me. It cleared it up for me. I wasn't sure if it's like a ha ha or heehee
I wanted to go see a doctor for that one. So he says it's just laughing
I left once and you had wait you had to see a doctor after laughing. Yeah, I don't know what it was
I mean, it's involuntary. So seeing a doctor was probably the right move. Mm-hmm
We ready to absolutely
I'm ready. No, I'm feeling great about myself and my team. How do you like a soldier so fun? Very fun in this
How do you like what you're doing I love engine and he's just any gooners in the call
No joking though. I'm all about joking respect that
You guys like jokes, I was the first ever good. Yeah, I like jokes
Pop crits once these guys drop
jelps, I
Was too scared to gel if I heard it breaks your dick
No
Safe all I heard is somebody's
Did I always read these threads growing up like dude don't gel broke my dick
Wait, what is what is going on? What is what is that?
Lq so good luck with that search just prepare to wipe your entire search history after that it better yet search on Bing
We got punch heavies. I
Trying to snipe a tank I got let me get the heavies tank is completely under control
Okay, clear up front clear up front
second tank
Money, I need jump height
I'm gonna miss some money man. Oh
All right, we're good. Okay. Yes the tank bagel pussy this tank
Working on it. I love how that's turning into like this smurf word every every time it makes me laugh, too
It is currently in the oven. Oh
I understand
That's all that's good on two levels. Oh my god bagels and
that oh
and
Here we go, they go pussy kill the tank kill the tank kill the tank in the oven there
It's almost there guys. It's almost there
It's like Comedy Central up in this piece
because
In the oven don't worry about it the old just golden
Company's a great round. Just a great round. That's great. Except somebody missed 25 bucks, but I just saw the money
It's right there. Yeah
Damn, oh
Was on under that's that's sneaky
Just restart. Should we start?
Another wave another dollar I was thinking about we should probably just redo the whole thing. So we start the stream. Hey everybody. Welcome
Start all of our streams
What is that accent a damn germ the heaviest Russian
We
Get it some more from some other people in the call not just a couple
Heavy
Me is a heavy weapon. Yeah, I'm ready. I'm American
What are you did Christopher Walken and I don't know who?
Astroglide, I think I was dug dug. She didn't let her mind your waddle impression. I don't want they don't want to hear the waddle impression
I love no. Yeah. No, I do I do
Hey, it's me the heavy weapons guy. Yeah, they want to buy it the 29 hyperdrive
Damn gives a bubble or the good water. So I can't like a server
That was very good, but I don't know who water is. You don't know what?
Character just liked it. I just liked it. What is water look like to you based on that voice like if you had to guess
One eye is purple because he's got hit in the face and he's very he's got like a mustache and a lot of a
Like a five o'clock shadow. Yeah, and he's someone in my check. Can you draw that?
Peru dude, so cringe. That's him. He's got it. Did I I don't think that was even close. Wait?
No, I think it kind of was I thought is it? Wait, what is he from?
What is what Oh does have a mustache, but he's you know, he's a flying alien. I
Think he does he
Wait chat. Does he have a mustache? No, I don't think so
It doesn't look like Danny DeVito and Matilda. I
Think that's what stir described. Yes, sir. I think you saw Danny DeVito in Matilda and that's why you recently, right?
Yesterday
Just can't get Matilda out of the brain. She's just like me. Did you know Danny DeVito directed that movie?
No, really very talented guy the director produced
I'm pretty sure he directed that. Yeah, that was a directorial movie for him
He's done a lot of
Stuff that you wouldn't think
We are absolutely destroying this. Oh
I'm gonna hit you
I thought you're about to die. There you go. I'm feeling great. I'm feeling electric. I
Mean, we got to go to hard mode. This is a little too free for dollars somewhere
spies
spies are
Here nice. Oh a spike on me. Nice. This one spot spy is quite nice poke
I'm not here careful. Imagine playing a spy a grown-ass man. Well, I use the focus the wrong time
Grown-ass person playing a game. It's so funny because that's probably like the hardest most meticulous class to play
You need like a certain level of adult intelligence, I think to be able to do it
I've been saying as much as I can lately
Imagine a grown-ass man doing that a
little bit of a
Heavies are going around the left side
Yeah, I seen him. We have the bomb though. Yes seen it
old news
Right. They keep saying here comes the spies. I haven't seen him. So someone's doing a great job on our team
Oh shit! There's a bunch of heavies going behind
In the middle. Is this a spy?
Holy shit, how many people? Oh, there's a lot back here
This person evil. I can crit you if we need
Are we alright?
Money somewhere money money money. Where's the money on this side? I got it. I got some money here. Oh god
Yeah, oh yeah, all right, this is it this is the hard one who's missing the nine
Wow
stir, I
Mean if you're the engineer standing on the roof shooting its guys in a totally random spot
You don't say that money dropped over there. I don't know to go get it. It's fair home
Imagine being a grown-ass man saying something like that
Talk about money
I gotta do this. I gotta do this. All right, a lot of blast a lot of blast like what the blast
Any crits any critters?
Yes, any fire? No fire. Three tanks final wave. I think that's what I'm doing
I think we're pretty much ready to rock and roll. Mm-hmm
Grown-ass team ready to bagel puss. Grown-ass men talking about bagel pussies still
Grown-ass men
Some grown-ass men playing TF2. What's going on?
Uh, this is what grown-ass men are meant to do
Well, I can't afford
Easy grease
It's gonna be like three tanks back to back to back a lot of medics just make sure we know that okay
I'm ready. I don't know about the rest of the people on the team
That press f4 when they're ready, I'm ready those feelings also already at this point, I believe remember you're not blinking
What I was last time I blinked you guys
Actually calculate that
Yeah, they have like they have like a notebook. You're right down
bling watchers, man
Why did you just scroll fall damage? I just heard you scream Doug. All right, lad. You ready?
Yeah, it's always this air coots guy
Okay time to clutch your kick
You imagine a grown-ass coots
Don't don't don't be come on
There's this is DPS that we didn't get on the tank. There's one second. We lose if we lose this was why?
Hey, all right
This is hard to look at
And he's doing zooming in and out. I don't have the bomb but
No
Try to get the heavies. Oh you got you got him
If he is a spy that spy is not one of us that one of us is me that me is a sniper
That's sniper is a pyro
you talk like the guy in Disneyland on the
Indiana ride I
I do. Yeah, he gives you like the safety instructions
He's on Indiana Jones
Who's he? Yeah
Why did I come here? Hey, there you go
Much real say I was there recently sentence. Hmm. Where's this final?
Yeah, no, they're wrong with that I would say you don't
Are we gonna throw you want to have this fight?
We we got two warriors right here. Let's go high five
I make fun of Disney adults and then they're like you're a Nintendo adult. I'm like, you're right. Oh
This man's awesome
Behind the tank is two soldiers. We should get them. Yeah
Working on it working on it
This like shield in front of me, by the way, I'll stop them check miles. I think it's amazing
Thank me. The work is we need some yeah, and I I'm a sniper. I can help
I'm weak you guys tank, but I can shoot a bit
Thanks fine
Thank you. Good. Yeah, we're good. Oh
We tank is it still going got me feeling like I got it. I got the thing. I
Shouldn't have been that concern. All right, wait my money. Uh-huh. Excuse me guys
What's wrong? Oh
Right side. Yeah, we get some heavies with boxing gloves. I'll watch the bomb. Oh, they're breaking me laugh
They got a laugh. That's what a laugh is. Oh
Yeah, if you don't know what how it goes it goes
Sentry buster. Oh, I'm the engineer. Oh shit pushing it back pushing it back. Oh
Got it. We got it. We got it. Thank you guys. Appreciate it
Not even a factor right now. Not even a factor a sniper on the right. Oh, we got a lot of big boys coming down
Oh, okay. I
Need a sniper to get rid of these shields. Yeah, I need to I need to back out
Okay, I can crit you go
Got it. We're good
round two round two
Don't get a medics get them. All right
These heels are insane
Dude, what?
I'm down though. So
Buster. Oh, I am about to
Whoo, nice job as a waste of fucking karate
All right, we're getting collapsed on here
Take time and then we're done. That's it. Yeah, I
Was free. I'm not gonna lie
Shields kind of good. Yeah, Doug's kind of crazy as medic
Jonas buff. Oh
Sniper we got some snipers on the map, too. Oh
You got him. You got him
Crazy
Mental all right, man. We got somebody get something cool. They're nuts
All right, big old sword
Banana nice. Oh, yeah here. What we get. Come on. No whammies for me. No whammies for me. Give me a jacket. Oh
Yeah, nice that's my favorite weapon in the game, I don't think I got anything is that normal you didn't get anything got a
thruster oh
Yeah
Because you do you have to complete the tour and you've already done this apparently I guess. Oh
That me too. I didn't get anything either
shit
Yeah, and my result screen is bugged
Let's try like the hardest mode 36 year old man. Yeah, give us the hardest mode
Yeah, come on like it was a lot easier because we didn't lose $400 around
But still they made fun of me for losing $6
Almost
Eight-year-old man by the way people in chat. You don't even know how yeah, that's it's me me and Jerma. Oh 38
And we can send this comp at the hardest one. They have this cop is not losing too many
I think if any I think we got what it takes to do the expert you want to oh boy
Oh, this guy thinks he can handle expert all of a sudden
Okay, all right, I just want to make sure everyone in the call understands. I'm trying to talk up the call
He's saying that he's talking about how none of you can do it. I can do it. Oh Botswana
Hey, I mean, I'm here to I could do I could do it. I could try it
Operation gear grinder warning expert missions are much harder in all caps. This is written in the game
Advanced missions require all six team members to be strong contributors
So the fourth class is the demo man and the demo man has two primaries
He's got the rocket the grenade launcher, and he's got the sticky launcher. This sounds like a mode for some grown-ass men
Yeah, cute up for man up. We are grown-ass man up, bro. You look like don't Chocula ban that person for a fucking hour
Huh?
Actually, no actually don't ban that person. That's fucking cool. I'm into that
She is not playing dark and darker now. They can do update came out. Do you have to crash for me?
Oh, no, never mind. It didn't sometimes the loading screen looks like a crash if you were tabbed. Yeah, I was tabbed
I'm playing geoguessr. I we forget you've never played tf2 and you don't know how like buggy the game is
Old the code is
All right. So what what are our strengths take your pick? I'm a nasty little tank
I'm a dirty little tank. I can I can scout well, I can stay Scout
Yeah, I'm fine going mad again. It was fun
I kind of want to do walk and load demo that suck now or I could spy
I'll do sniper again. If you guys think it's a my chats like I should do so
I think our last team comp was efficient effective and fierce
That's my thoughts and then they end
Yeah, doing something a little goofy, but let's give it a try. Yeah, let's let's let's give it a shot, bro
You are throwing right now. You don't know that okay, you know
Turn off on scoping after shooting in the options might feel better. You believe they're accusing me of being high right now
Take excuse me. Yeah, excuse you any crits this round not this round. Maybe I just do
Chat, that's not what I need. I don't I seems kind of use that way. Can I use the cow thing now?
Go golfing the cow mangler. Yep. It's honest
So that that does not have any ammo you just have to recharge it
It does take a little bit extra takes a little bit extra time to read. Oh, but it doesn't work of my guy
Yeah, so that that would only be on the soldier. Oh, yeah, I'm not soldier turn on damage numbers
Do you guys have your damage numbers on or no? I see it. Yeah. Wait, how you see damage?
It's in the every time I shoot it goes and it shows me every little number a classic TF2 videos
We should uber charged
Hybrid night in MVM with an Omega L face. Well, you haven't seen it play out. Oh, this is a bad map
We should have done the other map. This is actually gonna be really fucking hard. It's gonna be hard
I want to pick a map that we already knew and there's only three missions on the hard one because they made this cool mode
And then they never supported it after that ever again. What I thought valve did that a lot
There was MVM came out then like two years went by and then they added up like omissions in one update
But there's a whole bunch of community maps for this that are pretty cool. And we all love it
Some road add some roguelike elements to it and boom, there you go. Yeah, they could just call it TF 2 2
CF charge money for it all over again live
Mm-hmm TF 2 2 would be good if 2 3. Oh
Wow, oh, whoa. Whoa, dude. I got a DM from uh, I
Got a DM from Cody Ko and he said I did the Billy Billy challenge
which I thought meant the NPC challenge because the streaming said Billy Billy and
And then he said I threw up at the end so he was trying to say the dug dug challenge
But he called it the Billy Billy challenge. Oh
That's your challenge
It's my challenge in the sense that I did it first I guess I didn't created it
Poking it. So yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's your challenge
It's your challenge in the sense that you created it did it first and popularize it and made the rules
You don't have much ownership. Gotcha
Yeah, I wanted to do it and I wanted to hire like three or four
massive bodybuilders
And just go do it and pretend like already spies
Already spies. Oh, yeah, they're not messing around
Behind you behind you just spin around spin around just okay. What? Oh, oh, there's a spy behind me
Yeah, no, there's there's a lot of it's all it what is going on? It's like ten spies
Yeah, it's a lot of spice it's the hard mode it's hard mode is what you how many spies are there what the insta-kill, dude
Look at the top and if you see the spy icon there, that means they're still spies. Oh, we don't a teleporter
So we do we always $1
No, we it only gets consumed when you lose like no no when you win. Sorry. Oh
Here we go. Finally, okay long enough. All right, go go go. Oh, that's
Shit
The heel guys we got to kill the heel guys class work
The hell is that working drama? These guys take extra melee damage. I forgot to say that because they have those. Oh
That was me. I was me
You piece of shit
Dude you got the double donk. That's right. You're throwing I'm fine
This is a terrible start
Snipers focusing on us across the way. Oh
This is nasty. This is nasty. I got crits when we need guys getting healed. We got to kill the healer
Trying to push the bomb back. All right, we're okay. Yeah, we just back seven and kill it one shot or no
Can you can you watch all the back step?
This is just wipe it
No some things you can one-shot some things like the big giant ones
I don't think you can they just do a lot of damage to them. Geez
I'm having a hard time on spy. All right
Nothing, but I got disoriented shit. Wait, you know
That's coming in. Oh, yeah, that's here
now it's here at
We're okay, I'm a dead man
For you, they're deep in our
Oh
This is over
Okay, I am going to take I'm gonna blame me. I'm gonna blame me
I'm gonna blame me. I
Did great. I don't blame Doug and I don't blame Doug. I'm gonna play. All right, let me so I think
Do bear charge. I think this is better. I got I'm gonna go Angie. We need those spies are frustrating
I wonder if I should put on this thing use Huntsman with lead arrows
All right, I can do this. Should I not be sniper? Should I be like another class to help? What are you feeling?
I don't know. What should I light them on fire?
You should just turn around. I row is every now and then I feel a little bit
Just turn that song on and every time it says turn around turn around
No, would you go to a concert if they did that and they just kept getting higher and higher for an hour
Like a shepherd's tone. It just keeps going who's playing up until the point. It's a dog whistle
Well, then that's a problem
Yeah this generation of like how cool we are
Maybe you just go you film that song on your phone like as a selfie and then you leave after it's over
Now that's the whole concert they don't do anything else they do the one. Oh, that's it
Oh, then you're good. You get four hours of that. They come on and they're like we understand that
This is the only thing anybody ever sings of our anything we ever have ever done. So we're just gonna do this
And then they get really mad. They're like, how many of you fucking assholes even know a single other lyric?
Yeah, besides turn around or how about this one our house in the middle of our street our house in the middle of our street
Our house does that same line not even the full song you did it three times and I'm upset
Would you want more or?
Spice spice spice. I can't stand
Yeah, those are all spies
And that guy I can't aim still a couple spies
Oh shit, um, just run just run just run just run get off
I do
They're just smacking my shit with their bats, what are they why are they up here?
I'm gonna create you. I'm gonna create you go go go
And there's one to your left. I don't know how much I'm helping here chat. Oh
Good them spies ruin everything
Good. We got this. Where's the supply cabinet? Oh my god, who?
You're way too close to me. Oh, I got you. What the fuck is happening back here this
Ton of scouts ton of scouts. Okay, not even close guys when you walk
Be aware this five spies. It's fun. What? Oh shit. Oh, yeah
Here's a spy
You guys just all sounded like the fucking seagulls from that fucking aquatic movie. What was it fighting Nemo? Oh shit
Aquatic movie
Wait snipers left side. Oh, no. Oh, no
Well, I'm coming in
Heads up gamers. Okay, so I got a spy or a sniper for our left. Okay, right, so I'm gonna create you
Staying at the back. Okay, that was a little premature. Oh
Heavy okay interesting play
We're okay
Everything's all right. It's not we're not it's not over yet
Goddamn close to it
We're fine, we're fine. Okay, we just need to make it for this round great recovery
by a spy
Everywhere. I don't trust any you fuckers. It's not me. I swear
What right behind you by the entry
Okay, all these snipers. Does somebody help the snipers? Yes, I'm doing it. Oh
My goodness, I'm dead. Oh my god, we're okay
Trying what we try in here
Holy shit, which are just spies left rounds over. We've got this soldiers coming
I don't think we lost any money either. Did we?
I don't know. Holy shit
Snipers on yeah, I think they're on the left. Yeah, okay
Let try to play conservative so I can get to the crits
Get that money money money money a lot of money on the right side a lot of money on the right side
Hmm. Oh god, we did it though. Yeah, we did it. We did it was stressful. It's pretty stressful
What did I need?
Honestly rage knockback rage would have helped maybe a little firing speed
If I have a little how long that you're gone. We actually did fine. Yeah
That was wave one
That's what's stressing me out about to get very stressful get bloody Karen. All right
Um, where do you guys want the dispenser where's the ideal location for
Um
Maybe this house somewhere on top of it. Where do you put it? Here's fine for me
It's probably safe here if you want to run back to it
Don't need the metal. I did this a full ammo case up here. I'll be good. I
Am RTG then you should put it here
So your back can be to the metal and you're not getting shot
You see what I'm saying? If you if you say anything to this guy, he just like shuts down
I'm okay
Stop giving me advice. That's what somebody said. Yeah
Yeah, that that other guy is still banned for saying that you look like Count Chocula man that guy
What the fuck just happened?
and that guy I
Thought something was wrong with me for a second
These things just happen naturally
I was like, you know, I'm not a lot of medics. That's a lot of medic sir. Oh
Sentry going down
Where was the uh?
Bro, he's got okay behind you behind ammo relocated
But lots of spies up to this to the roof on the top, right?
All around you and veneer spies behind you behind you that guy. Oh
God, there are there's so many of us. Why are there so many teammates there? Yeah
I'm just doing sentry at the at the last point. There's a guy coming right now
Got with bomb
God damn fucking spies
All right, we're good. We're good. He's on me. He's on me
Shit, oh shit
Right, oh it's upstairs now, okay, there is it either to the right or in the middle I have to stay back here
Oh shit the noise
Oh boy, this is gonna get really ugly
Jeez, he's strong. We're in a lot of trouble guys. Look at all these scouts. Oh shit
What you're gonna be back two seconds cool. All right
Body block it up here
We're good spies coming in spies coming in again, dude. They are very strong
Turn around
Why behind you it's behind you that guy's by right there that medic soldier spy soldier is a spy right now there's a soldier
How do I miss all of those shots? There's an invisible fire is
Soldiers coming in on the left side with soldiers right scout
Spy sniper just standing here. Oh nice wrench, dude. Yeah. Is that you Vinnie? Oh, this is me. That's me
I'm up here. Yes, okay
Not bad. We're doing all right
Oh
Look, where are you? I'm all the way back
Sentries coming out of ammo. He's bringing it all though. I
Think you see the crate crate boxes up here or the the metals up here five coming again fucking this fire
Oh, I hate so much. But yeah, we did it
Nice and not bad. We got most of the money
German wars your refill station. Ah
It was on the top right, but when it got kind of hairy, I just brought it back here
But I will put it I'm gonna put it where that fence is next time where you were last time. Yeah, I like the fence
Hmm. Oh
Baby, all right money. I think that's still 30 bucks somewhere. Why is it? Oh, there is shit. Nice
You got it. Oh, we did. Oh, did you maybe not? All right. What's uh, what's uh, what's the status this round?
It's a little blast resistance. You think?
Yeah, it's definitely time to get some resist
Blast resistance for sure here. Yeah one jump and jump on the sign literal God spot. What really?
The red icon at the top means they're big ones, right?
Like the three red the three red I believe is crits. So those are the crates was the blue. Okay. Oh god
The blue outline is crits the red is just big and blue and red is big
Okay, hold on. I'm up. I gotta get up here
So I'm gonna put this this is gonna have a pretty big range be able to see how far is it?
Yeah, it's you can stay pretty far away from it
Need you now
Fucking need you more than never
Fuck in my head. No, we said where your eyebrows. They're right here
I just I have a big brow bone and it's summertime. So I absorbed them
Raise into my eyebrows and my hair lightens
Yeah, that's that's normal
Summer brow bone sounds like a good like album name. I think Douglas
Brow bone
Alright, let's have some fun. Oh, she's coming in. Yeah, I'll probably create you for this
Let's just kill him
Yeah, quick tank behind you behind you
I'm trying to help. Yeah
The tank we got it is not aware guys tank
I can handle the soldiers back here. You guys focus on tank. Oh
I'm muted and call. Give me a minute. Give me this crit
Big heavy coming up big heavy took out everything
This here. I'm gonna I'm gonna create you again. Do you have ammo but
Yeah, I'm using this shotgun I think it does a little more no, no your crit will do more get out your man again
Oh, yeah. Yeah, you mean crit got the the big lad
Your chance we might need help with the tank I think we're okay
I have two crits that I can pop if we need it Doug. I'm ready to heal
Where my gun is just not made for this device. Oh, they're okay. I got you
Oh
Yeah, I'm not I'm not doing damage against that fucking tank
Leave a pyro
I'm gonna I think I'll get crit just in time for this. Can we get up and shoot this tank?
We should be okay. Oh
That is whoa big heavy big heavy on the left right side. Yeah big with y'all hell
I got rage. I'm crit for it with some fun. I can push him back
I'm taunting it. Oh, wait, what? Oh
There's no way we lose this guy
Fuck you got me
Holy shit, we might die. Oh, I died. Oh, no. Oh, there's another heavy
Okay, it's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay
Left heavy left heavy focus
Heavy versus heavy. It's too much respawn time
This heavy needs to be killed. I think we're all right. You might die. I try to get like half behind the staircase
I died. It killed me. Oh, oh, thank God
Good job guys, and I need you now
That was tough, I think knockback rage is decent easy
Maybe I do this and then this no shit. Do I really even need metal?
Yeah, I do, but I need defense
For tanks you guys the heavy is usually the best at shooting at wall crits. Just throwing it out there
I don't want to be that guy. Look I do shoot it and then my chat my chat just my chat roasts me
Okay, so I'm just sitting here my chat goes you your guns literally resisted again
So you shouldn't be using that so like I'll tell endure if you what you're asking for me
Just to endure this this this punishment of being made fun of for using a gun. That's not very effective
I will I think you're doing just fine. I think you're doing good. Yeah, you are. I'm gonna change my position
I'm gonna go up. You just got to use goon tactics
I'm doing literally while live and they just go heavy does reduce damage to tanks. Why are you shooting at us?
It's ridiculous here like reduce damage is still more damage than it would be if you didn't shoot it
Yeah, we need all the damage we can get which I crit somebody else then when we're attacking tanks
I
Think you still crit the goat. I mean you were shotgunning it for a full like minute or so
Shotguns without crit do like a quick thousand. They're pretty good
All right, I
Prepared isn't it weird how it's always Doug. It was me this time dogs a thinker
It was me this we got this we got this we're just I just you know
Goon max just goon maxing
Apparently, we're we need a pyro pyro
For the tanks. Oh, we set it back here. Okay. Oh, well, I mean this one we're melting
Ludwig, please stop shooting it you do reveal you've reduced
You're shooting this right now you're it sounds like you're reading my chat
What are you doing? You do produce damage? Don't you know?
He doesn't know. Oh my god scouts. Oh my god. I
Need ammo. Oh good. I mean, I shouldn't be shooting the tank either, but it's it's something
It's a couple, you know a little bit of damage each time
Yo, let's focus on the people back there. Let's just get him. I got him. Oh, never mind. Okay all dead
I guess crit the tank. Oh
Thank number three
nice
To your right like you're a lot of them I
Pissed on the spies
Okay, they're all dead. I
Was nice John Rick you don't know I'm trying to get a headshot. I'm one of these fuckers
Well, we're kind of killing it right now. It's good sniper down the road
A lot of tanks this round get the money. Oh, fuck. Nevermind. Not getting life. I have rage to push back a big guys
Guys, what was that? What's that noise? Oh, they're big. They're very big
Just a free round, holy shit
Dollars I see it. Yeah
I am so fucking impressed
How do we do this shoot backwards fly thing cuz it's not working for me, huh?
What all right?
It is time to resist perhaps a little bit of blast, but he's blasters bullet errs fires
These are a lot of melee damage
crit melee and
All a little bit of blasting and some I do a little you do a little blasting
Maybe hey, it's me
I think I got a good comp here
Doug I was I was watching your stream Doug and I saw you raid and now I'm seeing parks are with Doug. Please stop feeding
Yeah, there's a little side
Yeah, I'm noticing and I feel like you're losing
Do you know you can just raid people while streaming as many times as you want
No, yeah, you can just straight away. Why do they go? Where do they go? All right? Where do you it's like two Christmases?
It's like a divorce in Paris. I'm gonna send some beers over to Vinny. I'm doing all right. I'm doing all right wait
So if I don't I'm somebody here, they'll all go that way if you raid them
It'll put them in the chat, but then you're still live so then some come back, and then you can rate again
Right, just lose all your viewers, but it's funny. Who am I rating? Who am I reading right now?
It crew oh my chat member said you multiply the viewers it creates new people from scratch
We just all raid Vinny at the same time get him to like
Let's give any like 80,000 concurrent viewers. Yeah, I'm down
That actually
Wait, what are we doing this?
Oh
Not another car, oh shit, okay, wait wait wait wait. I don't have the ability. I can't move
That's bad for us next round. We need to do that somebody. That's so funny
Who wants to have like a shitload of viewers?
I mean listen I say I'm nervous about it, but I wouldn't like downright refuse it
Well, you'd have to send him back to somebody else though in the call
I can do that is like we don't need to get your permission
Okay, so here's how we're gonna do this so we'll all who else who wants to do the take in the first one
I'm
First one and then I'll pass it down to stir okay, so at the end of this round. We're gonna
Everybody's gonna raid Vinny
But Ludd you're on YouTube right yeah, this doesn't work for me. Okay, but I will I will laugh
That's fine. So people we're just gonna slide you a laugh in the background of this pool
Yeah, we definitely need you like tackling in the background. Oh, I'm gonna. I'm gonna create you once everybody's down on the ground
Damn these guys sped up yeah, I had there was a moment
I thought it was lag sniper on the back right multiple if anybody can get him my screen went sepia tone
There yeah, there's I think there's piss snipers. Yeah, you're covered in piss
Where was that?
Where's your thing this time German up top here where I am up here. Oh, it's a D. Okay?
It's a way. It's a streamer Illuminati thing. I don't know what's going on. I think I missed the memo
It's gonna be a very funny spot
Money getting pissed on a bit
Trying to prevent us from getting pissed on a little tough
targeting left guy
What hi I'd shield up
targeting right guy
good
Little little laggy yes, it lagging Bob Bob coming up. Hey, I'm back
Oh
My god, okay, so when we do this
Best guy got bomb all right
Oh, that's a lot
We got crits in like five seconds, I'm coming up to you to your left to let him in a pop it set go
No, you know there well there goes the century it's okay, it's under the round
Dispensers still up I am back. I think we're owning
Yeah, we we did all right. Is this the heart? This is literally the hardest difficulty scout fast scout very fast out at very full
Hell, he's already back. He's already back. Oh, I slowed him down with piss now
Oh, that was so much good hit actually almost through the oh I use the shotgun cuz I thought I'd be cool
He ran right by me. I
Need to do this. That's why I bought it
I'm gonna leave a mini sentry back here in case of what is left. What is even you lone snipers running through?
What's happening
Like yeah, what happened here making me nervous. Oh, they're there oh
There's no way we can handle this wave
We got all the money
Yeah, Oh big scout on left. How come everybody's doing the leg?
Hey Ludwig, we lose because you
Good catch and I need you more than ever a plus
That was a cheap round they didn't give us much for that. Yeah
Nice. All right. All right. I've already raven. I
Don't understand. Okay, so we're gonna put we're gonna collaborate all of our viewers into one stream and then that stream
We'll just pass it to the next stream and we'll continue this forever. So we all have a hundred thousand viewers
We're gonna like break all of our
Records, I'm gonna materialize viewers. Yeah
It's just vine sauce, yeah, and then who's after me stir I think stir should be after everybody get in the car
You're going to Uncle Vinesauce house. All right, everybody go to go to Vinesauce. I'm raiding. This is very interesting
Let's see how I'm also doing it. Yeah, but your stream is still on you don't you know
You're still streaming. All right, I've sent him. Oh my god. Are we good? Okay, so I'm raiding Vinesauce. Yeah
Hey guys, I'm raiding Vinesauce. Oh my god. Okay, I think so soon coming in clutch with my gaming lifestyle
Okay, but here's this is this the last round? I don't know. Is it so at the end of this round?
You have to pass it to somebody else. I was gonna pass it like right away or should I do like
What do you what? Yeah, we're doing around because I'm not sure how much longer we're gonna be playing this
What round are we in right now? Five? Six?
Six out of seven
What we could do is we just keep passing the viewers along up until the round actually starts and that person just has to deal
With them during the actual game. Or how about just at some point after like a minute or two just pass it
During the game. I'll just pass it in like a minute. I hit a new record. You just got me to 25k
I think like 15 was my record or something like that. So
Thanks everyone
30k you're at 30. Wow. You're the number one TF2 streamer. I oh my god. Oh
My god right now. Now we play with this for a little bit and then you pass the stir
Okay, what is stir? What's your name on twitch? It's just ST er. Yeah, okay
I
Play some ads right now
When you are when you pass that to stir that's exactly what he's doing. I'm telling you I know he is
You know what? I'm normally not like this, but I'm gonna I'm gonna do it do it stir is
One minute ad button. I'm sorry. Everyone. You don't need help on kill
You just like just somebody a twitch gonna look at this and be like, I don't know. God. Yo, my twitch is lagging
I tried to load the twitch front page and it lagged. I don't know if it was related
My god, okay
We're crashing
Nice to have you here. You're mine. Now. I'm not raiding forward
Stir you're getting the next I'm raiding. I'm raiding you now. Here's what here's the deal everybody that I go to stir
That's from my stream follow stir. Like click the follow button when you get low do it. You guys are gonna love my stream
It's gonna be three minutes of ads. I was gonna say I knew you do you're gonna run ten minutes of ads
Okay, my raid button is actually laggy because of how fucked up my stream is right now by the way, it started
Yeah, and by the way, you guys are gonna be trapped over with stir with like five minutes of ads
I can't even I don't feel like I should do that when I guess I'm
Who is like whose stream is visible right now to people all of everybody
It's glitched. My raid button is glitched. It just loaded Jerma's channel twice
But not coming back here. Are you wait? So we are creating people
Yeah, I think we are materializing people what?
How about this guys?
Scout behind there's like a big-ass medic as soon as this works. I'm gonna raid. Oh, I got it
We got to kill the healer me a minute. Yep, medic
Get the big medic in the big medic raid me raid me big medic break a big reddit
Big read it big reddit big reddit reddit reddit medic
Man
Doug you just running around. Well, nobody's alive
What oh, oh my god. I didn't mean to do that. Where is everybody? Okay, I
Let's keep it together. Let's keep it together
There's a heavy is almost last right now I could be a scout please walk off scout done big big scouts
soldier on left
Don't tell anybody I did that ever since you got so big my sauce you can't change on us, man. I know bro
I'm gonna raid you I see you. Here we go
Everybody go to stir follow his channel and then stir you got to pass it on this guy is melting me
Okay, there's five seconds five seconds five seconds bye everybody bye bye everybody. Hello. Bye. Thanks for being here. Thanks
Stir you got everybody. I got everyone. I'm gonna double it and pass it on
So wait, so that means you need to get to like 70,000 viewers
Yeah, okay. How we can if we just keep raiding we'll keep creating viewers. I know you're gonna help out behind
I'm trying to play the game
We're gonna get
The medic benefits from the quick-fix uber as well. So the medic is also crazy healing and hard to kill
Work can I get your
How you say?
Reload ammo thing. Yes dispenser
This team this team got crits what the fuck happened to my view count it says you're already waiting
I've got I felt I fell off guys. What the fuck I thought I was
Where the viewers go and it literally says you are already rating stir and it won't let me raid stir again
Oh, let me investigate
Dave Vinny they came from you. They're here now, huh?
I just got like an achievement level three good level three what level three on twitch?
I think they sent him back to me. Why is there a new rain? I turn. Oh, wait, what's going on?
I got sent to stirs. So oh, oh
Right because we're in a different chat room
It looks like the raid went through and we broke twitch I like on my raid button there's double of everybody
Here, I'll go ahead and raid stir again. Just be safe
Let's raid stir again because we've created enough people I think we're ready for another round of sending them
Wait, did I just type in stirs chat raid stir? What happens then?
It still says I have 31,000 viewers which is insane and I rated so I don't know why this is happening
But okay, so we've created like 40 or 50 thousand people. Yeah. Oh 8k now
I
Got everybody
I'm down to 8k stir got everybody. Okay, so now it has to pass it on. I think are you here?
I mean, it says 10,000 for me whenever I'm like refresher refreshing the twitch directory all the
Number you have 21k now. I think we're are we deleting viewers? I think we're yeah
I think we just started deleting people. I think Jeff Bezos like shot up out of bed cold sweat fucker. God, damn it
They're sharing viewers around like that
Dare, they yeah looking at the the TF2 directory. I think we just deleted people. Oh
I
Think it's just I think twitches doesn't know how to update this cuz I'm seeing 30 on Vinny and 20 unused er
I'm raiding poke you go poke. Why I don't have a fucking entrance. I'm sorry guys
Who am I reading? I'm reading viewers got lost in the void. They got lost in a pub
It's working even though I think I was already raiding Vinny. Yeah, we're getting like weird diminishing returns from doing this
Yeah, this wasn't well, I
Think I did all right for myself. So thanks everybody. You really got me a lot of followers the way you started it. Oh fuck
Well, I need to Chris this I guess
Hey everybody, welcome to the channel
What are we on? What are we playing poke?
We're playing tf2 with my best friends guys. Yeah, why we just met tonight gamers
Already
Why is the healer not getting hurt?
Because he has the quick fix uber. I
love
Blood you are like very much. You're playing. We're like playing a goofy funny hot potato game over here
And you're like what the kill the healer. I can't even fucking do it cuz I got YouTube
I'm trying to get through the damn round
Yeah, are you playing sad music or something? Oh, he's got my upgrades. Oh shit, that's not good
Scouts go big scouts. I got you big scouts coming in right side. Hey, do we have a sniper, right?
We can just react to you to the lovely channel. I mute it
I
Sold her to your left
Okay. Hey poke. There's somebody kill me. Somebody got raided. It came from my channel
I'm ready to stir then to have any then to you and they called me an idiot
Can you ban that person? I'm not fan of what they said. They call me stupid in your chat. Can you ban them in there for me?
Yes, this bit totally threw everything off I'm so confused we were gonna beat it on the hardest mode
All right. So where where is everybody now? I think they're here, but I'm ready. I'm ready to raid. Oh, yeah
I see my books. All right. So where have we not gone come to Papa? Yeah back to Doug Doug. Yeah, we got it
We'll circle it back to Doug. All right
rain Doug Doug
Fantastic stream today guys. Thanks for stopping by rating Doug Doug now Vinny. You have half the viewers you had before the raid
Wait, I'm trying to rate is that only a thousand
We broke something no, it's broken it's broken
All right, everybody return to your respective channels go home guys every go home
Go back to where you came from leave
Everybody go everybody go back to where they started and guess what deuce Adams?
I would say 30 to 40 percent did not think this was humorous at all and they went to go watch somebody else
Yeah, they're they're watching like we just broke someone's Samson PC
Yeah, they're sitting there trying to press the button on their remote like what the fuck did they do
Wait, this is a Sunday
There's some twitch engineer on call who just got an alert and I had to like get to his desk to fix this
I can't believe and his name got me banned from Albert Einstein. Also, too. This is that kind of weird
I I started with 70 or 80 thousand viewers
This is kind of something's wrong here. I'm down it
I don't know if anybody else is seeing that that's
70,000 people tonight. Hey, yeah, thank you for the raid man. Appreciate it. Did it go did it work?
I got 1,600 people from you
I got 1,600. Wait, I mean a couple of them came over. Okay, I'll try again
Do it again, yeah, you only got like it was like home alone you left a bunch of them behind
I'm doing a raid. This is 600 people now
Okay, it gave me an alert that it was 1,600 but it sent me 16,000 this is now my new viewership record
Thanks, everybody. Oh, I my chats gone. Hold on man. You guys really like to have to you. Yeah
Look at the directory right now. We're all up
Doing so well, you know what we can all use that like max number thing to like get like like sponsorships
I don't do with them
But you know you guys can be like yo, let's do this. Let's do this. Let's do this
Like sponsorships, I don't do with them but you know, you guys can be like yo, look at the max numbers
We're all like fucking diesel streamers. We can get like the sickest promotions from like HelloFresh or Cox dash or whatever
Wow, I'm an ad guy. I believe the highest is what he'll have all the time guys
My number isn't going down and I feel weird. What do I do now? I just restart the stream
shit your pants
shit yourself
This new product shit your pants. It's right here. I'm bringing it back to you
Keep it there if you want
Real real quick. What do we actually do with this heavy medic combo?
Head shot the medic like full burst damage the medic. Sorry. I was raiding poke. I forgot why
Kidding I didn't fall off. I was joking
Because the medic is also healing at like 10 times speed
Don't worry Germer, I'll help you refill your ranks. I
Don't know if I'm streaming. I don't know if you guys can hear me. I keep checking to see if I'm muted
I don't know what's happening. I don't know what is happening. I think stir might be muted. I haven't heard him in a while. Yeah
You bird
Medic get the medic get the medic at the medic. Well, we have time. Okay, you birdie you bird and try him
But the the medic just keeps healing
Sorry, go back to the last point. Go back to the last point. We're good
Everybody fall back to the last point
We're gonna get it right here do it
I'm raging him backwards. I rage him the wrong way. Can you fire this guy? Oh
my god
Okay, shit. I'm gonna go go go. Oh
No, big scout big scout. Yes
Dead ice job. All right. All right. That was a way eight eight eight money's eight bucks
All right, everybody. Go say hi to uncle Jerma for me
Okay, I don't know what is happening. What is happening?
You know, why'd you read me again?
It must have been a glitch from earlier. All right, we're gonna raid Jerma here
I need you more than ever. All right now, let's see where everybody ends up. Well, everybody stop
Yeah, after you guys read me will like we'll stop and we'll you know from here. We'll
Why don't we do one last any crits any crits here any crits here coaches? No, we're good
Random person and read them
50k on him. Oh, no, we need crits cuz there's six tanks
Yeah, we need crits, but they we didn't we are not worried about being attacked by crits
Let me just open my chat back up because I haven't seen it in like 20 minutes. I'm feeling very prepared for this one
I'm thinking it's a dub. Is this final round? Yeah, it's final round right wave seven to seven. I think this is it
Yeah, this is the big one
Maybe I should buy crit for me
I
Made it ammo. I'm am I was like what I always run out of crit canteens
And it's like a halfway through the mission you died by crit canteens again
Okay, if you're like have money and you're in spawn and I'll be where the fuck is my entrance. Oh, there it is
Someone came into my chat and just said how come ten minutes earlier. I saw Vinny at 31 K
Like they don't understand what happened. We've confused the chat gaslight him say it never happened
I mean
Okay, I'm gonna put my dispenser over behind this fence over here
somewhere raid stir
Yeah chat, I would always have 31 K if I didn't do the diaper chief it
Wait diapers. So I'll say diapers
Diaper chief in particular. It's a bit that my chat really really likes
What is it? Well?
There's a not ready
Seconds you guys ready in Metal Gear Solid
hmm
Do you know the DARPA chief in Metal Gear Solid?
What sure?
It it's the diaper chief. Anyway, let's kill that tank. Okay, I like it. You know what that deserves a rate. I mean, that's a good
Yeah, thanks, man
If you guys like diaper jokes and welcome over the diaper grown-ass man talking about diaper. Yeah
That's man
Diaper sauce Oh grown-ass man sauce. Hey, I wish I didn't say that about diapers. Can't talk about diapers
There are not many diaper streamers on twitch. So, you know, it's a niche that you got to fill like a diaper itself
Maybe not many like do you think there are some? Oh, yeah. Yeah
There's a few right? Yeah, it's a limited amount but
Someone's got a film we have ubered
Far
Way, we're good, right? He's dead. Yeah, he's dead giving us a boost tank time
medics
like I
Got a tank you guys won't focus other thing
I'll create you now just to work on the tank. Oh, hey, man. Thanks for the raid
But it's weird that you'd raid me and we're all still playing together. I usually like in stream
Yeah, I think I'm gonna wrap it up here, okay, that's so fucking funny
Ending send our viewers to Ludwig like just tell them to go there. No, it's not possible
Well, we can just tell everybody to go twitch to YouTube is like the trail of tears of the social world
Well, so we'll be funny is like so many will be lost along the way
It's more and then they would leave and YouTube would go. Oh people hate this stream and start recommending it
Cool I'm gonna pick someone with three viewers
Pass it along wait you
Get snipers. I'll work on the snipers. Oh, so who wants a raid?
I just got I'm gonna I'm gonna raid the fucking food is my shift over
Like we're all does it channel that?
Scout and medical, right?
Don't come here
Yes, what?
second tank
Okay
We've been doing very well
It'd be really funny if we sent someone everyone to someone that we know and then told them that we expect them to be sent
back
We don't have your emotes we don't speak your tongue here like if we come to all of us
Subs will send all over we find a small viewer. Tell him. Hey, you want this big raid, but you only have it for 10 minutes
Sounds like a mr. Beast you do your best bit you do the diaper chief fit always
I'm gonna do if you guys are
I'll do it. Oh, I thought you meant like if you were the streamer getting raided. What do you do in those 10 minutes?
You have the viewers. I'm fan. Oh, yeah, you do you your best bit I
undress Oh
Well, where are you streaming these days?
We are about I think to beat an expert aren't we? Yeah, I'm about to I'll pop you right now go
I'm really surprised pretty easy considering like we're barely paying attention at this point. Yeah, you guys did a great job. This is actually yeah
Cannot attest to that. I've been dripping sweat
Now you bit you can pull it and pull a bird big numbers. Love I've been watching you. I've been seeing what you're doing
See that I see you doing the jump spin down move. I've seen it
I do like I do to go with that. It's like stupid. Oh, it's like not even helpful
I've crit for you go. I have two more crit canteens. I'm just gonna give me one at a time go
And last one go
I'm just gonna shoot the snipers back there because they're annoying do it. Well, I think we got it
I think we do think so the the other mission remaining is I think considered to be the hardest one
Is that the like 99 wave one?
That's the one of this tour, I mean this the one of this tour is
Forget the name of it
But it doesn't look like dust bowl. It's like a whole metal city. We did it. Nice job. Yeah
I
Got no way. No way me. No way me. Give me something good, baby. Something good. Something good here
No way me. No way me nothing but a hat nothing but a hat. Come on. What is it?
Give it to me. Give it to me. Give it to me. It's
Back up
I have that already. I got that ten years ago
What the heck nobody got a hat like last time. Oh, all right. It's back up
All right gamers should this be the end here? I think a lot of fun. That's a good one. Hey, I
Want to go out heroes, so I'm worried if we escalate
That was it was awesome. Very very good time. I had
Seriously, some of the most fun I've had in a while. So yeah, this is a great game and you guys are awesome
Then why is it over? Thanks for the sick raid, by the way
So seven days of Dyson
Wouldn't be opposed. I'm in I'm in roblox boys
Walking now we're cooking I was waiting for some for some gas to come up real some real game. There you go. All right
In this disco, we'll write something in the we'll play video game next time you guys are down our video game sounds good
Thanks for organizing this appreciate you German appreciate everybody else for coming playing. No, it's great
Thanks for taking the taking the invite. Love on good games
GG's y'all is anybody else continuing to stream that I can raid? I'm gonna
Actually going to continue to be live. I'll actually you know what don't answer that it's funnier if you immediately go offline
Cuz you can rate offline channels. I don't need to actually know if you're saying well, this is now my Sunday stream
This is where I'm playing terrible stuff. So I'm gonna go do my terrible stuff after good. Bye everyone. Hey Vinny
Here come the viewers many. Thank you. Goodbye. You don't have to by the way. I'm fine, but I'll see you later
Bye. Oh before I go I've been thinking about this the whole time Jerma
You gotta play this one game and anyone else but I really want to see Jerma play this one game
Wait, wait, you don't care if I play I'm not really
I
You would hate it
Bouncing duck simulator bouncing duck simulator Vinny's other game. That's not the game you play the placid plastic duck simulator
No, it's different was a bouncing duck simulator. Oh, yeah video 100% you'd like this. I'm a big duck guy. Yeah
Sir, we'll talk later
Oh
What was it down dancing or bouncing bouncing
Actually bouncing duck simulator, you know what Doug you in this too. All right. I'm in. Yeah, let's all play it Wow
That'll be fun for you guys
He's gonna seriously hate every second of it so you can watch we'll talk
I'll do we're gonna get a call and just restream stir stream playing five nights at Freddy's. That sounds like fun
Yeah, I'll read that
I'll see you guys
All right, that was a lot of fun hopefully you guys had a good time the vibes were immaculate so I will
Didn't plan a stream in too long tonight, but I'll be live tomorrow. My voice is like dry some water
Tomorrow I'm gonna play sorcery part four. I'm gonna start it and there's also gonna be quite a few things to talk about tomorrow
monster grotto beasts
TTS mod discussion and be showing it off and something else. So grotto beast info tomorrow and
Sorcery, what about viewfinder? Yeah, I do want to play it. I do I do I do what about the BLT?
Yeah, I'll be munching on a BLT tomorrow. Of course what time probably a little later than
Today's stream. So thinking somewhere around
Hold on, you know what? Let me let me just open the last few crates that I have right like what am I?
I have one more key. Which one I have one key remaining which which crate am I gonna open with this?
Which one of these is considered a good one?
92 I don't have everything from here 92 92 92 92. Okay. It's so funny. I can still see
Raiders from different channels talking in here a raider from dug dug. When did you get when did you get here?
I'll do 92 what just happened. Yeah, it's kind of cool
All right, I will see you guys later. See you tomorrow. Are we starting around?
Probably like five Pacific somewhere around there chill with some later evening sorcery talk about some announcement stuff
Go over some stuff. It's gonna be fun and I am actually going to genuinely raid Vinny
So, I don't even know whose chat I'm in right now. Am I in my chat? There we go. Evan. He's doing his
Sunday stream. This is pokes chat right now. That's right
So, but you it says you're raiding from dug dug, but you actually were came from poke
So you might just be pokes chat. I don't know. I'm confused, but it was very fun. Talk to you guys tomorrow
See you soon. I didn't even tweet. No, I did. I don't even it doesn't really matter
I'm so disconnected from all social media Twitter
Discord I don't even like you use it tweet now, dude. I don't know
I don't tweet that the stream is over. That's a really funny joke. I mean that that's real
That's good material, but no, I don't think so. All right, good stuff. See you tomorrow. Take care. Call your mother. See you later