Hello, ladies and gentlemen. It is time for DLC Crack Night. Welcome, welcome, welcome.
Well, it's not really night yet, but it will be when it's over. This is, uh, we
might be in for a long one. At least longer than you've been used to recently.
There are 258 videos on this stream today. Maybe. Alright, listen. If we get
like five hours into this and like I can't take it anymore, like I might get
hurt. If I start, if I laugh too hard, I'm gonna get, I'm probably gonna get hurt. So
we got, we're gonna go into this very very much with we'll see. But there are
six and a half hours of videos and that has been shaved. There were hundreds and
hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of submissions. I actually was probably
gonna talk to the mods here and see if we could maybe, like we did last time, do
like an extended edition where maybe we could have, oh, here's like the, is the
extended cut with like another extra 300 videos or like 200 videos or something.
I think we did something like that last time, though. But for the stream
purposes, there are just over six and a half hours of videos. Just about six and
a half hours. And that's without any pauses in between. That's another thing
we have to keep in mind. So it's six and a half straight hours of video content.
Hurry up, hurry up. I'm not just gonna, no, I've been waiting for this for a long
time. And I haven't seen really any of these. I'm looking forward to it. I want
to wait, people gotta trickle in, man. You don't want to just start the movie
before everyone gets in. You gotta have the previews first. Now this is all you
got. It's me talking to you for a preview. When you go to the movie theater, the
movie doesn't just start at 730. The movie starts at like 755. It does. No, it
doesn't. What do you mean it does? At 730, the previews start for like 20 minutes.
And then you have to watch the same like AMC movie theater commercial where the
Coca-Cola fills up the cup really fast and it fizzes all over the place. And it's
a fucking large and they give it to this like guy that's like five, six, my size,
five, seven, five, eight. And is supposed to drink that whole thing? No. You get
this huge pot thing of popcorn. Nobody eats a jumbo popcorn. They eat the top
half or eat the top third of it. And then they can look sad and they go, fuck, I
shouldn't have got a big one. And then what? What do you think happens to it?
That's why. Did I ever tell you the time that Burger Boy brought in to the movie
theater, a bag of double cheeseburgers and ate them like popcorn? Did I ever tell
you that story? I did, right? Yeah. Yeah. But those of you that don't know, Burger
Boy went, we went to the movie theaters and he brought with him, it was his
popcorn. His movie snack was a bag of probably six or seven McDoubles. And
that's what he ate for the movie. Like it was popcorn. And if you think about it,
like, okay, see, he was taking the wrappers and he was like putting the
wrappers in the bag. And then at the very end, he squished it down to this tiny
little just small in your fist bag of waste. And he threw it in the trash. Like
fuck, fuck all this bullshit with like get a large popcorn and dump the popcorn
in the trash and this big cardboard bucket. Burger Boy was being
environmentally friendly. But yeah, he did eat seven McDoubles over the course
of about two hours. That's based. He's a king. No, he's still just a boy. He's not
Burger King. That would be copyright infringement. He's just a boy. Don't
rip. Don't forget that. You can't be Burger King. One of those already
exists. You can be King Burger. He's a sellout. What? Fuck the king. Excuse me.
Savor the king, please. Get it right. It's been rebranded. Anyways, we're gonna get
started. There's lots of videos. I'm looking forward to it. I have a
playlist. It's just gonna play. I'm gonna pause it. Well, maybe it depends on what
it is. Here we go. You guys ready? Are you ready to do this? Here, I have to prove
that I exist like once every three or four years, three or four weeks. I exist.
One thing that I have noticed about these videos, kind of funny in its own
way, is this green screen footage was taken at the absolute pinnacle, the
absolute part, the absolute in the middle of the quarantine. And my skin is like
transparent white. Hadn't been outside in probably fucking seven or eight weeks. I
have lost a little bit of weight since being on this medical problem, and I had
this quarantine haircut, and I look fucking crazy. I look, let's just be real.
Let's be honest with everybody. I gotta be honest with you. Since then, I've put
on another couple pounds. I've been alright. I've been trying to treat some
of these issues. I look really fucking crazy, but it works in a way because then
you can use it for whatever you want. Hey, you want a crazy guy in your fucking
YouTube video? I got DLC for you. There's plenty of it. You look scary. Fucking
quarantine haircut, like my haircut was like long on this side, short on this
side, like puffed up like this. I like made my face look like it's skinny. I had
like a pale white face from not being outside in like eight weeks. I lost weight
from the fucking medical shit, and I didn't even realize. Guys, I have not
looked at really any footage until like very recently. I looked at a couple
things really early on, but I didn't really grasp how crazed I actually
looked in a lot of these clips. Start the movie. The fucking
previews, alright? Yo, don't talk during the previews. Turn your phone off, guy.
You're talking during the preview. I'm the preview. None of you should be
talking. I'm the preview. You're at the movie theater right now. You're
watching. I'm the preview. Stop talking and turn your phone off now. That's what
they should do. Forget about, fuck the Coke, like, let's go get a snack in the kitchen.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Have me, I'll go full screen. Have me say, hello everybody,
welcome to the movie. Shut up, shut up, and like point around. Hey, you in the back,
shut up. Turn off that phone right now, motherfucker. And I do, it's 20 minutes
before a movie starts. Have me be so irritating that I piss everybody off for
them to either leave the movie theater or turn their phone off. I'll be like,
turn off your phone, turn off your fucking phone, you're all assholes. Like, I'll do,
it'll be 20 straight minutes. And then it'll be like, God, like, fine, Jesus, man,
shut the fuck up. Or they'll leave. And we got their money anyway. Right, folks?
Produce gave 10 subs. They'll specifically keep the phone on. No, they won't.
Because if a phone notification sound is played, there'll be microphones
around every, by the way, there'll be microphones at every seat. You'll lean in
and go, Hey, what just happened? I went to the bathroom. Like I pop up on the
screen. Seat 21. Seat 21B. Talking during the movie. Talking. And then everyone
will know. They'll go, what if you fart? Oh, excuse me in seat 1A. We've got a
farter here. We've got a farter in 1A. What a weird like fucking dictator movie
theater I run. You ready for the movie? Uh-huh. Funny stream. He farted. Oh, my
thumb. You guys thumbs do this? Oh, it looks weird. What a great preview to the movie.
Hey, you guys, you guys thumbs do this too? Oh, yeah. Cool. Do they? Wow. Okay. Hey, enjoy
hereditary. All right. You guys ready? This is called Jerma Family Road Trip.
This is video one. I think they're just random. Stoned? I'm, no, I'm not.
If I was stoned, I'd be going like this. Hey, you guys ready to fucking go? Go.
I'm stalling because I want people to be here, all right? I'm not clicking play
until at least 30,000 people are here. You gotta, I've got my ego to take care of.
Three, two, one, let's go. Hey, mom. You are in big trouble. Hey, mom. Hey, I'm gonna go to
McDonald's. Mom, what if I'm gonna go to work, bitch? Only McDonald's. We're a McDonald's
family for Christ's sake. We only eat McDonald's. Oh, excuse me. Some of us are trying to sleep.
It's just me in the same shirt. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. We can't just go one to
the other. Okay. That was, that was awesome. Turn off autoplay. Hold on. Autoplay is off already
because this is a playlist. I don't know. Autoplay is not on. I don't have a button for it.
No, we're not doing rapid fire. I'm in a playlist. It autoflays. Ready? This is called going higher.
Pretty good. Welcome to hell. I want to see that one again. I want to see that one again.
That was perfect. Can you see my heart through the shirt? Welcome to hell. Hey, welcome back to
I murder you. My ASMR channel that I run before the video starts, before I virtually murder you.
Just please give me a thumbs up and a like and spread the video around to show to your parents,
you know, and try to get me some followers. Yeah. Okay. Let's get started.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. Why is sneaking around ASMR?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Did I come and kill you in real
life? What? While you're watching the video? Look at that neck. That neck is made out of like stone.
That's not even a human neck. That was carved. What are even are these? What even are these veins?
All right. Coming up next, we've got creepy guy sells you a toy. Okay. Here we go.
Existence. I'm certain of that. And I'm giving it to you. That's right. Take it. It's yours.
$400. That's the rare Pog. What are they called? Pog Pops. That's the rare Pog. That's slimer with
the hot dogs in his mouth. I made I bought I bought it for 500. I thought it was going to
keep appreciating and it didn't. It went down in price a little bit, but it's still worth $400.
$400. Wait, why am I getting like arrested? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on. Welcome to hell. This is illegal to sell a Funko pop. That's because I'm scamming. Oh,
I made I bought I bought it for 500. I thought it was going to keep appreciating and it didn't.
It went down in price a little bit, but it's still worth $400. In reality, it's worth about 20.
It's worth 20. Okay, this next one is called once in a lifetime. German edit. Oh, I have to make the
I got to make this really clear. Let me get on cam for this. This is really important shit.
Here we go. Here we go. So stop. Hold on. There are going to be spoilers for movies and TV shows
you have never seen before. I'm certain of it. So just listen to me when I tell you there are
going to be spoilers in this stream for TV shows that you have probably wanted to watch that now
you've seen like the last four episodes already. This is a music video. Well, maybe you haven't
even heard the song yet. I'm just saying I got to make this clear. I got to give the warning
right now that like you I don't know. I have no idea what's in it. I don't know what's in here.
I have this is new to me too. So I can't wait to get like season eight of the walking dead spoiled
for me. It's probably going to happen just to let you know. Okay. Once in a once in a lifetime.
Yeah, it's an intentionally bad like cartoon character haircut.
When did I? I'm doing this. Vod's fucked. The Vod's fucked in all of these.
Is this the music video shot for shot? Is that what we're watching? Okay. This next one is
Jerma is count Duke. Who's awful something awful apprentice. Oh yes. It's a star wars one first
star wars one of the night books. Get ready. Chancellor, you all right? Get help. You're
gonna match for him. He's a sixth lord. We don't want to make a mess of things in front of the
chancellor. Wait, what? He killed me. My powers have doubled since the last time we met count.
What does his son just bring your idiot kid to work day?
Wait, what is he doing to me?
Shit, I shouldn't do it. Oh, no, no, no. I gotta see that again.
Chancellor, I gotta see. Wait, why is he killing me? Why does he kill me?
I supposed to be dead.
I'm so glad somebody used this.
It's so stupid. Why would you lightsaber do that?
Was it an ice cream cone? Why a lightsaber is as easy to fall off as like a one scoop ice cream?
Shit. Oh, my God. That was fucking hilarious. Okay. This one is called Germa meets Zelda.
Jesus. Yeah, we're gonna link to the we'll link to the whole playlist at the end. You'll be able
to watch it as many times as you want. Okay, I'm ready. I've composed myself. Germa meets
Zelda. Why didn't I fly off the screen? This one's called Germa sings us a song. Sing solid notes.
Okay, sweat. Oh, God.
It's pretty good. It was hitting those notes. Yeah. This is like when somebody does a Hey,
I did this theme song with like 10 of me doing different instruments and beatboxing.
So I didn't do any of this. Somebody else did. I made a couple of strange noises. I loved it.
And about to look and let me tell you something. And look at this. Look at this shit. And we got
like three or four seconds of black for me to pause it and go. I loved it. All right,
coming up next. Fortnite. Germa can't wait. Fortnite default dance. Let's see if I can
pull this from memory. Is it like? Is it? That's a single ladies dance. I don't know it. I was
gonna do orange t shirt kid. That's the only one that I know. That really is the only thing that
I know. All right. I see in the corner already. I see this is a this is Nickelodeon. This is
I don't know what this is. This is probably a spoiler for a TV show. It's probably I don't
know what TV I don't know what's a spoiler for a TV show. Here we go. TV is this from Legend of
Korra. This is a Legend of Korra episode. Just if you're in the middle of watching Legend of Korra
right now and you're like, Oh shit, I got to go. Go. And they come back in exactly one minute.
Okay. Three, two, one. A lot of mileage out of the break dance. Yeah, seems so.
We seem to be getting a lot of mileage on the break dance, which is a good thing,
because that's what made me had to take three months off of doing any strength. Hope you used
it. That was the sole reason why I was like, probably should figure out what the fuck is
wrong with me. See, I don't look like the guy that is in that video. All right. This is called
Jerma gets an S rank. You do. I know S rank. Okay. We've seen, okay, this is the best part of the
one we're about to watch is there has been like six or seven Velociraptor Jurassic Park scenes.
And I'm so happy that here comes another one. Cause I already, I just saw a spoiler. I saw the
new Raptor and we're just, I let's, okay, let's go. You know, what's going to happen. You know,
the whole video. Wait a minute. What? If you were these two kids, you'd be like, all right,
there was like a frat party down the street. We're fine. Let's get the fuck out of here.
Hello episode one. Not real kids. We're not a real dinosaur.
Okay. Hold on. I want to see. Hold on. From like, I'm right here. I have to see this again.
Wait a minute. What? That's the best part. To episode one. Not even have JermaCraft
either. Just episode one. It's not real kids. We're not a real dinosaur. Oh, that was great.
That was awesome. Okay. Coming up next we have shit. What really happens during a German nine
eight five P break. Oh fuck me. Jesus Christ. Who's in here with me?
I was curious to how people were going to do guy goes down the water slide.
I was like, wait, is anybody even going to use this fucking footage for anything?
Yeah, I don't like your shit. You think I need this? I go bare ass. Is that implying that I go,
I go to the bathroom into that? I don't understand. It's supposed to be guy goes down. It does. I
can't even, who cares about the context of the original clip. It doesn't matter. All that matters
is what the product, right? Okay. Here we go. Jerma plays Quidditch, but Snape hates him. Okay.
Okay. If you're not a bunch of idiots. Excuse me. Can we be quiet, please? Leave it to me.
Some of us are trying to sleep. Come on. Come on. Oh my God.
Stay right here. Toothbrush. I can't do it. I can't do it. I can't do it. Up and smoke.
Every single animal on earth. There's an elephant. I found elephants.
Okay. I think I might need to take like a year off after that one. I was leaning back and just
dying. That was fucking crazy. That was crazy. I want to, I have to see it again.
Mr. Potter. If you're not a bunch of idiots. Excuse me. Can we be quiet, please? Leave it to me.
Some of us are trying to sleep. Oh my God. Minecraft arrow. Brush. I can't do it. Up and smoke.
Every single animal on earth. There's an elephant. I found elephants.
Oh, that was amazing. That was unbelievable. Okay. When you hear Jerma Collins is coming up next.
Okay. This is a Spider-Man one. This is Jerma and Peter get paid. Apparently.
And you pinned them in two. For that, I give you a hundred and you're lucky to get that.
What? I need that money. I missed the part where that's my problem.
Why am I here? Hey, what the hell? I need that money. All right. What, what do you want?
The bat or the frying pan? You don't get the choice. I'll be taking that way. He stole the game.
Excuse me. My exit now. He could look at me. Thanks for the fucking crazy amount of money.
You could have taken that guy apart. Now he's going to get away with my money.
I need that money. What the hell? I don't even. Okay. I've seen, I have seen Spider-Man and I
don't even know what happened. Does that happen in Spider-Man? I don't, I don't remember. I feel
like that was two, three movies put together. It's been a long time. Okay. E-Clown Asylum.
Arkham. Transformers transform into object of flight.
Fucking bones. I'm an SCP.
Hey, welcome back to I murder you.
That was scary at the end. That was fucking scary. Okay. Here we go. This is
Jerma PG character customization. Get ready for a real jock shocker. I talk a lot of shit. I
fly off the handle. I get angry, but I'm disciplined about it. I speak very, very clearly,
influently and intelligently. You just walk in and you just go like, I'm selecting the character.
Okay. Quarantine or unkempt. Yeah. Voice? No, that's a motion. Hey, look at this nice ass.
What's my destiny? Slugger, disaster or magician? What's happening guys? Jerma here for the 2000
subscriber. What do you guys want to do? I can, I can barely do any. Stuck in my robes.
Am I a wizard yet? Oh, he wants to be a wish. That's what I just did on camera too, by the way.
I just did that exact same thing off camera. Oh man. That was awesome. There was a lot of detail
going on there. There was a ton of detail. This is called the Jerma house. Lighthouse.
This is the lighthouse. Okay. Oh, thank you. Okay. Thanks for saying that. Cause I have to
make it really clear that I'm going to, someone's going to ruin your movie for you. We know, but I
know. But you, everybody says that until their favorite movie gets spoiled. I don't care.
Infinity war. Yeah. I've seen that one. Oh, shut up about spook hands about spoilers. Wait,
this is the lighthouse. Wait. Oh, I haven't seen a lot. I got to get out of here quick.
All right. This is a one minute and 40 seconds of the lighthouse. All right. Of me, of me being
like all over it and ruining it. Here we go. Yeah. Yeah. You want me to walk around like I'm
a fucking monster and start fighting people, hating people. That's what you want me to do,
but I'm not going to do that. I've got a brain up here and it works just fine. Oh, by the way,
I got a 4.0 GPA in college. What did you have? What the fuck was that? So I heard who'd you got
to fight today, son. I seen you swarming with a goat. Okay. Let's leave him be. Let me tell you
something. If you can do not do it diplomatically, then you shouldn't be doing it at all. I heard
that you punched him. Did you, you punched him? You punched him in the face. My son doesn't do
that. I'm sure I don't. Diplomacy only. You know how much trouble I can get in? More tall tales.
I'm in the zone. You know what? I can, I'll handle it. You are grounded.
You're grounded. We don't fight in this family. Eat your gosh darn life. I keep saying that stuff
and I don't want to. Welcome. What the fuck? Welcome back. Okay. I, whatever. Here's the
thing about these clips. They have been transformed so, so ridiculously that I don't even know.
I, that, that could have been any movie, right? Like that could have been, that literally could
have been anything that I've seen in my whole life. Okay. This is called German becomes a
YouTuber. Here we go. Welcome back. Hey everybody. Guess where I am. That's right. On vacation. Take
a look. I never get to go out of places like this. That's so much fun for me. And before we video
get started, if you could please give me a thumbs up for being on vacation. Well, you're not on
vacation. You're doing all this cool fun shit and you're not. And I'm going to continue to do
all kinds of really cool shit. And you're just going to watch me do cool shit.
Well, the plinketto board, that sure worked out great. God, that looks like fun. That looks like
a lot of fun. I wish I could get up there. Is this, is this red letter media? Hello. Welcome to
another episode of best of the worst. I'm Mike. My name's German nine eight five. What? I'm a huge fan
of yours. I get guys sick and I, I, well, okay. You don't mind. I'm really sweating right now.
Okay. So I spin the wheel. I'll spin the wheel. You look okay.
Did it go the other way? Yeah. Oh fuck. Yes. We're going to be going through our fursuit crushes.
Wait, what? He's killing me. Oh, he's a very sweet suitor.
So, um, he's a, he's a dancer. Yeah. I just get lost in his eyes. He's so dreamy. He's got real
nice eyes. You can just kind of stare at them for a while. Ken confirm is a good cuddler. He's got
a real nice curl on his suit and he's also a YouTuber. That's right. He is. Hey, your memories
have arrived. Huh? That's real cute. Photo dome. Look at that. First one. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
hold on. Look at that. Okay. The one on the left, seriously, I'm sorry. I have to pause this.
The one on the left looks like a colored pencil version of the one on the right. Like that one
on the left is like a good piece of art crayons and stuff. The one on the right is a person.
What is the thing on the left that looks like a police sketch? Yeah, it does. That looks like a
police sketch of a person scuffed footage of you. Okay. Let's go. That's real cute. Photo dome.
Look at that. First one is the sky. Skies can be cool sometimes, I guess. That's a rock.
The pretty interesting growth of a rock. The way that it was growing out of the ground was pretty
cool. I'm getting like deja vu right now. It doesn't make any sense. These are fucking terrible.
Did I do this exact same thing and go, oh, this looks like shit? This happened the last time.
It's in a twilight zone. Holy shit. Twilight zone. Oh, this is an alien. A bug is going to blow
out of my head. My head is going to explode and those two eyes are bug eyes that has taken over
my body. And the rest of the body is where my nose is. And it's like a big reveal. Holy shit.
Hey, what's going on, everybody? I am here on vaca... Do it fucking right. Oh my god. So bad.
That stupid ass channel. Okay, Jeremy goes to war. Wow. Do you see this? Do you want it? Here,
take it. What the fuck? Take it. Take this from me. Take this from me. Take this from me right now.
Take it from me. Take it from me, dude. I don't want to fucking hold it anymore. Take it from me.
Take this thing out of my fucking hands before I freak out. Take it from me. Take it. Take it
from my fucking hands. Take it from me. Take it. You don't have to take it from my fucking hands.
I love it. Let's keep going. Going up next is Jermball.
Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. No. That was... One more. One more. One more. One more.
Jeremy gets kidnapped by his psycho crush.
Hey. Hey. Now I only have eight more hours to go.
That was Joel playing Desert Bus. Okay. That was pretty good. Pretty good. Pretty good.
The best of TF2 featuring German 98... The best taunts of TF2 featuring German 985.
All right. This is the killer solo.
I got to dance. I got to dance.
Jermball plays in a game show. No. That is... No. That is not Joe Biden. Okay. I'm seeing a lot
of people say Joe Biden. That's not Joe Biden. It's not. That is Bob Barker.
It is. Okay. But it's all blurry and like scuffed up.
Okay. Let's go. For bids today. It's exciting. Kayak equipment.
Kayak will go to the one of you four who bids nearest to the actual retail price without
going over. Lisa, what do you bid? $1,000. $1,000. Kimberly. $1,800. Crystal. $8.59.
$8.59. Jeremy. Yes. What is? $12. That's right. I think I have a kid with a problem here in
Contestant Square. Have security standing by. Please. Actual retail price. $17. Wait. Me?
Wait. Me? I get it? I get it. No way. Jeremy, you have to beat 75 cents to take over the lead.
He has to beat 75 cents to take over the lead. He just won $10,000. And now he has 35 cents.
Spin it again. Spin it again, Jeremy. Jeremy would love to see 65
cents on that wheel, but he won't. He saw it, but it went by. This is not going to work out. No.
I lost. I know you guys can't say anything on TV. Thank you. It was a pleasure.
All right. You tell you, this is a new way to play this game.
Is it broken? Can't you see it? Look, it's broken.
Seriously, I have a hearing pain. Do it again. Again. Again. Okay. How about from just right
here? All right. I'm going to mute this time. What is? $12. That's right. I think I have a
kid with a problem hearing him. Have security standing by, please. Actual retail price, $17.
Me? Wait, me? I get it. I get to go. $17. You have to beat 75 cents to take over the lead.
To beat 75 cents to take over the lead. He just won $10,000. And now he has.
$6,500.
in it again jeremy jeremy to see 65 cents on that wheel but he won't he saw it but it went by
this is not gonna work out no i fucking i lost fucking i know you i can't say it in that form tv
thank you it was a pleasure
all right you tell you this is a new way to play this game is it broken can you just see
it look as if it's broken okay we had a bunch of subs but i just want like you guys have
found such great places to put this shit it's hilarious i'm so i'm so glad uh we have 50
community subs from freddy dredd freddy thanks for the 50 subs holy shit it's like it's like 50
subs a day from freddy freddy dredd gives like 50 to 100 subs like every other stream it's
ridiculous i can't i i could pay for like a house with the amount of money that freddy dredd has
given me thank you for the 50 community subs freddy dredd and thanks for the house too
i might as well say hey thanks for the house go buy a house buy a house
thanks freddy it's crazy what you're doing and it's completely unnecessary just know what you're
doing you don't have to do it you really don't it's a lot of money man it's it's a crazy amount
of money i can't wait to buy you a nice steak dinner at denny's that's right you get to order
off the dinner menu not the breakfast lunch menu uh but 50 subs we have five from ajax the mediocre
10 from captain squiggly thanks both of you five from ferd and five from morning maple thanks you
guys all of you for subbing the fucking channel let's keep going thank you all of you it's crazy
amounts of money to give anybody you don't have to do that for me don't you don't have to don't
ready what is your name are you excited to be here that's pretty good
what are you gonna say i don't know what i'm supposed to be doing really
you believe that you can win you and me i know yeah we're gonna do it we and you are gonna do this
yeah okay the stage is yours good luck i've wanted to do this for a very long time this feels great
i can do this and i can do this
no no no that's all right sorry sorry i just
like
that was good there yeah living beautiful walking
miracle love people not knowing your name is so right and so wrong because i think the world
is gonna know your name i think right now because you are going what oh okay what happened
okay to the roof that was absurd the point right into the camera that was good oh what a psycho
okay this is psych psychotronic germa it was the live button oh psychotronic germa
okay to the roof
didn't we just see this one with the nickelodeon clip
i have no fucking idea man don't ask me i don't i have no idea what that was but i mean i was
it was a who it doesn't matter uh metal gear solid a metal gear germa here we go
two f-16s just took off from galena and are headed your way fucking idiot i gotta go
germa look out there's a tank up ahead you're probably wondering who i am let's just say i'm
your biggest fan smile it's a backseater
let's fight
good game nice guy nice guy
ladies and gentlemen turn it up turn it up get to shut this off okay uh this is germa 985 the third
body rock
oh
you
that was great that was i loved it that was amazing a lot of work went into that one that was a lot of
editing uh germa celery man they don't know this is this is from paul rud doing he was on tim and
eric's awesome show which is required reading for this stream by the way so is steve brol here we go
what will your first sequence of the day be computer load up celery man please yes
could you kick up the uh 43 d3 d3 d3 d3 engaged
and sequence oyster
uh give me a printout of oyster smiling okay
i don't think any of you knew that i could do this boston break dance
oh no what no no no wait wait why kicking me out of the server no no no i've been voted off
the best part of a title here is law and order hopefully mute safe if you have to write hopefully
mute safe in the title it's probably not mute safe here we go the intro okay what is this picture
of which where did you get that photo i know that was awesome yeah that was that's a that's a clap
that's a clap right there we had five more subs from adventure mf dan and five from rare pepe
body lotion thanks guys gerbil misses change shirt wait jesus christ god i did not expect that
at all i did not expect that would caught me off guard i'm so caught me off guard that was
fucked up jesus okay anyways uh another 50 fucking subs came in from phylactery lich this time
so that's a ton of money dude thank you guys are giving too much money i can't even man 101
top spot what's that what does it what's 101 mean holy shit i think the stream was just one two three
four five viewers for like one second does anybody get a screenshot of that oh thanks
with this stupid i want to fucking money thank you phylactery germa 95 news special report
good evening everyone welcome back to the germa 985 news station i am newsbot 3200 filling in for
newsbot 2200 and i am joined by my co-anchor fireman is he doing anything tonight we bring
you a tragic event that occurred last night at the rat burger high school during their prom night
a mysterious yeti attacked the school causing the injury of several students and indirectly
starting a fire in the school we go live to reporter germy on the scene germy used germy hello
can you hear us that's your cue wait what happened hello well we'll check in on him later
recently a video of the incident was posted onto youtube under the title wow wacky yeti
killed my friends lmao why is on my channel viewers that the following footage may be
disturbing yeah i'm really enjoying the school dance stop doing the ad we interviewed several
bystanders for their thoughts on the footage hey it's got a pretty good point who needs more
fruits and vegetables and mixing together and okay i go what do you want what do you want
i better watch my fucking stream whoa when i oh he's falling he's killing me
we will bring you developments as they occur wait it appears germy has noticed he's supposed to be
reporting live germy oh hey remember me i'm that guy that's supposed to be live right now for the
last two hours how are you and look at what it looks like now look at how it's it looks
fucking fine it's fixed i here's the have one here okay listen hear me up i've got to tell
you something right now it's very very important you need to hear this um so i in plugged in right
now is oh we seem to have lost signal with germy accidentally and not on purpose how unfortunate
in other news popular cleaning supplier toilet sheriff has filed for bankruptcy after a disastrous
marketing campaign spirit oh thanks to modern editing here's uh that was that one was that one
was crazy i want to mix uncut germs i don't know if you've ever you may never seen that movie this
might be an adam sandler thing uncut gem spoilers incoming also clap hope they don't spoil i hope
they don't spoil the movie i've seen uncut gems i hope they don't spoil anything thanks to modern
editing techniques we can use existing footage to complete the film well i'm germa 985
watch you see on this channel i like to call myself dr jekyll and mr germa because i i have
two different sides i have my fun i have my professional side and i i mold them together
into sort of this lunacy that is you come to my store you come to my city my name is ato this is
well i'll tell you what i know it's the dumbest fucking bet i ever heard of is it like a currency
thing or i mean what what is it
this is me this is how i win
seamless huh you're fired and with good cause that was fucking awesome
clap clap clap clap clap the best archer on germa craft come on almost got him you stay right there
punk oops right between the eyes what about you stay there stay there oh did he shoot me
or did i okay did i shoot myself with the bow did it come back and hit me no he shot me
oh my fucking god uh jordle is up next but dude okay 50 more subs from chris weed piano
that's a great name i don't know anything about it i don't know what like the context or like
inside joke that is but like chris weed piano that's uh that's that's cool that's a cool name
thanks for the 50 subs that's a lot of money people are giving me too much money
thank you the lemmy 20 subs and slimes are brown thanks to 19 subs this is a lot
jamie 28 228035 community subs you guys just like to shower me with gold coins thank you
that's fucking ridiculous jordle
don't step in that it's a toilet you know what i mean i totally got you hello and again welcome
to the aperture science computer aided enrichment center we hope your brief detention in the
relaxation vault has been a pleasant one your specimen has been processed and it has been
noted as being below average height in the event of a tall shelf a weighted storage
cube will be provided for you to stand on before we start however keep in mind that although fun
and learning are the primary goals of all enrichment center activities serious injuries
may occur for your own safety and the safety of others please refrain from
the portal will open in three two one
oh fucking weirdo congratulations the test is now over all aperture technologies remain
safely operational up to 4 000 degrees kelvin and ice cream are on its way goodbye
so i just die wait so i just die oh well that's unfortunate uh coming up next is
germa dances till we're all dead the name of the song the song okay the song is called till we're
all dead
it's pretty good this is pretty good
drop it
bod i what i can't fix the bod it's destroyed and i feel like i'm doing that thing where i'm
leaning really close into your ear at any oh the music stops good if i can talk to you shit
screams over it's not though it's still going i was doing the thing where i was leaning into
your ear at the party or at the bar desperately trying to communicate with you and if the bar or
club or whatever they had just turned the music down by even 25 percent there's nothing i hate
more than not being able to talk to anybody i'm out with or that i'm doing anything with it sucks
it's stupid i don't understand it if i have to yell over a vacuum cleaner to talk to you
i don't want to go there just turn the fuck turn the music down just a little turn it down turn
that music down now creature runs in a glass door and fake uh french bakery program
herma rides the spinny chair looks like fun looks like a lot of fun i wish i could get up there
oh get them off get them off i'm gonna die herma strikes again no more heroes
they fixed all the kind of annoying bullshit that is in this game
but i still think this game's really good i still like this one all right here we go coffee cheetos
chicken what the fuck drink nine didn't think i had fucking life saver didn't you
i guess it was a little entertaining this is the end boom bada bing sorry about the wait
i had to pee my pants episode one of germa crap the strawberry on the shortcake
yeah somebody used it oh it's not wait doesn't end that's not the end of the video
do you i don't do you want it here take it take it take it take it take this from me take this
take this from me right now take it from me take it from me dude i don't fucking hold it anymore
take it from that was good too all right the musical man excuse me can we be quiet please
some of us are trying to sleep
fucking
you can probably imagine i'm gonna need some water i'll be back that was great good get some water i
have a woman it's right in front of me okay hold on this is okay this is from the movie hereditary
all right okay thank you i really appreciate that i'm gonna leave this on the screen for five
seconds wow thank you for this i've seen this movie if you haven't you know what's happening
you know what's about to happen i'm just trying to warn you right now okay i haven't seen it i'm
just come back in two minutes and 28 come back in three minutes i'm trying to give you an opportunity
here's the opportunity right now just take it if you haven't seen it take please i don't want to
ruin movies for you three two one go you okay man what i don't think it's possible just seems
like there might be something you want to say oh i had a long day at work i got fired well i mean
it's kind of it's kind of insane son son son son son son just say it just fucking say it
let me tell you something if you can do not do it diplomatically then you shouldn't be doing it at
all i heard that you punched him did you you punched him you punched him in the face my son
doesn't do that diplomacy only you know how much trouble i could get in i'm in the i'm in the gosh
darn who i'm getting heated here my son a united states representative that's your i'm your dad
yeah i'm the representative not you that would be strange now wouldn't it you got to do things
diplomatically or you're ground no you know what stop i can i'll handle it now you are grounded
you're grounded we don't fight in this family i'll eat your gosh darn i i keep saying that stuff and
i don't want to now down to business we gotta go to grandma's house
wait what what oh okay all right all right uh that was fucking great five community subs from
burmy loop thank you for me loop for the five fucking subs
taunt demonstration the boston break dance wait didn't we do this already oh this is another one
how much is mine wait this is a real
is it what is actually in tf2 it is when do they put that in here we go this one's called
german tetris uh by the way this is a real game okay so this is this is a playable game
and i'm going to play there are i think three games that people have made and i'm going to
play all three of them i'm not going to play them today we're going to open with that
when i come back next time because i want to be able to play them and not just skip through them
real quick so we're going to play all three of the germa mod games some of them are mods some
of them are not it's malware hey they've been scanned okay they've been scanned but that's
going to be fun and that that's awesome i can't wait uh exploded hornets entry one i don't know
what this is the germa disappeared i needed to find out what had happened i managed to find
these tapes of the last video he recorded i tried to piece them together the best i could
marble hornets what's marble hornets marble hornet spoiler is that a show that sounds like
a show name that sounds like like an anime marble hornets okay well this is a spoiler
for marble hornets i don't know what season welcome back everybody guess where i am
um that's right on vacation take a look i never get to go out of places like this
so it's so much fun for me look at that it's a it's a palm tree can you believe it i feel like
i need like a fire behind me you know what i mean wouldn't that be better if there was like a
fucking fire right here wait wait hold on a second wait what that would be fucking terrible
oh what was that i gotta go oh my fucking lord
definitely was following germa and i don't know what i'm going to keep searching to find answers
wouldn't it be funny if this is real hot just kidding be careful though there's apparently
a giant rat around oh ben elinor fifty dollars five thousand fucking bits this is like six
hundred seven hundred dollars in not even an hour and a half thanks guys take care of yourself
first again like i told you you put me like ten rows down take care of yourself first pay for i
don't i don't take don't care about me first ever i'm getting a lot of fucking money and you don't
you don't have to do it take care of yourself take care of your friends family members loved ones
hobbies passions or you do anything to me if you ever do drugs no no give no no no not drugs
all right put me above drugs don't put drugs above me no put me above drugs i believe i think i
deserve to be there uh but thanks to the fucking 50 bucks hope you're well remember to drink milk
i don't i'm almond milk for me i didn't say soy milk so all the fucking people on the internet
here can have a little bit of a break that's not what i said i said almond milk let's go
germa mom germa mon stadium what the fuck holy shit you miss that one why does it do the narrow
tone run that was awesome hold on yeah i didn't i guess i didn't realize when i first watched it
this is a fully rendered 3d fireman animation i didn't really even think about i was like oh
yeah i guess i didn't my brain didn't process it was there this is awesome
that's so awesome
and you can get your fireman 3d innovation for two dollars and 99 cents in the dlc of pokemon
turbo all right someone anyone cut germa's mic
i got my friend over this is my buddy oh that was great that was unbelievable i have to just hold on
okay here's the question though those of you if you were a huge fan
right you're in the audience this is happening do you boo or do you cheer
which one i feel like you try because you don't want to boo because they're doing the song there
you're there you're a big fan of the band but this guy's ruining everything i feel like it'd be like
i don't know would you like talk to security i feel like it'd be like yeah nice job i love you
guys and you go like to a bathroom break you grab a security guard hey man um i fucking paid like
145 dollars for these seats dude like i'm here with my fucking girlfriend that guy sucks can't
can we i just want i came here to see the fucking rolling stones dude can we do something about
that like maybe i feel like that would happen i don't think i would be screaming i would
cheer the band on but i would be like i would want it to change okay let's go germa trek the
next germeration i got my friend over this is my buddy this is my buddy dan right tv's right there
and i'm watching star trek
last time on germa trek the next generation get out of the fucking way i am going to kill him with
my bare hands i will take him by the throat like a whip out of the sop of this dwarf
the enterprise has encountered the enterprise coming into visual range what last it's two
enterprises on viewer hey man welcome to the stream my name is germa nice to meet you right
there bingo right there's a follow button if you click that life signs there is no indication of
life and i do lots of fun things on this stream like uh playing hitman we played that last night
that it's right there i'm captain picard of the uss enterprise get to shut this off shut them all
turn your lights on your house off too watch my fucking stream don't you tell me what to do
kill it
more breaches eminent
weapon smoke
wait there's another episode we're registering very curious readings from all censors
come on try thunder for a clean machine
fascinating
captain i think you better take a look at this
idiots we can use a tractor to use that nobody use that you'll be in big trouble what
so i just go around the galaxy and harass everybody
didn't think i could do that did you make contact with this right
you was it one arm in the air holy shit i gotta change clothes after this one
so cake anyone captain i made the most scrumptious cake
happy birthday
i can't believe you used that that's a i've never heard that in like four years
like wait i have to go back i have to go back i have to go back i'm missing everything
cake anyone captain i made the most scrumptious cake happy birthday
happy birthday
hold on can wait wait wait wait wait no no that's not what i want to do that's not what i want to
do i got my friend over this is my buddy that's can i just say this guy this guy is fucking
holy shit this is a superhero who the fuck is it was there a superhero was captain america
in star trek it's like the biggest guy i've ever seen
but his name was brachula what's his name bacula dracula not brachula
bacula okay his name was scott dracula scott brachula okay all right all right all right
here we go the next one's called germa okay this is harry potter spoilers i know there are people
trust me i know he's a boy i'm gonna minus dude i'm gonna people gonna yell at me dude we know we
don't shut up stop this like there's like almost 13 000 people here one of you is don't know you
know what i mean so harry potter spoilers incoming to another year at home your target is dumbledore
the clock is ticking 47 good luck wait what that's not i don't know how to put a tie on
i don't know how to put a tie on who's that teacher talking to professor quarrel
oh that's professor snipe head of slithering house
pretty mature on that one don't want to be evil too quickly i stand for you think you can do me
severus please all targets neutralized excellent work 47 you know they say the stars align
for this wine
is with the teleporting what's with the teleporting that was here comes germa goes to the beach
we do a pee break all right we'll do a pee break after this
around hey sing it hey man you know i quit i quit that shit i gotta get my tools oh god damn
hello ladies and gentlemen welcome to episode one of germa craft the series where i play mine
craft this is gonna be a single player let's play building terrain oh my god this is so exciting
this is episode one i was spooked i almost did i really did absolute perfection in the key that
our souls were singing as we danced in the night i remember how the stars stole the night away
you've seen the size of my arms
i thought you were somebody that i'll say that i know dancing in september oh you want to fight
fight okay that's like a 400 you a big f but fuck you for controversy making fun of me
oh wait wait wait i was uh i need to address this on stream again because listen did i eat any
tomatoes last night so this is the virtual world and am i gonna have any oranges today i need more
this is what happens when you do too many drugs i'm in the middle of a check that's all i hear
that's all i hear shut up shut up i like don't care about sonic the hedgehog anymore
okay i didn't want to i didn't want to knock you out but i did i'm on crack like i'm on crack
today i don't know what's going on here it's it's crack that's a little too high for me
come on one chicken please that'll be two dollars that those those don't cost that cost way way less
than that i have 10 of those only a few of these left in existence i'm certain of that and i'm
giving it to you okay i don't know what that is but are you sure son thank you so much here
take it thanks i gotta go excuse me yeet that's you up there you're going down i'll make sure
you're changing my super flying jet monster jet monster activate did anybody use this for
an actual monster is it just gonna be me on the green screen didn't think i could do that did you
baby
shit it worked be brave motherfuckers hey man welcome to the pirate boat my name is
pirate germa nice to meet you and don't forget about me i'm compact
are you a pirate oh i'm not a pirate i'm a i'm a i'm a begging e-clown accurate
jump i have nothing to do with this okay what do i have to say for a small person
what's up man cowabunga dude here we go yes this sucks okay that video was awesome but don't you
feel like that you just watched that video inside of a dream of you watching that video that was a
that was a video you watched in a dream it was crazy there's so much to unpack on with that one
you could watch that one 10 times since it's a different movie every time all right we're
gonna take a pee break i told i promised one person they were like please dude i'm gonna
piss my pants and i'm like all right we will be right back grab yourself water here's intermission
number one wait a minute i'm back out of water under the bathroom let's go this one's called
germa pain max pain okay here we go so glad i got to go to your birthday party stay there stay there
holy shit just listen to me i don't want to fucking i don't want to shoot any of you relax wait i'm
not this is not jeffrey's birthday party yeah no no relax relax man we got one job dude we're
gonna do that job hey hey hey hey hey hey put it down come on man relax my name is dr andrew
michaels pleased to meet you okay hold on a minute what what's going on here okay that that was
this is called germa gets an mri did you pay somebody to do this my name is dr andrew michaels
pleased to meet you this is an actor that you hired to do this he's in front of a green screen
this is an awesome wait is this also a green screen guy all right hold this all on we're here
for a brain scan wait wait me wait me i wait i get it no don't worry we're gonna get to it right
away because i have to say that i am a fucking moron and i have the iq of a six-year-old and i
i have i i might be in the dv for a couple hours and you've signed your here you go form
form
that's not me okay don't sell it though i don't know don't sell it do not sell that i think we're
ready to go am i supposed to be dead i've done this hundreds of times nobody's ever been harmed
what
twitch chat making his debut trying to come in and call me all kinds of fucking names and shit
is good yeah fuck twitch chat get it out of here it's art it's quiet i just all right i saw
i saw something fucked up arena no no don't eliminate me don't eliminate me twitch chat
i am a machinima partner
slugman's not 30 years old yet don't even say that to a person
has to be depressed so slugman
your brain is a masterpiece of evolution and design i can see the image of god and the design
of your brain looking at it on the scanners watching all the neurons flashing
truly puts me in touch with the creator of the universe this is amazing what a discovery
talking telepathically to you you could literally run this department this guy's
so fucked hey he can't hear me because i'm talking telepathically to him so i can talk out loud
i can say whatever i want about this fucking asshole oh god well this has been a lot for you
so you need your sleep and you need your rest it's time for you to go to bed that was great
that was fucking crazy that was i don't even know what to think about that one
oh that that one was all right i had to look look don't skip it it's all right i die whatever i know
2020 hindsight i saw i saw something up somebody's ass okay and i was like i have
to fucking get out of here i don't know i saw i see it like it was something up somebody's ass
i don't know what the way you want to do like oh let me just keep that i gotta skip i gotta
fucking run i don't know what that is i have no idea what i could i could be anything
i just saw that and go i don't know what it is whatever whatever whatever all right
this is called germa sets up a tent that was great but how do you get inside yeah it's all
crushy looking
that was awesome hey folks so as the title of this video states i have made a germa you i made a
germa keyboard what do you mean a germ what do you mean a keyboard this looks like an incredibly
elaborate setup um all right i'm intrigued a keyboard but what is a germa keyboard you may
be asking well i like to think of it as a tool to make live germa edited music videos or youtube
poop music videos if people still call them that basically it plays audio and video at the same
time through the so wait a minute this is back when looney tunes used to have a live orchestra play
over their cartoon this is what this is don't pause don't pause videos or youtube poop music
videos if people still call them that basically it plays audio and video at the same time through
the push of a key the main reason the video looks like this is so i can prove that it's not edited
video and is actually the keyboard now it's not really that robust yet i've only got one song
sort of pre-programmed in but i'm happy with where it's at and i figured that i would show it off
first let's go over real quick how it works we got my keyboard connected via midi cable to my
interface which sends information to both pro tools and my program audio from pro tools is going out
to my looper but only to put effects on as i see fit and that audio is being recorded elsewhere
there's got a looper now let's talk about the function of each of these keys up here is my
pre-programmed song where i've got kick clap chords beeps bass and most importantly sneezes
each of these trigger a loop when they're pressed all of these pressed in time together form the
full song during which i can drop out parts as i please also i can give germa fancy backing lights
using these two guys wow now these keys are the real fun stuff each of them correspond to a
particular germa clip from his most recent green screen stream edited to match the tempo of the
song each of them are sensitive to the duration of the key press so clips can be cut short if you
need and there is no limitation as to how many can be pressed at once so you can go wild
and lastly down here is the more straight up keyboard with two octaves of germa goodness
featuring five bassier notes with an extra octave down and a toggleable keyboard visual why am i
like a can basically here you can play whatever you want or solo over the built-in song which i
am not good at also the germas down here can get a little sticky for some reason i'm not sure why
and i figured that i would tell you now with all that in mind let's take it for a spin this is
gonna be crazy oh it's going into overdrive oh so there you have it folks the germa keyboard
i miss this was a real challenge to make but i had a lot of fun with it so i hope you did too
also i would love to keep improving it so if you have any suggestions for features or even
different people i could make keyboards out of feel free to tell me in the comments also also
i'll probably upload a cleaner version of the visuals since this looks kind of bad also also
also this project kind of got away from me so here are some keyboard renders i made for no
reason look at them go we okay thanks for watching bye you selling the keyboard you're selling the
rendered keyboards and that's your opportunity to have a link to show up on screen of you selling
the rendered keyboard like a direct link i wouldn't be able to stop you greed uh that was
i can't believe that somebody would make this all these tools it's unbelievable here me ends
the germa verse wait didn't we see this one did we see this one no no no no no that's i'm thinking
of the okay hold on this is actually thank you for doing this is important because there's a
lot of people here uh yeah i'm gonna leave this on screen for a minute and it's probably a spoiler
for a tv show too i don't know if you like recognize this image down there yeah you know
here we go ready three two one go is this nocturne spoilers somebody just like
clicked out the x what i said that good here we go
so
turn 39 that's a lot of damage absorb i love it pace two pace three
uh
where's the
play this game right now
so ridiculous
this game is really hard
this is a like parody of it looks ridiculous it looks very hard wait that's it
you guys are going all out for this one we have full animated 3d cutscenes characters
you guys are going all out i like it that was awesome uh germa verse episode one skyrim
germa edition no flashing lights all right good thumbs up you ready here we go the elder scrolls
speak of the past and the future now skyrim looks to the future to its ultimate version
the character creator
i'm in so stay right between the eyes
about you
you get this dragon yes what do you want
you're gonna say that to me you don't even know who i am
oh okay so now you're gonna like talk shit to me
okay you gonna keep doing that you want to keep doing that okay
oh
this dude has a better green screen than germa and i went to a studio
anyway it's about that dragon um so are you okay look look in there there look you can see that
the watch tower has been fully destroyed god again seriously focus on me
he's a better green screen it's pissing me off
i can't believe he has a better green screen than me
better actor than you oh no oh no all right
getting out acted on my own stream
let me tell you something
all right this this dude filmed himself in front of a green screen to make his video okay
that was that's pretty intense effort that was fucking hilarious and i i do okay acting too it's
not they were good it was good both we both were good it's you can leave it at that we have good
remember gets in a fight with himself and dies okay
you guys
excuse me can we be quiet please some of us are trying to sleep sleep on the ground in my office
we've been on this job for the last two or three days and i am fucking tired i am tired
of hamburgers in this town that don't quite make it i just wish just once
just once that my cheese was soft and cold and my lettuce was cool and crisp all at the same time
you know of course i do yeah well i say you got it i'm talking about the new dl uh i forgot the
line i'm talking about the new mc dlt hey i'm talking quarter pound of beef on the hot hot side
and the hot steve hot the new big dl t so hot for some lettuce and tomato on the coo coo again
again really you're gonna do this again i words cannot even comprehend how it do you eat ass
oh you've got a mouth on you don't you i'm coming out there i'm not even going out the window
i'm coming down there and i'm gonna fuck you up ridiculous yeah yeah yeah yeah talking still huh
i'm gonna just go with the front door
delusional germany five on vacation in the sewer three two one hey fuck fuck hey what's going on
everybody i am here on vacay do it fucking right oh my god so bad stupid ass hey what's going on
hey everybody welcome up on vacation vacation vlog coming your way
that site behind me it sure does look cute anyways i gotta hurry up and get to a cut
before i blow my stuff so hey welcome back everybody guess where i am
that's right on vacation take a look i never get to go out of places like this
so much fun for me and quickly get started if you could please give me a thumbs up for being on
vacation well you're not on vacation i'm doing all this fun shit and you're not
all kinds of really cool shit and you're just gonna watch and give me money to do it too and
i'm gonna fly around the entire world and i'm gonna do a bunch of cool shit hey you and me
i'm scared of the guy that was just on camera and i i did it it was me what an actor
hmm okay this is lonely rolling germo with the with the metroid goldman and mayer
oh lonely rolling germo here we go three two one
hey man welcome to the stream my name is germo nice to meet you right there bingo right there
that's the follow button click that every so often you're getting notified that i'm streaming
and i do lots of fun things
doctor
it
is
so
i cannot believe you took the time to make a person that doesn't speak japanese to make me sing that
whole song in japanese by pulling out just consonants and vowels that i've said what on
earth at first i was trying to figure i was like i was like my these lyrics or is it just the tune
of the song and then when it became clear that they made me they they frankenstein'd me speaking
japanese that was insane all right this is a project this part of wooden music without other
people's help this is a also a video game by the way uh this is steam workshop mod for rivals of
aether and i this is another one that i could play and apparently they've added something
somebody modded something in or something i don't know what it is i we're gonna find out right now
i may be small but i sure got lots of power are you fucking kidding me
you know you have to gain viewers that's how i get power i lose viewers i lose power
what crashed my mid-range pc when you did it all right well be careful
up special is the raptor directable recovery movements poorly animated down special north
save yourself from a lethal hit rewinds position by one second
ronald mcdonald in this game wait what what do you mean what what was that
yes that's my fucking name now that's what i'm gonna call my special move is super yeah
that's awesome rivals is mugen essentially that was i love it i can't wait to play it
gabby just can't wait to go oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait i need a minute
i gotta process what just happened uh germa absolutely germa absolutely destroys the west
minster agility championship okay uh i can't i'm gonna play all these by the way that's how
we're gonna open the for the stream when i come back uh after the weekend here so any game that
you see they're gonna be played for like i want to play for them for like an hour i want to go
through this i think there's at least three of them so at least all right i destroy the west
mister agility championship three two one gabby just can't wait to go what speed on that dog walk
redirects a little bit make sure they get that push push push into that tunnel outside of this
jump andrea hang in there maybe she might have got a last for a quick second
has to be 43.20 now that's fine it's just time that's time it's just time wow we're taking the
long way around everything it looks like but this is a young young dog through the weepers
he's a young dog 35 this year that was very well made you know how annoying it is to do
even one of those cuts forget about 55 of them in a row the tunnel was the best part yeah i agree
all right this germa heaven custom remix you're the rats hi hey hi how are you how you doing
you
uh that was incredible that was incredible something that i think a lot of you guys are
starting to become aware of uh is i couldn't make a video this you don't understand what i'm saying
like i i couldn't do this like so much of this shit is the video after video after video after
video after video after video after video even after it being shaved down by a lot of videos
there's so many you guys you guys are all know how to use editing programs really well
these aren't like shittily made things these are top tier of tier one shit starting to become aware
of omega low no i mean like i've been aware of this for a long time this is tier one shit this
is not like tier like five yeah that was kind of funny that was kind of good this is unbelievable
the song you had to make the song too you had to put the song together that was great it was
absolutely remarkable stuff coming up next hey we got hope remix one but it's germa instead
we get more i love rhythm rhythm heaven right whatever rhythm fever i'm ready one two three
go hello please enjoy this dumb edit i enjoyed making it very true for each dream
the never-ending seesaw
ah that just feels good to watch those that's it will they make another one are they going to
make another rhythm heaven i hope they do we need it i need it yes no not for the switch for the
switch it's one of the three ds i want one of the switch so bad how many games have you said about
nintendo that you want to have so bad it's a bunch i think that could that would should just be there
right anyways it's called our germa pun one punch germa all right this is i think is this the the
intro to one punch man i believe this is the intro to one punch man i don't know it's probably
not spoilers but just in case just fucking leave if you've ever seen an episode of one punch man
quick the intro they record themselves like pretending to like
so
no ifs ands or buts just standing whoa i know what this one is um by the way
one punch man is a great show what is it what an interesting concept first of all what an
interesting show based on the comic fix not based on the manga right obviously that's what i mean
but what a cool shit about a guy that punches people and then they die in one hit like that's
one punch guy it's what a great fucking concept i love it how could you not like that how could
you not like see the trailer and know oh this guy punches people once just go watch it but
don't forget oh well i don't know where i could be just please just watch episode two two of them
in a row surprise it took this long to get this bit rate the bit rate is yeah the bit rate went
down why did the bit rate go so low 2007 youtube aesthetic wait is this just jojo's bizarre adventure
i hope so here it comes no oh i thought that that's not i thought that was a
bee stars these stars oh okay well this is a bee stars reference here it comes
that looks cool in the background the real one what is that
oh
look at my face what a professional green screen and if you get the damn lighting right
wait jerma wins the playoffs with the vikings yep that's how you look normally you're saying
but we start with breaking news this noon as a car fire spreads to two detroit homes leaving
someone trapped inside of one of those houses and that story tops our news this noon it all
unfolded in the area of waveney and cadge you just north of mack avenue about nine o'clock
this morning and we are learning that a heroic rescue was pulled off by an off-duty detroit
firefighter what is this real i don't like this one vacation vacation vlog coming your way
hey that was real news that was real news anyway that was real news as real news i don't
i don't like i don't do real news happy birthday to you just want to give you a quick little happy
i'm here wishing you the best although i know i haven't probably seen you in 10 years wait what
these little videos for you because the phone's upside down at least i can do
real news is real news and i don't if somebody got hurt or something i don't want to like
you know you know i don't want to make like a joke about somebody actually potentially really
getting hurt in real life right yeah i don't want to you be careful there i don't want that you know
star trek here comes another star trek they were saved and it was fine yeah i know i know i know but
no real news no real like tragic potential events here comes another star trek
someone just got timed out for saying star trek what is this wait hold on hold on i i know it's
probably it's probably the face i just did isn't it i don't i'm not going to show it on stream i
don't care i don't want i'm not going to show it on stream that's too bad all right i'll show
it on stream all right i'm going to show it on stream okay that looks like somebody is that
looks like your grandfather is laughing so hard at something and he's dying at the same time
like he's watching the he's watching like the the roasts with jimmy uh jimmy dean and whatever
it is and he's like laughing so hard and he's fucking having a heart attack dean martin dean
martin right not the sausage guy all right here we go germa star trek let's play for one set of
repairs now they need him for more apparently their ship is quite fragile hey remember me i'm
that guy that's supposed to be live right now for the last two hours apparently your ship is in need
of more than minor repair and look at what it looks like now look at how it's it looks fucking
fine it's fixed i here's the tractor beam to tow you to the nearest base listen hear me up i'm
going to tell you something right now it's very very important you need to hear this um so i in
plugged in right now is the webcam and it was there's a web is a usb 3.0 and a usb 2.0
i don't think data was going fast enough into the into the i had to put it in 3.0
that's awesome so i in plugged in right now is the webcam and it was there's a web is a usb 3.0
and a usb 2.0 i don't think data was going fast enough into the into the i had to put it in 3.0
holy shit
you didn't think i could do that did you
another one of these wait is it the same okay this is germa stops the apocalypse
i know it's unbelievable i can't believe it either an asteroid might hit the earth
what wouldn't you agree that nonsense what i gotta go i gotta get out i gotta get out
into the sun the nature of streamers jeremy elbertson how do you i don't know how do you
give hugs i don't know how you get how do you give a hug you people just kind of do that you
just go like hey like hi nobody comes like this like i'm a giant like venus flytrap buck like
squish you let me just tell you that i gotta be honest i've never seen this movie i was spooked
um i was spooked i almost did i'm a green screen rick no hey i am i am i hey rick
hey hey morty oh what is it i don't want to turn myself into a green screen oh no yeah morty you
can be whatever you want in front of the green screen oh i don't want to be you rick have to
morty get over there and be me no i don't want to morty morty we're gonna be on reddit morty we're
gonna be on reddit here on the green screen happy birthday john you're 16 everybody gather around
john it's about to blow out their candles all together now all of us happy no i can't you do it
buddy all right
happy birthday to you feed me this shit only mcdonald's we're a mcdonald family for christ's
we only make me make we only make mcdonald's i'm really enjoying the school dance
okay come a little closer
gas player five thousand dollars that's not that's too much is he do you like spend it on something
i don't know what you do is it is like is it like a is it is it is it like is it like a currency
thing i mean what is it i'm not sure i mean is it like some kind of currency thing i'm not sure
it's not real i'm not like this at a real not a big deal you know like not a big deal at all
you know what i'm saying not a big deal at all drew from my retirement account and liquidated
this is just sad this is sad this is just sadness let's do it again
do i win the big one do i win i gotta win the big one right at the very end
it goes to the bank five years old getting old he's an old man she's an old man
oh what man wait i'm not this is not jeffrey's birkin party that's pretty thick headed
but nothing compared to the rich thick frosty mug taste of an a&w root beer with a&w it's good to be
thick-headed happy what the fuck i love it i love it i love it what a dumb ass
oh he's an old man she's an old man oh what man wait i'm not this is not jeffrey's birkin party
that's pretty thick-headed but nothing compared to the rich thick frosty mug taste of an a&w root
beer with a&w it's good to be thick-headed happy oh my god unbelievable uh germa wants some peace
excuse me can we be quiet please some of us are trying to sleep what happened what i yeah
that was fucking nuts that was scary all right this is called germa walk are you ready i've been
drinking the water out of the sink the worst thing i've ever done in my entire career sad
oh please please germa alone holy shit that hair is bad fuck fuck hey what's going on hey welcome
to my channel welcome my vlog as you can see i love die you motherfucker
ah awkward morning routine so remember if you like that video follow me on my journey
well i virtually will kill you virtual murder virtual asmr murder oh that's doug by the way we
just heard a spoiler for the video that's doug uh this is germa's nightmare after this one i'm
gonna take it i gotta pee i'm gonna take another quick break i'm gonna see how many more we have
left it's probably quite a few here we go that's the one you realize how fucking ugly you are to
get close here take it take it take it this take this from me take this from me right now take it
from me take it from me dude i don't want to fucking hold it anymore take it from me take
this thing out of my fucking hands before i freak out take it from me take it you don't have to take
it from my fucking hands
let me see
okay uh all right hold on hold on let me let me take a piss oh my goodness i don't i don't i
want an image of that ron mcdonald guy that was me i kind of want that don't you want that picture
just somewhere even if it's in a folder in your computer somewhere you don't care about it i just
want it somewhere right back okay i'm back those who that are curious we are uh about a third of
the way through the videos we're not even halfway so i'm going to make the decision before we get
any further here when we get to the halfway point there's going to be a part two we'll do a part two
because it's going to be like five plus hours for part one and at the rate that i have been flexing
my chest back and forth i don't think i'm going to be able to sit here for another four or five
hours but hey we can do it again and by the way this is not going to be like oh we'll do part two
like a month not within the next like four or five days so let's keep going we're not we're not even
close by the way we have at least another hour plus hour maybe two hours before we get to the
true halfway point here we go here are my dances oh by the way i don't think any of you knew that
i could do this oh didn't think i could do that did you that's pretty that's that's real that's
pretty real that's me
dude you know those movies you ever see a movie
when it's fucking popped up from the top it's a boom microphone is that funny
that's all no ideas is happening okay that was germa goes to interrupt some movie germa 95 meets
germa 984 let's all get hype for metal gear solid 5 get hype play button
it's true you and i are yes twins but we're not ordinary twins we're twins linked by
cursed genes you're fine you got all of the old man's dominant genes i got all the flawed
recessive genes wait why the um what you can't back
hunter from
it's the jex factor
you have gone through an obstacle far greater than anybody
much older than you could even imagine going through and then you come to this point and
you make choices and you made the choice of singing that song and it was so heartfelt and
so inspirational i just want to say thank you thank you it was amazing your tones and the way
that you fell off the note was just on point you do have a beautiful voice and i can't believe
happy birthday incredible well done just you know what i just had this feeling when you walked out i
can't explain it just your spirit the choice of song your voice i think you're really special
get past this stage i predict great things are gonna happen for you there's something about you
you sorry i'm gonna do this wait wait me wait me i i get it
the golden wait they've added a golden buzzer hold on a minute why did they add a gold the
golden buzzer means you can just veto everybody and just say that person gets to go what's the
point of having three judges when you just have a super button that one of them can just press
yes that's been a thing for a long time i don't remember there being a super like
omega l really it's been there for 10 years well i've fucked this guy but not watching
america's got talent ever i've never seen any full episode i've never seen an episode
i have never seen one full episode of x factor marriage has got talent or american idol within
the last 15 years i've never seen an episode that could have been there from the very beginning
anyways here come the fuck up i'm listening to germa's pirate marching band
hi squash oh hi what are you playing i'm playing as what are you playing i'm gonna be playing team
fortress two as
leisurely drives what just happened what the fuck was that what the hell happened why did i do
i didn't do anything i did that was fucking crazy i was like oh holy shit all right next one
yeah i actually do want to say something really quick uh it's pretty heavy but it's awful and
terrible it makes me feel like shit um yeah i've heard about chadwick it's that's a horrible
horrible fucking thing and it really has been messing with me because he was young as shit he
was very young and it really really just crushes me because he was colon cancer and i have colitis
i have like colon problems and i get sigmoidoscopies and colonoscopy i've had like four of them three
of them in my life and it's just just so terrible to hear about that it really truly is he was a
great fucking actor you talk about black panther like come on it's incredibly sad
but yeah i wanted to just because that that's just it hit me pretty fucking poorly when i
heard about it but yeah uh we can keep going we're gonna do elberton's fifth sympathy here we go
it's supposed to be food it's not just overacting everything
toilet visit what what do you want from me you fiends you bastards you villains
okay um oh my god why am i chained to the toilet
okay everybody guess where i am that's right on vacation take a look
i'd never get to go out of places like this so it's so much fun for me frog buck
there it goes let me put my feet up that's a pretty good that's a pretty good view
this actually looks pretty relaxing i would do this
this is valuable worth a lot probably pineapple food for the first time
my favorite
that's pretty good that's really good hold on that's like 11 30 you have the venue till 11 30
it's like dude you gotta we gotta get the fuck out of here man you gotta go to sleep it's derma
darko i believe this is donnie darko spoilers for donnie darko i'm voting for ducacus okay in class
that's unbelievable son you're such a fuck ass you can go suck a fuck oh please tell me elizabeth
how exactly does one suck a fuck what's the fuck ass my kids are the smartest
oh
use that one delete that one
bastard they got me they got me do not stop until i germa one signal or dramatically throw you to
the ground and request a towel i'm ready it's from kung pao
oh
should we keep going he said to hit him until he gave the signal to stop did anyone hear the
signal well he was whining for a while do you think whining was the signal hey whoa easy we
should wait a second or so hey guys come on oh well
it's just a scream all right what's the kiss thing what was that hey wait wait
he did say the part about dramatically throwing us off his body oh yeah go ahead throw us off
you think he wants his tower no i'm not playing jump king ever
there's a blood all over my head hello every all right this is germa convinces you to watch
a better video wait this is my video hello this is my this is okay this is the second or third
video i've ever made in my whole life back in like 2011 okay let's go hello everybody
hey my name is hill juggle i'm i'm jermy's hey hey how are you great good thing i caught you
good thing i got you right at the beginning of the video today we're gonna play you're gonna
deluxe mode it's
i disagree i disagree that video okay that video is about like 12 and a half minutes too long
it's a 12 minute and like 41 second video but i did i did think it was good though
uh here comes germa wars episode one the egg menace this is uh star wars episode one here we go
i missed this is my town there you go oscar
dude i looked over here this way you just didn't do it in what sm1 i see all these
costumes and all these these devices and all these these things to play with and it's a
fucking mess over here it's like this like 75 items over here wait and then i'm fucking over here
there's a door right there and there's a big the guy you're in front of like a green screen
you're like apparently driving right now oh wow look oh this looks really great on my
fucking green screen this looks so stupid hey you remember that water park this did look so
funny i remember the first time i've ever seen
you
i'm waiting for you to throw a piece of popcorn into my mouth and i'm very confused if you haven't
done it yet it's fucking awesome barber germa oh i don't know how do you skip like this
oh what do you want good morning you and me i know you we're gonna do it fine what good i see we
don't have to wait today son you are in big trouble listen i'd like for you to take a little more off
this time you know especially around those ears that reminds me my dog got itching ears every time
she would scratch herself she'd howl and she'd squeal so you know what oh i decided to take it
to the vet but instead of him fixing her itching ears he told me to go home and get a pile of her
stool well of course we go like i couldn't imagine what does that have to do with itching ears so i
went home well not to get the number two instead i call the veterans hospital and they tell me well
we treat people here not dogs and that i should call the vet hospital but i said this is the vet
hospital isn't it you know he hung up
what's with you
i'll make my exit now look at me all right i tell you i wouldn't if my son was sitting there
and the barber was doing this all right everyone get your place hold on hold on at the number two
the barber is doing this here not dogs and then i should call the vet hospital but i said this
i'm gonna say okay it's time for us to leave because the barber is he's on all everything he
probably combined like four or five things and together in a blender and just drank it and i we
have to leave now but i said this is but i don't think i'm gonna be here with this guy
you know he hung up on he's too busy talking
drama kicks to all right everyone get your places all right today is the big day wait is this the
actor is this the better actor back better actor okay all right just remember that today is the
big day excuse me can we be quiet please some of us are trying to sleep oh sorry we're we're
shooting a okay better green screen it's not a better green screen is more technology than
i have get to your places uh today's the big day just hi hi hello yes how are you
yes hello what do you shut up shut up all of you okay listen sorry that we're making all this
ridiculous it's like this every single day i understand and i'm sick and tired of hearing it
look so i can hear you all the way up here okay and i pay rent too okay well keep
we'll keep it quiet all right we'll keep it quiet we'll lower wasn't it already closed
anyways um everyone get get get to your place all right and just leave him alone
jerma again leave him alone you're gonna do this again come on yes okay sorry okay listen
we're trying to shoot something here and you're being a big distraction to me and everyone else
here everyone who's trying to do their work all right you got a mouth on you don't get this
all right and you're just coming out here in the street
i'm coming down there and i'm gonna fuck you up
okay oh that hurt oh that was that was
this is the monster
jerma on monday night i'm gonna come down there i'm gonna fuck you up oh okay let's go wwe monday
night raw
985 at freddy all right that was
don't you feel like it would be annoying to be in this room this is how you walk around this room
okay you ready yeah yeah i still uh yes i'm still going to school i'm still at uh yeah i'm still at
you you you uh what are you doing now how are the kids like that's all that's the whole day
that's why is that nobody why doesn't i don't like that because i don't understand what it is
it hurts to be in this room for five minutes you're gonna see the images of these lights
for four or five hours after you leave gonna be burned into your retina i want i want to just a
soft lit room with a little bit of no fucking loud ass music of a jazz band playing like five
rooms away behind glass so you can look over and you see them playing in the glass in the club
and then the it's recorded inside of the glass and then they pump that whatever volume they decide
through a control system into the rest of the club you understand that's the perfect solution
four hours of jerma condensed into 27 seconds oh don't skip it there's every school cafeteria
i've ever been in jerma goes too hog wild on stream and gets wicked heart heart wrenching
i don't think any of you knew that i could do this
yeah i had a ton of fun but i think i really fucked myself up once the fun juice wore off
i turned into the tin man keep an eye on sus my doctor's gonna ground me and was forced to
perform a torture dance for 7 000 people my spine and leg have been broken and shattered
no one helped i'll just type jerma venus and chat hog champion laughed at him spent the rest of the
night crawling around in the sewer because he had nowhere else to go
played league of the witches curse part three um hold on a minute here this is this is a long
running series are we caught up because remember there's there's like three or four of these
this is this is faster i'm a purple alien are we actually caught up or is there from three
four months ago is there a part two i think i'm caught up right because last time was the the
frog right and the witch you watched one and two okay so yeah we are caught up because the
recap recap just watch the last one all right yeah we'll do a recap we'll do a witch's curse
because we need to be recapped this is part three of a series we're gonna go through them
very quickly don't wait this is just a recap save it for the end um hold on all right we'll do all
right we'll do it in the end we'll do we'll do extra p break okay we'll we'll do it we'll actually
you know we'll save for the end no do it now all right well let's do it right now let's do it right
now give me give me links you got links we want witches curse one and two let's see which is
curse let me write it we're just having witches curse we're not going to watch the whole thing
we're gonna skip through it so you can get it we'll do it with a recap i'm not gonna click that
that's a rick roll i'm just gonna i'm gonna find it myself which is curse part two the scientist
which is curse part one i got it i don't even need you guys help all right so here we go we're
gonna do a recap this is which is curse part one fast germa and purple alien you know your
favorite characters oh fuck whatever watch the whole thing okay exit the helicopter evaluate the
damage all right what's worse that image or the first image that pops up when you type germa
nine eight five and do an image search they're pretty comparable i wonder what that means
which is shrunken them see we got shrunken they begin to search for the swamp to fix the cure for
us being shrunken down what's in the distance right we remember this part what is that what is
what is this thing right here
isn't that just wonderful
yeah
i'm such a big fan of the vast germa purple alien universe scientists to the scientist
okay we have to get teleported to the scientist
all right there you go you recap you recapped on episode one we teleported to the science lair
oh this is not the germa cinematic universe i'm sorry this is the fast germa purple alien
cinematic universe so here we go which is curse part two the scientist i was ready to go it's
just mirrored scientist is very smart this is vr chat isn't it it's a vr chat avatar
oh i've recapped recap i remember this this way that we start shitting and
been like throwing up and stuff i've recap and that's a real cat
enough of the nails bastard and purple alien
okay this part okay we're gonna this is the recap part
i guess we really didn't we didn't even need a recap for two did we could have just said we ate
scientists still does not notice them okay he turns the sink on
don't skip of course i'm gonna skip
okay we get out of the water and then he he doesn't notice us still right
oh yeah he shoots a rocket launcher at us
okay so he still hasn't noticed anything but he clumsy old fool he knocked two cups on us
he needs to help them they have suffocated to death all right so what's part three we
continued okay so we're dead dead all right i didn't want to do that yeah actually maybe i
did okay here we go ready which is curse part three this is the sequel to that one so you now
you're all caught up purple planet club this is all vr chat so as you need to come to earth
immediately it's an emergency your nephew purple alien and his friend fast germa are dead fast germa
and purple alien the witch's curse part three resurrection alien's uncle is going to earth to
meet with the magical frog purple alien back to life or he is breaking down
i think this is this person's actual cat by the way which makes it better
seven lives remaining they will go into the frog's hidden tree lair yeah that was only one death
so
yeah i guess you could be right
how did he get us
wait they're alive
germa and purple alien in a shocking move judge suvampavich has sentenced the scientist to death
by being fired from a cannon into the ocean when questioned why he pled guilty the scientist
commented that he thought the judge was quote asking how he felt officials say this execution
in at least 10 minutes that wasn't no that wasn't real news that was a that was a fake
news segment there it is that's part three resurrection that video cost at least five
dollars crackhead streamer coming up take this from me right now take it from take it from me
dude i don't want to fucking hold anything well take it from me take this thing out of my fucking
hands before i freak out i wasn't ready for this i wasn't ready hold on slow down oh this is rat
cup final germa's at raptor's highlights you're getting paid let's hope he's okay you know that
like peter dinklage is dinklage meets germa at the coffee shop what do you mean p like peter
dinklage you know that like peter dinklage is going to be at the starbucks you know they always
go there so you go to the laptop you hang up a little bit you see the limo pull up you see peter
dinklage get out you get up you're gonna get in line you're gonna get a coffee maybe i feel like
another coffee you get in line he comes up behind you you get your coffee you turn around give him a
little bump oh sorry i didn't see you there at peter dinklage and he's like yes i'm peter dinklage
you're like wow that's all cool peter dinklage that's all game thrones right yes that's right
game thrones oh cool man uh we'll do later yeah that's what i'd do he'd be like well nothing
thanks for asking me would you like to come over yeah dude i'm getting kind of busy but uh
i don't see if i can schedule it schedule it in something like that you know what i mean all right
yeah he'd be like whoa oh my god germa germa 985 wow wow uh i've seen i've seen your work
and i'd be like oh wow yeah cool dude and then he would look at me dead in the eyes and be like
i'm actually a big fan of fucking morons acting like idiots and sucking at everything
and then i would be like what uh i don't know what to do and have my face to start to you know
your face starts to get a little red you can tell your face is like slowly you can feel the blood
kind of going into your face if you want uh and i fucking my brain in my brain he knows he knows
that i'm turning red i think that he get even more red and then you like kind of like do something
to make it look like that he was supposed to be red in the first place like what you look it's
it's like hot in here they turn this like starbucks keep their like temperature like 80 or something
jesus fucking i don't know what you're talking about about peter that's like funny but that you
say that i feel like i'm going crazy and he spits directly into my face and there is just there's
no debating that's what you're meant to do okay stranger danger germa greenspring is valuable
worth a lot probably oh hey would you would you like one here take one
take it take it take this take this from me right now take it from me take it from me dude i don't
want to fucking hold it anymore take it from me take this thing out of my fucking hands before i
freak out take it from me take it you don't have to take it in my fucking hands
die you motherfucker you actually have like
sorry to say i've got more tricks up my sleeve than fucking udini
you're high up in the mountains of iceland
welcome back hey everybody guess where i am that's right on vacation look i never get to go out of
places like this so it's so much fun for me and before we video get started if you could please
give me a thumbs up for being on vacation well you're not on vacation i'm doing all this cool
fun shit actually on vacation and i'm going to continue to do all kinds of really cool shit
and you're just going to watch me do cool shit and give me money to do it too and i'm wearing a black
shirt to the beach a bunch of cool shit hey you and me we're friends
oh
i feel like i'm on drugs right now
there's been so many drug ones both physically and metaphorically
oh my god okay what's life is pain
i look fucking disgusting i look horrendous why are your arms so skinny
it's the green screen it's like the green screen bleeding in
this is gonna be a single player let's play and when i say let's play i use that term
pretty loosely because
i'm
triumphs at least i'm hoping so go grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee i'm losing my fucking mind
i can't even pay attention let's get this started create new world world name is going to be
turkey arms i i'm losing my mind
ladies and gentlemen the best joke of the decade
it's 30 percent of the vote the entire germacraft episode play i feel like it just did
spam hold on this is spam oh it's the coffee pops right okay
okay it's the coffee pasta oh my god i'm gonna lose my mind oh okay i'm gonna take one more
p break i'm gonna see where we are my whole body hurts right now final p break we are at
all right we are we are like 10 videos away from being at the halfway point 10 20 and then we're
gonna save part two we're gonna save the other 130 plus videos we're gonna do it again next
weekend we're gonna go at the same time we're gonna do saturday again saturday afternoon oh
yeah it's we're not we're not even halfway we're at 122 videos 130 130 to 140 videos is halfway
oh my goodness why didn't i peel it earlier i did i'm just drinking a bunch of water all right i'll
be right back one more p it was the turkey arms thing that you guys are saying just i fucking hurt
myself i'll be back in a few minutes okay another about 10 to 15 videos or so maybe 20
doesn't know far we get and here we go you ready are you back are you here are you with us right
now up next is germa's shoplifting psa reflex mega center where i play minecraft this is
going to be a single player let's play and when i say let's play i use that term pretty loosely
because i'm wait that's the thing on top
so scary his shirt changed yeah don't shoplift guys yes look at that it's gone
one punch germa versus big robot boy okay here comes one punch man episode two i think
wait is this is this season two is this season two i haven't seen season two i don't want to see
anything from season two season one yeah like is this season one don't scare me like that okay
here we go ready that's a season one fake fan all right that it's the first season it's a season
one episode two of i almost said fall guys okay now this is one punch man so here comes
some spoilers for one punch man i gotta do it every time one punch me if you've seen series
then i've been warning you here comes an episode one of germa craft
oh
it's a pirated episode it no it's not it's not
i mean hold on this is this is a really important question to ask if i put me over a main character
of a show can i watch that show if somebody were to do the entire in the full episode one through
ten of me doing all the lines is it like a cover is it a parody at what point is it like i'm just
just me doing the whole episode i mean it's very clearly transformative content right but with this
would that even be i don't know if you're talking about a copyright law loophole
i don't think is it though i don't think that would hold up in i don't know you're going to jail
no it's transformative you change it it's the media becomes something completely different it's
not this is not completely different this is just me doing it okay so we're gonna um
it's transformative it is you guys are freaking me out right now i'm getting freaked out
all right that was cool all right let's be freaking me out you're freaking me out i'm
getting freaked out i we're gonna go to the next one you're freaking me out i don't know what this
hey it's me the youtube guy it's from the matrix
this sucks i hate it stop pretending this guy sucks don't die dad next this sucks play better
you have to lose try to become human suspects all yours
oh this game's copyrighted no it's it's not pirated
runescape uh dance six what the fuck is it doing now supposedly she can rap
cool name wait wait wait wait terrific these are all terrific
meets the next one g-rex cool name superpowers
we can use no this is transformative that's transformative my face and look at these pop
chips next cool i like you so you have the power to finger my butthole yes all right all right
i'm done with this one no ha ha nice right next that's this person's name yokiken
that's good yeah so uh where are you from new fucking jersey so you're let me you're an alien
i guess how does that uh help us what's going on in the back room next next last but not least
peter yeah i'm really enjoying the school dance
so do you have any math homework
they have
i i i have uh i have mrs stevenson she's the worst
yeah that was a tiktok video wait what do you mean tiktok this is a tiktok video
this is okay germa place fall guys deal sunday featuring sunday what
is
finally this is just another poster for mystery men i just remade the movie mystery men there
we wicked crack video i don't think i could watch this one right now wicked crack video
hold on i'm gonna hold on i don't have time to do this i'm gonna give you a warning this is wicked
crack video this i don't know if you have your photo sensitive like it probably is gonna be
fucking cracked so just be aware of that it's be careful
okay
take this right now take it from me take it from me dude
i don't want to fuck over
new intro no oh yeah it's over okay okay let me take a look i don't want to spoil anything
all right we are going to be at the halfway point in exactly and probably two in two more videos
well you know and one more we'll do with this one two more all right two more videos i think
i gotta go take a bath yes we're not even halfway yet we are just we're barely crossing the halfway
point there was a lot of there's a ton of content and i knew i was gonna have to break it up into
this is called germa's day and animal crossing take a shower instead no i don't want to do that
i don't want to take a shower i want to take i want to get in the bath and i would just put my head
my entire head underneath just blow as hard as i can out of my nose so there's like
and then my hair turns into like weird ghost material it just floats around and you just
get that weird ghost material feeling with your hair and your nose and then you just come right
up i'm getting why am i getting question marks when you put your head under water your hair floats
up and becomes this weird like ether aether whatever material like netherworld whatever
material no it's true it really is somebody said it thank you one person what your head telling you
what your next time you're in a pool or something just just see how it feels and see what it looks
like and touch it it's weird somebody said that somebody said true i saw it i saw it in the chat
but you can't fucking lie to me never bullshit a bullshitter creamer no i'm saying i'm not i'm
telling just go what do on your own time on your own leisure just put your head under water like
when you can when you're comfortable it's true thank i'm so happy to see this all right derma's
day and animal crossing he looks like a cowboy oh ah i started over get it off get it off get it off
is it an animal crossing what is this
what no what emergency bit shit oh
actually had to go get the wood you actually animated all that
oh that's true dedication for a video
how much is in there
it's a lot all right how much money is that it's three what 300 how much that's a lot are you
fucking serious right now to make an account believe it believe what this oh it's narrow toe
i thought you're talking about believe the bits okay this is narrow toe i don't know what episode
this is is this just an episode of tv
so
i don't i've never seen i don't know what this is and i can't react to this
fuck all of you it's knocking out all right i have to watch another one or two
gerbil wins the 2013 iron ball with the kick six
56 yarder it's got no does not have the leg and chris davis takes it in the back of the end zone
he'll run it out to the 10 15 20 25 30 35 40 45 50 45 there goes davis davis is going to run it
all the way back arbor's gonna win the football game he ran the miss field go back he ran it back
i'm really enjoying the school dance
so
there is not any nutritional value in pancakes you're right hey fuck hey everybody i am here on
bay do it fucking right oh my god so bad hey what's going on i've never seen this movie
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait that was what what that was i've never seen up yeah i've not
seen up no are you kidding no i've never seen up i just i know the part with like the balloons and
stuff i just know that it's about a guy's house that's pulled around i've never seen it i swear
to god something like that right there's a dog there's a like a dachshund watch it watch it on
stream i can't watch movies on stream that's the most iconic thing in the whole movie i've never
seen i don't know what it is i'm gonna watch it tonight i promise uh i was giving that part
for the stars of america's game at sing jack and fana white same video thanks everybody
here it comes it's worth one thousand dollars let's go yes uh what is twelve dollars no
all right okay all right that's it i have to stop here we're going over the halfway point
oh my goodness gracious we have made it to halfway through the dlc movies in just about five hours
oh i have to go like take a bath or something i've all my stomach and my chest every four to
six minutes has gone from laughing you know what i'm saying when you get that like laugh laugh laugh
chest chest chest oh my goodness i knew it was gonna happen too but this has been fucking
hilarious five straight hours and we're only halfway this is so much more but for the purpose
of not getting too fucked up and not exhausting like a 10 hour long stream of this we're gonna
do a part two exactly we'll do it exactly next week same time saturday again oh the arnold one
is would just put the nail in the coffin right there thanks for watching everybody that was part
one of dlc movies they were just as good as i thought they were going to be i think i have
noticed though mate we still have like another 150 videos to see but no saw i've only seen the
soft footage once or twice oh maybe we'll get a saw i spent like an 40 minutes in the green
screen doing saw no saw we'll see oh all right i'm gonna remember my place here i got it right
here with the germtastic voyage is the next video i am ready next week no jojo either bad don't
maybe i have 150 videos to do so i will see you guys the next time i'm streaming will be on
wednesday we're gonna go wednesday thursday saturday sunday this coming week i will see you guys then
or wednesday thursday saturday at least maybe you'll see how i feel on sunday because i feel
like my chest is gonna hurt on saturday i'll see you guys on wednesday take care of yourselves
we'll see you soon we're gonna go over as if we're gonna do credits really quickly
my god uh here they are i didn't i press the button i get i press the button here there for
the credits this is all the subscriptions tonight we had a ton of community subs hundreds of them
so thanks to everybody that did that all in alphabetical order link to the playlist um
not no not yet not yet not quite yet because then there's a other whole half of the videos
that you'll be able to see not yet not yet we're not done with them we have a
little we wanted to watch them together no spoilers imagine having an anime and manga
series older than some of these zoomers in chat what do you mean imagine yeah next week you guys
are gonna get the playlist when it's done there i am gary there i am look there's so many names
on this list every stream there's so many names i can't it's too many people but we did have five
community subs back to back from yes and malcolm thank you guys already dread came in with like
5000 community subs like yeah he does every time it's insane bilactory 50 first weed piano
what a great name 50 it's just fucking unbelievable oh i just like stretched back and my back just went
goodness all right i have to go i just heard like my back just laughed like popeye for a second it
was like oh all right i gotta leave fuck i'll see you guys on wednesday damn it there i go laughing
again laughing at stuff i'm trying to think what my favorite one was i don't think i have a favorite
do you have i i can't think of favorite i think i liked them all i liked all of them it was not
one that i really probably said hey you know that was like that was like kind of good i think i
laughed my ass off at every single one i'll see you guys on wednesday thanks for watching i have
to get up right now and leave immediately have a wonderful rest of your night good night see you soon