Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Super Meat Boy Mondays.
In this episode, we're going to tackle the Salt Factory Chapter 3.
So what do you say we get started and watch the cutscene?
Alright, so he's got my pig girlfriend. She looks like a pig from behind right there.
He turned into the moon, went into the Salt Factory. I love this music.
This is like one of my favorite songs in the whole game. I don't know why.
Just like that. Here we go.
This is where it's going to start to get really, really bad on the rage front.
So let's see if I can't just pull this off.
Can I get it? Yes.
No, I can't. I should have just jumped over it. I'm an idiot.
No, screw the Band-Aid. I don't need it.
There it is.
We go up and down. I don't even remember.
It's been a long time since I've played this game. Looks like we're going up.
Level complete.
I can walk on this, right? Okay, good.
I was going to say, hopefully I can walk on this.
Jump, jump. Let's go, Super Meat Boy. Show them what you got.
You know what? For a second I thought that was in the background.
Like the foreground. I couldn't run into it.
I thought it was part of the scenery.
Now I know. See, now you...
Oh my god. I'm shifting in my seat. I've got to get comfortable.
Get the key. Nice and easy here.
No bologna. No bologna and cheese sandwiches here.
Now I know that happens. It's good to know.
Run!
Oh, jeez, I forgot that happened.
See, that's definitely the worst part about playing this over again.
Just blindly. I forget all these levels.
Now I know that happens so I can...
God, the noises that are made.
Warp Zone, Warp Zone, Warp Zone. Can I get in there?
How the hell do I get in there?
Oh, for the love of Pete. Whatever.
Hold on. There we go.
Oh, no. Hold on.
Ninja Meat Boy.
20 points to who knows what that is.
Oh, let's keep it skiing here.
Tribes Ascent. Just like Tribes.
It's all about the skiing.
Hey, Blush Baby.
This is my favorite part. I love this.
Yeah.
Boomtown. Oh, I forgot. Oh, yeah, these things.
You have to kind of dodge these things.
They shoot a little slow, but they have homing capabilities.
So you want to b-ya-hoo and then you want to b-ya-ha and then you want to b-ya-ha.
Otto, what do you want?
Otto just walked in my room.
Which means my door is open.
Which means the other big dog, the big, gross, smelly dog can get in here now.
And I don't want that.
Not that I don't love my dog, but he's a...
He is big and he is gross.
Here's a little quick story about that dog.
So the big, huge dog you've probably seen in videos past.
We have to give him to the groomer every couple months or every few weeks.
Because he's just so big and disgusting.
He just stinks sometimes.
But he's a big, lovable ox. We love him.
His name's Boo Boo.
Oh my god. That's the fifth time that's happened.
Enough. Enough. Enough.
My ship sails in the morning.
I wonder what's for breakfast.
Come on.
Dog. God damn it.
You see, they have to explode.
If you don't get them to blow up, then you're in big trouble.
Like that. See?
There was like...
Please. God. No.
Okay. Time to...
I really got to pay attention here.
No.
Oh my god. I'm going to throw the friggin' controller into the wall.
Come on.
Alright. Wait for another one.
Good.
Now. God. In. Heaven.
Go.
I'm sick of this.
There. That's it. You're supposed to turn and run.
And then do it again.
Thank you very much.
Holy crap.
Oh no. I didn't want to skip that. Crap.
I wanted to see all those deaths.
I'm sorry if you wanted to see that too. I apologize.
But I have such an itchy trigger finger in this game.
I just have to go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Woohoo.
Got to stay in the middle. Got to stay in the middle.
A+.
Yeah.
The bend.
Welcome to the bend.
Bender bending Rodriguez.
Bite my shiny metal ass.
Oh no.
Me and Fry are going to go do some terrorizing.
Come on, Professor.
I don't think I'm going to do.
Why do all my voices sound the same?
Every voice is just like grandpa.
Whatever.
Just go. You know what? I'm just going to go. Go.
That didn't work so well.
Got to wait here.
This is the word. Meat Boy levels where you have to be patient.
I cannot do it.
When you got to be patient, I can't do it.
I cannot stand it.
I just want to go as fast as I possibly can.
That really just killed me.
Got to go as humanly possible.
As fast as I possibly humanly, humanly can.
No, come here.
No, my...
Oh, at least I'm not dying.
Oh my god.
What the hell?
Alright, that's not going to happen again.
Told you.
Get the girl.
Take her back to mom and dad's.
Have some dinner.
Meet the fam.
Oh boy, this thing moves. This thing moves and yet it moves.
Isn't that a game?
I think that's a game.
Oh crap.
Otto.
There we go.
Hello, my queen.
Rustic. Sounds pretty rustic to me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh god.
Okay, good thing I didn't...
Just got to go, got to go, got to go.
Alright, getting to the boss here.
I think the boss is...
I remember the boss in this level is
difficult.
And I'm probably going to use so many lives
at that boss.
It's not even funny.
Oh my god, how am I going to get this
like that? That's how you're going to get it.
And you're not going to die here.
It's all about the patience.
My patience, my young padawan.
And you will be victorious.
Don't go yet. Okay, go.
Yes. Alright, well
right after beating that level, we
just had a crash, but that's okay.
Back, ready to do it again.
Come on, bro. Come on, bro.
Oh, look at these dodges.
Dude, why am I playing
the Super Mario Bros. 2 level where you have to
dig down? I forget
what you have to do here. Oh my god,
what do I do? Oh my god.
Wait a second, wait a second, wait a second.
I totally forget what you have to do here.
What does go-
Oh, no, no, no. Okay, I remember, I remember.
You go through here. Okay.
There we go. For a second
I was just, by brain, had no idea
what was going on. Would you just get in there
you sloppy bastard?
And this is going to be another Biahu.
Yes it is. Oh, hi.
Uh, Biahu?
Now I know you. I will probably say
I hate
these things. These are the absolute
worst things in the game.
These stupid missile launches.
Oh, you're going to take this- come on.
I'll jump over you all day.
Yes. Okay.
Hopefully I don't crash at the
boss, because that would not be good.
Brownie. I gotta go,
gotta go. Help me. Please.
Oh, you're here. Of course I'm here. You're my
girlfriend. Excuse me, you can't
touch that. I will be hitting this button
right now. Or pulling this lever, same thing.
Here comes your toilet.
Who's it going to be?
Oh my god. What the hell
is going on? What is this?
It's- oh, it stinks.
What is it?
Who is that?
Hey guys, it's me.
Brownie.
Alright, let's go.
You have to beat this guy in a race,
that's all I remember. Oh, you are
done. I- come on.
Oh, no.
I gotta be right up his ass the whole time.
I can hear, like, my phone
ringing. You guys hear that?
Whoever you're calling right- whoever's calling
me right now can't talk. Fighting
Brownie. I'm not really fighting him, but
racing him. Oh,
you just got passed.
You just got passed, man.
You got passed. Just don't
screw this up. Oh, what a
s- come on. No!
Ugh! Damn it!
I was way ahead of him, too.
I was running circles around him.
I have to stay way ahead.
This is where you gotta get some ground, right here.
Down here, and then don't be
a stupid idiot.
See, right there I screwed that up.
Screwed it up. Oh, my god.
Totally screwed everything up.
Go, go- oh, who's talking to me on Skype?
I'm getting all these, like, notifications.
Come on, you bastard!
What? What? What? Okay.
Thank god.
I made it.
Please don't kill me. I'm- I don't wanna-
I got you, buddy. Don't worry.
Thank you, man.
I appreciate it.
You'll never take him. I'm gonna throw another brick in his face.
You'll see-
Dude, what are you doing?
Leave him alone. She-
I love you.
I love you, too, man. You're gonna
get it. Hi there, how are you? You're dead
when I see you, man. I'm jumping over there. I'm gonna kick
the absolute crap out of you.
Not if I press this button.
I'll just throw it at you.
Alright, guys.
That's chapter three in the bag.
The salt factory.
The salt and sugar factory.
And hell is
next, chapter four.
Let's see how good I do there.
But in the meantime, of course,
enjoy the rest of your day or night, and
I'll see you guys all next time. And of course,
take care, everybody.