Good afternoon, everybody. Hi, I'm there the transmission works. I'm able to transmit data
through a wire
Into your house. How are you?
Unfortunately, it's not perfect. Oh
Oh, I feel it. I could feel it. Our internet was
fixed in quotes
and what that means is it's not fixed and it's
It's they're working on it
They did something they screwed something up and they're trying to fix it. But unfortunately for us
We have to deal with it
Hopefully does not drop that many times
Hopefully doesn't drop to zero
But I I gotta try right? I can't just like oh bye. See you later guys. I'll see you in like three weeks
I've got to try and
this is what this stream is we're gonna try and
And
It's Alex and I because it talks is having this problem too because he also lives here. We've been running
full twitch tests
You didn't know twitch has test servers that you can just stream to and it's a pretend fake stream
and we've been doing this for about two straight days now and
The problem is way less evident than it was
Three or four days ago, but with anything who has any idea?
What may have seemed okay
Yesterday for the whole day with a few drops here and there it was like, alright, we get a whole day of green
Let's go. I'm going for it. And that's what this stream is. And then right when we turn it on, of course it's problems, but
What do you say we talk about since it's been a while? It's been like five six days since I last streamed
That was not my intention
But a couple of things happened if you didn't see I tried to keep some of it a secret over the weekend
I was part of the vinesauces. Hope
Joel's vine wrestle segment. I invaded
Jerma Jerma wrestling Federation invaded vine wrestle. I didn't really talk about it because I wanted they wanted to be a surprise
so I didn't really
Say much about it, but I won't give you any spoilers, but if you haven't seen it, I recommend it
Hyphus crossover. That was a lot of fun. And although I wasn't able to stream on my own channel
I was able to participate in that and it was awesome for a great cause. They do that every year and
I'm just happy to participate
But yeah, I did that. We've also got a couple of ideas
for the future and
what I mean by that is
in the future in like
Don't do this to me. Come on. It was green fucking for the last like
15 hours
Come on
You got you got to give this to me it's been too long you got to give this to me
It's trying
But anyways, I'm just I'm just looking over here at the like drop frames. I'm just like no, no, please don't do this to me
Please I just want to stream. I just want to turn off my live stream. I don't know what they did but
Besides the carnival stream we're just gonna sit here and talk for a minute because
It's been a while. So besides that carnival stream, which is coming up in probably late September
There's another stream that I want to do that would be really fun and it involves the idea that we talked about
the where's Waldo stream where
Somebody or people come together as a community. They make up some fun slides where I have to find on the stream me
green screen cutout on stream
now
That sounds like a lot of fun
but then I thought about you know, what would be better instead of it just being a
Segment where oh, I'm gonna do like 30. Where's Waldo slides. No, I'm gonna do on this stream
I will give you it will once I get everything set in stone. They're probably in a few weeks
I want to do an entire highlights magazine stream. I'm talking dot-to-dots
Hidden objects where's Waldo coloring book section if you remember those magazines they were ridiculous
I want to have like a ask the editor section where people ask me things
It's gonna be a whole highlights magazine
Now this is sounds like it might be hard to do but it won't be it actually would probably pretty easy
so that where's Waldo idea sort of evolved into this and
I would say at some point next week
I'm gonna get some hard details down and we will have like submissions
For this stuff because I'm gonna do some stuff too
I want to I want to like hire out some people to make some crazy shit make a print
Yeah, I want it to be like an actual
Like book at least mine at least I want to do that on stream
But then it actually might be better if it was all digital
I'll come up with all the other the hard stuff here, but that will happen probably in the next few weeks
So I want to give at least a couple weeks for people to submit stuff. So next week we'll give some deadlines there
But that would be fun to do. There's like a jokes, but they had a joke section in highlights magazine
So I want I want you guys to submit your best jokes that I'm gonna read them on stream
It's just gonna be all copypastas more lifelines the minus two section
It's gonna be the same coffee pasta will there be a cereal stream
Um, I thought about the cereal strip, but his thing about a cereal stream
That's kind of it. You open up the boxes of cereal you eat the cereal and then what?
That's it. What are you? What am I?
That is like I would classify eating cereal on stream as
like
Let's say there's like a content layer content level from zero to a hundred. That's like a four
Sleeping on stream is probably like a two
Streaming a black screen is a one
You know I'm saying so that you're only like two or three notches over streaming a black screen with no with muted
So, I mean maybe I would it might be fun but I think that would I would want there to be a segment of a bigger stream
Zero is you're not live. Yeah, but anyways, we're gonna play streets of rogue, which is a rogue like a game
But it's also a kind of an adventure game too could be a bunch of other stuff
How would you know you've never played it neither of I what's a 100? Oh
Carnival stream that's I mean if you were to make a carnival with twitch controlled robots that play
Games on stream like at least at least like three four five of these games on stream and like clowns
I would say that would probably be somewhere around a hundred. I think that's my barometer
anyways
There's also a
There's also a twitch integration in this game. I have no idea how the hell this works, but let's see. Hey, there it is
streets of rogue
Kind of wanted to come back
soft today
Because obviously I I don't know how it I'm
Essentially, I've got a blindfold on I have no idea what's gonna happen with the internet
All I know is that it's on and I'm turning I turned it on and here we are
So there's no going back now unless they turn it off and then that case it's off and we went back
But that's kind of the the state of the update. Let's try it streets of rogue. Here we go
And the guy below me, why would I do that? I'll be green. We're green. I think I'm ready
Elected on vague promises of lower taxes more beer is true color things showed me the art
Okay, this is like the tutorial what happened before this?
Elected on vague promises of lower taxes and more beer
Okay
The whole camp the mayor's first executive order were a massive raise on taxes and a one-time confiscation of all
alcoholic beverages
He stated that the confiscation was so he could throw the mother of all ragers for his constituents
Okay, but in reality there was only like one keg and a bag of torture. I listen
I like this. Yeah, it's already a full letter grade. But in reality, there was only like one keg
I like that. It was super lame. All right now bring it back down full letter grade
I don't like this part
He used the money an extra boost to fund a private army of goons
Happy to carry out his every nefarious bidding before along the city had fallen into a state of chaos
But there is still hope a secretive organization
Organization known only as the resistance has been formed to fight back against the mayor's tyrannical leadership
And that is where our tale begins. It's time to embark on your journey into the
Streets of Rome, baby. So you want to join the resistance? Hey, well, there's something you should know our standards are for entry
I'm extremely hot. I'd offer where you've been hurt in my eyes. You know, that's very fair farm
The first task is move around use WASD. Holy crap. You did it. I'll open that door by pressing the E button
Which one II?
No way. No way. This is the farthest anyone's gotten in a long time
I left a little something for you in that chest. Can you figure out what to do next? This music's pretty good
II
Okay, so that's a lockpick pick any lock just don't expect the owner of said lock to appreciate it
Wow. Oh my god
Haha, but but there's no way that you could possibly figure out what to do with that thing. Oh
Haha. Oh god. I
got a
lock door here
Use lockpick just one
Whatever click it. Yeah. Holy crap. Holy crap
Why oh no, he spontaneously exploded
I'm so sorry you had to see that on the plus side you must be doing pretty well so far for him to get that
Excited he had a lot of emotional problems. Anyways, no use moping around. I'll take over from here
He's gonna explode too. Just watch I'm teleporting you some money use it to buy a hacking tool from our staff shopkeeper
50 bucks
Staff shopkeeper as you oops
What are you buying I'm buying
hacking tool
Jesus
Single-use device that will hack into any computer remotely
Okay, and he didn't explode. Oh, he will
Access your inventory by pressing Q
Then right click the hacking tool to select it and left click the computer
Which computer that one?
So right click to use and then click on the computer
Try to do from that far away
Open locked doors read email. That would be rude. Ah, you're right. It'll be pretty rude. Yeah, I don't do it
Try it again. Okay, open locked doors. I got it. Okay. Sorry. Good dad
This is as fast as I can move. What's E entrance?
Alright, so I'm at the computer
I'm gonna send you on a little trial mission to see what it is. Press tab
Destroy the generator which is up here. So I gotta go left up right up right down. Okay
Gonna send you a little trial. Let's see what to do. All right, Nick, what can I do anything go on the bathtub?
punch
Can I punch the computer? Yeah, but I don't want to break it
Should I break the bed?
Someone is on guard duty in the building past this fence to see more info hold space
Hostile, it looks like he won't be too happy to see you. And by the way, if someone's name is yellow
It means they own the property
I'm teleporting you a wall bypasser try using it in your toolbar press the number key that it corresponds to its log wall bypasser
What what tip?
Okay, typically a red door means people don't want you in there
Door do not enter. Okay, this is bouncer hostile
resistance later, alright, so
Just open the door and just kind of knock. Is there a knock on door?
Meet our staff bouncer. He'll be playing the part of bad guy, but he's been interested instructed not to fight back under any circumstance
Hello, nice to make your acquaintance rookie. Feel free to wail on him as hard as you can. He's a big guy. He can take it
Excuse me, but I don't recall agreeing to this when you sign your resistance paperwork
Perhaps you'll recall section 7c which states members are subject to any and all of the resistance leaders illogical dangerous and are sadistic whims
Look, you have no right to allow some random guy off the street to take shots at me for the sake of some what you call
It tutorial
We can do whatever we want to you. We're the ones in charge
You know, this is the same sort of ridiculous authoritarian crap the mayor pulls
Mayor that's the mayor stop being a wimp. You'll be fine
This piece is a double agent. We gave you that sweet hard hat. Remember?
fair enough
Grab that weapon wait
Baseball bat. Oh
damn
Grab that tranquilizer gun and cycle to it with mouse wheel. I
See, okay
How many do I have to shoot him with? I did way too many. I just over tranquilized him
I got the key to the base
Okay, do you see that blue meter at the top of your screen you'll get skill points for things like murdering and lockpicking, okay
Right like up here. All right
For murdering and what gets more points now walk through that red sensor is totally safe and not harmful at all. Teehee
Bah ha ha ha. I'm sorry. I couldn't resist that never gets old. I hope you're okay. Take this bacon cheeseburger
You can quick use your health items by pressing F
Is it really why does it have to be a bacon cheeseburger?
Really? Didn't I talk shit about this like a few days ago?
Okay, take the bacon cheeseburger
Quick use your health by pressing F bacon cheeseburger. Oh just that was so epic
There's something you can use to deal with the lasers a little more safely. Just use it like you did the other weapons
What is it a rock? He's raw rocks people
Really?
Holy shit, I can throw rocks at people. All right, this game just got way better
You mean I'm wet. Why am I wet? I have no way to open this
I'm gonna give you a really cool special ability that you can use to teehee open the door to use it
Press the right mouse button
wah
I call this the Waluigi scream the special ability that gave you was cry profusely
I mean, that's not very useful at all. Is it check out on your stats screen press R
Nobody liked the Waluigi scream. I thought like wait, wait, hold on
Maybe are we on the internet because I always thought that if you say the word Waluigi or do
W-A-H-H you automatically are way cooler of a person
Is that not cool anymore?
Well, all right. I'm gonna have to remember that
Damn. All right. Well, I apologize about that. I thought that I thought that Waluigi Wow was still like automatically
retweeted
Special ability where is it cry profusely cause you to cry like a little baby
Serves no purpose except to embarrass you. Okay. Well, I did get embarrassed
It worked it worked you working as intended
Here's a key. Oh, whoops
I just accidentally teleported into the elevator where you first came in open your mission screen with tab
Then you can look at the entrance to teleport to the entrance. Oh, that's cool
Once you grab the key, you can quick teleport by pressing left control under normal circumstances. This will teleport you to important locations
All right
Destroy that generator to complete your mission. You got it
I
Can't throw rocks at it, unfortunately, I can't do that. How do I do it? I punch it. I
Don't think I would ever hit like a space heater with a baseball bat. That's probably a bad idea. It's gonna blow up
Tutorial done all you knew to get out of the way. You're no fun
Anyway, sorry for all the hazing. You're pretty tough cookie. We only lost one person during this exercise. That's a new record who?
Congratulations, you can join speak to the doctor when you get in we'll see about getting you another bacon cheeseburger
I'm in a home base. Oh the first guy right the guy that exploded, but I thought that was like a magician thing
You missed a rock. Is there like a go pee? Oh god his free points his free comedy points if I can do that
Get out of here. This is not the doctor. This is the
Okay, I
Don't know why I
Was the first person I saw in a room. I look okay. I knew that was a toilet, but this could be I know I'm fucking stupid
So I have a few other things to let you know before we send you out on the suicide men
Oh completely achieved mission of taking down the mayor
Since you're new to the city, you should know that it's built in vertical layers like a lasagna. I fucking hate lasagna
slums at the bottom then the industrial area then the faux outdoor park downtown and uptown at the top
The only way to get from one level to nexus through the elevator
In addition to your primary mission won't you do a bunch of other stuff too. They'll be highlighted on your map like that generator
You just blew up
You'll need to finish your missions on a floor before you can travel to the next one
Resistance leaders like myself will help you out by sending you rewards for completing these missions
But that's about all we can do for you. We're less doers in more idea
Why am I doing like the person in line at Disney World to monitor that you walk by
I'm like that actor that is on the screen. I'm gonna slow down here
For example, it was my idea to send you out on this mission
So do me proud because they might be a promotion in it for me as you may know the mayor has banned chicken nuggets
Due to the fact that they once caused him a mild tummy ache
Wait, did you ban chicken nuggets?
Chicken nuggets have since become a rare and precious commodity
Re if you can scrounge up some chicken nuggets
We can trade him for things that can help you out
The doctor the thief and the soldier can brief you a bit more on the nugget situation
Or if you want to be heading the city the elevators to your north. Good luck to you young road. Oh
By the way, stay out of the occupied restrooms that kind of activity embarrasses the resistance more than it does you
What a callback. All right, so I can what's in here a fridge
Can't open this as a safe in there won't just open it
Can I steal from my own self?
Well, if you that's doesn't make any sense if you steal from yourself, it's just yours
What about the fridge?
Trash, it's just mine. I would be taking an item from one place and putting it in another place in my house
Beds are I don't think I can do anything these things. Oh
Everybody everybody good co-op. Oh, yeah, there's like there's a multiplayer room traits. All right, I want to learn about this
By the way, I I've since activated
something so
From now on if the stream does go to zero if I just disconnect
There's gonna be like a little streams not gonna turn off
there's gonna be a little like disconnect symbol and
I have like a minute or two to come back
So I put like that protection on
Let's see if it works. Oh
Bacon cheeseburgers. Oh, sorry. I ate the last one while I was performing a long surgery. I
Know your body better than you do that sounds weird unlock traits
These traits will appear when you gain a skill level and compete complete the current floor
home sickness
Followers will always follow you to the next floor
Tax likely to do crit damage more
Lasagna ignore that's lasers passed by lasers on the tank. No in fighting can't hit most people you are aligned with and they can't hit you
Huh, there's a lot of stuff here do I have any money? Oh these these cost chicken nuggets
There's a lot of stuff here. So I don't have any chicken nuggets
XD
Come on. It's fine. This loadouts rewards. Oh
Damn, all right. This is gonna it's too much for me to know. I think I just have to play
pod processor
bulletproof vest reduces bullet damage
All right, I need to get you. Let me get two chicken nuggets before I do anything else
So this wards trades a loadout
Choose a loadout item to be taken into the next game re-roll items. Oh
Okay
mutators I
Can literally hack the whole game? That's how leet I am choose a mutator clear all mutators that you've enabled
More knockback is applied to all hits. This is just kind of making the game harder
Yeah, full health for everybody. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I'm not doing that right now and I already did this
Hard did the tutorial. Let's just go down. I'm ready
Let's go down in the slums
What on earth is this?
Who do you want to be today?
the Hamburgler
No, wait, wait, these are classes. All right. Hold on
endurance speed melee firearms traits
Potential to not suck a random stat gains a point every other level up starting with level 2
More traits to choose from when you level up
Gain lots of extra XP earn fewer chicken nuggets
Okay, what about the soldier health gradually regenerates when below 20
Starting at your machine gun
gangster blood basher
team
knife pistol friend phone
What's a hamburger will have sticky gloves stand behind your victim and use this tool to steal from their pocket like the sticky bandit you are
Honor among thieves purchase tools from thieves at discounted prices. These will not steal from you
Business owners want you to leave
Enemies have more difficulty aiming at you. I kind of like it. I got a crowbar
hacker
Pretty good speed remotely hack any computer
You can move while hacking
What about I kind of want to be a doctor? I'm gonna be the doctor
What?
chloroform
hanky move behind enemy use chloroform step three profit
Can't use weapons except for some thrown items each followers health can be restored once per floor
I'm gonna be the doctor
ear warp whistle first aid kit and tranquilizer gun
Okay, I want a big smile. Hold on. Yeah, I need a big smile
Dr. Mario
What does Mario have for hair
Like that, right?
Yeah, all right. We're gonna be dr. Mario
One of the few true pacifists in this dangerous world indeed
The doctor is very skilled at pacifying people with chloroform, but business is currently booming
What with all the beating being administrated by cops since the mayor's new law of the land was put in place
Despite the extra cash flow the doctor would rather the streets be safe and has decided to join the resistance
Okay, big quest
Spread your righteous message of peace and chloroform by not killing
A hundred too many a hundred many people too many people
And chloroform but not killing too many so don't kill anybody
All right. I'm gonna try it. Let's just go
Unaccept you I have no idea what to do go
Go go
Okay, attack special interact inventory. Yeah. All right. All right. Let's just go. What have I got in my minute?
This is the the Legend of Zelda flu
Temporarily destroys the hearing of everyone on the floor. Give them the peace and quiet they deserve
Can the doctor punch? All right. Let's take a look at the map. So we got operate all switches and you get free item voucher
Break out of prison
Pritter upper. All right, so we're gonna break people out of prison
All right, let's go
Hostile so I have to get up. I have to sneak up behind people and use chloroform
It's the clerk. All right, hold on
Tranquilizer gun. All right. I'm gonna go open door shoot Clark with tranquilizer gun nine eight
Wow, all right
Key to the bank and a safe combination. How long are they out for? All right, where's my chloroform? How do I do chloroform?
No, that's not chloroform. I thought it was first aid kit tranquilizer. I think this can I just right-click on people behind them?
Holy shit, did it work? What? Okay, cool
Recharge door. What's this computer? Can I have computers?
Open locked or unlock safe. I want read the email
Okay, I don't I open up a safe. I
Got all unlocked. I locked on like the door
What's this purple stuff turret? Oh, it's a security cam. Can I turn off security cameras?
All right. I don't think I can go this way. Yeah, I can I get it's time, right?
All right, when it goes around in a chloroform
When this I got an opportunity, he's got a gun. What if he shoots me?
What if he just shoots me? Do I die?
How much health am I 95 health?
Am I good? Oh, hey
Okay, I got I got a gun. How do I put the gun on? No, I don't want to use the toy gun
Oh, I can't I'm a doctor. I can't use guns
pretty good tuber reaction
Can I shoot these? Let's get can I tranquilize the security camera? No, how the hell am I supposed to do this?
Okay like that safe. Ooh, what I got the combination of the safe, don't I?
The $47. Okay, I got 47 bucks turret. What? How do I get over here? I have to go
Ammo dispenser. How do I get up here? Is there a way to get up from there? Oh
Okay, that was for real that wasn't a YouTube reaction. That was an actual that was a human reaction
How do I get over here I
See right there. That was a tuber reaction, but it wasn't who's this? Wait
Hey
How you doing assist me? I'm a 20 bucks. Let's go. Can I tell them what to do?
Cause a ruckus administer treatment give items. Hey
Take a gun take the gun and take the baseball bat. All right, you're ready
Okay, let's go. No, no, no, don't cause a ruckus
Hey, I trust you here. Take
What I have a nerf gun you take the real one by the way nice to meet you in the prison
I'm gonna turn around now. What a clear shot up my head
For 20 bucks. All right, what trash?
ammo dispenser refill gun
22 bucks not worth it
Loadout. Oh medic. It's just okay. I can add to my loadout. All right break these guys up
I'll handle this you stay here. How do I say stay here?
You gave this person your money and your gun
Wait, come here. Ah
That's twice. Ah
Too many people. What are you doing? Wait, did you just take my money?
What do you mean too many people? I got to break these people out. All right, ready? I'm gonna do this passively
Check it out
Wait, hold on. Why wait wait wait watch out get out of the way get out of the way
Okay, I'm gonna wait till he comes back and turns around you can knock on the door
Got it. Okay, break out
Everybody out what I just I just opened one door. Oh god. Wait, no, no, just leave. How do I I?
Thought I had that's like a skeleton key. I need more keys. All right. I should have got the chest
Can I break this down? No
Computer. Oh my god. Give me a fucking break
Good thing I used the key
What's in the chest six bucks? That's it. All right. I have to destroy this right?
Are there people coming in here? No
Operate the switch get the item vouchers here. What about this thing? Oops
Let's do something
I almost killed that guy. I always exploded that loyal
Don't just run in here like that
Okay, let's go up this
Alright when they run when they sprint over here, it freaks me out
drug dealer loyal
Dammit, why did I have to use that key?
All right you can I tell you to go in here. I have to operate that switch
Nobody in there. All right, you ready you?
Uh
Cause a bruh. No, you're gonna get seen by the cameras. This is locked. Oh Jesus
I have to go all the way down. Don't I can I make it through just?
Get him get him
Shoot him. What are you doing? What are you doing? What are you doing? Help me. Where's the help me button?
You didn't want me to stand here and get shot I
Did not I did not what a waste of $20
Operate the switches. I have to break the cameras. Okay. Who's this drug dealer? He's hostile
Holy shit, he's strong. Whoa, has he got three nuggets? No, I got one. I can't I'll kill this guy. I want to kill him
laser emitter
rock, right
Okay, free item voucher
Floor clear elevator open 21 bucks. Give me the rock
Do it what I'm stepping on every trap. All right, how do I get this person to how do you get followers to actually do things?
Well, I can go in here. I can go in here and I can attack the scientist
hacker
scientist what do you think should I
knock
Hello, you don't need brains to be a scientist just hard identify item. What's in here peanut butter? What I just get
Wait, what's the syringe? Who knows what effect this mysterious liquid will have on your body?
There can only be one doctor me still
Didn't use the key. So that's good
hair filtration system
No idea
All right, slum dweller. The hacker is let's knock on the door. Hey, I am anonymous. Well, I guess not anymore
You have any stuff in here refrigerator?
bartender
Slum dweller, what about TV? I don't want anybody to assist me get out of here. I just want to change your televisions
That's it
bartender slot machine. Okay, I know what I'm doing
Open the door. How's the window? Hey, how are you? How do I talk to him?
Can I not talk to them buy from shop use a voucher?
Eases your pain in more ways than one 10 health beer martini
plus 10 health
Thanks. Okay. I
Just got free beer
This is like this is one of those shitty open bars when they give you one ticket. Oh, yeah, welcome to the open bar
It's a super huge party. Here's your drink ticket. The next one will be 18 bucks
All right. Well, did I waste that? Oh
shit
Sorry, I'm sorry. I just like destroyed your house. I'm flooding his house
What's the mission?
Alright, I'm fine. Did I get any chicken nuggets? I'm such an asshole. Alright, forget that. Let's just keep going
Everybody's nice to me here. Why is everybody so nice to me? He's gonna my doctor. Oh
shit, oh
What am I thinking? No, not always crick. What I just get I killed somebody
Hey, do you steal something?
Who's on my team? What is going on over here? Uh
Oh
Come on, come on
Get out of the way get out of the way get out of the way get out of the way. Oh
Mystery I don't I don't have enough money
Those guys look like taunting me
Complete all your mission objectives to proceed to the next floor or the city or fail them if that's your thing. Either way is good. Okay, I
Got all my objectives done, right? Yeah, I did. I got them all done
next level
Press E. Yeah, it's a elect ability
Minus two
Let me elect ability. I angered ten out of ten people. I didn't kill any innocent people
I knocked out nine out of nine. I killed one person. I
Didn't die. That's good. Oh, I can pick a trade
He you leveled up select a new trait for your character
Enemies have more difficulty aiming at you. All syringes are identified. I comment on that is
You're doing something bar fills much more quickly
Either this one or this one
Drugs, this is just level one two. I went down the first pipe in Mario. Great. Okay, so what does this do?
get away from
syringe sulfuric acid who knows what effect this will have
bonus effects sulfuric acid two seconds
What is this gonna kill me?
Law of the land if we didn't see it it didn't happen
Please commit all crimes within our view if it's out of our jurisdiction. We're not dealing with it
No fighting unless protection your property then we protect you no breaking break dancing is acceptable
No stealing no tampering all punishable by death
Okay. Well, I need to heal
Like it for burgers
Okay
So the mission here is operate all the switches
Get the money up here and then retrieve the blueprints from the chest
Free these people over here, okay free people
Take stuff. I can afford not to eat fud six days a week
Open the door again. I did that is took the fud. That was pretty mean. Oh
sleeping
No, I'm gonna go to another level
Quick tell him to sell all of his shares of his company when he goes under twice. What's that?
translator
Slot machines don't touch him. So I this is just like a town. I don't have to be like a psycho or anything
Like let's just do I'm just gonna go. Do I have a key? I'm going in there. I'm getting up
It doesn't work like that. Apparently ATM. Oh, you're a doctor, too, huh? Do I have a key? I don't I
Thought I did
No, let's just do the mission. I can figure that out later all kind of hostile
Okay, how do I open this?
How do I go? Are you facing this way or that way? I can't tell
Okay hacking tool. I got an axe. Oh
My he just killed that guy. Wait, I I freed
Okay, he just hit that guy right in that head like three times. How is that a crime? Oh
God damn it. Okay. Hold on. Where's my tranquilizer? Where's my tranquilizer?
How do I stop this? I have this I have to chloroform him. He's way faster than me. Oh
Shit, they got me in a pickle
Come on refer on quick. This is loony tune shit. Now. I'm chasing him police baton. Got it. Okay, was there the was it a cop?
No, there is oh
There's a lot of cops over here
I'm in trouble. I'm in trouble
Alright, so I can't go up there, but I have to go up there
Look, can I no I don't have any money. Why do they do the stupid thing in the machine?
Alright, what's the main mission is over here, right? Retrieve this item. Can I not go in this door?
I guess I can
Who's in here boon?
Computer over there too. Can I sell these items? I can't even hope this is locked. No, I'm good. I'm good
Take the blueprint. I got three chicken nuggets and I leveled up
So that leaves me with this one operate all the switches and get the money. Oh, there's a sell-o-matic right here
Okay
These guys not gonna come attack me right baseball bat 13 bucks
Yeah, I'm just gonna sell these I can't use any of them sword. All right, I'm gonna hold on to the sword and the ax
hard hat
No, I'll keep that any ammo for that thing
Beer, I need the beer
Cigarettes, I don't need those. I don't think for anything
Translates gorilla speak into any language except for one the language of love. So this isn't just I don't need that, right?
That's just like a treasure
Places on a locked door agitate the door in some way BAM. Okay
All right, I think I'm all right. I don't think I'm kind of scared. I don't really know what to do
All right. This is a goon here
cop here
All right. He's not I didn't do anything wrong
Opening the door is not wrong. Can I talk to the cop?
Ignore you ignore crimes on the whole level to 50 bucks. No, it's not worth it. What's in here?
shelf I can free you
What's in the plant?
Item and plant why is it? Oh shit, I just broke a plant. How do I hide this doctor sucks?
All right, I gotta get in here
Wait load automatic
augmentation booth
There's so much to do in this game. All right, this is what I needed. I thought you guys forget crimes if you don't see me
What you remember this you remember this hole you remember me how?
Alright, I'm not gonna kill him. I'm just gonna walk them through and they're gonna burn
Ready? Oh god, it's everybody's bad. Everybody's bad. I'm dead. I'm gonna die
Hey, why are they shooting at the cops?
They'll kill each other
It doesn't matter. They don't even need me
chicken nuggets. Oh
I just cut pinball machine
Okay, somebody turn and hit this thing
This three of us here arrest the one that's closest. No, don't just give up. I need to go in here
Turn off all the switches. Is there one more? Where is it down the bottom go to pacifist?
I'm trying. It's like oh, yeah, I picked my first run to be pacifist
Don't you know that I am a toddler? That's it. There's five dollars in here. That's it
Okay, I can go to the next floor. So if I hit control
All right, you know, can I teleport up there? I?
Can't teleport indoors
Have to be out here
There's too much danger. Oh shit
All right. I'm thinking of going for chaos here. I just have to get up there and just go in the door
What have I done? Oh my god, I'm gonna die. I turned in the one fucking maze that didn't have the cheese in it
Oh my god
We're good. Get away from me killed somebody
Accidentally time eight minutes. That's not bad. Here we go endurance plus
Increases endurance was endurance and increased up
Enemies are more likely to run away during a battle and easier to knock people through walls. I think I'm gonna take endurance
or this one
Disturbing facial expressions. Yeah, I'm gonna do endurance make yourself ugly
No, I don't need to I'm not aware. What am I not aware of?
What did that say?
Retrieve a tooth. What did that just that the big thing popped up and screamed at me while I was looking at chat
Okay, get the baseball from the gangster and I get a four-leaf clover
Retrieve the tooth from the safe and I get 58 bucks. You got it. There's an ammo dispenser right here. That's what I need
refill the gun
what a
hundred bucks a
Hundred dollars. I have to do it. Okay. I need the gun. I have to have it. Hey, let's go do this first
Gang who has the thing up here. I need to have like a crew. Don't I?
Why is there a robot shooting rockets at us?
Um, I didn't does that count for me that shit doesn't count for me, right? What do I do about this guy?
Why is there just a pick the narrowest fucking hallway in the world?
Who threw money in the trash?
No, just open it. I love how he waited the fire. Oh
Wait, be careful. Oh
Fuck he's right here
The game told you no look. I was looking over a chat because somebody called me ugly
So I looked over I was like, I'm not fucking ugly and I didn't see the big thing
I asked what the big thing was and then somebody
All right. I'm gonna be soldier. That is start from the beginning. Do I start here? What do I start at the bottom?
Who did I pick soldier slums one go? All right. So what do I get?
All right, I'm ready one of my missions get the baseball from the chest
Go I'm no longer a doctor. So like I'm I forget what the traits were though
All right, where are we going up here?
No, I'm skeezer. I'm used fists landmine. I don't do that. We gotta get in
Right there. All right, I'm gonna go to the computer unlock the door
The doors not up here. The doors down here coming in. Give me that chest take all mission complete got the mini fridge
Next slide
All right. What's down here? There's
There's a chest in here. I'm gonna get the chest
Do they get what they see me? Do I know I don't have a cause a problem or anything, right?
Still no, forget it
Give me the chest. Where is it?
It is money and stuff in here
I'm gonna fuck a put this away. Just walk in the store. I
Get I can't do that. Whoo. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. Just watch out man
Was it a gorilla is it hostile
character unlocked
What does it I can be a gorilla character?
All right, that's pretty cool
What do I have for ammo? Not very much. I'm gonna put this away sandwich
All right, I was gonna do a knife destroy that you got it. No, I don't want to blow this up
Is there another way to get in? There's two gorillas. All right, just blow it up. What cancel then I don't come over here
Don't come over here
Scientists get away from the door get away from lunch get away from your lunch get away from your lunch
Stop, what are you doing? What do you think? This is gonna do
Guys, I don't want to hurt anybody. Oh, no, our life's work
I'm gonna cut one of them. All right. Now you're gonna run right? Yeah. Okay. I'm not chasing him with a knife
I just want to open this up. I can't open these stop
I
Don't want to hurt anybody. I really don't want to hurt all of you. I don't want to hurt
Get away from me
Leave me alone. I don't want to hurt anybody
All right, open the doors
What? Okay. Yeah
No, no, no more scientists
I don't like playing the mean character. I want to play with the nice character again
I don't want to be the guy that like kills people. I probably shouldn't have picked the soldier
Huh? Okay. I got plus one elect ability somehow. Let's see backstabber
All map markers are filled at the beginning of levels. That's cool
Melee attacks from behind you two times damage of the victim is not in combat
Ten times of using camouflage
GPS
Backstab. All right
Bouncer what do we need retrieve the blueprints over here?
Just get all the stuff. There's two things right here in here
MacGuffin muffin
There's a clone machine. All right, let's go
Anywhere you can get in here without causing a problem. Not really backstab times two damage three two
These scientists have knives. Oh, he picked up a bat
My grandma clone item. Oh, that's cool. Okay
Burger on the ground. All right. I lost my helmet. That's not good
What's going on in here? I gotta get in there. Let's go up
Retrieve item from the drug dealer
Watch out for the for the person sized hornet. That's outside your window
Why would I destroy that? Is this a deal or do I have to take it?
bribe with item bribe threatened as a 45% chance
Okay, I got it. Oh, I got a shotgun
Nice. All right. Now I'm a force to be reckoned with current run failed. Oh
Shit, I've destroyed generators. Okay. Well, I'll remember that the next time
So I got the shotgun
I need to get the muffin now
These guys aren't hostile. I have to go in the shopkeeper's back room for this. How do I do this without causing a problem?
buy from shop
I can't sneak behind him to blow up the wall
uh, I mean
Will that work?
Stop run away from me. Get away from me. I'm dangerous
All right, got the muffin. Okay. Next is uh bottom right here. I don't want to use all this ammo
I do need a heal too
M
What's it m?
That's not on my mini map. What is that? What's m?
It's a side quest
Are you gonna attack me?
mission
Neutralize the bartender and you get five chicken nuggets for this shit
Uh, okay
Wait, didn't I already neutralize the bartender?
neutralize
I promise about holding a grenade
What? Oh, I'm gonna
Oh i'm good
That's a lot of chicken nuggets
five chicken nuggets
I need to heal
Do I have to have a burger right? Yeah
I'm close to leveling up. Maybe I shouldn't
I'm not okay. I'm not gonna get any trouble. What's this syringe do?
I have a lot of random stuff kill
Ammunizer as a reward for killing three people your guns will receive ammunition
To ensure that the cycle of violence continues
Okay
Detonator for normally you'd need to be up all night to get lucky with this. You'll have better luck all the time
insert groan
I feel like garfield the Monday killer wrote
half of these uh blurs
Anybody else feel like that?
All right. Let's go with uh, i'll drink a beer
Okay
That's enough. Let's get going now. I just have to do. Uh, that's a lot of money. I'll do this destroy this
It's a safe down here, too
We got
safe
Turret I should be all right. Don't run in front of that
Although i'm gonna have to neutralize this guy
Um, I could just place the detonator. Yeah
Let's go
Can I hit him through the wall?
Oh shit
I ain't failing this
I ain't gonna fuck that up safe combination. Oh
32 bucks that's that was worth it
Okay, I need to go down here
Nobody in what did I just do poisoned? What do you mean?
Uh-oh
How long does it last seven seconds? That's not gonna kill me, right?
God damn it. All right
I just have to destroy this and then i'm done
This is a computer over here. I need to know what in the name of god
The stupid pressure plates. I just keep thinking that tiles
All right, i'm out
It's 56 bucks. All right, let's go
Full health there it is finally. All right, give me the shotgun
Let's go up front here. Nothing else, right? This is safe
It's not worth it
No, it's not worth it. I'm going
Is it worth it? No
So what does the green and blue mean? Does that mean it's a rarer?
perk
How does that work?
Health gradually regenerates when below 40. That's really good
Increase this attribute is just melee. Okay followers gain extra health
The plus means it's an upgrade. Okay
I like this one
What is it gonna be two instead of one?
Greatest trades blue is attributes of stats. All right, that's cool
There's something in the area status effect
strength 10 what
All right, I gotta start moving
Three two one. What does that mean?
Always crit. Oh shit. Okay. I get it. It's gonna be all right. I get it. I get it
Why is the person tiny?
No, no, no, why is everyone so small?
Um, what are what are the missions?
Destroy the generator neutralize the hacker you got it
What how did that not destroy the wall i'm invisible
Oh dear. Okay. Um, somebody just exploded but i'm not sure why
I don't know why they exploded. Um
i'm gonna wait till
Shoot through the window electro touch. Wait, wait, wait electro touch electro touch
What? Why can I not hurt him?
Neutralize the little guy get him. This is out of control. All right. Um
One more thing to do just gotta do the destroy the generator
Weak, okay. I'm gonna wait this out
Get in here
No chest or anything
I gotta go through this bullshit again
That guy always creates I had to do that. There was just two i'm invincible. All right. I got an item voucher
Let's go
I want this chest
Fast come on. Hurry up
That's it
All right, get me out
out, please
Come on. Stop being dizzy
Stop. No, don't waltz over to the stew accurate. Okay
I need like a cello matic whatever they are
I'm getting weird because i'm big
What the hell?
I didn't even know I could do that. Oh, just run away. Just get away from me, please
I can't teleport right now. I have no control over the character
All right. What do I have? This is a knife police baton. All right
I don't want to be part of this
I'm gonna just collect the items though
Nobody dropped anything
Okay odd but whatever
Ammo refill the gun. All right, I want my shotgun reloaded
worth it
What about this load out of attic?
Give me a door detonator. I'm gonna need one of these
All right, let's go mutator unlocked. This is the second floor new zone industrial one
What does this say?
Welcome to the industrial zone. We strive to provide a safe working environment for all of our expendables
All right, what's the mission here?
industrial so I gotta destroy two
Of those things operate the switches give me the hard hat and then I have to get
Retrieve the will from the drug dealer and I get a ghost gibber
Okay
Let's go
Thank you mini what does this do keeps your food nice and fresh
A couple of landmines. I'm not gonna get enticed by I can't get enticed by this
I'll do it once
All right, if I see okay if I see 98 percent nose, uh, I won't do it
No, i'm not gonna do it. Can I sell stuff buy from shop?
Random cocktail. No, I gotta I need one of those selling machines
Is there one around here?
generator
No, it's gotta go
Try it once
I get
Done. All right, start the generators retrieve the item. I wonder if threaten will work on this guy
Is it really only one way to get in there?
Oh shit, that was not a smart idea
I didn't know they exploded that violently
All right, now they got him. He's pretending to lag
I have it set every every like 20 minutes. I have it set to like cause a problem
My internet I have it make it so it shuts it off
Uh, all right, let's get the safe and let's do this first. Is there anything quiet?
Not really
Another generator where
Can you turn that off so we can watch? Oh, there's a dis twitch integration in this game
I just have to turn it on
I don't know what it does. I want to do a few rounds where I just got familiar with the game
So maybe we can add some stuff
All right. So next thing I need to do is where's the uh
One more generator, but should I even be doing this?
All right, there we go. Sellomatic. That's what I want
Chat picks the perks for you at the end of floors. All right, that's kind of cool
Touch me
All right. I'm gonna get rid of the
I'm gonna get rid of a mini fridge
I'm gonna keep the sandwich. I'm gonna get rid of the
machine gun banana
baseball bat police baton
This thing's expensive
hacking tool
I don't know. I just don't know what's good
All right, i'm gonna get rid of the knife
Get rid of the machine gun, maybe
I'm not using the landmines at all
Oh, well, I don't know streamer actively avoids twitch mode to ignore his viewers
Well, wouldn't that be not ignoring you guys?
Isn't me turning on the twitch mode?
engaging with you guys
Isn't that what that means?
All right. I need to do this. I gotta go in here and have to
Turn all the switches off
And when I say no, I mean the next building up never mind. I'm not supposed to be in here. Why?
There we go
Who's in here? We got goon two goons one goon
What is that?
tube
I'm gonna say i'm gonna go up and then down
What is he coming to?
Turn this back on
Oh, you can fall down there
Read emails out of the way
All right, how close am I to leveling up? I don't need to heal
More switches the workers come and turn them back on
Free check. I gotta do go back home and get some chicken nugget on upgrades
I'm going this way
It'll be easier to turn that off without causing a problem
Got it hard hat floor clear
Let's get out. Although is there anything else I want to do?
I could destroy that
Should I?
Yeah, I okay. I failed the total mission. Does that mean I shouldn't even do this at all?
I failed everything didn't I?
So is me doing this actually do anything?
Am I just wasting time right here? It's already filled right? Yeah, there's no point
Well, i'm already down here. So might as well just do it right? I'm like already here
How big is this explosion?
This looks like it's gonna be pretty big
It is an overloaded generator. All right, that's good. Let's get out here
I unlock jock
Total deaths one
Enemies have more difficulty aiming at you
You're doing something bar fills more quick. Uh
What does that mean? You're doing something bar. What's that mean?
Experience
And i'm gonna assume it's exp, right?
Oh, it's that when the bar that fills when you do something. Okay
Yeah, i'm not even gonna do this anymore because I failed it. I'm an idiot
All right, so we need to neutralize this slum dweller
We get three cardboard boxes just they're all kind of right in a row
There's a atm over here and there's a safe right there. All right, let's go
I don't want to make a whole lot of noise. Let's go baseball bat
Knock on the door. Let it open
whack
I took three bullets four bullets
I'm gonna die. I'm going to die right now. I'm gonna die right now. That's how ridiculous why did that just happen to me?
I just ate the guy's whole clip and he ran out of ammo
Ooh, all right. Uh, yep. I actually have a silencer on this now. That's good
finally
Eat the sandwich clone machine
clone self
Okay, you can have a grenade and a baseball bat
Uh, let's go worker
power box
There's a mission over here. What do you want me to do? Excuse me doctor?
mission
Rescue the drug dealer and you get five chicken nuggets. Let's do it. I think you've had enough. It's something I never said
All right
rescue drug dealer
I'm gonna have like 20 or 30 nuggets after this. It's gonna be kind of hard
considering
This is the police station
Is there a way to open these doors without causing a problem?
Is there a computer?
Shit, how do I do this without causing a problem?
Does this ignore crimes? No
Keys. Yeah, maybe a key
When is he gonna play minecraft again?
in 20 minutes
It's a lie. I'm not doing that
Oh, no
How am I gonna do this?
I can't just blow this because it's gonna kill him. There's gotta be a key that I can get from somebody
I'm gonna have to try to get a key from one of the cops. Let me put the sign. No, let me
Yeah, somebody has to have a key
There it is. You did it minecraft resident sleeper
Oh wait
That's right. You're a prisoner. Um
We're gonna go down
Don't get burnt
Down down down down follow follow follow. Let's go go go
Nope. Nope. Nope. What do you mean? Nope
All right, I did it five nuggets resident resident sleep
I can't do those. How does that work? Next up on the list is to
Go this way. Whoa
I did look it's not he's annoyed
Yeah, I got blown through here with a gun in my hand. I didn't do anything. Why did he do that?
Did he steal from me? I don't understand
All right, I'm gonna turn these off. Let's see this one first retrieve the item from the worker
Oh god, this is gonna be ugly
My mystery item sure
hypnotizer mark two
Use this on someone to make them align with you because everyone needs somebody to lean on. Okay, that's cool
He's ugly
Uh, my partner's gonna die here. Can I tell you to stay here? Just stand here
Poison great. I'm trying to make you stand here and it's killing me
Oh god, you stepped on it, too. Just stay here
Where should I stand down in the corner over there?
You're gonna die on you
What what is poisoning you? Why are you still poisoned?
I'm confused. Okay
How am I gonna do this?
What this is supposed to be silent?
Shit, give me the tooth and let's get out of here
Wait, they can turn off the gas. Oh god. Give me a break. I'm an idiot
All right, come with me. Let's go
We just need to do this part. The chest is chest. Where's it you think?
No, it's not
I need to i'm gonna die. I need to heal we have to get the fuck out of here
The streamer doesn't have pepe laugh enabled
No, I guess I don't no, I don't you're right
Oh shit, I don't have that enabled. What am I what am I supposed to do?
All right, here's another bullshit mission
You stay here
Stand here
I'll do this on my own. I don't need your help
Countdown started
Let me
Holy shit
What?
I just got bounced around like crazy. Oh, that was annoying
Uh, let's go to the home base
I want to I just got a lot of chicken nuggets
Gorilla, can I talk to the gorilla?
All right
Whatever new traits
25 chicken nuggets these will appear
In the game. Oh man, I don't even know
Knockback damage is decreased
You can recruit up to three people but they suck though. They're idiots
Explosions caused by the players don't damage the player. That's pretty good
Wall wall hopper melee weapons can destroy certain walls when equipped for a large durability cost
gain extra experience
burning bullets
Drop weapons contain more ammo
Damage inflicted on the player may not cause any health loss. What?
a crit
That's weird. All right. Well, hold on. There's more stuff to do
rewards loadouts rewards
Accuracy, these items will appear as rewards when you complete missions
Right, okay
Call on your buddies to teleport nearby and help you out of a jam or just keep you company
time bomb
oil container
I need to i'm gonna drop the music a little
all I hear is
the
Main menu screen of like a ball rolling ipad game where you have to roll the 3d ball around
And get it into a hole at the end of the level. I don't know why that's all I hear
What else we got?
electro pill
Play that game
All in due time. I think i'm just gonna have to I think i'm just gonna have to buy something
I'm so bad with shit like this guys, you know that
Choose a loadout item to be taken to the next game. All right, you can just pick something to axe
I mean some of these are really good
mutators
Can I unlock characters?
Choose a mutator. All right
Unlock stuff. All right, i'm gonna unlock. Um, I don't know
i'm gonna unlock
Uh, i'm gonna do that cool trait down here
I like this one melee weapons can destroy walls. It's done. I can't even go back on it
So I already did it
cool it with
cannibals
Cannibals will no longer attack you on sight
Each father's health can be restored once per floor. That's pretty good sneaky fingers
People won't notice when you're doing something bar is filling
Receive money at the start of each new floor
That's I mean, yeah
That's pretty cool
I think it's anything under three dollars
You can't hit people you're aligned with and they can't hit you
I like it. I unlock something down here
Let's hear can't hit people your own class
Twitch twitch. Hold on. Let me hold on. Let me do one more round on my own. I'm gonna try to get to the end
One more round on my own and then we'll put twitch integration on
I want to play I want to play. I know I know let's just hold on
I'm going for it. I'm gonna go speed run here
So I cannot
do industrial
Okay
Complete slums with five non overpowered characters
Who's it?
What does that mean?
Do the gorilla, but that's it. Is that an overpowered character?
How do I change this character? I don't want to beat this guy anymore. I want to try somebody else
loadout
Is there a way I can like change my character? Oh at the start of the game you choose it. All right
All right, let's go
How do you at least get to like the third floor?
That's how we unlocked jock
four to four endurance
Actually really good at everything except terrible with
guns
Hold special to charge forward and break stuff stopping
You can't
Receive xp for each object and wall destroyed
Can't use computers or other complicated tech
Sucker items in shop costs more make loud noise whenever you move
That sounds like it kind of sucks
gorilla
Hold special to charge a devastating attack. All right, can't speak english
Business owners want you to leave humans won't join your party
You can't use projectile weapons
You can have three people follow you
Knockback from damages decrease firing guns doesn't cause knockback
Scientists will attack you on site
You get extra experience for killing scientists and bananas give you times to health
Should I do the gorilla?
All right, so I can't speak
I can't use guns
And kill scientists
All right, let's go
Let's do it and free all gorillas. So you got it. All right. So what do we got?
Just destroy things is it a scientist i'm gonna kill all scientists our doctor is scientist
They could be a drug dealer rescue. All right
I can just break through the window
What's the special button?
Oh, I can't go through walls
All right, let's make this quick. What's what what's what wait, wait, wait, wait
Why are you hostile towards me?
You're gonna chase a gorilla down. Really?
I don't know. Why are you doing that?
What's the
Rescue every gorilla from captivity
Every single how can I tell where a gorilla is? This is gonna be impossible. How am I supposed to tell where a gorilla is?
safe
Accuracy. Ooh, don't even need it. I'll sell it. Come on out. Take me to the exit. Oh shit
Well, okay. I'm gonna escort you to the exit and then
The person has found money on the ground
All right, come up to the exit and then i'm gonna turn around
Good
Thank you. That wasn't a gorilla
I know I know that wasn't a gorilla. I just
I know that wasn't a gorilla. Is there a gorilla on the level?
Wow
Through here. All right mini fridge
How do you make the gorilla noise? I don't know
How do you make a gorilla noise? Do I have I only have his fists?
Oh shit, I want to get in there
I can't I can't even blow that up. I can't get in there
Cannot do it
All right. Did I miss it? There were no gorillas on this level, right?
I didn't see any
No, there's no gorillas here
Punch the window and climb through can you actually do that with this character?
No, let's just get out
You can with all characters. Oh shit. I didn't know that
This is new
Should I do money? I should have do breaking into walls
Probably the break walls one
Money is useless. Is it? Oh my god
Run in progress. All right. There's a gorilla on this floor
Retrieve item
I cannot talk by the way
So how do I do this?
I can't speak english. I just have to punch
All right. Well, let's go
ammo stealer
And a knife looking for the gorilla safe in there
That was pretty good lineup. All right. Got a bat safe combination. Forget about this guy coming to get the safe. No only I am
incriminating photo
The resistance leaders would never cheat on their spouses help this completely truthful narrative prevail
What what am I supposed to do with that?
Like a secret item. Let's head up
Gorilla save gorilla. Let's go out
Done. Okay freedom
Have a good just a couple of gorillas. Don't mind us neutralize. All right, can I just blow through this?
I'm gonna break through this and kill him
Oh, wait a minute. This is a bad idea. I don't know because that was smart. That was not smart
Oh shit. Oh shit. What do we do?
Oh god, okay. Um, where's my other gorilla friend?
Neutralized where is he? He's fine. There he is. We're good. All right, can I give you stuff?
I'm gonna give you a banana
All right. You're fine. We're gonna sell the guns because we can't use them
silencer
And you can't know we're selling the ammo stuff
Chris's firearms attribute when using any projectile weapon. I just I don't have any I can't use weapons
Put that down
And get a melee weapon in your hand
All right, let's do this mission
Retrieve I got it
incriminating photo
That was easy
Five chicken nuggets
Nice. Okay
I need to do to destroy that
All right. We're gonna go right from the back. I'm gonna break through the wall and just hit it once
Did you just give him the banana peel?
Where's do I have bananas?
Okay, why did you just do that?
Can't break this
Did I oh I can't open the door because i'm a gorilla, right?
All right, nice job
Oh
The whole audience just went oh
Oh, come on I thought he was gonna give me another second
It's all right, I get leveled up and I free them we're good
Mission accomplished. I can't break through these just get out the door and let's go
Go on. Let's see
Mission accomplished. My only friend is dead
Ooh
Hold on. Does this mean I can break through the metal walls?
That's pretty good. Let me try it. All right. I don't have any melee. How do I do the scream?
Killer robot is after you watch out great
How do I do the scream doctor?
Come here
All right, I get
Oh god, what have I done? Wait, wait, I have an idea
It kind of worked it kind of worked
Can I kill the robot?
Okay, he's gonna hurt this money in these graves
Give me this money. Just keep doing this
shit
God damn it. I'm gonna die. I need heals
And maybe I want that money first though. He can't see me through walls, right?
He that's so much damage. He's hurting himself at 30 every time. It's not even close. I have to run
Oh shit
Um
I need to heal. I need to heal. I can't
Scientists kill it ghost
Friendly ghost
Can I add the ghost to my team? I don't think so. All right, I gotta go go go go go go go hurry up
soda machine
Oh, no, you got a gun
Oh fuck
Is the fucking robot no
Please
Oh, what do I do?
Where's the robot? He's right here
This is so stupid
I need to buy another banana
Why is he still chasing me?
You just blocked that you gotta be fucking kidding me
Fucking stupid like shop owner
Damn it
All right. Let's put on twitch integration. Let's see how it is
Let me make sure I have it set up right
I don't I have no idea what this is gonna do
But it should be on
What does it do?
like it
It's on it's apparently turned on
Let me do some traits. I'm gonna stay with the gorilla
blaster survivor
Explosions caused by the player don't damage the player. I like that
Thieving tools may not break after usage cause people you hit to be knocked back further. I don't like that
hiring people cost less
Saving crowds more nearby followers. You have to list damage you take
Health giving items will affect your nearby followers. That's kind of good
Can't hit people of your own class unless they are hostile
That's pretty good. All right. What about one of these two ones?
Followers will always travel to the next floor. All right, cool
So I I
It's apparently turned on. I don't know what commands you're gonna have
If it even is gonna work
We'll find out
Staying with the gorilla it lets us vote on stuff. Okay
Let me look at this again. I can't use projectiles. I can have three people
Knockback from damage is decreased
kill scientists
I can do the lunge and bananas give you more health. All right
Turn it on. It's not working
Well, I just I turned it on
nothing
Text at the bottom of the screen for twitch settings. Yes. Do I maybe have to reload again?
Maybe i'll reload again. It is on instead. Yeah, it's on in settings. I have like the token or everything
Everything. Yeah, everything's turned on for voting
Okay on right
Vote duration 30 seconds viewers choose traits on viewers choose levels disasters on viewers choose rewards on
That's fine, right?
leaked
Maybe it takes a minute
We'll see what happens. All right operate
Let's make this quick
You didn't tell me that it hurt me
Oh cheeseburger
Turn off all the lights in this person's house. What a mission and then we have to rescue this
office drone
Excuse me
Scientists extra experience from the scientists, right? All right, let's go. I can't speak english
uh
Okay, how do I tell him to follow me?
Wait
Not like that
He won't climb through the broken glass
Oh my god
We're dead. Just kill me. Just kill me. Just kill me. Kill me. It's not even worth it. Just kill me
Just do it. Just do it. Just do it. Start over
Damn it. I can't just fail the first mission. Let's go same deal. There is no
Okay, there's no uh gorilla here
scientist, yep
I'm oh look at all these scientists in here
They're all armed though
Not a good idea
They're in the trash pretty cool
What do I need to do up?
Treat the item in here. I can just climb through and get it and climb out
Let's do that blast
I need a melee weapon with this guy
Drug dealer clerk annoyed. Yeah clerks don't like it when I come in here
I'll fucking deal with it
Hold on I I can't shoot a gun but I can use a computer
How does that make any sense?
Come here. Come in. No, no, don't let him run away. Don't all right. Well, I don't care. You got away
Gorillas can use computers. Are you stupid?
You wouldn't got a friend
Give me this
Gorilla is hard
Okay, I gotta get over here
Got the baseball
Rewards choose a reward for your friendly streamer
What? Oh, it's working. It's working. It's working. It works
How do you do this?
Do I get to vote too?
Give me the sword
Don't give me the grenade. I can't use the grenade
Sword. Yeah
Mm-hmm. That's pretty good. Thanks guys
Thanks for looking out for me
23 bucks
Uh, I gotta go up just get me out of here
Nothing else, right? Nope
ATM can I break the ATM?
Will I get money from the ATM? No. Yeah, you're in you're in yeah
My fate is in your hands
So, please be nice to me
Shit, i'm not doing that. Why would I do that? Wait, do I have to do that?
Get the briefcase from the chest
Can we get hit by the fire? Oh shit
Up is down and down is up
No, I can't
I can't control this
I have to hold up to go down
How long does it?
Do you have no idea how fucking hard that was to do? It's still the other
When does it stop? Oh my god. Thank goodness
Even swinging in this direction swung it over in that direction. That was horrible
Okay
I got everything I need
Let's move. I'm not doing the generator. No reason to just go
No gorillas on this level either
Choose a trait
Okay. I'll let you see what they do
And he's more likely to run away
Followers gain extra health and receive money at the start of every new floor
Why did I know everyone was gonna pick this one?
Oh, I didn't muck her ass. She's ugly
All right. So, uh people run away
One person said that one guy said that and you're still holding on to it
All right, kill doctor get lockpick
Get the hard drive from the gangster and turn off all the switches
Okay
What do I got here? Banana peel. Oh, that's cool
food
Sell that
Put the rock on here. All right, so I can make it send your opponent stone a trip to the ground
How does this work?
Now that's what the other gorilla was using
right
i'm gonna buy a banana
and
Should I clone myself? I don't have enough money. Never mind. There's a mission up there, too
No gorillas to free
Let's go do it
What do you got?
Uh free slave get five nuggets. Okay, it's down at the bottom
Out here. It's down this way
What are you doing? What are you? What are you? What are we freaking out?
What is what is what are we freaking out? What's going on here?
What what is this?
What the what the fuck is this?
Accomplished in 87 what we released this for the most accomplished. Why did somebody make this?
We released this for
That's fucking terrifying. I told you I told you guys I told you this like a year ago
Eventually, you're gonna be they're gonna get you can say anything. They'll get you to say anything. They'll get your face on shit
There's no there's no such thing as authenticity anymore and another five years. This technology will be perfected
You're most accomplished. How did you do this?
I'm gonna show this
Because this is absolutely outrageous. That's me on the screen. Like I was in this scene had to open
Hold on. We've released this for the most accomplished. If 87 we've released this
If 87 we've released this for the most accomplished if 87
You we've released this for the most accomplished in 87 you we've released this for the most accomplished
In 87 you we've released this for the most accomplished
I hate this we've released this for the most accomplished
computers
aren't
See, I see it in fucking like 100 years
When like we will we're not going to be under control by the machines
Someone will come up with some algorithm that replaces human brains and we're just it's over
I don't know how you make something like that
Yeah, and that's like the third or fourth time that's happened
Some of you guys are getting really good at this like uh, do you eat ass like yes, of course I do
I've seen that before
Some of you guys are getting really good at this. I just want to be dabbing
Also, uh another great thing about the oh you can your face can be put on anything. I could just deny anything ever
Like i've that's never i've never done that I can deny it because look you just see how good the fakes are
It's easy to deny to deny everything though. Okay. I got to how do I get you out of here?
Do I have to kill the guards?
Hey, you got that was like a joke that that was the equipment. Come on
You're gonna stab me over a joke. All right, i'll take the axe for sure. All right. Did you get out? Did you go?
I didn't kill the guy accidentally, right?
No, i'm good in 87
Wait, where's this? Oh, he's up here out of the way I will take the chicken nuggets. Thank you
Huey louis. All right, so that I should be able to retrieve the items break through the door
No, it shouldn't be too hard though. Why don't you break free like
Oh should you you guys have to pick every reward I get
Free item mini fridge, which makes food better
Uh shuriken people generally dislike when you plant these in their faces or has literally nothing to do with smaller rodents
But does increase your chance of scoring a crit by 100 percent
Why would somebody deep fake me onto that? I still can't get over that
Can you deep fake me onto willy wonka when he does the pure imagination song?
Somebody get on that
How long would that take would that take like two quantum computers to get that done in like the next couple hours?
I'm not talking the whole scene. All right, we gotta go on with that chest
easy
And a burger dropped good within the chest
Something to sell
good
No gorillas, right? Nope
Really good and well-trained deep fakes can render entire scene in about two days
That's not worth it that's not worth it upgrade trait
Oh, that's way too much money
That's some
Oh my god
Neutralize the doctor
Of course, let's turn off these switches get out of here. Oh, okay. I'm getting out i'm leaving
Key to the bank watch the full deep fake what hold on
What do you mean the full?
deep fake
Somebody did the whole scene
No, they didn't
Why?
What?
Oh my god, you gotta be kidding me
Wait, let me see this
Why
Why did you make this?
I don't have any reason for you for anybody to have made this
I we have to watch this i'm putting it on screen
all right, so spoilers for um
american psycho if you've ever seen that movie before
and uh
Just know that if you haven't seen it, this is a scene in that movie. Okay good. Well, we good. I think we're good
You understand
You like huy lewis on the news
They're okay
Their early work was a little too that's not me for my taste
When sports came out in 83
That's not is that me that's not me artistically the whole album has a clear crisp sound
And a new sheen of consummate professionalism that really gives the songs a big boost
I can't tell
He's been compared to elvis costello, but I think huy has a far more bitter cynical sense of humor
Oh, yeah, we're straight up. Yes, alan. Why are the copies of the style section of a play do you?
Have a dog a little chow or something no alan is that a raincoat yes it is
In 87
What what is he saying
What is it saying?
What is it saying except to fuck you
Uh, okay. I looked over it and somebody said
Major tos warning and i'm like, what are you talking about?
Oh, right when he uh brutally murders this guy with a fucking axe on camera. Oh, right. Yeah
That part I forgot about that. Okay, it's not real
Yeah
It's cool if it's a video game not if it's a movie. I don't make the rules
Hold on. Let me see this
Where did it go? What is this?
This is so fucked up
It this is ridiculous
I couldn't tell if it was christian bale of my face. It was too weird. We'll get we're going to down paths
That we never should have gone down
Let me tell you a story. Okay, i'll tell you a story
Um, i'm gonna put this on screen and i'm gonna tell you a little story
Give me one second because it needs to be said
You're like huy lewis on the news. Okay, so
What was supposed to be
What was supposed to be?
like 50k
on a computer
has turned into
People doing this shit for fun. You were only supposed to send an email to somebody once a day
You understand?
Once a day you were supposed to send an email or maybe receive the equivalent of a fucking text from your mother
You know what i'm saying? Not much of a story but more of an observation
That's like my hair
All right. Wait a second freeze that
We have to do this because I need to see if this is for real. Hold on. Can I pause this without
This out of the way
Fuck it is
Why is it exactly the same? It's just a little like it's a little cleaner. Hold on. I can I can flip it wait
Let me flip this
I can't I this is too weird for me. Don't look at that. All right, i've had enough
It's hard to even process that that's even possible
Remember when gps was a big deal when you had the thing that told you directions
Wow
Just technology it tells you how to get to the person's house. I'm going to pretend that you were in this movie killing somebody
No, what happens next?
Skynet. Well, that was a good little uh intermission there. I think let's get back to the game
Face cam so we have more footage to use
No, I don't do face cam. I only do face cam like once a month
No, I I was in front of a green screen for like six hours you can't pull some of that
Let me just be the gorilla. Hold on. I gotta get in there. I'm never gonna turn my face cam on again
Someone will use it
Someone will use it somewhere without my permission
That was it. That's all that was in there
Turret turret. What do I do about that?
I had to go the other way
So you let a goon?
61 dollars pretty good the turret only shoots if the camera sees you that's good to know
I want to at least get to like level five
Am I ever gonna be able to do this?
Syringe in a trash can I wouldn't pick that up if I were you
Um, that's all right. This is gonna be hard to do
I'm gonna have to break a door
climb through a window or
Because nobody wants the gorilla in the store, right?
Maybe if I can just go right through
Wait, is the cop gonna see that?
Sometimes you gotta just go for it. You just do let's go
new
Floor here we go. Give me something good guys, please
please
Followers will always follow you to the next floor. Maybe weapons can destroy walls
Or items in shop costs less, but I can't talk
So that's not gonna help me
Choose wisely
Three is 100% useless, right?
What was that? Oh, I get two
Hey, wait, wait, wait, slow slow slow slow slow down slow down. Which terrifying disaster should befall your poor streamer in the next level?
Bombs are falling from the sky a bounty is on the player's head. So random people will attack
Or a killer robot. No, don't do the killer robot. That's guaranteed. It runs over do like bombs dropping
That's like funny yellow bell moment, right? Come on
Really? This one sucks
This one actually sucks. I'm probably gonna lose i'm just gonna go to the end of the level as fast as I can
Any gorillas on here? There are two gorillas. Great. I need to i'm not gonna be able to do this
I gotta go fast
hurry
I I did mean to punch that person
all right, uh
Free everybody right computer
Give me the rock
Open everything
Done go get out everybody out
gorilla
Where is this gorilla? There's a safe in here though
Holy shit. That was a slaughter
Get out of the way. All right safe
Uh, all right, here he comes. Here he comes. Uh this way I want the food in here. All right. I'm good
This red team versus blue team. Well, red team doesn't even know it's on defense
Oh, hell. Yeah, i'm just gonna sit here
Items oh shit, what have I done oops? All right, I can uh
What is in here there is a
Use a lockpick
Gorilla lockpicking. Okay, it worked
Give me that
Uh, where is he? It's across the way
arcade machine
Okay, i'm gonna have him blow up this wall. I'm gonna pick the item up
Oh shit. Oh shit. I'm in trouble. This is bad
Shoot it. Oh my god. I'm just trying to
No, please
I don't have a way to open the safe. I can't use a computer either. How am I supposed to open this?
Wait, can I not I I hate this fucking robot man. This robot sucks
No, I just punched a cop in the face
All right. Well, how do I use the where's the computer?
I thought I couldn't use the computer. All right. I might I might be all right
Where is he?
out mystery reward
Floor clear elevator open. All right, something good
Before you stick that syringe in your arm, perhaps you should know what it does
Carbobox as long as you're hiding under this no one will notice you unless you move around. Okay for luck
Where's the robot?
Will this work on the robot if I go into this immediately will that help?
Yeah
Where are the okay gorillas?
The gorillas there's a beer over here. Okay, I gotta drink that beer can robot can gorillas drink beer
No, no, no, no, no, keep going this way
I need to get that beer
10 health, that's it
Okay, I gotta get
Oh fuck no, I hate that stupid robot
All right. I'm not doing the gorilla anymore. It's too hard. I'm doing
Receive xp for object and wall destroy. All right, can't use computers or other tech
A very loud
I can break everything i'm gonna try it. All right this time i'm going for it. What's the mission?
Destroy air filtration system
Okay, destroy every object of a certain i'm gonna destroy all the air filters
Neutralize sure
Can I destroy walls?
No, this character sucks too all these characters suck. All right, I got this sucks
Oh gorilla. No, i'm sorry to stay there. He's gonna blame the game thief
Get away
I need to destroy the air filters. How do I only have 27 help? What happened?
That's all I have
I'm just gonna stick this into me. I think
Yeah, i'm just gonna stick it in
Oh, that's good
What a great, uh, what a great thing to get. Okay
Anything down here? No, it's one filtration system. I may miss one down below but whatever
I don't want a mystery item
I do have to go retrieve the item from this guy
Break things to get experience. I know i'm but i'm like an alert people
See, I just pulled everybody over i'm gonna die
See i'm dead
i'm dead
Shit, please don't kill me. Please don't kill me. I'm dead. Oh my god
All right. I'm up. No, no, no i'm being something i'm being like a regular character
I'm a gangster or hacker
hacker
remotely hack any computer
Let me try the gangster
Bloods will attack on sight extra xp for killing bloods. That's red, right?
Recruit up to three followers
Okay
Wipe out every last blood that you come across and ensure permanent crave dominance. All right, I guess let's try
There are five that are here so I need to how do I recruit people? All right, we need to
Double kill good just talk to the blue guys. Okay
Uh bribe with item threatened. Okay. I'll take the combination
Um, i'm gonna use the key and we'll use the combination
39 bucks not bad so far. Okay, this is not bad not terrible
Are these blue guys?
Do these count as uh, how do you guys get out of here?
buy from shop
drugs
No
I gotta get through here
Any more of those, uh red guys?
Oh, oh, oh i'm coming i'm coming i'm coming
Oh, you killed him. Uh, oh
I hit every single attack every single one. That's gotta say something. I'm not sure what that's supposed to say, but it
Not very much. I guess
The game has auto aim. Yeah, I knew someone was gonna take it from me
Somebody was gonna take it from me. I knew they were
Through here
No pressure plates good
What happened to this guy?
Oh burnt
10 not
Why is there a timer?
Do they all turn back on?
wait
three two one
What I it's all right. It's not the main mission. It's fine
What?
I I didn't know that. All right
I thought that I was gonna turn them all back on again. I do have the cell phone which recruits people, right?
Uh doing bar fills more quickly easier to knock people through walls and you can't hit people you are aligned with
I think that's a really good one. If I were in the chat right now, I would be pressing three
That's if I was in the chat
If I was streaming the game
I wouldn't have to say because uh, you were in the chair
Stop me
Yeah, I mean come on that that's perfect. That is
Everything we're looking for nice. All right. So now
Let's go
Any
There are three red
Team members here destroy everything neutralize. All right
There's a red team member right there
Leave a gun or a knife
I don't know how I hit you through the wall. I really don't understand that. All right
two more
Destroy that mission in here
Let's just check it out retrieve the muffin from the bartender
Sure thing and i'm gonna recruit you
Join me both of you
That's what i'm talking about
So we're gonna get the muffin from the bartender
Should be easy with three of us. Let's go this way. I did kind of just go the long way, but it's all right
Hello
Threatened 65 chance take it don't hurt me
Worked did it work?
Do I have it? Okay, I got it
Uh, there's a chest in here though. Should I get it?
Not worth it. Let's turn this in
How many chicken nugget points do I have now? Probably a lot
At least like 30 or 40 right after this
German by beer
uh
How do I destroy it? I'm gonna do that last
That's gonna cause the most chaos
This is probably timed again
Do not enter
Uh, this is also a do not enter but
I mean at some point all right cause
all attack go
um
Got it. Nice. All right. No, no, no, no, no, don't chase it to back back back
How do I pull you back back and stop running all the way over there? Whatever
I want to do to attack this person not kill everybody else
It's good to be the boss
Shit, how do I get over there? Uh, oh
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no hurry go go go go go go go
No
Got it. Now give it a bad
Uh, come here you take the gun
uh and
you
Take the bat. No, you take the knife. Okay. I want the bat
And I want the beer too. All right, we're good
One more thing right
Two more of the red guys and we have to destroy and neutralize destroy this stuff down here. Let's go up
Shit, I have to kill this person
Whoa, what happened? Can I stop them? Do I get points for that?
We have to all go and swarm this guy
All right, everybody go in
We're good. I don't I can't what do you mean? You don't feel so hot
All right, we got a new uh recruit right
There we're good one more burger and gun
This little thief just keeps running around
He had one health
so
Just kill this thief and take whatever he has he's been running around like crazy. Don't shoot the gun
Uh
You're not gonna let him do that to you. Okay. Good. How is he an innocent?
Innocent, I don't believe that's true. Sorry
Oh, do not let him do this. He's gonna kill everybody
Go on get it. Nice. All right, you're fine. Why would I just do that? I'm fucking stupid
I'm gonna use the key. He'll come out
I actually have to use the key
He's dumber than the ai grenade identify one ammo stealer a cardboard box, which one this gets pretty fun
I want to see if I can utilize this
We'll see cool done. Don't need the generator exploded. There's one more thing to do down here
Now that's it for the recruits, right? Yeah, okay the chest up there i'm gonna get it
I just did that in front of the cops what an idiot what the fuck
Die again
Why rock my only hope?
Oh my god
All this for probably like fucking five dollars
just watch
Really and I I I could smell it from a mile away
All right. Now we blow this up
Destroy this this is gonna be horrible
Can I I can't throw a rock at it? How am I gonna get rid of this without causing a pull on?
I don't have any bullets
Just punch it. Yeah, but I don't
What's my exit strategy? This cop's everywhere. I'm gonna punch this and then get destroyed. All right, how about um,
Okay one
Punch it and then use the cardboard box. That's not gonna work
Oh
Do it again do it again. I'll do it again do it again
Uh, I just gotta go it's too overwhelming. All right, let's go
No fucking around
neutralize go
Make it happen. How do you block a knife with your hand?
Done fridge go open food. Got it. All right, what's next?
Rescue the hacker and get one more of those guys
Keep going forget about the gorilla
Hey, how are you?
Join me looking good looking good looking good looking good. No red over here
All right up through here
Got a beard you have a weapon. Yeah, you do
Oh
All right when you get out of the way 14 bucks, let's go
What?
All right, follow me. Is that a blue guy drug dealer a lion?
All right. How am I gonna recruit you without?
Why would you do that? No you idiots?
Just come here
Stop, all right, follow me everybody follow me
Stop
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Please just come this way follow me down here
Okay, read the emails
God damn video game
And this is it. There's one more person to neutralize though. I'm missing one. Oh sword. No, not good
detonator
Okay cardboard box
perfect
It's always cardboard box until I unlock a few more things
two one
Let's teleport to the front and then go down from here because i'm still missing one person. Where are you?
Where is this person? I need to at least complete one damn mission
There we go. Okay, you got a gun
Didn't even know
Give me some good facial expression blaster survivor explosions cosmic player. Don't damage player. That's really good
All of these are good except for this one
but I know everyone's gonna pick that because
You have to these two are very good for what's going on right now
But can it beat out the like the meme response? I wonder
Followers gain extra health and I don't get hurt by my own explosions
Oh, come on
It was following very closely too
Oh, well, i'll make it work
There are two red people to neutralize. You got it
I'll get two people in here. Let's go get them first
aligned
Oh
Come open the door
Wake up. That's uh, two free people right away. Can I bring this guy too?
Are you supposed to be here or what? Yeah. All right
neutralize
freeze ray
Try talking to him
Yeah, you're right. I haven't been using very much diplomacy
at all
freeze ray
All right. I'm gonna everyone stay here
I'll stand guard there
Who heard that?
No, no, no go 15 hp. Is that it's not worth it. Everybody follow me
Okay
There's a lot of stuff in here
All right, everybody stay here
Do not move all stand guard go in the corner and nobody move
I can handle this
You're just gonna get yourselves killed
Uh, all right
What am I gonna do down here?
destroy this
Use key. Come on. I don't mind you
Is it good?
All right, I can get this
Is it gonna make a lot of noise fight back fight back fight back
Fight back. What are you doing?
Holy shit, you guys are pathetic
Unbelievable
We only just you say stay we don't do anything
Okay
Four dolls i'm never opening another chest ever again
That was less than the other one
Retrieve that
Should be able to go
Oh, that's what is that hacker?
hacking to any computer
Pretty nice
Okay, you i'm gonna let's do some distraction here. Whoa, hold on
All right you
attack
the security camera
Oh, you can't I can't have you just attack the security camera
That's kind of annoying
He didn't he didn't even say let's go back here. All right
No way to open the door
I have to blow it up
I can't even blow this up
I tried diplomacy. It didn't work hard hat shotgun ammo stealer or critter upper. Give me the shotgun, you know
What if it's a tie?
Uh, it probably does it again with the two that are highest maybe
or
I don't know
All right, I got the shotgun
There's two where the two uh red people
I'm gonna say up
I have to go back and upgrade some traits to
mission up here
What do you got?
neutralize some folks
Are they red?
Uh, i'm gonna have them do the dirty work here and I don't want to take any damage
All of you get in there this job
Hey
Okay, can you come with me?
Where are the red?
Everything is five dollars always
Always five dollars no matter what
And i'm still missing these two
Did anybody see them? I didn't see them anywhere. How these people down here
Where are the two red team members?
Did I just walk by them at some point?
Why is this guy not following me?
They don't show up on the mini map do they?
Shit i'm gonna pee my pants. Aren't I?
Oh here they are. All right, let's go in
Go with the guy with the gun first
All right. No, don't point the gun
whiskey
Syringe a lot of random items cool
I can't pick up any more money
They show up on the mini map if you already found them. All right, we're good
time to go
melee plus one
Items in the shop cost less or melee attacks do times two damage from behind
I'll take any of these
Except i'm not really buying stuff from the store because i'm I don't know i'm not really doing that
backstabber, okay
Oh no
Which terrifying disaster should be follow your streamer?
Who's is spreading trying to touch it?
Zombies are on the level and a bounty is on the player's head
I don't know what we haven't seen any of these. It's always just here comes the robot. So
Apparently it's going to be zombies
I'm opening up the cell phone and i'm calling some friends the second this loads up
I'm using one of my phone friends here
I'm gonna die down here. The dead are restless. It's zombie time
I'm making a phone call
Yeah, i'm sorry. I'm not doing this shit
All right, let's give you some items
uh take
a knife
and then you
take uh
No, the shotgun's mine
You take the pistol
Still the freeze gun. All right, let's go
There's one red person and it's the person we have to kill so they're right here and then they get the item from the worker
Let's go
All right. That's not that's not horrible
I can deal with that. It's only like one at a time
never mind
uh
Okay, let's just go in. Um, we're gonna just go get the item
Just I don't just get it
What happened? What's going on? Okay, uh
Lockpick item voucher silencer or ghost giver
Jesus
I only have one bullet left
So this kills ghosts. I haven't seen very many ghosts
I would love
All right. What do I do?
frozen, um
cool
Do I still have any people left?
uh
Uh, what that's done completed slums. I gotta get the tooth from
this okay
Zombies all dead
I think so
What are you doing? Oh, wait. No, no, no, no, they're turning into zombies. This is bad. Very bad
Oh shit
um
Oh god, this is horrible
Somebody help somebody help me
Are they ghosts?
Wait, they are ghosts
They're tech they are they are ghosts. They're technically ghosts
No, stop fucking hurting me. Why would you fight me? It makes no sense
sucks
Do I have any okay this guy I have to freeze him
Just shoot
All right. Got it mini fridge
elevator open out
Got it
All right. I'm safe. I'm fine
Everything's good
That was a little chaotic, but it's mine
I am going to keep the axe out
in the event
that
I just
Destroyed that guy and now he turned into a zombie
Which makes it even worse. All right, he's dead
This thing is too good. I'm not gonna use it. I mean
Just get me the hell out of here
with this
Syringe i'm gonna take one of these. What's this one do?
What's it doing damage resist? Look at all the items everywhere. I need one of those cell machine things
No, just go just go
Everything's done
Take out the ghost gun
Just in case I run into anything
in the meantime
Yep
well
No, why do you have to turn? Okay, i'm going with the bat
Back up back up back up back up back up
Are this going to keep coming back to life?
Done character unlocked cannibal big quest done for this levels can't hit people of your own class
Explosions caused by the player don't damage me and all map markers are filled to the beginning of levels
Not bad
And uh, let me go. I gotta go pee
Let me take this opportunity to actually go to the bathroom. It's been like three hours plus
I'm gonna go pee grabbing water
It's all positive. All right, please
Industrial one and let me at least get through industrial one
All right, hang tight
I'll be right back
Hello, I am back
36, huh? That's a lot
Okay
for
Here rescue. Okay, uh shurikens
So I can teleport to these things
Well, that's real convenient. I thought you could only teleport at the end
All right
let's
go
In here
I want to do no. No, no, no, no, no, no. No, I need friends before I do this. Should I call the number?
Maybe I should give the phone call
I didn't do anything. Who did that?
What I didn't do anything
Should you do grenade or grenade? Which one?
What does this do?
Is that just higher crit chance?
How does that work? I'm not sure
We're gonna find out
I've had it a couple times before
I want nothing to do with that. All right, so
Electro pill
there's only this
This I apparently three or four of them through killed
Oh shit. Hi guys
What are you talking about?
Join me
I'm not in good enough shape to join you. Oh
They already did it
I took too long probably. All right, let's go
I think they're getting killed right now
Oh, they're sleeping
Come here
Let's be friends
Kill the weaklings. I'm not gonna do that
offer motivation
You're the best
We just had a beer
Motivation for what?
We're gonna down
Don't stand over there. What are you doing? No, no, no, don't don't
I why am I supposed to stop him from doing that?
I what's wrong with me?
I'm confused right now
Five dollars again. I told myself I was never going to do that again
Whatever, let's go i'm done
No, there's one more person has to die one more red
Okay confusion is gone
You know what? There's more money in a trash can
That this shit wasn't worth getting any chests. Come on
There we go
How are you guys still walking around?
Come on. I can't break it from here
Oh shit, i'm sorry, man, that was brutal
It's done goodbye
Let's refill my shotgun
Breeze ray
Just spend the money. What am I gonna spend it on just refill everything?
Watch out. Here we go
Dude, I don't think i've ever seen below two one
I don't think so
All right, so we got uh neutralized worker
Okay, let's start with that one
I want to talk
Borrow 50 dollars how many times can I do this?
Why do I still have debt debt to who?
I just put money in there. There's no way it's not in there. He was a bank owner
Neutralize sure thing. Let's go with uh, something creative
What's going on? Who's fighting?
a fight
Let me see
Anybody else?
All right. I gotta see him now
You guys all have guns
Hey, he just got this guys. What the fuck are you doing?
Why did that happen?
There was no reason for that
but who is
team or who's
Fight, I don't know who's fighting who?
I'm just gonna pick the stuff up that dropped
Okay, um
neutralize you
Got him that guy's strong
We good
All right, nice
So that's done
Got the money on that one. Now we have to go to the left
Fuck the chests. I'm not getting any of those
There's no reason to pick any of them up ever
Where are you going? Are your fighters why they have their own faction?
Destroy the crate
And get a blueprint
Okay
Hey, give me that money people just freak out randomly start hurting each other. All right, I can destroy the crate
Can I do anything with you?
Such a rowdy group we've got here
I didn't
Why does the guy have a gun?
All right. Here's the idea freeze freeze grab the crate get the hell out
I don't have room. Oh my god
Okay, got it
fight fight
fight
Fight, please
You're on your own sucker
I gotta turn the quest in
It's bought me enough time for those chicken nuggets. Thank you very much
All right
Destroy the generator
There's still three. There we go
What's going on boys?
Ham sandwich, what? Oh
Let's roll
Two in here
There are other people playing this game on this same map i'm convinced
Uh, well, let's go destroy this
Just go in
Don't let them touch the king. Don't let them touch the fucking king
Holy shit, give me up
Oh, no, here comes the fire men
Holy shit. Oh my god
um
Is everything all right?
Is it safe to come out of the hole?
Okay, I think it's okay
18 bucks
What is wrong with everybody right now? Why is everybody such a psycho?
Mystery reward. What is it gonna be?
I gotta get more items. I have too many nuggets
Too many nuggets
I'm full
Of nuggets. I'm not good at using these though. This is gonna work
No, it's not
It's only when the camera turns around right? Yeah
I don't want to read the damn emails. Let's go
There's still three. Ah
How am I gonna do this?
Do I make grenades? I have to have like a grenade, right? Wait
No, he has to die
He can't just run away. Come here. Come here
Slip on that
Why you're not that strong one more?
And that's it
Up here
Maybe in the jail
It's not worth breaking in there
I will just kill myself accidentally
You're gonna be in vegas
What's a restaurant?
Hash house a gogo
It's in the link
It's a 24-hour restaurant. They have some of the best burgers I've ever had the place is insane
Please eat there
Are one of these firefighters?
one of the red team
Wait salamatic. Thank god
What the hell do I want to get rid of here? I can't um
bloom box
Surround just sell the syringe, right? What the hell am I gonna do with this?
I have too many items
inject
It's like taking a pill in isaac
It could be horrible or it could get 28 bucks
Sell the cigarettes. Yeah
What does it's in the link mean the link l i n q?
Is a casino in vegas on the strip
It is a casino
It's the link l a n q. All right. Where is this last red guy?
I sleep in a bed
Isn't this against like gangster code?
Well, that was horrible
Didn't even get a chance
Oh, what do I have? Give me the shotgun ammo freeze gun. Yeah
Let's leave
Out homesickness killer followers will always follow you to the next level balls or i'll take any of these
This guy's a psycho. What's wrong with this guy?
This one's good. Hey, thanks guy
Oh
Radiation blast radiation rains down upon all outdoor areas every 20 seconds find a bunch of hidden bombs before they decimate the area
But there's a war going on
Not a fan of any of these
There's a war
going on
or
Deactivate the hidden bombs
god
Should I just stand still?
Try call maybe I should make a phone call
What is it just that one guy versus everybody?
uh
Don't get in the middle
Okay
Where are they going though? They don't they're not shooting me, right? No
They're fighting each other
Are they fighting each other?
I have no idea what's going on, but i'm gonna take my advantage here
I'm just gonna beat the rat
Wait, there's hiding the toilet
We're trying that guy's an item get it. I get the item from what is that thing?
No, no, just
Just climb in the window
before this guy dies
Uh, hope you get how big of an explosion is this gonna be?
identify one sword
Oh identify the syringes in my inventory
We need to know what they are so I can throw them away
You must sword. All right. Thank you. All right. Let's take a look and see what this is
Everything I got away
What's left? Uh, I get to retrieve the hard drive from the safe
just down
Okay
Oh god run
uh
Just go they're not trying to kill me
Who are they trying to kill?
Uh, I need a better weapon than this
I need a shotgun for this one pick up two goons
Really sloppy, but whatever soldier versus the cannibals
One more guy up here
And then I guess gonna leave i'm not getting stuck in this
Okay, um shit
I can't wait now. They're coming to the bar now. They're coming to the bar. Maybe he'll just die. Oh god. He's gonna kill me
freeze right
Oh god, get me out of the bar
Kill him. All right, he's dead, right? Uh out out out out give soda rage poison
Holy shit, help me somebody help me, please help me
Uh refill the shotgun and that's it
Somebody help me it's too many cannibals i'm freaking out right now. This sucks
Um
Please I can't teleport
I have to go up
Heal. I have nothing to heal with
I don't have any more stuff to heal with
Eat the cheeseburger. I can't I press an f it's not doing anything
I don't have anything see
The box what do you mean the box the box?
Use the box
Get me the fuck out of here
Too much going on. Wait, this is a dirty ham sandwich over here. I gotta get it
All right, i'm up. Wait
Oh
Stop what is going on? Stop, please?
All right, just give i'm just right here. All right, go go go go go go go
I don't care if I didn't do everything
I did it
firearms plus
for
money every day
Which one do you think I should do?
How much money is it?
How many nuggets? Oh, this is the first floor floor three
Park one
What have we got? What does it say?
Welcome to the city park aka cannibal country
Warning outsiders will be horribly mutilated. So in reality, you're not really that welcome at all. I apologize for misleading you
Should I make the call something in the bush? So i'm gonna come out of the
Jesus
I even knew that shit was gonna happen
Wait people are just gonna jump out of shit now
I hate this can I pick up the trap?
Barbecue i'm gonna step in these traps over and over again
There's a buddy in here
shopkeeper vendor stand
What is this?
What do you got?
Oh, I got a voucher. Don't I?
Cod piece word up. This will protect your junk
Did I get it? What is going on here? What the fuck is that?
Why are there a bunch of ninjas chasing me?
Make the call make the call make the call
All right. Good thing. I made that call. I got a lot of swords to sell now. How do I have 350 in debt?
Oh, this is pokemon shit. Okay
All right. I got a lot of uh
Swords, where are they?
How many do I have?
Can I sell this?
I kind of want this underwear
rage poison
Whatever. Forget it
voucher
Can I yeah, I can use the voucher, right?
Nice. All right. There we go. I got underwear on now
Don't hit the shopkeeper you hit the fucking shopkeeper
You're getting it
You hit the shopkeeper and now he's coming after it's good thing. I got the underwear already
Uh, thank you ryan
ryan
hogs for the 50 dollars
5 000 bits from ryan
They say cool emote
Curb is slender. What is that?
slender man
No, give me the grenade. Don't give me the lock pick. Oh another item voucher. Thank you guys come back
Oh, I gotta hop
What is happening
Oh, we'll get fucked. Come on. No
Come on
Wow
All right. No, I got it
Is this barbed wire? Oh my god, it's barbed wire. I'm gonna die
Where are my friends?
I'm dead
I'm going home. I just got screwed
Hello, I had to go back to boston. All right. I got a lot of uh potatoes or whatever these are
What is this?
You know, it's funny. I don't know which one of these images
Could be the one that's the artwork
Which one is the interpretation? I don't know sometimes. I don't know
Okay, i'm i'm gonna do rewards
I haven't done any of these
Let's go down here
Friend phone as a reward. That's pretty good
Flamethrower. Yeah sledgehammer. Yes
killer thrower
Yeah cube of lamping
window cutter
ooh
A leaf blower causes extreme noise pollution aggravating bedroom programmers the world over
But in this game, it creates a huge gust of wind
All right. Let's go check out the perks
Leaving tools may not break after usage
Hiring people cost less so don't do that
Items purchased from vendors may be given to you for free
I like this one
Hitting objects and walls doesn't make any noise
That's awesome
Lasers ignore you pass by lasers undetected. Yes
Okay. All right. I just unlocked a lot of stuff
Remove bad traits from the pool
Click unlocked items to remove from the in-game pool
So I can take them out from here
All right, let's see. What's what a bad one
How many can I take out as many as I want?
Well, I like these ones which one sucks that's good
That's good
Syringes are thin and these are all kind of good
I don't hate okay. I hate this one. I don't like that one
Okay, I need to have 38
Which one of these sucks?
Well, I don't want this
I'm not playing as a gorilla
weapon
sword sugar
interesting
Shotgun is good safe cracking tool. I don't think i'm gonna ever use this
No
Doesn't do it for me
Identify wand is all right hacking tool grenade. The ghost gun is pretty good
Fireproof suit i've even seen half of these door detonator cigarettes what the no get these out of here
Cigarette lighter
That's kind of cool
Okay. I'm all right with these
Yeah, I don't need that identified wand anymore, but I have to get that actually as a
Yeah, that's true
Let's get rid of it
That's good. All right. Here we go. Try it again
So I have to do
to be able to start
in industrial or park
Complete slums with five non-overpowered characters and it will unlock it
Do gangster again put cigarettes in the air filters. Oh, that's just horrible
That's just mean
All right straight up is a recruit in here
Come with me
All right, just e
Turn all these switches. Let's go
Play the cannibal or riot
I will try the cannibal next round
100 promise did you even hit him once? I don't think even hit him one time
two three
Four dollars great
Okay, that's done
bottom right
Can I get out from here? No
Yeah, i'll do a cannibal run
That sounds like fun
Where's the the bartender?
Is on the red team?
What?
I didn't have to do that
Why did I do that?
I saw the yellow uh orange indicator. I thought that was
Well, that was dumb
Well, we're going in here didn't take very much damage. We're good
Okay, retrieve the photo and then get out
Use the gun for this
And then you're over here over here
Whoa
Holy shit, let's go. All right, give me the fly thrower fly thrower fly thrower
You know, you want to see it. I want to see it too
Pyromaniacs rejoice with this weapon. You can burn down certain walls and objects. I don't know people
It's kind of sad
Let's see what it looks like
That looks pretty cool
done out
safe in crowds
nimble fingers
Or backstabber
What's it gonna be you guys?
What do you think?
I would say this one
because i'm playing
as the
blue gang members
But you do what you want
I am but a humble servant
Who's up?
All right, straight up in here
There are two
Let's go in here and get you
Chest in there bartender
Excuse me bartender
No, i'm not gonna like torch this bar. Not worth it
So we're
up here
Hmm cage
Can I purchase loose hairs from you?
um
No
No, you're gonna like put it into a petri dish and try to like make some kind of monster or something
No, I don't I don't want you
Using my dna for anything
All right. How do I um, I think I have to get rid of the
Yeah, I gotta get rid of the slave master
All right knife. No
Let's fire flamethrower. Let's try it
Works pretty I got a leaf blower nice. No, I didn't you guys have to pick it. Don't you?
All right up here. There they are. This thing's awesome
flamethrower is pretty good
Here we go
I can't fire in here
Did I use the horn
All right. I gotta get in here and help
We're good. Didn't lose anybody. Did I?
You shouldn't come in here. I you came that was
Just leave leave leave leave leave him leave him. Look
How am I good? How am I good today?
How am I doing today? I'm good
I'm doing pretty well
How about you? You doing good?
Ow damn it that hurt a lot. Give me the key. Give me the key
You made amazing roasted potatoes
I haven't had roasted potatoes in a long time
I know that sounds really strange for someone to say that
But I don't I've never had
It's been probably like a few months since i've had roasted potatoes in the oven
It's not something I really make or eat, but I will take this lecture. Let's try it
Oh, I can't break these walls
Uh, I gotta go over here to the thief
Take the horn out
Can I like horn over here and have it blow up? This is just a noise maker after god
Oh
God damn it the stupid thing. I'm so stupid. I just have tunnel vision and look straight ahead
every time
And now
I can't even get over there
This sucks
Go that hurts a lot. Remember you are very smart
Hey, thanks
Hurt him
Fake message. That's fine. All right, let me get out
I don't care. It's gonna be five dollars. You all know it
I think something good
Ooh
I wonder how much that compounds on top
Either one of these are good
All three of them worth picking
three followers
Oh, no, oh do this right do this right
Shifting status effects players and npcs get new status effects every 10 seconds or ooze
Lots of riders are causing chaos in the street
Might need to use the phone on this one
Maybe it'll just run to the end
There are seven
Of them really?
Riot riot riot riot
Good. Let's give me the money
All right. I need to uh
Go get the crate. Come here. No, no, no, no, no down here down here. Where you going?
Follow me
Need a recruit. I feel like i'm playing mortal all over again. Get back here. Just wait
Stop running away. Get over here. No
Whatever
It's fine
Just got your rass kick
I'm coming in clean it up. Don't worry
Papa Jeremy's got it under control
I got some stuff. I think I want to sell here banana field don't want to take enough inventory space
these syringes, um
Get rid of the baseball bat don't need it
Okay, come here tom. I'm trying to get you to follow me around and you just keep whatever
We're on the same damn team. Anyways, who cares?
straight ahead
In this labyrinth here
I got the axe
wrench
Why did I hit the cop for that was stupid?
All right, can we relax gotta get in there?
Yeah the fuck away from me
Oh, no, the drug dealer is dead
I'm gonna take one of these syringes
That's why I should sell all of them. I just went in a full circle
How do I get in here?
All the way down here
How do I miss this?
Oh, that's like in a weird spot
Don't touch that. It's a pressure plate
Yeah
I deserve that. Oh, well
Damn it. I deserve that. Can't even pick up the cigarette. Can I again? I need an ammo crate
Hmm
I don't know
Killer thrower
Seems like that's going to be the one
Did you use the item voucher from last run?
Uh, yeah, I think so
Remember I got the underwear
So that's it need two more. Where are they?
Oh, they're all the way down here. Really? Come on
What's that? No bartender dead
All right, let's do this
Did you say I think you stink?
I think you stink
Where's the last one over here?
I do not stink. I can promise you that
Come on, let me pac-man this guy damn it
Pac-man kill him
God damn it
Get over here
No, please
Somebody took a syringe and became invisible
Where are they?
All right. I'm out. Goodbye
Wait recruit this guy
Oh, please just get away from me
Okay, I can I can bring these recruits downstairs, right?
Just leave
No, not yet. Hold on
Somebody drop food
Help me up here, please
All right. Fuck it. Just leave. Okay guys this food available. Give it to me
Any food bad
I have plenty of money
There's nobody there. Just gotta do the two missions and get out
There is a level up soon. You're right. You're right. You're right. I should probably calm down
Can I wait? Can I use the wrench on this and make it so it doesn't do anything?
Can I just say
I feel like that would work
Can I do that?
Yes, right
Yes, you can
Oh god
I don't know what to do. I'm stuck. I have no idea what i'm gonna do. Oh, okay. I'm fine
Oh, thank god. I leveled up. Holy shit. That was horrible
Safe combination to get it
Well, i'm not gonna use this right now
I'm thinking I just sell that that's gonna kill me
I'm actually gonna die from that. I can probably guarantee it
You suck, but I like this stream
Well, thank hey, thanks
I appreciate that
Glad you like the stream welcome
If you like what you see
Then let's hang out
Not in real life. I mean just like here
I unlocked the shopkeeper
I finally got some more weapons. I feel safe now
Keep the baseball bat. All right
Now we gotta do uh over here
Get that worker
You know, I do want you
Come from the door, please
More bullshit over here
Of course
Can I come over? You're already here
You're already here
Just stay
You're just a free kill to whoever is over here
How do I do this without?
Um, how am I gonna do this?
I'm gonna blow it up
I can't open this
Stand back
You asshole just get out here
Good didn't have to blow it up
Out all these are pretty good except I don't use the door detonators
ever
hmm
Mini fridge is probably the best
That'll help me because then food will be more filling
That's it. I'm out
You idiot not you me
Let's get out
Nobody else is on this floor. What about wait? Hold on. I think there's a cell machine over here
All right, let me sell
This knife is worthless
I'm selling the syringes. I'm not going to use them
I haven't even what about the boombox? I've never even turned it on
I think i'm good
Sell the killer thrower. I feel like I could use that pretty well somewhere
Hitting walls and objects doesn't make any sound can't hit people of your own class
And can't hit most people you are aligned with
Good stuff. Oh those of you that weren't here tomorrow
Tomorrow, we're gonna do a comb stream
That's right
We're gonna do tier lists
flash games
And some other just bullshit
I got so addicted to doing those tier lists. I want to do them again
It's allowed to be tomorrow night
And if you're fairly new to the channel and you don't know what a comb stream is
uh
it's a stream where
I just put on the webcam and we just do like fuck all for like four or six hours
We just do whatever
All right. What do I want to do here? A lot of stuff to do. It's gonna go right at the front door
It's the streams where we get footage for our deep fakes
Probably true
Probably correct. All right, let's get right up here
It's the best way to get in here
I don't want to do this
Can I like honk on this and have it not work?
What about the wrench use wrench to deactivate
Minus 30
I can only do that once
I need a silent killer
This all makes way too much noise. Um
Okay, what if I like honk blast him through the own his own laser?
Kind of a little sort of sort of worked
Uh, do I have any of the melee weapons? No
Retreat the shit out of them
Oh fuck he got a bat. He's got a bat. He's got a bat. He's got a bat. He's got a bat. Shoot him in the head
Okay, i'm good the honk blast technique would have been pretty good
Will you eat five more mcchickens?
No, i'm gonna take a break from fast food
No more fast food for like a month
I don't eat it that often but
Lately, it's just been yeah. You know what? I want taco bell. I want mcchickens
There has not been a time in the last like month and a half where i've gone. Yeah, I want a cob salad
Oh kale sounds good today. No, that has to stop. I have to start to actually care about that
Okay, so there's two more
So you come with me
Safe back there just open it
Uh
I got no reason to go in there. He's got the key to that safe, but it's gonna be nothing in it
I haven't been eating unhealthy
I've just been craving
All the unhealthy stuff that doesn't mean i've been acting on it
All right, you got a job for me?
Neutralize the thief and can I buy food from you?
All you have is beers
I take them
pretty loud speakers
countries to visit on a vacation tier list
Yeah, if you guys got some good ones and uh compile some for tomorrow because how we did it last time
I just picked up random ones from the chat
So if you find some good ones, i'm gonna do a candy list
So if there's a good bunch of candies chocolates like skittles that type of thing
Is it worth the 15 hp that actually 30 hp to go in here? No
Definitely not. All right. Is my loud in here?
Clerk all right. What about you? Can I get food?
No, i'm not borrowing any more money
That ended very badly. All right, so I have to go all the way down in the corner here
Don't let him alert anybody good
All right, somebody go get that security camera. Wait, can I just turn off the wrench?
I got it too bad. It's still alerted everybody
Give me the bat
Disaster disaster. All right back to me back to me back to me great everyone you've ever met
uh
That's not gonna happen
I can't I don't even remember anybody i've ever met
Yeah, what am I talking about? Yes, I do
But hold on I could probably name you
I can name you at least like 30 or 40 people
Do that right now
Can you name?
Let's just say the last hundred people that you've met
I don't think you could
It would take a lot of thought
That's way too much. Yeah. Okay. What about the last 20?
And i'm talking that like met for the first time
Where was it and who were who was it?
Okay, I gotta kill everybody in here
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait all attack
Start with the goon
Neutralize the goon. Let's go
And then from behind the door
We just get a free shot here
You're done
Oh, don't not you you i'm gonna get ready, you know, we'll just do it with the wrench few times. No, what do I have?
We can just beat this guy up
open the doors
Got it, right. That's it. Three out of three. Let's move
You know, I actually I probably think I would have trouble with the last
Five people that I've ever met
And do this from behind the wall
All right, watch out back up
You fucking idiot
What is he doing?
No, no you were inside the fortnight circle you idiot we had him at least I won damn it
Thankfully didn't hit me. What the hell happened?
They were here. No, they're not
It was so unnecessary. I just took like 30 points of damage for no reason
I could just leave
Five nuggets ammo though
Assist me what no
I can do that for free
uh
I refilled the shotgun because I just wasted it all
Let's continue
Hello
Good good good
They're all good turn on the face cam. No, I don't do face cam
Unless it's tomorrow
If it's tomorrow, then yeah, there'll be a face cam. There we go
Which terrifying disaster war on the streets
Radiation rains down on all areas for every 20 seconds or a bounty is placed on my head
Now don't do war zone again
War zone is too random do the other one do this one. Don't do this one do one of these two
We haven't seen it yet
Two seconds. Come on
No
And it won two it won. I got shit for that before closing the poll early
It's a war. All right. Well, let's just go do the stuff. I need to do quickly
Like kill this person
I didn't really mean to do that now. He's running great. Come on. Come here
Oh shit, who's this?
All right, I need to neutralize this guy
I get him both actually. All right, we'll eat this
Really?
That sucks
Did I shoot a soldier I saw that I shot a soldier
That's bad
I have the whole team on me. Oh, what have I done? Oh, no, i'm freaking out. How do I teleport?
Oh my god. Oh my god. Why did I do that? What's fucking wrong with me?
Watch out for the train
I'm just I have to get out. All right, we gotta kill the guy up here and get that thing and leave
We're going here. Okay, get in there
Where's the other red guy?
Shit
Oh my fucking god
Killer thrower what I do
What's what's going on?
Let's go. I I killer thrower. I just
Be stupid. I can't believe I took that syringe. It doesn't do anything slow and confused. Great. I'm selling them every single time
every single fucking time
No, please please I have to aim the other way
Stay back
Oh, it's just okay. It's the butler
Do the axe I can get out of this
onto the park
Okay, so this is I activate it and then when I throw something they explode
I understand. This is probably the best
no ghosts
so the internet
This was kind of the first stream back to make sure that it works and to test it
It's been okay
I have
In four and a half hours
Just over like one percent drop frames. It hasn't really done been terrible
Could be way worse if you were here a few days ago like four or five days ago. It was unbearable. I couldn't even stream
Let's hope they continue to figure out what's going on
One percent is bad. Oh, yeah, it's bad, but it's better than like 30 percent
Which is what it was before and dropping to zero and the stream turns off
It's gonna keep happening
All I can do is deal with it
And try to get it fixed
so
At least I can have my screen be on and not just turn the damn thing off
All right. Here we go. Now I gotta do
Everything is clear. Everything's done. Give me up
Yeah, forget it. Holy shit. Who are you?
He jinxed it he started saying the words
If you say the if you say cox in a row as the word is spelled out
Your internet starts to turn off
All right, this is gonna be bad. I haven't gotten past the floor one here. Have I?
I'll take a soldier. Can I recruit you?
It's worth it
No, it wasn't why the hell did I do that?
I thought that was one soldier
No, actually that was worth it. I'm glad I did that
I have I put the jukebox down
Why is it not dancing?
Oh, no
Uh, there's a crazy person in that bush. He's gonna run out with an axe. What's going on?
Why is he dancing
He's the only person that's dancing out of all the people that we're able to dance. It's him dancing great
Okay, the axe is the best
three out of three dead
chest
That's good, too
Jerma go in the water go in the water. That's not gonna go in the water
That would be a mistake
Oh shopkeeper
Nice
I still have to do the two missions. Okay
Can I buy stuff from you, please?
safe buster
machine gun
I need the food
taser
can't afford
What does the muscle pill do?
so activate that and just use the axe and just swing around in a circle
Watch out for
There are vampires in this game, too
Why?
Why are there vampires?
Okay, the vampires are hostile to me
All right. I've had just about enough of this shit
Which one too bad that wasn't a rocket launcher in castlevania
That is too bad
Well, you had the holy water, right? Did you throw the flaming holy water?
Thanks for the four leaf clover
Okay
so now
Just have to rescue this person and get 37 bucks and then get out
And there's a celamatic over there, too
Good. In fact, you know, let's just sneak around
This is not easy. What the hell is it leave now who me?
He's throwing me
whiskey
Yeah, I need it. I'm gonna sneak in here celamatic. All right
Let me syringes real cigarettes
Who is dying up there?
the knife
Probably the wrench too
Can I sell the clover?
Put the silencer on the pistol
That purple lake heals you that is the most bullshit thing i've ever heard in my life
right click to combine
Left click to be okay. There we go
Go in the purple water
Is the most horseshit thing i've ever heard
You want me to go in this water and it's gonna heal me. Sure. Okay
If this poisons me
I get 5000 subs
Oh, never mind. I don't get anything
Oh well
I don't get it
What are you so happy about?
We get 5000 now
Syringe? No. All right, let's go up here. I can't believe that's real
Honk come on out this sword
Seven dollars. Wow
That's a lot of money
He's a gun. Don't he? Oh yes, he does
bruh
How did that miss? Let's go
Poison the water. No, don't don't don't don't do that. Don't do that
I would have
fuck
I want to go into the water
Where to go? Oh, the jukebox is still down there. Okay
Uh-oh, i'm overstaying my welcome in here. What happens when it gets to zero?
Is it doesn't a bad thing, right?
zero
No, okay
You can make a custom class in this game. That's pretty cool
Yeah, I do want to say after this I don't want to see what I have unlocked watch out for cannibals
There's one over there
And we're good floor clear
Three chicken nuggets good
Oh pretty good. Can this game be a common stream choice from now on?
Um, I don't know. I'm just kind of just playing it
Ever since it released I've wanted to check it out
I'm not sure if I would do this all the time
There's a lot of content here though
You could put a lot of time into this
That means so that means no
I didn't say that I said you could put a lot of time into this
All right. We got a bunch of stuff over here. We're gonna neutralize some people get that chest. I'll go for it
sure
What the hell are these? All right, there's killer plants now
I'm kind of curious. What does that mean? What does a killer plant mean?
Can I pick it up? Can I have a killer plant?
What does this do? It's not
Okay, there's no reason me to do this. It's just a chest over here sugar
Speeds you up
Okay
Interesting. Give me the
I need some new weapons
My guns are low
Shit could have seen you coming from a mile away, but i'm stupid
You shouldn't be that big of a problem. What do I got rocket launcher right in the front door?
That was pretty good
No, no mystery item. Let's do a ski thing though. Cool. All right weapons, right?
I'm gonna buy the sandwich. Yeah, i'm gonna buy both the heels
I need them
All right. Next is
I'm not doing that
I'll use a knife until it's gone clone machine
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, what am I cloning? I don't want to clone anything. Stop
No, what are you doing? Stop
No, I want to go in the door
I almost just stepped right on that
Moron already there three
Ready to go shit. Well, there are the three
All right, i'm gonna be careful gonna come down here. They're gonna die
No, i'll get them shit
Oh
He has to die
Only one more thing to do in the right side and this is the other guy here and then I can get out
Most of the end of this, uh this area
Yeah, this is it
Then there's the third level and then the the fourth area which is something we've not seen yet
Wonder what it is. I don't know find out
Give me the gun
What do you got?
Give me beers
Watch out for the bear traps and where do you go up here?
Where the hell are you? Where'd he go? Down there?
He needs one bullet
What the hell is he?
Is he hiding in a bush?
Oh, it's the
Other one up there
Pretty good. Oh, this is gonna be pain in the ass
These guys are all armed
I'm gonna have to go for it
Great got it. Uh
Give me the I don't know. I don't know. Okay. I have no idea. They're all good. Good choice. Good choice
I can leave right? Yeah, that's it. There's other stuff dying
Bombs dropping hidden bombs or killer robot
Is it gonna be three for three
These are all terrible
Where is he over there?
All right. I kind of got straight up in the middle. All right, let me get a freeze ray. Just go
I have to go quick
Do I not have anything I can destroy the buckets with?
He did it for me. Can I turn this off with a wrench? How do I turn? How do I do this without getting hurt?
Oh fuck i'm in trouble. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm gonna die
I just unlocked a new character
No
God damn it. Oh
Stupid poison barrels, I can't destroy them unless I fucking smash them
I'm going home. That's so aggravating
I gotta walk up and punch this thing because I don't have any bullets left
All the while a robot's just walking down with a rocket launcher
bullshit
Give me this thing
Oh, I like that too
All right. I'm doing a new character
Let's see who we have
cannibal
Feast on corpses to gain health human meat is the only food that can restore your health alcohol works, too
Business owners want you to leave most people won't join your party
So I have to eat dead bodies
What was the other ones I got bartender?
Serve cocktails to anyone like it's your job or something
Okay
Most people are initially friendly toward you
Enter some private property without an issue
Three followers can follow you and all syringes are identified
interesting
shopkeeper
Recognizes that everything has a price can purchase items from anyone at marked up prices
And items in the shop cost less
So you can purchase anything from anybody
I think anybody else I feel like I got somebody else. Let's try the cannibal
That's fine
wait
So I have to eat people I can only eat human meat and nobody likes me
so is this just like a
murder run
Okay, eat a certain type of person
Eat a doctor
Well, you're all safe
Create a character next time. Okay, I will it's a lot of money. Okay, eat. How do I eat them?
I'm stuffed
Oh, it's right click
So it heals. Okay, that's pretty ridiculous. All right, eat a doctor. Okay, there's doctors in here
So let's go eat a doctor
All right. Well, that's
Actually, really really really really good of a perk
All right, let's go do the missions
Do both in a row
Destroy and retrieve let's go this way
First no, we'll do this one first reward. All right friend phone
melee durability spray
That'd be good to the axe
More cannibals does it actually call other cannibals?
That'd be kind of funny actually
I'll just eat them
Is there a certain amount of people I can eat in one map or does it not matter?
We're traps too. All right. I'm leaving. I'm leaving. I'm leaving. I'm leaving. I'm leaving look
You can watch me leave
I don't know how to get out. Where's the exit?
I'm gone. I'm gone. I'm out
You whiffed
I'm gone. Leave me alone
Leave me alone. Look, I don't want to kill you
Look, I don't want to have to knock you out. Okay, but I will
This guy is mad
Yeah, that's right run away. Hi hamburger. No, I sell it I eat people
Shit nice. I'll take it. This is gonna be interesting though because I have to destroy this. Um, okay
How does one get in there?
annoyed, um
I can just break through
It's not really a reliable way to do this unless I
Maybe hold on. Oh shit
All right, I can do it
Did you actually see me? No, you didn't
No, no, no get out
Floor clear have a lot. We're good ate the doctor next level
I unlock the shape shifter
Don't know what that does
There are a lot of characters
Shape shifter is great
What are you giving me?
Hmm. All those were kind of not super great for this character
All right, eat a cop
And do all these other missions. Okay
Eat a cop
Hey, all right
Nobody get in
No, i'm just going to the front door screw it
Yeah, fuck it. Just come here
Tell me to leave
Yeah, get out of here
Grenade hacking tool boombox or mini fridge i'm currently resisting bullets, which is a good thing pretty split
like boombox it is
I like this character. This character is really good. All right, I gotta eat a cop
I don't like bananas
I only like humans
But it's free money
Retrieve the incriminating photo from the worker over here
I'll try
The alcohol still is good though, right? Yeah
Front door. Yeah
I'm just gonna wrench
Oh shit
Oh
It hurts
I need to feed on more people. Okay, I gotta eat you
You better stop that. Oh, I gotta eat that cop
How am I gonna do this though bear trap? I'm gonna put like three bear traps down like right here
Okay
Done. Can I pick these back up? No. Oh, well very cool
Turn this in
These guys they're not hostile, right? I keep thinking of for some reason i'm playing so much on the gang character
All right. Now i've done that
Have to do these two up here and let's go
I'm just gonna go in break the window and just get it
Goodbye
No cop, right?
Health is not a problem with this character. So i'm it's all right
And then across the way wait, wait, wait, what's up here? Hey, hey, hey, what are you doing?
Uh
Let's eat them both
Here comes one man spam
Cut that out
Final break out these two good. All right. How do I do this without getting in trouble?
I don't it was that easy
Break them out and then eat them. Well, I don't need to my health is fine. Good to go
I want to start playing this game again
Oh
That's one this one this one this one this one this one do this one
Bodies are cannibalized faster. There's nothing else that matters. Just press one
No, it's fun game
There's a lot to do
Kind of keeps the carrot on the stick in front of you with all the unlocks and all the perks you buy and stuff
That's good. Oh, here we go
Who's bombs dropping or riot?
We've seen riot. We've not seen ooze or bombs dropping
But it is chat. So
Chances are they're gonna pick the one
We're never gonna see off there's an equal amount of fight against that
Yeah, we're gonna see ooze
Ooze is spreading. Don't touch it
I get the curve go
Don't touch the ooze
Eat a goon
And then there's two things up there. Okay goon eat a goon. Oh god, come on
See how long this takes
That's much faster. All right, cool. Let's open the uh, let's open it. What about
Oh
Goon eaten. Oh, I don't see very much ooze
Anybody see any ooze that guy's a gun
Can I use guns? Yeah
Why am I acting like I can't use it?
Turns out this one sucks
I don't see any danger at all
These are ooze. I don't see ooze
No, this is safe
I do have to get rid of these though
Turn around
Look at the map
This down here
Oh, it is spreading up here. I'm really far away though
I'll be done with this by the time it gets up here
We're good
Oh god. Oh fuck. Oh god. Oh fuck the ooze
No, I can see it. No, it's the darker
gray on the mini map
The ooze approach it. I'm gonna go look at it
Because i'm done
I ate a goon. I did everything I needed to do. Yeah
I kind of want to look at it
I'm curious
What does it look like?
Okay, it is just creeping
Does it kill people?
Is it gonna wipe out this whole bar? It's not even going in the bar
Oh, well, it's too dangerous to teleport. Why?
Touch it. It's safe
Nope
Eat a slum dweller
That should be pretty easy
Oh shit, i'm not hurt
No, there we go. I'm good
What do these power bucks shut down the power box?
Well, now we gotta eat a couple of cops
I'm gonna waste a fucking space there
Stop it. Oh my god, you're killing me
No, don't let him don't let him
Oh
No, I can't eat him if you do that
You get more hp if the meat is cooked, right?
All right. What is it? I need to do
Uh worker, uh, I didn't mean to do that
Well, they'll be cooked now, right? Let's test your theory
All right, they're gonna be cooked
You actually would not like
That's real
That's kind of unbelievable
Well little details, huh? All right. Let me turn this shit off
Turn off the gas open the doors
Neutralize this person. All right cook them
Oh, the purple water doesn't heal cooked meat doesn't heal better. I how am I supposed to trust you guys?
You know, many times i've been baited in games like these before
I'll take a shotgun
Either one of these works for me. I can do a sword. All right, let's cook them
Never mind. I just kind of chopped him up
So, uh operate all the switches
Just climb out the damn window
Oh, wait, wait, wait
whoo
handy
This is really handy actually
Look how handy this is
We gave you that. Yeah
That's what i'm saying
I'm thanking you
You guys really helped me here
And I much appreciate it
backstabber
That's pretty good
or that
Any of them I got a lot of money like this. I have to buy some stuff
Clone yourself and then eat the clone
Didn't they make a movie about that?
There's a whole movie based around what you're saying
Hello. Hello
I'm here
I'm still here
Yeah, eat a worker. Is that a worker? Yes
Stalking this guy
I don't want to do this around anybody. That's why
No, he exploded shit
Ow, god damn it
The stream's broken
What is it all screwed up again?
Yeah, you should be able to just kind of refresh it
That's not a worker
Where is there a worker that's in a room that i'm not going to explode accidentally
Worker worker worker. I need a worker
Come on
I did not mean to blow the last worker up
That can't be the only worker here
Well, we're going in
Um, anybody know what just happened because I don't unlock the safe open the doors
All right, this is gonna be timed. I think
I have to get in there and break this stuff
Should be good
You just steal from the cop
Why would you pickpocket police officer? That's probably the dumbest thing you could ever do
I still need to eat a worker
Shit
That's a slum dweller
I'm not sure there's another worker on here
Firefighters count as workers
Worker. All right
I need to do this right
I think that's the only worker here
Wait, hold on
doctor clerk
doctor
Yeah, it is
so
wait
office drone
worker, all right
I don't want to kill him instantly
This backstab will kill him
I don't have an opportunity to
He's going faster
Got it. Nice
Let me get a gun
No, this one's gonna suck over here though
Strength. Ooh, strength strength. That means I can uh, I
Very very very heavy swings, right?
Nice and I think does anybody eat that I explode them all too much
I think I blew them all up too much. That's fine. I'll leave this cop
No, I won't
They all just explode
Trade the item
Wow
That's pretty good in here. Oh
I'm fine
Baseball bat got the item. Okay. Yeah, I'm gonna cook this person
Yeah, this one
So that chairman's gonna be insane here
At least it should be yes
All right. Let's uh
Let's gently push
Okay, never mind
uh
What the fuck i'm so mad right now. I'm furious. I can't fucking believe it. I need to eat these people
Everyone explodes now
Everybody explodes. How do I make it so people don't explode?
I have to kill them with a gun
Use the flamethrower. Yeah, but not right now
I need this
That's it, right? Yeah
Graceful floor hazards are not triggered
Melee weapons can destroy walls or all syringes are identified
I like them all
This one's terrible
shifting status effects
Radiation bombs or hidden bombs find a bunch of hidden bombs before they decimate the area
I feel like that one's gonna be terrible, too
Find all the hidden bombs. You think i'm capable of something like that right now
So I have to find the hidden bombs
Now what constitutes hidden?
Active bombs are hidden find them
Oh
All right. I gotta get in now
bomb
All right. This is
What oh the fire department?
No, it can't end like this
What happened?
I have two minutes to do this
Okay. All right. Go go. Go. Go. Go. There's only a few more
move
Uh, what a long hallway. That's so unfair
Is he begun?
Oh fuck
Who's am I live?
Fuck
That sucks
Three minutes is not enough time
All right. Let me go pee and we'll make a custom class. I'm gonna try it again. I'll be right back
God damn it
So let's do a custom class
And we'll uh, we'll do like one more run that should take us right to about six six and a half hours
That was a quick pee. Yeah, that was a long one actually
So how does one do this?
Oh, wait, wait, wait mutators. No, no, no, I don't want those
Did I wash my hands always? All right. Uh
I think what traits I can do
cool
also cool
I like that though
Teleport anytime regardless of location unless you were in immediate danger. I like that as well
Did you wash your legs?
Uh, no, I didn't go pee and then put my feet in the sink
So let me see here. So let's go
Almost in this three times
So, how do I make a custom class? Okay, create a character
uh
Really? Okay. How about uh, how about just me?
well
other me
Okay
Are you ready to save this character?
Uh, yeah
All right. So hair type
How do I
That's how do I change this?
Edit character load character
They uh, okay base again if I get it body type
Definitely the hoodie
Uh, i'm gonna do german at eight five colors, right? That's pretty close
No, not bald like me
No, no facial hair
Uh, that's pretty that's good
legs
Is there pink? Oh, yeah, there is
eyes
wide open green
Is there a light green?
But accessories
Oh done
Uh, um, this is tricky
Yeah
wreath hair
There's there you go. There's jacks. How do I do the stats? Can I change these?
Attributes, okay and determines how much health you start with four
speed
Four melee four firearms four
Oh, i'm out of points
Uh
I say jex is better with finer arms
perfect man
Yeah, we're gonna do four endurance four firearms
Okay, four speed
special abilities
cannibalize
charge chloroform hanky
possess
primal lunge
or sticky glove
I believe these are stats, right?
Those are points
possess
Primal lunge adds too many points
traits
Oh shit. Hold on primal lunge. Can I do one more?
No, 19 out of 20. Come on. There's gotta be something that's one point
Have to be four firearms and then I have to be terrible at melee
primal lunge
Can't do anything else
Okay, anti-social
Most people won't join your party are to the deal
backstabber banana lover
No blaster survivor bloody mess everyone you kill gets gibbed
No
charismatic
Hmm computer illiterate
Short stature means you take more damage and inflict less damage and can fit down toilets
Not for jex, sorry guys
We need like a super aim
loud
This is me loud and toilet humor
master of disaster receive xp for each object in a wall destroyed
Potential to not suck
A random stat gains a point every other level up starting with level two. That sounds pretty good. Oh shit. That's a lot of points
Okay
master of comedy
Scientists attack on site. No, we're gonna bounce settle
items in shop cost less
Specialist gorillas attack on site
Only human meat is the food that you can eat
I mean, should I do human food? I don't even have cannibal eyes
Is jex a sucker?
Cops will attack you on site vocally challenge. Can't speak english
Uh, jex is kind of a sucker. You're right
Wanted oh unlocking home base. I don't have these yet
Okay, everybody wants me to leave and people won't join the party. That's fine. You can do it on his own
All right
Skinny nerd
Or was it I can do it on a good one make him anti-social most people won't join your party, but he's really good
And he's not good with computers. No
Should I do the you can like go down toilets?
Okay
Speed and they like and go up now. Wait, hold on. Wait, what about items?
Okay, bacon cheeseburger. What do you have one of these baseball bats beer boombox?
Yeah, he definitely has like a he definitely would have like a jock strap on
Fireproof suit flame thrower
hard hat
You take the boom box from the claw machine
Put this get the silencer
Definitely need to start with a gun
pistol
Start with a pistol
And a machine gun
Start with money
Yeah
Whoa, 10 points. Holy shit
Start with a shotgun shotgun pistol
No, no cigarettes
All right. Wait, wait, wait
I have 17 18 19
Should I do another one of these?
Oh forget about this stuff, right? Who wants that?
Just do bit of perks
drug a lug
Follow again. No
More traits to choose from when you level up
I like that
Jax is fucking loud
master disaster, too
All right, and then all right, right, right
i'm also going to put
A point into speed
And melee we're good
Sounds good to me
No, that's a lot
Looks like a self-part character generator
All right. Good
I think we're ready
This is the one
Why does the super loud guy?
Have a silencer. That's a really good question one that I can't answer. Why am I so small?
Really? The guns are bigger than me
That's not that's not good. Okay
Let's move
I need to go down a toilet
You can start with 300 bucks for 10 points. That's insane. I already forget what all the perks were
rescue
Jax i'm, sorry
I'm sorry. You just that's not gonna happen
All right. We're gonna try to go through the toilet. We're gonna travel like the rats
I can't open this. Oh, I can't open it
All right. I'm gonna kill the guy behind the counter
shopkeeper
Did that just brick shay and hit me in the head?
All right, you're free. Let's go. Oh wait
Do you have a toilet in here?
Celebrate another one. I birthday bash. This is so stupid. It really is a little south park guy
Go on don't really have to take you all the way to the entrance
flamethrower
Good the more range the better. I don't want any melee
zero
Yellow to see a toilet. I kind of want to try it
Like can you just hide in the toilets or do you flush down the toilet and end up in another toilet?
All right, this is where the writer
Uh, I don't really understand the point of that but okay
There's no secret
Things to do so instead of get up
Oh more choice is good. That's good
That's good
That one's good
Oh, what is this what just happened?
Toilet, you know where to go
See you later sucker. This is stupid
Oh, I broke the toilet. Don't ever run away from jacks. I was gonna go eat that guy neutralize you got it
Jax break out of prison you got it
Get jacked. Where's your computer? Where's your computer? Jax lands every fucking shot dude. I'm telling you
All right, let me open this out to the entrance
All the way to the end all the way all the way down the whole way fast. I didn't realize that was this fast
teleport, ooh
Wrong way wrong way, right? I'm stupid. I still have to wait for him though. I can't teleport with him
Done i'm supposed to be able to use the teleport in the toilet to go to a different toilet
But maybe there's only one toilet
That makes sense
Yeah, no melee melee the jacks is not going to use melee
I have like one or two points in it. The voucher is good because I could probably get a machine gun
Going pretty fast. Just give me some good perks and we're good
Oh, this is bad. I'll take one
The other ones are awful
I take more damage and I think I deal less damage right because i'm small
In the game riot riot we have to riot
It's time to riot
Well, that's fine
I'm just gonna move as fast as I fucking can
Up and up
Ooh, that's the accuracy one who's up there. Hello. How are you? Nice to meet you
You don't fucking miss
Oh, I just shot a gorilla. All right, give me uh
Give me the shurikens. I can
Shoot shoot shoot
No, no, this thing sucks this thing the leaf blow is terrible
It has one or two very specific use cases. Well, nothing to do with that. All right. What do we got?
rescue
So small it's easy to get through
There when do I can break through?
What? Oh, let's go
No, no, no, no get in here. Stop fighting. Stop fighting. Stop fighting. I got to make these count
Thank god looking buff today. I know I ate a full breakfast this morning and then I turned on the stream right now
Check this out
There there it is. Give me a mini fridge. I'm not you're gonna utilize this mini fridge
Not the cardboard box mini fridge. I need the food. I need to get food and eat it
I'm not going to even activate this i'm in full jex mode
Which means i'm shooting and running around and dodging and i'm not going to use that
You're killing my run
Unbelievable. Okay, try to use that fridge
destroy that
Got it
Yep, this is lame
And what do you know check this out?
That took way too many shots. I don't know why it took that many
It's not a gun. It's not a gun. Jax is not good without a gun. It's not a gun
He was waiting for me. There's so many cops out here. I need a toilet
I need a toilet bad
Okay, give me a toilet toilet toilet toilet quick quick quick. Hurry up
Let's get out. I'm done. Right? Yep
Use the box
Ah, it's too late
I need to I gotta reload my guns
What do we got?
I'll take it
Oh, no, I won't
Shut up. Just give me what's in the chest
A whole lot of nothing take the drugs. The drugs always suck. I've never taken drugs and then it's done anything good
Except for that time
Not that time
And I took that sulfuric acid. Okay, I have like five things going on. I'm like on so many drugs
I'm double confused
It's gonna wait till it wears off it's impossible
Talking about real life
No, why do I have this melee durability spray?
Okay, give me the item celamatic right here. Good
Thank you
Ammo stealer nice
Let's get rid of all the stuff. That's melee
melee melee melee
um
Melee melee
Uh, that's good. I need to buy ammo though
Melee get rid of it
I can't buy anything with that voucher because nobody will sell to me
It's kind of irritating
Ammo box. Where's one?
Goody dispenser ammo dispenser. There we go
Steal the ammo first. Yeah from you
What'd you give me?
All right. Okay. All right. Do again from you
All right. All right. Let's go three two one
Give me the drugs
Operate all those. Okay
Uh, I also want to buy something from him too if I can
What do you got? I'm gonna use the voucher
Um muscle pill critter upper
I'll do critter upper for free
What what happened
He resurrected
It's because I used the computer and turned off his safe
Oh, all right
Why do you have your computer right next to your door? That's not my fault
What am I supposed to do
I'm gonna get a gody dispenser
All right, that's fine
So we got whatever I don't need it nuggets. Anyways, let's go neutralize
up here
Uh you
How you doing?
Felt with the oldest trick in the book
Come here
That leaves us with
Just gotta go over here retrieve the item from this guy and then get out
It's a long way
10 bucks in the trash
What's wrong with you?
Clerk hates me already
wait
Give blood
What? Oh, it's you get my
It worked. Give me the um
Window cutter, please
Please
Whoa, all I had to say was please
No, no, no, no, no, no, that's not gonna win
Almost okay. That's fine
That's it
i'm out
Bring on the disaster guys
What do you got?
Don't do that one
Uh, this one's good
This one's good
Uh melee. No, no, no, these two are good
good choice
Excellent choice guys
All right. We know this one's dumb. This is just like a speed run
Bombs falling from the sky and radiation rains down upon all outdoor areas every 20 seconds
Bombs or radiation
Bombs gonna be close
Do they telegraph or do I have to just avoid them? I have no idea
Bombs are dropping look up. Oh my god
This is gonna be horrible. All right. Well, actually this might be good because I would get
everything for free
Don't group up where the bomb dropped
Drop them over here so I can get the safe
Oh, fuck
Neutralize. All right. Be I gotta be careful
safe
Okay
No, no, no, that's not worth it. I have to just neutralize this guy
Where is it? Give me the pistol
up here
Jesus
Got it. Uh, give me uh, give me the freeze ray freeze ray freeze freeze
No, no, no mini fridge. It's not gonna mini fridge is good, but I want the freeze ray because freeze people and then it can hit the bombs
No, no, don't give me the mini fridge. I want the freeze ray
I don't want the mini fridge
Have any food for this to work. All right, what's left destroy that i'm just gonna have a bomb drop on it. Holy shit
Whiskey give that to me
um
Should I no let's do this
No, I don't want to need this
All right. I know how the bombs drop
Where it lights up?
I want that safe though. Just drop the bomb on this guy right here
right here
Whatever, let's go
I'm just running from the bombs. Who's that is a bomb
All right, right here drop one right here and then let me get out
Here it comes
Will that do it?
Oh, come on drop one over here so I don't have to go in that
This guy's dead
Come do it
Is it gonna land?
Do it right here
Oh, fuck it. Whatever
Where's it dropping? Oh god, I don't know where it is
Hey
Dude, it's fucking chaos outside and you're gonna act like this right
Actual chaos outside. Are you stupid?
Oh god
Thank you elevator open. I need health
That's it. Right. All right. Get me out of this bomb nonsense
Turn on twitch integration
um
It's been on for like two hours
What?
Okay, random item
Yeah
It's been on for like a couple hours
I don't want to talk to you
Yes, you do
What is that bracelet of strength?
Probably belongs in a much more medieval fantasy oriented game, but who cares increases your melee strength
Give me like the big heel
Water pump. What is it? No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Is this a heel?
No, it's not a heel
Is it electrified? The water is electrified now
Uh, is it though? I just poisoned it. Oh, it gives me electro touch
Okay. Oh, that's an electro touch forever
Can I electro?
Get rid of these
They die
Oh, yeah, they do
What is that?
Okay, nice
Turns almost any item into food
Food that probably causes cancer, but that's beyond the game scope
Wait, what?
I can can I put the shuriken in there?
What did it turn into? Oh turning it into the bud
Is there any more melee shit?
No, that's good for now
I wanted to eat the bud
But it ate the first aid kit and i'm about to level up
You have no idea just how badly I wish I could save state like 10 seconds ago
Hey
Oh, I got a friend phone. I'm just gonna sell it. Nobody likes me three dollars. What a waste
What a serious weight like why would I?
You got to put at least like five dollars ten dollars in those chests. Come on. Why am I hurting?
What the? All right. Wait, is there is there a sublimatic? Yeah, there is all right. Get rid of the
I don't want this. It's confused. It's terrible melee
Get rid of the banana peels. They don't do anything
get rid of the
Uh the phone
twice
Nobody I don't have any friends
All right. I'm okay with this
Can I buy anything else?
Axis melee. Yeah, but this could be desperate an incredibly desperate attempt for me to just run them around axe is really powerful
power powerful
Yeah, the axe is really powerful
God I like to talk
So we got uh, I don't want any of that stuff
All right. I'm good to go. Just uh destroy the box
Is there an ammo container anymore?
No, just bartender
See what I mean?
I don't even know what happened. I just knew that I need this axe now
Because everyone's coming after me
That dude had 10 bucks
All right load automatic
here
Um, I don't have the silencer equipped. Well, so hold on. Let me do that real quick
and then
Hi, I don't understand. What does the atm do?
Oh, it can be stored between runs. I get it. Okay. So what what's the point of me doing this just to get a
76 bucks for another gun
Just ammo
It's a lot of money for ammo though
Yeah, it's not worth it. Let's just do this
Uh, i'm gonna have to use the axe. This is why I kept it
Right into the water
It's better if you start the game with rare items because it puts those in there. I see
Cool none of these are very good for what i'm doing right now
Unfortunately
I'll be happy if I get down to the one after this
Yeah, the leap blower would be actually kind of good here
Just blow people into the water
Thank you
And it's technically a gun. So
You are correct. It is a gun technically
Not like anybody was arguing with me about it
Yeah, you know, you're right. You're right. Yeah, who's right? What are you talking about? Get away from me
Cocktail whiskey I should buy some of these no don't want that
Thank you
Resurrection does that last until I die because that's a huge deal
Oh shit, i'm done with all the missions. I'm just gonna get out walk him into the trap
You avoided it
Okay
Goodbye, there's an ammo thing right there. No
No, no, no, no. No. All right. Stop
Okay, get out get out get out. Okay. All right. All right
Did I refill the wrong thing? Oh, this is good. This is good
Was this three two coming up?
three three
Something like that, right?
Yeah, extra experience is always good. That means a full hell
said that with like a
English accent or like a scottish accent for some reason. Oh, it's a full hell
I don't know. Sometimes my brain just turns off
Selling that
All right right in there
Destroy that
I should be okay. I just yeah watch this ready
That's a huge
60 bucks you had a lot of money. Wait, where is it? Was it where is it?
That was clearly 60. Wasn't it? I did not know you had to equip those
Uh resist bullets or resist damage. What is the difference?
Let's go neutralize some folks and then retrieve the chest. Okay. Wait, he doesn't like me, but I don't have any more of that stuff
Do I?
oh well
I walked right into that. I saw it coming from a mile away. I knew it
Was staring at it. I just walked into it
Back up that scared the shit out of me. Did he bumped into me or something? I need some ammo for
the shotgun
I needed to do it. I still have resurrections. That's good
Nice, dude
Can I give him the flamethrower?
No, how do I approach this?
I have to just shoot them
They don't have any weapons, right? I'm gonna take the critter upper
Yeah
It was worth it that one that one that one that one or the grenade both will work. Good. Good. Good. Good
Thank you. Thank you. All of them doing a good thing
Three you fools
No one
getting there
annoyed
Wait guys
I didn't start it, but I finished it. I think I was a run killer again
It actually has been three for three even if I didn't die to the robot
The robot's presence causes me to panic every single time
I gotta get over it with Jax though
This one was terrible too. You only get three minutes to do three bombs across the whole map
I've i've never gone down through the park
Hasn't happened in the six and a half hours i've been playing this game
All right. Here we go. Come on
I just have to do retrieve the muffin and rescue somebody up here right in a row. Here we go straight ahead
retrieve item from you
No, he's okay. He's already here. I'm gonna wrap around
away from me
Where is he?
I had to
Nope to the entrance. All right, follow me
That hurts terminate him. All right. He has a clear shot right now
None of these are very good
I can't use any of them the phone to sell maybe for money
Something like that
Yeah, it's an easy sell
All right, watch it. He's gonna fire one. I got full health
Wait, can I
Oh, this guy's the guy I need to
He doesn't know i'm this person right?
He's he's gonna walk by me or is he gonna shoot at me?
He doesn't know he doesn't know right?
He doesn't touch me. He doesn't shoot at me. He just okay. This is good. I figured it out
Drop him drop him
Step on the pressure plate and drop him
Oh god get
Come on
Oh, he just direct hit me
Wait, why does he know now?
Why does he know now?
No, I went out. I went out. I went out. I went out. I want
I just got crushed
All right teleport, right?
Wait, wait, wait, I need to slow down. I need to go up. I'm done. I need to teleport out
Oh my god
Where what do I have for weapons just keep everybody away from me? Okay, I did it
Okay
Okay, I I need to make some food
That stupid robot
Why didn't he shoot me when I was?
In there the first time
Yeah, but i'm really loud. Give me this one. That means i'll get money and I can buy some stuff
Explosion survivor. Okay. This is 401
downtown
first of all
I need to make some health
with this
then
cigarettes
Three rocks
the lockpick
Window cutter. I need health
um
Not the french don't I think that's good
All right. I'll be all right. I need ammo though
Welcome to hip and happening downtown. Enjoy your stay, but not too much. Let's not get crazy
Okay, look just keep your expectations in check and your gun in your pants and we won't have a problem
I need to sell something. I need to
Just gotta move up
I have one bullet get the shurikens out
police box
Do the ammo stealer? Yeah, we gotta find somebody with a gun first
altar
What have to do with the altar?
No, that's way too expensive
I have no reason to use this right now. I wonder what I have to use that for
super weapon
super goon
This is gonna be awful
Hello, what'd you take? What'd he take?
Alarm button, you know, I haven't gone in any toilets
At all. All right. The mob is here. Um
Um
Everyone just froze
That was terrifying
All right. I got a retrieve item from you
Load automatic. No
Cut it out
Toilet. Oh, okay. It actually worked
I'm sneaking into the movie
It's rated r i'm not supposed to be at this one
We're just staring at him. I have to get all the way behind him. That sucks. Oh my god. Okay. Well, nobody cares
I'm gonna try to sneak behind this guy
Oh, it didn't work
Does he know no
Oh my god the mob help me bob
Do something
Into the toilet. I'm gonna go to the toilet. It's gonna work
into the toilet
Get away from me
No, not back in this toilet. No, no, no, go back get back back back back
Okay, I need food
Everybody hates me
How do I do this?
Give me that gun. Okay. Good. What? Okay get box. I need that whatever it is
Steel and I don't I have the key
I just I just bounced that just bounced off the fucking wall and hit me in the face
Oh shit, it opened up. It opened up. Hold on. Let me get in there
I don't have to do shit and there's a fridge in here too. Relax
Oh, it's a cheeseburger
Oh, thank god
Okay, i'm still alive
Let's make some food with um
that
Um the window cutter the last cardboard box. I don't care
I have to heal
The friend phone do it twice. I need health now
So i'm gonna steal ammo. Let's heal
Do you have ammo?
I almost just walked right into that. Okay, i'm gonna steal ammo from the cop. He does not have a gun anymore
He's annoyed about losing his gun
Okay
So far so good
Secrets, no good to go. Now. What are the missions?
Salamatic right here
People just keep getting crushed by this thing
Okay
I'm gonna sell. Um
The boom box
Wisen is there an ammo station that I can do later?
augmentation booth upgrade trade
That's way too much money
Now it's time to do the mission. I have ammo. I have life
I need to go in here and retrieve that wallet from this person
I'm not allowed in here
I have nothing on my quick bar either
Which can't what am I gonna have on here? Is it weapons?
Just wait an hour while everybody dies from the train. That's not gonna I don't think it's gonna work
This is so this is hell. How am I gonna do this? I have to like start burning people's shotgun. I think
pistol
Give it here. Give me uh, like the shuriken
You know what to do
I love how helpful everybody's being right now
Being very helpful. All right. Now I gotta be careful. It says I just heard something
Now it's neutralize the doctor
Okay. All right. I gotta
I gotta get out of here
Is there any okay? Wait, there's that I want that
It could be something in there worth taking
bucks not worth it
And this dick heads in here now
All right out
Okay, give me these stray shurikens
neutralize
I can't break through this
So I have to kill the clerk with a well-placed shuriken through the window
Got it dick no, just relax
stuff to sell
All right, neutralize. I was going with the shotgun. I'm not gonna miss i'm not gonna mess this up
All right, four one down
Done good. That's it, right? It is
Four two coming up. There's only one more after this
This could be the one a random shit a toilet
Can use a ammo box
Thank you. All right. Is there a uh load automatic
drug deal
Goody dispenser. No, I do have to retrieve the eye. How am I gonna look at this place?
I have to go talk to that guy
I have a lot of money. I'm gonna bribe this guy to give that to me
Yeah, if I fire up you think i'm gonna fire something in here. No
Not gonna happen. Am I am I I can't i'm not allowed in here
Is there a way I can sneak in here? Is there any windows or anything?
There are no windows
I have to go in the front door, but there's a guy for locking the front door
Toilet, right?
Is there a toilet in here?
There's gotta be a bathroom in this club
There is all right. That's gonna find the right toilet
Try this one sick
Nice. Okay, what's better? I just want to talk to this guy. All right, i'm done talking
This one's 70 bucks. This one's 70 though
Wait, I requested mambo number five and everybody hates me now
That's the joke
I had to know what that did. All right
Another mission over here and isn't does he hate me? No, he can't hate me because he has a mission
All right. I'm out of money
rescue the doctor
I'll try
What's wrong with mambo number five?
Um, I is it the my I get that song in the macarana confused every time
I get a bartender annoyed
Dude, but there's no toilet over there
All right. Well, i'm thinking all right. Here's one thing i'm thinking shuriken through the window
No, i'm thinking shuriken open the door. There's only two there's only two people in here that i'm gonna be trying to kill me
I could probably get this guy right here
shotgun blast through the
Let's see coming over here. What are you coming? What are you doing?
I'm doing this job for you. Why are you coming out here? He's got it by the train
Like I took the money. All right, don't care
Come on out
Don't get hit by the train, please
Chicken nuggets this guy's almost dead
Thanks with chicken nuggets. Oh and by the way
Let's see what he got in the back
Five dollars again. It wasn't worth it. It's always five dollars always
last one here
Destroy, I think I can do it with a well-played shuriken
That bounce all right. I'm not it's not gonna work
Dick see ya one more. All right, I think it's gonna spray
Uh killer thrower the shurikens really it's gotta be that well, it's too late
No, that's not too late. We're good
nice
All right. I'm gonna hold on to this
This is my oh shit button
Shuriken will be instant kill
I just need to make sure I have some shurikens. Do I I have four?
I need more of those
Get me more shurikens when they appear you guys know what to do
I'm gonna refill the shurikens and i'm gonna take that pill
And it's that's the instant. Oh shit button
All right, let's teleport. That's it. Right? Just this last one
Selamatic right there. Let's go
Play mambo number five or riot
No, i'm not gonna have this whole stream get dmca'd this whole stream is gonna get muted because of one dumb song that
Yeah, I called it a dumb song. I did i'm sorry if you like it
All right, we're gonna neutralize this guy
There are no front door
Hand over your cash
That's just great cause fucking all kinds of problems. What do I what should I do about this?
Machine gun. All right selamatic time and give me that chest
Who's that? What? Oh
Five dollars. Ooh
This is super good
All right, that's it. I wouldn't do the selamatic though. Where is it over here? I'm not gonna let you take that's the accuracy mode is
Is too good like get out of here
It's the scratch offs all over again. All right. Am I allowed in here?
I'm definitely allowed in there if I use the toilet
I'm never gonna get it. No, just leave
Mixed up environment mutator unlocked. They're all
Okay
If I die, I have to play mambo number five. Okay
The whole song or like 12 seconds?
Oh shit
Don't pick this one. Do not pick this one. It ends every time
It's gonna end again and i'm at the end. I have one more more to do
Give me something easy
Give me the ooze. The ooze is so easy. Give this to me
This is
It's over
And I don't have any food. Wait, I just thought of a genius idea
Let me come over here
Come on over here
Do I have shurikens? I do. Okay
um
Get over here
I'm waiting for you
I need to land one
One shot it has to hit
And i'm good
How long does it last for?
Ladies and gentlemen, this is mambo number five
Be a buzz like I had last week
I must stay deep because talk is cheap. All as I continue, you know, they're getting sweeter
So what can I do? I really beg you my lord to me learn this just like a sport anything fly
It's all good. Let me jump in please send in the trumpet a little bit of Monica in my life
A little bit of erika by my side a little bit of Rita's all I need
A little bit
The song sucks
What a dumb song
Deep fake that wasn't even me. I didn't even just do that. Somebody just turned somebody to just just fucking hack the computer
And put a deep fake on camera. That's what i'm talking about. That shit sucks. It's bullshit. I didn't do that
I can't believe somebody made that deep fake
I
Why do I have to lose every time to the fucking robot?
But let me lay I have some defense here on your offense. I've got defense
that item says
That is it. It instantly kills an enemy, right?
It was like take the instant kill for throwing stuff, right?
What do you mean wrong item?
No, look at look look look look. Where is it?
That's misleading. That's a misleading thing. What's it called?
Killer throw everyone wanted to be able to throw things at people and make them explode into giblets to live your dreams
so it's not
Killer thrower that so it doesn't say instantly kills them
But yeah, it doesn't say instant kill
Yeah, it doesn't shit
Oh, I was so close to stop picking the robot. It's causing me anxiety
I'm never gonna get over the robot
All right
No, no, that's it. That's it
We've been going for seven hours
Fucking robot. So tomorrow i'll see you for the comb stream
I said false song. I didn't say false song. I said I was gonna do for like 12 seconds
Yeah, it got late
Thanks for saying this game's fun
I would play this one again
If you enjoyed it
but I mean
Uh checking it out first impressions with germa 985
It's pretty fun. It seems like you can dump
Uh, like at least 20 to 40 hours into this game
It's pretty cool
But yeah tomorrow we're gonna do comb stream. We're gonna do uh more tier lists
I'm gonna lip sync the entire mambo number five song
From start to finish
And we'll do some flash game. We'll just hang out
It's like a whatever stream
Should be fun
Uh, the internet still seems to be an issue
but
At least I don't have five vods this time
Because before they fixed one of the there's probably two or three different problems
but
We dropped
20 000 frames in seven hours, which is just barely
at that level of
tolerable
Anything over like one percent drop frames would be
Let's hope it improves as we continue to go over the next few days
It was good. It was all right
Don't listen to this deep fake promising us thing
All right, let's uh
Let's call it
That's a perfect time to stop I think because starting a new run would be like another 40 50 minutes
And it's getting late
So let's go back earlier. Let's do the uh bits
and we had
two dollars and fifty cents from um well dough and well dough
Hey derma, i'd be surprised if no one has suggested this yet
But you should definitely contact
Michael reeves and william osmond to help with your carnival stream
Alongside the robotics team if you haven't heard of them look them up on youtube
Uh, unfortunately this robotics stream
There are two different
Companies that are involved
One of them is handling the actual engineering and building of the robots and the other one is handling the stream stuff
I mean i'm like grand
Uh the overseer or whatever. I'm like the executive producer, I guess you could say
But there's a couple of teams
That are working underneath
Essentially everything that i've said I wanted to do
So I really already have
A whole company, you know team of people who are going to be doing like the stream portion
and I don't think I have
the necessary resources to contact anybody else or have anybody else come on board or
um
There's a lot of moving parts
How can you afford all this?
uh
I
I kind of I kind of just don't give a fuck about all that
I'm doing
Just fine. You know what I mean?
Uh, I
The money that I make and the money that I put into this stream
I would rather put a shitload of money into a stream and still be doing just fine, which I will be
so don't worry about
my monetary
And my financials because I've ran the numbers a bunch of times if I'm saving a lot of money, so don't worry
But I really don't care about
trying to
Maximize my profits on twitch
If it means that I get to potentially do and stream
one of the
Most interesting things I think I've at least personally ever done
on camera
Then I want to do it like that. That's it's worth it to me to be able to do something like that and try
So
Tingy thanks for the 10 community subs right at the end here. Thank you so much tingy
That's where you get your money
That 10 community subs just came in
But if i'm able to do this look I want to look back in 10 20 years
When i'm done with this maybe all together. I'll be like i'll be like fucking 50 guys
I'll be like 60 years old
I personally want to just be like hey, remember when I did that and yeah, it costed some money, but
It was worth it. It was where it was a lot of fun
And it was a big like community fun event. I don't care about
Trying to well, you know, hold on. I can like keep that buddy
No, it's worth doing this it'll be fun when I spent two dollars whenever I spent a two dollar bill on that carnival
Another 30 years
I don't know about that
Two. No, not two billion
Don't ever stop streaming for the rest of your life
hmm
I don't have any immediate plans, but I don't know. I don't know if i'm gonna be the like
55 year old 60 year old guy on here
Why not? I don't know that's
I'm gonna like retire somewhere. I don't know. I have no idea how long i'll be doing this
I don't have any plan or any goals
with this
I'm just gonna keep doing it until I don't think it's fun anymore
That could be 50 years
It might not be I don't know
Cry if you retire
By the time that I stop streaming or really really really dial back completely
It'll
It's it's gonna be a while from now
All right. Uh, this is that's a this is a very normal thing
Hold on. So so me telling you guys, you know, you might get
It might be 20 more years of this
No
We'll think of it this way, right? How long did your favorite tv show run for?
I'm of the opinion and I I truly believe this
That there's a time to end the tv show
Because all the tv shows that go on for more than like 10 to 20 seasons
they
They start to lose why they were interesting in the first place, I think
After like the 9 to 15 seasons
Because it might be time to wrap it up, you know
20 seasons
Twitch is a lot different than television, but you know the same
I actually was having this conversation with italics the other day and
We were talking about this
Okay, so let's so twitch, right?
What what happens when you play every game, you know?
It's like a fossil fuel
When you do everything what happens if you do everything like 10 years from now you played every game
Every game that's worth playing
We just have to wait for the new ones
They make new ones. Yeah, but i'm just saying like what what happens when you do everything?
Prepare for more irl
Yeah, but I already told you guys. I don't i'm not gonna do irl streams unless they're
bits
I'm not walking around with the selfie camera out of like the subway and be like hey
So guys don't like the subway doors like clothes on the fucking selfie stick like oh shit
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Stop the train. Stop the train. I'm not doing that
You're doing an irl stream tomorrow
Yeah, but it's it's it's different because I it's
I don't do it that often and there's nothing wrong with that. I have nothing wrong with an irl stream
I'm just saying I I don't want to do that. I don't want to every day like walk around vegas
I don't want to do that
I'd rather do something else. Let me comb my hair on stream. Yeah, when was the last comb stream?
Two like two years ago
A year and a half ago
It was a year ago that I combed my hair on stream and just hung out
So come on
Is this the guy who's saying mambo number five into his comb like it was a microphone?
Yes
But long story short
Don't worry about my financials
We might fuck around here a lot, but i'm gonna make sure that i'm not gonna cause myself any problems
It's not gonna be an issue
I'm gonna be just fine. So don't worry
I appreciate the concern though
I'm looking forward to it. It'll be fun
But let's keep going with the bits
Stop dropping coins. I'm doing that. I'm okay. That's subconscious. I'm just picking coins up off the because they were a mess
I did this I did this little like uh thing where uh
Joel called me after vine bristle and I pretended
Because that's a spoiler. I was cheating but I like he like rolls of coins in my hands. That's a spoiler
We're not going to spoil this here
He's counting his money. We got one
two
Three that's a dollar right there
Anyways, uh, thank you to lewd sheep for the three bucks. Hey
Jermbo this message is so that you notice a creative person called yen wen len who made great art
Find their message if you can
Or did
And ignore this once you do
Yeah, we put uh
yen wen has insane incredible art we put yen wen's
art up on the screen pretty much any chance we get it's
It's incredibly detailed. It's it's perfect. It's fantastic
And there's not much else I could say that's uh more than that. So we usually check it out every time
And i'm sure we'll probably come across it if it's here
But thank you lewd sheep
Uh trotter. Thanks for the 250. Hey germaine. I just got my one year sub badge
I want to say thanks for all the good times. I know it's cheesy and you get it all the time
But really thank you. I'm extremely excited for the future
German fireman, so am I
There are a lot of interesting things to look forward to
I really appreciate the support. Thanks for being around for that long. Thanks for being subbed for a year
That's 12 straight months that you have decided that I am worth your five dollars a buck
For more considering whatever potential tier
Thank you
And that goes to all of you
Thank you abomination zero for the five dollars and ten cents germa. I need your help with a magic trick
Can you act like you're playing and then show yourself holding up the three of clubs and say is this your card?
Uh, yeah, okay
Watch out. Watch out tunnel tunnel tunnel tunnel tunnel got him
Is this your card?
it's no
Apparently not
There you go. What if you want to do with it? Go ahead. Thank you for the five dollars and ten cents
Thank you the lemonade parade for the ten dollars
Oh, wait a minute here. Thank you for the ten bucks. First of all and second of all
Tried the tuna and pretzel thing you said to try
It changed my life
Knew somebody and knew it
All you had to do is taste it
and realize
I hope more of you do that
Tuna i'm talking tuna like from the can
With mayonnaise whipped up crushed up like it's gonna go in a sandwich. Don't put it in the sandwich
Get pretzel sticks or a regular pretzel doesn't matter crispy ones and slide it smear it on the with the tuna eat it
Trust me
Uh does she do it do it. I don't care if you try it once and then you hate it
Come tell me you hated it
Because we got the lemonade parade
Uh just said that they it was amazing
And that's one
They were like 4,800 people on that stream. So one out of uh, 5 000 is
Okay, but that's not a very good number. But still nobody said it wasn't nobody came here and said it was bad
Uh, thank you frody weapon for the 250. Hey germ congrats on your vine
Wrestle participation
That's right. I was in it. It was a lot of fun. We're not gonna do any spoilers
Because there are people that may not have seen it yet
They want to watch it
so
Thank you. It was i'm honored that I was even considered to be part of it in the first place
Retacted hey gnarly. Thanks for the 250 gnarly 62 in 87. Huey released this
for
It's one of the most accomplished albums
Yes, it is
I have not seen that movie in a long time. I remember it being a very good movie though
That was when christian bale was really starting to kind of become
an a-list actor, right
uh, we have
two dollars and 50 cents from snooze
And snooze says
Hey germ, I doodled some of your pals a few days ago and people in the discord seemed to like it
So i'll send it your way
There it is
I love how shito has legs
Shido is a scorpion
That's very cute. Anyways, your streams are such genuine positive points in my week
And although I can't give back a lot, please know how much they mean to me and so many others
Thank you and by rights
bisexual pride
Thank you so much news
I am forever
forever grateful that that people think that people think that this
Stuff that happens on this stream is worth drawing
fan art for or community art for
Sometimes I can't believe it and it
Every day i'm just like is this like really is this like really happening?
This is this community is real, right?
I didn't just like have a bunch of uh, uh, this is real
No, sometimes I can't believe it and it means a lot
Thank you everybody that contributes all the time
To this channel you make it what it is
Wear bots
I don't believe that
Am I a deep fake?
I don't know
I don't think so
This whole stream could have been a deep fake and you would never know but snooze
That's uh, very very very awesome stuff. Thank you for the art
i'm kind of realizing that shito and fireman could be
related somehow
Somewhere down the road
But thank you for that
whole of one zombie. Thanks for the five dollars
I'm not sure if you heard or seen of ai portraits, but it made you into a joker type of villain
This shit is fucking freaky
And also made one less creepy
less creepy
Uh by less creepy you mean somehow more creepy who comes up with this shit
How do you even make a program that's capable of doing that it's the eyes the eyes are freaking me out
Yeah, I don't know what it is about the eyes
One of them's like off
My eyes look like that
But thank you whole of one zombie
Hey lazy luke. Thanks for the 250
In the past five months your streams have been there've been 4.6 million messages in your chat
43,912 unique users chatting
And 10,387 unique emotes used
Just some numbers that I happened to come across
It's a lot 4.6 million messages
That's almost five million
That's that's almost a million messages a month all me on other accounts
You got a lot of accounts then
Interesting data. Thank you. Lazy move. I thank you
Stiff funky the funky chicken or stiff funky chicken. Thank you
You mentioned you had a an idea for setting aside stream time for your videos. Yes
The stream ended before you could finish the thought right? Right. That's right. I forgot about that
I was about seconds away from talking about how I wanted to start to do a thing
And the internet turned up
So let me actually go over that real quickly
Because so many people give so much interesting stuff on these streams
I would rather set up
like once or twice a month
a
Community video night community art night kind of bunch them all together
So we can do them all
Because it seems like every couple streams is like another video that's somebody spent a lot of time on
There's some artwork that people have submitted into
the creative channel in the discord
I think that maybe once or twice a month
doing a
Hey look
There's like five or six videos and like 12 pieces of artwork
And just for like an hour or so either before or after a stream just go over it
Especially especially
The video stuff
Because it really feels like oh, hey jerma his video. All right, let's uh, put it on right now
And maybe there's not as many people here
They maybe would want to see it too. And if they knew that it was oh, he's gonna do video stuff
Then maybe they would stick around for it
But that's what I was gonna talk about before
But in case let me see
I want to see a yen when
I have some art links. Let me make sure that I can get these open
Um, no, I can't wait to see this I got the links now
Oh man, this is awesome. This is fucking awesome
All right, let me get these on the screen because these are great
Let's see, this is gonna be probably really high resolution. See if we can get it on here
This is uh what yen when it says
What they imagine the carnival stream what I would look like on the carnival stream
You might be and you might be pretty close let's get it on there man
I need to have like a better system for this too
Because my files are like all over the place
Is my windows crashing right now? What are you doing?
Here we go. Ready?
Let's get a good view of this
You might be onto something here
Let's get let's get right into the face the eyebrows are the best
I can't wait to do that stream
I want nothing more than to have that done
now
All in due time. It'll be worth the wait
And then here's another one. Let's go. Djerba base face
Which is the start of it. This is kind of what I would look like without the
Makeup on I don't know how some of you. I don't know how some of you guys get this detail
It's so good
Thank you so much for these. Yeah, man, they're awesome as always
We see what I mean. Like I want I this is doing this like once every month or so
Would be great
With videos or other it doesn't have to be just art or just videos. It could be anything
But those are fantastic. Thank you so much
So much time so much energy and so much effort went into those
And all the other art that I get
and videos
Some of you guys spend weeks on shit and I wish there was more I could say
Some of you guys are so talented. Thank you so much for this fucking incredible stuff
Damn
Djerba's nuts. Thanks for the five dollars get baited nerd bet. You won't say my name
That's why I said it because I want to prove that I would thanks for the five dollars
Uh s wid harry. Thanks for the five dollars
Hey, djerba been a fan since the tc hydro time machine video and I wanted to say thanks for everything you have ever made
I've loved almost all of it. I'm gonna be going to the fighting game tournament
Evo next week to compete in smash ultimate and samurai's showdown getting pretty nervous and excited. So wish me luck and thank you
Evo is next week, isn't it? And it's in vegas
I gotta get down there. I gotta get down there at least like an afternoon and like look through the window, right?
That's happening in las vegas
Yeah, compete in evo. It's not gonna happen
evo road trip
Go there and make a noise what like on camera? No, i'm not gonna be like, uh, you want to be one of those dickheads
That it gets quiet and I go like
Yeah, it's been turbo everyone's gonna be like that guy's annoying
Like maybe like 40 of you will think that was cool and the rest of you'd be like, all right
You just like fucked it all up. What are you doing?
I forgot that was yeah
I'm gonna have to get down there. Okay. I'll check it out
Thank you for reminding me because I forgot that that was even happening
Now
But good luck competing in smash ultimate and smash ultimate and samurai showdown
Well, I wish you the best. Hopefully you do well
That's really cool
Good luck to you. Uh squid harry
Halo soft boy. Thanks for the 250. Hey, if you're interested in more roguelikes that look fun. I've heard of cataclysm
dark days ahead
ilona
rimworld
factorio space station
space station 13
Yeah, i've heard of space station 13
And then he said shout out to seph
zentich
This was a fun stream
It was a fun game
I very much enjoyed it
It's kind of a more of a play the game and hang out with chat kind of stream
But those are
I I had blessed it was great
It's a good experience
Thank you tingy for the 250. I missed the old germa the one that always had an end of stream joke
Not this new germa will all we get is an end of stream voice
All right, fine
All right
Fine you want to get i'll do it now, but now you know what's happening and it's over
Thank you tingy. Thank you tingy for your 10 subs too. We came with a lot of subs earlier
And those subs are going to be on the screen right now
I can't really express
how
how much I
Really really really appreciate
everybody's support here
Sometimes when you you know, if you're not live, this is a kind of a streamer insider thing
I'm sure other people have talked about but if you're not live for like four or five six days in a row
People tend to kind of drop off in subs
And that's fine. It's a bit perfectly understandable where you're not obligated to give anybody anything
money wise on the stream
But I noticed that
Almost nobody it stayed almost exactly the same for like a week ago
And I opened that up and I was like, holy shit
So
everybody that continues to sub to this channel even when i'm not live that's
I have no words
Thank you
Because that was one of the first things I noticed was like, oh, holy shit like nobody everybody's still here. You're all still here
Sometimes you get in your head as a streamer or a youtuber like oh, they're still gonna be here in a week or two
Thanks for being here. Why would they leave?
It's not that they wouldn't or they would it's just that sometimes it's um
Goes through your head sometimes if people still having a good time. Is this still people are still having fun
Do people still like me?
So, thank you
They're gonna be on screen right now
Really appreciate it everybody
Two years and i'm still here. That's what I mean
That's a long time
He says how much you appreciate appreciate you as he counts his money
I remember you passed your prime, but we love you
That was
Just wait just
I know that i'm 34. You don't have to tell me i'm already very well aware of that
I'll be 35 in a year. Do you understand? I know that
You're not that old and then there it is get in my head again. I don't know what to do
I'm not 34. Haha. Take that
No
As
As dennis said and always sunny i'm i haven't even begun to peek
He's decaying
All right, so some more bits to go
We have uh, sergel butt for 250. Thank you sergel butt
I won't be able to check out the stream tomorrow because i'll be at work
But you should definitely check out this website for flash games called i'm not going to read that
Because i've read that out loud before and I was told what it was so no
Um
No, thanks
Uh, thank you short stack for the three dollars
These are my last remaining bits king use them wisely for your retirement fund apparently. Thanks for the laughs as usual. Thank you
Thank you short stack for three bucks
Thank you, thank you. Thank you
T jake thanks for the 10 bucks t jake. Thanks for all the amazing streams. I hope you enjoy doing it for a long time
Well, i've already been doing it for a long time
And I still enjoy it so
Kind of already there
It was my eight year anniversary
On the internet making videos and streaming in june. So it's been eight years
And I still like it still love it
Thank you for the ten dollars t jake
Appreciate the support
Uh cool cool lucia. Thank you for the three bucks
You and your streams have such a positive impact on my life germa
Thank you so much for everything you do for your community. We really appreciate it
Keep doing what you're doing. Love you
I think I got one of the best community. I know people say this my community is the best community
Oh, I got the best. Yeah, I know. I really I think I think I got one of the best communities on twitch
Find me a funnier community find me like a funnier
more like
Community. Yeah, come on. Everybody says that but I i'm serious
Everybody, you know, my community is just the best. They're so awesome. Everybody
No
You find me you've no no fuck that listen to me
You find me a community of people that could put together the green screen videos for like seven straight hours. Really
I don't think you could
You you find that
Someone made a deep fake of you
Yeah, i'm telling you every every stream. There's like something new that somebody made that was creative and really really funny and interesting
You're gonna need a uh, uh minus two minus two. Shut up. Shut up. Don't minus two me
You're gonna need a like streamer metal detector that's set to funny like
To try to find a better one
Fucking comedy. All right, let's keep going. But no seriously that there's a lot of
There's a lot of funny people that are in this community
It's proven all the time
You know what i'm talking about. I don't even say anymore
Got to end this doctor's here, too
How many times has a bit message come in that says hey germa, i'm a fucking doctor
i'm a scientist
I fly planes
It's almost it's like
75 of every message
But I can't help it I if there's things to play with in front of me i'm going to play with them
I'm sorry. I put them down
Oh, you got the 10 000 seagulls time to delete the command using somebody else's achievements as a flex
No, that means that I
This stream this streamer here
Doctors gravitate towards this streamer doctors scientists lawyers
plane flyers
Pilot, you know, they gravitate towards this stream. Why why are there so many doctors here?
They're worried about you
Yeah, I heard about this guy chairman on at five. He's like we're getting fucked up. He had a bunch of like intestinal problems
Maybe I should probably check that out and see if I can help him
I'm being written down in like a textbook
Very thoughtful of you guys. Yeah
All right, let's let's keep going
Okay, you know when money stinks
Oh this this money stinks
That heavy heavy heavy like iron
Smell that like metal
Like sweaty hands metal smell. This is disgusting. I haven't even touched this
I I just picked it up and it just filled the whole room
I'm gonna wash this money. Is that weird?
Would it be weird if you just filled up a little bowl of soapy water and watched the money?
Is that weird?
Why would that be weird?
I don't want germs on my hands from the money from all the random people
You know how many people probably look, you know, how many people probably touched this quarter?
A lot probably
This is probably at least a handful of people that touch that
Probably like 50
I don't know how many people think touch this penny. I don't think touch these quarters
He's a fucking magician. He's pretty damn good
Hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey
How many people think touch this penny?
No strings. I don't have strings here
No strings
I'll prove it
How many people touch this penny? I don't know you tell me guys
fake
I'm pretty fucking good
Hey
Hold on. Hey
Hey, nothing in my hands, right?
Nothing to me. Nothing in my hair. Nothing in the hair, right? No wires. No, nothing. Keep an eye on my hands
Got one
How did that happen?
You're gonna pull off your wig
All right, i'm fucking out of here
Thank you to uh, thank you to dubski dude for the 250
Hey germa the following is my most upvoted post on reddit surprisingly
But something tells me you and chat would enjoy it first link is an image second is a quick story. Both are stream safe
I love that's like a free text. Hey, everything's stream safe
Um, you didn't actually do this though, right?
germa doesn't
Mod me in the next 24 hours. I'm taking this picture at home depot and asking them what they think
This has 1.2. This has one almost one and a half thousand uploads
Okay, so wait
Yesterday I posted this pic demanding that I be modded or I unironically would visit home depot and show them the image
My demands were not met. The story is true
Everyone says that's the story is true
Uh right before his story is not true
I started up by printing the a aforementioned picture onto a seven by ten executive paper
Quality the print was a b-plus in my opinion, but it was lightly smeared by some
Rogue drops of cherry juice. I needed my vitamin c that morning
I couldn't redo the print as I had work in five hours and I didn't want to be late
It was the moment I found myself in my car only a few minutes from home depot
That I knew I had made a mistake. I'm just a regular person and these are people and not twitch chat
They can't even conceive of basic germa memes
This was just some depraved inside joke that I was about to take uh too far
I started to sweat and grip the steering wheel tightly but all I could think of was you missed that one try another
Playing over over and in my head. I wasn't gonna miss this one. Oh my god
I parked my car in a handicap zone. I'd only be there for a few hours. So no big deal. All right
Come on. I just needed to focus and take deep breaths else. I would have had no story to share with the subreddit
These upvotes are really important to me. What else would I derive my own self-worth from?
I
Entered the store and was hit with the trademark smell of fresh wood and paint thinner
It doesn't smell like that. I must have stepped in a puddle while walking in
But that was the least of my concerns. My knees had already started shaking and a crick in my neck was acting up
I felt like the terror. I was experiencing by what?
That the bathroom upholstery section was where I found myself
my anxiety would spike every time I came within five feet of another person and I tense up because I couldn't shake the thought that
Everyone knew why I was here and that they knew that I knew what they knew
I avoided eye contact at all costs and it would talk to myself out loud
Anytime someone would walk by and attempt to make it seem like I was preoccupied. This toilet is a b-plus. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm
This is a long fucking story
As an afterthought I glanced towards the rental section. I saw an employee. They didn't seem busy. That was it
Uh, this was it. I had come so far already and I couldn't back out now
My knees began to visibly wobble
And my shoes were covered in paint thinner
Well, that was the puddle. Why hadn't they cleaned that off the floor?
Fuck, I don't know. But before I knew I was up in front of uh, this female home depot clerks, uh
She looked up at me with baby blue eyes. How can I help you?
It felt like all my internal organs had crowded into my throat. I was stunned
I didn't know what to say. What the hell was I doing here?
I had driven all this way to show some innocent person a photoshop picture of a twitch streamer
And I truly lost my damn mind the print
out of my hand
Was drenched in sweat cherry juice and paint thinner which had smeared the ink into a bizarre collage of colors and shapes
My hands were trembling but as I was on autopilot. I laid it on the counter and I said well, what do you think of this?
It felt like time had stopped I was done for I would never be able to live with myself after this
The employee squinted at the picture with a very confused look on her face
Is this she whispered and then paused the pause felt like an eternity
I should just turn and get out of the store. I should just leave now and undo the damage i'd done myself confidence
But my feet were like concrete the paint on my shoes was particularly thin at that point
Is this the streamer that died to pinwheel?
A huge burden. This is how you know the story ain't real a huge burden instantly rolled off my chest
I couldn't believe my luck another human being in my town that understood
We both began shouting the most obscure germa memes in the store and our celebration caused quite the scene
Customers began gathering in a crowd around us. It was twitch chat
They were pog champs and germa hearts and germa chomps bits rain like confetti and even nightbot was there muting a few people
Oh that nightbot
Okay, why am I reading this whole thing?
Why am I doing this?
But then the absolute worst thing imaginable happened the home depot manager drawn by the commotion stomped through the crowd
He had a grill master xbbq badge on his chest
He looked me dead in the eyes and said
Why the hell did you bother writing this entire thing?
I was dumbfounded. How did he know all I could do was turn to you the reader and ask you
Why did you read all this?
Your eyes drifted down the length of this final sentence in your brain
In your brain, you heard the word jubated
gg idiot
That's it. Remember we talked about deep fakes
in like 50 years
Like this story
Is just gonna be here
Somebody is gonna come across this somehow somewhere
100 years from now
And be like what the fuck happened here?
Who was this person that they're talking about who wrote this?
You know how many of these exist
this
The in like 200 years
People are gonna have so much trouble interpreting
Human history, you know, like we don't know really what the hell happened like fucking thousand years ago
We are reading like for I don't know like for instance, um
Like shit that happened in like the fucking 1400s
That shit was like written down and like spoken and passed down from person to person
Who knows if one of those stories that you heard about like king fucking edward the second or whatever
Could just be a a jubated twitch chat to somebody made it up for fun
How would you ever even know?
Who knows if half of this history the material in history could have just been a shit post
And they were laughing about it like could you imagine in 2000 years if they ever find the home depot story
In in fucking 500 years, there's gonna be an hbo special about this post
There'll be a seven-part mini series about this post
That's literally what mythology is
Yeah in the 500 years, we're gonna be the mythology
What is our legacy?
I'm worthy of being mythology
HBO is gonna be around in 500 years. What the fuck is gonna be around in 500 years?
Don't you kind of just want to know?
What's gonna be the most popular tv show in 500 years?
What is it gonna be? What is it?
What store are people gonna go into?
What's everybody's favorite food? What's the pizza of 500 years in the future?
Is it still pizza?
I mean pizzas lasted a pretty long damn time
people eating pizza like
Saint
Christopher Columbus
Was eating pizza
That's not that long ago
He was eating papa jobs
It's probably still gonna be pizza
And this home depot story do I genuinely think there will be humans in 500 years?
Well, apparently because I can't retire. I have to I have to keep streaming. So
I hope so there better be
That was dubski, dude, though. Thank you for that elaborate story
A flug boy. Thanks for the five bucks. Just dropping to say that I had quite a bit of a scare the other night
When my account was taken
But i'm back
And I have the 1000k
100k badge
Here's to one fucking thousand more dollars germa
Thank you
Glad you got your account back
Also, if you were interested at all in destiny 2, it's free september 17th with all year one content
Pretty good to know
Thank you flood boy. Glad you got your account back
I think I played destiny 2 for
A little while but in my brain destiny 2 and the division 2 are the same game
I I cannot separate them
You know like the it's the same image joke. It's that
I just every time I hear of division 2. It's destiny 2 every time I hear of destiny 2. It's division 2
I don't know. They're not I know they're not
They are are they?
All right
Good night everybody
I'll see you guys tomorrow. We're just gonna we're just gonna chill
trying to do
Um easier streams recently just because of the internet
I don't really want to set up any like elaborate cool shit to do and oh
It's turned off by
So we'll do uh, just a little hangout stream tomorrow
Do some more tierless hangout on cam chill
See you tomorrow
Have a great rest of the night. Thanks for sticking around. It's uh, we kind of went pretty late tonight, so
Same time tomorrow 3 or 4 pacific
A great night. I know i'll put them down
Take care guys
Good night