No, what? What am I doing? Fuck. Yeah. Thank you. I want to go over to the forest area. I want to get out of this area. Oh, but this area is tough. Oh boy. Oh boy. Mage OP. Look at my health. No! Oh, I just wanted to get the money. Fuckin'. I just wanted to grab the money and I lost a character that was very, very good.
Oh my god. Do I have a miner? No, I want my miners. I want my spelunkers. Those are my favorite characters. This guy has ADHD. He moves faster. So let's see how that is. This guy has ADHD. I don't even have enough money to upgrade anything. What the hell?
What the hell? And as you upgrade, as you'll see, you build the castle. So if I go over here, once I put 1410 gold into this ability right here, this shinobi, upgrade shinobis, another tier of my castle is going to be built with more options for me.
So like this will unlock two more options. That will unlock two more options, et cetera, et cetera. But I don't have enough money to do anything because I died. I want to max this out, this one down here. But look at how expensive that is. 6000 gold to be able to have more gold drop.
That's a bunch of BS. So I picked the spell sword. This is kind of a hybrid mage slasher film. What is making weird noises here? Hooray! Let's go. Oh, okay. So she shoots the bigger things. I completely forgot about that. What do you have for runes here? I should probably do some magic runes maybe?
No, I'm going to do double jump. Forget about everything else. I'm equipping double jump because double jump is so important. I just never put it on. Take my money. Let's go. Building the random dungeon. I'm not even sure if there is, but I wish there was a way to be able to have different kind of character traits roll more often.
I think that'd be pretty cool. So you can kind of build for more miners to be part of your lineage. Are you trying to tell me I only got one gold piece from that? Are you kidding me? Those rooms are usually full of money. Oh my God, I'm going to scream. I'm going to scream. I'm going to scream. I swear to God, if that happens again, I'm going to screech as loud as I can. Just go up here. Oh my God, it's time for the rage.
Time for Jerma rage to start boiling. Screw you and screw you. Go back to hell. Okay, I could probably do this one. No, I can't. No, I can't because I can't shoot up. I can only shoot through the walls this way. Well, that really sucks. Damn it. You had to come up from the ground, didn't you? That's so annoying. That's so annoying. I'm actually not really doing that bad considering the amount of times I've been hit. People are dropping a lot of money.
And I got foe. You know, just take a huge saw blade. Nice. Oh my God, I thought I was going to one hit you. 783. I want like 2,000. I got to stay alive enough where I can get two grand. That is where it's at. I'm going to go right. I haven't been down there yet. Let's go.
Alright, so this is the old boss room. I've already beaten this boss so the doors close, but there's two chests in here every single time guaranteed. Look at how much money we just made from that. Holy jeez. Holy jeez. I'm going to take a sip of my coffee. Coffee.
Every time I swing at somebody, I get mana back, which is amazing. I didn't know that was on this guy's traits as a spell sword. That's unbelievable. Alright, this might be like the... What? How am I supposed to get over this? Can I jump on those vases? Wow. Okay, this is difficult. Holy double jump to the rescue.
Well, that's a bad room. Okay, this is where I wanted to make it. I want to make it over here so we could go through some of this, make a little bit more money. You guys get the idea. 12 gold. I love gold. The look of it. The texture of it. I love gold so much. I even had my whole, oh boy, gold finger. This is going to take me to the other area. Yes, it is. I don't really care that much as long as I can get back over to the forest. Forest, obviously.
No! Look at this dog. Hello doggy. Another chest. This is looking like a good run so far. The first pretty much good run is happening like 20 minutes into this. Please kill him. Please. Get out of my way. Get out of the way. If I get 5,000 gold this run, you better believe. You bet your ass it's going into that money thing. Hey, didn't your mother ever teach you not to throw stones? Throw stones. Watch out for this skull.
No, shit. Don't let me die. Those are spikes. Those are...
And there goes the run because I just took like way too much damage right there. That was so dumb.
Why can they shoot through walls? Look at that. That's going through the ground. God, that's so annoying. Euro? How many euros did I pick up this run?
Dropping through the ground is very simple. You just sit down and then A. I would also recommend you have a controller for this game because doing this with mouse and keyboard or just keyboard is probably just like a Super Meat Boy where it's insanely difficult to use and the other one is just way better than the other.
Internal entry. I'm going to have to go through and read these one of these days. Go just read through them all because they're pretty funny. I will make my father proud. Don't think you will. I don't think you will because I'm going to make father proud by collecting all the jewels.
4,155. We're doing well so far. Got to get over that 5,000 mark. If I want to upgrade that thing that I want to upgrade, I'm going to have to get over the 5,000 mark. Thanks for the rocket jump.
No! I'm freaking out. I'm freaking out. Slow it down. Slow it down. Be careful. I ran out of...there we go. Okay. Freaking out here. I'm freaking out so bad. I don't want to lose this run. I do not want to lose this run. That would make me very sad because I'm so close to getting that mark.
What was it? 6,5900 or something? Something like that. No! Take the big one, man. Okay. I got to go up. Up and away. Both of y'all get out of here. I can't get that chest because I'm too big. You can be a dwarf in this game. That can be one of the traits and you can sneak up there.
Let's go the other way. I don't trust the left way at all. Absolutely not. Okay. Let's go right. Or just walk into that rolling wheel of death. It's a great idea, too. Damn. Big saw. No money from those guys. Are you kidding me right now? Watch out for the bones. Watch out! No! No, you son of a...
No! No! I don't want to run into his arrow. I'm gonna do it. That chest might put me over the edge. Go through this room to the left and then to the top right. So you guys see what I'm talking about? How life leech is so important. I would have been dead like three times in this run. Is there anything in here? No.
I'm always so bad with these types of traps, man. My brain, I can't even think. I need to go then. No. Okay. Don't die from these spikes, please. Ooh, I found a blueprint. Blueprints are ways for you to make gear. You find them scattered around the world and you can buy them and equip them. That's how I got those items that you saw previously.
Where am I even going? I gotta go up. Damn, man. Damn it. I might die right here. That was pretty nerve-racking, not gonna lie. If I take one hit, I'm dead. One single hit, I'm going to die. Let's hope that doesn't happen. Like right...
Did you see that? How did that not kill me? I can't believe I didn't think that could go through the ground. Get out of the way. I am shocked right now that I'm still alive. Absolutely shocked. That's a huge guy. End of the road. End of the road, guys. Thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. And that's where we die because there's too many boss things in here. Damn it.
Well, I still don't have a miner. Well, let's do the upgrades for it. Where's my... Spellsword's actually pretty damn good, though. Spellsword is really good. Hmm, I got a lot of money. Upgrade my HP. I'm going to do this a couple times. Let's go with damage again because I want to... I have these good attack up, though. Hmm. We could always do mana cost down. I don't have any money for that now, though. Let's do more damage from spells. Makes the most sense.
And now I'm going to leave here with this money. Oh, I could have a higher mana pool. Yeah, let's just go ahead and do that. The gear I have on is fine. Spell, sword, spell, sword, spell, sword.