Oh, he's early. He loves us. Just saw that.
Oh, then you- you're right. That's a true statement.
Aye.
I have tears in my eyes. I'm crying right now.
Vod watchers skip 25 minutes.
Uh, don't. Don't do that.
There's no reason for you to do that today.
We're not stalling today.
There's no chubby bunny today.
Enable peepoween right now.
No.
Vod watchers, don't skip. He's about to do a cinnamon challenge.
What, you mean the videos where I take a gigantic spoon
and just place the gigantic spoon of cinnamon in my mouth
and instantly just spit it all out all over my kitchen?
And I, like, foam all around my mouth while I scream?
No. That's not worth it. I don't want to clean my kitchen.
Dude, you guys don't know is when that video turns off,
that person has to spend the next probably three hours
getting every grain of cinnamon off their fucking kitchen counter.
And off the floor. And then they have to wash the floor.
And then they upload the video.
And if the video doesn't get enough revenue
for that to have been worth them destroying their kitchen,
they gotta up the game. They gotta up the ante again tomorrow.
Yo, first stream caught on time? What's your name?
Hey, Fanto. Thanks for the sub.
Oh, they're not subbed. Hey, thanks for watching.
Thanks for the watch.
Hey, thanks for the watch. I can't believe you gave me a Rolex.
This guy's crazy.
Yeah, we're gonna play Saw 2. It's been long enough.
I'm playing Saw 2 in the first week of Halloween.
Well, the only week of Halloween.
We're starting the week of Halloween with Saw 2
because I just want to get it out of the way
so then I don't have to look over at the chat
and see the next four straight days, three straight days.
Hey, we're Saw. We're Saw, dude.
You're supposed to be playing Saw right now.
How come he's not playing Saw? When is Saw?
We're doing it first.
Three days of Saw in a row. No.
I would be, I'll tell you right now, I would be shocked,
electrocuted even, if we play this tomorrow.
I have to make a prediction.
I feel like this is an electrocution string.
I'd be shocked if this turns on tomorrow, this game.
I would put the screen over to the game,
but I'm not gonna do that yet because it's flashing red
and it's horrible to look at.
I don't want to, just, it's terrible.
It's awful to look at, so I don't want to make you suffer.
Enable face cam. No, Saw 2? Why do you need that?
There's no scary moment in this.
Hey, thank you, Clore, the terrifier.
Five community subs, thank you.
Do it, do it. No, no, no.
Why are you playing the sequel, you fucking Looney Tune?
You know how much this was demanded of me
for the last three or four months?
Veto. I'm not gonna veto this.
Do you know how hard this game is to find?
This is a rare ass game.
I think as of right now, only one of these is for sale.
As of this moment right now,
there is one copy of Saw 2 for sale on the internet.
Just saying, pretty rare.
Look, I'm gonna warn you, this actually is horrible to look at.
Here it comes.
That's what's gonna happen.
I guarantee you this whole game is full
of glorified crossword puzzles for choice.
I can't look, yeah, it sucks to look at.
All right, you guys ready?
Ready to do this?
We're in the helmet.
By the way, how is it possible that Saw 2
looks worse than Saw 1?
Is that weird?
I'm not playing on insane mode, that's dumb.
Why would I ever pick insane mode for Saw 2?
That's the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
Okay, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Okay, Michael, it's me, Saw.
Okay, I'm gonna stop.
I can't abuse that today.
Wait, what?
Is that a mirror?
What was he looking at?
Why was that just a VR cam, like a third-person VR cam?
Oh, here it comes, shh.
Are we all drug addicts?
Your impression is better.
This is actually the guy that is Jigsaw.
Oh, I hate eyeball stuff.
X, X, X, tap X?
Tap X to stab yourself in eye?
Wait, I missed?
Wait, why?
He didn't even tell me what to do.
Oh, Campbell, Campbell, slow down, slow down, slow down.
Don't do that, don't do that.
What did I try to...
What did you do, Campbell?
Inside your eye, there's a key.
Oh, Campbell, Campbell, Campbell, Campbell, Campbell, Campbell, Campbell,
I see your stomach.
Oh, Campbell.
Oh, this is fucking disgusting.
Campbell, Campbell, that was just from the spirit of,
that was just from the spirit of Halloween.
Here's a shot, Campbell,
I swear to god, the key is in your nose.
Saw, please.
Oh, I did it.
That sucked.
Wait, do you get to play as Saw this time?
Imagine you get to play a song make traps. That would be so much better. I gotta turn the audio up for me
It's so low. It's so low
Come on do it
There I can hear it now. Alright, so we walk where do we oh, okay walk here
That really hurt when you are injured find a health of hypodermic and use it on yourself to suppress the pain after finding a health
hypodermic
Press L1 to use it. This will restore your health. I'm walking around really casually right now. I just like the last game, right?
How is this one different you think now is the time to take a hard look? Yeah, that's just it eat yourself
escape from the basement
First puzzle of the afternoon. I can't wait. It's a little puzzle mini game. Wow
Look around. Oh
Fucking god damn it. All right select and rotate. Yeah fun
Another one of saws
terrible children's puzzles
Wait, look around around for what having a blast here residents sleeper
Just let me do the puzzle and then we'll get to eat. Would you get to eat somebody this game?
I saw the review. Oh, I get it. Okay, let's get a match
I saw I've read the review of saw to like the one of the reviewers was like it was really like interesting
It was kind of a fun game until the interactive eat the guy sequence. It was just sickening
So I mean we're gonna get there eventually I think oh, I got didn't know that was on him. I guessed that
You know have a flashlight that can be used to illuminate dark areas. Okay, cool. I actually did I didn't know that was on his chest
Alright, so I illuminate dark areas escape from jigsaws workshop. Hey, just as long as there's no shotgun traps
I could care less saw blade
Why can't I see that? I touch items and I can see what their use is
Don't get it pendulum blade. You're a psychic
Is that really what this is combination lock wonderful. I can't wait to do this a thousand times
We're gonna do one two, three four or five. All right that combination impale and impaler. That's the name
That's a car. This is for the first game that we did that to the first guy
I look for you got you say code over code Chevy Impaler. You can see but do you understand?
Campbell
Oh
Five-seven-three, I got the hey I get by brute force the first part for the last part. It's what?
Okay
What that wouldn't kill you? I don't think that would kill you
I'm pretty sure you could fucking not be hurt by that
You would probably stub your toe or bend your knee the wrong way. Wouldn't you just twist your ankle?
Oh, there was spikes down there
Imagine setting that up. Okay, if you're setting that up you can fucking fall down there and die yourself
Can't you if it's that easy? That'd be so horrible. Imagine putting the planks up here. Okay, just be careful
Don't fall flat in
Okay, so tap X
I
Still don't think that would hurt you that much
You'd get a little messed up
I think but I you would get maybe cut like your stomach might get cut
But why would you land flat on your face?
You would land kind of on your feet a little bit and go down to a knee you might scrape a knee or two
Okay, explore for an exit. I
Check all right with r2 l2 smash. How do I just swing it on my own?
I don't get to use it. Oh
What happened to that guy? Oh, he got killed by one of these like a hydraulic murder traps
He was she was just trying to get back in to watch turbo 985 stream. He just took a piss
Thank you. I'll take the plus twos. Thank you. Thank you
Alright, so what now what I get in here. Oh this way
Broken fence. What the fuck is that l2 r2?
You have to crawl around first person. Oh, that was so much more amazing if the rat came sort of biting my face in first person
Let me get me on a team. You know, I mean get me on the team
I would I would put that in I'd make sure it was in if I was like the creative director of the game
That sequence would go by and I'd be like no no, no, no, no that rat comes and starts biting your face
How did you fuck that up? Okay. Wait. Oh, there's pig face. Where are we by the way?
We're like outside inside outside underground above ground inside. I don't get it. Where are we? What building is this? You're in my house
Oh cool. That's so cool without a record of your game. Nobody will know your fate
Save your game by approaching the old tape recorder and pressing X
So what every time I get to one of these I describe the last thing that happened
Okay, why not just carry it around
podcast saw
That's so dumb. All right, I got a nail in a hypodermic
I'm just gonna call it a needle cuz I don't like the word hypodermic is hard to say
Hypodermic it feels like we're that there's too many things in the word
All right, pick the lock to the door. Sure. I answer the phone. You found one of the 25 I can answer the phone
Where's phone? Okay. What the fuck is going on? What?
That's hit my face. Oh, did I did it crush my eye?
You have to actually
Like Millennium Falcon this thing
That's so stupid. I'm gonna hate that after an hour you leave him alone
His his story repeats itself his history
Repeats itself. Hey his story in history. I mean what does the game's about the last guy? I press square instead
Yeah, it does it sure does repeat itself they replaced us shotguns with
Stomach knives. That's great. Okay, cool. Let's go
Where's the phone? I fucking hate this already. I don't want to do this one
I don't want this is worse than the the this is gonna you understand that eventually
This is just the fun little tutorial. It's gonna be locks that are four miles long
The door is gonna be 40 feet wide and like 25 feet long
It's gonna be pain in the ass and you know, it it's gonna be a huge thick ass door later on for sex
What no there was a
Alright so saw to they've added you do two quick time events to stop the thing from killing you when you open the door
Okay, and who cares about the puzzle piece? This is dogshit stuff when I'm gonna watch do it again. Here we go
I don't want to do it. I just want to open the door
You may be wondering if it gets worse and they put those everywhere. Yes to both. Okay, great. Yeah, I can't wait to play it
X triangle it's square. Okay. I was gonna say there's no way that fucking kills me. Why would they kill me?
All right, squeeze wait. Hold on. There's a room with the timer. Wait, are we missing it? Where the window go?
Oh, he closed the windows on me. This is the flashlight is terrible
Why does flashlight only go one foot in front of my face?
So wouldn't I be able to see it on that wall, this is the worst flashlight I've ever seen earthquake wait
No, somebody. Hey, don't step on that. It's rigged. You're gonna fall down here. You're gonna sprain your ankle like I did
I tried to tell you and I was crushed under all that rubble run for your life
To alter your movement speed hold down our one running can save your life, but will make some events more difficult to survive
Well, I don't really need to have run for my life. Now. Do I?
Nothing chasing me at a laugh. Oh, why is it cuz it's just watch your step. Do I have to run through this door?
I have to run through and just put my elbows and wrists up and just smash through with my shoulders
Stacking the TVs like that. It's probably really hard to do that if feet the rammer
Okay, uh, you definitely have to ram this door, right?
What?
You're not
You didn't even hit me with your head. What is it? What about it? What does it want me to have him ram?
Right here. I've already seen this scene in Monty Python. I know how it ends. Oh, come on that I punch him
Oh over the elevator have him run
He saw me open that he doesn't have his eyes covered
Let me get this straight you die
Before you take a step into the fall that my front foot got in there and I died before I
Went in I don't have to do that again. Do I thank God? No, I do fuck. Okay. Well, I know to do
We'll get it immediately
Please
Stop stop
Stop
Okay, we're good. Let's go
defeat the rammer
Okay, right or left get the help. Hey, by the way, happy Halloween in a week
But hey, we're here on Monday. It's Halloween week
Gonna be checking out some scary games some games. We have not played gonna be a wild week
Why don't you stick around four o'clock? Wait, isn't it four o'clock right now? No, it's two
Is this game as stupid as the last one? We're just yeah, it is it is as stupid as the last one
I have to pick out just you have to just touch every stupid filing cabinet and pick out all the old couple
Scissors, that's a weird room. All right, what's this?
Imagine that was just him. He's really really way smaller. That's his chair
Okay, you monster activate the circuit panel
Put it in here. It's the same one. This is the same game. This game sucks. I'm about to delete the game
Oh my god, it's even more stupid than the last one. It's you have to do opposites. Is that what this is?
Yeah, it's like positive and negative
Isn't it? How can I move this? I already hate this with a passion. Okay, so this is needs to be oh my god
How did you make this worse than the last game?
They took the puzzle thing from the last game and they said hey make it make it way fucking worse and even less fun
What am I even supposed to be connecting here just all of them just red to yellow
Yeah, but this is not even connected anything and the worst part is I can't switch them because it just bounces you back
This sucks. I just want to connect it. All right, so this has to be gone. Which way does this face up?
It doesn't go this way. They're magnets. I was I don't I don't how the fuck am I supposed to turn this though?
Nice lightsaber sound please for the love of God
Why let me turn it so I can connect this shit. I can't imagine making these
Steakums brain this sucks. This is stupid
Why did they make it even worse?
Why can I not just spin this around to connect to this? Oh my fucking god
Why why can't I just spin this I never I will never understand. All right, call me call me a psycho
All right
Call me like you're bad at video games
I don't care if you put like connect the fucking wire puzzles like a hundred of them in your like
survival horror action game
You've you've made a mistake. You've made a mistake a big one a huge one put on some pounds
I did I put 22 pounds on since like March
I met the jigsaw killer and I let him escape his price was too high and I was too weak
Jigsaw was holding Gordon's family hostage at gunpoint shots were fired and I ran over to respond
If I hadn't been in the next building, I don't know what would have happened
We would had a shootout in Gordon's apartment then jigsaw escaped and I gave chase
Jigsaw was a short man with brown hair large blue eyes
I gave a render to the office that found me after I was released from the hellhole Whitehurst
Jigsaw trapped me there. He did horrible things to me in the end
He made me choose give up chasing him so that the others may live or continue pursuit and watch them die
I gave up the chase. Mr. Freeman. I don't know if I made the right choice found a case file. Well, let me get in there
Escape jigsaws game. What is it gonna be like Picross this time there?
This is a magic trick. This is magic. Oh, those are both actors. They there's gonna be like electricity. They're gonna scream
It's gonna open they're gonna be gone right now. They're just setting up a thing. Those guys are getting up. They're getting untied
I've seen this I've seen this David Spade act before oh
God this game fucking sucks
Don't say that. Come on. Don't say that. What choice is that? What do you mean? Okay. Well, let's go first major decision of the game
It's a stupid balance
Okay above me. I can't
But that is I can't I don't I'm just gonna win. I'm playing the video game soft
Therefore I'm never gonna sacrifice myself. Otherwise, I have to go back to the loading screen. Sorry, dude. I win
I'm always gonna pick me guys. I don't think that would have played out a different way
I would have gone back to the checkpoint. You'd be surprised what tools can save a life
Sure, thanks for the Warcraft
2004 esque tooltips right clicking will open up your stacks in your inventory
They still have that shit down there lizard. It's been like 15 fucking years
I think people know how to tab target by now take them off. Oh, I'm looking at a window stop with the wild references
Look, it is first. Why what's going on here? You're never gonna not get wild references
It took up like five years of my entire life. I have to investigate
This guy's not doing anything. This guy's just shining a flashlight. Ooh, wait the question. Oh, well
It must be the Riddler. Well, hold on a second Batman. We're not sure about that yet
Textbook Riddler Gordon
Commissioner Gordon I could ask you to leave the crime scene. I'll take it from here. Where's to face?
We have no idea where to face this mission to Gordon Freeman
The volumes too low I got you anything solved
Yeah, thanks
What is that? So who's doing that?
Who is turning the TV on and off from like 1991? Oh, it's you look user detective vision
I'm gonna fucking throw up if I stay like this
See you later. Commissioner Gordon. See you later Batman and by Batman by the way, I'll take the binoculars down
There's no reason to hold them up constantly. It's gonna make you sick. All right, right. Sorry. Let me go back to regular FOV
Yes, it's me I
Would have loved it if it was just Batman, you know what I mean? If it was just Batman standing there silhouette from that far away
Tanktop, I don't know what's going on
What how did you even get in here you had to go to the door?
Okay, that had to have just been the girl or like my colleague somebody just followed me out and put us like a mask
On I have to restart for what rise and shine
We get this guy's story be so much funny if he says like dog poop or something
We just the tortoise in the hair is the hair goes really really fast than you so we're gonna be the tortoise in this scenario
Why did he just say that?
What was the point of saying the tortoise in the hair? I thought there's gonna be way longer
Try wait a little bit. Well, suddenly just here like four or five seconds later bang
That's why I waited. All right. I made it
No, okay, which we get that guy that guy's still alive. There's no prize for second place
Aka
You know what I would do in this situation I'm dead serious
I would probably just look at like the camera just be like hey, yo, dude. I'm fucking into this
Let me help you. Let me help you. Let me be like, let me be like your right-hand man
Let me let's let's get back at these people. Let's let's get back at all these fucking people. I'm with you
I am I want to be on your team jigsaw and then he's gonna go
I'm your guy. Just let me in
And I go through the door and then when I get there I'm like, hey, what's going on?
I'm ready to help you and then my hands go around his neck and I squeeze the life out of him till he fucking turns
Purple and then I leave he needs someone to chew up the glass
Hey, by the way, some of you guys might not know this glass don't come broken
This is has to be broken for this little bit here. Where's that guy? Okay, how do I leave?
Didn't give me a second chance wasn't just to open the door. Oh
Okay. Oh, yes broken glass from glass being broken. No, you you don't order broken glass
You don't go to a glass
Blowing whatever company and say hey, I'd like a 5,000 pounds of broken glass
You order of panes of glass and somebody has to smash them on the ground
Who was this?
AB
ABCDEFGA. It's okay. It's the letter. It's the alphabet
15 okay, so M is one just somebody screens such a screenshot. I don't care prove you deserve a second chance
SON
Okay, what's SO SON?
The password is son
SON
All right. So if the password is s son, then we have to assume
ABC so what there's no s here. Is there oh, let me count
All right, and this and L is 26
L M N O P M N M N M is 2
L M 2 L M N O P Q R S would be 7
So it's 7 2
7 2
Wait, what's it doing? Oh is 3 and it's 2 right? So it's
7 3 2 I deserve a second chance, of course
It's just not even why even have the door Ruby deserve a second chance I did prove it now give me a needle
Uh-huh. Fooled you tricky. Wait
Not this time
And almost shot him in the head. I still have a flashlight or did they take that from me?
I think they took it from me. Why would you duck? I don't know nice
How do I attack with weapon? It's not what I wanted to do. I just wasted a health pack. How do you swing?
It's not r1 not r2 not l2
triangle circle a fight
Square it's not square
what TV's
He's talking I guess you're taking up. Oh you are
You and me. Let's go. How do you attack?
This is this is this is turn-based combat. No, it's not what's a swing. It's turn-based combat
No, it can't be it actually can't be
It's QTE based combat. The first game
was you could swing the bat and swing the melee and have a gun and
Take his life to earn back yours
Why would you?
Make it a QTE game though. This is we're supposed to revolutionize and
evolutionize our sequels
Why take combat out of the game it had to have been people that worked on this when the lead guy was like, okay
So here we are. We're gonna take combat out of the game. Oh
That's probably really fucking bad. We're gonna replace it with QTE's. Oh
Fuck. Oh fuck. This is bad. This is really bad. All right
I need to sir. We have to find a fuse search the random boxes
I can't I can't see where a box even is veto. No, I can't veto this
I have to at least suffer through this for a couple of hours. I have to I
Beat saw one. I can't let saw to beat me that easily. What did I miss?
We're gonna give up that easily. You guys are gonna give up that easily
Check the body. Oh god. Damn it. Yeah, we were fighting for his his fuse that he had in his pocket
It's vile put it on now. I'm not vetoing where I'm gonna suffer through this for at least another 30 minutes at least
Did I pressed it right I did he's gonna torture us no, okay
This is really important for you guys to understand. I am NOT torturing you
I am torturing me and you are watching me get tortured. I'm not torturing you
I'm the one with I'm being alone. We're getting electrocuted. You're watching me get electrocuted. Okay, follow the rules
Am I gonna get uh, am I gonna get minus one attack on my next buff? What is it? What's the card?
I fucked it up. Who cares?
What's the guy say follow the rules? Is it everyone gets minus one attack 30 seconds. Uh, I
Have to stop it at one of these at four
Fuck am I gonna stop the fourth digit at four?
What?
Sorry, dude, you're dead. I have they often be zero
They're all gonna be zero. Hey, it's really hard. I'm sorry
If it were you over here, you would have the same problem
I feel really bad man, but you can't be mad at me for not doing a puzzle
You would have had to do the same shit. You had to deal the same thing. Wait, what's that say? Oh
peak
That's so stupid
It's so dumb. Just I fucked it up. But whatever 3054. This is
Escape room, you know when you can play those escape rooms. This is what they do
This is escape room that you all pay 75 dollars each to do
They set this stuff up for you. So you can make sure you can leave
This game was probably 60 bucks when it came out. Oh shit. Okay. Oh that person tried to go in there and he died
What can I do? Oh
Hey sequence coming up. I think it's gonna be a chase sequence. I can't wait
I can't wait wait, but I can't wait for his ex at the right time to swing my weapon at a guy
Alright, was this combination lock? I don't know. I don't go find the
glow in the dark shit this riff next message
Why'd you do that? Listen, it's a serious crime as a sex offender. Oh, this is the guy that guy was sitting there
Okay, well he exploded there is a little bit of him is over there some of them is over there some of them's on
The wall back there
All right. Is there another answering machine? No, wait
This would be a second message on the machine
He has a script
Didn't go back and delete these ones
He tried to do the thing where he calls somebody and leaves a voicemail and deletes like eight of them before he gets the perfect
one
Just waiting for one of these to be like I wait for this to be like next message next message next message
Next message. Okay, that's it. It's a family guy joke. Oh
Oh
Defend oh good. I just hit the ball 300 yards in the golf game. I'm fucking click what
This is so much worse than the first game. It's not even funny. This is not it's so much worse than the first one
Oh, we're suffering. It's Halloween. And what do you do on Halloween? You well, you don't you don't suffer other people suffer though
You know, like you watch
Exorcist and like everyone's suffering in that movie. It's kind of what this is. That's what you're doing
It's all twice. I suffer. Yeah, just imagine my head just went around in a circle and vomit came out of my mouth
I need a key to go over that. I don't wait wait. Oh
Wait, hold on. There it is right there 8 1 2 0
Just have the doors open just have them open. It's so meaningless. Just have the doors open
It's just extra time in between opening each door. I already go down here. You can't open this
Filler yeah, okay. Hold on. Oh, let's see third times a charm strike three. Who is waiting with a shotgun?
Okay, that's pretty good. That's pretty good
They added that just to do that. You know what? I will give them the benefit of the doubt and say that that's what they
Did that for? Oh my god, this is so far back. Don't fuck that up again. Oh, wait, I have a chance to save this guy
But can I go in the room? He's in
Can I go in? Oh, come on. I wish I could just go in the room. I can't just go in
Trying shit, dude. This is fucking hard. Oh, man. Sorry. It's fucking hard over here. We go for five guys hard
Let me get that wrong real five four. Oops. No messing around. I actually I want to get through this cool
Yep, we went over here. We said what the hell happened to that guy. We snuck in here got the thing here
What was the T pose? Yeah, that was weird. You just let a guy explode and left
Well, that's cuz that was the second time we'd seen it. I don't know that way. All right, we go to this way
Here he comes
Holy fuck. Are you kidding me? Why did wood come out of his head? Why this guy made out of wood?
All right, we're back where we were. Everyone relax. Everybody chill out. I'm not gonna get caught by this again. Oh
Yeah, okay, there's I need the key
Exanima or this is pre-recorded exam of this. I'm playing scary horror video game right now. All right, let's not fuck this up
Here we go. He doesn't do it twice. He does do it twice. Why is the gun still there?
Oh, I thought it was somebody holding the gun at the door. I
Four three zero. I thought it was like every Tarantino movie, but there's just like
What's that somebody at the door? I don't want to even play this one. I don't have enough things to do it
Okay, I can do it. I can't I don't have enough. I don't even have remotely enough to do this. All right. Bye. Wait
I didn't think I could pick that one up. I would go big one first. Come on. Come on. What what?
What stop going out of the game? I don't think I have enough
We said Coggers. I can't do it. I don't have enough. Wait, I can do it
This is because this is because Chuck E. Cheese said poggers that time when he went like poggers
No poggers. I got it. No. Oh, I got a key. Oh
Pretend to be engaged
Gotta pretend to be engaged in the game and say things like ooh and huh and oh got to pretend to be engaged
Can't have dead hair. I can't have more than five seconds. Goodbye without a noise coming out of my mouth
People will leave they'll leave and they'll find somebody that's funnier and has more voices come out of them. Gotta fucking talk. Okay
Where's that? Where's that locked door guys?
Over here. I think it was yeah, it is. Let me unlock it real quick. Keep talking keep them here
Balancing board lookout. Whoa, it's tricky. Oh chat. We almost lost it
Stop knock it off. What?
You know that back wall back there. I feel like I've done Christmas decorations like that before
Yes, cuz like fuck it. Get him up. I don't care. Just put him up
It doesn't matter who's gonna be mad about it of the case file
Shit, I'm doing that thing again
Quick jingle your keys for us
2020 decoration stats
Strats no, that's all decoration
You just don't you know, you just duck you decorate the front part of the tree wherever your tree is
It's in a corner. Just decorate the part that is visible the 180 degrees. It's visible. Don't do the back
It's just extra time. I was getting them off is a huge pain in the ass. It's razor wire
Well, this is not I don't that's not my Christmas decorations, right? I what do I do need a nail? Oh
Good thing. I looked in the one dumb place that it was it's not a pain in the ass. It's tradition
Well, no, it's tradition for the first like ten years
Until everybody kind of doesn't care anymore
Once you once you get over the age of like 15 16 17 18. It's more
All right, let's decorate the tree. Oh
Okay. Yeah, that sounds like a good idea. That sounds cool. Oh, can we just do the plastic candy canes this year?
that's enough right and by the way it all plastic candy canes that you easily hang and
Lights wrap it around or just put it all over them. You know, that's that's enough. Look if you decorate your tree like crazy
Um, you know, I'm glad you and your family have that awesome time
Well, whoever you and your son even other whoever just you you might just do it for fun
Glad you enjoy it. Give me the plastic candy canes and just some red lights and I'm done. Fuck this guy
No, I didn't say that it was stupid. I said I did say what did I say was stupid? I may have I didn't know
I didn't I never said it was stupid. Look in the nightstand of the window. He's a Grinch. No
Sorry. No, I've never broken into a bunch of people's houses and stolen items from their house. I'm not the Grinch
You call me. What's the bah humbug guy? Okay, the ballroom Scrooge right call me Scrooge not the Grinch
Scrooge is worse. Is Scrooge worse than the Grinch?
Let's break this down
Scrooge
Ebenezer Scrooge. He was like a billionaire or something and he like owned all of New York or something, right? He was a dick
What did he do? Well, I don't remember the story
I remember he was just kind of like an old guy that everybody like thought was a big Ebenezer Scrooge. What secrets are you killed people?
He killed he literally killed children
Starved children and killed them
Okay, well
Maybe stealing an iPad out of somebody's house is not as bad
I let me retract that statement. The Grinch is not worse than Scrooge. Oh wait
Didn't the Grinch like kill people too in the original story? Oh in the original story didn't the Grinch?
Didn't the Grinch like kill somebody?
No, sort of what he did something crazy. He did something bad. The Grinch ate people. He ate people. Wait a minute
Hold on back up here the Grinch ate children. No, he didn't. Why would Dr. Seuss do that?
I have guys both of these stories. I have not seen or read or heard in more than a few decades
Yes, there was the Ron Howard Grinch movie, but I only watched that movie with the Jim Carrey noises
I didn't pay attention to the story at all 15 years ago when it came up and the original cartoon I watched
20 years ago Jim Carrey fanboy. Okay, so that's a bad thing. Oh
Thank god, they're not all like that
100% he sucks
Alright, hold on a minute. I need you to go watch the mask just do it just tonight
It's like a Christmas movie. Wait, it's a Halloween. It's a Halloween movie
He's in a costume and he goes to costume parties and stuff watch the mask tonight
Do it and then I want you to come back tomorrow and then tell me that that Jim Carrey is not good
I just had you have to do that. Why the TV's in the ground. He's getting kind of he's getting a little
Rave party here. Wait floor puzzle
Okay camera
That hurt
But I have to
And looks like what we have here is person amber I had to do it at least I'm sorry I had to
Okay, step on the hearts come on the tape and then step on the camera
And then step on the heart and then step on the puzzle piece, it's not gonna be that easy
It is gonna be that easy
No, it's not go down
camera
Okay, I don't get this one just jump over
Yeah, just take a running start and jump over it and roll on your back the first time you get electrocuted
Don't you think you're just going to throw your body over this as hard? That's not that far
That's not that far. Some people can step over this if they really wanted to you can jump over that
Vito this at 3 o 5 p.m. No, you're stuck here
All right, but is there like a thing to look at here? Why a heart what?
heart camera heart camera
What TV I thought it was gonna be that easy
Okay, so now heart so that was heart
Camera tape art camera tape
It's the same the set I can't get to a cassette from here puzzle
He's doing the same thing
Well, what the fuck is this puzzle? You have to start from the same place
Answer was outside of the door. Oh you walked into
That's not stop pretending you're gonna lose viewers. That's how you gain viewers. So don't tell me not to do that
TV at the beginning it's on that TV. Is it wait? Hold on God art
Tape, uh-huh
Art tape art tape of the safe spaces. Okay, cool. I'm gonna get hurt. Let's wait
What art and tape like go diagonal just you know, you can't go diagonal
I'm gonna get in trouble for cheating. You just did I wasn't watching I was watching the stream
I know for a fact that almost everyone here does not care about that. That means you care about this game. There's no way
Wait, are these please tell me this is saw. No, come on. I can't just play his audio tapes
I can't play his like auditions now feels bad, man
Okay, that's cool. I got a lockpick now. It also doesn't help that this game is
ugly and dark
It's it's too bright and too dark at the same time
It's like it's only bloom effects are the lighting and then it's just pitch black. All right, how do I go to the next one? Oh
My god, I have a weapon. I need a combo now. Let's get the combination
Where's the combination is a three combination thing. Is it in the ashtray? I don't think so
515 145. Okay. This has a puzzle piece on it. Is that eight?
855 855
What time is that?
Shit eight. This is 835
What wait what time is
My covers gonna get blown here in a second my covers about to be flown my covers about to be blown
Right. Okay. 826. Well bike my cover gets to stay not blown. Yeah. No, it's not
It's two point six GPA. I may have I may have had something
This guy's not an enemy he's like a this is like a guy like a victim. That's so funny. That's so funny to me
What did it what it was? What was hot? It was like, oh
Okay, that's really really funny. Oh
Everybody must have thought I was insane dude. He can't read a clock
I saw the but oh my god. I have seven seconds
Turn it on quick. I got it. Oh
Why is it stuck at 20 when you take a plate out of the microwave too early?
Am I going because I just open that door go on go watch out
10k Ted it's really really horrible that
10,000 people just watched me not be able to read an analog clock for 30 straight seconds. That sucks
You know like I have to live with that now
Remember I told you this is just watching somebody suffer. What happened in my oh, what'd it say?
You see what he broke the metal pipe in half
All right. I won't mess this one up. I promise this was sock nails. Okay nails
Heartbeat nail heartbeat foot nail heartbeat foot nail. Wait. Oh
Those must be the ones I can't step on hammer
Nail I have to do it in that order. I didn't do it in order last time. Did I that was a misclick?
That wasn't I didn't do that nail a heartbeat. What?
Nail heartbeat over there. Hail heartbeat foot. I actually did not mean to click on. Oh shit. Here we go
They go jigsaw anything else
That's somebody else will read those feeling all right. Can we veto the game for you? No, you know, don't veto the game
I'm playing the game right now. You don't have to veto the game for me. Okay finds them to cut the chain
So I need bolts or something. There's no chance in hell. I'm vetoing this game. No, not yet, please
God if only I could get in the time machine the amount of people that
Begged to me to play this game every day for like three months and now everybody wants me to delete it
Nope sick
Here we go. I got the thing to cut the chain with
We have to beat at least the first boss before I freak out literally 5,000 new viewers did not hear you make that promise
Oh, that's true. You're right. This is 10k people here. So those who that weren't here
I I promised I was gonna play saw 2 three months ago for Halloween. Everyone was like, oh my god
I can't fucking wait, dude. It's gonna be the most fun thing ever
I have no idea what just happened
Okay, we've made a hole in the ground
Thank you, sir. I don't want to fall because I have to go down there, but I'll die if I fall from this high
Apparently the humans in this game weigh
1,500 pounds
Some people do don't they?
What's the fattest person ever on record? I can't just jump from here. I kind of want to just fall down, but no wait
900 pounds the fattest person on record your mom
Nice, please click the link. No, okay. I will was it. What does it say good link?
Okay, this is you know
I love when people say this shit because I know for a fact that you do not think that this is real
Well that too. There's no way that anybody thinks that was real if you thought that was really you'd be they'd be something wrong
There's no way that anybody thinks this is real. It's just not like it. No, this is absolutely not
I'm having a bunch of fun. I'm having a ton of fun
It doesn't get to be the worst stream of 2020 unless I don't have a good time. That's true
You can't stop complaining, but it just sometimes it's fun to complain. What do you think? Oh shit. No, no, no, no
No, the game saved the kid. Thank God. It's one of these it's the same thing. It's traffic jam puzzle
I need to get the whole thing. We gotta go through. I feel like I'm just playing the other game. It's dudes wicked whiny
Yeah, okay. I'm not gonna
Stop you and be like whiny shut up being that guy. I mean, yeah mods already did. Oh, well, okay out of here
I'm just kidding. I'm kidding. All right. So what the hell am I doing?
Wait, didn't I just?
Wait, what?
Let's just unblock the door
What oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, right
Okay, let's go into that slot over there. That wasn't in the last game. That wasn't in the last game
You just said to unblock the door in the last game. Give me some credit here, please
Which is cart cart listen man. All right, where's saw? I feel like I haven't heard his voice. It's making me mad
I cannot believe that you have to do this. I can't
Believe it. Don't do it. Do I get a gun eventually? I think I do like God hand now
I already did. All right. Here we go. This is this is where it's gonna get interesting
Here he is co-op mission. All right, so we're gonna read codes to each other. I got you. Okay
You activate switches on the correct order to escape the room. All right, I've got ah
Do I'll start at the top six
Six five four. Oh four. Try that one. How much time we have we have like four hours? Oh
Wait eight zero
Right zero just make me spell boobs
That's eight zero zero eight five. Oh, I can't even do it. I can do it
Can I this one six?
How do I know what order they're supposed to be in?
Eight fun so much fun here too bad too bad
Give me the numbers
Okay, so I had it right though. It was zero
Zero eight. Wait, why can I press eight?
Check the wall. Okay, everything starts with zero zero nine eight
Shh zero zero six eight seven zero five. There's too many of these zero eight zero. That's not eight
zero zero zero eight zero
five
zero
Zero nine it starts with eight
Wait, did I just press zero? This has to be faked. I can't be I can't impress eight or zero
Ignoring us what eight is already pressed. Oh, so it's eight. It's start always starts with eight. Oh, okay
All right, eight zero. All right, move this shit out of the way. It's definitely right here. It's definitely right here zero
It's probably right fucking there. Watch this zero
Eight zero. Nope eight
Need those numbers
Looking for eight. I don't see any eight. Hey, I see nine. I see you six eight
No, no, no, no
Yeah
They miss it eight
Eight oh eight. Oh, okay. Yeah. Yeah, there it is. There it is eight. Oh
Six four seven eight. Oh four eight. Oh four six seven. Got it. Eight. Oh six four seven. There it is
I see it eight. Oh six four seven. So we get eight. Oh six six, right?
eight oh six
four seven
five four
There's no time limit
Cheating it's on the wall. We turn on I don't think that's like a Jonah Hill character
Show it to us fine
right here
in eight, oh
It's right. I saw it before that's why I pressed it. Hey right there. It's on your screen
All right right now. It is currently on your screen right now on
Your screen. I sit right there. I saw it. I saw it. I saw it. I saw it. I saw it
I saw it. I saw it. I saw it. I saw it
I saw how did you guys even see that when I was walking around being a dickhead?
All right, so we talked to this guy. Okay, so in the first game, you know
We're just like we're just murder which is killing criminals
I mean I am gonna put it on his dick. So you guys will blow the row up. Oh
Okay, so but now what do we do unlock this door? Why does everything have to be see what?
Her to the lobby. I have no guys. I have no idea where the lobby is from here. You promised us exanima
I don't promised exanima
Said I'm gonna look into it at that
Is this not the lobby but to keep going back? It's not this door. Oh shit. We can go on
Let me go in here. How does this guy get out of the mall me?
Um, I just kind of tricky. I'll be honest with you and I'm not making this up. Did I park here?
When did we come in? I took the right and went down towards where the food is
But is the store I think I feel like everybody's like that. I will tell you with them at complete total confidence at the last
Ten times I've been to a mall maybe eight or nine times
I walked around going with my horn because I had no idea where the car was probably eight or nine times out of ten
No, I feel like way more people that will admit that actually do that. You guys don't do that
Just get a valet at the mall
What what mall do you go to that has a valet?
Mall valet at Walmart imagine there's a valet at Walmart. That would be so ridiculous
Hey, you know holy shit imagine like a
Imagine an app where you you can just drive to it like and be
You can be a valet somewhere. That would be so ridiculous. You could have like be a valet at Walmart
I need someone to my that's just uber. That's uber with an extra step like I'll come get come get me in my groceries and just
Drive me home come get me and drive me to my car
next-level laziness
an uber valet
Can't even all right you guys have I got okay. All right. All right. I gotta play
Play all right, so nothing up here all right ban the word exanima
From like nightbot have nightbot start banning the word exanima. I'll do it
Yeah, okay
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay? That should be done
toilet was that reach into the toilet and grab the
Key or something right like the lap yep?
For a second I thought those are all in my head you went bobbing you've stuffed your head in there
Probably not smart. It's the same animation
Well, it's this it's probably the exact same copy and pasted video game with new rooms being made that case file, okay?
Exanima band hold on Otto wants to go on time
Oh my goodness that just bloated show Otto hold on I have to itch my eye
I did this
What's currently the thing wait?
There is someone waiting to be freed in the lobby in here all right? Let's get him
What are we gonna? Do everybody just wrote? I know that guy, but what do I have to do?
I told you this is where you eat somebody so he's definitely gonna die you have to play candy crush
Turn all the lights off sure how about this one?
How about that one?
How about this one and then how about that one and then how about this one and then how about that one and then how
About this one and then how about that one and then this one?
Saved you how about this one and then we'll do that one and then how about this one and then that one and then how
About this one
Saved you let's go this one
How about that one and we'll do this one and then we'll go this one and then this one and then that one and then
We'll do this one and then we'll get will you that one and we'll get you with this one and then this one
And then we'll shut this one off
No, and then we'll shut this one off
Shut that one off and then shut this one off and then that one and we'll then we get this one and then we turn
Up this one and that lets us go to this one
Fuck and I I gotta ask why I game over there. I didn't die
Revolver is powerful
This is like an anti tank round in there all right. I got it. I can't even get one to do the first one
I hate this shit. I hate these. I don't look why can't they be one where I could press the button really fast
I'm so good at those come on. Come on. This is it shit. He's dead again. He's fucking gonna die again
What I didn't get it. I hate these things
It's just like I don't want to sit there and press like the light button. I hate this shit
I hate these like to press the button to close the door two doors open. I mean I just close them all just
Just
Smear your hand on it was this all right. Why is the game frozen? You're watching me all right?
I just hate these I'm so bad at these why can't we want to be singing to the microphone well?
Why can't they be a rock band-esque hold like a an a note? You know ah?
I can just do that so easily. I can't this stuff is hard for me. It's god damn it
I'm so I can't do them. I just upset hate them fucking hate these I
Hate these little like little little tinkering tucker little tinker and blow the guys fucking heads out about a sprinting competition
We just sprint as fast you can I'll beat you every time all of you. It's not timed. I can't wait to hear
It's not time so it hits the the two around it which they'll put one up top
Then we go like this
Can't see basic patterns. Yeah, I didn't go to math school, okay? I
Went to swim wicked fast school. I can do that all right, so then this one
So this is a lot this will turn this one off, and we'll like this one up and turn this one off
So this would be this would be lit up and we do this one now. We need to do left
I'm gonna press. Are you sure it's not timed to press left and right I mean it's not timed all right
So then this one if we press this one it'll get rid of this one turn this one on and then we need to turn on
Somebody said no no no no wait wait what and then this and then this and then this no fuck
You guys want to hear something funny I have pretended to do these
Since I was a child
You know when you when you get it presented with one of these things and you do it you just go
Oh, yeah, I guess this one and the guy guess that one and then this one. Oh, I got it
Yeah, I I just I've pretended to know how to do that making it. Yeah. Oh, yeah, absolutely just faking it
I I get how this works, but I don't care enough to give it the time necessary to do it
That's why I never do these puzzles because I'm just like oh, I don't buy press a button and two of them pop up
Jason I don't care fuck this give me it to skip this throw that rip it in half and throw in the trash
Or I just press a bunch of buttons and eventually get it and then people go. Oh, he got it. Yeah, I know
Hello one sec. Oh, you know what to do look on the screen all right right in the middle
Right in the middle sounds good all right now. What that's it a guy
Yes, screw you jigsaw you maniac stay right there George. I'm gonna help you
Start live stream hey hey guys. Hey, what's up everybody?
I need your help
I'm inside this room right here and this guy's gonna gun this mouth over here
But this is a little puzzle that I'm gonna get can you guys like we need to click maps on this shit
And you guys can help me out here in the middle again. Let's just put it back to where it was
What are you doing? What are you doing? That's not? Oh you met you. Oh, you don't care. You're just driving a dick
I get it. Okay. What can you please help me? No helpers, okay?
Looks like we got middle. Thank you. Okay, we did again
We were back to where we were before we're doing. Please only vote once just click on every square till you get it
That's what I typically do, but when there's a gun in a guy's mouth. I can't do that
Got you guys oh I burned you guys pretending
Father's dead he'll kill them all supposed to head towards the entrance. I'll try to find some help all right
I'll see you on the other side. Don't get yourself killed, okay. He looked it up
No, I did the thing that I said I always do I just just fucking hit random buttons until it wins
Come on. Oh, I was on the phone
Ever happened to you. I'm gonna break you down a scenario anytime you talk on the phone to anyone
That's another person that you do not know
How do you typically talk hey? Yeah, okay? Yeah, the appointment is over next week sounds great
Yeah, I'm a normal person just like you. We're both just we both talk just we both pretend like we're humans
Sometimes you accidentally let slip slip out being a human being on the phone
That happened to me the other day. It's calling about a package that I got I
Was like oh, yeah the path. Hi. How you doing? Yeah, I'm just talking about the package that I was supposed to get
It's you know it was it was a little late. I'm just seeing if it was it's still on time
We're gonna be coming on time. Oh, let me look that up for you sure wouldn't you give me that you know tracking info
Okay, cool. We're both talking to like this sounds awesome, so
fucking
So what time haha sorry about that. I'm really sorry for the profanity. I'm really what's happening I
Said fuck it. I was like ah so fucking okay. What's the time frame like it?
Uh
Sorry, I'm really sorry. Sorry. I was just a person for like a second. Sorry. I was a human
We pretended not be humans when we talked to strangers the thing is that the person on the phone was just like
Okay, I'm coming
Okay holding a crutch. I don't think I trust the guy just walking around with a crutch
Like you didn't find a better weapon than that and just a wooden plastic metal crutch
Get her out of there. I would I can't step over there. I have to find to do like a puzzle or something
Yeah, it's over here. It's in there. Okay, just
Something in there can't open this
Swim in there. I can't go in there guys
Okay, so should yes, why can it? We'd wants me to go in I have to turn that shit off before I go in so dark
Yeah, I know it sucks. What is he doing?
Oh, it's not cool. He doesn't have the force. Can you please pause the stream? I need to make a hot pocket
Yeah, we'll give you two minutes. Wait a second. Oh
How long say to make a hot pocket a minute 30 seconds something like that
It's three minutes to make a hot pocket. No, it does not three and a half
Does it I thought it took like two? Well see the problem is you're not using the crisping sleeve
You just put it on a plate you just microwave it. No, you're doing it wrong Freemurr rushes hot pocket viewer
No, I'm not. I'm giving him plenty of time. The problem is you're eating a hot pocket. I mean, that's yeah, that's true
I don't really like them that much. You know, I used to eat the
Wasn't there a pepperoni meatball one? Yeah, I used to eat the pepperoni meatball and marinara one all the time
All right, you back it's been like a minute, right? I'm just give me $50 minty Fox
Thanks for the 5,000 bits. We know. Thank you minty for the 50 fucking dollars. They say play it
I'm not sure what I'm supposed to play but thanks a huge amount of money
We also have five community subs from Malcolm. We had ten community subs from Austin
Atlantis and five community subs from Clore who we got earlier. I'll talk about exanima
I'm gonna ban me for saying that I should time me out for five seconds
Hey illest Gambino, thanks with five community subs pretty cool. Thanks a lot. Are you back?
Hey, what if this person's just went to go make a hot pocket and they were like now the saw to stream sucks
I'm just gonna go. I'm gonna go play ball and then what if they just don't come back? We gave them all this time
All right. That's all right. That's fine. That's enough. All right. What's one of my neck?
Missing something rescue the woman trapped in the box
Locate the pool pump to drain the pool
Yeah, it kind of makes me want a hot pocket. Is that weird?
I don't like hot pockets for one very specific reason
Because they're too hot to eat and then by the time that they're not hot to eat they're too cold to enjoy
This sucks all around and press the that's the very hot. It's very very hot. Okay, keep clean around this dirty laundry
I
Stolen bit what I steal that from I stole that from somebody. I mean, it's an easy joke
It's an easy reference to make you stole that from Jim Gaffigan. I know I didn't I did not steal anything from Jim Gaffigan
He did he stole so many things from Jim Gaffigan. I didn't steal anything. Oh
That's just that's baloney
If anything, I have all my material completely not made. It's all mine
He really thinks that doesn't he?
Thank you
Who the fuck is Jim Gaffigan?
He's a senator. He's senator from I think New Hampshire or something need a gear
No, there's no gears. Who the fuck is Jim Gaffigan? Oh, I just got really really sad. Oh
Someday in the next 10 to 20 years. It's gonna be that's not gonna be twitch anymore. It'll be like itch
The itch.tv or something. I'm gonna get hood 20 years from now on the new streaming platform
Aren't I what are you guys that's like 15 16 20 years old?
Whatever third the 20 20 years that you're gonna 10 years from now
You're gonna get make it big and then I'm gonna be gone
I'm gonna be retired in like 15 20 years or something and you'll make like a look at me and
Everyone's gonna in your chats all gonna be younger and they're gonna go what the fuck are you doing? Oh, that's uh, that's a
German Alberson bit the fuck is that guy and then you're all gonna watch the videos of mine that I made in like
Oh cringe. This guy's wicked cringe. Oh my god people watch this. Oh, how did they oh boy?
Yeah, other people must have been young
It's okay, it's alright what we're here now
We're here now me and you just you and me the hell was the point of sneaking through here
Is there a valve here or something? What was the point of this? Why would they say it in 30 years? It's already cringe
Now it is quick everybody go. Oh my god, just give me a valve so I can screw the thing in
You're watching this in the shower
Okay, oh, how you doing that?
And anybody see it's probably gonna be in like the washing machine or some stupid
It is it's actually in the fucking washing machine
Borderlands joke the rats are the best part of this game so far. Okay, so just get burnt by the steam and grab the key
He's really gonna be pissed off when I gently lean my face in here not too close and it's super relaxing
He's not gonna be happy about that
Oh
Now the whole place is steam
Okay
Got the key. I'd rather boil water
Instead of like a steam joke
Like that's a steam joke
We're good. I have the key anything else you use the crutch to hook the key
Yes, you could you absolutely could do that. Well, what if you drop it?
What if you don't get it well enough, then you just dead
Hey more of this bullshit can't wait
Well, it's wish it they wishes they could live here live where
What the fuck is this?
my mouse just fell at the same time I
Hooked my mouse with my leg in it left at the same time
And I made a clicking noise
That's I don't know why that's more funny to me than anything else. That's a that's a I that's a me thing here
You guys didn't get to experience that I'm sorry you couldn't
Yes, you had to be there and the face cam on you will get the face cam
Maybe if you're good, you're gonna be good. Oh
I want I'm turning the gamma up on this thing. You know what I mean?
It's time. It's time to turn up the gamma. We sec
Turn up the gamma. How was that cheating?
All I was making my hot pocket real quick. This is way too dark. I have this something going on here
Oh my god, that's a million times better. I can actually see the puzzles now
Imagine actually being able to see instead of what it was which was this I can see the doors
Thank you. Okay, let's go
You can see too. No wonder everybody was like dude veto this. I can't see anything. Oh shit. This is wicked ugly now
This is this is way uglier now still veto. Why would I'm not veto?
It's been two and a half hours. There's no veto here. No. Oh
I am you made me play this you said play this game. I want you to pull it saw to waiting room. You remember that one
We're sorry
No, I'm not done. I'm actually enjoying this. There he is. Oh
We just had him
Key to survival lies within okay. Is it here? Is it here? Is it here for is it too?
Question mark wait box nine
Okay, five eight four two like that's it, right? Oh shit. Wait five
Same number
Same number same explosion joke, right? That's so stupid. I love it. I love it
Just don't ever click on five again. That's the explosion number. Yeah, what was it? Here we go
So
Key to survival lies within
within me
within you
Is it is it?
nine
Is it here number four?
Imagine not having infinite lives. That's just where the character dies in the story
What's the actual percentage chance of somebody actually getting through jigsaws bullshit?
This is probably the five millionth person
He's had to try do this and how much of pain in the ass it probably was for the last guy when he set up
Four miles in eight warehouses worth of traps and the guy died at five in the first room
You get to write all that other shit off on your taxes
Okay, is it the shotgun shells on my back? Is that what it is? It's one two three four five six seven eight
That's nine. There is no nine. Okay, there's a nine right here
Just the amount of people that died to this one. Okay lies within
It's not the shotgun shells
It's not five. I hope look I opened one box the first time and it didn't blow up. What box was that?
Think of this one. Okay
Which number was it? What did I open first?
It's not just in order, right? It's not one two, three, four five. It's not right
the wires, oh
Shit, you're right. Okay, that one goes to nine and then goes over here to
Here, right? This is this is one
Open the ones that yeah, but I figured it was like that's how you deactivate them to open the one where the cord was going in
Nice Elmo laugh. Oh
For some reason it was like, oh, that's like deactivate them. I don't know
But why would that deactivate them? We just it would activate them. So just don't open the ones that are not connected to the wires
There's nothing to do with how many shells I have in my back or something in me within you
No, that that don't even who cares about the writing on the wall
Okay, do not open five
Do not open
Eight's okay eight is safe eight is safe. There's no cord going in there
That one right there is wrapping around it. It's not going in there. There's no cord going into eight
Impossible, there's no cord going to eight or seven
Cuz that's going all the way over here. See it's still going it's still going that one goes all the way over
Okay, no, what cord is going into eight that one is okay. Excuse me. No cord going into seven
Thank you. Oh, I've won
That's it. That's it. Is an eight out of ten link here that took so long
Yeah, I did but what do you want to do? What is it? What is this? I'm gonna press this button
And I'm going to press this button. Well, that's unfair because I just was able to see in the last five minutes
Bring the elevator down on dude. What's the point? All right elevator?
Get it on the X
Get that pump. I'm here. I thought that was the girl
uh
What Iron Man character was that because there's no way the human could do that
That dude went through five different
Stories through the ground
Okay. All right. I'm gonna go in here
move
Please take my groceries up to the seventh floor apartment before time runs out
So funny
It was smooth that was showing off. Oh my god. Why is all the broken glass here?
What is this?
No, I have to build something. What does he want me to do? What the fuck is going on? Oh, oh
It's changing. All right. What uh, what's TV that tells me what happens? Oh, no, this doesn't okay. This one doesn't blow up though
Right. There's no gun in anybody's mouth. Just had it. I just had it. I just had it
What does that do? No, no, no, no, no change change
Jump over it. What the fuck? I you just reach over it. It already triggered. That's gonna hurt me, isn't it? No, it's not
No, wait, how do I reset? Can I reset this? Just go go. Oh
What? Oh
That one was easy
Reset Randy reset Randy. I'm down. Okay. Now we have to push this somewhere
straight through okay
Wait, let me get some of these
For the next door. I have to open it. Would you guys be able to stand this dream if that's how I talked the whole time?
Maybe a little I don't know if that's supposed to be scary, but that's that guy was not scary
Just walking over here
Okay, where's the TV that explains this? We got snake hand
snake hand knife skull
but it's actually hand and
knife and
Knife ah and and knife skull snake and
knife
skull snake knife skull
snake
Hey, cool. It's in the box a nail. Well, that was great
He's done it good again. Oh down all the drag marks. What's the dead space thing on your back?
Those are oxygen tablets and that how it works in dead space. That's your oxygen level Oh
Two tabs. All right, we got to follow the track that guy ran away wherever you went
Oh, okay. So this has to go through I need to push that thing
Where oh I gotta move that
I gotta drag that thing across the whole game. Don't I like any Zelda game?
Um
Kind of don't I don't know not really I look I love Zelda. There's a cool franchise, but no
No, not on stream
Maybe one day maybe oh eight seven six. Oh
eight
Seven six. I don't hate Zelda. Why are you guys saying? I hate Zelda play dead space
You know, I might it's really you might see dead space here this coming in the next week or two
I don't know maybe the one problem I have with dead space
Is I have already I've never played it
I maybe played like a little bit of somebody's playthrough
But I have watched somebody play through pretty much that entire game more than once. No, you know
Maybe no not not a streamer. This is years ago
You might see it possible
He's too scared to play it himself
It's a pretty scary game. Oh
VR right. Yeah, so VR
I'm gonna do VR scary games
I have two or three horror games that are VR. That'll be for one of the nights coming up this week
Probably if not tomorrow
On the next day, that's right scary VR games coming the tomorrow the next day soon
Yeah within the next two days. I was gonna do it today
The reason why I didn't do it today is because I've been very tight
Recently, I had some body work done
I've been mushed around and moved around a lot with my problem. Yeah
Yeah, I've been pretty sore over the last
Six or seven days like at least the last three days. What happened this guy's in the room now
Oh, he ran through. All right, come and get me
I'm just trying to find a good place to s this
Hit me you died to ramming Randy. Oh, why'd I lean back so fast? No, I got to checkpoint
Dying means I die and I turn the game off. I was the X there's an X on a wall somewhere
He needs to ram into
I'm gonna I guess it's like not there
About right here
Really? I'm in the wall. What the fuck he pivoted so fast
Get it. He didn't get it
fucking God
Somebody said me when somebody takes my McDonald's Oh me when somebody steals a fry out of my books. Come on
Stupid. No me when a friend asks for one of my king-size Reese's. There's only four in there man
They should be eight. They should put two on top of each other. It's not a king-size. That's barely anything
king-size
Run into the fucking wall
Come on. No, I don't want to stick my
Have to do it are you fucking kidding me? I just got dark souls, dude
What are you a hide knight give me a break, okay, I'm getting I'm getting
real real sick of this
And him in the head I smash him in the head with this that was not a ram that was a chest bump barely
He faked you out
The idea is that he's hitting you with his head, right? That's what we're led to believe here
A Red Dead Redemption 2 on PC 1 2 3. I mean the 1 2 3 at the end actually made me read that so
It's pretty good work
I'm gonna play the tape
What does the tape say?
These people are not he's not like savable people
You stabbed children with knives Patrick's you
You ate children you murdered children. I
Swear to God didn't they like you did drugs for like a week or something. Like what is all this?
Break that. Oh, he was the one that was stabbed. So what the hell are you doing jigsaw fuck off?
He didn't hit the wall, can I just walk through
What I?
Can I be honest if I'm doing this right, right?
I have to try to get him to hit the door a few times the crack a few times
This is in a situation where like I can't read the analog clock, right?
You would tell me I would know
Let's get the abridged version, please. I got one. Oh
my god
Why can you do that? Why can you do that? That's not fair
You have to make him run into the mattress. No, you he already ran to the mattress like four times. Just do the skip
Hey, how's your Halloween week going so far? Hopefully good damn it. I tried to time it
I actually did time it pretty well to the end of the cutscene move
Circle the other way at this bitch. I can't move right now. He's still running. I can hear him
Okay, he hit me and the wall
Who got it easy? Oh my god
First scary part of the game was right there. You can't use Wilhelm for every scream
Yep, you can if you don't pay for any others. You got a new link me one sec
Let me get through the balance beam section sure thing. I'll open that up, dude
Okay, but why this why is this a big deal and it's too dark and this is so dark
I'm gonna turn the game up. It's ugly now
Yeah, take a take a selfie of your face in the dark with the flash on
Look at it, and you tell me what you think
What how did you click the wrong one? Why are you guys linking a picture of my like bulbous ass? I don't understand
I mean, it's definitely photoshopped. I'm I got I do have a big ass, but it's
Absolutely, I think that's photoshopped. I don't think that's real not at first try
There are no it's probably like do I really need to prove it?
It's probably four or five hundred thousand
Images of a screenshot of me my ass or something. I'm sure it is. Where are they? I don't know
I don't look up pictures of my own body parts
Well, do you think I'm gonna tell you I know where these are? I know they exist
I don't type in Jerma ass Jerma's ass like Jerma's balls. Like I don't type. Why would I type that in?
I know what they look like. I have them. I have they I own those things. I can look in a mirror
I don't need to look up my own ass on Google
I know what it looks like and I can look at it naked in the mirror. What's the code code bullshit?
All right, did I miss something? We're see code
Oh
What's that not air? Oh
I need a code, please. Oh, yeah, I promise. This is not the first saw game
Those you guys that are asking wait, ooh, all right. That's weird. It looks very similar. I know oh
There it is. Oh, it is
zero eight seven saw noose
Hatchet whatever that means saw but what number does that mean? I think that actually that is supposed to be a number
That's yeah, that's zero at zero something seven or be three three zero seven zero eight seven
So yeah, I had it right. Wait, where the fuck is that thing? I had it right didn't I? Oh eight seven
No, it was eight. Oh seven one. Oh seven eight. Yeah, it's eight. Oh seven then was it a was it a six Oh six seven
But how would the news the news has to be a zero, right? That's not how the puzzle works
Oh six seven. Well look at four numbers inside the room that was there
It was symbols on the walls in the room eight six seven. We might be overthinking this
All right. Wait, there was there was something on the wall where I was look for numbers related to the symbols
Yes, yeah
Six two one. Oh my god, please. All right that person if that's not right
I want that person timed up for five minutes. We'll see we'll see you get to stick around
You're about to get a five minute timeout. You're out. See you later
815 all right time that person out too for five minutes. I'm not kidding you. Yeah, come on. You hold up the stream. Oh
That person got VIP that person five minutes. All right. Now we can push this thing modem
11,000 people here. Holy shit. I'm just realizing that now. Hi
What's up?
Going on. I've been good. I was eight one five, right?
So it had to been something like on the wall that corresponded
With the symbols and that person has a walkthrough up
Because they're so desperately trying to make sure that I don't stay in the same area for like 40 minutes straight that they hope
That they're the one guy just putting solutions in the chat and I get it. I actually I appreciate it. What hurt me
All right going down. Let's get this thing that saved a lady. That's been trapped in that box
Everything's good. I happen to catch a stream of you playing a game. That was my favorite when I was young
When you were 10
Wait, you played saw the video game where people get like they're like heads cut off and like their bodies like maimed when you were 10
I
Didn't do that. Do you guys have experience with the M rated kind of R rated stuff before you were like 15 14 13?
I kind of I didn't
I was like 12 13 14. I don't think I did
Maybe like maybe maybe like 14 13 14 15 like I caught an R rated movie
I was like, oh, I snuck it. I found a way to sneak it
But I mean after like 15 it didn't matter anymore. I don't think I played Silent Hill when I was seven
What did you think?
You know, what did you think?
The whole thing let's fight you must have been terrified
Hold on. I guess I'm trying to the pocket turn power off. I feel like sevens a little young for that
Wow, very I would say very young for that
That's a being a wimp. I
Don't I I don't think I would want to be seven years old and see like the godfather
I don't think that what I would probably be like what's happening. Why is people killing each other?
Where's that guy's exploded? I don't think I'd want to see that my brother watched the exorcist when he was six. I
Feel like that would just really mess up your little child brain
For months potentially years. Are you telling me you can't I mean you talk about Barney the dinosaur and the wiggles
to
People being like having their heads exploded and eaten and like swears and stuff
I don't think you'd I wouldn't be able to handle that don't freak me the fuck out
Is that the guy that I've let out the beginning that the guy that got out free?
Well, there are consequences here. That guy's still here. Wait, can I open that?
Whatever don't even care. It's kind of spooky. Oh
I wonder if they're gonna move positions. Oh, it's just we just have to go stand in the corner. You mentioned Silent Hill
Okay, that's
nine three eight
Anything else there's just nine three eight. Mm-hmm. Fuck. I thought I messed it up
Game fucking stinks. Oh, there we go. Choose the next one, please. I really wish that that would kind of come back
Let's say sucks a lot of this sucks. This sucks. This fucking stinks
This stinks is better like that. I think that I would want to see that word used more
Like it's underused
Okay. What was it?
935 I don't remember nine three eight. Hey camera. Okay. Hold on. We have
quarter pills
camera, maybe pills
quarter pills camera pills
recorder pills
camera pills
In that order your thing the quarter
Hills wait, how do I recorder pills camera pills order?
Camera pills president sleeper snooze
sleep
bed
blankets
Nightlight. Okay, we're making progress here hills
quarter
Sly Cooper waiting room. The same thing's gonna happen. I'm gonna open I'm gonna open sly Cooper and
Immediately immediately it's gonna be like over socks. It's stupid. Fuck you for buying this idea
This is so long. This is so long. This is taking forever
Alright, that was pretty long. Can't break it. I'm going there. If you said sly Cooper sucked
I would just sub just to unsub
But here's the thing if you sub you're giving me five dollars when you unsub that just that's you saying
I'm not gonna resubscribe in 30 days
So I get the money regardless
big puzzle
Memory it's not about the money
Oh
Sucks, okay, let's start in the corner. No, I don't. Oh you have to put the piece in fuck
Okay, hold on
I need a left in a left in a top left in the top with a bottom in the middle left in the top bottom
In the middle a left in the top of the bottom in the middle a left in the top of the bottom in the middle
I left in the top of the bottom of the middle a left in the top of the bottom in the middle left in
The top and a bottom in the middle a left in the top and a bottom in the middle
Left in the top of the bottom in the middle. No left in the top of the bottom in the middle
Left in the top of the bottom in the middle. There it is
Okay, we need left and right and a top and a down left and right and a top and a down
Left and right and a top in a I
Want you to see my face when I die?
No damage, of course it did damage. It's not very much. It was a prop effect
It may I may have felt the flames a little okay. Here we go
Got it. All right, we need a
Down the corner. We need to let a top a left and a top left and a top and a bottom in the middle
It was right here, wasn't it? What was it? They just scramble it
Scrambles it every time where the fuck is that piece? Come on, right next to it. Fuck. Okay, we need the holding arms out
All right. We need a top and a right and a bottom in the middle top and a right and a bottom in the middle
we need a
Left and a bit left and missing and missing and up
Left and a missing and missing. Okay, we need a top and a right in the middle top and a right coming into the middle
bump on the log of the hole in the bottom of the sea
there's oh, there's a
Whoa
For warden up. There's a ward on the hair on the free other
I can't I could do the whole thing if I'm gonna do it
There is a hair on the flea on the board on the frog on the log on the bottom of the sea
Yeah, there's a ward on the hair on the flea on the frog in the log in the bog
I could do it. You gave me the whole thing. I
Saved you this is a betrayal
Wait, okay. What should I do?
We both is gonna have or
five six, okay. All right, here we go right one two three
four five
six one two
three four
Five six. Oh shit. He's moving. Where's he?
speed runner I can't
What okay if you point down there, there's a subscribe button down there, you know
That's what follow button could follow for more puzzle gameplay. They call me the puzzle master
That's where they you know in trivia nights after they call me more puzzle master gameplay
What door just opened I don't know I'm paying any attention back down the Riddler slugpog
Did I delete that? Oh, you got one? Hold on. There's
Okay, there's a
speck on the fleck on the wing on the flea on the hair on the ward on the tail on the frog on the bump of
The branch of the log in the hole in the bottom of the sea
There's a speck on the fleck on the wing on the flea of the higher the word on the tail on the frog in the bog
In the bog. I got it the first time. I did it the first time. It's fine. Oh, yeah, we'll save this person
You're the one in the box lady. That's not a good bargaining chip to say fuck you to the person
That's the only hope you have if I get choice between you and the puppy
I'm saving the puppy just want to let you know and I go down. Okay that hurt I guess
Again anything to say jigsaw
Move
Okay, I guess I
Reset. Oh
What am I moving I need to how do I get over the other how to can I stop them I'm filling it up faster
What the hell just happened?
You're fine. Just hold on a minute. There it is
What just hold on hold your breath the average human can hold their breath for 60 seconds. I got you
You're good. Why is it? No, I don't I don't understand. Well, I can't press any buttons. You're doing great
You have to line them up at the same time. I haven't I've done that like three times now. You're doing really good
Holy shit, we got a Navy SEAL here
I'm doing this obviously completely wrong. Well, I'm just hold it there. I can't though. I
Don't I believe what am I supposed to do?
Sink them I already did that
It lined up and the thing could go right down the middle. You're still alright
They all have to be just going this at the same time
I was I thought it was they all to line up right in the middle so that the water can just go through
But I didn't I do that already on the second one it would lined up correctly needs to be perfect. Oh, okay
That's stupid. Nothing's perfect. Here we go. All right
Nothing's perfect almost a little more
All right. Nothing's perfect done. I did that last time. I'm mad about that
I did that last time and it didn't work and I was like, well, this doesn't make any sense
But if the price of the different, uh
Got it. You got you can hold your breath. We have time when you start holding your breath. Fuck
No
No, she's gonna drown
Just the bottom was not even eyes off to
We have time we have time. We have time. Come on. That's it. What?
Fucking dead why
why
Line them up. So they all go and they all line up at the right point at the same time. She's drowning
Scary shit, isn't it? What's the game have that's too high? I'm getting it this time. I'm doing it
I'm swear to God what that doesn't count. I have to let it go. Okay, go go go go go go go go go go go go go go
Go go go go go go go go go go time time got plenty time now. Wait, we're good. I hold on easy. Okay, hold on. Oh
Get the fuck out of get the fuck out of get the fuck out of get the fuck out of here
You know your name
He was and what you did to him you're a monster these slippers are really comfortable by the way and we're in the whole time
You broke him I did just save her life. That's true. Oh, yeah, I'm not done. I'm not done with you. I said I'm ah
Come on. Oh, they trap you in here. She leaves saw two
So after saw two they didn't make another game
Five more movies came out but nope, they weren't gonna keep up with this
No way
There's seven of these eight of these. I wonder why I don't know weird
It seems bizarre that they wouldn't make another one means the first ones were
so good
Bizarre, I think one to end this on a high note. Fuck. Oh
No, this TV fell down. He can't berate me back. Ooh
There it is wait take it out the puzzle in record time
You know, this game would have actually been really good if you have to make choices and kill somebody and keep somebody else alive
We could have at least made choices
Rather than just do another light puzzle to save this guy or he's gonna get squished
Okay, I need a lever and I need
Dig so you suck at making stuff. There's a house with a wall with a dad at the bottom of the city
All right, find the lever find the acid plating area. This open none of these are open lever
Build my elevator. Well, it's obviously not here. Can't go in there shipping and receiving
Big so what the fuck do you want me to do here? I watched a door open. Did I
Sure, I was looking away from the video game. I might have been looking away from the video game at that moment
Alright, let's go. Oh, did I accidentally just not die from whatever that was circuit? Oh
It's got to come from up doesn't it sick. Okay. Now we got to get yellow has to be this way
Has to be this way
Way, what'd you do that for? What the fuck? What just happened dumb fuck this is wrong. All right, hold on
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, it has to come from up and down
So therefore it has to go like this or this has to so we're gonna say
Kill this and this over here and then that goes like this and this is wrong again. It's wrong again
Okay, it's wrong again. I okay. I did it. I did it very very very well
Accidental, all right, find the lever
I
Needs in your chat
Not a joke Kanye's here. What's up? What's going on Kanye? What's up?
You're gonna tweet out the screen
Imagine that's easy
Alright, it's just Kanye holding a picture up that says like a reddit AMA time stamp on it. That says hi Jerma
All right. I got you. I got you. How do I get it? What's with acid?
The color was messed up
I thought it was the other one pink and red. They look kind of similar sometimes
Melt the chain
We're good
It's Amanda again. All right. How many times I'm gonna drop my mouse on the ground
All right. Don't accidentally turn off like the stream or something. Come on. All right, what's in here?
All right. There's the valve I need
Nothing. Okay, that's the valve up here. We've got there's no timer. So this is fine get you when I get you
Get him I'm getting him
No danger in this game besides stepping on glass and stuff
Was that all right, we have a combination lock it's probably one two three
well, let me scoot closer to you walk pick the DLT box and
That's it. Just the lock pick. Sure, but I say that I won't know definitely gonna order McDonald's. I'm gonna uber eats McDonald's
Yep, oh I think so
What did that do? Yuck. You don't yuck McDonald's here
Alright, who has the code? I went guy with the walkthrough that's sitting open that's spamming it in the chat right now
What is it? I four three and I was hoping that the last security guy just forgot to scramble it when he left
Six nine four. I'm getting flashbacks the last time I did no I'm not doing this again
I'm actually getting flashbacks the last time I played the first game. So what did that connect? What does that do? Oh,
I got over I'm going elevator
Stab I wonder if there are any celebrities that watch my stream. What do you guys think?
You think I do like Brad Pitt's here. Sometimes he's just a huge fan, but he will never be able to say that out loud
He will never say that
Brad Pitt's probably under the covers right now with a right
iPhone screen in pajamas. Okay. Well, I need a coupler. I'm just spam search every box
The door about Chuck E cheese
Chuck E cheese is not a celebrity. He's a toy. He's a big toy. He's not a celebrity
He's a mascot is a mascot a celebrity. Okay, would you would you say okay, would you say the?
Like the guy dressed up as the penguin or like the penguin hockey team
Is that a celebrity the guy in the New England Patriots Elvis costume? Is that a celebrity?
Darkness illuminates. Well, thanks that no it doesn't why'd you just tell me that?
apologize to mr. Cheese
No, he's a great mascot, but he's not okay
They don't Chuck E cheese does not go to the red carpet during like the Oscars or the Emmys or anything. They don't interview
Chuck E cheese to ask him what he's wearing. Oh Chuck E cheese come over here. Let's see what you're wearing today
Well, it's uh
It's it's a it's a shirt for a toddler
It says see on it for for Chuck E for Charlie and I wear pants biker shorts that ride way up to high and they're a
Little too tight. I wear this John. I wear this every day. Oh
You look marvelous
Really? Hope I get the Emmy
This doesn't do anything
Nightwing t-shirt and cargo shorts. What about it? What is it best dressed from what?
I can tell everyone looks stunning tonight on the red carpet
Shit oh
That's not good
Where where is he he's okay, he's on the red a red carpet
All right, but hold on a minute. Is this like the Oscars or is this like the Nickelodeon Teen Choice Awards?
This dude's awesome. He just done. Okay. Oh, what a celebrity, huh?
This dude like I went when like half of your press like doesn't even give a shit that you're on the red carpet
He's just guessing where that photo is. He doesn't even care
He's happier to be on the other guy's camera
You bet your ass this guy's gonna put his face right in and focus the fuck out of that camera when like ariana grande walks
By not for Chuck E cheese apparently. This is a staged photo
This is in front of this is in front of a backdrop. This is a backdrop. There's a backdrop. It's not a real carpet
This is a backdrop. No, it's not real. There's a backdrop here
Anyways, yeah, I'm okay. Sure. Have you ever been invited to a red carpet thing?
No, because last time I ate as many hors d'oeuvres as I could
I was really really hungry. I hadn't eaten all day and there was somebody walking around with like the free shit of food
There are clams. Oh, wow. I'll take bacon-wrapped scallops
I just ate a ton of them and then after that I never got invited back to anything else and I know that's why
I'm certain that's why
That's a saw that that that's a boomer joke
Yeah, okay. Sorry. All right, and you can't make can't make any references to anything that I
I'm old you have to where I'm going you guys have never had a hors d'oeuvres before
What's the answer? I don't care. I just I know it's like to turn the light on in that room
But it didn't work. I don't have a coupler. Why can I just have an infinite coupler coupler, please?
This is the bathroom again. How many guys have been to a wedding? You guys never had hors d'oeuvres before I find that hard to believe
like by the time you reach the age of
17 15 you've probably already been to one or two weddings here it is on the image a
German 520 1026 20 PS. I love saw 2
He took it at the red carpet. I'm not even put it on stream because I don't even know
What's the answer? I know somebody has it. Please. Please. Let me continue the stream
I know somebody has it and don't fuck with me
please
Please please you I don't want to do I don't want to go in that room and look for it. Oh what?
454 please at least one of you do the work. No, I'm not doing the work
027 come on. Help me out here. Help me out do the work. No, I'm not doing work. Do the fucking work
I'm not doing the work. It's it's not six to one
No, it's not
Please two three four one two six
The worst come on I don't want to do this I've tried it's I can't even figure the what am I supposed to do
darkness illuminates
Let's take a look sure is dark in here
Turn the light on well, I think I'll turn on the light for a little bit
Juggles the clown
Oh
Condition illuminates. Oh
Happy Halloween every happy Halloween
Okay, do you see I don't see anything behind you there's nothing here
I'm spinning in a circle in the toilet darkness illuminates, but there's an inside the toilet. There's something for that couple are
Just a couple of humans
Get it
Rab
What does that have to do with darkness illuminates turn on the lights? I can't do that
And to that Goku. All right. Now, let's go back to this stupid thing wherever it is
Plug in the coupler do the the lightning thing. It's not 620
It saw 621 everyone wants me to write that
Where's this room with the coupler in it? Where the hell is this room that year? It was 620
Thanks a lot
Apologize, I am sorry. I'm very sorry. Please accept my apology
Did it right that's free I did it I've been uh, who the fuck are you? Where did he come from?
Defend if you could please do I'm hitting square. I promise
Grandpa scream. Yeah, what was with the grandpa scream? This guy looks like he's in his 20s
We did it we can leave way I what did I do I feel like this came down here walked around a circle
What did I do? Holy shit? Okay. That was about as a head shotgun. It's the first head shotgun of the game
It made this one so much easier because it's gonna be a quick time for every single one. We've got one is we got hand hand
knife skull snake and
knife skull snake and knife skull snake and knife skull snake and
knife
cool, right
Sure nice game nice liar game
Which is slow. I was not too slow. I was right on top of that
The really roundabout way to get whatever this is a puzzle piece. It's not what I wanted
I wanted a lever or a stake or a wheel or something. Not this shit
Let's go
Obama's in the chat
He's under the covers
His pajamas. I did it. Let's release you from that
Wait, stop. He shot me. I got shot by that gun
I
Don't explain to me why this guy's doing this again wasn't didn't I wasn't stick out the gun in his mouth
Or is he? Oh
There's a minigame too. This is gonna be fun. You know, he can't come over and shoot me the back of the head, right?
Yeah, that was very very easy
Please chat. Let's tell me where his weak point is. It's not his chest. I shot him in the chest twice
It's not his arm because he has a thing on his arm. It's not his head fucking please help me
Somebody do it for me. Somebody looking up for me. I can reload it. Wait, what do I go? God damn it right there
Go through the door. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry
Ram is in the chat. We get raided by Jerma. It's cool
What's up? What's up everybody? Don't with the emotes. What's going on guys big ray. There's a big one
That's a shitload of people. What's up, man? Hope you had a good stream. What was Jerma doing today?
Are you serious he's playing saw to I saw him play the first one that game sucks, huh?
I feel bad for him. It's like really hard to keep up with that
We don't play on on this channel like it's far too difficult to like be able to play a game
That's old and terrible and like, you know talk to chat and everything like I wouldn't do that here
Props to him though like props to him like mad props sing the raid song. Of course. Well, I'm crazy
Yep, wait acid corrodes metal as well as flesh. That was very that's it
Thanks, man
It's gonna get dunked in the acid
Don't you believe I would get out of here. I'd get out of here. Okay use the key to enter the lacquer
Studio. Well, well, what's in his cell anything interesting? Yep
Oh
Wait this well, what would the dude over there? That's that's dude over this thrown acid on people
Saving people in strange manners here. Hello Michael over that time that you
Burnt that entire village with all these old ladies in every house because I'm detective tap saving you
Did they just do like a secret handshake, did you see that
You're gonna get head-smashed in you're gonna get head-smashed in
Guarantee her head smashed in over there when we go over there lime rates lime raid
Slimers, what's up?
welcome
slimers
climbers put your hands up
stand up
Unenthusiastic rate. All right. The next time I get rated. I'm gonna do a very unenthusiastic raid acceptance speech. What's up?
How's everybody doing?
No fucking way
Dude, what's up?
All right, just don't touch the bombs raid
Have you ever eaten a corn dog? Yes, I've eaten a corn dog
Why does that matter by the way? Well, who cares if I've ever had a corn dog?
Does your opinion of me change if I've if I love corn dogs or something? What about okay?
What if I have one and I don't like it? It does change. Okay
Well, you're trash
Trash I way I like corn dogs. I didn't say I didn't like corn dogs
If human flesh touches it, does it explode? I'm assuming yes
Okay, that's don't go in here. Don't go in this one. Don't go in that room
Well, all right
Open this I think I have to go in there. What else am I gonna do go up, baby?
You have to yes, I have to go go go go go go turn it off
Turn off the gas. Wait if I turn the gas off burn off the gas
That didn't do anything big if true Barack Obama tweets Wow. I can't believe
Germany's playing my favorite game team fortress to
It would suck if you ever played something like saw to
In seven years, I can't go in there yet. What do I do? What do I do?
Go in there keep to the left and go clockwise. Well, I need I need refresh
It would suck we played something like saw to in seven years when's autos big adventure 3 that's not gonna happen ever
maybe
Jump down. Oh my goodness
Right here, what do I do? What do I do? What do I do?
hurry
Help fucking hurry. I'm hurrying about Oh faster actually didn't I didn't even take up the um,
The syringe at the beginning. That's my mistake. I'm sorry
CVT
relax
So VR tomorrow, you're gonna see some fucking wild stuff. I got the Walking Dead video game
I've got a bunch of scary shit
Not end of stream. No, no, no, no, no. No, I'm just saying you're gonna beat this game tonight
I would say the
Likelihood of me completing this game is 0 so
This is the only time you're ever going to see me play this game ever. I ain't ever I'm this is it
I'm playing until I'm done and then I'm done and it's going it's going into the it's going into a box
Wait, hold on. What's the point of going in here?
Zerking off in VR. Well, not that
Where do I there's no way I'm near the end of the game as the last game was like seven hours
You don't think this one's gonna be at least
six or seven hours
Go go go go go
Give me a fucking break
Is this in the game? Why is this in the game?
Whoo, okay. Am I dead? I know the audio tape. I'm not even happy to the audio tapes guys
There's no way we're after the game. I was gonna say this and I didn't feel that. All right. What's a good McDonald's order?
What's a good McDonald's order? I'm talking your favorite. That's McDonald's order gets ordered and I'll promise I'll eat it off-stream
Medium fry. No, I mean large fry always you want about
McDonald's cheesesteak. Hey, you know what? I actually Wendy's has this new hamburger. What the hell was it? It's a
It's what's a new cheeseburger. I saw it. I was like, holy shit looks really good. What is it Wendy's thing?
They it's a pretzel thing. It's a pretzel bun pretzel pub burger. Yeah, anybody had that yet
That sounds really good. It's a pretzel bun with the pub cheese on it. It's pretty good
Might have to change my order here. I have to order some Wendy's Uber eats. The sauce is kind of bad
Oh, that's unfortunate. Is it get a happy meal? It's not weird that it would take five or six happy meals before I was happy
Right, okay
Your dad
It's not good. It's really not good
It's a bear. No, why am I even doing this? Why waste a lockpick on this pipe?
That's the kind of insult that the person uses because they know that it's gonna piss you off
It's not even about you. It's about just me. It's making you angry. What is about you? Hey, your dad sucks
Like you don't fucking know my dad
Shut up. Yeah, your dad sucks. Yeah, I saw your mom at the grocery store
Hey, I'm mrs. Elbertson. I'm here is mom
That's not what she talks like fuck you buddy
Get off me stop touching don't touch my face. That's touching my face
And then you both go to detention. This is personal experience
This happened the last week
In my schoolyard you want to talk about a fog jam moment. I'll give you one right there
Anything but codes have to be
Fucking four-digit painted on the wall codes
That was easy not gonna kill me with a shotgun trap this game you would have done it twice
How do you get back here that kind of an odd spot to be sitting?
I don't know. That's weird. Don't touch the chemicals on the ground new game mechanic. I'm actually glad to see a new mechanic
Don't touch the poison. I
Didn't shout gonna be like a gun
Done knew it. It's one of these guys
Okay. No, what the fuck did you get right next to me? Okay. Do you guys remember resident evil 4?
When did resident evil 4 come out?
This come out after resident evil 4 I did remember the fun part
Don't want audio tapes. I want puzzle piece completions. This game came out in 2002. Did no it didn't like 2010
This is on playstation 3 2002. You're the one that wants to play it. You why are you complaining?
I'm not playing. I'm holding a ouija board right now. I'm not playing this. I'm just hanging out with you guys
Alright, so now that's you gets a guaranteed hit every time
You can't go in this room
He's too cool for saw 2
It really isn't even that bad. They're worse games, you know, like look itchy
So where I just have to leave through here then what's the point open this first?
Can you play atari?
Yeah, you know I plan on getting a shitload of atari games
And just doing it with the joystick with the original joystick
Like be really really fun
I close him in here. Bye
open
Where'd he go? Where'd he go?
But why won't this open it's sealed does he have to break this don't even tell me he has to break this
Out of here to climb up on this shit. Don't I?
Lock him in there. Do you have to do you have to lock him in you're too slow
Let's do this again. Maybe what about the electrical wire?
Wait a minute. That's that's a pretty good idea
That wouldn't a bad idea
All right. I got him. I trapped him. What does that what does that do for me?
Do you just leave out of the room? Did he leave out the way? What? Watch out don't touch that
Um, okay, I have to get through there, but I can't step on that
Missed a button prompt. No, I didn't I got it
Climb the ladder was it? Oh that blends in really well
Like that shit red
What orange why is it the same color as the ace file? I got it
Go this way
Dummy. I can't wait. I can't wait for there to be a light just push the button puzzle
It's coming up right here. I can feel it
I know it is lennie the person. Thanks for the 10 community subs
Seema, thanks for the 10 community subs and scrumpleton. Thanks for the 10 subs. There's a lot of subs back to back to back
Thanks a lot guys. Shit
Dynamite sure. Okay, so move that without hitting anything
I'll give it a try
Hurry
Get it out of the way. All right out of the way
Good, it's uh, go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go
Oh shit, keep going
No, wait, what grab a grab grab grab grab grab grab grab grab grab grab grab grab grab grab got it
Back back back back back back back back back back back back back my eyes. Yeah move it
Wait, that's not the thing
Red team wins
No mission begins in 10 seconds rowing for views. Yeah
You get the most viewers
You go
And you go i'm way ahead of it this time now I understand what's happening
I got it really funny stuff, man
Thanks, dude. Appreciate it even peed all stream
Yeah, you know, you're right. I haven't i'll pee i'll pee when I like to stream ends. I feel good to keep going up here
What was that?
Anything in the way this there is right? No, okay all the way at the end. I don't have to pee. I'm fine
Good that it that's it. Right? It's gonna go in. Oh shit. The door opened that door opened over there. Oh
Hurry, hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. No fucking way. Do I have to do this? No fucking way
No way
Oh my god, you gotta be fucking kidding me
Oh go go go go go go go go open open open open open open quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick
Come on. Where's it? Where's it? Touch it touch what touch it touch this thing
Where do I touch?
Oh, I know it wasn't time. Okay, we're fine. That was a good audio clip
I didn't even hear it. Go empty your bladder calm down. I'm
I'm fine
Don't worry about me worry about you
All right. So we gotta be careful in here
What do you need? That was the guy we let out in the very beginning. It's this guy
We'll close one by one
So we have to
What do we have to do?
Who do you take it? What do you take advantage of the fuck? Oh, uh, whatever
Uh, it's all right
It's all right. I'll clean it up later
Oh one of these
That's the color change color
Do the thing that's in the back of the cereal box here. Maybe uh cuckoo the cocoa puffs bird
We'll give you a uh, if you set it 10 top boxes. What do we have to do hydration?
I did it. I just turned them all off
Let's turn them all on
I got them all on
Okay, do it again
Don't worry. I'm on the case
I'm coming
Only one more. Ooh, this one's super tricky
We're missing here. What are we missing this one down here?
All right, come up and then tell me give me a big hug
You'd spring me. What did we ever do to deserve this, right?
What we did what we do. You gotta make a living. What do you think?
You're some sort of hero going around rescuing everybody
Do me a favor and stay out of my way. I don't care about myself. Not anymore. You get out of the sail
I'm putting you in a fuck you. I'm not going to prison
Well, uh, you know what? I guess
We probably let's take a break
Let's do that. I'll take a break. I will be right back. Give me two seconds
Just get up. I'll be right back. I'll secure that later
That sucks. I just grabbed my keyboard like holding WASD. Like the fuck are you doing dude? Hey, i'm back. It's a good break
No, I didn't skip that
Snooze
What a snooze
Oh my god
What that's a snooze
Oh power the elevator again, even this motherfucker is sounds so sick of this
Key to the elevator every time I've popped into the stream the last few hours you've said snooze
I I think that's the first time i've said snooze in four and a half hours, man
I don't think that's accurate
It's so bizarre
because
The animations are in the game. There's a swing animation. There is a you hit me animation
So why make the whole thing qte?
last game
Had combat that wasn't qte
You're not adding anything
You're just taking away my ability to interact with the game
Remember this game jerma says this game sucks. I hate it boring. Oh my god
Cat so play something else jerma. Wait, what does that say? I want to read that
This game sucks, I hate it so boring. Oh my god, so play something else chat. The game is not that bad. Calm down
Yeah, that's you you're accurate. No, no, no, no, hold on. That's not accurate
I'm having fun playing the game. I'm not having fun playing the game
You know what I mean? I'm having fun like playing the game and hanging out. I'm not having fun playing the video game
I'm having fun playing the game here. Not the video game
There you go. It's a fun experience, but not a fun interaction. Thank you for
Literally saying the thing I wanted to say
You're in the cam on good thing. I wasn't naked
You look a greasy face
I don't
Greasy face put on a green screen to cover your nakedness
I don't know
Come back
No
You don't want me here. You don't want me here. Come back, please
Come back on please. I will at some point during before the stream ends. I will I promise
Hmm really look bad here. That's a bad feed
He was about to tell me something
Um, so what did that really do for us? I moved that
Like who fucking cares?
All right. What's the scariest vr game that's come out that I haven't played I play dread halls
I think that one's probably number one gross. All right, let me add five nights at freddy's
Easy listening what I can't wait fucking wendy's and mcdonald's, you know, sometimes just love it
You're loving it. I'm loving it
Yeah, that's true
Don't push it push push push push push push I pull this or you're normalizing being unhealthy
uh
I didn't say eat mcdonald's every day
You know, it didn't go
Eat mcdonald's every day
It's not the jingle
Just because I love it doesn't mean i'm gonna eat it every day
Have you got a funny ad campaign though?
He's trying to kill us. I'm not trying to kill anybody
Now what this is product placement not really
Oh, I can move this all the way product placement would be if the cam was on and there was a
There's like a mcdonald's wrapper
Just on the shelf behind me the whole time
All right. We'll have to go around again. Why can I not push this?
I can pull it but I can't push it. Why that's as far as it goes. That's dumb
cam on
fine
Happy am on
All right. Now we have to leave
All right, my head's gonna explode. Hold on
Why is this place on fire? What cam off? Why can I not move this shit? I can't move
Are you kidding me? This is stupid. Okay
Turn it on and now lose the shirt
Wrong website cursed link. I don't know what it is. What is it? Did that do it? Can now I push it?
It's really cursed. Well now I now I need to know
Uh, that's not even me. It's not me. Oh, no, it's not it's not me
Hey, you you fucked with my mouth or something. Yeah, you like fucked with my face. Yes
Let's go ahead and sneak by
Uh, have I hit more than three people with an axe in the whole five hours i've been playing I haven't right
There's melee weapons everywhere for no reason. It's not a single solitary reason to have melee weapons in the game
It just looks cool to hold I guess
All right, so that turned off the fire, but who really gives a shit?
What's this? It's a better link
Uh, I don't know if I'd call it better
I'd say it's a little more of the uh, wait someone's talking who's talking
Where is this guy if we missed something important? There's something cool happened
Ooh
Burnt berry, you know
What do I want to say? He was obsessed with fire 45 minutes sexy open it
Uh, yeah, yeah
At least at the very least it's not timed. We all know how much we love that shit
Okay, how am I gonna get this can't even get that one it's gonna be a split, okay
Okay, wrong. I hate this shit and don't play it. I yeah, I know you're right. I know you're right 300 people left
Well, they probably had they probably we talked about mcdonald's if we're getting mcdonald's thousand left
That's a lot that's a that's a major viewer crash why it's not going why they only come in
Two things coming out of these ones you can turn the battery. Oh my god. Why did I not even why?
That saves me so much pain
Get out of the way. Get out of my way. Get out of my way. Get out of the way. Oh my god, dude burger king
Oh burger king is here. No way
Burger king sucks. It is the worst of the three fast food restaurants
If you have a choice fuck burger king go to wendy's and mcdonald's first every time how's that for an ad?
Except they're all on the chicken nuggets and their fries are the best
And I like the way their burger tastes this single just cheeseburger. It's got like a flame broiled flavor to it, but fuck you
Very open this fries suck. No, that's that's not even real. You know, it's not real
The burger king fries are actually pretty good. All right, what did I just turn on? Sorry. We're talking about food
They're the worst. I think uh, you know, okay. The whopper is actually a decent item. It's all right
No, this one, you know burger king does have one really really good thing over everybody else
Kind of a weird thing to say but you'll know what i'm talking about if you know
Uh, they have the best lettuce
Uh, I didn't die. It didn't blow up my head
Burger king has the best lettuce on their burgers
It's crispy and crunchy and watery and like
It's the only fast food place of the big three that goes
The lettuce what about the foot lettuce?
That's that one one guy somewhere in the middle wherever they were
Yeah, just because one gross person did something gross at a restaurant what's the number 15?
A secret does burger king have a secret menu. That sounds like a secret menu item. Here comes some coughing
There
Oh
Oh, it's uh, it's it's tank girl
All right now you turn off your steam
Fuck you germana. I'm not gonna put that on stream because it's fake. I'm not gonna I'm no i'm not putting it on stream
You can have your little fantasy. I'm not putting that on stream
Oh shit, I burnt her
That didn't like it the game didn't like it, uh, what does that mean?
Okay
One omega l8 omega l, right?
Except this is a playstation 3. Oh, I have to ask a question
um
So when I turned the playstation 3 on and for a while after I turned on
I smelled plastic a hot burning plastic
Coming out of the vent in the back
What does that mean?
Did you get me out of here fuck me get yourself out
That's normal
Your ps3 is going through puberty
Oh, so it's not that one. So which one is it?
down
Smells like burger king. Okay. This might be this might sound gross, but it's kind of the reason why I don't hate burger king
Um, you guys ever use a grill?
And after you're done cooking the hamburgers on the grill
Two to three hours later
The smell that comes from that dirty grill
You know what i'm saying?
Like it it that that it's got like meat and grease all over it and cheese on the bottom and shit
And it has that that old
grilled smell
With food, you know, somebody knows what I mean. That's what burger king food smells like it does
But it smells kind of good
Clean the grill. No, i'm talking about the grill is clean. I'm talking after you use the grill
Like an hour later the smell that the grill has
Of course, I clean the grill, but you gotta wait till the coals cool off
You know what? You guys you don't clean it immediately. What do you guys forgot propane?
dorks
I'm kidding. Um guys, come on
Really?
Really? That's where you're gonna end your viewership is there I called you a dork because they use a propane grill. It's been
10 years that's the one you're going out on i'm just kidding
Charcoal tastes better though
It does I gotta get the fuck down there
Uh, I think charcoal tastes better. I'll give you the pros and cons
Charcoal is a huge pain in the ass
It's not worth it
at all
It takes so long to get ready
It takes so much time and effort. The cleanup is fucking horrible
But
I think it tastes better than propane
Am I wrong? I don't think so
I think i'm kind of wrong. Oh, some of these are fake
Uh, wait, what?
Uh, what? I have to do them one at a time
I think I have to do it one at a time. All right now red
Wait, are you gonna do it? Okay, cool. Let's do red. Turn it. Did she kill me?
What did she do? That wasn't correct. It was green. Choose wisely
Wait, wait, did I already do it? You only need to do blue. Oh
Oh, yep. That's another thing. Somebody said it another reason why I hate propane. Uh, it's a
It's a little tube
That has so much shit under pressure the thing can explode. I don't like it's got gas in there
You know how much I hate gas
I'd rather have rocks that get really hot
Than just gas stuffed in a little container. Where does it all go? How does it fit in there?
How does it not just blow the fuck up?
I know
Nope. Nope. Nope
It's safe. It doesn't matter. I'd rather have hot rocks
Taste the meat not the heat
And I like the way that like that wood charcoal
I think it adds a lot
Taste the meat
No
Put it on there until it's black
and then
Crunch it with your back teeth to try to chew through it. You guys ever cook food for anybody?
You guys have that have you got you guys have a man in the grill?
And you know
That you're just like oh my god, please for the love of all that is sacred. Let me cook this shit, right?
It's like six people here right now
It's five people here four people here
I I need this has to be good
so you cook
and
You uh, yeah, I know what i'm doing. You need help out there. No, i'm good. I'm good
Hey, what do you like medium? Oh, yeah medium. Well medium rare. I don't know. I don't know how to do any of those
But i'm gonna say yeah
To try as hard as I can to make you not throw up
I'll take medium rare. Oh, I don't know what the fuck that means
They're all gonna get cooked till uh, like black in the middle
And then when you finally take the shit off the grill
And you you go. Oh, yeah. Yeah, don't tell everybody the food's ready yet
You you take a bite out of a hamburger you make your own hamburger first
Everyone's still talking and hanging out and okay you bite in is it?
Is it purple in the middle?
and if it is
You put them all back on
Or the worst part is when somebody else comes over and they want their food
Shit
You bite yours right fucking red in the middle. They don't want that
Oh, man, he's the grill master. There he is. Jeremy the grill master. Let me take a bite of my hamburger
Pretty good. Hey, yeah
Hey, look at this guy with the grill
There he is
What you don't know is that person over the course of the next 30 minutes
Is going to take a bite
Chew it walk into your bathroom spit it into your toilet flush it come out
Spit it in maybe put it in their hand put it in their pocket and shit
And they're gonna spit it into the toilet like five times
That person is going to spit that food over the four or five bathroom trips
So they don't want you to think that the food was bad
It's true. Have you done this?
Yes
Not into the toilet though
Just go to the bathroom
You chew it up
Dude, I got okay. Somebody gave me a raw steak one time
And I was like, what the fuck am I gonna do about this?
So I took the steak
I opened up my underwear dropped it in my underwear and closed it
And then I grabbed both my hands on my belly and went
yummy
Can I please have the key in your pit? No, i'm fucking kidding
What's the objective?
Locate the warehouse
I don't what what was the point of what I was just doing?
Can't use this to save clips. Oh, we need to talk about that for a second. Don't we?
So apparently there's like a bunch. There's like a twitch dmca apocalypse upon us
Right. I just want to make sure everyone knows this
I i'm not deleting anything
I don't save vods on twitch anyways and clips if you want me to delete every single clip i've ever had on this channel
that's
Hundreds of thousands of memories
That will never be recovered
I'm not i'm not taking them down
If it comes down to it and there's like a tool I can use or if there's something I can do about it
But what you I we cannot be expected to just go delete
Five plus years worth of shit. I mean if I have a copyright now, all right, then give her delete it
I'm not gonna I that's that's too that's too stressful for me. I'm not gonna do that
Yeah, if I delete all clips I might catch a few copyright ones, but then the slap disappears forever
I'm not okay with that. Why would I be okay with that?
No idea where the fuck i'm going. I I promise I never listen to music ever
I don't I don't care about music. I don't think about music. I I never listen to music ever ever. I don't care
I don't listen to it
I promise I only listen to music
Uh in a dark room with a bright light on my face
And I make sure that no one's around I open up all my windows and look what I do any neighbors around
And I put it on at the lowest volume and I sink down
I put my fucking ear next to the thing and I hold it there. I hope nobody else fucking hears this
Don't hope nobody else hears this shit. I'm gonna be in big trouble
I'm gonna fuck this steak. Don't forget it. I told you I like what do you mean? I that doesn't make sense
Where the fuck do I go?
I'm about to rage quit the game. Oh, no, I can't I can't be here
Did you come on the tv and say hello again, uh peter is this it you're too far in
Yeah, no, that's accurate
I really am
Uh, I just got 50 dollars
5,000 bits
from espada escalada thanks to the 5,000 bits
50 bucks
Keeping clips is just another reason. You're the best streamer on the internet. Also. Here's 50 dollars for your lawsuit
I
look I
YouTube did this similar thing before
And it scared the shit out of everybody
I'm gonna wait for more info. I'm gonna wait until it's really like yeah, if you have
You're getting deleted. I want a little bit more info. I'm not removing
It's like six years of everything i've ever done
I'm not gonna do it
I want more info
Speaking of more info
What the fuck am I supposed to do right now?
You should switch to blender. I think the game's telling you to quit
Okay
I this is like the only way I can really go
But I can't go this way the elevator. Yeah, I can't press. I need a key for the elevator
I can't press the button burn cam on you lost another hundred viewers. Stop saying that
Don't you know that when you say that it makes me feel like it's self-conscious that people may have left the stream
Don't say that to me. Don't do that to me
The fuck do I go I can't do the elevator
Like don't don't worry
I know why they left because I've walked in a circle four times because this game
I know I get it. It's all right. Don't you don't have to a hundred people. No, I'm beside why didn't 5 000 of you leave?
Let's don't put don't go stay
Watch me continue to do the same thing over and over again expecting differently else. What is the definition?
Sanity it's down
Help me
Why am I really trapped here?
Why?
No, help me. Why?
Cry cry cry
Go to the storage room the fucking storage room
40 mcnuggets. Holy shit. That's a good idea
storage warehouse
Let's see. I think it's broken. The game is broken
The game's broken
It's a broken game
And I think i'm running around like an idiot
The door it's not opening
Okay, how do I die? Wait, hold on there's a hidden key behind the ladder and then you called me an idiot
But wouldn't a hidden key mean it's I don't see it
Yeah, the game is hard crashed. It's actually hard crashed
Oh
Come on
You give me like a reason to end the stream game
For tomorrow for vr scary night y'all you're gonna come to vr night tomorrow. It's gonna be scary
I think it's gonna be scary
Whatever plans you have tomorrow whatever streamer you plan on watching it better be me
You understand i'm gonna do 100 nugget challenge after two
No, i'm not. All right. Well, this is all right. This is what this is a good place to end it
It's been five hours. I only streamed for four six hours anyways now because of my boomer back
It's a good place to take a break and get some food. This game was terrible, but I had to give it a chance
How could it be worse than the first one? I have no idea another 50 dollars from wade. Thanks wade for the 50 bucks
There's no messages. That's it
Well, I had look I had fun on the stream didn't have fun in the game that sometimes that's okay
That's a lot of fun. I can still have fun. So tomorrow
We are going to play vr walking dead vr
The exorcist vr I might be making that up. Um, a couple of the scary games. Yeah. Yeah, the exorcist legion
That's the one gonna be terrifying and I think I might start tomorrow
I want to be at night
Something about playing a scary game and you take off the headset and there's just a bright sun in your room now
I want to be dark and nighttime and we'll see but it doesn't matter. We'll start at two specific
I know that's still late for a lot of people. Yeah, I know we'll do two
Well, that was saw to the game that uh half of you demanded I play for months
Hope it was worth it and i'll see you tomorrow do a cam before you leave. Sure. How you doing good?
We're good. See you tomorrow. See you tomorrow. You like it when my eyes are wider like this like this
What makes you connect with me more as a streamer like this or like this when you squint? Okay, cool
Let's get the credits rolling. Thanks for the subs everybody. There was a lot of community subs tonight. I'm gonna go
Uh uber eats some I can't fucking believe I couldn't read an analog clock like three hours ago
It's unbelievable to me like holy shit. I had cvd man cvd drops. I can't fucking believe it
I cannot believe it. That's worse than the omega symbol. It's the worst thing i've ever done on stream
Probably I couldn't read the fucking analog clock. I was trying so hard too. That's the worst part
I was it was so embarrassing and i'm sitting there desperately being like what is the five one?
Like you have to be making that up you have to be pretending no one can be convinced that that was not real
There's no way
It's impossible. Anyways, let's get the credits on. Thanks again everybody. Here are all the subs tonight
Thank you for your insane support that I continue to get for some reason
Thanks a lot somebody said germa if your ps3 is still making that burning smell check under your disc tray
Mine usually does that does that if it's oil is low ps3 has oil. No, it doesn't
Like a car
What the fuck i'm just imagining windshield wipers on this thing and you press a button
Just wipe the top. All right where i'm gonna send i'm gonna send you guys to kitboga tonight. Oh say hello
I actually saw the the he has this thing where it's like an ai that automatically talks to the scammers
It's like a text-to-speech like ai bot or something. That's insane. It's absolutely insane
It's hysterical. I think he's coding. I don't think he's calling uh scammers tonight. I think he's just chilling coding
That sounds pretty chill. I think I might hang out there with my mcdonald's uber eats go say hello
I'll see you guys tomorrow for vr scary shit. Goodbye. Good night. Have a wonderful rest of your night. Take care guys. See you soon. Goodbye