Alright, let's take a look here. I can swing left. I can swing right. I can swing down.
Can I swing up? Not really, but this is extremely awkward.
What is my guy doing right now? Who is winning this fight? Did he just knock it out of my
hand? Can I get a stick? Oh, a stick! Give me the stick. Give me the stick. Give me the
stick. Have I been up and spotted? These guys aren't hostile. Oh, okay, cool. These guys
are not hostile. Excellent. Now they are. Should I run from this? I feel like I need
to run and not like... Alright, let's do it. I'm almost dead. I'm dead again. Holy shit.
Just be on your way, game. I can't die here. If I die here, I'm going to be extremely upset
considering... Do I attack this guy? I kind of have to. He's looking at me weird. I gotta
Here he comes. Come on. Come on. I missed. I missed and I'm going to die for it. Damn
it! I don't know what I did. I did something wrong. I feel like I'm a little kid in a Halloween
costume his mother made for him. Oh, sure, honey. You're a Power Ranger. Yeah, you are.
I promise. You're not a box. Did the other kids make fun of you? Keep moving. Keep going.
This might be a bad time, but can you give me some directions out of here? I'm kind of
lost and I can't see because there's a box on my head, but if you can lead me out... Ow, my hand.
I don't even think he can hurt me. He can't hit me. You have never seen my impenetrable box fought
like this before. I'm going to sit here until this guy hurts me. Oh, he's getting through.
I wonder, can I swing back? See if I can fight back. I don't think so. I can't fight back.
Oh, wait, he's getting around. Hey, cut it out.
Go run. Run. Stop running into walls, please. And just escape. Escape this horrible castle.
Get away from me, you cretin. No. I am going to club this guy. Just wait till this guy makes
his way around this corner. I'm going to smash this guy's skull and he's going to wish he was
never born. So let's just pretend like we don't want to hurt this guy and he's going to keep
walking. No, he's not. Here we go. You want to see how I do things? Oh, my God. I can't even do it.
I'm already dead. I wanted to sledgehammer the guy and the guy was holding it like a
pool cue for a second and he didn't even reach back. I'm trying to do like the swing with the
physics. I forgot to put clothes on before I came into the arena. I've got like a big diaper on.
Oh, come on. Get away from the wall. Get away from the wall. All right. Go back right. Nice.
Nice. Okay. I'm just turning into the Star Wars kid at this point. That old like internet video.
I won. What the hell? I haven't beaten this guy. I have not beaten this guy. This guy's got the
shield. Shit. My face got stuck in his shield. That's horse shit. Whoa. Oh, come on. What the
fuck was that? Protect yourself. Damn it. Oh, this game is so hard.