Hi. Hello again, everybody. And TV here. Welcome back. We're gonna play Dusk. Picking up exactly
where we left off yesterday. This game is really good. Can we just please see Otto before you're
naked? Uh, you can't really see. Hold on. He blends in with the, he blends in with a blanket.
Let me see if I can brighten this up so you can zoom in on him and brighten it up.
I'm not sure it's possible, guys. Actually, maybe it is. Okay, hold on. Hey, Otto. Hello, Otto. Hello.
What are you doing? Yes, it's me. Otto. He's like, what are you doing? Who's my good dog?
There you go. Otto spotted. This is just what he does, guys. He just likes to hang out on a big
pillow and go to sleep. And he also likes going outside too. He's like a lizard. He just like,
he basks in the sun. That's what he does. He finds a spot in the house that has a strip of sunlight
coming through. And then he just gets in it and just lies on his back and just absorbs every ray.
He's the best. He works real hard. Yeah. Are you sure he's not a cat? Pretty sure. Let Otto play.
Hey, guys, Otto doesn't know what a video game is. I hate to break it to you.
But we're gonna leave just right where we left off. Dusk. Now, here's the thing about games.
I'm sure a lot of you guys know. There's this period of playing a game that's like this,
where you're up and up and up and up and up and it'd been stress, like good stress. Muscle memory.
You're into it. You're ready to fucking blow away everybody. And then you go to bed and you wake up
the next day and you play, you're like a wet noodle. So I'm gonna have to get back into it.
Here we go. Oh, you can't even see it. Oh, thank God. I thought my fucking whole stream's gonna
turn off. So I gotta, I gotta like move my arms around. I gotta get ready. I'm probably gonna die
like 10 times in the first five minutes. Maybe I'm not gonna die at all. What are you talking about?
But I love this game. This game's been more fun than anything that I've played in a long time.
Stamp it. I enjoy this. All right, let's go. Oh, where were we? Save, load here. I just started
level two. Oh, Otto wants to leave. He's like, now I want to leave. All right, let me let him out.
Hold on. I do. I thought he was gonna just lie down, but he's like, get me out of here. I don't
want to be in his room. So let me go let him out. Hold on. I'll be right back. Okay. He had his fun
lying down. Did he show Otto already? I did. All right, here we go. Load it. Press any key. All
right, let's get back into this here. Timing on that is good. Four, five, six, seven. One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven. Timing. All right, let's go. Oh, by the way, I was told I've been
doing this wrong the whole time. I was like flicking around and doing the the jump that way.
That's not how it works in this game. You just have to like jump diagonally like that.
I was going like doing the source engine jump and that's not what you're supposed to do.
And I was doing it all stream. Well, this is new. All right, let's take super shotgun out. Wait,
no, rifle. Yep, yep, yep, yep. Right in the head. See you later. Where are you?
All right. All right, blue chip is up there. Blue door in front of us. This is that little people
here. Yep. Yep. You're here for that fucking commentary. You're here for the yep commentary.
What's he at up top? Oh, yep. All right. I'm making I'm going to make some pretty good progress
today. I'll tell you. I thought I wasn't ready for this game. I used it. I didn't know they
could use it. They can. Where are they coming from? Where's where they come from? All right. I need
health. I don't slow down. Give me the blue chip. Save the game. Oh, fuck. No. Okay. How are we
doing? Good. I'm going to get over there. Good. Good. Good. Collect all the collectibles.
Save it. Oh, pod. What do I want to do here? Anything over this way? No. Can I jump from
here to there? Let's find out. No. Damn it. Damn it. Say pod one more time. I fucking dare you.
Jesus. I want to collect ammo because I want to make sure I have enough
as we continue here. I feel so good to play. It feels so good to play. Oh,
ain't fucking wrong with you. So I have the blue but all right this yellow over there.
I hear another yeller. Where's yeller? Secret door. Okay. I have to open this. All right.
There's a yeller in there. I don't know why I'm calling mama yeller. All right. Let's go open
the blue door. All right. Save it. I'm ready. What should I use? Let's go with mortars. Okay.
These are all going to open it. It's going to be a bunch of aliens because look at this.
There's a power up on top. Don't get fancy with it. So what am I supposed to do? Okay. Here we go.
Ready? That's probably the yellow key card I assume. How do I get up here? Can I jump up here?
Need to wall climb. Well here we go. Screaming doctor. Oh Jesus. Oh there's a bunch of screaming
doctors. I'm dead. Holy fuck. I don't even know where I am. All right. Settle down. Oh man. He's
made out of noodles. I am. I'm not. Okay. If I get touched once I'm dead. This guy's freaking me out.
Look at his pattern. His pattern's all fucked up. His pattern's all fucked up. And there's a guy
up there. All right. Don't do this. Just run in and shoot him. Oh my god.
All right. It's going to happen once. It's going to happen once. Get my mortars out. I'm ready.
I forgot about these guys. I almost had it too and that's unfortunate. I'm going to mortars.
It definitely went up. Oh a crossbow. Probably mortars. It's just been once. I'm going to get
him to run outside and go. Got it. All right. Now I can settle down a little and take out the
the rifle. Let's get the big guys upstairs. That's it, right? Damn it. All right. Not
pretty good. Not bad. Could have been better. Well, now I know you're up there. I could have
jumped through the window and grabbed that. No, that's super. That's super. I don't even know
what that is. That's like ultra move, right? Well, I have ultra move. Let's just get some health and
okay. Should I? I'm going to get ultra move and then I got to get the, uh, maybe that key.
Let me go down here. I'm going to save the super duper move.
Bastard. There's another guy down here. There's like a bunch of people down here. Isn't there?
Yeah. Oh my fucking God. I didn't know he was right there. All right. Come on.
Holy shit. She can go through there too. I don't know. She could aim that way. Stop cussing.
All right. Fine. I won't say any, I won't say any bad words for the next five minutes
or I'll eat. If I say, if I say a swear word in the next five minutes, I'll eat a ghost pepper.
What? That's good. What was that? Oh, it's, it's a when to go. Uh huh. All right. Give me this thing.
Where am I? Where am I? Where am I? Where, where is he? Where is he? Where am I?
Is there another one? I hear something. Okay. I can open that gate now. No, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. I'm going to go save the game. Let me grab the, yeah. Turn this on. What's,
what's the matter? Ghost pepper swear challenge. Yeah. I'm good. Ghost pepper swear challenge.
All right. Let me keep going. Uh, what door opened? A door opened. It was this one.
All right. Here we go. I'm going to get the, give me the super power and I'm going to jump
through here. You ready? Let's see if I can do it in one swoop. Nope. I'm terrible. I almost set
a swear word. I would have to eat it. I would have had to eat a ghost pepper. Good thing I didn't.
Oh, I don't even like that one. That one's not that good. Geez.
Don't grab it yet. Even thinking about swearing. No, it doesn't. You guys even,
have you ever even seen somebody eat a ghost pepper? No, you haven't. What you've seen is
you've seen YouTubers take a tomato that's under ripe and they eat it and pretend it's hot and they
go, Oh, they take sun dried tomatoes and then they pretend that they're hot. Here we go. Here we go.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. I'm doing it just so you have like a bunch of
clips of me saying it, even though you already, okay, hold on. Oh, here we go. Goodness.
Okay. Here we go. Did I just throw it over his head?
Gotta go to the yellow door. Good work. Oops. Hey, thanks. What, were you talking to me or were you
talking to chat? I hope you're talking to me. Get these onions. I hear somebody shooting. Who is it?
Wow. It's you out there, isn't it? I haven't gotten any secrets yet, which concerns me.
Okay. Here we go. Super hot. Super hot. Here we go.
How's he doing? Oh, there is one of those. I don't like the slow mode. It freaks me out.
All right. We're good. So now we're not good. Damn it. All right. It's okay. Okay. Here. I'm
not going to say it because I was going to say that the thing that I usually say, but I'm not
saying right now. All right. Here we go. Wait, save it. Give me these onions. I'm just so
concerned that it could be something around the corner. I'm ready. Yeah. I got a stuff saying,
here we go. Oh, it's going to be assault rifle and it's going to be fast. Let's do it.
Oh man. Wait, that's okay. I was panicking for no reason. I thought these were projectiles
coming to kill me. All right. I thought these were just bullets flying everywhere. That's why
I was freaking out. I don't want to touch that yet. I want to collect. There's a button to press
too. And this teleporter takes me somewhere. Hmm. A cage lowers. Oh, the other cage. Right.
All right. It's harder to not say here we go than it is to say the F word.
That was green. I thought it was a bad guy.
We clear. Don't get run over. Thank you. No secrets though. Damn it. How did I not get any
secrets? That's bad because there's a good, a lot of ammo and shit. It's been five minutes.
I'm going to use pistols because I just need it. I need to start using them. Yellow door right here.
This is horrible. I already don't like this level for obvious reasons. I need hunting
rifles. My favorite weapon. It's you down there, isn't it? Yep, it is. Make sure nothing else here.
Secret. I don't want to get zero out of five secrets. Is this Turok? This game is better
than Turok. Check over this way. Yep. This is what I'm saying. I gotta slow down. Okay.
Okay. Let's go. Save it. Is that a hunting rifle? Thank God. Psycho scientist. Jesus.
I hate those guys. They run so fast. All right. Red door.
Hunting rifle. My favorite weapon because I'm pinpoint accurate with it. Got two in one. I'm
going to get up here. Secret. There's two. See, I already am doing better than I was last time.
Put the hunting rifle away. Let's do pistols. I've been neglecting them so hard.
A lot of those guys around corners. What was that? I just heard a laugh. Oh, I thought that was a
wheezing laugh. What do I have ammo in? Only the pistols, seriously. What was that? I heard it.
Yep. I knew it. I knew it. I knew it. Point blank. Dead. Downstairs. Let's go.
Where is he? Didn't even take a hit. All right. I got yellow key. Nothing else, right?
Nothing else I need. No, let's go. The darkness spreads. The darkness is spreading. Blue door.
Saw a rifle. I'll use it. I'll use it. That sounds like a good idea right now.
What is that noise? I don't want to turn the corner. I don't want to turn the corner.
I need key. I almost just shot that. This is one of those adrenaline pumping games. I love it.
You open a door sometimes and it's just like you could just feel all your blood turn to a stone.
And nothing else in here. Go down, I guess. There was another way to go.
Down? Something down there. Okay, there's diamond down there. Just wait. I'm gonna go. I'm going
down. I thought that I could have. No. Going in. There comes somebody running. Oh, shit. I just
got triple tapped. Got him. Whoa. Wait, is there another sentry? There's another sentry somewhere.
If I move, I'm dead. Where is it? Where is it? Oh my goodness. Okay. All right. Shotgun time.
Let's replace that. I'm gonna use double shotgun. Yeah. I think that's time for it.
Why are they pushing each other? Who? It is blue. Let's get that blue key. What was it over here?
Right there. Can I get up to this one? Oh. Nice try. Almost. Almost killed me. It was close.
There's a lot of stuff here though. I don't want to just run away. Wait a minute. Let me check. No,
let's just go. Somebody else will get the secrets. One of you guys will get the secrets.
Run. I can hear him running. He's got like, hooves. That's the way. Wait, what's over here?
Nothing. That's a lot of mortars. That's a lot. Uh, maybe a rib. I got, I got a lot of,
I don't want to use these yet though. This is a boss killer. Let's use mortars. Did I
tele-frag somebody? What happened? Where is he? I can hear him. I can hear his hooves.
I can hear his hooves. Where is he? I hear multiple hooves. Oh, where is he?
Ow. My whole body. Okay. I'm fine. Oh, he's still alive. Oh, okay. Can I peek out now?
Good. That's why they gave all those to me. How kind of them. Go up. Oh, why is the gas in here
now? All right. Blue door, blue door. And then I got to let Otto back in the room.
He's like, I want to get out of here. And then he's like, let me back in. The blue door is down
here, I think. All right. Was it? No, it wasn't. Where was it? All right. Hold on. Let me go get
him. Hold on a second. Okay. Now he's happy. I'm watching like 15 minutes. He's like, hey,
this room sucks. I want to go somewhere else. We'll see. You good? He's good. He's just a cat.
All right. Blue door. Secret. Oh, this is good for me. That's very good for me. There he goes.
Down. Just sitting down. Good boy. All right. Let's uh, that's a red door. What was the blue one?
I remember I always look at them and I go, there's blue door. And then I forget where they were.
Where is it? Use your map. There ain't no map in this game. Wait, is it this way? Was it over here?
Did I go back too far? I think I went back too far. Press M. There's no map in this game, guys.
It was next to the red text. What is that? I always just say, there it is. There's the blue door.
And then I, it's gone immediately. I forget where it is entirely because the game made me come back
up here. So it has to be up here. And that has to be back up this way, right? It has to be.
It was just around this little corner. Here we go. Red door is back down there. Remember that.
Clip it for me. Oh, you dare? Holy shit. I just got destroyed. I'm going to get up on these roofs.
I think I'm going to try to at least. Can I? I have to press. I have to touch this. Oh no. 5G.
This is the source of the 5G. We're going to follow this all the way down. It's going to be,
it's going to be an alien down here. Sparks take from men, bad, which has never been taken.
I always knew that 5G was fucking just Satan. The whole thing, the whole wireless technology
makes no sense. Like you could send that shit through wirelessly with no wires.
The whole thing's fucked up. I just quick saved it right here. That was probably a huge mistake.
All right. I need to use the daredevil technique. Can't open this door.
All these doors don't open. There's a switch back here. What's it for though? What was that?
Oh, shadow. Oh, that's how you light up a place. That's a gasoline tank. Wait, the red
was in a secret. The key card for the red door back there is a secret. That's sort of
hard. Oh, we got the lights back on. This is fine. I heard it. Oh my God. I just fell down.
Where am I going? The root. What does it say? What does it say? There's too much smoke. The ruins
held knowledge. We sold our souls for it. All cars built of concrete. Fed with blood.
I missed the flashlight. What? Where? Where's the flashlight? Are you serious? I'm going to run.
I can't see anything. Navigate with your bullet holes. There it is.
Ha ha ha. Okay, just give me a sec. This is the way back. I don't even use the pistols anyways.
Wait, what's down there? Oh, that's where I need to go. Navigate with bullet holes. There we go.
The ruins held knowledge. We sold our souls for it. Couldn't read that one. All cars built of
concrete. Fed with blood and bone. This door opens elsewhere. Nice secret. I'll take it.
Get everything first. Something bad is going to happen when I press this button
and then grind it up. I think I just power the facility with meat. But wait,
I don't want to end the level yet. No, I thought it didn't say end level. It just said open door.
Usually it says end level. It said exit, but it doesn't say end level. It says end level.
I've been trolled a couple times with exits before. No, I'm going back. I'm going back.
It's this one, right? Did I get that shit? Yeah. All right. I'm not going this way. I'm going back.
Here we are. Red door. Now, fellas, ladies and fellas, where was that red door? I don't remember.
Over here, right? Was it this way? Red door. Here we go. That's what I'm talking about. That's
quite, that's a secret. Now I have to get back to where I was. So the real question is,
um, huh? How do you want me to do that? Just have to run there. But there's power here now.
Am I going to lose the health that I just got? Nope. Good. Now I can leave. Where the hell was
it again? I can open this. I can open these those too. Remember these wouldn't open before?
Wait a minute. There's like another door or two that were closed. This was, okay, this one was
closed. This one was closed too, right? Ah, don't read the tweet. Already did. Now I can leave.
I just 100% level. I did. That's the first time I've done that. But you cheated. It's all right.
You can go back and re-cheat. Here it comes. No turning back now. All right, there's health back
here. These two of them. Bad. That was, that's why there's all the health back here. I see. Mortars.
Exterminated. Crossbow. Why is this here? I'm not going there yet. Let's go this way.
Kill him. Whoa! You were standing there. Big whoa. Big whoa. Anything down here? Red door. Okay.
I want to take a mental picture of this place. Stairwell. Goes down with the, great with the
lava. Around the corner. Great with lava. Downstairs. Red door. I got it. Memorized. Downstairs.
Red door. Lava. Great. Got it. Okay. Yellow door. Yellow door is in the same room as red door.
They're in the same room upstairs instead of down. Up the stairs. They're in the same area. Got it.
Okay. Green pyramid. Red door. No, don't say that. You're gonna mess it up. I know what it is. It's
red lava. Great. Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. That spikes. If I slide under there, I'm dead.
That's a mama. Whoa! Nice aim. Let's check the rest of this place out. What we got?
I have a lot of the riveter ammo. I should probably use it.
So now it's boss only. Bosses only. Red key. I know what that room is. That's a new enemy.
No it's not. I've seen that enemy a million times. Gotta make these count. I can't just miss.
I want to get up there. Blue key up there. Whatever. Just let me out. Red. This is a room
that's gonna be full with people. They're all down. They're all down. They're all down.
Give me... No! Stop it! I want this. Can that go through the grate? Yep. All right. Anything
else up here? Secrets. Money. Blue door. That's... This is where the blue door is. I would forget this.
Green sewer room. This blue door. He only cares about money.
Killing spree. Pretty good progress. What's the point of being down here though? Can I open this?
Oh my... No! No! No! Fuck! Speaking gibberish. That's all... Just gibberish. Whatever. Boss only.
Am I bumping into the wall? Oh there was a wall here. They've turned us mad. Teleporter.
Let's move. Kill him. I'm up now. Here it comes. Yellow.
Yellow key. I know what that door is.
I only have 30 health. That's not good. This is very bad actually.
Missed a secret wall? What? Where? That's not it? What is it? I got it. Put the motors away. Double
shotgun. Did you actually... Did one of these little idiots just got me? I'm gonna turn this
corner and I'm gonna hear that. No. I'm almost dead though. All right. That was... I need health.
I need health. I need health. I need health. Damn. I thought there was like... I thought there was gonna
be something over here. Give me a saw rifle for this part.
I can slide under these. Can I not slide under these? I guess not. Nothing under them anyways.
Damn. Took a while. All right. I'm going... That's a terrible place to fight this. I gotta jump around.
All right. Double battle shotgun. I'm gonna jump over him. Kill him. So let's drag him back here.
That's a tight place to fight this thing. Maybe if I run by him. I'll try running by him.
No. Just gotta be right in his face the whole time. All right. There's the key. Is that the key?
No. Well, shit. Can I break this? 15 health. Hmm. Well. Am I missing something here?
There was no switch I could have licked around. Is this a collapsible door? Wait. What about
switches over here? There we are. All right. Okay. I got it. I got it. I got it. We're good.
Any repeaters? What do you mean repeaters? Any repeaters? What? I don't like that sound.
This is why I saved it. This is why I saved it. I swear to God, Jeremy. That's why I saved this.
We're gonna. Okay. I'm gonna keep it out because I keep hearing this shit and I'm gonna press the
button and I'm gonna get attacked again. What the fuck is this? Why did I use the. I saved it there
too. Why did I use it on the alligator? Oh no. I used it all on the alligator. That wasn't even
the real boss fight. That was the pretend boss fight for the real boss fight, which is this.
Did you just bounce that back? All right. That actually wasn't that bad.
Uh, is there. Do I have to do that? It's something else happening now. Is that the boss fight before
the boss fight before the real boss fight? I don't know, but make sure I have everything.
Okay. I guess we're just going. What about the blue door? What about the blue key? Oh,
it was the real boss fight with the rats. Yeah, it kind of was. What about this? What about
that? How do I do that? Oh no. I didn't get it. It's okay. It's all right. One of the walls was
faked. Ah, shit. Pretty bad secret finding on that run, but it's all right. This one's called the
gauntlet. Hooray. I feel like this is going to be fun. This is going to be a very fun part of the
game. I want to get these onions. Bring it on. I can't jump up there. I absolutely can. What is
all this? Wait, where did I just go? I don't even know where I just went. I went through like a
teleporter. I thought, I thought it was going to be this. I thought, okay, I don't know what in my
stupid ass brain. I thought that teleporter was going to go to here. I thought it was going to be
a shitty engineer teleporter that they just build out of, out of just muscle memory. You know, you,
this is, you exit the spawn door. Here's the teleporter and then you go and there's the exit
just because they put it down because they were just OCD putting stuff down.
I don't know why I thought that that was just try. Okay. I'm ready. I still want to get this
stuff though. Is there like a fake wall? Cause I can't reach this. Do a rocket jump. That's
going to hurt me too much. No, I'm fine. I got 150 health. Let's go. Let's fight them.
So here we go. Let's do mortar first. Fuck. I'm in trouble. Slide jump. Does that work?
Rocket jump. Yeah, I'm going to hurt myself to rocket jump up here to get the same amount of
health that I'm probably going to lose by rocket jumping. Do a crossbow jump. You can,
you can crossbow jump. What? I hold on. Am I about to kill the boss with this magic soap?
Wait, where'd the soap go? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is the soap in there? What'd I do with this?
That's not, I feel like that's kind of, uh, let me, um, I don't, that's not fair though.
That's not fair. Like I just beat that, that I beat him. I magic soaked him. I mean, look,
you told me how to jump up there, but I saw the door. I mean, it's, it's intentional.
All right. Well, that's fun. Let's go three more to go. I can just walk around and just look at
this. Oh, I'm in danger. There's too many things here. It's the last one. Am I a cheater? No,
I didn't put input any commands. How do I open this? Maybe I should just leave. There's only
two here. Just take the other teleporter. Where's the last switch? I don't understand. Go to the
other one. I already did. Wait a minute. Hold on. I was, I must've been turned around like three
times then. Cause I, I've tried to go to the other teleporter. Wait, is this the, is it the,
no magic. Where's my magic soap? I hear rock music. Where's my magic soap? I put it in here,
didn't I? Uh-oh. Uh-oh. One more to go. Don't get that yet. Sequence complete. Where is he?
Where's the boss? Is he, is he dead? Oh, he's just dead. What's the, I got an achievement called low
tech. It's cause I didn't fire a gun. It's cause I soaked him. I just beat it. I beat that episode.
That was the final boss of the episode and I instantly killed him. As you step into the
unholy portal powered by ungodly means there's no doubt what you must do. Hubris and fanaticism have
woken something powerful, horrible beyond anything you can imagine. You must uncover the truth. Who
knows what nightmare awaits you in the nameless city. Cool. Episode three. Let's do it. In the
nameless city. Out next week? No, out right now. This difficulty is not intended for a first
playthrough. Although you are German 985 and this is your first playthrough, but you have enough
skill to be able to press this button. That's what it said. Mint? Low doubt. What is going on?
Why can I, why am I, I can cheat? Why can I cheat? Is this cheating? What's going on?
So I, is this, is this supposed to be like, you go like the God level? No campaign to, oh.
Oops. New episode. All right. I see. Okay.
Episode three. The nameless city. The iron cathedral. Welcome to hell. Sickles.
You don't get to keep anything. Let's move. Get my flashlight though. And I get the sword. Is
this going to, wait, is this a sword only level or something? The sword is a silent takedown at
a hundred or more health. Hold attack to charge strike. What? What? Charge strike? Silent takedown.
Why does that matter? Gotta hide a gas can back here on me. I'll be sure to use it the second
the door opens. And two onions. Let's go. Do I have to sneak? All of a sudden it's a stealth game.
Wait, wait, wait. What do you mean stupid? What's going on? What? Gas can on the wall.
What wall? What? What are you talking about? At the spawn. I love how I'm stupid for this.
It's stupid. How idiotic of him to not go back to the wall at spawn. It's kind of fun
playing a game. We get out of here. You didn't even do that. What the fuck was that thing? It's
a night. It's a, it's a, it's a night. Oh my God. Do I have to fight it with the sword?
Do you, is there a parry? It's a parry. That's a parry. I can't charge it. I have to be at a hundred
health. Wait, this is the, hold on. I'm not going this far yet. There was a weapon over here that
I could get. No, not yet. How do I get over there? I probably have to go down at some point. All
right. That is the right one. Is the only way to go. Kill about dipshit stupid dipshit idiot.
Fucking idiot. Stupid. What a dipshit idiot. Fucking idiot. At 50 or more morale, hold aim
with the sword to block attacks. Yeah. And you got a soap right here. You know, I'm pretty good at
finding the soap. I will say I'm really good at finding the secret soaps and using them is another
thing. Where'd it go? I'm good at finding the soap. I'm not going to be using the soap.
Wow. All right. I'm not going to be using soap. All right. Now let's go.
I don't have a hundred health though. Stupid. Where's the soap? That's why your name is Jerma.
I mean, that's pretty funny. It is. Wait for the guy with the night. I need the night.
This fun. This is fun. Wow. I love it. And I soaked. No, don't. Why am I even doing that?
Hey, what? Where did you come from? 112 health. Where's the soap? I'm just gonna bring it with me
everywhere. It's always good to get rid of one of the hard enemies with it. Although is this
unlimited use? Can I use this as many times as I want? I'm trying to attack. Not going to work
like that, man. Sorry. He got annoyed at this. Check. I still don't understand what the smelly
crystal does. What does the smelly crystal do? That didn't block it. All right. I got the blue
key, but there's a lot of ways to, there's a bunch of random vents in this level. I guess over this
way, but there was another way to go. I think I could down. There's a crystal over there,
but wait a minute. I can open this door. I think that's progression. Hold on. My power went out.
What happened? Mine did too. What? I just turned the stream back on. What? Do you live in Vegas?
We're all mad here. No, this is okay. So I do have a blue key though. Wasn't there a blue door all the
way back? I already have to pee. What a disaster. Because that could go down. Oh, I gotta pee. This
is messing with my brain to be able to play the video game correctly. Yeah, I gotta go.
I'll be right back. It's messing with my ability to play the video game. This is what happens when
you just drink large coffees every morning. Be right back. Don't go anywhere. Or if you have to
go, fine. But if not, then stay. All right, we're good. I just dropped my lip balm on the ground.
It's capped and everything, but it just hit the ground. I have to get another one.
There's germs on the ground. How big is the large coffee? How many ounces? You don't even want to
know. If I told you guys the amount of ounces that I had in my coffee, you'd think I was a
fucking sicko. I only do this like once every few weeks. But every time I do it, I always feel
bad about it. That's a secret door if I've ever seen one. Nice. Good thing I went back here.
Now I got a mortar. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yeah, it's 32 ounces. Yep. I know. And even worse,
way worse than it being 32 ounces. Light ice. You're a fucking psycho. Hey, can I get that with
light ice, please? Oh, okay. So you're, you're, you're a mutant. Okay. Got that. Now I need the
blue door. Where was the blue door? There was a red door here. Anyone remember the blue door?
Anybody remember a blue door? I didn't burn it into my memory because I don't think it exists.
Blue door? Was there something else I could do back here? Blue door. I remember. And I got the
soap here too. You know, I didn't burn it into my brain because of that. This one, a blue door is
blue things next to the door. Nice block. I can't get more than one. Okay. I, for some reason,
I thought I could get two with a swipe. Is that open? That's okay. And then there's a beep too.
There was somebody that guy fucking, that was a multiple jump scare in front of me, guy running
at me and to my left, a fucking horn at the same exact time. I don't know if you guys heard the
horn. It was a huge beep. Somebody probably heard it. Someone with good ears. The soap is so good.
Oh my God. I just got embarrassed. That was embarrassed. Just straight up. I mean, just
embarrassed. So, so let me get this straight. You got, it's gotta actually physically hit the weapon,
right? It's not just, hey, your, your screen is now safe. I blame the double jump scare.
All right, we're good. Now let's go back here and get the diamond. I don't even need it.
Let's throw some mortars down the halls, huh? Soap is taking too much time. I'm going soapless.
Okay. So it's just, it's a, it's a mystery good to go around here.
You got to find the right way. It's a maze. It's a mystery. There it is. I don't think that's it.
Remember the crossbow? I just jumped over that sword. Just want to make sure we're all aware
of that one. All right, that's it. I got the, the new crossbow bullets. I didn't get anything else.
There are wells to go. I guess the lava arrow pointing down. Sure. Does the book do anything?
I feel like the book doesn't do just whatever. Throw me. Could have got those all with one hit.
Not efficient. Look at this inefficiency. It's angering me. There we go. And I, you know,
I missed the crossbow goes through walls. That's right. It does. I forget.
Yep. That's pretty useful. Efficiency. Better. Not efficient. I feel like I could probably be
efficient in this room though. What the fuck is this? Why is there a dog in a box? Bad dog.
Bad dog. No, not you. Not you. I know you're in the same room, but not you. I don't want
them to hear that. You're a good dog. You're a good dog. Yes. All enemies dead. Fire and ice.
This is a new item. Lava cannot harm you. Oh, that's in limited time.
Do I have two swords? Oh, that's too bad. All right. Now what? Where is he? There. I need
another one of those, the lava head. Unless maybe can I go up? I'm going to try going this way.
I guess I can go this way. Did I miss anything over here? Oh, you son of a bitch. I, how did I,
why you? Yeah. 28 health. Just, I got to shoot this thing. There's a secret wall here. Hopefully
there's health here. Dick. All right. There is health in here. Good. Lots of, uh, really?
Really? Now what's that going to do for me? Hold on. Can I get up there? Holy shit.
Well, um, that's cool. I made, I skipped this blue door. Just don't fall. There's something
over there. I have to make this jump. I have to get this load. Why did, did I, hold on,
did I just save it right there? No, I didn't. Okay. So now save it here so I can get back across,
get back across. We're just gonna, we're going to save scum again. Not that it's not that bad.
All right. Now I'm going to open this door. I have no idea what the hell I'm doing right now,
but apparently I'm doing this. Oh, fuck. Why did I just do that? Don't, why would I jump away?
That's like, I just did like a fight or flight. It was flight. Flight. As much as you could
describe what that word is. Flight. What? Oh, I can't, I can't right click. I can't,
I don't have any morale. Fuck. Zero morale. Right. Okay. I need to have at least 50, right?
Damn. That's not good. I feel like I'm going to need that, uh, gas can.
And there's a soap down here. What the hell did I do? What, how, what direction is that even going?
I, I need the blue key. Am I, I'm behind the door that the blue key opens. Right? I think so.
I think I just have to go back. Yeah, I just have to go back down. Um, whatever. Okay. I guess I
know that's there. No, I'm not soft-locked. I'm good. Has to actually go this way, which is the
correct way. Okay. I thought that wasn't, that was not an enemy. I thought it was. God doing like
the extreme NPC walk. Pistol. There's nothing even here to shoot. I got the super power up, but it
didn't. Okay. There's red and blue door over there. I need a key, man. No one opens elsewhere. All
right. Um, I guess I'm just going down. I ain't going down there yet. Now I am. Finally some
morale. It's been forever. And a shotgun. Finally. Shotgun shells. Ooh, I could go, let me jump.
Hold on. Don't go there yet. What's over here? Nothing. I've already been over here.
Lots of shotgun shells. It's armor. What do you mean it's armor? What's armor? Secret? What do I
do with this? Uh, don't go in the, is that going to light up? Is that going to, it doesn't explode,
right? No. Should I bring it with me? He's going to bring it with me. No, I'm just going to throw
it in there. Just whip it in there. I don't know if that did anything. Here comes a fight.
Yeah. Yup. Yup. I can climb any wall. Hold on. I need to make, I'm not going to do this yet. I
want to get stuff. Oh, fuck. Whatever. Just finally. Okay. Um, just make sure I don't miss
anything. Smelly crystal. I don't know what these do. Okay. I should probably, I probably need to
get up there. Is that soap? Hello? What did I just, what the hell just happened?
That's a backflip. Nothing else I can do. This is gold. Good. Good. Do a flip. I told you I could
do a backflip. Have I ever proven that? No, no, I actually can't do it anymore. Absolutely cannot
do it anymore. Too old to do it? Yeah. I, yes, I'm too old to do that. Without a doubt. I'm certain
that I'm too old. All right. Now I can use my sword if I need it. We're going to go back down.
We're going to. I'm not fucking around with that. No loot? How dare you? I could go up a little
higher I think. Yeah, I can. Ah. The crossbow is a lot of fun. Oh, drunk fighting. I was too,
I was too drunk to hit me. I don't know how that works. That makes no sense what I just said.
Blue key. What door over there? Oh, that's the door. That's the, that's the blue door.
Okay. Right. Now I can just go this way. Got him. That guy fell to his death. I didn't have to do
anything. Come on. Kill me. I'm here. Kill me. Boss fight incoming. Uh huh. Three more of these to
touch. I'm going to get. All right. Let's see. What about, what about mortars? Or sword maybe.
Rifle. Best weapon. The waves of destruction. To know. Any more writing? Two more to go. One
more to go. This is a rifle. This is going to be a sniping level. That's much as certain.
I think it's probably inside. The damning cooling gun. Cooling sun. Where is it?
Did I miss one? I must've missed one.
Here it is. Oh, they're flying.
Shit. It's hard to see my crosshair because it's snowy. It's very snowy. Yeah.
Jerma gave his older brother the controller. Yeah. Junko. Jerma's older brother. Junko.
Junko. All right. Got red key. I can go back down. Uh wait. Did I miss anything?
It's just fun to shoot in this game. It's very fun. Just is. All right. Let's go. There's a red
door down here. Somewhere. I don't know. Whatever. Wherever it is. It's back this way. I think it's
back here. Right? No. Where is it? No. Where was it? No. It was back here. Don't worry. Just
leap. Oh my. Oh my fucking god. That scared the shit out of me. I was about to say have no
fear. Junko will save the day. That's a one hit kill. Good to know. Where the? Holy shit. It's
an ant. It's one of those monsters. Just stand still. It's gonna hit. Should I do it? Yeah.
True hard run would have no saves. Sure. I guess. But the true hard mode is also take one hit of
damage and you die. Actually that's not even actually what that mode is for. This is the
hardest game mode in the game that I'm on right now. The one above it is a challenge mode. It's a
challenge mode. Specifically challenge mode. So it is true. This is the hardest difficulty of the
regular game. There's a lot of people dead over here. Well this is gonna be fun. Actually it's
gonna be fun. I like the ones where you can just like ski around. All these. Can I open these?
This door opens elsewhere. This door. Well I know you exist now. That's good. Who's talking?
What are they? I'm not gonna use those bullets. Might as well use them for that. Hold on. Give
me this stuff. Go down the well. There's all kinds of little things to look at. This one opens.
Where is he? Up top. Yep. What the? Flying fuck.
Fuck. Quit edge guarding me. Was this Smash Brothers? Not fair. You can open these doors
from the other side. All right. Let's go. God damn it. The sound. It hurts. It hurts. It really does
hurt. Oh. Let me just get these all open. Give me that. Oh my under. My armpits are itchy right
now after that. I don't know. Is there any doctors in here that can tell me why that is?
Why do I have itchy armpits after being scared? Wait. It looks like I can jump off the ladder.
You doofus. I don't want to be up there because I can see. There's the red door.
I can get that gun. There's an extra sword. What is it? But if you already have a sword,
what's the point? Rifle. Let's just use it. I think we're clear. I thought that was yellow.
There's a red door and then a red door and then red door. There we go. There was no reason for that
to happen. There was no reason for what just happened to happen. You know what I'm saying?
There was no reason for that. I don't have any morale. I'm dead. What the fuck? Let's just grab
the key and instantly scream in front of me. Guy. Oh. All right. Well, I've got to be aware of that.
Shit. Give me this health. All right. Here's my ammo that I wanted and I fell.
Kill that guy. Wait. What's in there? There's shit in there. Don't get that key. Get in there.
What's in here? Not bad. Shotgun. I need a big shotgun. I've got plenty of ammo. I think it's
time to start this. What do I have for my hunting rifle? Not 15. I want 15. I refuse to play unless
I have 15 hunting rifle ammo. It's the only way I feel comfortable is up there. Plus, I will not
do all this. I need to do ammo collection now because I won't do it later. You all know it.
That looks suspicious. All right. Wait. All right. Let's go. Wait. There's so many little
like nooks and crannies here. What does this do? A house opens. Which house? Another house? A house
opened? No. Too many things. Which house opened? Is this house? I can go in here.
What is this for? There's a lot of places to go here. I think this is the house, right?
Was that the house that opened? I don't know. Maybe another day I'll figure it out. Let's go.
Right off the bat. Too many of you. Jesus. How am I not hitting you? Oh, fuck. I forgot to
quick save it right before. Did I? No, I did. Kill me. Kill me. Kill me. Kill me. That was bad.
I forgot about the guys in the air. Let's go. Clean it up. That's how you get it done. Is it
Junko or Jungo? Tell us before a civil war starts. No, it's Junko. Like junk. It's not Jungo.
It's Junko. All that brother Junko. Imagine your name was Junko. Junk. J-U-N-K. Junko.
Like junky. No, not junky. That's not. Junko is. That's fine. Give me this. Didn't even use the
powerups either. All right. It's time. I got a red key. You gonna play this one on me? Huh? That's
why I saved it. Red door is up here somewhere. Where is it? Up that way? I know there's a weird
red door somewhere like hanging out over here. Sure thing. I'll take a secret. Found the double
shotgun. I'm so happy I went up here. I'd be naked without this. All right. What is that red? There
it is. Oh, really? Look at that guy over there. I'm just gonna hide behind here. Of course,
you're not gonna show your face. You're dealing with Junko. I would pity you. I wanted to kill
you without picking that up. I just killed somebody. What? There he is. I fucking can smell him.
Big guy. Don't go in the well. I'm gonna do it just because you told me not to.
Well, we're in some shit, aren't we? Erratic. Erratic. Got him. This is the door that opened.
I can climb any surface. Which thing do I climb? The tallest thing here. Where am I? No, go, go,
go, go. It was the tallest thing here. None of this matters. Do you drown in this game?
What's all this down here? Can I? I'm gonna drown. All right. How do I get out of here?
Monka. Oh, that's it. Go, go, go, go, go, go. Out, out, out, out. He can't fit through here,
right? Can he fit through this? I gotta get further away.
I wasn't gonna cheese that one. I've cheesed the last boss of the other encounter. I can't. Just
come on. There's a yellow key. The shadow sunk our city. His monsters stripped our bones.
The water rises. The bones are their dollars. Wait. I can swim around. All right. This sucks,
but this is actually kind of cool. Swimming around. Let me get that health. Bomb the wall.
Bomb the wall. Bomb the wall. What wall? Which wall do you want me to bomb? Bomb the wall. The
wall. In the wall. The wall. All right. Well, bye. You had your one chance to tell me where it was
and you had to be funny about it. You had to be cute about it.
What are those? I don't know what fish is now. And they're fast. What a dodge. Did you see that
dodge on his part? One fish, two fish, red fish, dead fish. I don't think that's how the Dr. Seuss
book goes. I can hold my breath for a very long time. Fish moly. Why you kill me? Is anybody else
convinced that fish moly is like 29 by 29 instead of 28 by 28? It's bigger. The emote is bigger.
Did it win? Are you winning? Crypt of the. More of this. No, I don't like not having.
Ah, okay. Sword time. No, super shocking. I hear a new enemy type. I hear breathing.
I already got the yellow key. All right, we win. I need my flashlights.
Oh, I just got. The door opened somewhere else. Oh, the yellow door is right behind me.
Okay, this is dead end. The basement door opened. Okay, red keys up here. Ah,
what's this? I blow it up. That's unfortunate. I hate this sound. I hate the sounds. I hate the
sound. I knew it! There's a new monster. I told you it was a new monster. It's a big scary, like,
big mouth frog guy. It's so stressful. What is. Okay. I hate this shit. Shotgun shells.
Thanks. I guess. It looks like we're going in here. I knew it! The chaos enthralls us.
The chaos crawls to me. Jesus Christ. Look at how much damage these things do. You guys are the
worst. What does that do? Uh, just to kind of avoid to get back.
I was trying to pre-fire him. I have 30. I have 20 health. Wrong way. I'm dead.
That was tricky. Who has a flashlight? There's a. I already have a sword. Why
does it want me to use the sword? I don't have enough morale to use the sword.
The closer they got, the more they suffered. I don't have enough morale for this. I need
to just use a. Who's in this one? Anybody? Can I just close myself in here? That's your secret.
Your secret is shotgun shells. That's not a very good secret. Don't tell anybody about my secret.
I'm getting closer to him. He's going to run down the hall. He's going to run down this hall.
Might as well make it. There's not even a hallway.
Wait. Wait. What? Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Time out. Time out. Time out. Time out. It's not a frog.
It's one of the invisible ones. Time out. There's a. They're, they're down here though.
It's definitely, uh, it's, I can't use that shit. It's going to kill me. I'm going to end up blowing
myself up. Is there a chest right here? No. I don't have a key. No. There's something else
to do here. I need to get the blue key up. I guess I can go up, up there. No. Did I go this way?
I've been this way. Did I miss something else? I mean, very clearly I can still hear that guy
breathing. Did I not go in one of these doors? What the fuck? Where, where is he? God.
Oh, this is not supposed to be a scary game. This is not supposed to be a scary game.
It's the flashlight. There's the key and I'm going to get swarmed. The second I turn around,
I'm going to spam mortars up the, up the, up the door. Safe for now.
I really don't like this level. It's too scary. It's too much. Can I blow that up?
The ladder there. Well, I'm going to use it if you want me to.
Where is he? Where is he? Where the fuck? He came all the way down the stairs and I didn't even see
you. Now I got 12 health. I got more. Deeper. Not yet. Hold that thought. Not deeper. That
opens somewhere else. That's definitely the door that opens when I press this button. Don't fall.
Deeper. I got stuck in the wall. Curve at the frog over here. Curve at the frog. Is it going to
kill me? All right. So let's get this going. I'm going for it. I'm going to move quick.
Ah. Oh, she spits. Where are you? Who's left? There's somebody left apparently. Where,
where are they? I have 14 health. Where are you? That's not health.
Oh man. Oh man. Oh man. Oh man. Oh man. Oh man. Oh man. Oh man. Oh man. Oh man. Oh man. Oh man.
Where you at? Where? Where is he? What is it? What is it? What's, what's, what's chasing me?
Give me all that stuff. I gotta use the assault rifle. Max ammo on it. Always use the thing you
have that has max ammo. That's a tip from a professional video game player. See? There's
my key. Super health. That's the red key for the red door. The owl clove opens. Where's the owl
clove? You want to help me out here? It's above you. Oh, wait, is there a secret up there?
No, the owl clove opens. Oh, you idiot. That's convenient. What the fuck? That's convenient.
Didn't find a secret. I got a couple of them. Is that beavis or butt head?
Both of them at the same time. Uh oh. Open environment. It's time to show off our skills.
You missed a secret. I don't care. I shouldn't have done that. Uh oh, here comes the army.
Sword only. Just kidding. That's a lie. Watch out for the, I was gonna say Burger King frog.
That, there's no, there's no Burger King frog, right? Okay, that's wave one. Let's, uh,
that's activated. Cool. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Hey, why don't you make it hard for me?
I mean, you didn't read the biography of my character beforehand, unfortunately. You didn't
read the biography that says like, oh, watch out when he gets the sniper rifle. Don't go at him.
He's fucking lit with the sniper rifle. I got hit once. Yo, boohoo, got hit one time.
I, oh, he's a 99 percentile. I actually like this. This is fun. All right, let's do it with
the crossbow. What's hitting me? Oh, what happened? Okay. That was bullshit. I didn't even see them.
I didn't even see them. The problem is, I mean, what was I thinking? That's the problem right here.
These things are following me around in a circle. Let's get some health. Good. Over here, health.
All right. Cool. Let's do some mortars. Good job, Jerma, you fucking stupid dipshit idiot.
Okay, I got everything I needed. Let's just activate the last one. What about in the
cathedral area itself? I think there's probably some things I didn't get. Yeah, there's some health
back here. Just making sure I get it all. All right, last one. Where is it? Mob that guy?
Don't mob that person. There's no reason to. It's not that one. I already got that one
back here. No, I got this one too. Where is it? There it is. Open. It's time for the final battle.
Whatever the hell's in here. Something's in here. Lots of shotgun ammo.
There it is. All right. I think, I think this is going to throw 10 times what I've done already
at me right now. When I press this button. Shoot this. I did it. The rising wind brings the stench
of rotten meat. Yeah. Okay. Uh, should I get out of here? No, that's a, how do I get away from the
tornado? It's coming for me. Do I have to leave the area? Let's go. Where is it? Okay. I have to go
around it. It's, it's changing trajectory. It's changing trajectory. Oh shit. Kill it. I can't,
you can't kill a tornado. Oh my fucking God. No, I have to go around it. You can't kill a tornado.
There's a way down. All right, here we go. Why does it know where I'm going? All right,
hurry up and go down. Wait, is there secrets in there? It's gone. Wait, this is what I'm supposed
to do. I thought that's what I was supposed to do. I thought I was supposed to escape the tornado.
Oh, all right. I'm sure I get all this stuff. I don't know what I was supposed to do.
I thought I was running away from the tornado. What is that? Magic egg backpack full of ammo.
Oh dear. I had 50 health. I just fell off. Okay. Well, that's a lot of you're coming up. Okay.
That's a lot of you coming up right now. This thing pushes you back.
He's fucking dead. Oh, I'm going to kill him. I'm going to kick his ass. I'm going to stab
his throat in his fucking throat. And when I get up there, it's you. Funny. Fuck. I didn't have any
morale. I thought I had enough morale to do that. Oh well. You thought, you thought it was like
funny. He went. I'm just going to kill him before they get up here. Fuck him. Where is he?
Just shooting his shotgun from this far away. Shooting the fucking ground. This guy's freaking
me out. Why does he not run up yet? Okay. Here we go. If he kills me again, sometimes you got to
just go in. Good. All right. Now we've got a door here. We've got a secret spot here. No.
You can take a lot of hits. It's all right though. Save it right here. Get in. I don't have a fucking
morale. Just kill me. I thought I had, why did I lose morale? 49 morale. Who? That doesn't give me
morale. Why are you even putting it on your bar? Now I got morale. Give me that. Well, I didn't
find it because I can't get it. I mean, sure. I found it, but I can't reach in there and get it.
Get out of the way. I thought these would flush the whole way. I thought they, I thought they would
flush. Every time I looked at it, it was like that right there. This is connected right there.
I'm moving around quickly and I thought it was connected or whatever. It's fine. All right. Where
am I going? Uh, get the super pistols. Not yet. All right. Super pistols and the door go.
There's nothing in here to do this with. Okay. Keep going. Find something to do. Find something
to kill. Quick. Find somebody to shoot at. Find anybody. Got him. I still don't have any keys.
Did I miss a key? Wait, do I have a key? No. Oh, there's a door. I would have loved that
fucking special movie. That was absolutely deranged. Yeah, I know. What would it say?
What am I going to tell you? Sorry. I was like, I was in the middle of talking.
I was like, oh, that's going to be, and then somebody just grabbed my sides and like squeezed
really hard. Like a squeaky toy. Red key. What happened? Why did I put it away? Why are they
freaking me out? Which way are they going? Okay. I gotta slow down. Wait, wait, wait. Why are you
taking out the signals? Why are the signals out? Okay. I saved it. I seriously, why is the signal
coming out? What was that all about? I like took this out and then all of a sudden the
signals got replaced and I lost all the health I had. That's so, so, uh, I'm actually upset right
now, but it's all right. Well, that's what the problem was. All right. If you don't, if there's
zero ammo in your gun, if you click, it just switches immediately to the next one. That was
the problem. That's when I got all fucked up. Where are these fools? Fool. That was fucking
really fast. Anybody else play video games here? Wait, I don't want to go through that yet.
Wasn't there a red one up here? I remember that being a red door and be going red door,
secret red door or something, right? Or am I making that up? No, I told you I wasn't making it up.
Riveter unlocked. I'm not going that way yet. It's just a, so that's the door I was thinking of. Okay.
Okay. Nothing in the crossbow, hunting rifle. Let's just move. This game is cool.
Laugh my ass off. Yeah, I know. Let it come through. Three, two, one, go.
What the hell? What was that? Don't watch it come all the way down, dummy.
Because I knew he was right here. There's like four of them here. I have to start using these.
Always use the one with max ammo and then collect ammo and then fight a boss with 40 health. Sounds
like a plan to me. Oh, you didn't even check behind the portal. I know the effects of the
fast fire totem will stack. So what you're saying is pistols get both fast fire things and just go
spam. I'll take it. Where am I? Okay. Where am I? Where am I? All right. We're good. I'm going to
do too much. I gotta stop drinking coffee. Save it. I know my large coffees. I thought that was a
guy. All right. Hold on. Where are these motherfuckers? Yeah, good. You got your cameo.
You got, you got to be on camera. All right. I still hear somebody. There's a lot of stuff in
the way though. There's a lot of things to pick up and a lot of places to go. Why don't we check out
down here? Look at that. Super bullets or something. I know. Okay. I'll take it. Sure.
What's up there? Who cares? Welcome to hell. Secret. Oh, what's on the other side?
I have bees. What's that? Another sword. I can go down here. Can I? Oh shit. Okay.
Red door. Wait, that's not a red door. Yes, it is. I have a red key. What are you dumb?
Back in the back of my mouse hole. Back in the mouse hole. Too many of them got
they got killed by a creeper. Oh my god. Fuck. Okay. Go up. Look at how much that is there.
But wait. What the hell? What? The reason why I'm opening all these doors at the same time.
Like a dope. You can't be serious with me. What? Retreat. Oh, what is in here? I shot over his head.
You got lucky. You on the other hand are still alive. Blue key. I'm kind of running an ammo.
I need every bit of health I can get right now. And there's still those guys here.
The frogs are still here somewhere. I can't slide under there. Fuck it. Whatever. I think I'm just
gonna go. I hate hearing that breathing sound. The heavy breathing drives me crazy because I know
somebody's here. This health and this ammo right here. Just fuck it. This rain health.
Sure. I guess. Whatever. Where is it? Where are you? I can hear his like stretchy pants.
Can you hear him? He's like spandex. Hey, you're the coolest fucking person I know. You're the
coolest person. Just step on the gas all the way down and flood your engine with gas and just go
really fast for five seconds. It's so awesome. You're so cool for doing that. Everything about
you. I wish I could meet you and hang out with you. I would assume that that person speaks in
one word sentences. Yeah. You like going real fast, huh? Yes. Okay. You know that's like you
can really like hurt somebody. I don't know. Oh, okay. But I go fast. Cool. Great. I hate sharing
the road with you. This place is condemned. Oh, there he is. Whoa. Don't look at me. Don't look
at me. Don't look at me. I don't have any clothes on. Where are my clothes? This is a nightmare.
I'm in a nightmare. Fuck you. It's doing the like super pog face. I'm gonna die. I have to.
Okay. What do I want to use? Hunting rifle? There's another one down here.
I think it's right behind. It's right behind the door. Nothing. Is he dead? He's dead.
There's another one though. Shit. Is that right there? Oh, no. Not this stuff. Not like this.
All right. Shotgun time. All right. I'm gonna put, I'm gonna block the doors so he can't go
around me. He cannot go in front of me. He can only come to my left and right.
No, just my left. He can't go through that front door. Okay. Well, I know this is only for bosses,
but there's rivets here. That's enough. Get the health in there. Oh shit. I don't know. Where am I
going? Oops. Where am I? How am I? God damn it, man. God damn it. Wait, there was just a chainsaw
guy. It wasn't even a frog. It wasn't even a frog. I can kill these guys in one shot. What a...
Seriously, that was what I was scared of? That's what I was so scared of. Unbelievable. Not even
a frog. But seriously though, I'm gonna do mortars, rivets for a little bit. Welcome back.
Two and then get you with two and then get you with two. And then that's all right. You're here.
You're right. Why would I shoot myself in the face with this? Don't ask me. I can't give you an answer.
All right. Let's move. There's one in here. Good. I need to do the slows. I want the health.
Rivets right there. I know you're gonna... Are you serious? Check. Turn. Why aren't you turning?
Turn. Excuse me. All right. Let's move. That's good. Now we've got to... I'm gonna do just these
shotguns. Go. No morale. Don't be... Don't make a mistake. I don't like when they do this shit.
It's too scary. No idea if this is the right way. No, I just... You're doing the hyper cam guy voice?
No, that's even the right way. I don't know. It could be. I don't know. Oh boy. This is where we move.
All right. Somebody teleported though. Somebody teleported. I heard it.
So when I go in there, I have to be ready. See? Where does this put me? All right. Let's just go
back. All right. What's up? I guess that this is the end. Pepe hands. What? See, I even checked
behind at this time. Nothing on here. I'm very proud of you. Press any key. Homecoming.
Let's get to full health almost. Welcome home. Hold on. I need to... I need to put back on my
my glued on grip from the Razer Deathadder. Yeah. You know what I'm going to say. I don't even need
to say it. You don't know. You don't even need to know what I'm going to say. You already have heard
it before. If you're in the store and there's two mice next to each other, one of them is a
like $100 Razer Deathadder and the other one is like an Amazon basics $12 mouse, that's the better
one. Like the default Microsoft mouse is better than this mouse. I'm serious. Imagine gluing on
grips. Can you imagine that? And they can come off. All right. I got everything I needed. Wait.
I mean, I kind of need to try. Oops. I didn't hit it.
Why am I not dead? Hey, thanks. Wait, I'm just... That's a lot of stuff flying around.
Oh, I got him. Nice. That... This is a secret. Is it really though? Yeah, I know. I'm playing with
bumpers. Yes. I'm at the bowling alley and I'm... What is that sound? I heard a sound. Wait, there's
some stuff to explore over there though. I'm not... I don't want to do this yet. I think this is like a...
I activate that or something. Oh, it's that thing. Why use two when you can use four? All right. What
does this do? I feel like if I touch that, I'm going to progress. I don't think I'm ready for
progress right now. Yeah, not yet. Hold on. I got the key. I want to go and see what's over there.
Okay. There's a house here. Stop laughing at your own jokes. Yeah. I was just... You are not fun.
Looking for health. I hear a little jingling of keys. Hey, any key jinglers here? Am I doing it
right? Well, sorry to intrude. Giant ball of skulls and death that lives in a regular house.
All right. I know there's going to be another one. What's in the basement? I don't know.
There's something in here. Look, very clearly there's a key. I think I'm supposed to touch
all these. Why did I do that? No. Touch it again. Touch it again. Touch it again. I don't want to
do that. No. I didn't even get to see what was in the basement. No. I didn't get to see... No. I
never know what's going to be in the basement now. Where am I going? What the fuck is happening?
Touch that. No. I need to touch that. Okay. I got to touch that one. I got to grab this one.
Okay. Go this way. And where is it? Oh. Is this door open? Oh, shit. I missed it. Oh.
Oh. I needed to be normal again. Whoops. I... Where's the world? Okay. Load the save.
It hurts my brain so bad. Just reach that. I can't even... I need to hit that again.
I actually think I'm fucked. I'm somehow moving further and further away. I think I can't do
anything. I can't turn. I can't move. I can't... Wait. What? Oh. Um. Okay. I need to see what's
in the basement. What are you doing down here, man? There's nothing in here? I guess there was
health down here. So it wasn't even worth coming down here. Why'd you do that, dude? He was just
fucking vibing. Well, I don't... I don't know. I don't care. All right. Now I'm going to try to...
I have the blue key. Here we go. Ready? Flip it. And then... Which way am I standing? Okay.
This is the way I'm standing. I'm going... All right. Where the hell am I? All right. So
I need to get a button. So I'm no longer here. There's a button. Let's get hit by this tree.
No! Almost had it. What about this one? Can I get hit by it? Let me get stuck here. Through this...
All right. I'm in a new house. I hear it. Oops. All right. Well. Um. Okay. Now if I go...
There's a switch that I have to hit. I saw it. It was over here somewhere. Like, right...
It's right there. Where is it? Where's that switch? Oh, there was a... What was that? All right.
In the barn is another switch, but that's just gonna make it right side up. I think I have to
actually, like, travel around like this. All right. Where am I now? Can I get in the barn like this?
Right there? All right. I'm in the barn. Shit. No. I can't reach that. How can I do a rivet jump?
Ah. As I said, I'm hurting myself and not hitting it. What happens if I go through here? All right.
There's that. But I'm not on the right plane. You know what I'm saying? I need to get, like, that way.
So I gotta flip it. Shit. Can I... Can I get up there? Maybe I can. I'm almost lined up.
All right. All right. All right. All right. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. I'm on this island now.
But which way am I going? I gotta go... Not quite. Not quite. Not quite. Not quite. Not...
Just don't move. I thought I... I gotta hit that... What happens if I press this button, though?
There's health here. Got it. What? What the fuck? What did it open? I don't even... I have no idea
what it opened. Um, where the hell am I? Holy shit. This is the most disorienting thing I've ever done.
Uh, I... Where am I even aiming? All right. Got one. I need to go right. I'm gonna throw up.
I'm gonna throw up. I have to hit this and spin around. I got one shot at this.
I didn't get it. All right. I... Blue. Blue. Blue. Blue. There's a blue... I'm at the blue door.
Okay. Let's... Let's go. Oh, no. I don't want to... Do I have to press that? Oh, no.
Do I have to press that? Do I have to? Wait. It's like there's two of them in here.
Just... Aye, aye, aye. What is this? The neighboring garage opens. Don't do this yet.
These guys in here. How can I be... Hello? How can I be here? What's this screaming for?
Somebody.
Okay. Oh, man. So, what's the actual end goal here? What's the end game here? Computer? And
that computer don't have time to play with myself. No, I don't. Is it to get in the barn like this?
Or... I'm not sure what this wants me to do. Let's see. Wait. Okay. I'm upside down now.
This one just makes you go upside down. I know this soap in there. Don't worry.
So, if I just go upside down, that means I have to get to the upside down one like this.
I've made it to this island. There's also another island that has stuff on it like that one. No.
Where is it? Somewhere around here, isn't it? I know. I know about that. But wasn't there
another one of these? Smaller, with a bunch of stuff on it? Where was that? Oh, whatever.
I'm trying to... What? Where's my... That's the one right there. That's what I'm looking for.
Good thing this stopped. Do it again. Yeah, I knew there was one of these. There. See?
All right. That was worth doing. What about that? No. Okay. It's time. Just be ready.
Where is he? Where is he? Where is he? I'm talking about none of those. Hit him. Dude.
How did he get missed that many times? Look at how small this area is.
What? Those are some... That's a pixel perfect missing, apparently. Fake health box. All right.
Let's spin. This is going to be puke inducing. There's a key. Okay. I got to get that key.
Yellow key. Got it? No. Yellow door. Over there. So...
Oh, I'm at the end. That one was a little bonkers. Almost perfected. I wasn't about
to go try to find the third secret there. That was a puke level. As above, so below.
This is the very beginning. Oh, it's not there. What the fuck?
Okay. Trying to get on this ledge. I did. But is there any... No, nothing here.
I would put a secret here. Oh, never mind. They're all like this. Full morale. Yellow door.
Oh, might as well fill it up. I'm going to keep the sword out for now. Never mind.
Would have loved to have picked up that hunting rifle ammo.
Health. I'll take a secret. Ooh, nice. Yes. That's exactly what I wanted. Thank you.
Break it. Why can't... Rivet gun. Save it. I'm probably nearing the end of the episode.
What is it? 10 episodes? 10 levels per episode? Something like that. Let's get up there.
Okay, switch guns. That was dumb. Ready, go! I hear a lady.
There's two of them. Go into the light, Jeremy. I didn't plan on it. All right, I'm going to have...
Let's do these two on switch. Oh, boy. Never mind. Oh, boy. Why?
Please die. Please die. Please die. This game is so stressful, but it's so fun.
Where are you? All right, I want shotgun and mortars for my switches. Godlike.
And then I go and do something like that. Give me health. What was that? What is... Who's firing
in here? It's you! I just saved it right there. Save it down here because I don't want to die there.
Oh, my fuck. She's coming down the stairs, man. Don't blow that up. It's gonna hit me.
I hate these things. I can go get those. What do I have for a... Yeah, I'm gonna get crossbow ammo.
Okay, there's a fire... There's a Mario slide portion of this level coming up right here.
But let me get everything. There's another person. How's are they in? Are they in here with me?
What? Open. What's the point of this? What's the point of that? What's the point of this?
I don't think there's a point. All right, secret health, but I don't need it.
Okay, I see where you are. I see where you are. Holy shit! Okay, we're just bombing it. Hello?
Oh! What happened there? One, two, three. Great. Where were you? I don't... Guys,
she was in the bottom floor of the house. How many times did I pass you?
Did she go up a tree? Oh, something activated.
All right, don't go in here yet. I want to take care of this shit. Let's get in here. Same deal.
Now I can chill and bomb it. That's gonna hurt me, isn't it? What the fuck just happened?
What just happened? Fuck it, we're going in. People are in here. There's so many people in here.
There's so many people. All right, there's like three of those whispering ladies in here.
Now, what does this get me? I heard a beep. All right, interesting. Anything else in here?
Wait, this just takes me all the way back to... Wait, what? Why would I want to come back here?
This is the... Oh, the fuck? Hold on. H-E-I. No, that's right. That's where this yellow key is.
All right. Well, let's get the hell out of here. Guys, what is going on right now? Where the fuck
am I going? What just happened? This is like really, really far away. What? I'm so confused.
This may as well have been six hours ago. All right, here's the house. All right, I made it.
All right, so that was not the way I should have... Okay, I have to get... Right, right, right.
But I gotta get the... I gotta go down here. I don't have very much time to use this.
Is it just death down there? I think that you just die. I gotta find out. I'm not sure I'm
supposed to do that. I mean, why would I be able to come all the way down here though?
There's nowhere else to go. I knew it. I knew it. So what was the point of this? Is that a secret?
I guess. He's answering himself. I guess I go... I didn't get a yellow key yet,
and that's what I'm looking for. Was there a yellow key somewhere up here that I missed?
Like through here? Because this wraps all the way around. Don't go down.
Just go across. All right, maybe this is the way to go. Trust your eyes. Now we're all the way back
again where we were last time. I'm just going to rocket jump up. What the... Oh, it's the wrong
button. Wrong one. It's this one. Keep moving. Where are you? I can hear you. Where is he? Above
me? There you are. There you are. Oh, and you came through the door. Those things move a lot.
Oh, he hit me right in the face. Jesus. This dog... Stress. Stress. Stress. Stress. Stress.
Stress him out. Stress him out. Stress him out. Stress him out. Stress him out. What else do we
got? Anything? Any more food here for me to... for my guns? Any more food for my guns?
Yes, there is. And food gun. Maxon hunting rifle. There we go. Wait, what's this?
Weird little door back here. I can hear you wailing. There you are. This is a long stairway.
What's this? Cast machine? I guess there's some stuff down here. Hey! Where is he? He's in the
teleporter. Great. He's lighting his shotgun up to my head. He was just waiting for me.
All right, give me a second. Well, I'm trying to... I didn't... Didn't I get another key?
I swear I did. Somebody's sprinting down here, I think. You're not. We're good.
You eat 5G gum? I'm chewing 5G gum. All right, that's real funny. I mean, just hilarious, dude.
Absolutely hysterical. Funniest person. Hey, actually, it's a shortcut. Thanks for the
shortcut. Appreciate it. Good. Sweet. You want to play that game? I can play that game.
Get out of here. Take that. Memories dry and crumble.
This game's too hard for you? I'm about to finish the game on the hardest difficulty.
What are you talking about? Yeah, I think you should, like, I think you should, like, put...
You gotta throw in the towel, man. You're, like, you're, like, 42 minutes from beating the whole
game on the second hardest difficulty. I think, you know, maybe you should throw in the towel now.
This is time for you to throw in the towel. Yeah, now is it. Do it now. Where is it? What the hell
is he? He's freaking me out wherever he is. Why did you even fit through the door? Why did he even
get in the door? He's really... You can't fit through there, man. No way. You don't fit through
that door. Let's go. Okay. Take out both of these. Now, watch out for the dog.
I don't even know where he came from. He kind of just showed up. Where is he? He's gonna...
Through this wall. Okay, got you. Oh! He can hit me through the grate. Sorry. I just negated
everything he just did. Stop commentating. Just win the game. This streaming shit is distracting
you. All right, I'll turn... Let me turn my stream off for a few hours, guys. I'll see you later.
Dude, you need to turn off your stream.
Did I really just get a, dude, turn off your stream comment? Did that really just happen?
Dude, just turn off your stream. What the fuck? All right, hold on. I got... I'm ready to move
forward. Dude, this streaming thing is like... You gotta just complete the circle. I have to...
But this is the beginning of the game. Dweller in the darkness. Okay. I mean, you can clearly see
that. Oh, you're gonna give me a soap? Don't give me a soap right before one of the last boss?
Am I actually gonna get a soap here? Holy shit. This is a lot of stuff. Okay.
Just remember... Okay. Let's go.
Holy fuck. All right. What's a better hunting rifle? No.
Salt rifle. Yeah. Take out a little guys first. That's planned. Just spawning still.
Oh, it hit me. Found the sword. Good. Now what? Oh, all right. Let's keep... Let's keep... It
keeps rolling. It keeps rolling. It keeps rolling. Fuck. Bad. Bad. Bad. Bad. Give me this...
Go up. Holy... Thanks for the help, man. Don't kill me. Oh my god. There's so many of those
bullets firing over at me. Oh, there's so many of these bullets firing over here.
Oh no. No. I didn't save the... I didn't save the game. Oh shit. God. That's insane.
All right. Fuck. That's hard. I gotta do the same thing from before. Let's go.
But different. Here we go. Watch this. I have a better strategy than this.
Salt rifle is not good for this. I really should just... No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No. Kill me. Kill me. Bad start. Kill me. Kill me. I'm gonna use the... I think I'm just gonna use
hunting rifle. No. No. No. No. What am I gonna do here? What do I want to use? Crossbow?
Maybe the crossbow. I need crossbow ammo. Is there even crossbow ammo here?
I wonder if I... Can I actually take a second? Probably not.
I think I'm just tilted from the last round. Yeah, that's absolutely what's happening.
Bye. All right. All right. Start over. Regain strength. I'm gonna do the same thing at the
last time. Salt rifle. Get rid of the guys on the ground. Salt rifle. Get rid of the guys on the
ground. Let me see how... Does this just activate if I walk forward? Or can I actually look around
for a second? Now I get the music starting, right? Yeah. Okay. You just have to go.
If that ran into anyone, holy fuck. That was kind of a mistake. That's like too much.
Yeah. That's way too much. Too quick. Where's my... Just hit six. Give me a break.
God damn it. Oh, fuck. I got all the time in the world. Don't rush it.
I'm gonna leave one person alive. That's the strategy here. Okay. Let's pick up some shit.
Did I actually get hit by the one fucking little asshole that's right here?
Okay. Got health. Oh, this is over here. Morrell. Okay. What's up next?
I gotta be ready for it. Up next is... All right. That's a good save point. I think I'm gonna do...
Let's just go. I think it's... I don't remember, but we'll just fucking deal with it when it happens.
Oh, it's a shotgun guys, right? Oh my fucking lord. That's a lot of people. Fuck you twice.
Fuck you a third time. Ah. I'm not prepared for what's next. What is next? It's just these idiots.
What is he? Stupid. I almost had an ammo. Okay. Now it's just the mad scientists that are running at
me. I can handle this. I need ammo for a gun. Is that it? What's that? The invisible. The invisible.
Invisible. Invisible. Invisible. Invisible. Invisible. Everybody sick? Everybody getting
sick? I was getting sick. I had to stop. Oh my fuck. That's a bad idea right now. Whoa. You're
spawning on me, bro. You're spawning. I'm gonna charge up over there. Oh. It's too many. It's too
much. It's too much. It's too much, man. It's too much. Oh, I can't even... You can't even slow down
either. You can't even slow down. I'm dead. Oh my god. Oh, man. Oh, man. Okay. I have to start
saving it. Oh, okay. Slow down. Fuck me. Oh, yeah. Right this part with the fucking animals.
Where are they? Dude, jumping like this is gonna give me a fucking brain aneurysm. It's gonna run.
These guys. I'll do anything with these guys. These guys.
Oh, fuck. I have to do this for a second. You can't do that for that long without having your hands
come off the keyboard. I'm gonna just snipe. It's much easier. Now we have to do this stuff.
It's crossbow time. Don't get overwhelmed. Just get them all before they spawn. Get them all when
they spawn. Damn it. Okay. Fuck. I gotta use the shotgun for a little bit. Oh,
how are you still alive, man? What a flying goddamn diaper.
I've expelled like all my energy. I don't have any energy left. I just quick saved and got hit
in the air by this fucking dog. I hope that's it. That's not it. Save it right here. Oh my god,
please. Save it right here. What is it? What is it? I don't understand. Is it the dog?
It's rats. They're just on the ground. I'm not gonna kill the last one. This is my break. Okay,
this is my break. Any other items that I can pick up and get health? Rats, rats, rats, rats.
I want to get into this next little... Where is he? I can hear him. He's gonna probably kill me.
Imagine if he killed me. I would cry on stream. I would turn the webcam on and just cry for you
guys. Okay, and 84 health. There he is. All these bullets. 86 health. Okay, I'm ready. Let's go.
Whatever it is. See ya. Go left, left, left. I have to go to the bathroom. I'm gonna pee.
Yeah, I gotta pee. Even if I do it, I have to pee. I should be okay though. Although I'm at 11 health.
Oh yeah, I have to pee. And I need a break, man. I'll be right back. I gotta pee.
Dude, the temperature in this room is probably like 95 degrees. I'm heating up this room.
Fucking intense, man. All right, let's go. I shook around a little bit. I stretched.
Whoa. All right, where are we at? Oh yeah, it's just a rat. Just a rat. Okay, so the next thing
that comes up is the chainsaw guys, which are one shot with this gun. All right, let me see if that
helps. You're not dead? I'm just gonna hit by a double-barreled shotgun. Oops.
No, you can't. If you stop moving, you are dead. You're just dead. Like, you gotta just keep the
hook. Hook. Hook. Hook. Or you're just dead. Guaranteed dead. What's that? What's that? What's
that? What? I just, what happened? I thought that was a new enemy. Oh, it's swordsmen and ladies.
Oh man, this is not good. And it's the ladies. I just stay on the outside. Oh fuck, man. Okay,
I gotta relax. I even know how the hell do you relax like this.
They're just like kind of killing each other. Y'all think I'm gonna be crazy. You think it's
gonna be I'm crazy, but I'm gonna get. No, not yet. Okay. Look at all this health everywhere.
Ah, just pick it all up quick. Watchers up the gate. Oh, oh shit. This health pack in the middle.
I gotta go in the middle. I gotta go in the middle. I gotta get this health pack in the middle.
Oh, I can't do that. That's not gonna happen.
Health pack. Health pack. Health pack. Holy fuck. I'm dead. No.
He's still bouncing around. Yeah. All right. What about this like this guy, this like Jason?
Nope. Down. All right. I'm gonna take out. I don't even know what I'm gonna do here to get
this health if I can. I gotta take out one of the horses. Yeah, dude. The horse has gotta go first.
Like they just got a great. I'm glad I walked in this killing.
Don't no, no, no, no. We got really goodness gracious. This is on. This is ridiculous.
This dialed up by a thousand. Whatever my ammo.
Imagine if you still have the soap. Don't remind me of my failure. It wasn't bad. Trying to get the
dogs. Oh, that hurt. Oh, that was, that was insane. That was ridiculous. That was fuck crazy.
That was fun. But that was nuts. Can you imagine playing that if you get hit once you die?
Taking, you die, you die in one hit. Oh, I would, I don't know if I'd be able to do that one.
Let's make sure I got everything. Even every little tiny little crumb of every crust of health.
I'm picking it up. Okay. There it is. So now what? Just through the door. Okay.
Damn. What was the one secret? What did I miss? It was the thing at the start.
What? I could have actually done that. Dusk. Okay. I've got ammo in the house away.
Crystal. Left crystal of madness. I'm not doing that.
I'm not going to lift up the crystal of madness just yet.
Stuff that's in there. Just want to make sure I have everything.
Is this the actual final final battle? What's up here? I would, I would make a comment on it,
but why would I end? Guys, there's a soap here. Why could I use the soap and whip it into the
last box? Okay. Let's keep the soap over there for emergency scenario.
Now let's go pick up that crystal over here. All right. It's been a fun game.
It's time to see how it ends. Are you going to come out of there or do I have to go in?
And with my soap, you finally arrived. You shall be my final test.
That started quickly. Jacob. I got to be moving already. You finally arrived. You
shall be my final test. I'm going too fast.
Okay. That was a mistake.
Kill him. Unworthy. Unworthy. Just in case I saw off lock myself. He was worthy and he accomplished
there. You should stop streaming. This game's not for you.
Who did you expect at the end of all of this?
God, the devil, perhaps it's just me.
Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Who is this? Okay. I need to, um, I found a secret.
How do you kill this guy under over his, in his glue, in his body, in his face,
explosives, the light, the light. What's going on? I need to get him in the light.
Okay. I need to save it like right when he's about to be done talking.
He was worthy and he accomplished so. You who were faster. You.
I can't save it. I have to save it while I'm falling.
Who did you expect at the end of all of this?
God, it's just me. It's just me. And here we go.
Oh, damn it. What? That's what you do. Got it. Okay. What? Wait, I, I, this is all this stuff
on the particle fix. If I hurt my head, I'm like looking. All right. So there's another crack.
All right. I don't have to do that. Okay. Okay. He swings. Then he goes to go get to jump over
his arm. Got it again. All right. I figured it out. Oh, man. I'm going to do that a thousand
times. It's going to end up killing me. It's all the green, man. It's messing with my brain.
I have to restart. Just die. It's, it's all the green is causing me problems. Where is it?
There's a light. Where's it going? Fuck. Oh, yeah. Move your hand. Move your hand.
Fucking God, man. You didn't get it.
How do I, can I shoot with my regular?
I don't want it. I want to spread it equally to everybody on earth.
How do they get pacifist? What was the secret completionist and pacifist?
I like that last touch.
Must always rain beneath dust.
My brothers have escaped you. My brothers will not die in vain.
That was really, really fun. So what did I do? It's just throw in the towel. This is not,
this game's not for you. That's like one of my favorite comments of the whole stream.
Like that was, it was, it was funny. So that was dusk, but I'm not done with dusk.
There's another game mode that I want to try where you have to fight waves. I'd like to try it.
Play the rat level. This is fine to see where I will find the secret rat level. That's fine.
Finally. Yes. Check out amid evil. I'm going to do that next. I was looking at that actually
last night. We're not going to play that now though. We're probably going to do that.
Is that one of them? When you look dead. All right. Let's do endless. All right. So
let me give you a rundown. That was, that was very, very good. Very good. 9.3.
I had to, I was 9.4, but there was that one part with the vents. Remember I was,
I was going up and down and I had to drop it by a point, by a tenth of a point. 9.3. That's very
high. It is something about the shooting mechanics in this game felt just way more fun than other FPS
games. Now I actually liked this game a lot because a lot of the old school shooters,
they were like the cardboard cutout sprite type stuff with the 2d plane sprites.
I actually am not a big fan of that. And I don't not, I don't hate it or anything, but just,
I like how this game doesn't do that. It's 3d. There's no sprites like the 2d sprites. What are
you a Gen Xer? No. The rat level is hidden in episode three map four. That's good to know.
All right. Level select episode three map four. How do I pick the level? Do I,
do I, can I not pick a low? Right. Okay. Episode three map four. So this is one, two, three,
four. Not with this current loadout. I want just, just give me everything. So where is it?
Is it hard to find? It's right there. Where are my guns? I didn't select them. How the hell did I do
that? All right. Hold on. I need my, I need my guns. Oh, you actually have to activate them.
I see. Okay. So where's it at? Just play until I can find it. Kind of. It's over there. It's over
there. Why am I still crouching? There's the key. Yeah. Yellow key. Find the toilet. It's red.
You go fast here, but it's probably a bad idea. I can't see.
Close the door. Basement door is down here. I got all the guns in the game. Why am I?
Now we go down. Wait. Get the chest of trust. Just for fun. All right. Down here.
Pick up this thing. Sure thing. Go around this way. Right. And we go this way. And then we,
all right. Through here. Quickly. Here we are. I made it. There's two guys down this hallway. I
remember. I remember them coming down here. I remember you. There's another one. Actually,
I think, no, it's a, it's a Wendigo. Right. From what I remember. Wasn't it a Wendigo?
Going too fast, but I have to. Oh, please. He's dying to frog wheel. Yeah, whatever. Okay.
Okay. I remember this part. Sort of. Kind of.
Right. All right. You know, I'm looking for a toilet, you said. Wendigo is in this one.
Okay. Was I not supposed to kill that? Okay. Where's my flashlight?
I still haven't gotten my flashlight. I think I should have by now, right?
Because I just ran through a ton, a ton of shit. Okay. There we go. We're good about this guy.
There's nothing in here, right? Okay. Now the next part.
Because this is the blue door. Was there another way to go?
No. Yeah. This way. This flashlight. This blue key. Okay. Let's move.
Okay. I think I'm close, right? It's before the toy. Don't copy pasta that. That was bad info.
Don't copy pasta. Don't. Bad info. Let's get my crossbow ready. Activate this.
You. And you. How are you doing? Good. Good. Forget about this part.
Dog. Don't think he can't make it out. He can.
That shoots room. Okay. Somebody else. Where are you? Silence. All right. Red key.
I've got the red key. I need to go back. So do I activate this? When you go through
the yellow door, turn left and look behind the junk for a secret switch.
Our club is open. Brings us back to here. It's pretty rad. I don't use that term very often.
So I'm done in here. To get back there. Go back all the way down to where I was before
that red door. How far back was it? It was all the way up here, wasn't it? Chaos crawls to me.
Right. Okay. What does it now? Look. Is it back down here? Is it? I can't get back up here through
here. He found the strawberry room. Did I miss it back up here? All right. Now it's just the
red door back here. All right. There's the yellow door. What is the red door?
Damn, that's far. That's all the way back here. All right. Wait. Didn't I already do this? I
already did this. No, this is wrong. So wait. There are multiple red doors. Oh, shit.
Left after yellow door. Isn't that the one that I just opened? So left after yellow door.
Is you talking about like go here like through here? Should I just open a wiki behind the junk?
Okay. Now nowhere. He's actually blind. What are you talking about?
Okay. So if this changed, this was the I knew I had my in my brain. This was a different.
I'm not taking this. So like this was why I pressed a button and all of a sudden the whole
world changes. I didn't think this was anything important. Flush your sins away. I thought that
was the secret. This is this. This is this is not bullshit. This is a real place. I thought. Wow.
Okay. I stand completely corrected here. This is a whole new level. All right. I thought you guys
just taking the piss. I thought that was like a secret way to leave that level. All right.
Whatever. Let's go. All right. All right. It's time just to smoke them out.
Yellow key. That was a direct hit. Leave all this stuff. Red key is the cat police.
All right. A couple ways to go. Let's try this way first. Hey, you little bastard. Fuck. They're
going to bite your toes off. I hope not. All right. Red secret inside of the secret. Interesting.
All right. Got a red key. This is another secret. Hey, it is. And shotguns. Put on the rat song.
All right. Germa the rat song for one hour.
This is going to start fucking with me. Wait.
I can't take this. I can't take. I can only take this for like 30 seconds. Ecomaniac.
No, I can't do this for more than a few minutes. I'm killing them. That's not something.
Put on the birthday remix. What happened to the song? Oh.
It's infiltrating my brain.
Yellow key.
Oh, man. It's like a maze. All right. I need yellow key. Yellow.
All right. Birthday remix. I can't hear this anymore. That's I just clicked on the wrong one.
It's staying. It's staying.
This song is so fucking stupid.
I need a blue key. No. Fuck this song. I don't want to listen to this one either.
How about a rat's birthday mixtape? This has 679,000 views. I didn't upload this.
This is a video. There's a lot of views. All right. I need to get a yellow key.
I'm lost. I know that's what the blue door is, but where do I get the blue key? I'm so lost.
There it is. Turn it up.
Is it not done? That was actually a giant rat.
Blast yourself back down. Did I just, didn't I try that? I was standing on it.
Hooray. That was cool. What does this put you out? Just you skip to the next level.
This puts you on blasphemy. That was fun. All right. Let me actually,
I'm glad you guys told me to do that. All right. Endless mode. The farm.
I want to try it. This is a series of waves.
Damage numbers or something. Has there been damage numbers this whole game?
Oh, I probably shouldn't have done that. All right. Wave two. Where are you? Oh, behind me.
Give me. Oh, wait. Shotgun. Yeah. Give me the shotgun.
All right. Is there any health? Or do I just have to survive? Oh my God. He was, he, he's up there.
He just spawned on top of me. Why does he get to wave three? I can do better than that.
Is this shooting faster or am I insane? Taking damage on wave one? Laugh out loud.
I just want to make sure I get everything. All the, all the levels, you know?
So what's a respectable thing to get to? What's a respectable wave? Three?
Twenty? Twenty? Are you kidding me? Re-chat. Re-chat. Once you hit 20, you're in the big leagues.
All right. Using rifle on that kind of enemies. Seriously. Discussion. Go home. Go home.
Go home. Turn off your streaming. Go home. We're just running around in a circle.
Really just hit me. We're just running around. Just stop running. Just turn. What? You fucking
asshole. Jesus. Holy. No. He was. Oh, I can do it. No. God. What is this? Did he wrap around
behind me? He just gave me one hit. Stupid. Give me all my shit. Give me all my shit. Give me all
my shit. Give me my shit. What's shooting me? You must learn everything. Collect. Collect.
Stop. Put on the rat song. I'm concentrating. I'm concentrating. I can't do that.
No way. No way. No way. There's no way. No way. Dude, you left your stream on. I'm playing.
This is a, this game's dangerous. This is not a drill. German 95 is playing the ratacombs
and it has the song on in the background.
This game's dangerous because I, I just, I know I have what it takes to get to like 10 or 20.
But I've been playing, I played it a lot today. I might be blending together. I know I can do it
and that's, that's what, that's the problem. Is me thinking I can get to like level 10
will keep me here for five hours straight. I'm going to slow down. What's with the speed? You
don't have to go that fast. You really don't. In fact, it's probably better off if you don't.
Okay. Let's just keep it going. Okay. That's good. I have to at least get to like seven or eight.
I have to. Now I'm going to get to level seven. How would I ever call my mother later and say I,
you know, then talk to her on our weekly Sunday discussions.
Easy. Careful. Careful. Don't get that. Does that, hold on. Does that respond every time?
I want to spam. I can't, I can't look away. I get to spam it. Whatever the answer is.
Fuck you. Jesus. Maybe. You can't say maybe. Guys on top have to go first
unless you're literally right in front of me. Oh, somebody. I don't know who it was.
Oh, is there another chainsaw guy? There is, isn't there? I know there's a chainsaw guy hanging out.
He forgot he was streaming again. That's okay. Holy fucking my face.
Chainsaw guy. Where is he? I know he exists. What? Who? Dick. Oh, what the fuck? There was
a chainsaw guy behind me the whole time. He missed somehow. He missed. I don't know how he
missed. All right. I got to seven. I can stop. I'm done. Game's fun. Okay. That's instantly done.
All right. I'm happy with it. I got to seven. That's all I care about.
Fuck. That's a lot of guys with the shotguns. Can't reach 10. I'm okay with that. It's tough.
It's tricky. It is, guys. It's tricky. Play a different map, you donut. I'm a man.
I call that bullshit. He thinks he's screaming again. All right. If I don't get to seven,
who cares? But I'm going to do a different map. Oh my lord. I didn't even know he existed.
Didn't even know. These guys are so fast. Like they're so fast. My eyes are itching. What do I do?
Call the eye doctor. Did I actually get hit by that? Somebody's still running around. It's this
guy. Is the dog still there? I hope not. Where's the dog? All right. Wave six. We're skipping this
one. Die. Oh, will he die? Okay. I'm seven. The problem was I had the shotgun equipped and it's
just not fast enough when you have like 10 people running into the room. That's going to fuck with
me. Give me all the guns. I know there's somebody behind me. I know there is. I know.
Oh, excuse me. Okay. What's with that spawn?
Did you just juke me? This is hard. This is tricky. This is where
what especially the spawns. You just don't know where to go. You just got to keep moving. But if
you move, what if there's a guy, what if a crazy doctor spawns on top of you? Just stabs you.
Give me all the stuff. I have no health. This is a wash.
Is there anything down there?
Two shots with the crazy doctors. Didn't want to pick that up. God damn it.
Hey. Oh, my health is so low. Where are those onions? Where are those onions?
Where are the onions? What? What just happened? What if it hit me? All right,
let's go through the cathedral. I'm burning up. I'm burning out here. I probably should
have picked that up after. I don't want to be stuck out. I got to get items. Whoa. That's
this is going to be scary. Guns. Need them. Don't use these yet. Back of my head is itching.
Why is my head so itchy? What's wrong with my body? I'll take the sword. That's actually pretty good.
Dogs got in. Who's left? Day. The tornado's here. The tornado is here. I did it. Is there
another tornado? Another tornado. Damn it. God damn it. I'm out of cool shit. I'm out of good shit.
Whoa. Oh, my God. That just threw me off so bad. Where did you even come from?
What? Oh, all right. It's my last attempt. This one. This one's too long.
There was one mistake and it's over. You make a single mistake. No, no human error allowed.
Don't you dare. I got dead. All right. Last attempt. That's it. And I'm done. All right. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. Give me some weapons. Give me some shit. I got to get items. Okay. Now
I'm going to do two rounds inside the cathedral with the riveter. This should be good enough.
Okay. We're good. Stay in here. That's why the tornado comes. So you can't pull this shit.
There's a lot of health out there. All right. It's time to move out. Here comes the tornado.
Oh, I'm in trouble now. I'm dead. See you later. I wasn't getting up. Yeah. I'm not getting away
from that one. I couldn't go left because there was the, uh, I was fucked. Damn. I threw it. Well,
I mean, I just, I couldn't get around it fast enough. Okay. This is actually it. No matter what.
I need to get the other weapons. I'm thinking. All right. Get some weapons. Why? Hold on. Why
would you just do that? Why are you? I hit right. I, what grenades do I? No, I'm in trouble.
Machine gun fire. You gotta be standing right there. Dick. Dude. He's going wacky. All right.
I got to try to get to past seven. Although I'm running on empty. It's all right. No excuses. Let's
go. That was bad. That was very, very bad. That was the worst thing that could have possibly
happened. I thought he was already on the other side. I'm dead. Yeah. Oh yeah. This is over.
Where'd the dog go? Oh man. It's so, it's so intense. I'm so addicted to it, but it's
so intense. Again. No, no. I, I'm at, I think I'm at a wall right now. Maybe if I started with this,
look, I blew every ounce of my video gamer essence on that gauntlet level where I had to
fight like 5,000 people. My gaming spirit is depleted. His gaming meter is low. Boost is morale.
So here's the deal. I'm going to do it one more time. I'm going to be quiet this time.
Fuck, fuck, fuck. It's like holding my breath. Oh, fuck, fuck. I still got it. Did I just,
holy shit, calm down. God damn it. You fucking assholes. God, this spread and the damages.
God, this sucks. Well, I'm dead. Oh, okay. I need help. That's not good enough.
How am I ever going to kill these guys when there's 10 of them that spawn on top of the roofs?
Let's get away from the spawns, I think. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Give me the, uh, there's a rifle ammo.
No, I didn't want you to die. I didn't want you to die. Oh, it's, oh, it's so hard.
God damn it. Oh, it's so hard. They're all up on their rafters. You got to like almost
hide it. You can't hide it here though. No, that's it. That's it. I'm just, I'm okay. I'm
going to say my goodbyes to you while I do this and I'm not paying attention so maybe I'll do better.
So next week, I'm going to be gone for a couple days. I'll see you guys on, uh, what's today?
What is today? What's today? Saturday? Sunday? Saturday. I'll see you guys on Tuesday and what
we're going to do is we're going to start the Outer Worlds. I'm going to just play. I've been
putting it off and putting it off and putting it off for a month. I've actually been putting it
off for a month. So that's what we're going to do. I have no idea how anything about the game. I
just know that it's the new Vegas guys. Is there a new video game? I can't believe you didn't die.
There's the guy with the gun here. He's right there. There he is.
There's his punk. All right, slow down. Give me this shit. Pick it all up. And look, here's
the thing. If Outer Worlds, if I don't like Outer Worlds, then I just won't play it.
It's that simple. You either like it or you don't. Okay, I have an opportunity here.
Okay, the strategy is shotgun. Whoa! There's somebody else. All right, I did it. I actually,
I finally did it. I can go to bed now. I can go to bed. I've done. I've done. I did my thing.
I'm going to cash out here. All right, this is who wants to be a millionaire. I got to the
$40,000 question. I just got it and I'm done. I'll take the money, please.
All right, I'm going to pick up the S. Not yet, though. I need ammo. Okay, good.
Let me just ammo. Five community subs. Thanks for the five community subs.
Near shoe. Thank you for that. What level is it? Oh, I, what did I? All right, that's it.
I had to do that. Getting to level 20 is where it really begins. Holy shit. I can't imagine
how hard that is. If you get past level 10, 12, 15. Oh, actually perfect time to stop. We're just
at about exactly almost six hours. Exactly what I thought it was going to be. So I will see you
guys again on Tuesday. We're going to do the outer world. Get to level 10. Oh, I can't. I'm
burnt up. I have to ash my body that is a cigarette right now. Like there's just,
you haven't ashed it. There's just dead cigarette for the entire length of the cigarette. You have
to ash it. I'm just dead. I'm a burnt out cigarette right now. That was a weird analogy. Can you tell
that I'm burnt up? What did I just say? I have a cigarette ash when you drag it all the way and
you add it, but I haven't been ashed. Uh, dusk was amazing. That was a really, really good game,
but I'm, uh, I'm spent. I'll see you guys in a couple of days for the outer worlds. If you
don't have dusk, see if you can beat my score. Level nine on endless mode of the farm. Put in
the comments if you got there and what is your favorite weapon? Please make, please give me
engagements. So there's like 30,000 comments in my comment section. What's your favorite ice cream?
Guaranteed to get like at least 15,000 comments, but I am out of here. I'll see you guys in a few
days. Thanks for watching. As always, it was a blast. That game is fucking great. Highly recommend
this. There's a lot of content too. That took a long time. That was six hours today.
What? Five and a half, four and a half hours yesterday. That's like a 10 hour game. I did not
expect it to be that long. Let's see what we got here. That's kind of loud. Yeah, I never,
I didn't try the challenge super impossible hard difficulty. I feel like I just wouldn't want to do
it. I would take, you take one damage and you just die. I feel like that would be angry at that game.
If you 100% every level, it's like 15 hours. That's a lot. I spent more time in dusk than I did
a lot of first AAA first party games that come out 12 hours. But yeah, uh, let's do the bits.
I'll see you guys in a few days. Thanks for watching. As always, let's get to it. Who's the
Oh, at the top bits. Let's see. Oh, look at that. Oh, look at that. Wait, is this real? It changed.
Is this for real? I don't think it was this from like three days ago. How could this be so incorrect?
I don't understand. I don't think that's right. But thank you to all of you. Anyways, let's go back to
a six hours ago. We had cream corn, thanks to 250. Hey, Germany, do you think we're going to get
another German awards on New Year's Eve? It was my favorite stream last year. Reminiscing with Chad
on the highlights of 2018 was a great way to close out the year. It'd be fun to do the same for 2019.
Yes, there's going to be another stream awards. Why not? It was fun. It's fun to look back on what
people nominate and what actually wins some of this stuff. Worst noise. I have in my mind what
the worst noise is. It's definitely going to win. There's no way it doesn't win. I can't even tell
you what it is. I don't want to influence any voting. But if this is selectable, there's 100%
no way that this loses to anything. It's making me laugh. Worst joke of the year taking vote. Yeah,
let's come up to the same categories. It should be a good time. Anyways, yes, it's in the plans.
But thank you for the 250. Thank you the plushie for the 500 bits. What's your opinion on pulp and
orange juice? Do not like. I don't want to do not like pulp in my orange juice.
I also don't like pulp and lemonade. I know that's some people say I like pulp and lemonade,
but not an orange juice. I disagree. Can you believe that they still sell heavy pulp?
That shit was so gross. You can buy lots of pulp. That stuff just sits up on the shelf.
Nobody buys that. No, you don't order orange juice like you order your peanut butter.
But that's just my opinion. It's actually kind of hard to find because nobody buys it.
I hate orange juice in my pulp. Well, that's weird. Jerma, you are a weak bitch.
Somebody time that person out, please. Just like 15 seconds is all I'm looking for for that one.
10 to 15 seconds so they can sit there and really think about what they just said to me.
No, because I agree. Hey, you're supposed to go to defy the king.
It ain't the king stream. It's not fucked the king yet. Not yet. No, I don't like pulp and
orange juice. Thank you, future gamer for the 250. What do you plan to do with Jerma985 and
second Jerma with the new Copa stuff? You could get fined like $40,000 per video if they decide
that you do not properly label your video as for kids. What? None of my videos are for kids.
I feel like even TF2 videos could be interpreted as for kids just off the thumbnail of a colorful
character. I'm not going to get fined $400,000. It might be a good idea just to label all of them
as for kids as a precaution. I mean, not for kids. Here's why that is not going to ever happen.
Because what about the guy that uploaded a video nine years ago and he doesn't even know the
password to his account anymore and it's not for kids and he doesn't even remember making the video
and they're gonna find that guy $40,000. Fuck him. He goes to jail. No, YouTube is just,
YouTube is a mess. You want to make a billion dollars? Anybody in here want to make like
$500 million? Raise your hand. Would you like to? I can tell you how. Just make a YouTube competitor
that is only for children. Only. Not YouTube kids. No, no. Just like a children's learning
center that's just all videos and you can just make educational videos for kids
video streaming site. If they're so concerned about this, why don't they have YouTube kids
be a separate uploader? If that's such a huge concern, separate the uploading. Make it so you
have to upload a video to YouTube kids. Why should I? Why would I upload videos just to
YouTube and like, Oh, whatever. I don't know. Who knows? But I think I saw somebody talking
about this the other day. And by the other day, I mean, it could have been anywhere within the
last three months that if you want to go through all of the videos you've ever made and make changes
to them, you're talking about dozens and dozens and dozens and dozens and dozens of hours straight
just to check a box. It would take forever. It would probably take you like 30 to 40, 50 plus
hours just to check those boxes across. Like if you had thousands of videos, they just want you
to label your videos for not for kids. I, yeah, guess what? Smoking is not for kids either.
Somehow they end up doing it. What? How do you, how do I stop that? Endorsing, not about endorsing
child smoking. I'm just saying like, how do I prevent someone from not clicking on a video?
You know, kids aren't supposed to swear, but they do. If I upload a video to YouTube, I mean,
oh yeah, I guess this video is not for kids. Go to your favorite porn website right now.
Is there a thing that says, excuse me, you're not allowed to be here? Yeah, click. What? That's all,
that's the only thing that exists there. So what you're saying is we should blame the children.
No, no, I'm just saying like, I don't, I don't know who's could or couldn't be watching my videos.
If I'm going to get like fined in quotes or whatever for somebody watching a video of mine
from like seven years ago, I don't have any control over that. Should I just label my whole
channel like not for kids? I guess I could just do that. I don't want you to, yeah, I just don't
want to get fined. I have to look into this because that just seems strange. What about when, okay,
so what about when HBO shows a rerun of the Sopranos on your cable network and your kids
in the room and you don't know that they're watching it? Do we fine HBO? HBO? How, what the
fuck? It's all about the data collection. It's about advertising to kids, not kids seeing bad
stuff. See, I think they just fucked it up from the very beginning instead of just separating it
out completely from the very beginning because now you retroactively have billions of videos
that are not suitable for anybody that just exist. It's about kids, it's about kids seeing
completely shitty content. Oh, you're fucked, dude. But regardless, I don't know, I don't think
I'm going to get in any trouble for it. I'm going to have to like talk to Mac and go check on the
channel or something and see what I would have to do. I don't know what I would even have to do.
Watch VA ends up with like a hundred thousand dollar fine. I don't know, we'll find out. We'll
see. I don't think it's going to be that big of an issue. We'll see though. But let's move on.
Interesting thought, interesting conversation though. Thank you, future gamer. Appreciate it.
Propnator, thanks for the 1500 bits. I hope this is enough for a hangry pizza. I love pizza.
It definitely is enough. I will absolutely use that for a pizza. Thank you so much for the 1500
bits. Appreciate that. Emmanuel Depressed, thanks for the 300 bits. I originally thought you had
peaked with Shpee, but after long consideration, I've decided you have now peaked with Omega Pig.
Omega Pig. True? What do you mean, true? Spooky Spitfire, thanks for the 250. First,
this is a pretty interesting game. Second, I just had to spend like 60 or 70 dollars on the binding
of Isaac. Rebirth and afterbirth, because PSN sucks ass. Do you have any recommendations aside from
like never buying stuff from the PSN? You're covering a lot of bases on that one, so
that's all the advice I have. Why is it that much? 70 dollars? Is it really 70 bucks for everything
on PSN? It seems like a lot. They don't have a complete edition. Probably not from the US. Oh,
right, right. They probably had to buy it like three times. That's not good. Well, I'm sorry
to hear that, but thanks for the 255. Appreciate it. It's a great game. If this is the first time
you buy it, because that's a decade worth of content. That game is so much fun. Enjoy it.
Hole of one zombie, thanks for the 300 bits. Have you ever thought about playing System Shock 2?
I don't know how to put it other than your streams are hilarious. I think it'd be awesome
to see it get the German 985 treatment. German one guy. I've heard that's a very good game.
Put it on the list. Thanks for the 300 bits. Spooky Spitfire, thanks for the 250. German Isaac felt
bad for me, and on my second Judas run, I got super mush chocolate milk and then fucking brim
in the first two floors. On the third floor, I got Tammy set, so I basically... Wait, hold on.
What's going on? Isaac? This is two different people with two different Isaac stories.
You guys should talk to each other. No, it's not. The same person. This is the same person.
Why is it listed as a different person here? It's the same person. Why are you a different
person on my list here? What? Hold on. It's, yeah, twice right here. Okay, I had to refresh.
That was quick. For a second, I was like, holy shit, you guys are like, you guys should talk
to each other. Anyways, every single boss and floor, including Satan, it was beautiful.
You just bought the game and you did that? Well, you've ruined the whole game for the
rest of the time. You can never play Binding of Isaac ever again now. It'll never feel the same.
You have to do that again. You're gonna get to Satan with like the magician tears,
and you're gonna be really mad about it. There are plenty of broken builds. I know,
I'm just fucking around. Give it the German 985 treatment. What? What are you talking about?
Thank you. That's really cool to hear. If that's the first time you really played it.
I will sit up there. That sounds, thank you. I have my first job interview tomorrow and I'll
give you more money through a sub if I get the job. Hope you get it. Not for my sake at all,
but for yours. I'm happy to be your favorite content creator. Thank you.
Good luck. You're gonna, you'll be fine. You're gonna get the job. Don't worry. Thank you.
Creamcorn, thanks for the 250. Germo, what's the lore behind you getting TTS to say Michael
instead of singing it yourself? I think I explained it before. It's, it's a joke about those
tapes you could buy where it just says the kid's name. It sings a birthday song and you can get a
specialized custom. Oh, look, let's say you have a kid and the kid's name is just John, right?
It was a tape you could buy that you put in and they had like a hundred of them. John, Jack,
Jerry, Jeremy. And all it did was it sang the same song and just replaced the kid's name
with whatever name of the tape that you purchased. So you felt so special when you're on your
birthday because it was, hey, Jeremy, it's your birthday. Hey, Jeremy. And it was like,
they're talking about me. They're talking, that's, they're talking about me right now.
I think they still exist. They're on YouTube now. Go type in like birthday song for David.
The same thing will happen for instance. Okay. This one I just typed in is this
exactly what I was talking about. Let's see what happens. I mean, this one's way cool,
but you get the idea. Here you go. Here you go. Here's enough.
Okay. Cool. That was good. I wonder, I wonder what happens if I click on this one.
Happy birthday, Tyler. What about this one?
Happy birthday, Justin. How about this one? They're all the same.
There's another one. Completely different YouTube channel. Completely different channel.
Now you see in the world of YouTube, you can make these and technology has gotten a lot better.
But back in the day, they just had one recording of the song and the guy would be in the studio
and just say a hundred names and they would put that one piece in there. I'm not sure why
they would do it that way. The guy didn't sing the song a thousand times. He just said a thousand
names and sang the same song once. I think these, I think the people are actually singing the whole
song every time, or it's very good editing. Uh, this is another, this is another channel, I think.
It's cheaper and faster. That's right. Happy birthday, Gladys. So there you are. That's what,
that's what it was. Let's see. Me? What? They're talking about me. And the kid would lose their
mind because they thought that it was talking to them. It's the same reason why Dora was,
oh, do you know where it is? Yeah, I do. You're talking to me through the screen. You just don't,
what, you're like fucking seven. You're six. What the hell do you know? Let's get the credits on
screen. Roll them. Hey, it's really good. Those are YouTube kids friendly, right? They don't have to
do anything, right? Thanks for subbing everybody. If you still think people are talking to you
through the screen and you're seven, you're not the brightest kid. I, I'm, I know I'm just using
like a random young kid number. Let's just say four or three. Yeah. Seven is like second grade,
isn't it? They're talking to me still. Yeah. You're probably old enough to know that that's not
really happening, but that would thank you cream corn for the two 50. There's your explanation.
That's, I think I talked about it before, but that's what it's from door cube. Thanks for the
two 50. I met an internet friend in real life today because it turns out we both go to the same
school. That's a small world. We had no idea until recently. Anyways, he's also a big fan of you.
Don't ever tell me the odds. That's really interesting. Both go to the same school and
both watch this channel. Uh, he hasn't had the chance to watch recently. If you're watching
tonight, fluke, I hope you're able to make it through final with flying colors. Hope you did.
Thanks a lot. Uh, that's, that's a really, really interesting story actually.
That's really cool to know. Thank you. Gnarly for the two 50. Glad to hear you're going to play
outer worlds. I just beat it and had fun with it. Just so you know, chat will probably pressure you
into doing a low intelligence run. Honestly, it's not that much of a detriment, so you can do it.
If you think it might be fun for a while, I don't know. I'm, I'm going to, we'll just see what
happens. Let's see what happened. Caught up at near shoe. Thanks for the five subs. Son of genova.
Thanks for the two 50. Hey, German wanted to ask you to play blood fresh supply. It's a remaster of
an old dos FPS. I actually, when I was looking at a medieval, it's another one I was looking at
and doom also the original doom, but improved. Hypo was telling me about his ways to make it
in widescreen and better. So it is not as fuel-conducing as it could be now. We were
going to talk about and see. We'll take a look. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Hey, snoozing copter. Thanks
for the two 50 German. How are you? We're friends, right? And friends borrow each other's money,
right? Can you lend me $2 and 50 cents? I could really need it. Thanks.
Well, I have no way. I have no way to send this back to you. Also, I heard you wanted to play
death stranding off stream. Did you? What's your opinion? My opinion. I'll give you the real one.
The real opinion. I am. Yeah. I'm not going to play death stranding on stream. It's too long
for me to want to play it on stream. I think it's like a 40 plus hour experience.
And I don't the gameplay looks fun. It looks cool, but I don't think I want to do that for
30 hours. I've heard it's fantastic though, but that's something I probably would do in my own
leisure time. Even if I don't know, maybe I don't even have enough time to even sit down and play
I tried to play through God of War off stream and I got to maybe 10, 12 hours in and
almost 15 hours in and I kind of stopped there. I could see playing death stranding,
pick it up once a week and play it for a couple hours and just deliver some packages and do that
for a long time until the game's done. That you won't see it on stream. I don't think so. Not at
all. But thank you, snoozing copter. Thank you. Dragon breath. Thanks for the 250. Hi, I wanted
to say that I'm surprised you never touched Noita. It's a 2D rogue light with pixel sand physics.
I feel like it's right up your alley. Sorry, I'm outside the realm of the recommended channel,
so please don't smite me. I just like the game a lot. Also, does anyone else hear birthday music
or am I going crazy? I've heard it's very good, but I don't know if I'll stream it. Not now,
maybe. There's a lot coming up here. There's a lot coming up in the next few weeks. Maybe,
maybe soon. Maybe in the new year. 5G birthday? But I appreciate it, though. Maybe you'll see
that somewhere in like early 2020. That's one of those games that's going to be forever on the
list until I get bullied into playing it. But I do want to. And finally, Spooky Spitfire.
Back again here with 250. Thank you, Spooky. Well, he transitioned to the end of the stream.
Just an FYI, I've gotten every achievement pre-afterbirth in Isaac on my computer. Oh,
okay. There we go. But it's currently broken. So I was just like, dude, what do you mean this
run is god tier? LOL. Also, I know it's old and you have already played it on stream,
but chat is nuts and forced you to quit it early. But you should beat Hollow Knight off stream.
Tell me how the path of pain treats you. Hollow Knight was good. But Hollow Knight was, that was
also kind of back when I never streamed a game more than once or twice in a row. The new one's
coming out soon, too. It was really good. Yeah, I know. It's just lost forever. Soon? Is it not
soon? Wasn't it 2020? Like early 2020? It's TBA. Oh, okay. Well, we'll see when it comes up.
But I probably will end up just because I have to play through Hollow Knight before I do the
sequel. And you can't just, wait, you're gonna watch, you're gonna watch the movie's sequel
before you see the movie's prequel? What? No, the movie's sequel before you watch the first one.
Of course, you would watch the sequel before the, well, did the prequel come up?
When did the prequel come up? If there was a visual representation of my brain right now,
it would be a single hair in a giant dark room. And on the tip of the hair is a little
flake of fire just about to go out. Just, and that's, six hours ago, it was a blaze in there.
There was a wood stacked up really high. Playing games like that just drain me. They drain my whole
fucking psyche. What are my thoughts on the Mandalorian? I think it's amazing. I think it's
some of the best Star Wars content we've gotten this decade. I think it's fantastic. Real shit?
Yeah, no, I really do. I think it was really, really good.
Spoilers? No, don't say spoilers. Let people enjoy it because it's great. But that's my time.
I'll see you guys soon. Thanks for watching. Thanks for sticking out dusk with me.
It was very, very good. Highly recommend. If you don't have it, go get it. It's a great game.
I will see you guys in a few days for The Outer Worlds. We'll just play through it. I will see
if I like it. If we don't like it, then we're going to play that fucking YouTuber hand simulator game.
I think I'll like it though. Good night guys. See you soon. Have a fantastic rest of your weekend.