No, you see, I pocket medic you all the time. It's time for you to pocket medic me.
Have you ever been pocket medic by like a god?
Can't say that I have.
So we're going up here?
And then where to? Where to, Master?
No, you're the soldier, you're the leader.
Alright, but that's not what you said last time.
So I'm just gonna have you lead us to doors that don't open. Oh my god.
I was gonna say something before you got there too, but I just wanted to make sure you're like, don't know what you're doing.
Hold on, hold on. Okay, we have to go up here.
Come on up here.
Don't pop it. Don't pop it.
Don't pop it.
Hold on to it. Don't pop it.
Not only is there gonna need to be a scenario where there's a lot of people, but I'm also gonna have to believe you can kill them, which might not happen.
Don't pop it.
I'm not. Kill the sniper before he shoots me in the head.
He's not gonna. I got him.
Don't pop it.
Alright, what I need to do here is I need you to pop it.
There it is.
Oh, I got him.
Don't worry. I'll take care of my medic friend.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, damn. What's that? More crits.
Look out for the sticky.
I'm trying to like help you.
I shot.
Wow. Good miss.
Alright, pop it.
Pop it. Come on.
You didn't even see him.
I was waiting for him to backstab you and you accidentally kill a dude.
I can't believe I accidentally just killed that guy.
He's up top.
Come over here.
I don't want you to die.
You think I'm gonna die?
That's cute.
Alright, you ready?
Oh, shit.
I like that first rocket straight into the ground.
What about that rocket? You like that one?
Now we do this.
Come here, cupcake.
No one ever goes out of that door, you know.
What happened? Look at the kill feed.
Did you kill what?
What happened? Who killed me?
He's fucking messy here, by the way.
Get a fucking comb.
Would you comb me here with a Snickers bar today, medic?
Fine, I'm going back to spawn and change.
No, no, no, no. Come back.
I'm sorry. That was mean.
No, changing it.
No, don't. It looks nice.
Doesn't look all messy. It looks fine.
Oh, he died.
Aim indoor and fire crit rockets indoor.
Stand in front of the door.
Here comes a guy. Use it.
Kill him. No, just kill him.
Face to the door. Not him.
Wait, don't shoot.
Next time it opens.
No, they're going to open it again.
This is a suck.
Let's go build it again. Let's go.
Don't kill him.
What do you mean don't kill him?
I mean, because I can ubersaw and I would have got it.
I'm going to die.
Are you going to die?
No, boy, they know, they know, they know.
They're like pushing down here now.
Run, run.
You have to commit to the joke, Star. Don't you know how that works?
Hide down here.
Do you have a shotgun?
How come you never use it?
I do. What are you talking about?
I've never seen you use it.
Oh yeah, you killed that spy, but that was like a joke too.
No.
Wait, they're right there.
Nobody ever comes through here though.
Oh my god, you're such an idiot.
That's what I was warning you about.
You were looking down that hallway.
Favorite movie. What would you say?
Favorite movie. I saw Amelie recently.
It was really good. But my favorite movie is probably Coraline.
Have you seen The Life of Pi?
Isn't it P?
No, it's Pi. It's pretty good.
You'd probably like it.
It's an interesting story.
Wait, after they cap it.
See, no, they got denied.
Okay, okay, you know what?
Yeah, after they cap it, because then they'll all sort of group up there and start pushing it.
That's sort of what happens.
Yeah.
He did not want that.
Oh, that was great.
Can they please push the fucking cart?
Did you just say did the tiger fart?
Yeah, I don't know.
Like, there's a part in the movie where it's a serious movie the whole way.
And then they're on the boat and the tiger just...
And like, PiPi looks over at him and is just like...
You're really going to do that?
You think they're going to fart on my boat?
You ever think they're going to fart on the boat?
Wouldn't it be funny if Burger Boy farted on your boat?
Wouldn't it be funny if Burger Boy farted on the boat?
I'm just taking a peek.
That would be funny.
No, if you take one peek, I would have laughed my ass off if you got headshot or something.
Just for no reason.
You turn the corner and immediately get dropped.
Are you trying to tell me that that medic that came in here didn't go tell all his friends that we were in here?
This guy.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
I got him, I got him.
I just freaked out and killed that guy.
There's a medic with Uber around this corner.
No, he's dead.
I freaked out, dude.
This guy has given us away.
Get the hell out of here, guy.
Fine, I'll high five you.
I didn't even work.
I can't even high five him.
He's stuck on the hill.
We agreed, we're waiting until they get the coffee part.
And we're going with this crits.
Because we're corner creeps.
Do you know how to corner creep?
Have you ever corner creeped before in your life?
I got arrested.
Okay, this is really boring.
No, I'm committed to this now.
I am committed.
I'm not going to leave.
When you go to do something, you do it to completion.
I'm hiding, I'm crouching.
You're looking around, I'm twitching.
And there's this one same person.
Here comes the Pyro.
Well, he's dead.
If you die to him, I will never forgive you.
I'm not going to die to him.
Let's just freak somebody out.
When their spawn door opens, we just pop.
How about that?
You're so bad.
Behind you, I'm going to die.
That's not behind you.
Oh my god.
Did you not get a kill?