Do you trade carnival?
Do you trade carnival? It's my favorite map.
You can just turn on the weird, don't you?
No, I have to be in the mood, don't you know? I have to be in the mood to make videos. Do you understand that?
I have to be in the mood. For you.
Hey, did you see that top comment?
German wants to be in the mood for starting well.
Look at all these snipers, dude. Oh, baby. This is how we do a little bit of shlob.
Wow, did you just kill a sniper who was standing still?
Shut the fuck up. I didn't see you kill him.
Yeah, because I wasn't in the game.
Look, I don't need to take advice from you, okay? You give terrible advice. Your advice is for the fucking birds, okay?
What do you mean my advice is for the birds?
If I was a bird, I would take advice from you. That's what I'm saying.
What kind of advice do you give to a bird, is what I'm saying.
I've never heard birds in your background before, and you just got all these birds going...
I've got this window open.
Do you want some advice for the birds? Shut your fucking window.
The plan is to be lob shlobs inside of their vent.
Do you know what that means?
I don't know what that means. No one knows what that means.
Don't get headshot.
Yeah, I don't know how to do that.
So stand right here.
Right here?
Right here.
Okay.
Oh my god, you have the worst plan.
There's no way they could get behind us, because we're blocking off the only entrance.
Yeah, we're blocking the entrance.
Where a lot of people are actively playing the game.
Welcome to the lob shlob den.
I can just...
You know that spy. That spy is going to come around for sure.
But there is something to be said, though. Whoever comes down this hall...
You're supposed to be...
I almost died because you didn't follow the technique.
Well, let's go get you a health kit.
Oh my god.
You better get him.
He's got a lock and load. He's not lob shlobbing like you.
Nice.
Have you heard of any good movies that came out recently?
Look at this. Look behind you.
We have an entire brigade of people just sitting in this vent.
Oh, before it was me and you, it was a duo, but now it's a brigade.
We had two people with brigade status.
Look at this.
Are we for real right now?
We got the one guy on red just sitting back there.
So what I'm going to do... You know what? I'm going to better...
I'm just going to go spectate after.
We're going to do this once or twice, and then I'm going to spectate.
Hey, quit headshotting people.
Hey. Hey, stop it.
This guy's just getting like free kills.
All right, so ready. Everyone on red, stuff back here.
We all have to be stuffed in the corner.
This is not going to happen, man.
All right, you guys ready?
Everyone with the default grenade launcher on the count of three.
On the count of three, start lobbing.
One, two, three.
Hold on, hold on.
Yeah, there we go.
There we go. There we go.
Good, good, good, good, good.
You ready?
So in three seconds, I'm going to count down, start doing the lob-slob.
You guys ready?
Three, two, one.
Go for it.
It's like two people just kind of came in afterwards.
Whoever holds this wins.
I'm going to do my own timer.
Whoever holds this, whoever has the most people in here on red team or blue team wins.
And you can only use the grenade launcher.
This is like, this is just, this is ridiculous.
Nobody can even do anything.
You might as well just stand at the very back and just lob into the side.
This one guy.
I wish you guys could see what this looks like.
This is just not even cool.
This is just so stupid.
Okay, let's all be spies.
Yeah, who brings a pyro to a bar fight, to a knife fight?
Come on, man.
Yeah, he wants to kick, he wants to get kicked.
He said he wants to get kicked.
I'm not going to do it.
I'm not going to.
Nice.
Three, two, one.
Knife fight.
This is going to last forever.
Why has nobody died?
Oh, I got taunt killed.
Did anybody on blue die?
Did you see that taunt kill?
I'm really surprised this actually really works.
Okay, you guys ready?
Here I am.
I'm going to go for it.
Let's see how many people, if I can get you guys.
Oh my God.
I can't believe that that works.
Wow.
That's, I got at least five or six people.
Yeah, that's so cool.
I'm just farming my strange.
Sorry, guys.