Hello. Is he live? It's not showing up for me. What up? I'm here. Refresh.
Hey, ready? Just see. Good afternoon, guys. How you doing? We have actually quite a few things to
talk about before we go forward with this, uh, this Tuesday. That's right. We're playing DOS today,
but stuff to discuss. Most important thing number one is a lot of people are gonna be
not happy about this, but I have to say it. You know, I'll wait. I'm gonna wait. I'll wait to
disappoint a shitload of people when we will lie for at least two or three minutes. I'm about to
disappoint everybody. Well, maybe not. No, maybe not. You got to tell us now. Just hold on. Hold
on. I'll tell you in a second. No, I'm not moving platforms. Why would I open up a stream like that?
Oh, hey guys. Uh, Gerber here. I just want to say I'm going to disappoint the fuck out of everybody
here. Wouldn't I do? I at least have to be like, Hey guys, move into X, move into Y, come on over.
I, why would I start with, Hey, you guys are going to be really disappointed in me.
So, um, all right. Well, it's been enough time. We've got like 6,000 people. That's fine. So, uh,
just say it, just get it out. I'm going to, I'm going to breathe in once and I'm going to say it.
The green screen stream is delayed. There you go. Okay. It's done. Uh, sorry. Uh, there's a reason
for it over the last like week and a half or so since this diagnosis, I've been doing stretches
and I've been doing some exercises to help target the issue that I have in my back and chest.
It has shrunk my mobility down pretty low. I'm very sore and I can't really move around
and like do a bunch of crazy shit, standing up and moving around and stuff.
So that's the reason why, uh, hopefully over the next few weeks that I could loosen up a little
and I'll get there. So it's still going to happen. I just need to loosen up a bit
because right now, uh, these exact exercises and stretches that I'm doing,
it like kind of hurts to breathe in all the way and like turn and look.
So there's no way I'm going to be like, here we go. Well, look at me,
here we get in front of the green screen. It's just not going to happen. But Hey, here,
babe, hold on. Let me immediately make you, make you happy again. Hold on here. Time to turn that
around. Uh, the Minecraft stream is still on pace for the 15th. So that's good. And that's
some good news. Actually, I'm going to be testing out the server either tonight or tomorrow. I'm
going to do some stress testing to it. We're going to fuck around with it. It's going to be
a fun experiment. Now that that's out of the way, that's a POG for me. Yeah. So that's out of the
way. Let's, uh, let's get to it. Those of you that are new to the channel, be like,
but like four months ago, four or five months ago, we used to play dos games once a week
lasted for three or four weeks in a row. And I'm going to do it again because a shitload
more games have been added to this archive list, like thousands of them. So I just went to sort
by newest additions and then we're just going to go take a look. Here's another little problem
with this stream today though. Um, there are, there are some pornography thumbnails, so just
got to be careful. I'm going to skim them first. Newest addition does not mean also censored,
but I actually, I already have a few queued up here. Uh, and by a few, I mean a lot because I
also went back and picked out some of the ones that we didn't do, but ones that I maybe should
have spent more time in some of the more popular ones. I know this is not one of them, but, uh,
let's just get to it. This first one, after we talk about turkeys, five community turkey subs,
happy Thanksgiving turkey and Zorro. Thank you for the five community subs, both of you
back to back. Let's go. This first one is, I don't know how long I'm going to play for,
but we'll see. Uh, the first one was called make a monster. This is the monster maker.
Make a monster, write a monster myth in your monster museum. So this one's going to be
fucking real exciting. All right, make a monster. Is there no sound in this one?
No background, background one, background two. We'll do background three. Use the right mouse
button or the space bar to view backgrounds. Use left mouse button or the enter key to choose a
background. I like that one. Oh, coming out of the spaceship. That's pretty good. Inside the
spaceship on the planet. Why is that? Why do they all have to be from a different planet? Why can
it be from earth? All right. I like this one. All right. How about bodies? Let's see. Bubbles, ears,
eyes, headgear, kids. What is, what is kids? Why would it be a kid? Is this, is this is clip art?
Okay. Here. How do I get away? How do I get out of kids? How do I get out of this menu? How do I
get out of here? Can you make it smaller? I, I don't think so. Oh shit. Make it bigger. You can't.
Is it escape tab? Oh, there we go. It's back, backspace. No, no, no. All right. We're learning
here. Ooh, I just accidentally space or right mouse, but view clip art. It actually is clip art.
View previous. Move clip art. One to nine. Change distance. Clip art is moved. Backspace removed.
V is flip. H is flip. S toggles shadow. C select clip art shadow. F1 help escape exit.
Oh, okay. So, uh, we're going to have to, we're going to have to lower it out. We have to lower
it up. And I, if I just leaked the rest of the fucking games, who cares? You didn't even look,
don't look up there. Don't peek at your presence. All right. Let's do, uh, legs one.
No, I need body. Actually, I kind of like this one.
All right. How about headgear? Lego hair. I'm just going to stay out of the menu. It doesn't
really matter. I got to bring this down. Is that a clown nose? Okay. That's like a clown horn.
Uh, okay. So you got a clown horn. Let's do, what about arms? Mouths? All right. Hold on. Arms too.
Okay. I'm not going to lie. I actually kind of like this game. All right. That one.
What was, what's this one? Hold on. No, no, no, no, no. Back, back, back, back, back.
Look at how easily entertained he is. Am I? Look, he's going up there to honk the nose.
This is so stupid. You're right. This sucks, but who cares? I'm having fun. The tabs,
Jerma, the tabs. It's, it's already leaked. What do you, you, what? I'm going to pretend it didn't
leak? Erasers. What does that mean? This is, what is it? A watermelon? What is this?
Big dog ears? Is that a mustache? I don't understand. Crop the browser. Well, here's the
thing. I can't. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. You know what? I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't. All right.
I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't. All right. I can't, I can't,
I can't. Hold on. There. There we go. Okay. No, this doesn't work. All right. Yeah. He'll have
like a, he'll have a Polaroid camera. No, no. I don't like any of these. None of them. Don't
want any of them. Eyes. I like these. It's like sonic eyes. These are 10 new emotes coming up.
No, that's not true. Should I, what, what, the infected eyes? What do you think?
Hey, Jeff, thanks for the five community subs, Jeff. Thanks a lot, Jeff. These aren't bad.
There's a lot of eyes. I would have so much fun playing with this if I was a kid.
Okay. Done. Now what about, what is bubbles supposed to be? Well, like they were in like a bath.
I don't understand. Like, oh, thought bubbles. Okay. All right. How about what else is up here?
All right. We're good. Done. Okay. Done. Now say edit speech. What do you mean edit speech?
Press tab to switch between words. Say ASDF to hear your word. Add new word. Say as what?
Select text. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Change speech. Edit speech. Alt H. Turn on.
Spell the word. Say the word. Say the page. Okay. Whoa. What happened? What happened? Where do we go?
What? Did it open a new tab? Oh, no. Google. Google.com. Ouch. There's so much info on this
screen. Fuck. These are all the cards I sent out. We know you use Chrome. I have to use Chrome. It's
easily. Hold on. There we go. How do I get it to say the words? Say it. Alt W. Now Alt T is saved.
I'm not, I don't know how to press Alt W. What does Alt W do? What does Alt W do? Because I,
Ctrl T opens new random tab. Alt W does what now? All right. How do I? Where's help?
Alt W say the word. Alt S spell. Alt T. Change speech. Let's do change speech. Oh my God.
Come on. Say it. Do something. We need to hear this. Do the roar. Do the roar.
It's Ctrl W? No, it's not. It's Alt W. Move the cursor over the word to. Okay. Hold on.
Type in, what does Alt W do in Chrome? What does Alt W do? It's Ctrl W? It depends on your add-ons.
It presses Alt W.
It closes the tab. It doesn't do anything. God damn it. Alt W. No. Oh well. We could have got a funny
voice out of this one. Alt T. I did Alt T. It opened up another Google tab. All right. Oh well.
Alt. Yeah. Well, what else? Yeah. All right. Let's get out of this one. All right. This one sucks.
When did I mute? Oh, it's this Mario. It's okay. This kind of hurts my ears. You unmuted the whole
stream. That would suck. Why would you need 80 lives? 80. Okay. Well, now we only have 79 lives
left. What are we going to do? The game is hard. Can I just get one enemy killed? Aren't they
lobsters? Well, no. They're lobsters or crabs in one of the games. That's not made up. Yes. Yes,
I'm correct. I know. That's a fucked up pixel. That was stupid. I hit it. I actually hit it.
You even saw the thing go up. You can't actually see it. All right. This is not like Mario Galaxy
that has the mini game that they've... You know what? I'm not even going to explain it. I just
got so angry that I couldn't even explain what I was trying to say. Long story short, it's fucking
hard to control. And I was about to go off on like a rant about how they've remade this like
10 times. This is the VGA version. I got stuck. I got mad stuck. I was just like...
I'm playing gold next. Uh, okay. EGA? CGA? Tandy! What is the Hercules graphics adapter? Should
I do the Hercules? Does that mean it's the best one? All right. Hercules. Uh, I can't do any of
these. Why can't I not do any of them? Click on the screen? Yeah. That doesn't... It's not doing
anything. Numpad? No. Numpad's not working either. All right. How do I do it? Golden Axe is a...
Golden Axe. Golden Axe. Golden Axe. Golden Axe. Golden Axe. One... First player use WASD. Great
job. Here are a few things. Important. Entering one. Command prompt. Faded color password controls.
Change the... That's probably why it has 200,000 views and only 400 favorites.
Okay. Yeah, the numpad doesn't do anything. I pressed every... I pressed every number on my
whole keyboard. It was archived a month ago. What the hell's going on? Hold on. Let me like... Let
me refresh the page. Got it. Oh, that looks horrible. What did I press? Please open your
manual to page four. Find the word in the lower right and type it below. God damn it! What is it?
Somebody has it down here. Type any word to get through the password request. Seriously? Okay.
Oh, we're going to do arcade. This looks like when Game Boy decided
they were going to put color on Game Boy. Okay. Okay. Every button on the keyboard doesn't work.
Only... How does left and right work but not anything else? What? What are the controls?
W... Up... W-X-A-D? S is attack. Q diagonal... Q-E-Z-C. Tab... Okay. So it's S. Tab is jump.
All right, dude. What the fuck is going on here? This one don't work.
RT Game Crowd just came in with a huge raid right now. What's up, dude? Thanks for the raid!
Welcome, everybody. We're currently reading the manual. It's an exciting stream here today.
Reading the manual for how to press enter in a 25-year-old video game. I'm not sure what you're
up to, but thanks for the raid. Welcome, everybody. Exciting shit today. Okay. Now, can we see some...
Can we see some fucking pogchamps with the chaplains? First play WASD. Great. Great job.
All right, but how do I... On the modern keyboard is a... Fuck it. We gotta go... We
just had a raid coming. We gotta go number munchers right now. Like, I can't fucking stall. Yeah.
Number munchers. All right. Play number munchers. Hall of Fame. Let's go to options.
Difficulty level. Third grade. There. It goes up to eighth grade. Wait. Wait. Hold on. How many
grades are there? Third, third, fourth, fourth, fifth, fifth, sixth, sixth. Oh, advanced and easy.
All right. Let's do third grade. Set content. Multiply. Multiples. Use... Challenge. Yeah,
whatever. It doesn't matter. We'll just go with the default. Okay. Erase Hall of Fame. All right.
We're good. Play number munchers. Do you want instructions? Yeah. Just to give you a quick
little refresher. Our hero number muncher. Munchies Digits. Munchi... Munchicus Digitus.
This is Regis, Smarties, Bashfuls, Workers, and Helpers. We have to be careful of these.
All right. To call timeout and freeze the game, press enter key. Press it again to resume play.
There. The squares. Okay. Playing number... Use the arrow keys to move them into muncher.
You must... You could also use... Yeah, yeah, yeah. Spacebar to eat a number. Yep. You may want to
quit in the middle of a game. If so, pressing the escape key will end the game. Imagine rage
quitting number munchers. Okay. Let's go. Equality. Two times... What does it want to do? E... What...
What... Equals one. This one equals one. This one equals one. This is really easy. Which one
of these equals one? I'm only in the third grade. All right. What am I missing? Equals one. Nine
divided by nine. Eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one. That's it. That's it. That's it.
Oh. He's actually struggling. No, I'm not actually struggling. I'm actually just... I win. All right.
What... What equals two? Two times nothing. Two. One. Two. Two. Two. Two. Got it. Got it.
One times two is two. Why are you giving me the answer? I should know this. Oh, no. He's eating
them. All right. Equals two. Equals two. Two divided by one is... That doesn't... That's a... That's a
.5. That's not even right. Six divided by three. That's gonna be three divided by six. Doesn't make
any sense. No, that's one. Don't... It's trying to fool me. Four. Eight. Twelve. Six. That's six.
Three. One plus... There it is. I thought that was a times. Two divided by... Got it. Equals three. Yeah,
put me in the fucking third grade. I would destroy this. Well, yeah. That's... That's Mr. Albertson.
See, he stayed back 25 years. He's incredibly disruptive. We're in three minus zero. That's...
You can't do that. Hey, Teach, you can't do that. Mr. Albertson, please. Just play your video game.
Oh, a video game? Almost got killed. Almost got killed. All right. I'm gonna go to, like, the eighth
grade after this and see how it is. Three divided by one. Three minus zero. That's just... Right? I
thought it was... Why are we talking negative numbers here? What the fuck? Zero minus three is
negative three. Whatever it is. I don't know. Who cares? Mr. Albertson. Yeah. What is it?
You can't just open Doritos in class. Why not? Shit, what the fuck you teach? Oh, that's two.
Four A12. That's four. No, that's two. Damn it. There it is. I did it. What the fuck was that?
What just happened? Why was that happening? Did I skip the cut scene? No, I didn't.
I didn't skip the cut scene. Don't eat my shit. Get out of here.
Uh, this is actually going to get very, very embarrassing in about two more levels or so.
You're gonna see just how long I've been out of school for. And that's the thing. I know a
lot of you guys say, how does he fuck this up? I know all this. I have not been in a classroom
in almost in 20 years. You know what I mean? Like you, you may have been in a classroom like
yesterday. I haven't been in a classroom in like 15 fucking years. You know, I don't think about
this shit. I don't think about like what 36 divided by nine is. What do I care? Once we get,
once we get to the hard ones, I'm going to, it's going to be guessing. Four divided by four is one
three. No, three, six, nine, 12. There it is. Five. Okay. This five, 10, 20, 20. Okay. 25 is
the one that's okay. This is going to get ugly. It's going to get actually very ugly. What? Oh,
I pressed the wrong button. No, I didn't, I wanted to get,
I didn't make it out of the third grade. You got to,
no, I don't want that to be listed. No, I don't want to play that again. Let's do this one.
Okay. We're going to do, we'll do equality again. No, no, no. I know. I want to, I got to go harder.
Yeah. Hold on options. Difficulty third grade advanced this time. So this is, I'm, I'm sitting
at like the front of the classroom, paying attention to everything the teacher is doing.
Let's see what advanced third grade is. I think I could do this. I'm pretty, I think I'll be okay.
I think so. What's your superpower? I can fly. Cool. That's like a Superman thing. What's your
superpower? I can manipulate water. Nice. What's your superpower? Advanced third grade. Oh,
good, good, good, good, good, good. Multiples. Oh no. I don't even know what any of this is.
Oh, by the way, just to like give you guys some, some lore here. I don't know how to do
fractions. I pretended to the entire time I was in school, I got almost every math test, like
an F on every single fractions. I didn't even care to learn it. When there is a recipe that calls
for like one seventh of something or like two sixth or like tooth. I have no idea. I need a cup
to tell me. I, I got like zeros on every single test. That was a fraction. I don't even do them.
I don't even use them. I, I work in whole numbers. Okay. Let's just do multiples,
multiples of two. Oh, this is the fucking easiest thing you could have done all day.
Let me time out. That's not two. Oops. It's okay. The controls are a little weird. I
there's no, I'm not. Why would I do that? Why would I ever hit that number?
Multiples of three. Oh no, this is going to get so bad. No, I try to hit the 15.
I got to slow down because if you go too fast, it'll just fuck the whole thing up.
Multiples of four. This is, and I know some of you, I'm pausing it right now because I know
there's a shit load of people in this chat right now who are leaning back in their chair
and they're going fuck. Once you go five or six denominations high on the multiples,
I don't know what they are. And I know a shit load of you were doing that right now. You know,
like, oh yeah, I know my multiples like six, six, 12, 18, 24, 32, 38, 40, 41, 42. I know it.
You can't lie to me. Where are we? Four? Look at all these 20s. Four, eight, 12, 16, 20, four,
eight, 12, 16, 20, four, eight, 12, 16, 20, four, eight, 12, 16, 20. Get it. I got it. Does this kill
him? Holy fuck. That's graphic. His bones going through his head. Holy shit. Multiples of two.
Wait, wait, did I just level up? I leveled up. All right. Well, I want to get another cut scene
before I stop fifth grade. Oh, no, I'll do eighth grade. I will just to see if I'm even remotely
capable of doing eighth grade math. I'm app. I'm not. There's no way I am. I already know. I got
to let I have to like do some breathing exercises like for the next few minutes because I know
like I'm going to be looking over the chat and I'm going to be fucking like mad that people are
like making fun of my like sixth grade education. You know what I mean? I'm going to be like,
I got to be ready for it. I got to be ready because I know I'm not going to do well.
And I'm going to look over there and it's going to be like, oh, it's so stupid. How is this? No
way. He's this stupid. I can't. How did he, how does he drive a car? And I'm going to be like,
fuck, I can't. I'm goddamn it. Shut up. God, why would you be happy to see like the charred
remains of somebody that exploded? What the fuck is wrong with this person? What's wrong with this
guy? All right, let's go. Well, it's getting harder. Oh, they've introduced a new enemy type
four, eight, 12, 16, 20, four, eight, 12, 16, 20. Where is it? Move. Oh shit. I'm, he ate me.
I did it. Okay. Five. What a classic game by the way. I could sit here for the next six months
and do this multiples of two. This is actually really, really fucking easy. Like it's very easy.
Watch out. Wait, wait, they're getting faster though. All right. How does this person die?
He's going to go check on it and it's going to crush his skull.
All right. This is easy. Let's, let's, let's go to, let's go to the fifth grade, right?
We have to do fifth grade or should I stay? Well, I'm going to, I lost. It's fine. This is,
we're going to go to the fifth grade. We're going to skip a couple of grades. I'm, I'm good enough.
I know, I know my multiples of three, two and five. We're going to go to the fifth grade. We've
leveled up difficulty level fifth grade. Easy. Sounds good to me. Okay. How about, uh, equality
three. All right. This is the third grade. I don't know. This is the fifth grade.
Not bad. It's not bad. That's four. All right. This is not going as bad as I thought it was
going to go. I thought this is going to be way, way worse equals. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, okay.
20, five, five, 10. Yep. That's correct. No shit. That was RNG dog shit. Get out of here.
No, that's not it. That is what four times four is 16,400. Is it? No, it's fit. I don't think
that's accurate. What are they teaching our children? No, that's 21. You'd love to see that.
No, don't say it. I'm not even going to do it. That's 10. Thanks for the help. That's not even
right. Hold on here. 20. That's 24 16. Is that it? No, two, four, six, eight, 10, 12, two, four,
six, eight, 10, 12, 20. No, what? That wasn't, I didn't even see that. I would have got that
immediately equals four. No, I thought it was times. Okay. I can't lose in the fucking fifth
grade on easy. I actually have to be careful now. Seven, six, five, four, three, four, five, two,
four, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four. Don't go up. He's going to go up. Two, two, two, four,
eight. There you go. This is what I'm talking about. Eight, 16, 24, 32. Got it. What? No,
I thought it was five. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again.
Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Dumber than a fifth grader.
This is 10. It's tricky though. It is. And look, let's give a little bit of credit to the children
that are doing these math problems. It's hard to do this. It is. Can we give some credit to
some fourth graders in this chat, please? Dude, I just lived in the wrong, in the wrong time.
You know what I mean? If I was like back in like the 1400s, we don't, I don't, we don't do math.
Math didn't exist. What would I have done in like the 1200s? I don't know. I would have been
like fucking, I would have had a farm or something. I'd be dead. Why would I be dead?
Plague. You have my, my colitis. Wait a minute. I wouldn't be dead because I have colitis. So I'd
be dead. You might be. Yeah, but I wouldn't, but I don't have to worry about numbers.
I would just live my life. There'd be no like iPhones. There'd be no computers.
You just, you just walked around town and talked to people. That's what you did.
You just like walked around. I'm really good at that. I would be great back at like the 12,
1300s. You just walked around. What is 14? NPC. Yes. That's what, that's what people did.
You worked like on the farm and then you just walked around town or you were like a guard
or you ran in or something. I would just be guy that sits at table in, in,
they needed tons of those people. What are we doing? 14. Oh, I don't know. I don't know. I know
these ones. I don't, I don't know these ones. Is this it? It's 14 right there. 28. No, that's not
correct. 10, eight, 12, eight, 16, 24, 30. No, that's not even close. Seven, eight, nine, 10,
11, 12. That's 12. Six, 12, 18, 14. What is this one? Is this it? No. Five, 10, 15, 20, 20, 30,
30, 40, 40, 50, 50, 60, 70. You all had to do that. Once you get past 60, I don't, I will not hear
this bullshit that you guys can do that like over fucking like 70 or 80 decimals. Oops.
What's the last one? That's 16, 28 and two. Yeah, that's correct. 60, eight, six and 84.
Nobody can do that in their head. Six, 12, 18, six, 12, eight, 24, 32, 32, 10. That's not that hard.
Yeah, because you were just in math class like fucking four hours ago.
Fuck. I didn't even press that. You know the last time I was in math class?
2000. The year 2000 was the last time I saw numbers situated like this. I got, I got a farm to take
care of. I don't know if I, why do I need to know what equals 14? We're good. 14 rows of corn. I
don't count. I just dump all the seeds in there and wait six months and then pull them out of the
ground. Oh no, this is, it's over. Once we go higher than like 13, 14, 15, 16 is when, no way.
There's no way I'm going to do this. Okay, get the easy ones. I have no lives left either.
That's it. Hey guys, I, you know, that's like funny, I guess in a way. It's a kind of funny,
but like him pretending to not know how to do like fifth grade, like multiplying and stuff,
like that's, he's better than that, isn't he? Like, I don't know. I just feel like I'm,
like I caught the stream for like 10 minutes and I just like, he's, he's just doing this like I'm
fucking stupid act thing where I can't do fifth grade math. Has he really gotten that low in
regards to what he's pretending he can't do? Now, if you'll excuse me, I have world hunger to solve
and I have a line of microscopes I have to look into to see, to see how many fucking
microorganisms are inside of my piece of bread that I do every day.
I'm like a bread microscopic person. Yeah, I'm pretty smart. I don't know. Why would you ever
do that? You're like weird. You're fucking weird if you do that. Why would you put bread under a
microscope all the time? What's, why are you doing that? Stop doing that if you do.
No, it did clicked. It clicked. It clicked on it. Wait, that's correct. No, it's not.
Okay, six. All right, I gotta get out of this game. I gotta get out of this game before
people really start to become concerned. All right, all right, just, just lose, just lose,
just lose, just lose. I want to see, I want to see what the eighth grade looks like. Eighth
grade advanced. Let's see if I can get one question right and then we can move on.
Eighth grade and above. I wonder if I can get one question correct. Okay, primes, equality,
factors. Factors of 66. What? That's okay. I can do this one. Oh, that's not a factor.
Is 10 a factor of 66? Nope. Eight? One? Eleven, right? Yeah. It's just what, it's just what can
make 66 eventually. This is how that works. Is it eight or is it 26? 26, 46? I'm not just
guessing. Factors of 51. Okay, yeah. 51. Yeah, just one and 51. That's what I was thinking.
It's a lot more than that though. Seven? Seventeen? Doesn't know pee pants.
No, and, and I, I don't even care. I, you know, like some people would probably get really upset
about this. Factors of, like, oh, sorry. Sorry, scientists in the chat. I don't know what every
factor of 29 is. That's the thing that you say that you know and somebody goes, all right.
Anyways, so about the other reports that you owe tomorrow. Does that mean there's only two?
No, there's not. Any scientists in the chat? Hey, go ahead, go examine some bread while you're at it.
Check it for E. coli or whatever you're doing. Is there only two? Oh, it's a barbecue. We're eating
numbers. Um, that's incredibly dangerous. I could, I could have gotten hurt there. Factors of 67.
I know every factor of 67. Okay, cool. You're ruining our cruise. Can we just enjoy ourselves,
please? Um, 13? No. Two? Four? Who said four? You said four. You said four. I looked, somebody said
four. Some of you. I saw somebody said four. I'll, I'll, I got them. Yes, they did. Yes, they did.
Yes, they did. Yes, they did. Somebody said four. At least two people said four. I don't know what
a prime number is. Well, it was going to be, it's any number that can be like divided by itself,
right? Something like that. That can go into itself. Divided by, multiplied by itself. It's
something like that. I don't know. I don't know. Why, why do I need to know what a prime number is?
It doesn't even, that doesn't matter. Oh, cut, cut the camera to like a close-up of my mother's face
crying. He was supposed to be an accountant. He was supposed to know. I want him to, I want him to
know his number. He's mad. I'm not mad. Hey, don't, don't get mad. Get even. Eleven's not a prime
number of 91. No, this is, wait, this is not prime numbers anymore. This is not prime numbers
anymore. This is, this is, this is different. This is different. Oh shit. I thought, I didn't
know we were on a different thing. All right. Last try. Last try. Last try. Then I'm done. For
real. I swear to God. Eight. Okay. Prime numbers. It's two. The only reason why I know this is
because this is how many days it takes for that package to get there that you order from prime.
That's the only reason why I know that. Greater than 19. Because I said the word Amazon. What?
Amazon joke. Minus two. What? Because it said Amazon prime. Was that too easy? But if, but if,
but if I say, why don't you go ahead and sub with your Twitch Prime? But that's funny. Let's play
Star Wars. It would if you said it unironically. That's all right. I know that we're all on the
same page with our math abilities, so it don't matter. Now this is F1 to toggle mouse keyboard.
Let's do, I guess. Is this a flying game? Princess Leia's rebel force. Select a death star.
Fire laser at desired death star. What? Okay. Uh, mouse control. Good.
How many death stars do they have? Shoot the fighters. Shoot fireballs. Shoot,
shoot the death star. Did I get it? This is actually pretty good for a game that came out
in like 1983. Don't I shoot it inside of the hole? Where's the hole? Exha- Did I get it?
Exhaust port. What am I, what's shooting at me? I think I just have to dodge, right?
Shoot the- Got it. Death star destroyed. All right, this one I'm, I don't want to click this one yet
because it's probably gonna, I'm gonna get stuck here for a long time. So we're gonna play this one.
This one's called the Elf's Christmas. This is called the Elf's Christmas Adventure or Go-
Measures.
Confused. If you give it a word that it doesn't understand, it will tell you what word it doesn't
know. Try entering your command again using a different word in place of the one the game
you're objected to. Your commands should generally be in the format verb, the multiple noun phrase,
preposition noun phrase object, some hypothetical examples of valid commands. Place a red rock
in the small bowl. Put the green rock and the small pebble behind the oak tree.
Read my poetry book. Swim in the swimming pool. Examine the golden ring. Attack him.
Get all. Examine the keys. Push the button. Okay. Why is there attack him? All right,
turn the doorknob, then enter the cave. So you do like then and and and the- Okay, I get it.
So you can type help. Gives you a hint and then inventory will display a list of the items you're
currently carrying. Okay. Holy shit. This is elaborate. Save. Oops. Will allow you to edit
your previous input command. List exits. Look. Verbose. Causes output to go to both the screen
and a printer. The alt key and the up arrow causes a north command. Oh my god. I thought this was
going to be just a short little fun Christmas game. This is Dungeons and Dragons rules. Do not.
Oh. Do not what? I did it. Octagonal room. Remember that you can turn the sound on and
off by giving the command sound on and sound off respectively. All right. This is what I have.
This is what I'm listening to right now. Hold on a second. I need to like do this.
Let me put on like actual Christmas music. Okay. You are in an octagonal room filled with
hundreds of elves. Each of the elves is identical and all seem to move in unison.
You stare at the elf directly in front of you. He stares back. You feel an itching in your nose
which builds and builds until- Achoo! The entire room of elves sneezes simultaneously. Why?
Why would you? What now? The entire room of elves echoes your sneeze. Achoo! Sneeze again.
Sneeze again. Such behavior would be most unbecoming of a Christmas elf.
Cough. I don't understand cough as a verb. How about um get up? Um look. There's barely enough
room to turn around here. If there was anything to find here you'd surely be standing on it.
Octagonal room. There's an elf directly in front of me. Talk. Talk to elf. Sorry but you don't have
time to mess around with the elf. You have a very important mission to help Santa save Christmas
this year. Please try to devote your energies and your mind to the task at hand. Octagon. Okay.
Feel. Eat elf. Eat the elf? You must be kidding. Uh such behavior would be unbecoming of a Christmas
elf. Walk. Leave. Exiting doesn't seem appropriate right now. Damn being an elf sucks. Right. You
yell. Yah! Yah! Yah! Yah! Yah! Yah! Your voice echoes loudly through the area and the volume of
your shriek causes the very ground to vibrate. You feel much better having let out some steam.
But nothing has changed. You can't talk or leave. So what inventory? You aren't carrying anything.
Grab toy. Grab desk. Work. Make toy. You don't have time to be messing around. So what the what am I
supposed to do? That's right. You're here to help Santa. What a smart elf. I think it is work.
Everybody sneezes at the same time. That probably means something. Look down. I don't understand as
the object. Look up. Look at elf. He sneezes as you look at him. What is going on? What's his
sneeze back? Um is this how we communicate? Stand. Stand up. Stand. Grab tissue. All right I'm
10 seconds. Look at floor. You see nothing unusual. Look at elf. He sneezes at you. Look
at chair. What chair? There's no chair. We're standing? Look at ceiling. Look at desk.
There's no desk. What? We're just all standing in a room? Go to Santa. What Santa? There is no
Santa here. Look at mirrors. How do I have minus 50 points? Hint. Walk east.
Look west. Look in room. What room? There's no room. Where are we standing?
Are we outside? Look outside. Make toys. You don't have time to do that. You have very important
mission to help Santa save Christmas. Look at ground. If there's anything to find here,
you'd be standing on it. Where is Santa? Look at shoes. Mirror room. The elves are just you.
Move feet. You're in a mirror box. Yeah. What? No that's not what that is.
Okay I'm fucking out of here. Next. Next. Okay we've got what's up here?
Uh we have why do I have two SimCities? Which one is better? SimCity and then SimCity Classic.
Just play it twice. Which one's better? Just play them both and see which ones. Just do like a
review. All right we're doing we'll do SimCity Classic. Start new city. Uh I don't I don't I
never played SimCity. Medium? Medium. I have no idea what any of this is. This is such a mistake.
This is a mistake. I have no idea what any of these buttons do. Okay city. I don't even know
where we are. Okay so this is a zoom in. I'm assuming I gotta make roads. What does this do?
Bonds. Ten thousand dollars. More residential domes needed. Power grid city form. Okay who are we?
Residential. Can't build on that dust pool. Residential. That needs power. Does that work?
Does that work? Does that do it? Thank you Red Lemonade for the ten community subs. Thank you
Red Lemonade. I've never played SimCity. You this is a mistake. So how do I make a power plant?
Nuclear gravity? A nuclear plant? This is an old version. Yeah it is. Do I have to connect
the nuclear power over here or something? Does that oh is this turned on? I think I got it.
So you have to all right. What's going on here? What are these little dots mean?
Wait we need roads. All right hold on. What's going on? Well these people can't ever leave.
Okay hold on. What's going on? Why is this happening to my houses?
Fuck the roads they're overrated. Okay so I have your graphics card is dying. More houses?
I need to move this around. All right this is my city. Let's go this way. Commercial. So this is
where everyone will work. Shit near the power plant. Power plant. We'll do uh nuclear. Tax rate.
Seven percent. Whoa whoa whoa whoa what's this tax rate? No no no it's zero. Twelve percent.
Go with these figures. How do I get them to go from here to there?
Insane. You're insane. You're insane. Twelve percent is high? Twelve percent? What? Twelve
percent is a high is high tax rate? Am I doing this right? Kind of. Twelve percent's a high tax
rate. He doesn't know. What what do you mean? What do I not know? It's five percent in Massachusetts.
That's state taxes. Wait do you guys don't know how taxes work? But I'm going to get
shit for number munchers. All right I need roads. Uh that's a fucking crazy roundabout.
But it's all right. There'll be less accidents. Oh shit. Okay how do I connect these to houses?
How do I get this to how do I get cars to go on the road? Does it work? You don't. They're
walking roads only. Oh I need industrial. Okay let's have I don't know. How about over here?
We'll have like an industrial section like here. Down here somewhere. Away from the city. I don't
have any more money. All right let's go get to work. Get to work. Let's go. How much?
Ninety-eight dollars. Looney's upset. Taxes out of that world. What the fuck are you talking about?
There's nobody even driving on the roads. All right four percent. All right I need to
generate some money. February 2199. All right am I winning? I haven't seen a car. I don't think
I did this right. Has he figured out that he's on the moon? Crime map. Uh that's every location.
Traffic density. There's no cars. People are just committing crimes. Is that why there's just trash
everywhere? Oh is this just like a complete anarchy? So much crime at the power plant.
Game over. What how? Disasters. Acidic mold. Alien monster attack. A large alien creature has
been spotted in a dust pool. The scientists want to study it. The xenobiologists want to dissect it.
The children want to play with it and the and the entrepreneurs want to capture it for a zoo. Good
luck mayor. Call me when it's gone. Where is it? I think this is the only citizen in the town.
There's nothing to destroy. He's just kind of walking around. It's just his town. This is my
first citizen. Uh all right let's use let's do a meteor shower to get rid of the monster. Monster
left. He sucks. I've I lost. Tax him quick. He's leaving. There was nobody here for him to eat or
kill or destroy so he just left. That was fun. This all right now this one's called nuclear war.
Uh but let me just get 5,000 bits. Ronnie ray gun. Tricky dick. All right I want to be tricky dick.
Uh Gandhi? Why is Gandhi in a nuclear war game? Why would it be? Diplomacy terminal one.
Warhead missiles. Who am I? Carnegie missile. 10 megaton capacity. Where did I just launch a nuke
from? Okay fire. You have no missiles of that size. There I have a 10 capacity. All right do it.
Smoking. Build? Weapons will be built. Click on nuclear war. Blitz's tricky dick for what? 10
million leave. Tricky dick. Tricky dick prepares a missile for launch. Oh you have turns.
Where is it going? Ganji has a concert for Kuka Mame's people. Four million leave
for Ganji. Ron ray gun fuels up a bomber. Your country creates instruments of destruction.
You must first deploy a delivery system. All right let's go. 50. All right let's go do it.
Tricky dick kills 14 million people with a bomb. Defectors leave. Your country gains five million
people. What? Ron ray gun drops a bomb. Radioactive fallout kills 14 million people. Your country
readies a lone missile. They're filled. Weapons will be built. This will click on nuclear war.
This will junk a missile. I get. They come to a barbecue. Four million people leave Ron ray gun
for the barbecue that's happening in the other country. Tricky dick blitzes your country's people
with lies. Eight million leave your country for tricky dick. Whose country am I? Ganji blitzes
your country's people with lies. Ron ray gun reigns flaming death on your country. All right
Ron ray gun. Your country's people add to their arsenal. Okay all right. I need a delivery system.
No you're stockpiling. All right let's do 50 megabytes to Ron ray gun. Who am I? All right
we're gonna grim reaper bomber capacity. All right it's ready to go. Has a concert from my country.
A million people leave for the concert. Ron ray gun builds nuclear toys. Your country puts a bomber
on the runway. All right it's ready. So now how do I decide where I'm going to attack? Can I see
like a bigger map? All right we're going here. We can rebuild it. All right you sure? Select an action.
That. Click the faces. What did I just do? City destroyed. My city's been destroyed so
Ganji has a concert for my people. Nine million people leave for Ganji. Ron ray gun scrambles a
bomber. Your country readies a lone missile. Okay so so do it. Tricky dick at it again.
How many people left in my country? 10 million people leave for the concert.
One million people leave for the concert. Ron ray gun sends a warhead.
Eight million. Your country readies a lone missile. I haven't I can't. Don't delete your shit.
I I don't even know who I am. I thought I was tricky dick but tricky dick is doing his own stuff.
I'm just in the center against four other countries right? You keep junking it. Okay so
this will junk a missile. No no but how do I just aim it? There's no like map screen. All right let's
say I want to let's say I want to drop. You have no missiles of that size. Let's say I want to drop
a missile here right? All right is that going? I did this last time. Six million people leave.
Why are they all targeting me? Your country readies a missile. Why did it not shoot it?
It shouldn't have shot it at Ronnie ray gun's facility right here. Click there. I did. That
should be doing it. Select an action before ending your turn. Don't I already have an action going
on? Your arsenal contains no missiles. Didn't I just prepare a missile? Warhead's too large.
The missile can only carry 10 megatons. Ron ray gun targeted by your missile. 10
megatons. That is a big thick fucking thumb. Holy shit. That is the whole it's a whole hand.
All right press it. So how do I press the button? Just go? Is this ready? So just nuclear war. Ready
done. Nuclear war. Preparing for impact. Ron ray gun sends a warhead to you. Six million killed.
I don't have any. All right my country is too tense. How many people live on this planet?
Weapons will be built. I'm dead. Defectors have left from my country. Your country against six
million people. I'm in the worst possible strategic location. This is just all-out war and
I'm the easiest person to target. Nobody is attacking anybody else but me. Forefront war.
Yeah this is bullshit. Your country prepares for war. I need to build like a I'm just gonna lose.
I've got nothing left. I have five anthills. They're just forming empty fucking holes.
Nobody leaves your country because it doesn't exist anymore. When did I what? I didn't do any
of this. Okay this person it's gone rogue. What's going on? Oh I'm done. It's over. This was all
okay this is a war between the four of these countries to who gets to land in the middle.
Now they're just playing without you. Yeah who's left? It better not be Tricky Dick. If Tricky Dick
wins I'll be so upset. No don't. Come on. Come on Gandhi. Take him out. This is it. Fireball engulfs
radioactive fallout. What was the? All right time to get addicted. I don't even care it's over.
Time to get addicted. Oh shit my volume has been down this whole time. They may have been sounds
in that game. I have no idea. Miner is a game of rare earths mining. You mine platinum, gold, silver.
You may have your minerals assayed at the bank. Watch your health. Make frequent stops at the
hospital. Arrow keys. Move miner in four directions. T B that's elevator up to the top and elevator
down. H is help. Remember that. X is exit. Don't touch it. Q is quiet. S R pump water. You need at
least a bucket. Drill granite. You need at least a drill. Enter. Need used to enter buildings.
Initiate dynamite blast. All right let's go. I have 100 health. I have 1500 bucks in my bank account.
Try the elevator. You have sandstone. Oh this cost money. What just happened? You found a spring.
You found streaks of silver. This is just Minecraft. Yeah. Wait, wait, wait. Can I? Oh shit I didn't
mean to do that. How do I pick up water? You don't have gills. You don't have gills. You don't have
gills. You don't have gills. What? How do I move? I'm drowning. I know. RIP. Here lies a brave miner.
He died with his tool in his hand. For the love of sweet Miss Mimi. His bank account was $1130.
Imagine setting your bank account on your gravestone. That would be really fucked up. Okay,
I want to try that again. I want to try again. This is fun. VGA miner. All right pump water.
Pump water. This time if I find water don't stand in it. What's in here? Welcome. You can't fly dummy.
Try the elevator. All right let's go. We're gonna go down here. Granite's too hard to dig. Okay,
got some silver. The mine is caving in on you. You lost some silver. Oh fuck off. Sandstone. Easy
digging. Dumbass trying to dig granite. All right I haven't found anything. Okay this silver.
Silver. How much money do I need? Can I sell the silver? More silver. Okay. All right go back in
the elevator. Is the bank? Oh there's like a hospital over here too. All right go in the bank.
You can't fly. How do you go in a building? E? Enter. Okay E. Welcome to the community bank.
We're pleased to assay for you. Our rates are not only competitive. They're the only ones in town.
Press X to leave the bank. Okay so I have today's quotes. Silver 15.4. What do I have? AG. AG is
silver right? Okay let's get some silver. Cash in all your minerals. A. Well that's a net loss.
Okay cool. How do I leave? How do I get out of here? Exit. B. You lost money.
Yeah I gotta find gold or platinum. Isn't X quit to DOS? No that's not okay. So digging costs money
and I don't have any this is I'm just operating at a horrible loss. Here be dragons. Here be dragons.
Here be dragons. Oh shit. What the fuck? Give me some platinum. It costs. It costs $20 to dig
and I don't even get $20 for silver if it's in one box. Volcanic tough digging.
What happens when you run out of money? Your bank account just goes negative. Oh that's what
happens. You go into debt for 15 seconds. All right I'm doing it again. I'm doing it again.
I'm going all the way. Okay I'm doing it again. I'm going I'm going down. Dynamite blast. Okay okay
okay okay okay. 1500 from the bank. The salon is closed. Where what about in here? Here we go.
Press V to buy 60 feet for $100. All right should I get a I'm gonna get a better pickaxe.
B. You have that. Okay E for bucket of F to buy torch. G for dynamite. Let's do A.
Okay I have a shovel and I have a pickaxe and I have dynamite. All right let's leave the store.
I now have better equipment. Let's go down here. All right how do I use the dynamite?
Y is dynamite. Let's do it. Bound gold. Okay here we go. Y. You need a torch. I can't just
I can't light the dynamite. Further? I can't. I gotta pay 100 bucks to go further.
Okay sell it. Sell sell sell sell sell sell sell. Sell gold and get thing for dynamite. Why do I
like this game? I don't know why. Cashing my minerals. Oh that's pretty good. That really
wasn't bad at all. Okay go in here and let's get a torch. I'm assuming F is torch. Be careful
with fire. I will. You like this but you hate Minecraft. When did I say that? I love Minecraft.
Okay this game's all right. I'm gonna go here. We're gonna go oh what's that? Oh all right I'm
dropping the dynamite here. Nice. Gold fragment. Oh look at how good that is. Just I'm gonna buy
those. What's the point of... Wait I have to go back up right? More gold. All right all right.
Okay okay okay okay okay okay. I'm going back up. You blew up the minerals. Did I though? Come on
one more. You found traits. The game did. I just opened up the whole game. I just got platinum
guys. Yeah you're ignoring the silver. Am I? Let's see what happens if I sell all this shit.
What we got? Oh yeah. You minerals. That's a lot of money. Plat. Sell it all.
$2,821. All right nice. Want to vote in the saloon. Not open. I need to heal.
Welcome to St. Woody's. We're pleased to take care of you. In God we trust. All of this pay
cash. No insurance accepted. What type of service do you want? You may be in need of surgery.
Your bed rest will probably be about two and a three days. Our fees are quite reasonable.
$100 a day. What do you mean you may be in need of surgery? Wouldn't you know? $100 a day.
No I'm not going there yet. Not necessary. All right let's buy the next layer. You may be in need
of surgery. Press V. V. All right we have more. Do it one more time. Okay two dynamites. Oh okay
all right let's go. What is this? What is C? What's a corkscrew? I can go down further by the drill.
Will that automatically start doing things for me? Oh shit we can keep going. How many would I get?
60, 60 feet. This doesn't cost money to keep going right? All right here we go. Don't get killed by
that. All right water exists down here. What do I need the water for? Give me something. Here we go.
Light it. It's dehydrate. That doesn't. No you don't do any of that. Oh shit. Okay watch it.
You can keep going to the left. All right don't blow all your money. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up.
Where am I? Okay fuck. I have 39 health. Get up. Up. Why is there so much water down here? Platinum
flat. All right back up. Back up. Back up. Back up. Back up. Back up. Back up. Back in the elevator.
In the elevator. In the elevator. In the elevator. In the elevator. Come on. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. I
have 29 health. One more like nugget and I'll be fine. Come on. One more nugget. All right good.
He's being greedy. No I got it. I got it. I got another platinum.
Okay back up. Back up. Back up. Back up. He's avoiding the ones with the minerals
because that happened. Sell. Sell. Sell. Sell. Sell. All right what do I got? A lot.
Okay cash it in. Now I do need to heal. It's going to take seven and a half days for me to be healed.
So that's 700 days. $700? Stay one day and one night. Oh man that's horrible.
I want to upgrade my tools. You got the money though? Yeah but I'm not. I don't want to.
Okay so if I press B is that going to give me a better axe? No I already have it. Okay C.
A durable drill. Do I just buy it all? D. It's a lantern. E for the water. I got every. I have
every. Okay I got it all. Let's go get a bucket of water. See what that does.
Why is this not open yet? It's a cute drill. Let me fill up the water. P. It's P right? Press
the direction. Oh okay P. Oh it just gets rid of the water. I get it. So what does the corkscrew do?
Pump drill granite. All right so it's D. D. Oh that's cost. Look at how much money that costs.
That's $200 to do that. That's not worth doing. At all. That's not worth it. Why would I even use
that? It's 200 per drill. That's horrible. All right let's do some water here. What? What happened?
What? What happened? What happened? What? Wait it's a hundred and it was a hundred and fifty dollars?
A pump? It costs money to use the bucket. To put your hands in water and throw what?
I. Oh god damn it. I'm so sad. Okay we're gonna play Dune 2 and then we're gonna open it up to the
to the people to vote here in a minute. Uh oh. Uh oh. Uh oh. Uh oh. Uh oh. Uh oh.
We're good. And urgent games. This is Dune. D. U. N. E. Dune 2. Not doom 2. A lot of people just
went oh come on. I thought you were playing doom. What about it? He didn't read the book? No.
I didn't read the book. Is this the one with the big worms in the ground? No that's Tremors.
Is this how the book goes?
The house that produces the most spies. Set territories and no rules of engagement.
So it's the purge. Only you have to bring like cumin.
Those alive? That seems very impractical for a plane to do that. I've never seen this movie.
There's a seagull plane.
There is no movie. There's not this is a movie right?
Is it only a book? There are like yeah there's like three movies.
There's no movie. All right is this a click and point adventure game? Is this a shooter game?
What is this? Battle for Arrakis. Play a game. Select your house. All right we've got Gryffindor,
Slytherin, and the ram. I'm gonna be well isn't the way this works. If you say that you're
Slytherin you're actually Hufflepuff. And if you say that you're Gryffindor it means you're
actually Ravenclaw. That's how that works right? And if you say that you're Hufflepuff
you're actually Slytherin. This is the cool one to say that you are. I'm Slytherin. I don't play by
any fucking rules. Yes you do. I can't select? Let's go. All right where do we land? Home planet
of the Atreides has a warm calm climate and the lands are lush and green. Okay what about it? That
defines spices? The rich soils and mild weather supports an extensive variety of agricultural
activities. In recent centuries industrial and technological development has added to the
prosperity of the Caladanian people. Do you wish to join house Atreides? Not yet no no not yet.
I want to see the other intro. House Ordos. The home plant it's like icy and cool looking. The
home planet of Ordos is a frigid and ice covered world. We presume the Ordos import their agricultural
and technological goods from nearby star systems. Acting as traders and brokers the Ordos
produce no physical products of their own and rely upon their merchandising skills to survive.
That sounds pretty interesting. I might be as I might be an Ordos. All right what about the
Harkonnen? This is a big fireball. From the dark world of Ghedi Prime the savage house Harkonnen
has spread across the universe. Accrual people. The Harkonnen are ruthless towards both friend and
foe in their fanatical pursuit of power. I am Mentat Radnor. With my guidance you may be able
to assist us in conquering this dusty little planet. Okay for your first test you will be
expected to produce 1 000 credits and not a granular less. You may earn credits by harvesting
spice and will need to build a refinery to convert spice to credits. Okay harvest spice,
refinery convert spice. If any of our foolish enemies attempt to attack your base you will
have the pleasure of seeing the invincible Harkonnen troops in action. Oh it's an RTS.
Okay uh construction yard is that there? Build this. Build it. Mentat. Oh I have to add okay.
Small construction slab. Wind trap power center. There isn't enough open concrete to place the
structure. You may proceed but without enough concrete the building will need repairs.
No don't do that. Do I already have a construction yard? Um can I select a unit? There we go.
Okay move. Acknowledge. Go look over this way. This map is tiny. Okay build construction facilities.
All structures are built by the construction facility. Got it. All right let's do. No no no
I didn't want to do that. Oh shit. All right I want a slab. Small concrete slab.
Place the slab over here. Where should I put this? Cannot place the foundation here.
Concrete. Use concrete to make a sturdy foundation for your structures.
Where? This is one person? All right all right all right all right all right uh just
get over there. Construction yard. Okay so now I can do a power center. It takes all right.
No no no I get it. I get it. Stop stop stop. I gotta build four of these don't I?
I have to go like it has to sit on a slab right? All the zooms and chat hating this game.
Oh I see. He's getting it. He's getting it. He's so stupid. He's so stupid. He's so stupid.
I need a thousand credits right? You have to start harvesting stuff.
Oh stupid idiot. Dumb fucking idiot. Stupid fucking idiot.
The wind trap supplies power to your base without power your structures will decay.
My power info needed output is 100. All right why don't you go like over here?
Start like exploring. We need to find resources. Yes sir. You go up here.
All right I need to how do I? Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit.
Shit. Shit. Shit. Attack. Attack. Attack. No don't shoot your own guy over here.
Get him. All right what do I get? Oh I got a new pink spice refinery. All right wait wait wait wait.
Slabs. Oh shit. Look at these fucking actions for a minute.
Seven. Can't place the foundation. Why? Good good good good. This is actually kind of fun.
I would love to play this online versus like six people. Try pressing M for move.
Well that's good. A for attack I'm assuming too. All right what do I need? I need like three. Six
right? That's six. All right keep on building this shit. The PSX version is cleaner. Yeah this is
this is old old old old old old. Very old. We got hotkeys boys. This is real RTS.
All right let's get the spice refinery on there. They improved a lot with red alert.
Yeah. You can feel the red alert. You can feel the command and conquer in this.
That like affirmative affirmative. I think it's the same voice just with a higher bit rate.
Come on hurry up hurry up hurry up. Red alert could be the best RTS I've ever played. It was such a
mess. I loved it. I might play that one day. That game is a fucking mess. It's crazy how nuts that
game can get. Convert spice into credits. What's that? Oh okay. All right we go. We're getting
spices going. Search for spice fields to harvest. All right what does the spice field look like?
All right move. Uh we need to find spice field. Damn I want to play red alert like right now.
It's like riding a bike too. I remember everything. I remember everything. Having like 10 construction
yards. Like 20 tonyas. Like a hundred power plants. I remember building power plants into
other people's bases to just put tesla coils all over this inside their fucking base. I'm playing
that like soon. Like real soon. That just scratched the itch in my brain. I can't wait to play that.
Do it now? No no no no. Can't do it now. Can't do it now. Oh I'm gonna though and it's gonna be
fucking awesome. You have no idea how much fun. I can't wait. I'm gonna be I'm gonna like destroy
that whole game. Acknowledge. We're doing it tomorrow. We're doing that tomorrow. I'm gonna
I'm gonna find a way to get it to work. I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna buy it. I'm gonna get it. I'm
we're doing it tomorrow. That's what we're doing. I'm just gonna play fucking red alert all day.
I can't wait. It's gonna be incredible. Yeah I'm gonna have like like 50 mammoth tanks and shit.
Like all going in different directions. I I love that game. I'm so happy that I ended up playing
this because it reminded me of how just dumb fun that game is. Is multiplayer still working
that game? Does it? Anybody have any any idea? There's no way it does. Not even close. No way.
You have to do a lot of specific things. The original version doesn't work anymore.
I'm gonna do some research and figure this out because if we could like get like a
how many people could play in it? There's open red alert. All right this is not a virus.
They're effective. Oh I can't wait. I love that game so fucking much. I'm so excited.
You have no idea. I'm so excited. My whole teenage life has been building up to this
moment tomorrow. I return. I'm gonna have an impenetrable fort. I'm gonna be unstoppable.
The turrets. The little caps. Remember those things? The little like tuna cans
that like oh dude I love it can't wait the origin version works on windows 10
why aren't why aren't games as cool nowadays they are they are they are I mean I I would agree with
you I really would but bloodborne came out like a few years ago like four or five years like
if I can't I cannot tell you that they don't make them still can I make another harvester
dude I remember having just harvesters the gold mines you have like 20 trucks
you have like oh I can't wait oh I'm so ready I'm gonna do I'm not going to bed tonight I'm
just gonna stay up and like get it ready he's radiating happiness yeah I'm so glad I played
this even if it is I know it's like the basic kind of it but it oh I can't wait watch I know
clip this and tomorrow tomorrow if what should be like this is fucking dumb this sucks like this is
not as good as I thought it was not even close this is so bad I don't remember it like this
hold on let me like let me switch out like rose-colored glasses almost there
durma you're more excited for this than you are for the carnival that's not true all right I did
it yeah you have pleased me continue to serve me well and I will see that you are rewarded
no because off camera you know when you're like in the shower and you just like dance in the shower
all right all right I'm good I'm good we don't see anymore I'm just saying we'll see that's
gonna happen tomorrow the stream's not over I'm just saying let's play uh Aladdin is this what
Aladdin is this type the word type any key on the cup okay I just I pressed one is this the one that
um uh the is that is that this one no it's not this one are you sure
let's steal to survive oops no I think this is it yeah this is it this is definitely it how do you
jump this is it no it's not it that's not it it's not it that's not it it's not it how do I swing
how do you swing okay a s w d e r this game's sick actually this is one for the genesis I mean the
super nintendo one is one thousand times better but this is the genesis one q space is jump alt
okay alt and control yep there it is
soundtrack is good I'm so sad that we don't get to hear
whoa this was this came out on dos no that's not the end this isn't bad for
dos no it's not it's actually pretty good wow wow come on wow oh his pants fell down
oh that's sad but the loser all right go up aren't there bosses in this game what was the last good
licensed video game I remember though I mean actually good licensed video game
spider-man for ps4 that's that that's true that's true yeah that's that's true yeah that game was
awesome that was fucking awesome um that was very very good but like take movie comic book is you
know you can make a good comic book there's been a lot of comic book character games have been very
good uh what td show or movie though spider-man yeah but spider-man's like that's a marvel
character that's not like based on the movie Aladdin like spider-man ps4 was not like spider-man
homecoming the video game right king kong return of the king lord of the rings oh that game was
awesome you're right those lord of the rings games worth up playing those two up playing those games
too those games are awesome oh man i'm remembering gandalf and the two towers game
those games that's so good all right write it down somebody i'm gonna i'll forget that somebody
write it down that's the one with the uh with the huge combo meter right this sounds like sarcasm
it is okay suck i'm kidding those all right i'm gonna pay attention to this game
no i really love those games because when you get the combo meter to keep going
oh man nothing will ever replicate that feeling
keep making him reminisce about old games till he plays minecraft that's not that old
wait is this that i remember this game had the uh the the cool genie level right they would they
were very similar this one of the super nintendo one was similar but the genie level the super
nintendo one was not very good this has a much cooler genie level the sega genesis one i remember
oh my god i'm a games are so this game's so good oh somebody write it down but i have to play this
one if i play that song will i go to prison no no no no no no no i'm gonna die no dying
this whole vod is prison no it's not how do you leave this level oh all right what do you get
what do i do five wish what do i have how do i buy something it's a deal all right well i got
an extra life come on wait no all right that's not that far away there's a boss right here isn't
there all right here comes the boss i remember this never mind is the game running at 75 speed
look at all this screen tearing look you can't what am i doing what am i pressing
ah the desert turn on the d-sync what song is this one i'm serious right somebody write down the two
towers game because i'm just gonna get them how long does the speed run for this game turn down
for what what does that mean what are you saying when you're doing that what does that mean
it's screen tearing now this is how we used to have to play games back in the fucking 80s
uh-oh froze oh oh dude you know another game listen to this game some of you guys are gonna
have like this insane eureka effect right here are you ready for this i'm gonna say like three
words and you're gonna drop your fucking steak and cheese sandwich mickey's magical quest
for super nintendo remember that game where you would get the firefighter game
where you did different costumes and shit and you had like the room put that on the list too
oh by the way we're playing all these tomorrow no we're not chicken sandwich just landed on the
ground who is calling me how do i can't get over the castle of illusion hd remake no no no no no
no no that's not mick that's not the magical quest starring mickey mouse it's the capcom one
that one was insane i'll beat that whole game on stream i don't care if it takes me all day
no get i just want to get to the genie level that's all i care about goof troop for snes
no no no i'm sorry that's not the magical quest starring mickey box get a ball ah dude that's the
original that's the original dark souls enemy placement he's in a mood i know it's because i
started talking about red alert and now i'm like so happy i'm so excited it's just like total like
mania don't die i like i have to get to the genie level to see if it's as good as i remember
come on he's like right here mickey mania like it's so good so many great fucking video games
go is it okay what's the notorious uh what's the notorious lava level that was almost impossible
was that for the super nintendo one is that for this one the the one that was say genesis
what's going on jump over that i guess i can't it's this one is it this one it's the magic carpet
level on both of them what the fuck dude this music slaps just wait oh that's the second piece
so that's the second heart piece how do i get that ow if i can hit one more time i'm dead
just don't get hit i want to see that carpet all right i got them both dungeon level always got me
oops watch out for the knife watch out for the knife knife knife really i'm out of time all right
quick everybody do your best genie impression oh fuck what a legendary character let's be honest
if there's one thing that can be truly said the robin williams genie is guaranteed
to make you feel like happy always no matter what doesn't matter what mood you're in you can
put on aladdin right now and you'll just be like i love this so much you've never you've never seen
it wait you've never seen the original aladdin with robin williams no way there's no way there's
go do it just leave the stream now and go do it you can get it anyway it's like on every platform
find the flutes how much more is until the it's a long game those of you that don't know though
uh the guy that plays homer simpson actually is the genie in a lot of media
dan castellaneta right in the tv show yep does somebody just say that's not true yes it is
that's yes it is that is true don't you fly yeah you fly up with these nope my inputs
yeah i don't know the words but that's what it does
gotta go to sleep gotta have some sleep something else
fake fan i'm not a fake fan oh no what a waste of perfectly good apples
is
where is it i gotta do my part street rat street rat i am not a street rat
gotta go to sleep gotta have some sheep gotta have some fun well i have time
i got it by all three it's trying to prove you've watched the movie pause it
what's the name of the song aladdin's song uh what's called street rat what's it called
fort game the aladdin the aladdin song by mr aladdin one jump ahead i gotta get it once
i'm gonna mute so you don't hear me i don't want you to hear the song
because i want to be able to pretend like i know what i'm doing
because i don't want the vaudeville to get muted
parents except he hasn't got him gotta gotta eat to live gotta steal to eat gotta eat to live
gotta steal to eat tell you all about it when i got the time i was close i was fucking close
i was close gotta eat to live gotta steal to eat tell you all about it when i got the time
it was close what's this part no where's that there was this the part that goes like
did they take that out let's not be too hasty still i think he's rather tasty that's what it is
he's rather tasty god i had ah i missed it fuck i'll get it next time god
i missed it one jump ahead of the platform two jumps ahead of the sign i'm dead
okay the first beginning when was the street rat part i don't know i thought it was like street rat
wear a tie that's not what it is here it comes here it comes here it comes street rat street rat
uh let's not be too hasty yes i think he's rather tasty gotta go to sleep gotta eat
fucking can't do it it's gotta eat to live gotta eat to live gotta steal to eat otherwise we
so now uh it's your turn it's your turn if you have your extensions enabled these are the new
additions these new date archived where are we going yogi bear visits the national parks
yahtzee and zookeeper it looks like it's gonna be yogi bear visits the national park
or zeppelin giants of the sky it seems like we're going to yogi bear thank you for voting
oh this looks crusty this is what it looks like if you punch the top of your computer
really hard okay insert disc two yogi bear vids the national parks do you need instructions i
yes i actually do yogi is happily dozing beneath a tree when he awakens to find that boo boo has
gone he yells at boo boo to come back but it's too late you will play the part of yogi it is your
job to locate boo boo with the ranger's help all you know now is that boo boo is in one of the
national parks you must use the park maps and have the ranger use his radio and computer
to locate boo boo then you must fly to the park and pick boo boo up if he's still there good luck
okay yogi bear and the national parks instructions when a message appears above the ranger's head as
you walk yogi back and forth you can press enter to perform the action when the message you see
something below appears you must land on one of the safe landing pads to discover what it is
when the fuel low message appears you must fly back to the ranger station landing pad
before your fuel runs out or you will crash okay yeah yogi i'm gonna go for a walk today
okay have a good time oh no oh where's our boo boo come back boo boo where did boo boo go
let's get some help from the ranger this is 3d glasses without the 3d glasses on
transmitting picture now of boo boo small bear sighted near a cave of strong winds
thank you ranger cave of strong winds let's see if we can find a cave maps
which would you like to see we don't know where he is in the whole country
what oh boo boo walked away i don't know what state he's in it could be anywhere
uh let's see one okay let's check uh texas the big bend in the rio grand river that's not it
okay how about how about that two grand canyon gorge is 270 miles long and one mile deep the
colorado river flows through the canyon which covers 1.2 million acres of land we're looking
for strong winds northern colorado many lakes and snowy mountain peaks this area used to be home to
the arapaho indians okay um uh which one did we not do before got it a series of huge caves
with lighted trails and many bats there are many rock formations created by years of one
this is a deep cave in new mexico he's in new mexico so he's in four all right back it up
helicopter fuel it up for me we're going to new mexico wait use the radio stop walking forward
you fucking idiot no yogi doesn't have a flights license uh where was it carl's bad caverns
please input the park's landmark feature what incorrect check the what are you talking about
what can i call them ranger smith calling all parks report any sightings of a short brown bear
named booboo small bear sighted near a cave of strong winds my mouth is opened like four times
ready to do the voice but i didn't do it i was like curling my lip i'm ready and i didn't do it
all right let's go we have a sighting where we're going all right let's see wind cave
oh wind cave what's a landmark feature it's windy no stop i can't we have to go to we find wind
cave it's go back maps all right how about four what it's wind cave new york wind cave new york
he's in three three and then one many lake streams and waterways no where's wind cave
region four map one region four map three northwest wyoming that's old faithful
no that's not true three and one five two and three southern florida nope four and five wind cave
okay the south dakota strong winds blow in and out of the cave there are yellow pink blue and brown
calcite crystal formations in the cave so we have to prove that we know where this is
so we say just calcite right we go to wind cave we say hey calcite and he'll let us go
nice picture you type wind cave no you have to type the feature all right let's go wind it's in
south dakota calcite which park will you fly to we're gonna fly to wind cave yes please input the
park's landmark feature i just i picked wind cave wind cave win others oh boo boo i don't know how
to fly a plane safe to land how do we find them you see something below i'm coming boo boo it's
the same one probably right you see something below safe to land all right stop go right down
all right safe to land see if we can find it it's boo boo hey boo boo's back why do they have to do
this screen ow stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop it that's the whole game okay that's
fun now what boo boo detected yahtzee or zookeeper uh-oh uh-oh it's torn imagine if that was sixty
dollars hold on my throat that game was not sixty dollars it was probably like twelve important
question would you rather have your current health problems you have for the next two years
or have one kidney stone for one night that one i'd rather have that kidneys i'd rather do kidney
stone like three times in a row three days in a row and just get it over with just get it over with
all right looks like we're going with playing yahtzee yahtzee this is like this text yahtzee
there's no graphics in this okay press any key this is the game of yahtzee from one to seven
players may play at the same time with each player's current status shown on the playing
board including total scores the only difference between this game and the popular home game is
that you may get multiple yahtzees here the first yahtzee scores 50 points and each additional one
will yield a bonus of a hundred points that just breaks the whole game in addition you will be
given an extra turn at the end of the game the winner will be a hit let's go okay fine okay how
many players uh two that's the rules of yahtzee play against chat that i can't do that i'll play
against myself do you wish to play against me yes how many dice to roll again i'm gonna i'm
about to veto this one this is mario yahtzee but 10 times worse um let's do i'm going one two three
no no no no no no no no don't roll again i want to hold no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
what are you doing backspace roll which three dice again no no no what do you huh veto sorry
i had to veto that that was that was gonna that was going nowhere zeppelin giants of the sky
i would have to play yahtzee again all right we're gonna do zeppelins don't this game is actually
good is it what do you do okay presents zeppelin okay what is this you want to play the easiest
yes select player a lot of choices this guy is a kid no it's not i don't know who any of these
people are all right i'll play as what this person this guy's a poser what enter the name of zeppelin
i think that's good zeppelin airship the suppository is in berlin i can't read this
bro production bookshop i can't read this workers one no no no no no no i get two million dollars
am i selling materials no no go back back back back it up all right we'll do you really want
to cease production of the airship yes how do i go back without an airship not possible to put
new zeppelin into service all right well then put fucking five people on it and let's have i don't
know five scientists all right let's get me out of here get me out of here get me out of the
workshop i'm trapped yeah i am tab control alt enter space space space put more assemblies
this is a song i know this song make me a ship make me a ship please whoa whoa whoa what what
has happened all right don't go to that screen okay fly not possible no gas or fuel fuel a depot
costs 200 pounds per week yes hydrogen is 200 pounds per week i got depot helium let's go fill
it up workers one to five improvements looks good to me fuel it up fuel hydrogen and helium
gas fuel it up all right we're fueled let's go am i stuck in this menu now there's no reviews on
this game there's nothing nobody knows how to do this b for back z x i'm just gonna press every
button no zookeeper 100 and then we're gonna scroll nice nice nice nice nice nice let's go
oh wait i gotta get you off the screen presenting davidson zookeeper help wanted
this official zoo world pass will admit hmm boo boo the first time you visit zoo world
helpful hints will appear on the screen click the screen when you finish reading the hint
to turn new user help off press alt h can't do that we need to release the galapagos penguin
to the waters of south america this is your chance to help the zoo read the message on the
bulletin board then click the screen remember first click the screen to make the hint bubble
appear the scientists are on their way to the wild but there's a band of troublemakers on the
loose and zoo world's a mess we need a zookeeper fast okay for a second i thought there was a lion
uh who is why is it like what is i don't what is this this is funky monkey your zoo guide
that is a troublemaker the troublemaker is thinking about which animal to bother first
see the area picture and the animal picture follow the troublemaker to that animal home
click the screen to get your zoo map he's gonna go fuck with the polar bears here's your zoo map
click the area you want to visit or click zoo central to get information and check your progress
well we'll go into polar regions
these are footprints of animals that live in the polar regions move your cursor around to
see the animal names click the footprints of the animal you want to visit this is a person this
is a human oh there's a polar bear is it going to be real footage oh no yikes what are these
cereal mascots i'm going to go and mess around with the armadillos these animals need help click
and drag incorrect food or plants to the recycle bin click and drag correct food and plants out
of the bins and click to set the temperature and humidity if you're not sure what the animals need
click zuni the robot then click the food bin seed bin animal plaque or background
you just gave me the wand all right what arctic bearberry is an interesting arctic plant it grows
along the ground and has bright red leaves bears eat the berries birds eat the berries too most
polar bear food comes up the sea they eat seals small whales and walruses fish and seabirds make
a tasty snack they eat seals they eat seals do they really small whales and walruses they eat
that i thought they ate like trees no no there's no trees in the arctic i thought they don't eat
rocks all right so we need to you ever heard somebody say i'm as hungry as a bear now you
know what it means somebody just sucked him up all right it's cold and needs to be medium wet so
where do we get food for you you don't eat bark eggs fish am i about to feed this guy a walrus
here have a fish where are where are you oh there they are i can see them oh no we have to save but
i have to wait what do they like for plants let me not forget that arctic forget me not it's
another flowering plant this is trash then get it out of here tropical fern water lily arctic plant
yum did we actually get to see you come and eat yum all right now how do we get them to come out
all right come on out yum wet and cold all right i did it now i have to go save uh not
grasslands grasslands let's get that other bad guy what the hell was this thing
aardvark it was i think it's an aardvark right
to make the animals come out clean up their home click and drag them the maniacs garbage or stir
crazy stuff to the recycle bin hold on this guy throwing beer cans into the exhibit mountain dew
so that's what they were doing excellent excellent work they are cool freezing frisbees
someone's playing games with the polar bears maybe you should jump in and find out what the
score is click the walkie talkie to see where the trump maker is heading didn't we just go
over here we need to put them in jail let's get a closer look what a fucked up animal are they
going to do a winnie the pooh live action because that's piglet right there they did no but they
didn't they did but they didn't all right let's go hello where's the before i veto this game and
by veto i mean i've already played it what the hell is going on now excellent you're taking good
care of the animals so there's lots of neat stuff in your suitcase you can check it all out in zoo
central neat you got something in your suitcase because you helped the animals to see your
suitcase click the zoo central sign to click to continue following the troublemaker click the
area footpath or our zoo map sign where's the troublemaker i don't have any zoo central oh
they actually are in jail zoo central is a great place to get information and check your progress
troublemakers wanted brain drain stir crazy the maniac greedy girt the greedy grinner
i think i've had enough of this one yeah i've had enough of this what do i have in here poker chips
what do i have here why control panel sound on oh i see all right that's fun next you're
ready for the scroll i'm ready for the scroll i have to be careful okay i don't here we go
wolf's bane vr slingshot or ween it's vr all right it's close but it looks like we're going
wolf's bane take it out you vibe all right wolf's bane that's it oh shit this game looks kind of
interesting you guys remember you wrote down all that shit right the games i want to play
all right we're going to do english okay sounds good yes yes wolf's bane let's go i can't read
that minions the young person driving late in the town of wolfburg
wolf's bane wolf's bird that's me as the moon slides from behind the cloud he hears
a blood chilling sound yeah oh damn why did he how
oh shit you got me as he goes back wolf's bane no you couldn't you had it's in look it's a
different font the legend of the werewolf come on and it's 1141 so that shit ain't happening
all right rid myself of the curse herman a god stands quietly watching your every move it's
his job to make sure that the village is safe from enemy forces hello my name's axel do you
know how i got here i don't remember could you open the gates do you not get bored standing here
have you ever seen a werewolf i'd be silly sir there'd be nothing as werewolves i'd be thinking
knock on your head has done damage this like crusty audio can you open the gates
certainly not sir you never know who or what might be out there werewolves possibly
uh how do i how do i fix this okay all right how do i how do i how do i get here i don't know but
you look like you've been in a fight and fallen in a ditch that must have been you uh screaming
last night don't you get bored no i quite like it actually see if i lived in like 1200s i just
you have to just exist in places let's get off am i sleeping what is this i don't want that
i was not i was trying to stab you i wasn't trying to give it to you all right let's keep going
the slaughtered lamb good day sirs shh don't answer him wolf gang he looks like he's been
attacked by the beast good day oops if you're seeking employment take a look at the notice
board on hambolt street there always seems to be plenty of jobs available there
uh can i have a drink what time is it wait did i just go to sleep i thought i was supposed to do
this like at midnight oh hold on it's like a wizard get off hello you look like you've seen
a ghost they're coming for us all boy you've had a few you're my best friend hello we are mere
mortals against the wrath of the wolves i don't want that i'm gonna turn this music off i have
to put after place the music it's gonna kill me what do you mean no you guys want to you guys
want to sit here and listen to this what's the name of this game wolfsbane wolfsbane ost doesn't
exist i want the distorted version no we can keep the sounds on it's just i can't handle that
anymore it's driving me nuts here here we go how do i leave his room how do i get the fuck out of
here i can't leave there we go and i'll do voice acting i promise good day sir bring me a large
stranger see oh god so good so good generic creepy pasta ost
it really is creepy pasta ost music oh shit look at the top we have like a majora's mask
it's locked get the apple you picked up the apple uh i seem to have been having a bit of trouble
finding my way around the village could you help me names can help open doors anything else i
should know motley ads my lucky number is one try to be double lucky what a fine costume you have
thank you sir i made it myself can i like help him that tickles i just want to like is he why
is he hanging there sir gerald jester don't be fooled by the fool his cryptic words can reveal
hidden truths of fucking course they do uh what else uh oh uh finding the correct path is as easy
as pie all right so find the pipe he's getting ripped i guess the door is locked um hello why is
the guy fucking attacking me why are you attacking me what are you doing i don't want that uh okay
why he's killing me he would just hit me with a stick over and over again uh wait is that
doubled it's a double door shit may i see the prisoner no visitors for the prisoner could you
show me to myself am i under arrest oh my we're busy today clear off i'll arrest you doesn't look
very ripe this game is based on real life events oh that would be interesting that wouldn't all right
i'm just gonna go in it's locked kind of give him this what about you want an apple
i don't want that incoming veto
i can't i didn't take anything he lost half his viewers to that joke
i didn't even make a joke two thousand people hate welp's bait now i'm gonna fight this guy again
that what is going what oh no we're trying to drop it like flies
they're dropping it's over keep playing until only one person's left
oh my god
oh you shouldn't have changed the music
uh minus 200 minus 300 oh god we're crashing into the ground
it's over it's over this is the end we just crossed the threshold 1.4 how low is it gonna go
how low is it gonna go who's gonna remain at the end of this whole thing i'm still here i'm still
here all right let's hit the music okay all right all right i'll put the shitty music back on i'll
put the terrible music back on i'm lost like 2 000 people i'm coming i'm coming all right hold
on wait wait wait oh my three thousand oh this hurts my stomach it's going down
uh i wonder what's actually happening this is kind of crazy
streamer laughs at losing viewers 1.1k this is the end twitch is broken oh whatever all right
this one sucks this one's just laughing as the market crashes well what would you do
you know if you opened up your portfolio and it was down like 75 percent i mean so you just have
to like light up the cigar and be like
not even a thousand people oh man we're going down to sub 1k who's gonna be left
who'll be remaining well those are those if there's this those are that are left that means you have
more of a vote you have more of a vote it's just gonna be me and i'm gonna keep streaming
to a brick wall and i don't even care hey yeah me york thanks for the five community subs
all right let's hey you get it you get a higher percentage vote that's good let's do that where
we going next 420 this is crazy watch this be the end watch this like a big scandal with twitch
this is it like this is it it's all but we have like delete it we have to delete it 200 people
i don't feel good check the news check the news check the news let's go to the news let's see
what's the news say what the fuck is this emergency alert system i i what's wrong with my computer
message is transmitted by request of the united states government oh reports are coming in from
officials of the undead rising from their graves and attacking the living in several states across
what the fuck they include massachusetts maine new hampshire vermont road island
connecticut new york oh no new jersey delaware and the district of columbia
oh no is a widespread crisis and it is believed that these undead creatures best described as
zombies these undead creatures best described as zombies i'm at zero
okay where are we going east coast i don't know what were we on viper i don't know no this is it
was vr slingshot okay do i actually have to no this is not going to like go into my helmet
or anything is it let me fucked up if it did okay okay let's go modem phone number
why do i need to put in a phone number uh press fire to begin how is this a slingshot
the lag is unreal is it press fire i don't know what fire is that one was uh interesting all right
so streamers choice guys i'm picking virus rage right i mean come on i have to do virus rage
you already had your choices and then i'm going up to video poker no i'm not i can't stream
video poker to zero people okay that's just not gonna happen virus rage uh okay press b to select
background practice mode space bar to get b oh that's better okay p to press space bar to begin
game virus one for space bar to begin what do i have to do video poker or riot this game sucks
no i just don't understand it i just don't understand it i just don't understand it i
just don't understand it okay guys today on the stream just chilling playing poker you know shit
six seven eight seven yes oh viewers going up viewers going up viewers going up viewers going
up play more poker viewers going up what do we got now 900 it's a sign it's a line nine back over
1k there it is all right if i get a full house i will change game not changing games not changing
games how many coins do i have what about what about the shields dude i can't wait to play
command and conquer that's three god i can't wait to play command and conquer i really can't face
camp if you get a full house six seven eight nine ten all right how many where's my money
this is the last hand i really thought people were dedicated to leaving the street i just think
yeah twitch is fucked up whatever i don't matter all right okay okay this i'm not doing this anymore
seven hour dos video poker stream just give me six fuck i had a flush i don't even i can't even
read these 1700 back in business all right and i'm really not gonna i'm not gonna sit here and do
this like that this was it's not even funny all right i won okay uh where are we going i can't
wait to play red alert i'm so excited uefa championships league tunnel b1 you guys are
only selecting tunnel b1 because it has a fruit snack commercial on it do a face reveal at 2000
viewers no i can't do that all right we're going um the virginia incident why is it what is that
oh no we're not we're going to tunnel b1 tunnel b1 2.2k face reveal why no face reveal
oh this this game is like 350 megabytes this isn't gonna run this is a big game
damn this has graphics in it guys is it loading can you see it yeah i'm gonna do my research
for red alert that's gonna be so much fun i think my computer is crushed uh tunnel b1
dude germa 3k we broke 3k no we didn't did we seriously i can't believe it
i can't believe we we broke 3k today's the day it's today here comes a face reveal
oh i dropped below 3k never mind sorry guys this game doesn't work this one doesn't work
please pick something else there's a couple of fun options i just passed 3k what the fuck are you
no way 3k 3k celebration eric is that the home depot song it was all right where are we going
uh all right what is this game i'm gonna go for it what is it
the home depot three is the dream song for three i'm sorry my brain is fucking fried this one's
also huge the bigger they are the harder they don't work by the way look at 650 megabytes
92 93 94 95 this is a huge game okay launching does it work i guess
oh this is two frames a second how much is that
this kind of looks like 3d movie maker target approaching fast
is it a dinner plate a blue confirmed that's affirmative blue ace she's tail
artifacting sorry i just painted this thing don't breathe in those fumes ufo object is semi
cylindrical unknown red markings a bit of static changing altitude accelerating accelerating
percept present is it spelling it out question mark alien anarchy that's not the name of this
game what am i the alien do i play as the alien that's a very quiet ship project and story
that's it that's it that's it it was just your short film and animation software
there's a game here you just watched someone's rat movie that's awesome then that makes me so
happy okay this is my 3d game studio we have to get the alien reveal we have to see the alien
there's no way this is the whole game this was 600 megabits megabytes that would be tiny yeah
that's just the intro here we go loading contact okay we're waiting it's gonna be at 5k they go
it goes all the way to zero then goes all the way up and it doesn't stop all right we i'm giving
this 25 more seconds it's worth it okay who am i controlling is this an fps oh dear this is an
fps i am the alien no i'm not do i have a weapon why are they just walking around grazing on the
grass hello what are they doing ants he just scanned me i think they're just scanning me
who is this not threatening can i talk to somebody what the hell was that there's a jeep here
hey they're friendly they're friendly they're friendly don't stay there they're friendly wait
wait wait a minute wait it's i'm an alien it's me it's me it's me what did we just want to scan
the planet run run do i have a scan why am i coughing like a human stop scanning and get over
there i don't understand am i not an alien i'm human so why are they killing me i'm still alive
you can't kill me motherfuckers okay it's because i got scanned i'm intrigued i'm gonna go find a
weapon control f12 speeds up dos box right is that gonna help though i don't think it's doing
anything all right all right like i go into the in the spaceship in the spaceship all right here
they come i need like a gun there has to be a weapon around here somewhere oh god here they come
there's a look at little house see if i can get in here can i jump i can't make it up her in the oh
i can it just took a while open control f12 control f12 control f12 there's a gap in the fence
is there should i just run away i'm just gonna run no way out is it you just there's an smg on
a hut near the water all right i'll try that smg on the hut near the water near the water
all right get out get out get out of the water get out of the water better get out of here now
i can't do anything w hit every button on the keyboard j z x c v b control do i at the very
beginning game the player receives a bio proc an alien device which works both as a map and
translator he can use four kinds of weapons including an alien one he'll also need to find
a key to unlock stuff all right come on where do i have that oh shit it's f1 okay where's the gun
near the hut come on they're right here don't make me do this again where's the gun give me
the gun all right grab gun get gun get it it's right here get the gun one two three four five
six seven f1 f2 space click go inside i can't move all right i made it in got the gun what
happened are they just looking for me okay that spaceship is way smaller than i thought it was
inches man inches this is uh 14 is 14 hours and 20 minutes
human listen the soldiers captured our shuttle you must find it here this will help you
beware of the grays now go find the shuttle greetings to the freeman
mr gordon freeman please what were those and um what were the aliens in half life yes the
cool ones okay warning you must rescue the shuttle at any cost your people are not prepared to handle
our technology one moment receiving life signs from a survivor proceed to the city hospital and
find the survivor why is there an alien in the hospital why not whoa i thought loading local
hospital they captured it so this is just a street you really need a better pc no it's not me
okay can i talk to people put it down put it down put it down put it down put it down put it down
put it down put it down put it down put how do i put it down put it down put it down okay it's
down no it's not i can't put it down and i can't walk put it down please put it down please
he won't put it down i can't take it off i can't i can't put put down it's so frozen turn off
okay increase the cycle rate of the emulator i know i tried i tried
okay don't why do i have a cross here go in the hospital okay this is a little better
what i just pick up ammo is this a hospital look at how huge these doors are this is a
monstrous door i am a normal human don't mind me i'm going to save what happened why are you
why are you shooting me why are you shooting me what the fuck what where am i what is this
i'm wanted well there's nothing even up here all right last try and i'm gonna go straight
the front door i need to see i have to see one thing last thing i promise i know it i know
everyone's gonna puke i know me too i just need to get in i need one more i need to get in there
i gotta get in that the hospital just go to the thing i will you don't have access to the second
floor spam control f12 i'm actually feeling sick i know i'm sorry will i die what the fuck
all right last try somebody said do control f11 maybe it's trying to go too fast
oh now he's losing viewers for real
okay i'm just gonna go into the hospital door i'm just i get i'm allowed into the hospital i'm
just a person that one had potential to why does it have to run like shit all right let's uh let's
scroll down tom tommy tommy's tower tommy's show and tell maze generator tommy tommy spades tommy's
old mate tommy's monopoly tommy tommy you made a lot of games tommy tommy tommy tommy tommy's
patience tommy's fan tommy's double l tommy's global thermonuclear war uh there's a porn game
under here by the way uh there's an actual like naked lady right here so hello and give me one
second okay uh you ready no porn right no porn games no like boobs in the thumbnails where are
we going tommy's porn so what uh that's a that's a risky click it's just like i don't know what the
fuck this even could be this is freaking me out i don't know you don't title your name sorry
ass unless you have like you're mad and i don't know it's a donkey we want tommy how do i get
how do i get points can't handle this one anymore uh try again okay i don't care i'm playing silly
night i'm just clicking that one no matter what so the slugger or smallinsk to moscow this is
going to be another management game where i have to manage resources and i'm going to get stuck in
a menu i'm going to play silly night here we go it's getting wacky silly night new game
all right i get it i get it i get it i understand 2017 key what does this do light the fire climb
kill skeleton uh it's actually kind of fun but how do i get green key i can't jump up there
i can't get that oh my god i'm laughing so hard the fucking he ha ha silly night this is bowser's
castle you just collect keys oh shit where am i next next next next hold on wait wait
hold on wait wait i need that golden key i wait i need green key no can't get up there damn this
game's hard all right fine fine fine fine fine it's fun it's cute it's cute it's cute i'm gonna
pick the one that everyone else is picking that besides that we didn't play the slugger it was
very cute all right let's do it yes one player f3 game speed one to eight what is eight uh i want
to be the home team uh or should i be what color should be okay f7 how do i swing wait are we ready
play ball do i have to stand at the batter's box play ball let's go all right here we go this is
the atari safe it's going too fast strike got him strike strike three you're out strike three
you're out strike strike i just want a chance to hit okay two outs i know i know i know i'm aware
this is the most boring thing i've ever done on the channel definitely this what i'm doing right
now is the most boring thing i've ever done on this stream that's not true oh oh please
what was more boring than this tell me fishing fish that was like some of the most fun i've ever
had but wait it's my my turn my turn how do i swing did i just hit it back to the picture
three times the surge okay no no this it was not the surge all right streamer's choice i'm playing
sink or swim all right now we're gonna go back and we do some popular ones somebody said the
labo is terrible what planet are you from what are you talking about those are the best streams
some of the best streams i've ever done i love those streams what are you talking about all right
keyboard and sound system silent sound blaster the sonic birdhouse stream that was fun remember
i hit my i hit my desk with a hammer that's exciting pause wrap jump activate switches
it's like sonic the hedgehog what is going on i have to save them all right go back everyone
over here all right then i go over there and we go target it's like lemmings but with less lemmings
done no bucket done i'm not gonna give it time all right it's time to go to the popular section
this is the popular section what have what have i not done in the popular section monkey island
is a game that's that's that's a long stream any standing out here because i played almost a lot
of these i remember the ford simulator any that i did i missed sim earth no i can't i can't i
tried it already do wipe out where's wipe out wipe out i scrolled by it oh this right here
all right we'll do wipe out i feel like did i do this one battle chess is classic it's a problem
i don't know how to play chess i know what every individual piece does but i don't know how to use
them all effectively it's a big game these games are cool and all but when you can play doki doki
literature club not gonna happen all right here we go this one's already not doing well
no this was a heavily requested one i can't make the cycles go faster
no i love my doctor i'm almost there just go through eight more splash screens
maybe the game will be okay sometimes that happens control f12 yeah i've done it a thousand times
sorry sorry i tried sorry what else we got here we did lemmings before
i love this like dos popcorn streams you eat a handful of dos games and even if you get a
crunchy shitty burnt ass colonel it's all right he's gonna spit it out anyway so who cares there's
still plenty of popcorn left hugo's house of horrors is this a good one no we'll find out
hey some adventure games we still we stuck with for a long time there's been at least a handful
of these dos adventure games that score of zero of 190 oh we have 10 community steps coming from
near shoe thank you near shoe i go in boss button you are in total control of hugo's destiny as he
searches the haunted house for his sweetheart palpy she was last seen going into this house on a
babysitting assignment you may control hugo's motion with the arrow keys or keypad and they
also give him simple commands to pick up or look at something which catches your eye a very useful
phrase would be open the door on the first screen for example others are look and look at okay be
on the lookout for useful or valuable objects they may very well help you in your quest for
penalty keep your wits about you save and restore f6 is inventory s9 is the boss button for people
who like to sneak in a game during office hours it simply shells you out to dos you must hit exit
to rejoin your game this button will allow you to keep a game going in the background while you do
your normal work in the dos shell holy shit you thought of everything type or print the hints
file at the dos prompt all right let's go open the door it's locked look at pumpkin there appears
to be something inside of it open pumpkin apparently our hero either doesn't understand
what you mean or doesn't think that would be very useful grab pumpkin okay you're carrying a pumpkin
kick the pumpkin in the face smash the pumpkin smash pumpkin okay the pumpkin breaks open to
reveal a key grab key you're not close enough is this game scary open door use key apparently
our hero either you use the key open door with key you're holding a key unlock door
okay open door yeah hey what don't close me out what are you doing this is san's house
follow the old man i'm having trouble going up the stairs quick here goes the boss jeremy
jeremy what are you doing over there um uh i'm just working on some stuff okay keep up the good work
all right thanks how do i go back in escape exit how do you go back in the game the mad
professor speaks oh there you are i've been looking all over the house for you look you're
late and we haven't much time step into the box and we'll begin the experiment the professor beckons
you to step into the large cubicle in the center of the room who's the ogre good okay igor press
the blue button igor grumbles something incoherent and deftly presses the red button you idiot igor
that's all i need a colorblind imbecile for an assistant oh dear i've got my headache coming
on again i've had enough hassle for one day i'm going to have to lie down the professor storms
off leaving you alone with igor they just made me smaller all right let's talk to igor you ought
to be aware that talking to oneself is talk to igor igor is good at taking orders but is not
much of a conversationalist igor press blue button igor presses the yellow button here we go press
the yellow button maybe he'll eventually press the right one i think you better leave that igor
press yellow button he presses the green button oh shit that's not good igor press green button
now he presses the blue one what do i do all right let's go find it let's go wake the professor up
open door now it's a bathroom i'd rather not 23 of 190 yeah it's going pretty well
three three three there appears to be something daubed on the mirror in red
it looks like the numbers three three three
all right where's the professor sleeping is this bed what's that what is that a head grab
what is this helmet grab helmet grab bag what is it you don't have it look look i'm looking i'm
looking look i can see no more than you at this moment look down look at face i describe it more
like a mask okay look at bed you get down on your hands and knees and peer under the bed to find
absolutely nothing oh come on put it on uh now snap igor's neck the high frequency cosmic radiation
emanating from this room knocks your mask into the floor okay uh let's go down put it back on
i will and i need to cosmic radiation the 5g room how do i i wait i could be smaller than going
there i can go in the little mouse hole okay hold on kitchen grab broom gonna do some sweeping are
we hey the broom must be gripped by some magical powers despite your best efforts you can't budget
well that's strange it's too green i hope this is not locked because it's panning the ass to get
over here three three three three three three bingo nice i'm so glad i went in the bathroom
uh what the fuck is in here it's too dark to see anything turn on light i don't have any lights
i need a candle or something all right well this is this is open get the candle from the table
good idea that's a good idea it's an outhouse good thinking good thinking nice work wait let's
check the other rooms first uh you ought to be aware that talking to oneself talk to dracula
dracula very good sir sniff eh just a moment you're not one of us you're a blooming interloper
come here you little boy i'm going to chop your head off you ought to be aware it appears your
game is up so to speak the butler did athlete slices your head off with a handy carving knife
uh you are carrying a mask and oh shit i needed the mask shit damn it play treasure mountain
is that on here what else we got treasure mountains right next to it let's know oh
super solvers treasure mountain that is right it's right here all right the master of mischief has
stolen the crown and hidden the treasures of treasure mountain you the super solver must find
the treasures and take them to the top of the mountain hidden keys can open the gateways up
the mountain this is mega man the elves can help you catch them in your net to get coins and clue
words they will help you find treasures in the keys as the treasure chest is filled you will
earn your stars win the crown and save treasure mountain i thought that was a face it was a
backpack oh it fits hi my name is flutter as your guide i will give you new player hints to help you
learn to play the game use left and right to move left to right up and go out the door okay
see i thought that was a face i thought this is yeah he's facing this way but a hat on look at
that stride drop coin well what did i do that for you spacebar to drop your net and catch
elves they have coins and clue words to help you find treasures
do i get them get over here to hold it
tall tall tallest small smaller smallest great job super solver here's your new clue word
i didn't get him flowers
flowers right there got the key you found the key yeah find the lock and press to open it this game
is unbelievable rocket ship you found a treasure this hiding place matches two of the three clue
words help me make another word start with c take away the c help me make another word start with
cake take away the c ache put a new letter in its place which letter should be take good job
super solver flowers you found a dog i cannot see over the wall because i am not very tall
flowers ground i have the key
day did dear dark these words all start the same pick one more word that starts that way
to play the starting sound game dish good job big round flowers can i make this easier than preschool
is there a difficulty
i mean harder
can i make it harder to make the game easier any clues in here options no it's just
it's it's just for like a two-year-old
catch an elf i caught like 10 of them your net is worn out find the net cave don't i have the key
i thought i had the key
me there they are there it is i need a net cave any beer why did you guys want me to play this
you picked it no somebody said to play it somebody said you better play that
it's cute you know what it is you're right it is cute i want to do more puzzles
yes net cave nets for coins what a rip-off yeah all right well here we go let's grab this guy
let's grab this one i'm wasting my net why won't they get caught all right back up god he's so
fucking dumb kids game kids game kids play this they don't the kids need to know how to use
dos their parents set this up for them and their parents play it with them
you think a kid knows how to mount a drive and dos nope i use my ears to hear a bell i use my
feet to smell a smell my eyes all right getting close to being the end of this one
round not round the snowmen around oh goes around key scary boss level the game looks bad
it's okay it's cute i hope we get a riddle at the end of this
wall that was holy shit man that was really impressive damn yeah you make it to my final dungeon
what am i going there are 300 treasures look for two treasures of each level
net scrub what
do
finish this tonight i'm not going to play this for another 10 minutes
let alone like three hours all right if i don't get the next little word puzzle
in less than one second i am stupid okay here we go
i just killed that person i just pushed that person off the edge oops
fed fed bed bed slide got it right here one
clubhouse now this is my clubhouse
oh this is kind of like the witcher three but it's better
yeah i've never played the witcher three i own it
i think i i have not even seen the menu of the game flying fish all right let's
see if i can do this in one second how about you could sell sell sell uh fall there you go two two
come here great bastard this game's good chat doesn't like good things
it's it's i like it elf x-ing
the tunnel shortcut
two ah four coins for another net oh by the way if you're wondering what we're doing
going to stream the game awards we're doing that on thursday
uh
that's cool it was cool it was fun but i i sat there and ate the popcorn for too long
what is super munchers the challenge continues this looks like words um yep dude i'm gonna
knock this out of the park this is like celebrities and shit this is not math this is words super
munchers options set content set adjust difficulty here we go what grade uh we'll just we'll do
player chooses that's fine all right i'm ready set the games animals famous americans food and
health geography music odds and ends this is gonna be amazing oh i can't wait to do this
let's go i don't need instructions we're gonna do beginner animals animals with fur or hair
elk uh horse dog rat goat dog uh beaver hair um a squirrel elk mole i wouldn't even want to go
that way i was like what i clicked over here that's stupid hurry up uh for hair flea fish
flounder swordfish got it stegosaurus all right this is a little too easy this is do you know what
a fish is what i thought it was hammerhead copperhead shark like i thought it was a shark
insects crab crabs and lobsters are insects did that one real quick the evil dr franken
troggle wants to create a franken troggle monster to foil this plot super muncher needs the map
that shows the way through the halls of castle franken troggle a disguised troggle has the map
but which troggle is it this one right here which disguised troggle is reggie code work
it's reggie just had a hat on that was that disguise good work super muncher now has the
map after three more levels you'll help super muncher with another mission animals uh bugs
considered animals okay just making sure some people put them as a different like category
what about okay no never mind shrimp this why don't you go this way why would you walk up
instead of right all right i gotta make this harder this is okay this is too fucking easy
this is so easy you know what i mean i i need to make this a little harder it's a lobster a mammal
where you going down okay what was that i'm super muncher you can kill them now okay cool
i didn't even mean to click that i didn't mean to click that i do not mean to click that um it's
trice bird bug bird bug bird bug bug bug hamster it's triceratops animals with feathers
i'm clicked on mouse all right super muncher needs a key to the mad doctor's lab a troggle
is about to hide the key where will the troggle hide the key ready hide the key i'm super muncher
you did it all right no more okay um stop here i want it to be harder not animals
options set content difficulty advanced and set games uh what the fuck oh this is fine okay that's
fine let's make this a little harder i do not need instructions famous americans odds and ends
odds and ends holidays holidays all of december that was all right furniture uh bed there it is
there a chase lounge chest that's furniture right walnut desk or an actual walnut borax
that's like a chemical i didn't want to click there why would you no and i don't even have
the fucking superhuman anymore what the fuck cars oh uh um i don't know the wednesday that's not
what about a colt the regal wednesday is not a car an elba oh i'm gonna lose toda topaz
corsica it has to be corsica or the crete i didn't click on reliant wednesday wednesday
my favorite kind of car the chevy wednesday all right how about uh food and health vegetables
okay um eggplant cardoon peas turnip a rickets ice cream five i don't know what any of these are
sulfur is not a vegetable it's a smelly chemical compound lima bean kohlrabi
herb spices and seasonings coriander propane saffron curry rosemary cumin
rabies bay leaf malaria oh god propane is not a seasoning it's a gas
osmium paprika and dante and dante somebody lied to me you lied to me that's fine and dante osmium
allegro mace there's like the thing you sprayed no is it fife it's at mace is a spray seasoning
famous americans sports figures okay uh what oh that's he's that's not a sports figure that's
just a guy that that's a really important guy that's an astronaut not a sports figure
all right anyway all right i know these uh okay uh i don't know tennis arthur charlton heston
tennis tennis tennis tennis tennis tennis i don't know anything about tennis you lied
i got fucking lied to this is like sir this one's too hard game over irving irving dempsey you idiot
dempsey mchale and irving who's who i don't know born in the 1800s george tekei what that one's
way too hard let's do geography countries in europe all right this is let's see countries in
europe uh it's alabama uh is lebanon in europe no it's not i knew it i knew it iceland no iceland
isn't it was iceland landmarks and features in asia i have no idea i have absolutely no idea
i don't know any of them i know it's not the panama canal or vancouver island uh uh
i don't know um the dead sea i sent one person said nile delta and i was like no it's not and
i clicked anyways god damn it lock nests yeah do it again do it again again again large bodies of
water other than lakes large bodies of water switzerland is a large body of water uh let's
see uh was it gulf mexico there let's go deserts i know that one because it's right here it's like
a hundred miles that way whatever it is super no that's that's not correct this one i'm missing
here which one is it the kalahari desert the atacama desert okay i don't know i don't know
it has to be this one there's another one indus far all right cities cities not no like cities not
the places okay phoenix uh tismania okay okay now that's it's not ill it's not chicago that's the
state guys uh nobody said that i think was being spammed i couldn't even read
i don't know this nope there it is the evil doctor frank and trogel monster create a frank
and trogel monster to foil this plot the super monster needs the map who has the map
south korea south korea south korea uh no i didn't mean to click that no i did not
i did not mean to click that okay uh um um no this one booty booty booty okay i got it got it got it
somebody lied to me again you guys keep lying to me the one person that keeps lying to me
what music musical instruments the sousaphone the tuba the uh i don't know
what any of this stuff is the alto horn the dulcimer the diphtheria theremin dulcimer
sherville they sound like drugs is it is it a dulcimer double bass clarinet chimes the theremin
the steel drum the the cornet the the motet liar top pop rock acts of the 1980s
they release this number four uh okay hold on hold on uh like stones madonna was madonna the 80s
yep uh all right pat boone who the fuck is pat boone you were the target audience i was not
the target audience i was like fucking two i was i was one years old in the mid 80s
supremes the cars uh war that's gonna be too hard it's gonna be all stuff from the 80s
audidence audidence i like this one holidays why am i so obsessed with this game sports uh
handball bowling boxing uh badminton softball tennis uh paddle ball field hockey polo rugby
yeah units of measurement inch inch pint uh pint minute measurement it's one it's a minute
a gallon an hour a inch kill a uh a ton a uh a jewel all right who's doing this
find them it's the same guy every time it's never anybody else shapes cube cylinder cube
circle diamond pentagon triangle sphere diamond parallelogram that's like a no that's a uh
that's a like a thing in poetry uh we're octagon pentagon triangle it is it is it is but what
parallel parallelogram okay an arm it's not an arm that's because he was standing on it
do you see that fucking reaction time oblong kitchen utensils oh man uh ice tongs a teaspoon
a ladle an egg beater a pitcher a can opener i'm not gonna get that yet because i might get grabbed
a egg beater a tablespoon cleaver egg beater tablespoon cookie cutter easy clothing a uh kilt
a overalls jeans uh kimono kilt coat uh shovel culottes culottes what's a culotte uh can't know
a trowel a trowel uh culottes jod purrs i don't i don't what the hell is that what's a jod purr
in the dumpster you hide it in the dumpster every time it's not hard and i'm standing in the way
it's always in the dumpster planets would you look at that neptune neptune mercury mercury
jupiter pluto no this takes place in the 80s when they were too stupid to know that
planet right constellations scorpio gemini pices scorpio uh big dipper uh what the hell was that
who did you just eat what did you just eat what did you just eat uh aquarius uh gemini up there
pices over here pegasus uh nope uh
draco uh
orion where are we what do we got draco draco sagittarius don't walk into them
i knew it was gonna happen i didn't click on gemini uh mercury what am i missing here hydro
is roads why would i ever listen to somebody if no one else wrote that cars bmw
porsche ferrari mustang porsche the big dipper jaguar oh easy where they gone sob jaguar
go to eat each other sky lark the festival that's not i don't think that's a car is it
go to thank god you didn't lie to me i'm so happy the reliant i clicked this before and it was
wrong oh shit the borneo is that right borneo is it real is it real is it reliant real what's the
last one the festival was that correct you fucker oh no i want to do it one more time but this time
i want to do food and health organs of the human body pancreas large intestine stomach
they live at the kidneys the large intestine the brain the brain the thyroid gland
the brain the the measles bumps that's not correct thyroid brain stomach large intestine
the large intestine and the thymus the thymus what's a berry berry oh it's right here okay
dairy products milk ice cream cheese cheese cheese cheese cheese
cheese whey yogurt whey whey that was very easy nuts pecan cashew pecan macadamia brazil nut cashew
almond brazil nut and let's go dude this is fucking just pumped up let's go the the litchi nut
the blueberry the date the eggs the way the bacon the cashew the turnip the bread the pear the eggs
the date is a date a nut it is a date and a filbert nut i gotta get to the third cut scene
wait who was it it was you vegetables i didn't i mean that typhoid parsnip asparagus a
is garlic a vegetable or is that a spice that's a vegetable technically right it's a that's a
vegetable it's like a root spice down people to classify that as a spice garbanzo beans
what's a breadfruit what is it what which one of these is a vegetable it's not walnut it's a nut
stop writing things that are wrong and i i'll see it and click it i know it's a nut i have them
downstairs i eat them all the time somebody said walnut and i fucking lost it oh yeah walnut that
seems correct is it the cardoon it's not a tambourine herb spices and seasonings okay here we go
now that's a vitamin uh ginger wait hold on i'm scared to go over there what's mar marjoram
marjoram is that it's everywhere it has to be correct cauli chili pepper what is cauli
de capo i'm not looking at chat ever again quartz sage oregano
cassia talc it's not talc you don't eat talc
thallium is it cassia curry jeez this one is doesn't look like nutrients vitamin a proteins
niacin is sodium technically a nick a nicotine no that's sodium not nicotine is sodium technically
the nicotine this game did come out in the 80s potassium riboflavin vitamin d proteins magnesium
calcium carbohydrates vitamin d okay acetone phosphorus oboe fuchsia beige cobalt rabies
potassium choline right i don't know i don't know what choline is nice okay hold on
mumps rabies dysentery acetone cobalt fuchsia what is what are these fuchsia liars if this chat is
full of liars liars everywhere that's a color that's purple it's cobalt cobalt is it it's not
cobalt it's not cobalt it's not cobalt it's not cobalt oh my god it's cobalt blame like
minecraft for fucking me up on that one i just think of the the blue stones in the wall
i didn't even look i didn't even look at the dumpster again i wasn't even looking
i wasn't even looking at the screen i was looking only at chat i don't know where he put it
thank you grains i'm gonna fuck this up i'm gonna fuck this up i'm gonna fuck this up
i'm gonna fuck this up i'm gonna fuck this up i'm gonna accidentally do something i'm gonna
fuck this up okay hold on i'm gonna screw it up what the hell happened no i want to get to the
next level i'm addicted to this dumb kids game i don't i don't know what a stout is the rush
i didn't okay i gotta i gotta rage quit i have to get out i have to rage quit i have to get out
of this game i have to i have to run as fast as i can fisher no he's sitting on loon cardinal come
on stop changing my words starling in cattle and sheep family cattle and sheep is a chinchilla a
cow no it's like a marsupial or a rodent these are different names for i don't i have no idea
wildebeest i don't i don't know what i don't know what like a visacha is i don't know what
what's a vischacha what is that i've never heard that word before never not once d hole is a fox
i know what the vole is i i don't get that's the that's the the little um the little mob boss guy
from uh zootopia so i know what that is that's not a cow it's definitely vischacha
i'm okay i can quit the game i'm quitting again i have to get up i have to leave again
uh i don't know what a margay is in the camel family i know what these are i know what an alpaca
is but not what a visuna is a drone a drone dairy bactrian camel has camel in the name it has to be
right all right guanaco camel okay we're never gonna get to see the second cut scene the third
cut scene i mean it's not ever gonna happen reptiles i'll get this one to check this out
dinosaurs dinosaurs is impossible because everything can sound like a dinosaur you just
have to have something saurus on it i'm gonna assume that all the things with saurus are real
okay there goes all the sources triceratops down here uh that's a tree pangolin monoclonius
fucking liar you fucking liar all right shit i want to play it again how do you drive a car
very very carefully all right we'll do one more we'll do one more i can't believe i've been sitting
here for six hours i'm actually surprised what is the one more though that's this is important
what's the one more that's the one more we did mixed up mother goose already what's the last
one of the night none of these are speaking to me right now none of them are speaking to me
remember pizza worm that game was sick speaking to me something speak to me here no no no no no
no it's not doing it for me god when you have everything nothing just the man that has everything
look at that i have everything i i'm not satisfied not that one wwf wrestle mania i played
it already and it was hard to control done got it checks quest i actually think people
requested that i play this what the fuck is this new game easy does it not so sticky gobs of goo
extreme ooze gobs of goo okay that's control is there a jump why does this have any what's this
have to do with checks picked up slime repellent why is this checks again you're the checks guy
they don't have a checks guy there is no checks guy to have a mini zork recharge uh checks hanger
2a is this supposed to be like the marshmallows or something does what does that do cereal it's
slime right what does that do checks he doesn't know the lore no i don't
this game's actually kind of scaring me something about this is just odd it's i don't know what it
is but i don't i don't like it at all i don't like this i have a blue key right
switch weapons i i have a spoon was that supposed to be melee cereal dusk yeah it is
glass of water it's a doom mod i guess yeah
he's biased against checks yes checks is awful it's just there's nothing too it's just like it's
it's chewing on cardboard now well i got red right what's it a healthy dinner there's carrots
and lettuce in a checks game why would it not be a bowl of checks and that more on brand they're
not chilling i guess all right what do i need to go what is that zork you picked up a zork pack
checks what's this say checks buzoic nutritional development center i feel like i'm walking in
circles am i i think i might be this somebody definitely has a speed run on this game
i wonder what the speed run for this is
uh
what the fuck
okay that guy was hard this room is full of enemies you can see a child being terrified of this
i'm terrified of this well that that means you're confirmed to be a child that's me it just is dusk
there are five levels you think i i'm not gonna beat this i'm surprised i got through level one
do it do it can i do that oh i got a rapid zapper oh next slide clap next slide clap
next slide clap next slide clap are they bosses press minus so you can see your amber oh shit
look at the little check face look at the checks face i don't like these sound effects
yeah they're pretty bad i'm almost dead i can't turn turn turn turn get the fruit
a bowl of fruit is 10% health get out of here
alt just straight what was that super checks armor 200 armor that's pretty good
all right this is just a bunch of beavers that's all i hear
even the scream too all right now i'm super charged i'm ready i can't fight the first boss
why am i still playing this i like this for some reason i don't but i do
can i go higher than 200 yellow key it's a classic yeah i guess it is
is new weapon oh you got the phasing torture let me test it love it all right good yellow
what whoa teleporter
you dead this thing's powerful whoa youtuber reaction whoa let me just open up this door
there's somebody in front of me whoa no no it's in here 2019 game of the year check i will see on
thursday join me germa 985 as we watch the game awards am i blind yes what the fuck are you doing
stop it please sing more where is it i didn't i try to switch this on
oh power lifter
i have a map doing
power lift that doesn't work giant enemy spider yeah i've seen a lot of people do videos on that
what's going on there by the way why are people doing that tab is the map oh shit something above
this it's just that kind of came out of nowhere from a video i mean like six years ago seven
years ago all right i need to get this i need to move this power lift power lift i can't get it
all right where we going oh i see where i have not explored that way what are you doing giant
enemy spider and i i do like a pokemon right i'm getting this right aren't i
open oh you're dumb where am i not going this way i have no idea
play the rest of the game like this um i don't think i can yes i can uh where do i need to go
oh shit i found it got it sword okay i have to turn the stream off like i have to get out of here
i have to turn the stream do you know why i have to turn the stream off somebody why why don't turn
the stream off for what because i have to i have to go and get uh red alert ready i can't wait
oh i'm gonna do a bunch of research this is not even the right way to go use the wall the wall
the wall wait what uh okay is this it's the that's the power lift you don't even turn it on it's
already on i figured out why i don't like these things because this is what a monster looks like
in your dream this is a nightmare monster you know when you have a dream about something
that that's not scary at all but it is because it's real in your dream this is what they look
like and it even looks like this in your dreams too well pixelated and strange and just doesn't
make any sense i've actually seen these green things probably in a nightmare before and they're
just so fucking weird and it doesn't make any sense and they're not scary but they're real
i don't like it yeah because you don't get a gun in your dream you you get like a dull pair
of scissors that you drop five times and you can't punch no it sucks all right what this is a secret
door what is this you guys have had the dream where somebody's outside your house and you know
they're going to come in and you know that the door is open or unlocked and you are rushing to
try to lock the door and you know that they're almost at the door and you have to close the door
not only does door have to close but lock too because they can just open it that's the worst
thing in the world so one of the worst feelings you're gonna have in a dream is here comes these
guys they're gonna they're gonna they're gonna come in and they're gonna kill me they're coming
in to kill me or do something terrible i gotta close the door i have to lock the door and you
get there and they're there and you don't turn the little thing or this also happens in your
dream your lock sucks and it doesn't hold them at all they just kind of put a shoulder into it
and it just opens you have this little baby lock oh that's the worst i can actually keep going
i didn't think i was going to end this stream getting lost in checks quest but it happened
yeah i hate dropping shit in streams this is the most annoying thing in the world
i wouldn't drop that that many times i would not fumble around that many times trying to like run
away your brain just can't do anything my blue door i've told you this before
but it is worth mentioning again another strange thing about dreams especially dreams that i have
sometimes is there'll be somebody in my dream that's supposed to be directly related to me
or a close friend of mine and it's not even them i'll be walking around in my in my house or
something and my dad will be walking around and it's like oh that's dad no it's my dad doesn't
have a mustache and black hair and that doesn't look anything like my dad but that's dad why is
that like that's just dead no it's not real dad and then you start thinking about like what are
dreams and am i like in somebody else's reality is this like a different life that i was in
and then you wake up and you go i gotta call dad it's past memories it's my past emotions coming
when i lived 400 years ago my father had a mustache i don't know where the fuck i'm going
i think i've had about enough of uh of doom checks i think i've had about enough there's a door over
here that i can't open well what what is it why is this listed here as a door see you're in my
dream yeah but how many times have you guys had a dream about me and i have a mustache and like
the orange hair or something click the link click the link i don't want to accidentally
so show anything fucked up what is it yeah i've seen this yeah i've seen this all right i'm done
that's it the stream's over i'm not doing checks quest anymore get this music out of here that was
pretty good though they got rayman on here why did i not just play that they got gremlins 2 the new
batch on here wait a minute i'm not done yet did i try to play i think i tried to play this last
time didn't i did i try to play gremlins last time no i did i played this did i yeah i did i
did i did yeah i played it already i remember playing it god damn it i did play it fuck show
the image i'm gonna show it don't worry is this what i look like in your dreams remind me to never
grow a mustache i mean the one on the left doesn't look that bad i can't grow a mustache this thick
guys this is never gonna happen yeah i do herald rivera
it just is that's a picture of herald oh all right herald oh rivera young let's see
this is any pictures exist of herald oh and he was young no none okay it kind of does it kind of
hold on we need a side-by-side comparison wario yeah i there is some wario in there you're right
what did i just save it to why is blending in with the bat i can't even see this
you know when you save a picture somewhere and you know you're looking at the right folder
but it just doesn't exist for some strange reason you're certain that you know it's here
okay i got it you would think this was not the top one the top one's not even close
you look older in the other picture
yeah i do i do look about five to ten years older than herald oh i'm the older herald oh
all right i'll see you guys tomorrow we are going to do it i'm gonna do red alert
it should be fun i'm ready to go nuts on this game i'm gonna do like custom scenarios and shit
it's um i'll have a backup just in case it's a disaster but i think it should be fun
thanks for watching see you tomorrow are you sticking around listed the bits and the subs
what game red alert command and conquer red alert i'm gonna see if i can get it to run
nancy drew we need a nancy drew cooldown we can't just go hard on nancy drew
i'm gonna do the original red alert the first one hey sauce bird thanks for the 300 bits
uh hey germa hope you're doing well this happened a while ago but i specifically remember someone
cheering to tell you that your larry david impression sucks well he sucks i think it's
great could you do larry david giving a final battle speech i'd love to hear it if you're
able to have a great rest of your night i uh no tomorrow i'll open with it tomorrow it's i can't
do it i can't do it i know i can't listen to my throat listen to my voice and there's no way i can
do it what would you have no way i know i can't i can't do it i have to do it tomorrow i'll do
it tomorrow i'll do it tomorrow here's the thing you guys need to know about impressions
that i do on the stream sometimes they just come out i don't know how to do them i don't i don't
know how to do impressions i don't they just they snap in and then that's it i can never do i don't
know how to do them i was doing um i was doing no country for old men a week or two ago it was
pretty fucking good i can't do that again i don't even know where it came from i have no idea where
it came from i can't i could not do that for you right now it's called possession it's called you
have a split personality what and one of my personalities is can do impressions you're a
vessel it's called you're fucked one of your personalities is larry david
i could do it i can no i can't only the person that takes over and does impressions can do it
and they're not here right now dude ronnie that was me pretending to be the person that takes over
thank you sauce for appreciate that that guy that guy's shift ended that guy shift ends two and a
half hours into the stream is this the guy who streamed poker to zero viewers yep that dude
just sits here in the back of my head for the first two or three hours and is like let's go
what am i gonna do what character am i doing today and two or three hours goes by he gets bored
and he leaves and he doesn't come back till tomorrow you can stay but i'm leaving he takes
20 of your brain cells with him probably hey michael thanks for the 500 but hey germa it's
been a while since i've caught you streaming and had the money to donate but i wanted to mention
that your rant about ghosts and family members watching us from the afterlife was almost a
straight-up rip of george carlin's material i loved it and i think it is further proof that
you're one of the greatest entertainers of our time you're great man thanks for everything
there's mitchell not michael thank you mitchell possessed by george carlin he's a joke thief
oh he's riz ripping him off oh damn it you know i think about that sometimes i'm like oh i have
this idea i want to do this and i want to try this and i haven't done this yet and then you're
like you i google search some of these things that i do has anyone done that yet and then you're
like no this person said something like that but you guys understand how in like a thousand more
years it's going to be really dip imagine like imagine somebody trying to make the speed joke
in like 100 years 200 years and they're like playing team fortress well this old game from
like 250 years ago wow this is great look at this character oh wait what's it the spy oh it's a
speed i plays the speed why am i even referencing that that that's like my greatest achievement
music too in like a thousand years every song will have ever been made
that we'll we'll get to the end of all notes in every order there's gonna have to be a new
form of music someone's gonna make a new instrument people are gonna have to start like playing their
like playing their like skin i don't know like grabbing their skin and like flicking it or
something
clapping that's true all right let me get back on track anyways there's gonna have to be some
new instruments or new sound waves in a thousand years they've gonna have been every movie has
been made they need to go to bed i'm not even i'm not tired i am not tired i think it's time
for the cadence to have some sleep where are we anyways uh thank you mitchell for the 500 bits
appreciate that thank you heathcliff the friday thriller thanks for the 250 bits hi jeff do you
mind if i call you jeff anyway can you do the neelix voice please i can't i can do it pretty
good though when he's when he's when he's here when he shows up and he gets in there it's it's
i think it's pretty good and you are actually talking to jeff which must be the person that's
in there congrats on 3k viewers i was here when you had zero how the times change i know that's
true i went from zero viewers to like 5 000 in one day uh i want to make sure i hit these subs
because i don't think i know we got we got turkey tama zorro carlos thanks for the five each jeff
gave five i want to make sure was i like i must have been preoccupied in my brain uh porcupine
gave five subs as well we had that raid from rt game crowd which thank you so much rt appreciate
anybody that stuck around uh that if you're still here thanks for watching thanks rt for that rt is
a swell dude i've had the pleasure of uh spending some time with him in real life really really nice
person good dude stand for approval uh bob boy of course who could forget bob bob boy's five
community subs thank you bob boy right now you hung out with a minecraft youtuber everybody is
a minecraft youtuber i'll put you here's your homework for tomorrow find me of somebody that
made youtube videos from 2012 to 2016 that doesn't have a minecraft video there's your homework
everyone's saying star that's not true sorry incorrect he had a whole series on his second
channel of like a 10 15 videos so sorry even i have a minecraft video three actually yeah
everybody has a minecraft video yeah he made yeah everybody has a minecraft video it was like the
biggest thing in the world it was the biggest thing in the world it was like fortnite times two
almost like what five six seven years ago it was a times two fortnite they had a convention there's
no fortnite con there's a minecon and it was more popular than like pax was so everybody played it
no fortnite con yet but no there's not going to be a fortnite con i will eat a whole shoe on camera
if there's a fortnite con just kidding just kidding just kidding just kidding just kidding
just kidding see now the clip is ruined it's not going to be a fortnite con it might be no it's
not it's not going to be that popular in like five years ten years it's a very popular game
right now but it doesn't have the minecraft staying power no no way no no way but let's keep
moving uh acceptable causalities thanks for the 500 bits when's the christmas stream there is going
to be no christmas stream this year sorry there was going to be one but the minecraft fuck the king
server has replaced it because the law all the time effort resources and energy that's going
to make this work so the minecraft stuff is going to be replacing any holiday themed christmas type
thing christmas is cancelled i'm actually crying it's all right don't worry uh but thank you to
the 500 bits thank you red lemonade for the 1500 bits and the 10 community subs thank you red
lemonade they say nothing just 1500 bits and 10 subs appreciate that it's very generous much
love to you thank you uh volemy gave 5000 bits earlier thank you for the 50 dollars volemy and
they say my favorite part of germa streams is the in-depth discussion of marginal tax brackets
and government revenue streams are you the king yeah that's me but thank you so much for the 5000
bits it's a lot of money so many of you give so much money to this stream thank you appreciate
uh sikilos thanks for the 300 bits they say let's go jeremy by the way jeremy is germa i can use his
first name because we are tight like that yeah i know top streamers it's not a big deal to me laugh
out loud i this is like top 10 favorite like bit message i think of the year for me i love this i
don't know what it's just perfect it's let's go jeremy in all caps and then in in parentheses
by the way jeremy is germa i can use his first name because we are tight like that yeah i know
top streamers it's not a big deal to me laugh out loud it's perfect oh it's a it's a coffee
pasta it already is a copy pasta it's a pasta don't worry jeremy you're not special hey it's easy
i was just like mean hey swivel thanks for the 1050 thanks for the 10 bucks swivel
they just say germa heart you germs all of us that's not just me thank you that's what i get
for ruining christmas you can't ruin christmas if you don't go and you can't tell me that not
going is ruining christmas no you can't ruin something you're not going to attend i have to
be there to ruin it i have declined your how how the christmas and invitation you if you say hey
you come to my christmas party and i go no i'm not oh you just ruined christmas no i didn't i don't
i can't go to your party i can't go how many other people are gone like 50 to 60 people will
be in my house but you were supposed to be there on christmas and i'll send i'll send an e-card
okay i have an idea and it sucks but like 10 people might think it's funny just do a stream
that on christmas day is just like a 40 to 50 second video that repeats talking about how i'm
not here today and it's like a weird little ad like merry christmas i'll see you next week i'm
not here today i'm enjoying my christmas like how desperate are you to continue to hey hey guys i i
i'm i stream guys guys i i'm a streamer right remember i'll be back next week i swear i promise
don't go anywhere and if you want to subscribe go for it i'll check them later after i open my
presents and i have a lot of them here take a look at this watch that i got it just loops for a whole
24 hours run ads i would stay to watch that after you see it two or three times it would just
it would get so horrible or like i'm not here right now here's a compilation of some of my
funniest streams and it's just like a 15 20 minute compilation of like funny moments that happened
and then it just repeats it and by the way the funniest moments are boring dog shit like for
instance like just just boring stuff that wasn't even interesting walking down halls and they're
picking up keys and stuff or like letting just dialogue play of a game like for instance when i
was playing outer outer worlds have one of those sequences just be one of the characters
speaking that's it and i'm not talking wow what a fucking moment on stream huh there was a thing
that i did last year that i kind of wish i did even more was the the year in review and when
none of the clips even happened i would love to do like a full 10 minute version of that but it's
so difficult to do that because you have to actually what you guys don't understand is that
those clips i actually had to go into the the wolf among us and get to that part in the game
so it looked like this was really like halfway through the game i've i didn't stream any of those
things i was sitting there in my chair after having like three four five of the games clipped and
edited and i'm just going what the fuck else am i gonna even play and get like an hour into so it
looks real create an entire fake stream and reference it yeah there's a lot of weird things
to do you played wolf among us i mean i did i i played wolf among us in like 2014
not on video or anything or have like and let's take a look at some of those moments from last
year and it's all moments where i'm just mad at the chat and shit and just talking shit and being
vicious and horrible like i don't have any good moments i'm just mean and terrible like i'm not
even i'm i'm awful like telling people like shut the fuck up and stuff like that you don't know
shit dumb motherfucker yeah that's right ban that guy ban him i don't want to see him ever
fucking again in my chat ever again it's just shit like that horrible like 10 times in a row
and maybe there's one clip in the middle that's like weird and having fun all right good egg
thanks guys appreciate it you guys i love you guys you guys are the best i'm you guys are so
awesome like get some hearts in the chat it's right in the middle of me being just like screaming and
and yelling about how awful the games are and how like i hate chat and everything
yeah next clip it's freaking offensive it might be funny anyways uh well there's still time before
december 31st because i still am doing the award show which this a lot there's a lot going on
hey i gotta get that going too i gotta get that going like this week but uh swivel that was
swivel for the 10 bucks thank you swivel zake thanks for 250 yo just wanted to share with you
my most important unwritten rule of life there's nothing here there's a quote and that's it thanks
to the 250 zake and thanks for the rule there are no rules is that what it is sad vega thanks
for 300 bits i'm riding this people crash to the end with you good sir might i request treasure
mountain as a dos game sometimes it was my favorite game when i was four we played it we played it
and it was very very very good probably the best game of the night besides aladdin i can't believe
they streamed this for like six hours plus that time just melted to me it was like 45 minutes in
my brain i didn't have to go to the bathroom i haven't peed in seven hours oh shit i probably
should do that uh yeah new york thanks for the five community subs this was a few hours ago but
thank you hey dark soul thanks for the 250 i fucking told you we were all fake do you believe
that you're in a coma now zero view small time streamer here's some bits to grow up big and
strong like a 10 plus view streamer that was crazy you know it's normal when
views view fluctuations happen all the time and like i don't really care but i will be honest
with you it was a moment when we were playing that werewolf game and uh dropped like a thousand
viewers and it's just like oh whatever that's that's whatever that's fine that's all right
but once it went like enough a thousand and it was going slow too it was not just like oh
you're at zero viewers is a glitch no no no it slowly slowly was ticking down to like 1600 and
i'm sitting there going this is is this people just leaving oh this is okay maybe i should do
something else it was i was like what's happening to me uh but no i obviously i don't it doesn't
really bother me but you guys stayed though right hey for real though thanks for the 250
glad to hear you're going to be playing red alert tomorrow i just wish command and conquer had a
happier ending red alert 3 was serviceable but every game after that sucked it's also
terrible that ea canceled tiberium and generals 2 that's it i'm sick and tired of ea's bullshit
oh what is this there's only one thing left to do this tim curry is escaping to the one place
that hasn't been corrupted by capitalism what i'm escaping to the one place that hasn't been
corrupted by capitalism space i'm uh what was it what was the third one what was the third
command and conquer uh tiberian sun people didn't like that one because it was too futuristic and
was a little weird i liked tiberian sun i'm one of the weirdos that actually liked that game
command and conquer oh it's great i can't wait for the fmv cutscenes that's the best part
but anyways let's keep going banjo boy thanks for the 300 bits hey germa i'm very glad that
you chose to stream on my birthday happy birthday and that my name is actually and my name is the
actual name and the rat's birthday song so your name is michael what the fuck also i finished
my master's degree yesterday and you're smart and aside from my own family you're probably the most
consistent thing during the whole process thanks for being an overall great guy ps i want to play
drums in the video game soundtrack i'm composing uh it would be very embarrassing for me how about
this sample that ripped vod sorry ripped vod hawkeye of mine thanks for the 10 bucks thousand
bits you forgot to turn v-sync on i think lul probably there's no v-sync in dos games the
technology didn't exist thanks for the thousand bits though hawkeye seriously
sad vegan thanks in preschool my favorite treasure mountain seeing it after like 26 years was such a
blast but collecting toys and playing with them all was such an addictive mechanic for a kid
yeah i could see that that game was really good i would play that i would actually play that if
i was younger it was fantastic blueberry juice thanks for the 500 bits can you tell me that i
look rather tasty uh just play the part of the song just don't play it on stream you'll get sued
thank you for the 500 bits hey eugene thanks for the 250 glad to see you back germa i hope
you feel better in the future this is finals week for most of us here so can you please bless us
with a beatbox rap to wish us luck on our finals good luck on your finals have a good final
oh yeah there's a beatbox guy that lives up here and he left like four hours ago
i just have to pretend to be this person i got like four other people that live up here i told
you this already i got the beatbox guy i got the impressions guy i got the comedian i've got the
guy with that's we got really strong arms not me i'm just like the shell i'm just the vessel none
of them are here no unfortunately well maybe the strong arm guy let's see i can lift my desk
um maybe not sucks that the comedian never seems to want to come out i mean i was going to think of
the joke but i can't i fucking can't do it i can't do it without him but thank you eugene
have a great final hey thanks for the 500 bits did you know that checksquest is getting a free hd
remake looking forward to the day when you play that i'm i'm i play originals play original
hardware everybody got really mad at me because i was on original hardware and i just like went
off just get the emulator why don't you just use an emulator i use original hardware original
hardware dos emulator no yeah no you must you must not have been here hey thank you
thanks for the 250 hey german you should play jurassic park the game but let the chat make
the choices what's your favorite dinosaur my favorite dinosaur is not triceratops too many
toys um stegosaurus and triceratops are just too too many toys uh not t-rex um honestly probably
what's the one that's in the water that has the weird fin arms and has a really long brontosaurus
neck what's that called the allosaurus it's the it's the one that looks like the Loch Ness monster
placio placiosaur is that the one let me see play placiosaur yeah that's the one
the placiosaur those things are insane wrong choice sorry what the jurassic park the game
is that the telltale one didn't they make one telltale made a bunch of random games before
they got popular don't they have a back to the future game too they did a couple of strange
games i don't know i'll take a look at it i haven't really given any thought hey butt square
thanks for the 500 bits boneworks waiting room resident sleeper i can't play vr until this like
i get over this issue i'm i like mobility is pretty low right now i'm doing this these new
stretches and this these new like i'm doing shit for my back and chest and every day and the more
that i do it it's just i'm just so insanely sore and shit i want to but it's the reason why i had
to cancel the greens and that's not that wrong word i had to move the green screen to at some
point in like probably a few weeks because i need to be able to be moving around i don't i don't
want to go in front of the green screen and be like oil oil i mean that's actually write that
down that's actually not a bad one that's like a wizard of oz bit put that down i will do that but
i'm actually feel that way so uh i just can't move around that much preemptive minus two what
it's the wizard of oz let's get the credits on the screen these are all the subs thank you subs
all of you what a name that was that was just like 20 digits hope you feel better yeah there's
it's a lot it's it's a weird mystery thing and we have some ideas and some of them are strange
i have a hiatal hernia that's one problem but i think i there are like two or three problems
connected together that make this one giant annoying super illness so hiatal hernia
costochondritis that's what they think it is now i don't know how did that happen i don't it kind
of just does my father had costochondritis i actually talked to him on phone and i'm like
yeah the doctor thinks i have costochondritis she's like oh yeah i had that for like 10 years
like what what happened what do you what do you mean you what what what what what
he's like yeah yeah yeah i went away i got some uh you can get like injections for it i don't know
but he told me yeah it took about 10 years to go away okay that sounds great i can't wait for that
can't wait to be 50 when my rib cage doesn't hurt that's great dad thanks dad thanks dad
but we'll see i just you gotta just do it or you gotta do you gotta do you gotta do what you do
and you just do it and that's it put that in your yearbook but uh we have a few more bits to do
i'm benjamin button when that's not correct benjamin button goes the other way getting
healthier and younger as you age yeah that's not that's not true i'm just getting old
reverse benjamin button is you just age this is normal yeah that's just a normal human
what are you guys talking about all right let's keep going actually there's only like two more
uh nintendo thanks for the 500 bits hey germa i want to buy you christmas socks i just need to
know what your feet size is why did you word it like that why don't you say shoe size that's
feet size shoe size that's how we say it what is my shoe size 14 it sucks when i uh centimeters
no size 14 when i open up doors sometimes i my feet are so long that like i'll actually hit
my toes when i open the doors like yeah like goofy all right what do you think it is i'll
tell you if you get it no you guys will get it somebody will get it in the chat just what do
you think okay yeah somebody got it cool there you go it's in the chat somewhere somebody wrote
it in the chat but thank you butt squire for the 500 bits i actually i can't wait to play
works it looks like it's gonna be awesome and nintendo for the 500 bits somebody wrote it in
chat i'm sure you'll find it hey ice cut digital thanks to the 250 gonna get real with you germa
album of the decade game of the decade movie of the decade i cannot answer this question
because this is like two plus hours of deliberation i can't i can't do that
that has that's its own stream like that's the title of a stream that's irl
i couldn't even come close at the moment yeah that's a comb stream topic for sure there's
still 20 days left to figure it out yeah you can't even name one video game
but i would hold on to that one peaceful hailey thanks for the five community subs and bob boy
both of you have five community subs thank you sub drop after sub drop keith king crimson thanks
for the 250 what if the sultan stream minecraft server is you as santa and we're all your elves
no it's got to be a king because it takes place in like a medieval town with a castle and everything
so it's got to be king see you tomorrow for red alert santa was a king really i mean i guess it
is like the north santa doesn't santa doesn't sit on a throne lovely carver thanks for the 250
germa if there is no custom i am the king choreographed song and dance number for the
king stream i will beat you up am i supposed to how am i supposed to choreograph that
there are things that we're working on though that are not what you think
it's gonna be fun i can promise you that look hold on will it work i don't know will it be
fun i don't know will you remember it probably i will i can at least promise you
a memory like that's pretty much all i can promise hey oh elden ring thanks for the
thousand bits will you beat elden ring on stream when it comes out very very interesting name and
comment thanks for the ten dollars in bits thanks for a thousand bits first of all and yes
i play every from software game on this stream the only one i didn't play on this stream and
beat to its completion was dark souls 2 because i had and bloodborne and i have it's because
i'd already played and beaten those games more than once bloodborne specifically like six seven
plus eight times he played armored core king's field okay sure no i what was the one that i
just played what was it called metal wolf chaos right yeah i played that that's from software
game okay let me put it this way all of from software's third person souls like games
we play on this stream so yes i'm going to play elden ring i'm sure i will complete the whole
thing on this stream and less it sucks and i'll see you tomorrow not if i do it first
that's the best part about playing brand new from software games it was like that with securo
nobody knows what's going on so if you play like the first day or two that it's out for the most
part people don't know where everything is and don't know how to do everything it's great so i
can't pick like the wrong weapon and i have everybody scream at me because i'm using the
wrong katana what are we doing tomorrow we're gonna play red alert and if that doesn't work
that's okay i have a couple of backups and then the next day we're doing the game awards
and then after that you're not going to see me until the minecraft stream but before that happens
before that happens i'm going to make sure i give a very long-winded explanation of what's going to
happen on that stream so as of the game awards stream in two days either before or after the
game awards we're gonna hang out for like an hour or so and i'm just gonna go over and explain how
everything's gonna happen i'm assuming by then i will have everything locked down and know
everything that's gonna happen see you tomorrow we'll talk again have a great night guys see you
tomorrow