Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here again with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, continuing the One Life series, because a lot of people like that.
I've gotten a lot of positive feedback on One Life, so I'm going to keep doing it.
There's two One Life gameplays in this particular video. There's going to be a CP Dustbowl sniper, as you can see right here.
Then there's going to be a scout on Badlands, CP Badlands.
So before I get started with this one, I've got to tell you that this is probably one of the best sniper gameplays I've ever done.
I get, I think, 12 headshots or 13 headshots in one minute or something like that, or two minutes.
It's pretty ridiculous, and I've got a couple of sniper tips for you too.
A lot of people ask me, how do I do sniper? How do I do sniper? I've done videos like this before.
Two quick headshots right off the bat, and I'll tell you right now, we are playing Guitar Hero right now.
What am I talking about? We're playing Guitar Hero.
If you play Guitar Hero, you know one thing. You have to match the button when the particular note comes down the line.
I'm going to try and freeze this right here and explain this to you, because if you can play Guitar Hero, you can play sniper.
So I want to go back to this headshot I just did on that heavy.
Think about it like this. Imagine the heavy's head is one of the notes in Guitar Hero, and your cursor is the place where you have to hit the button.
Now remember, in Guitar Hero, your main goal is to what? Hit the buttons right when they pass through your line of sight on the bar.
Alright, so here we go. Here comes Insert, your favorite song here.
Oh my god. We just learned how to play sniper. Oh yeah.
Now keep in mind, this does not work for every single sniper shot, but if you line up your cursor in their direct line of sight,
most people are not going to think that, oh, I better duck and dodge and weave and move around. That's not going to happen.
Most people, when they come out of a spawn or they're going towards a certain goal or a point, they're going to go in a straight line.
Or they're going to go in somewhat of a straight line that you can predict their movement.
So if you can put your cursor ahead of people and just match when their head passes through your cursor, you're going to headshot nine times out of ten everybody that comes by you.
Kind of a weird analogy, I know, but it really does work if you think about it.
So anyways, let's bring it all back to the point where I was at before.
Three quick headshots right in a row and watch this soldier bang another in the air rocket jumping headshot.
I love those. And by the way, did you guys see that horrible lag compensation scout headshot?
I was probably four or five feet away from him when I got him in the head.
I have no idea what that was all about, but at least it registered on my end, right?
So look at all the spam that's just coming into this room right now.
I can only imagine the frustration on the blue team.
I killed seven or eight people in 30 seconds, so I can only imagine.
Guitar Hero headshot, Guitar Hero headshot on that heavy, you saw it.
One or two people get on the point here now.
A soldier and a demo man, and I can't reach anybody from right there.
I got to turn this corner trying. Whoa, I got a spy.
Get him with the Shahansha. I'm looking around for him.
I ended up getting him with a smash crit right in his face right there.
And I actually didn't even tell you the loadout for the match.
Okay, the loadout is the Shahansha, obviously, you just saw.
The Bizarre Bargain and the Darwin's Danger Shield.
My default setup, absolutely, I love this setup so much.
Get a couple more headshots and I would have got the kill on that scout,
but he got murdered by that heavy.
And you know you're doing something right as a sniper when you run out of ammo.
I had no ammo left in my sniper rifle. I had to go get some.
Coming out of the house turns out to be a bad idea.
I got a little greedy. I wanted to try and get up front,
get closer to everybody, see if I could pick up some good headshots.
And also there was another sniper that kind of just came up there in the same window as me.
So here's another sniper tip.
If there's a sniper already sitting in one spot, don't go stand right next to him.
Make sure you pick your own little spot because that's a bad idea.
Because if a spy comes in there, he's guaranteed to probably kill both of us.
Not to mention the enemy team will know exactly where both of us are.
So there's no distinguishing between where two snipers could potentially be.
Oh no, they're both just sitting right there.
So spread out a little bit.
So I happen to notice that a sniper on the enemy team is now trying to counter-snipe me.
Which is fine. I'm all for the competition.
And I get shot right in the side, right here, blink, right there.
And I go, oh my god, it's time to go get some health and counter-snipe this guy.
As you can see, I do some crouching and jumping and stuff like that
because I don't want to get shot right in the face because I don't know where he is.
I'm not sure if he's straight ahead, if he's to the right, if he's on the building or something.
But it ends up being not a big deal because I end up backing up right into the knife of a spy.
So that's the one life as the sniper.
And we're going to transition from that right into the Scout on Badlands.
So this is the Scout on Badlands using the default scatter gun, the Mad Milk, and the Fan of War.
Which I didn't have until like three days ago, apparently.
I thought I had it, but I didn't have it.
You may also be wondering why I picked this particular gameplay when we're getting destroyed so badly.
If you look down at the bottom of the screen, they have one more cap to go before they beat us.
They were beating us the entire time, by the way.
But we end up coming back and four-capping them in about two and a half minutes.
So it's a really, really spectacular gameplay we do.
I don't really do anything too incredible, but it's the fact that as a team effort, we really pushed and we really got back to it.
It was really fun, interesting.
I figured I could show it to you guys and give you some commentary on it.
I noticed a Cloak Spy just started to decloak and was shooting at me, probably with the Enforcer because I had such low life.
He can see that because he's a spy.
I don't have any health, and watch this Scout.
This Scout jumps up there, tries to cap the point on us, and then he just kind of jumps off of it.
I was thinking, what are you doing?
You could have just potentially got that point back.
But we have a couple people on mid now, and they cap that.
So now we're back to square one, trying to pressure them as much as we can.
We got the middle.
They don't have any forces up yet, so let's just keep going.
Push, push, push.
Let's go, honey.
The baby's coming.
Push, baby.
Throw my milk right into the back of the Soldier's head.
Whoops-a-daisy.
It's not a big deal, though, because I come around the corner.
Scout right here.
Get him right in the back.
Bada-boom, bada-bing.
Let's keep going.
Keep the pressure up.
This is something you...
In five control point maps, if you don't keep the pressure up, you will never do anything, and games just last a million years.
So if you have the opportunity to pressure the other team and just keep pushing and keep going, it's something you really have to do.
Me and this Soldier double-team this Scout for a little bit.
I get the assist, not the kill.
And now it's time to try and cap this point as fast as I can.
And this is the turning point of the other team.
This Soldier, all he would have to have done is just shot me one or two times, but he ends up actually killing himself.
And then watch this.
A sniper comes over here trying to shoot me, and I get the luckiest crit in the world.
Right there.
That's just like, oh, man.
I would have been raging about that.
So now we got that point.
Coming right down here, trying to get the last point.
I know that nobody's out here now.
Getting right on the point.
That's the end of the game.
We win.
Comeback victory for the win, baby.
Thank you all so much for watching.
I hope you guys enjoyed these two One Life gameplays.
I'll see you all next time.
And take care, everybody.