Hey. I'm strapped in. I can't get out now. My arms are tied to the chairs. My back is tied to
the back of the chair and I have to beat Sekiro today. No. Welcome guys. He's strapped in all
right. I'll be right back. I forgot one thing. A tweet and a coffee. See you in a sec. I got
an LOL title. What's wrong with an LOL title every now and then? This is the worst thing.
Okay. I'm going to give you some insight on a streamer insight. Okay. So I just had to
grab like two things. So I had to go up the stairs. Down the stairs. Auto. You good? Okay.
Auto's been up. Back up the stairs. And then I just sat here and I forgot that I'm like,
Hey guys, how are you? Hey, welcome to the broadcast. Somebody said, wouldn't you have
finished any Dark Souls by now? Dark Souls 3 took me like four or five streams, didn't it?
And this game is harder than Dark Souls in my opinion. I think it's more difficult
than any of the Dark Souls games. Somebody said, no, you're bad. I beat Owl first try
and I beat Double Gorilla first try, but I'm terrible at the game though. You know,
just awful. I mean, he's just terrible at this game. Everything about he's terrible at the game.
I mean, he's just so bad. I can't even understand how awful he is. The Double Gorilla
where you fight two Gorillas at the same time. One of them has that and he beat it first try.
I mean, he's so awful at games like this. I just can't, I, I, I can't even watch him.
Yeah. I give it a rest. Never. No, I, uh, I just, if you're just joining us for the first
time and you haven't seen Sekiro ever, uh, I'm going to tell you just, I'll leave now
because we're going to talk about major things that just happened. Okay. Are you here?
Are we all good? All right. Uh, so I, that was your chance. I just killed my dad.
This is in this room, but literally the last thing I did last night.
I don't know what happens next. All I know is that people were in this room, right?
Yes. Okay. So I think I got to come down here. I don't have any seeds, right?
Shit. Well, I just made a choice to protect him, right?
This is the tree branch.
Yes. That's right. Yeah. I killed my father for a stick. Yeah. I could have just gone outside
to any tree out there. I could have just, okay, I could have like sneezed over here
and he was like, what was that? Could have walked over, grabbed a branch from here,
just snapped it off and been like heritage. And he would have been like, Oh, thanks.
What's so special about that branch? We don't have all the ingredients.
That it is the mortal blade.
Yes. It was given to me by the divine child of the rejuvenating waters.
Do we have all the ingredients?
The monks at Sempo temple abandoned the ways of their faith in pursuit of immortality.
The result is those who have false dragons heritage
known as the divine children of the rejuvenating waters.
A false dragon's heritage. I never would have thought. Wait, divine children?
Yes. Many were created, but one survived.
Further proof of the corruption this power brings to man with the mortal blade in hand.
I can now be made to bleed. We are one step closer to creating a fountainhead infant.
The ties of immortality must be severed.
Yes, my lord.
Okay. Well, you didn't really give me any more info.
I didn't really look at, let me look at the items too.
Cause I got, I got like two new things, right?
Didn't I get like something to read?
I'm trying to think of what the last thing we did was,
or the last piece of information here.
What about you? You got anything for me?
I'm glad you've come, Master Wolf. It looks as if your brow is less fur.
Oh, right, right, right. I was going to kill the tutorial guy.
Right. I was going to go kill Mr. Tutorial.
I could clear the essence as well. He's ready.
You're certain of this?
Yes. I want you to kill me.
As you wish.
Go on.
How do I do it? Can I do it any way I want?
Like can I get up there and drop a piano on him?
Oh no, he has to die by this sword, right?
Whoa, there's a centipede inside of him.
What? Oh, why the fuck does he have that inside of his body?
Oh, false tooth loaded with a secret shinobi drug.
Blue in color can be used repeatedly.
Crush the blue nostrum between the back teeth to die as often as one pleases.
What? All right, I'm just figuring out people that can't die have
the centipede worm inside them.
That's fucked up.
That's a cyanide tooth.
That's like some CIA shit.
Wait, do I have one of those inside of me?
I probably do.
Imagine figuring that out.
Imagine seeing that.
That's what makes people stay alive forever.
I would be like, how am I going to get a CT scan?
Don't kill me yet.
But just like, I just want to know if it's in there.
Well, that was, I got the tooth.
How much money do I have?
360.
I can't breathe.
All right, I got to, I'm going to cleanse the dragon rut.
Let's just do it now.
Everyone's been healed.
All right, clean slate.
Good to go.
Hey, I'm fine.
Now I want to, I mean, he's got two of these, so I can always have at least one.
What about pellets?
Maybe I should just buy a shitload of pellets.
How many do I have?
No, I have 24 of these.
When did I get so many pellets?
I don't even remember getting this many.
When did I get, oh yeah, I did go on like an item run, didn't I?
Are you going to try to kill headless today?
I don't even want to hear that name.
I don't even want to know that character exists.
It'll automatically make me upset.
In fact, I'm already mad now.
I don't even want to think about it.
I'm going to say we'll see.
I'm just preparing.
I'm just getting, make sure I'm ready to play because we got this.
We're in like the last, we're in like the final act of the game, I think.
From what happened last night, this has to be the final act.
I still need, okay, what can I, what can I get?
Let me see, sparkling, long spark.
Long spark and increased proportion of black eye over the effect can be prolonged
in the average fire.
I like the firecrackers, purple fumes spark.
Oh shit.
I want this, I want this so bad.
Oh man, I want this, I want this right now.
How do I get this right now?
That's a lot of money.
I'm going to, how much money do I have?
Do I have any things?
I don't think I have any of those pouches, do I?
I do.
Yeah, I have to, I'm buying it.
What was it, six?
I use the firecrackers so much.
It's like my favorite item.
I might as well just do it.
If that's the thing I'm going to use.
Because I have the materials to go from here to here.
I need two.
Okay, let's just start it.
What does this one do?
Forcing enemies caught in the last turn around.
This is the one that makes them turn around.
Okay, I can do it twice.
And then that leads me to here.
Oh my god, dude, do I have to go?
Do I have to get this as well?
Shit, this really is Monster Hunter.
God damn it.
I have to get all these?
Oh no.
All right, well, I have to get this.
I need more money.
What was it, I didn't see it.
I think it was like 500 or 600.
Just get more money.
Well, at least I'm upgrading these.
Okay, then that gives this to me.
I need 600 more, which leads to here.
This is improve Sabumaru.
So let's just get, I have a little bit more money.
Let's do it.
Two, three, four, five.
God damn it.
Hold on.
Play a different game?
No, I have to, come on.
Well, you want me to stop now?
Imagine stopping now.
All right, I'm going to sell like fucking four of these.
Imagine playing this game to this point
and then being like, well, that was fun.
First impressions, it's really hard.
It's really good.
That's it.
I'll see you next time.
Okay, so this brings me down here.
Okay, that, all right.
Okay, I am now ready to go from that in a straight line now.
So I have improved stuff.
That's what you do with most games you stream.
Well, if a game has, I mean, it really depends, right?
Okay, like a game like Kenshi, right?
That's like a 200 hour game, right?
I'm not going to play that like 30 streams in a row.
A game like Resident Evil 2, I'll play through the whole thing.
It's like a one and done kind of experience.
A game like this, it's just all the way through, one and done.
Games that require like potentially 10 to 20 streams
to even get to the meat and potato of the game.
It's a lot different.
Okay, so I have some better stuff.
Let's see.
That's already there.
I think I'm ready to go.
That was 50 bucks just came in right now.
Who just gave 50 dollars?
It was Fitty.
Thank you so much, Fitty, for the 50 dollars.
Hey, money.
They said, also, just so you know,
your chat's being monitored and recorded 24-7.
This is the internet.
If you don't think that everything you've ever typed
in this chat could be pulled up somewhere.
We're in 2019, man.
It's the internet.
You know what?
That's just the nature of where we are right now as humans.
Hey, future people.
Chat is just learning this.
Yeah, so when you told me like two weeks ago
to suck a fart out of your ass,
somebody can just find you saying that.
I hope everyone's aware of this.
Like when you told chat
that you ate a booger out of your nose
and you liked how it tasted,
and you were like, fuck, man.
It's like weird, but I don't know why I like that.
Five years from now, someone can look at that.
It's the internet, man.
You got to be careful.
He just admitted it on stream.
All right, where the fuck am I going?
I got, okay, I can dive.
Where do I want to go?
I've said some pretty dopey stuff, to be honest.
Yeah, whatever, though.
It was like, your future employer
going to go to your Twitch chat log
and see what you wrote.
It says here that, was your username ShitEater106?
Yeah.
But what about this one that's ShitEater107?
108, 109, and 110.
Those are all tied to the same IP address.
Is that also you?
Yep, it is.
Oh, any reason why you made five ShitEater usernames?
I'm just curious.
Well, you see, when I was 18,
I was in this guy, Jerma985's chat,
and I got banned four times
for writing I love eating shit in his chat.
And I got banned four times
over the course of six months.
So I just kept making new usernames
to say that again.
And I would get removed again.
And then finally, I was removed
from the whole website.
And, excuse me, what?
I don't think we at Johnson & Johnson
can have somebody like that around here.
You have to be careful, guys.
We here at Johnson & Johnson
baby tier free shampoo formula company 107,
105 through, 100 through 106 got banned
because we were putting formaldehyde
in baby shampoo.
We got banned five times as a company.
Let's go.
You know too much.
Yes.
What am I just like fucking started
to slash it up?
Use your eyes.
Is that what he just said?
Is the wound I just made
a small cut on my chest.
So this an infant.
It's so extraordinarily nostalgic.
Yeah.
Like the new Ghostbusters movie,
Ghostbusters 3 coming up.
Okay.
A sweetly scented bridal offering
that was written on the altar
where the fragrant stone was placed.
Yes.
You now carry the aroma
of the Fountainhead incense.
I believe the path leading
to the Fountainhead palace
will open before you.
If you go to the shrine within the cave,
immortality shall soon be severed.
A shrine and cave.
As you wish.
So the shrine, where was that?
Am I drinking?
No, I got a coffee here.
All right.
So that was, which one?
I see a cave.
What was it?
Cave.
I forget where it was.
Was that the misty place?
That was here somewhere.
Wedding cave door.
I think.
Somebody wrote egg.
Mod that guy for like 30 seconds.
All right.
I think this is obviously the place.
So go in this cave.
And now I smell like
I have a certain scent to me.
So now I'll be able to
open the secret door.
Maybe.
No.
Shelter stones.
Is this okay?
Do I have to get on this?
Or do I maybe dive?
Well, no.
This is, this is just a prayer outhouse.
Well, hold on.
Let me dive down here.
Is there enough?
Is there a pool I can dive in?
Is there?
There has to be.
Come on.
This is like a standing water somewhere.
Yeah.
Diving in puddles.
If I dive in a puddle,
I'll just break my teeth.
No, there's no pool here.
I thought maybe there'd be like
a little pool back here or something.
All right.
Let's go.
Somebody said small break.
I'm going to go in here.
God.
The impatience.
The instant gratification.
Instant gratification.
I want to look around the trees.
Okay.
Has it been a giant goat foot?
It's not somebody's playing the claw game.
I got it.
Okay.
This just got weird.
That's Mojo from Chrono Cross.
Odd reference, I know.
But it is.
Where is he delivering me to?
Uh, well, apparently he hasn't walked in a while.
I severely overestimated.
I was lying down for too long.
I have some sort of lactic acid built up.
I'll just let him go here.
That's just, this is fine.
He ended with a dab.
Oh, don't say that.
Your uber is here.
Oh, you guys.
Whoa, this is cool.
I kind of would have liked to have
traveled a little bit longer on Mr.
Siercaro, just in case.
That was fun.
That's the coolest thing in the game so far.
I hope he gets up when he's, I have to fight him.
Please let me fight this guy.
Hey, what was it?
Well, we ended last night at an 8.6.
This makes it an 8.7.
Not that much.
I only, it was like 15 seconds.
He's pretending he just moved.
This is pretty.
Wait, items.
From Software always does this thing
where they put an item directly to the left
or directly to the right behind something.
Like back here.
Oh, come on, there would be one right here.
If this was any other game, it would be right here.
You know I'm right.
All right.
Well, whatever.
Theory immediately debunked.
It's fine.
Didn't I fight this guy?
I fought like the illusion version of this guy.
Okay, I guess we're doing this.
Damn, that posture damage is fucking terrible.
Oops.
Oh, fuck, I thought he didn't know
he was going to keep going.
He's got three health bars.
Whoa, that hurts.
I'm not fucking with that.
Oh, no, no, no.
Damn it, I'm getting too greedy.
What's he going to do now?
Different, same.
All right, this is different.
I think I'm just going to jump up here.
Whoa, he can go up.
What the fuck?
What?
He has an extra long sword now.
Okay, maybe not a good idea.
Wowee.
Back it up, back it up, back it up, back it up.
Back, back, back, back, back.
Fuck, I didn't time it right.
All right, let's go, let's go.
I think I figured, I think I know what he's going to do.
Uh-oh, here comes a centipede.
Is he going to do the mist again?
Whoa, that didn't work.
Whoa.
Okay, all right, all right, all right.
Slow it down.
Whoa.
He does, it's all slides.
I got to get the fuck away from him.
It's, it's slashes.
Let's go.
That's a grab.
No, it's not.
Is it terror?
I have no fucking idea what that is.
Curious.
That's terror, isn't it?
He's curious.
Faster.
It's not even worth blocking these because it takes too much.
Whoop, that's far.
Didn't jump fast enough.
You know what?
Posture candy, I think, is what I got to use here.
Damn it.
That was quick.
I ain't giving up yet.
Hold on.
So what's this?
Posture bites, I need, I need posture candy.
Shit.
Not good.
Back it up, back it up.
Don't you forget about me.
That's, that's the wrong thing equipped.
That's the wrong thing.
Wrong thing.
Berry bush, berry bush, berry bush, berry bush, berry bush.
Oh, it's okay.
It's okay.
Fire.
I bring you fire.
I am the god of hell fire and I bring you fire.
I'm telling you, I got locked in the wall there.
That was very bad.
That was so scary.
Without that, without the firecrackers, I'm dead.
That was a last-ditch effort to cracker them.
Dragon's tally board.
That's an iced coffee, huh?
Possessing this increased the stocks that can be purchased in merchant shops.
Such a tally board is highly prized by the merchant class.
Old custom dictates that those of dragon rank are recognized as supreme merchants
by the imperial palace.
So what does that mean?
That means that I can buy more?
They just have increased stock, I guess.
Interesting.
That was a fun fight.
The last three, they've done like, the last three fights have just been awesome.
Let's get that power up.
True monk.
Uh-huh.
The corrupted monk was among the infested.
Standing over the fountainhead palace,
indeed, immortality would seem a fitting quality for eternal watcher of the palace.
Her true name is Priestess Yao.
He hated the guardian ape.
No, guardian ape was fucking cool.
It was just, that secret second boss fight was just fucking hard as shit.
Okay, attack power's been enhanced.
So I have a please backseat me.
This is a please backseat me chat, okay?
What do these do?
I feel like I've been holding on to both of these.
I mean, raise in prayer between one's palms to restore a node of res-
Do I get to only just do this once?
It just refills a resurrection node.
So it doesn't add another resurrection, it just refills one.
Does it consume it?
If I do this, that's it.
I just get to do it once.
One use.
So let's say I was having like an intense boss fight and I died,
and I had the black bar down there, and I took one of those.
I would be able to do it again.
You could do that, yes.
Exactly, yes.
I don't think so.
I love that.
You can use it after your res, all right.
Let's rest.
Dude, I- it was like two or three part-
When I had the poison equipped wrong,
and I thought that was gonna throw me off, that was gonna-
This is beautiful.
Fountainhead Palace.
Points.
All right, I've hit five.
I have that skill.
I've neglected this so much.
I just don't know where to go.
This is gonna increase it by one.
I don't think it's worth it.
Maybe one of these.
What do these do?
Shouldn't it be eyes?
Ooh, I'm fairly good at countering those.
I'd do the Makiri counter like six out of ten times.
Yeah, I'm gonna get this.
So now I have run and slide.
And, oh, I gotta get this one too.
No, wait, what?
I do have to get this, do I?
I guess so.
KDKD945, thanks for the five community subs.
Thank you so much for the five subs.
So, look at how close I am.
I just gotta kill like a couple people.
Damn, all right.
I'm ready.
I told you I was gonna come ready to play today.
I told you that.
Last night, owl gone in a fucking try.
Today, let's go.
I'm ready to game.
I've got my caramel macchiato from Starbucks.
It sucks.
It's really not that good, but I still have it.
This thing too.
Another five community subs from KDK.
Damn, five more subs from KDK.
Thank you.
All right, let's go.
Let's go.
Let's game.
So let's head out here.
Wait, one last thing.
Which one of these is the best?
What's the puppeteer one?
Maybe this one sounds interesting.
All right.
I don't know if anybody else gets like this
when they play these games,
but after like an intense fight that you win,
I don't know why this doesn't happen when you lose.
Maybe it's because your body doesn't have any time to relax,
but after killing that guy,
I was like this.
Like, and I need a second to just fucking relax.
Okay.
It doesn't happen when I lose.
I think it's your body just unwinding
because you still wound up the whole time.
I just gotta look at this.
Where's the selfie camera?
Just take a pic.
Take a note from the spider man.
Whatever.
I'm too busy looking.
This is beautiful.
This is the part that I like.
This is my favorite zone so far.
I could get hurt by falling here.
Oh, I guess we didn't even hurt.
Yeah, this is lovely.
Let me see.
Ooh.
KDK again is on like a five sub every 30 second interval.
Thank you KDK again for the five community subs.
That's...
Is that a dog?
No, it's got like a...
No, it's one of those weird alien people.
He's my friend.
See, I didn't kill him.
I just brought him back as a close friend of mine.
What do you want to do?
I don't know.
Finally, have a go...
Okay, you can co-op now.
This is how you do co-op in Sekiro.
You have to control their minds.
KDK again.
KDK added again.
Yeah, okay.
Those of you that are concerned about co-op,
just get this ability
and then pretend that your friend's over.
Oh, god damn it, dude.
Really?
You got hit by the fucking arrow there.
Now we have to go back to the beginning.
I have to reload the game.
Just try not to die.
From Software is like the worst making co-op parts of video games.
Let me go back and put my soapstone down again.
God damn it.
I didn't even know what that was.
I don't know what happened.
Fucking god damn it.
Yeah, I'll see you in 22 more minutes.
My game just had crashed.
I'm a funny streamer.
Thanks.
I tried.
We do like jokes and comedy here.
I'll give you a routine.
Ready?
Like, hey, it's me.
Playing on the drum.
Not anymore.
Got you.
Oh, my livelihood.
Another five subs from KDK.
Are you going to do this like the whole time?
Five more subs from KDK.
This is just going to keep going.
This guy's 43.
Not even close.
I kind of just want to look around.
I like this place.
He's 60.
I sound 60 at the moment.
Well, there's a guy over here.
This place is huge.
Ooh, all right.
Oh, these are the treasurers.
These are the treasurers.
Um, somebody just threw a toaster in here.
How do I get out of here?
It's okay.
This get out of the water.
Get out of the water.
That guy has lightning.
I told you.
Do you guys remember when I played Hitman?
And I made the reference.
I threw like a fucking piece of electrical equipment into the ocean.
And everyone laughed at me because I said I was going to electrocute everybody
that was currently in the Atlantic Ocean.
You tell me that I'm I'm I'm bullshit now.
That guy just threw a little bit of electricity in a gigantic lake and killed me.
That wouldn't happen with that.
Okay, seriously myth busters.
If I was in a, um, if I was in a lake this big
and somebody just put an electrical current into the water, what would happen?
Would I be fine?
No, nothing.
Okay, how small?
Okay, what myth buster level?
How small would the body of water have to be if you put like 10,000 watts
into the water?
Are we talking like a large swimming pool?
A bathtub?
A kiddie pool?
Let's go with lightning.
KDK just gave 10 more subs.
The electrodes would dissipate after 20 feet.
What?
Okay, so if I was in like a swimming pool
and you threw like a supercharged toaster into the swimming pool plugged in,
I'd be fine.
Are we sure?
Or maybe let's test it.
No, I just don't know.
Like I'm curious.
Okay, if like if you, that's why they say get out of the water.
If like there's a thunderstorm, right?
I remember when I was a kid, when I was like fucking 10, I had a pool
and it was always like the second that you'd hear like
my father would fucking rip open the sliding door.
Everybody get the fuck out of the pool right now.
Dad, what are you talking about?
He was like reaching and like trying to grab us like get out.
If lightning struck inside the pool.
I'm going to move on from this conversation because it's fucking stupid.
Okay, if lightning struck the Atlantic Ocean while there are people swimming.
Okay, I'm done.
I have to concentrate.
KDK, KDK, I think you have like, I think you're on auto by.
Ow, ow, ow.
No, not into the lightning water.
What, no.
Oh, where's my heel?
What the fuck is happening with my heel?
All right, I took, I took it off the bar because I was in the middle of heated,
heated exchange.
Okay, all right.
Hey, look at how beautiful this is.
Remember this?
Thank God.
All right, let's go.
I don't need to go in the house.
I need to go on top of the house though,
because that's where these guys are throwing shit at me from.
Why would there be stealth grass here?
I don't think I've ever aggroed one of these guys.
He's just like, snorting.
What is that?
The magic?
He's just throwing punches at nothing.
I don't know what that thing is.
What bar, okay, what is he doing from me?
Is he sucking souls from me?
All right, let's go back and kick this guy's ass.
Do they guys just have 200 fucking dollars?
Am I reading that right?
Why don't I just grind these guys?
Okay, let's go around here, get the guy up top.
Ahem.
But KDK, you've given so many subs.
Thank you so much.
Oops.
Well, it's okay.
Will he shoot arrows for me?
Go get him.
Will we go get him?
Go, go do something.
They're both just looking at each other.
What is that guy doing?
All right, well, there goes that one.
I just have this one more somewhere.
Check for items.
Holy shit, okay.
Well, you know what?
Okay, I'll tell you one gripe that I have with the game.
Are you ready?
Are you ready for it?
Not a complaint, a gripe.
It's different.
So I'm in stealth right now, right?
I'm in sneak mode.
Here we go.
I'm going to backstab you.
Okay, I can't do it now.
All right, what I was going to say was that was bad.
Listen, when you backstab somebody in stealth,
you are automatically like standing up.
I wish you would just stay crouching
because if I sneak up and backstab somebody,
you're just like this.
Then you kind of just stand.
That's a little minor gripe.
Oh, you want to go again?
How would you stab somebody without standing up?
Yeah, but I mean, like this is a video game.
All right, I got the Grape Wax.
I need, actually really do need these.
This is a Nintendo game, guys.
I didn't get that item, whatever it is.
There's different rules.
How do I get in?
Oh, this whole little area over here.
What's that guy doing?
Oh, he's sucking my life up.
That guy's sucking my life up.
Oh God, what happened when this fills up?
What's wrong with me?
The only way this guy's from stage right.
All right, I think I should just keep going forward.
So it makes you enfeebled.
By the way, the one guy in chat,
I did look over there and see somebody said,
let it fill up.
You get a flute, not a joke.
Very clearly that turned out to be a fucking total bunch of horse shit.
I didn't like do that on purpose, but still like what dog shit.
Never reading chat ever again, by the way.
Like coins.
There's good, there's items here that I want.
I don't want to just disappear.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't do it.
I think it's just line of sight.
How could you win that?
All right.
Can you, if you read this, suck a fart out of my ass.
You're gonna regret that in like five years.
Oh, there's the slide.
That's the first time I've seen that.
He's gonna regret that one in five years.
Any more items?
Uh, shitload of items over here.
Apparently somebody can still, oh, there's archers up there.
Item surrounded by dogs.
Two guys up here.
Where is, can I get up here without being seen by that one?
Yep.
See if I can get them both.
Oh, that's not a backstab.
Yes, it is in every book.
You're only an hour in right now.
Don't go too crazy.
You're gonna burn out.
I am the brightest star you've ever seen.
No, no way.
He's going to take the entire full brunt of a star.
I laughed out loud when that line went up, by the way.
No, he's crazy.
There's no way he can take the full brunt of a star.
I was the guy in the theater going.
Peek-a-boo.
That's how you do it.
I want you to fucking clip that.
I want you to fucking read into that.
When you talk about games,
gamers that you should pay attention to.
Top 10 gamers you should bet you pay attention to in 2019.
Look at that for a clip.
Keep that one.
Who's over here?
Okay, we have two dogs.
That thing got in the way.
These things are good.
Dog t-shirts.
Hydrate?
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, I don't know.
I think there's something wrong with them.
I don't know.
Like, I was watching earlier and I keep...
I feel like he was just kind of talking
like to somebody in his own head.
It was really fucking weird.
It was kind of maybe uncomfortable.
I don't think I'll be watching again.
Same.
All right, don't rest here.
You know, you have to play together and not over each other.
How many times are you gonna make the disillusioned viewer joke
as many times as I deem necessary?
Disillusioned viewer joke.
I do use it a lot, don't I?
Oh, every other streamer beat this game.
Are you taking your time?
Are you just bad?
I tag.
Yeah, did they beat the fucking true monk first try?
You showed me somebody that did.
I...
I took two days off in the middle of this playthrough.
Who the hell is that?
I first tried two bosses in a row.
You want to find me a streamer that is capable
or something like that?
I think this is just an NPC.
This is gonna be...
I've seen Snow White and the Seven Dwarves.
I'm not gonna eat that.
Okay.
The courtyard is cursed.
Ooh!
That was a big one.
They went up on two wheels for that one.
There's a bite down.
I don't even need to bite down anymore.
I have the tooth.
Uh, I need more information.
Don't go through the courtyard.
Why are you telling me this?
The Great Carp.
Alright.
This boss is a fish.
Wouldn't wish for an eternity like that.
The Great Carp.
Uh.
The courtyard is an accursed place.
And if you please, keep my heart.
I really hope this is not an underwater fight.
They gave me the dive capability.
Don't put an underwater fight here.
That's the worst thing they could do.
No.
If there really is like an underwater boss fight or something.
This guy...
I...
I already know what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna...
In like a year I'm gonna be reading
and watching YouTube videos.
Of top ten from software bosses.
And this is gonna be number one.
It wasn't the fight that was hard.
It was dealing with being underwater.
And it was unbearable.
Oh no.
Uh.
I'm not ready for this.
Go fight the giant fish.
Alright, well.
Can I like shot him up by throwing something?
That's a tactic right there.
The giant fish boss.
Oh.
Is that a boss?
No.
Mini boss?
Watch it.
No!
I can't...
I can't get, get, get, get, get.
How do I do something about this?
What do I do?
I don't know how to...
That happened so fast.
I thought I had at least a second or two.
That...
Why did that go so fast?
Dude, that...
That bar filled so much faster than it ever has.
Mad because bad.
I'm not mad at all.
I...
Look.
There's no way you saw me through there.
Stupid.
Dumb.
Nothing about it is fun.
Nothing about this is fun.
My god.
Alright, I have an indicator here.
What is it?
Is it a slash?
Is it a dash?
Is it a crash?
I don't know.
I have the indicator for what?
What is the indicator for if I can't do anything?
It's a grab, but I can't dodge.
I thought maybe you could time it and stop it.
Well, this went from my favorite area to being
my least favorite area in any From Software game that they've ever done.
And I'm talking worse than Lost Izalith.
I mean, but did you not finish this one too?
God damn.
Unbelievable.
Not even fun.
What?
What was it hitting the wall?
What was it hitting?
What?
Why was...
I couldn't do the shuriken.
Like, I threw two shurikens and it hit the thing.
It hit the fucking fence.
Don't do it again.
Give me a break.
Don't, don't, don't!
Oh my god!
I have to turn the...
Why?
I have to swing at him.
Oh my god.
Yeah, one of the only...
One of like the two stealth sections in this whole game.
Activision threw...
Activision made him do that.
Activision told him to put a stealth mechanic in.
Wait, wait, this is Activision.
We need to stealth in our video games
and all of our third-person adventure games.
Look, slow them down!
I want them to progress through this area.
That snail's fucking face.
And then they're expected to parry
like 200 fucking times in two seconds.
I don't care if they're gonna kill me.
I'll keep smoking.
What is that noise?
One, two, three...
That's not safe.
That's not safe over there.
Eel liver, cool.
It can go that way.
Let's check.
I'm just fucking around, guys.
This is faux outrage.
I'm faux angry.
Don't you guys know the true meaning of when I'm angry?
My voice gets shorter.
I don't announce the words.
I say things fast like this.
My voice drops down like this.
No, it's fucking stupid.
It's fucking dumb.
I don't fucking...
It's fucking not even fun.
That's how you can tell.
When I do like impressions of Activision fucking suits,
I'm not...
This is fun.
I'm having a good time.
Wait, why would they put this?
Of course.
Oh my god.
Please tell me they turn this way.
Did they go down there?
Why?
Did they just...
This is scripted.
This is a scripted event.
Dumb.
Okay, where do they go though?
Okay, I need to get this item
because they're gonna come back right now.
Confetti, I need that.
Oh, oh no.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Oh no?
They don't know where I am.
Oh fuck, I gotta kill that motherfucker right now.
Where is he?
It's Shito.
That's right.
All right, this is the strategy.
You ready?
It's saying a head has to work.
This has to work.
Okay, strategy is firecrackers.
Firecrackers kill guy.
One, two, three.
All right, I gotta shut up.
Is there anybody in here?
No, I almost just fucking died.
Okay, so I can go here.
Question is, is this the only guy in here?
I don't know.
I think that's the only guy here.
If it's not, then I'm fucking jumping right back up.
Okay, I don't think there's very...
There's only a couple guys on the bridge.
I wanna jump back up here.
I, I can't, I can't get up there.
I just came from here.
All right, there's that, that's done.
What about over here?
Anybody?
I don't think, I think I got him.
All right, I'm just gonna keep going around.
All right, what about this way?
What do we got?
We got a guy on bridge over here, right?
No.
Two guys over there.
God damn it.
Is there a way to hide up there?
Yep, can I?
I'm not sure where to go.
Is this that?
I can't go that way yet.
I mean, I guess I could.
I could backstab that.
No, the guy across the way, we'll see.
I mean, there's stealth grass right here.
Is this stealth grass?
I don't know.
Oh, God damn it.
This is a real stealth section.
They're like, you know what?
We're like 24 hours into the game.
Throw a real actual stealth section into the game.
I just, that guy not gonna turn around and see this shit.
If he does, I'm gonna be in fucking trouble.
Why?
No.
Wait, get in the water.
Oh my God, there's a guy here.
Who is it?
What's with the indicators?
No, don't.
Get out.
Run.
I don't even know where that guy came from.
Oh, fuck.
Okay, I can deal with him here.
What's with the fucking, all those indicators, man?
You're killing me.
Oh, you're killing me.
It's like the president.
It's the president of the Whistle Club.
What do I do?
Is he?
It's Gandalf.
It's the Albus Dumbledore.
How many more jokes can I make before I kill him?
Let's see.
Okay.
How much more is left of this section?
I don't like this place.
It's too, if I fuck up anything.
Imagine right now.
Imagine just fucking up now.
And having to do the whole section over again.
I don't care if I look like a coward.
I'm going to do this as slow and as meticulously and stupid as I possibly can.
All right.
There's two on the bridge.
There's a guy.
There's two guys over here.
Yep.
I don't even know where the fucking president wizard came from.
I don't know.
I think he saw me from across the game.
So now, oh, how effective is this though?
Will he see me if I walk out here?
Oh my God, it works.
It works.
Holy shit, it works.
Is there any more?
I don't know.
Who's over there?
Is there a guy?
I don't, it's a position.
Slow down.
Just stay back here.
No one will know I'm here.
Man, that would have been such a nightmare.
He keeps crawling around the corner.
This is harder than a boss.
It's not, it's not that it's hard.
It's just take, oh, I found a thing.
Thank God.
Wait, I hear something moving.
There's going to be one right here.
I'm not going to be able to commune with this.
Oh, yes.
Oh, oh, I feel so much better.
I have money though.
I got like, I have money.
I got to go back and spend this.
What was I going to get here?
This, right?
Increases damage inflicted posture.
Successful in the cure.
I wanted this.
That one's really good.
I land that pretty frequently, so.
And I have money that I need to spend.
Why did I rest?
It's probably, I don't know.
I'm just paranoid.
And I just did it.
Muscle memory, just press the button.
Okay, let's see how much further I can go down here.
I need, I got the money, but I need gunpowder.
Does somebody sell gunpowder?
I don't think this guy does.
Who sells gunpowder?
Okay, how many do you have?
Just one?
Oh, damn, I can just buy you up 10 of them.
I need two for now, right?
Was it four or five?
What was it?
Four or five?
I think it was four.
Yeah.
All right, so this is, I'm upgrading my favorite item in the game.
Long spark.
The effect to be prolonged for longer than the average firecracker.
And the flames bloom for a short time.
Nice.
We're getting there.
Let's put it on.
So I got spring loaded firecracker.
Shinobi firecracker.
Wait, am I stupid?
No, it's got long.
Okay, I already had one.
Okay, I was like, wait a minute.
Yeah, long spark.
Let's try it.
I didn't even look at what this does.
One can fluidly swap between two separate sets of attacks as desired.
That's cool.
Spring loaded axe.
I mean, it's pretty default of me, but I really do like these the most.
Let's see how this looks.
Call me a default streamer, but that's fine.
Whoa.
Well, that takes a little longer to do, but that's,
I wonder how much different that is.
That's a long cast time.
We'll see.
No, okay.
I don't have to hold it.
All right.
That's that's looks better.
So we ended up fountainhead palace.
One, two, three.
Wait, wait, I need my money.
I got to store my money in sacks because I got 600 bucks.
I can store it.
Money is stored in the balls.
That's an old one.
That's very old.
I can buy one of these, which leaves me with 80 bucks.
So I might as well just buy a pellet for fun.
Just have a ton of them in my inventory.
And speaking of which, okay, okay, okay.
I'm ready to dish out the pain.
I've never watched you until now and heard of you from Joel,
but you good sir have me moderately entertained.
Well, welcome.
Can we get a welcome in the chat for BenRick, please?
That's what we do to all new viewers.
We welcome them.
Let me look over here.
Moderately.
Moderately entertained.
Well, that's good.
Hey, first impressions are the most important thing.
I feel like I've given a bad first impression this stream.
Ooh, more divine confetti.
Ooh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Look at this.
Something over here.
Yes, there is.
Look it.
All right.
Go.
Up, up, up, up, up.
Go up, up and jump.
Oh, jump.
Jump when he throws the toaster.
Quick.
Jesus, that saved me.
Did you see?
I've done that too.
What the fuck is that?
Was that the lightning?
What just crashed through the bridge?
What the hell was that?
What just went in the water?
Uh, okay.
I thought that was a lightning bolt.
I'm going to rest.
If I rest, the bridge will be back, right?
God damn it.
This is Mario World.
This is the fish from Mario.
It's the same colors too.
This is the gigantic fish from Super Mario World.
Level three, six.
Dear God.
Well, I made it across the bridge.
Is he just in there?
It's a water boss fight.
It's an underwater boss fight.
Oh, I'm not happy about this.
No, I'm so bad underwater in every game.
I'm terrible under pressure.
Literally by the water pressure.
I can't do it.
Oh no.
I'm panicking already.
I'm like psyching myself up.
I want to get up there.
Because there's an item.
Can I make this jump from here?
I don't think I can make this jump.
Well, let's take care of this first.
Hey.
Aggressive.
Can I get up top?
Maybe.
I can go there.
And then over here.
Oh, come on.
No.
Wait.
Stop.
Just where am I?
Where the fuck did I end up?
Uh, the hell?
I'm-
I can get back up.
I just heard a fucking burp.
That was a burp?
All right.
Let's get back over here.
Takes us down here.
God, I'm just gonna have to jump from here, right?
Am I gonna make this?
There's nowhere to grab.
Guys, I scream in real life.
Okay, when something like that happens.
Okay.
What am I doing here?
Just-
I forget it.
Forget it.
I don't even want it.
Yeah, I do.
No, I don't.
I don't even want it.
I should change my title too.
When I get hit, I pretend to get hurt in the game.
Ha ha ha.
Did you see that?
What was with that spawn thing?
Did you see the spawns here?
What?
All right.
Guy over there.
I'm just trying to cover all my bases here, guys.
I don't want any bullshit to come kill me.
Somebody to fly and gonzo me or something.
We're taking care of-
Oh, I can get through from here.
I win.
Figured it out.
No, I can't.
Really?
There's no way for me to get any-
Grab anything from here?
How do I get this item?
How do I get that item?
There's a bridge.
I can't cross the bridge.
Do you not see the bridge broken in half?
I can't make that jump.
Cross the bridge?
That's a forehead comment, right?
Just cross the bridge.
Forehead.
It has to be.
There's no bridge.
Rebuild it.
All right.
Are you ready for this one?
No.
Just kidding.
I have a feeling.
Let's just keep moving.
Whatever.
That item is probably the best item in the game,
and I'm not going to get it.
Whatever.
There's an equally as cool item down here.
Wait.
No secret waterfall entrance?
Is there?
Okay.
What about-
Let me just check.
Okay.
I can go up from there.
I want to get that, whatever it is, though.
And then I can get back up, right?
Is that a water dog?
Two water dogs.
Three water dogs.
Four water dogs?
Oh, fuck!
It's an electricity dog!
Kill it quick.
Oh, my god.
Wouldn't that kill the dog?
It would kill the dog.
Um, where?
Where are-
Where?
Just because you have electricity coming out of you
doesn't mean you're immune to electricity.
Okay?
That was lucky.
Don't you know?
Even when Pikachu gets struck by lightning,
it still does like 5% damage.
It's just not very effective.
It still hurts.
Even-
Okay, if you put yourself in a suit of armor
and then you jumped in front of a train,
you're gonna be fine.
It's gonna hurt, though.
That was a baby.
No, no, no!
Oh, no!
Nooooooooooooo!
He has a laser!
The laser can shoot through the wall!
He has a laser that shoots through walls.
Fuck that.
I don't want to fight you.
I don't care.
Okay, get me up.
Jump!
Grab it!
No!
No, get me away!
Is he gonna shoot me through the wall?
How far does his, like, smite ultimate beam go?
Ugh!
Okay.
We're alright.
Jesus.
Um, I think I gotta go into that building.
If I were taking a guess.
Could deal with these, too.
I still have plenty of health.
I got out of there quick.
That was lucky.
Let me deal with one of these.
Yeah, let's...
Oh, man.
That's too many.
Uh...
What's this way?
I think I have to.
I don't...
I don't know.
Fuck it.
Okay, watch out for the guy playing soccer!
Alright, where do I go?
Where do I go?
Where's progression?
I think I'm going over this way.
Yep, I found progression.
There's no way I can do that.
I'm sorry.
I'm not gonna...
I'm not stupid.
He's a lightning dog.
Be prepared!
Be prepared for the lightning!
Progression.
Litecoin is down like seven or eight hundred percent since last year.
More electricity dogs.
That's a new enemy there.
That's a big guy.
It's a big bearded octopus person.
Um...
Does he have two bars?
That's a...
Is that a mini boss or is that an NPC?
I don't know.
I'm gonna keep going around this way.
I'm gonna progress.
Go fight it just to hold on.
I'm not gonna go fight that right now.
I need a new stone.
If I die, I have to go all the way.
You can't even see how far away I have to go.
All the way down there.
This is like 35 minutes of progression.
I ain't gonna blow this.
Oh, what the fuck are you talking about, man?
Are you serious?
There's another one.
Why is there another one here?
Do I have to go?
I...
I don't...
I don't believe it.
I'm not going over there.
I have to though.
I have to...
That's the same one?
No, it's not.
There was...
The other one was down that way.
Is there any way I can go up from there?
I just need to look.
I think I can.
Dodge.
I could...
I have to...
Dodges have to be on point right now.
Yeah, call that one in sick.
Yeah.
Oh.
What am I doing?
Hope this is not a bad idea.
Um...
Uh...
I'm actually terrified.
Is there a beach?
A house?
Come on.
Give me a thing to grab.
Come on, please.
No, don't do it like this.
Don't do it like this.
Something to grab.
I can't...
Nothing to grab?
Oh, come on.
You got to be kidding me.
Not like this, man.
I can make it.
Fuck.
Uh...
Oh, no.
Kill that guy first.
I don't even know where that guy is.
He's like up here.
I just killed probably the least dangerous guy.
He just double tapped me.
No, that's not fair.
I was on the ground and it bounced on my head.
What?
Oh, fuck off.
Fuck off with this.
I'm out of here.
There's no way...
I don't know where to go.
There's no way to go.
There's an item.
Oh, shit.
There's two items.
Nice.
And there's that guy over here, too.
There's got to be one path to get back...
To get up this way.
Right?
Like, look.
It's over there.
I can't get up from here.
There's the bad guy.
It appears as an illusion.
What about behind the waterfall?
I'm going for it.
Let's see.
Nope.
That ain't going to happen.
That just ain't going to happen.
That's not going to happen.
It's just that ain't going to happen.
I have to get the terror potion.
Anybody that has the terror buildup
that takes five seconds for the terror to kill you?
You've got to get confetti
and you have to get the terror potion shit.
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
Did you really just hit me from that far away?
What game is this?
What video game is this?
I was a homing missile from across the game.
What game is this?
Kill the streamer.
I just don't...
I'm maybe on the roof?
Like, up here?
I got from behind.
Oh my god.
Why?
I have to go all the way around this.
I'm trying to just skip.
Thanks for the unforeseen aid.
Appreciate it.
No, fuck it.
I'm just gone.
Go.
Fuck off.
Can I make this from here?
I don't know.
Let me try.
What's the ultimate goal?
To go back around this way?
Like, up there?
But I...
How the fuck do I get over there?
I can grab it from here, but there's no grabbing point.
Like, underneath and then up?
That's kind of what I did before.
Because there's no grabbing point here.
Oh, thank god.
I found it.
Okay.
Slow down, slow down, slow down.
There's a door.
Come.
Who?
No, I don't dare.
Of course not.
Ah.
Everybody's still alive, so this is bad.
I'll take one at a time.
Come on, let's go.
Fight.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Come on, I can take two.
I've done it before.
I'm scum good.
You too, come on.
Goff.
Anybody else up here?
Anybody, anybody, anybody?
I just don't want to have a problem later.
Video games, video games, video games, video games, video games.
All right, maybe I shouldn't have any more caffeine.
What's wrong with you?
I'm just happy.
I'm just having a good time.
Now, this is where I'm going to make a major mistake.
Can I jump from here and grab something over there?
No, I'm going to go that way.
Because there's a place I haven't gone down there.
And we're going to do it.
Don't get stuck in a wall.
I'm going to do it the correct way,
which is like stuff my body in here
and glitch into the wall
and to a point where I can fall down those stairs.
I fucking, I hate myself so much.
I fucking can't believe it.
There's an invisible wall there.
I can't fucking believe it.
I cannot believe it.
I can't believe it.
I can't fucking believe it.
Skip.
I'm so disappointed in myself.
I'm so disappointed.
Oh, the disappointment is unreal down here.
Like typically I would be mad about
like the bad grade I got on my report card.
None of my parents would be.
My parents would be upset with what I just brought home.
I'm actually more upset than they are.
Why does that keep happening?
All right, let's go.
Line of sight.
I can't hit anything through a goddamn wall.
Stupid.
You're almost as dumb as me.
There's an idol right there.
Is this a mini boss?
Target him so I...
No, it's not a mini boss.
I just have to deal with this.
Sit down.
Don't stand up.
Hey, guy.
The nightmare is over.
For now.
How much money do I have?
I got a lot of money.
I'm going back and buying a gift.
What the hell they are.
500...
It's a lot of money in this game.
You guys don't think 500 dollars is a lot of money?
What are you talking about?
Buy 50.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I'll sell a couple of dumb things.
Where's my large amount of ashes?
Yeah, whatever.
Next time.
Continue.
Great Sakura.
Jerma's afraid of headless?
Yeah, I am.
But I can admit that.
I'm terrified of finding that.
I'm terrified of finding any of the magical people.
Let me just try to kill this guy for fun.
Dragon...
Oh, Gatsaki.
That didn't hit him.
That's not gonna work.
Somebody else is hitting him now.
That was a bad idea.
Um, that was fun.
I'm gonna go this way now.
Oh, there's a mini boss.
Under pressure.
That's how I work.
What is that?
Okay, he kicks balls.
That's a lightning ball.
I got...
Okay, I got these idiots over here like fighting me.
Just die.
Like, I've got five people throwing rocks at me from behind me.
Come on.
Let's go.
You and me.
Lightning balls?
Fine.
Just get up on him right now.
But that hit me.
That's okay.
You have to long wind up.
Long is even longer than that.
Wait, didn't I...
Don't I have a move to stop that from happening?
Okay, what...
Don't I...
I thought I could, like...
Oh, that guy...
You suck.
I'm gonna pray for that, though.
Yeah, it's attack while you're in the air.
Don't just...
Fucking my god.
I know how to do it.
You don't have to, like, demonstrate.
Oh, thank god.
Oh, yeah.
At first sight.
At first speed.
At first sound.
I gotta breathe.
Nice.
Thousand bucks.
All right.
There's no more electricity.
Except that...
Is that guy electricity?
Electricity?
Gone.
I gotta kill this guy.
He's facing the other way.
You don't even know I'm here.
Oh.
It's this lady.
I was supposed to backstab this lady.
You got these great directions.
Large cave.
No.
Here it comes.
I've been trying to avoid having to do this.
Open the door to the palace.
It's under water and it's through a cave that's down here under the water.
And by the way, fight the fish boss.
Well, it begins.
See you guys in, like, four hours.
Lump of wax.
Okay.
So, is the palace this way or is the palace under here?
Let's just take a look under water.
It's over here.
The great carp.
Ah, I'm not an underwater boss.
No, they can't do it to us like this.
They can't do this to us like this.
God damn it.
Fuck.
It's a giant goldfish.
Whatever this is, just let me have it.
Coin purse.
Oh my God.
He's dead?
He's dead.
I killed him.
He rolled over like he was in somebody's tank.
What?
Why did he do that?
Just get me out.
Am I safe in here?
But where is the...
How do I get...
Is there a hole up there?
Oh my God.
Jeremy, get in the hole, please.
He seriously rolled over like he was dead.
Like that was his final breath.
I made it.
He smashed his head into a rock.
His last dash.
That's so funny.
I wish that were the case.
Well, waterfall.
I guess.
What's up here?
Wait, I'm gonna...
Let me examine first.
You never know.
There might be something hidden.
No.
It was worth a shot.
Up.
Hmm.
I think I found the back door to the palace.
This really is a pretty, pretty, pretty zone.
The fish.
That fish is cool.
Thank God I don't have to fight it right now.
Hopefully it's just like the snake from earlier.
And it's just a giant annoying obstacle.
I'm missing a ton of hidden shit.
Yeah, look, I can go back there any time I want.
I have a new sculpture here.
I am safe.
Let's see what's in here.
This is a room full of those people.
I'm getting bloodborne vibes from these people.
Door.
Where's your flute?
I have flutes.
Well, what's behind the door?
Is this a shortcut?
Yes, this is the door from earlier.
But this is not really a shortcut.
Because this, I just had an idol right here.
You know what I mean?
Why would I use that shortcut?
That's a chest.
It's like a coffin.
Is there a dead body in here?
Bunch of dead coins.
Well, I know I'm going back right now.
Oh, the lady wanted me to open that.
Right, okay.
What the hell is this?
Let's go.
I'd go back and talk to the lady.
Is she still in the same place?
Oh, she's you.
Well, that's a stab.
Don't embarrass me here.
Standard enemy.
I knew that was coming.
You see me block that shit?
Didn't even know it was happening.
Okay, bye.
Goodbye.
I just want to talk to the lady.
Oh, I picked the worst fucking possible place to jump down.
Hey, I opened the door.
What item do I get?
Prayer bead.
I just did it.
Come on.
Well, now that I'm over here, let me just look around.
Because there's a bunch of shit that's underneath the water here.
I have to rest at an idol, didn't I?
I need to go.
All right, I have a lot of these scales.
I have at least eight.
I got to go back to the guy.
That weird guy in the bucket.
Remember that, dude?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
What this two?
Why is there one of these guys down here?
The fucking most hated enemy in the whole game is down here.
Just give me the item.
Why is he down here?
Are there two down here?
I just want everyone to be aware.
There's two headless in the water down here.
No, I'll never see the end of that content.
And I'm fine with that.
I will never get the 100% steam achievement.
That's fine.
I could give a shit lesson.
I can't believe these motherfuckers are down there.
Two?
There's two?
Headless?
Two?
Watch that be three.
Now it's down here?
Yep.
That's fucking crazy though.
They're really not messing around at all.
Okay, let's go back up.
I don't think you can drown.
Anybody else?
I've these guys have.
Well, I think that's not these are the treasure ones.
All right, I got all that's down here.
Really?
That's fine.
Just.
Ah, I almost had it here.
These carps are everywhere.
I need to go in to see what I can buy.
What a bait.
I'm here.
This is so huge.
It's like almost feels like a waste if I don't go get everything.
I'll forget it this way.
All right, I think that's good.
Maybe one or two more things under these.
Scrap.
Good.
It's just bees.
They can't get you under water.
All right, I'm done fishing.
I got pretty much all the things I wanted.
Look at all that stuff.
Even if I died, how much money do I have?
There's so much.
Look at these four items here.
What the fuck is under here?
Oh, it's a fish.
Okay, one, two, three, go.
Worth it.
Okay.
Sweet.
So now I've rested.
Now I should talk to the lady.
Is this what we're doing?
That's technically a rest.
Try that.
Let's see.
Lady.
Hello.
Front door.
Did you make it?
She's still standing over there.
That's not her.
That's just a piece of metal.
Did I run by her?
Did I just have the blinders on and go right by that lady?
Really?
Well, the room is dark.
It's a pitch black room.
And you're telling me that, like, I can't believe you didn't see the lady
that's hunched over in the corner.
You didn't even look?
Yeah, because I thought she was just, I don't know.
Okay, guys, why would I know that that was the case here?
You don't even, like, look at, okay.
Look at this room.
Those guys are just eating people.
So I'm just going to fucking go this way.
Like, I, what?
No, you're blind.
Shut up.
Um, was that one even worth doing?
You didn't give me anything.
Not even, like, a little icon popping up.
Prayer beads.
Now, let's turn in the seed.
Oh, she was stabbing herself in the stomach.
I thought she was stabbing the body over and over again.
I thought she was, she was stabbing herself in the chest.
She wasn't.
She was stabbing the body.
Well, then, never mind.
Where's my item?
How do you know that?
You didn't see.
Um, I gotta go.
That lady goes from place to place.
She teleports as much as I do.
How much money do I have?
I got cash now.
Hmm, wait.
What can I do?
Oh, here.
Dragon Spring sake.
Give me a story.
I've given all sake to this guy.
With Dogen, Emma would keep our cups filled.
Have you known Lady Emma for long?
I found her on a battlefield.
A field?
She crept up slowly towards me.
Her eyes fixed, unwavering on the rice I held in my hand.
I got some of that, too.
You want some?
So I gave it to her.
Then she just started following me.
After that, Ashina became a dangerous place for the both of us.
Around then, Dogen adopted her as his daughter.
Wait, what?
I suppose it didn't really matter where she ended up.
Hold on.
One thing's for sure.
So he's happier for the fact she wasn't raised by a shinobi.
I've never seen this guy's face.
That's the person that raised Emma.
And Emma said she was raised by monkeys.
Yeah.
Let's go and talk to Emma about her really elaborate,
truth-stretching Facebook post.
Yeah, I was raised by wolves.
Were you?
No, you don't get that.
It's mine.
Master Wolf, it looked your brow.
Yeah, we've heard about my brow.
Goodbye.
We're just up here.
I might as well just get some more dialogue.
Anything?
I hope he's all right.
Oh, are you unhurt?
My lord.
Ah, this is for you.
Sweet Rice Balls.
A sweet sticky rice ball made by Kuro.
Slowly grants medium vitality recovery and constant posture recovery over a time.
Wolf senses it was crafted with feelings of resolve and a reluctance to part ways.
Okay.
So this is just a big...
I need to use.
I will obtain them.
Heal over time.
Yes.
I'm counting on you, Wolf.
So many items.
Number held one and a one.
I think this is just a one and done.
Well, thanks for the extra gourd.
I'm ready.
Palace grounds.
Eat it in front of him.
No, I need that for like a boss fight.
I'm not just gonna eat that in front of him.
He's not a boss.
I gotta go back and...
I gotta upgrade my stuff.
I think I have enough materials to do another one.
Oh, the fat guy that wanted the flower.
You're right.
I have that too.
You need...
All right.
Can I upgrade anything here?
I need more stuff.
I can't do it yet.
I need three more gunpowder which I could buy
and one more of that...
Is that iron scrap?
Let me see.
Does he sell that?
He does.
Okay, I can get that.
So I need...
How many do I need?
I need three of these, right?
Let me use my coin purse things.
So one more of these.
And then was it two of these that I needed?
It's two, right?
Two and then 600.
How much money do I have?
So now I need to take three of these.
Let's go upgrade this and then get close to the ultimate firecracker.
That's a thousand.
Shit!
It's a thousand?
That's so much.
Come here.
So what does this axe do though?
Is it worth putting on?
This is pretty deep in here.
Sparking axe.
Attach percussion hammer to create flame.
So bring a flaming axe down from above to strike an enemy.
Destroy shields made of wood and creates a roar of flames on hit.
Cool.
All right.
And then purple fume spark.
Here we go.
Final tier has been revealed.
It is...
Oh, it looks like...
Lazulite axe.
The hefty Lazulite blade inflicts damage even on guarding enemies.
It's like the super...
Minecraft.
What's the stuff from Minecraft?
Blue Lapis?
What's it called?
What about...
What's it...
Oh, the fuck.
Oh, man.
Oh, that's actually not that cool.
Never mind.
It's all Lazulite.
No Lazulite...
Sparks?
Phantom Kunai.
All right.
So now we need two of an item I have not seen yet.
It's like some kind of salt.
And then 1500 bucks.
I'm going to get rid of this and put on the better axe.
Sparking axe.
Better shurikens and long spark.
Combat arts.
I don't really use this that often, but it's useful sometimes.
This is the stealth one.
I'll keep it.
Can I help you with your essay?
Hey there, friend.
I don't think you'd want me to do that.
I'm going to buy...
I'm going to buy one of the...
Yeah.
I feel like I'm going to need these.
All right.
It's time.
The question is where...
Where is the barrel guy?
He's over here.
I don't remember.
It's either here or...
I think it's here.
Because this is...
He was very early in the game.
How early was he, though?
Oh, here it is.
This is it, right?
Please help with the essay.
No, I don't...
I can't.
Is this it?
Yeah.
Help him!
You don't want my help.
You'll get an F.
You know what?
No, I'll help.
Fine.
You want me to help you?
Listen.
Here you go.
Here's the advice.
Eat a good breakfast tomorrow.
I'm talking like two eggs, maybe one piece of bacon, some fruit, like a peach.
Sit on the couch for like 30 minutes, digest it,
make it get into your bloodstream, into your brain for brain power.
And then start.
That's my advice.
You need good brain power to do anything.
Like, for instance, today.
Good quality brain power food.
You've got to feed your brain.
And your brain is the most important organ.
It takes from any of the foods you eat.
How do you think you can, like, think?
Is you need good, high quality foods.
So I went to Burger King today and had a double whopper and two large fries.
I almost shit my pants before the stream.
I had so much time, I just fucked it up.
Oh, I need to look around.
Because there's got to be something under here.
Why would there not be something here?
The essay's due tonight.
Well, why did you wait so long?
You should have, you should have done it earlier.
All right.
Purchase items.
So I have 13 floating passage.
This is five, seven for the mask fragment.
Divine grass.
Does he have more than one of these?
I'll just buy 13 of these.
Skill unlocked upon requiring this item.
Unleash attacks in a flowing dance-like form,
overwhelming enemies in a furore of graceful aggression.
This technique belongs to the Ashina Sword School,
though it has been deemed heretical due to its foreign origin.
Red gourd.
Reduces burn buildup and slightly increases burn resistance.
It cannot heal the burn status abnormality, however.
Okay.
That sounds pretty good.
So this is just another drink.
How many, does he get five uses?
Oh, damn.
Give me that.
There's like three of these pieces.
I don't know if I'm going to be able to get all these.
I'm not sure if it's worth buying this.
How many pieces do I need?
Like two, three, four?
Mask fragment right.
I mean, I have the money.
There are three pieces.
It's really useful,
but I don't even know where to even start for that.
I know I saw the other one,
but there's apparently another one somewhere.
How many of these does he have?
He only had one.
Okay.
Well, that's worth it.
Well, I got the useful stuff.
I know where it is, right?
I know it's here.
You want to be the fish?
Holy shit.
Great Canadian fuck club.
20 community subs.
20 community subs from great Canadian.
Oh my God.
That's a shitload of subs.
That is a shitload of subs.
Thank you.
Damn.
What a great Canadian.
So you go, that's actually really good.
That comes up quick.
I like this better than the other one.
And then the other thing I have is slow.
You could like do a dodge or like dodge around and bang and then get out.
Maybe I'll try it.
Hey there.
Want me to just kill this guy?
No, I'm just kidding.
Cool.
So I have the gourd now.
Let's see.
Reduces burn buildup.
So I feel like I should have had this a long time ago.
There's been at least three or four bosses that were fire based.
I hope this is still worth using
because it took me a long time to get it.
717 subs.
Yeah.
You guys remember when we were talking like a few months ago
or two months ago, three months ago about crossing
like the thousands of subs that are on this channel?
Yeah.
Great Canadian has and had more than that I think earlier.
That's a shitload of money.
All right, let's go.
Time to fight.
No one actually is subscribing.
He's just giving everybody subs.
I never wouldn't see that surprising.
And here comes Kairatobi with 10.
217 from Kairatobi.
A lot of 17, 717, 217.
Interesting.
Got any tips for the Genichiro fight?
I'm about to lose my fucking mind with how hard it is.
Um, honestly with...
Okay, Splarg, five community subs.
Thanks a lot.
Thank you, Splarg.
I'll tell you with all the fights that are on the boss platform,
it's...
Everyone's...
I've read a lot of people talking about
be aggressive, aggressive, aggressive, going and go hard.
I'm not sure I agree.
At least for the fights that are up there.
I like to take a more parry, learn their moves
and just kind of block, block, block, parry, parry, parry, parry.
Sometimes when you go in, you can cross your brain up
with whether to swing or to block or to swing or to parry.
The deflect is so useful and it's so good
that it's, I think, at least on some of the fights
that when you fight a guy with a sword
to try and get the parry down for the moves.
And then there was another thing that...
Bebraham gave 10 community subs.
10 subs, 20 subs, 5 subs, 25, 5, 5, 10, 5, 5 from Freudian Weapon.
You guys trying to put me in another tax bracket?
Holy shit.
Here's the door.
Thank you for the tons of community subs, guys.
I have a feeling this is a boss.
Let's see what it is.
Maybe not.
Another zone.
I'm going to sneeze, I think.
Yeah, but ooh, item.
Just get it.
It is right here.
I need to use these.
I just never have the opportunity to go and do it.
Dude, if I could make a script.
Well, if I could have a script
that would automatically activate one of those.
Every like 30 minutes, I would have it work.
It's something like hanging on the tree.
What is it?
Oh, it's just a lizard.
Thank you, Jiber.
Jiber is 7.
5 more community subs.
Sub train, after sub train, after sub train.
Sub, sub, subs.
I like this little spot, though.
He was just chilling.
Yeah, but look, his anger meter is there.
Maybe?
Because back up here is the...
No, I guess we're going this way.
Dear Meaty, 5 community subs.
Thank you, guys.
5 more.
Looks like I can get up there.
So many subscriptions.
Come on, I can't reach the...
Jump from tree to tree, maybe?
The Zinger Slinger.
5 community subs.
Subs, subs, even more of them.
They just don't stop coming.
They are just here.
Forever.
Sub train.
Thank you, Zinger Slinger.
All right.
Is that an enemy or is it just somebody angry
that I'm coming up here?
No, somebody's just powering up.
Spliceable Spleen.
5 community subs.
Thank you.
Subs.
Holy shit.
All right.
That's too many.
Too, too many lightning bolts.
You didn't even do it.
God.
No, stop!
Just...
I gotta pull you down here.
Get it!
Oh my God!
Die!
Honest to God.
I can't believe that guy's still alive.
I'm shocked.
Damn it!
No!
Damn it.
Oh my goodness.
These guys are so irritating.
Uh, Krusty!
Thank you, Krusty, for 5 community subs.
All right, look at the health.
Like, give me a break.
What are you doing?
I feel like I'm not doing
even remotely enough damage right now.
How?
I just upgraded my sword.
What?
That feels so wrong.
I, I even...
Just kidding.
Fucking God, come on!
Why?
I'm not using the other resurrect.
Huh?
I probably didn't do, like...
80% of my health.
All right, let's go.
Just hard to deal with more than one enemy.
When you fight more than one person, you just...
Just fucking...
Chaos.
Can I go around this way and kill one of them?
Deal with two of them.
Oh, three of them at the same time.
It's just, that's not gonna happen.
I guess not.
You just have to do it.
Well, I got none of these.
Fuck.
As long as we're far enough away.
Damn it!
This is such a massive delay.
WHAAAAAAAT?
Wait, hold on. Let me read the message here.
Try backstab.
Hull.
Right? Right, guys?
Oh, they're dead. Nevermind.
Sorry, nevermind.
Should I pray?
Right?
This is Dark Souls game.
You have to write the funny line everywhere.
Behind every enemy.
Behind every person.
Is there an enemy that's facing over a balcony?
There's just a standard enemy.
It better be there.
This is coming from the man who talks about diapers and puke every stream.
Hold on.
Just wait.
I gotta defend myself on that one.
I'm not writing it down and putting it in front of every enemy.
I don't go behind every enemy in the game and say,
Look at his diaper!
That...
Every enemy?
Every NPC?
I don't do that.
Alright, what the hell is this?
This is like...
This is clearly a boss.
Old Dragons of the...
Oh god, they're just gonna cough on me?
No, no, it's like being at PAX!
I don't want to be...
It's like going on an airplane!
Well, okay.
They're just like puking.
Alright, let's go ahead and put on the antidote.
Yeah, From Software has such a massive, massive, massive hard-on
for fight like a hundred of the same enemy in a boss fight.
Really.
Bloodborne, it was the spider boss.
Deacons, like why do they have to do this?
I wonder if there's something like...
Let's see, hold on.
I mean that's kind of...
That actually is pretty effective.
Then I'm gonna get poisoned.
What else do I have here?
What the fuck?
Oh no.
Do I fight it?
Do I fight the tree?
I don't know.
Ooh, that's actually pretty good.
I'm poisoned.
No, it's not worth it.
It takes too long.
Can I like hurt the tree?
No.
Let's go back bread and butter.
Use axe on tree like in Minecraft.
Wait, what's this?
That was a different one.
That one's different.
Is this just the deacons?
What was that?
All right, I can re-come out this time.
This can't be it, right?
I mean that's satisfying to do, but...
All right, that's it.
Is that it?
No, of course that's not it.
Oh, I can't wait to fight the real boss
and then have to do that, what I just did again
because I'm gonna get killed by the guy
that swings like 300 times a second
because he's like one of the later game bosses.
They're gonna all transform
into a fucking monster or something.
Let's see if I can get this done.
I have to take a break after this.
I'm gonna lose.
I gotta grab a little drink.
Man, that's so cool.
Wow.
Oh, divine dragon.
Okay, so that's a sweep.
That's just a big sweep.
What else do you do?
I guess I can go like this.
Ow, that hurt.
Okay, he strikes you with lightning
and then you strike...
Oh, God, where's he going?
Oh, my God, what the fuck is he doing?
Wow.
Wow, this is really cool.
I love this fight.
Holy shit, that hurt.
I'm gonna die.
Bang.
Oh, fuck.
I gotta wait longer than that.
Damn.
Maybe I should just jump around to the trees.
I can't.
You wait.
I can parry the sword.
I'm so far away.
That seems like I shouldn't be able to do that.
It's kind of delayed.
Do again?
Lightning?
Nope.
Grab it, grab it.
Aw.
All right.
Fuck.
I'm dead.
When does he do the electricity?
All right.
Well, hold on.
Okay.
Oh, right.
Okay, so let's just do that again.
All right, well, that makes it a little easier knowing that.
Okay.
Oh, God.
Don't die here.
Give me some more trees.
Tree, give me a tree.
Holy shit.
What the fuck?
Where's the trees?
Oh, my God.
So all right.
That fight is a total joke.
And then he randomly just goes crazy for like 10 straight seconds.
Okay.
Well, now we're going to do the deacons again.
It's just a cinematic boss.
Died to the cinematic boss.
Whoa, who gives a shit?
It's the first time I've even seen it.
I can't believe you didn't beat that.
I mean, like, this is the first time you've ever seen this.
How did you not know that?
I can't...
No, you should have known that you need to jump on the tree.
Were you, like, looking at the boss and how cool the boss was?
You didn't beat it the first fucking try like you did the last three bosses?
I'm something.
No, do it.
Why did I fall?
Oh, it disappeared.
Hi.
All right.
Let's do this again.
That's really not even that bad of a deal.
Hi, King.
Thanks for the 10 community subs.
All right.
Here we go.
Lightning trees.
And then he goes crazy.
This is so cool.
It really is like an awesome fight.
That still hit me.
All right.
Which one's lit up?
None of them so far?
Fly around.
Which one?
He's going to knock me back?
Hello.
I see it.
What the fuck are you doing, game?
Oh, shit.
He was ducking.
I thought I was just going to go right into his body.
All right.
Here we go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just lock on.
I don't matter.
He can go under.
All right.
Go.
Any more?
Over there.
Here we go.
Time for him to do a bunch of stupid moves.
Let's do it.
Come on.
What do you got?
Oh, I was trying to.
I was trying to parry.
Fuck, man.
He's not.
All right.
Here are the trees.
I win.
What?
Whoa.
You're alive?
What's that?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Get it.
Grab it.
Do it.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
That was really cool.
Gracious gift of tears.
I kind of feel bad.
Well, that was definitely the coolest boss fight.
Divine dragon.
Commiem with the sculptor's idol and confront memories of a battle to permanently increase
attack power.
Tutorial boss.
Give it a rest.
Like, give it a rest.
Like this guy.
Lord Isshin, what happened?
That's impossible.
I've been curing it.
I see.
I'm sure you, the central forces, have taken this opportunity.
The key to the secret passage that leads out of Isshin Castle.
The secret passage can be found at the end of the moat in the Isshin Reservoir,
not far from the Moonview Tower.
So this is the same place we were at the beginning of the game?
Yes, Master Wolf.
The secret passage can be found along the moat in the Ashina Reservoir,
not far from the Moon.
Lord Kuro escaped the castle through that secret passage
and should be waiting for you in the Silvergrass Field.
Understood.
The Nightjar have left smoke signals under Lord Isshin's orders.
The smoke should lead the way to order.
Okay, so I have the key.
Cool.
Tutorial complete.
Now the new...
All right.
Anyone that says the word tutorial and boss in the same sentence?
I mean, you can write that, but if there's an LOL there,
or like a Kappa or something,
I want them permanently removed from my chat room.
If I see tutorial boss and only if there's an LOL in there too,
because you could just write,
hey, I died on the tutorial boss.
Right?
Or, the tutorial was really fun.
I really enjoyed fighting against the guy that couldn't die,
but the first boss was tough, right?
That's okay.
But tutorial boss LUL, or tutorial boss,
like, fuck you.
You're gone.
Forever.
All right, I gotta pee.
I'm very fat.
I gotta pee.
Look here, my logs.
Okay.
So there are...
There's over 2,700 people here.
Just checking up and doing a search keyword,
Control F for tutorial boss LUL.
Okay.
So 1,700 people are gone when I press Enter.
So I'm willing to accept an apology before I press this.
I'm sitting right here.
Sorry.
Somebody said not sorry.
Okay.
No LOL.
You suck.
Tutorial boss.
Coward.
Do it.
Not sorry.
Coward.
No balls.
Snap him.
You suck.
You're fat in real life.
Snap now.
Ban.
Sorry, dude.
Okay, there it is.
Yep.
No, I accept it.
I accept the apology.
Thanks, guys.
I like when you guys understand how you're being a little mean
and then somebody, you know,
you collectively can come to an agreement.
That makes me happy.
All right.
So let me...
Do I have beads?
All right.
Divine dragon attack power plus.
You hear that?
That's a fresh one.
I didn't even read it.
Whatever.
I gotta go read that.
I'm interested in the lore.
Where is it?
The divine dragon of the Everblossom
came from the west long ago,
eventually making its way to this land.
I got it.
Some parts of Ashina are exceedingly old,
water coursing through her ancient rocks
and so will allow the dragon to take root.
Okay.
Cool.
All right.
So I'm looking over at the chat
and I'm getting spammed.
Just spammed.
About how...
Don't!
Don't go there!
Wait!
So what do you want me to do?
Is it apparently an optional area
from where?
Just like from here.
There's a kite.
Okay.
This is the dungeon.
All these are locked up again.
So from the dungeon entrance
it's just from here.
No way!
Don't!
Can I get out of this way?
No, there's another window, right?
Let me rest first.
Turn on smart clicks.
There's an idol up there.
All right.
Here we go.
There's a door.
All right.
Find the...
Well, there's a guy spraying all kinds
of weird shit down there.
Hello?
Where?
So I'm apparently...
They're just fighting.
Oh, look.
I found the thing that people were yelling about
and screaming.
My ears are bleeding.
Because of how loud the screams were.
So it's down there.
Hey-o!
Just wait until them to fight.
You kill each other.
I don't care.
Why are they fighting each other?
All right.
Well, I don't know
if I wanted you to win or not.
Okay.
So...
Did I...
Was I supposed to hold on to it?
I did it.
Okay.
Yo, we are perfect!
Well, let me go get this idol.
Perfect streamer.
Okay.
So then from here
just go down this way?
Okay.
Who just...
How did...
Did everybody just see me?
Which way are they facing?
No.
This is just a fight.
My God.
Um...
I'm just gonna hang on the ledge
and just shimmy across.
Oh, there's items here.
Wait.
What?
All right.
Whatever.
You're killing him.
Stop.
All right.
I've had enough.
I've had just about enough.
Die!
The only guy fighting me!
It's a fair!
The guy shooting me!
If you didn't have a buddy
I'll not fire from your birthday.
Happy birthday!
Hope you have a good one.
Mystery dowsing powder.
It heals, burn status.
Burn, burn, burn, burn.
Fire, fire, fire, fire.
Mystery fear to her eyes.
The bloodshot, the waters of the fire.
Use this if you don't want to die from fire.
I got you.
Great.
Come on down.
Remember we talked about
how I need a fire thing?
Well, good thing I have it.
Man.
These guys have the two blades.
Really?
Like what?
Why do you have a trillion posture?
Like you have a million posture.
I got to bring your health down
to something like this.
This is fucking ridiculous.
Look at my posture.
This is the fucking hardest
enemy in the game.
They should upgrade you to boss.
Fuck off.
All right.
This is a big guy killing me.
Fuck off.
All right.
There's a big guy down here.
There's another one of these
goddamn dual welders
with the bane of my existence.
All right.
You had your friend
or your brother
or your colleague.
I don't even know
who the fuck it was.
Compare the two of you.
You don't deserve
to be down there.
Oh man.
All right.
Well, grab.
Interesting.
Drinking?
That's a slo-
Ah, that's a slo-
I thought it was a grab.
Ah.
Stop spamming block.
I need to know what he's doing.
You want me just to let him hit me?
Or do you want me to block
and see what he does for a move?
Ah, just let him hit me.
That sounds good.
Oh, this is going to be painful.
Because I got to go through
that whole goddamn camp again.
Fuck.
I got to go through this whole-
I can't-
Can I just sneak in here?
Ah, shit.
This is going to be awful.
I got to go through
this whole thing again.
I wonder what happened.
Okay, wait.
Hold on.
Can I, like, listen to you talk now?
I'm still Ashina Will-
Okay.
Um.
I wonder if I can find
a way to get around here
without having to do this every time.
I'm not in the right place.
Well, I wonder.
Is the entire camp
going to follow me?
Let's see.
Let's see how great
this area is.
I'm going to aggro the whole camp.
He's waiting for me?
Oh, that's not going to work out.
No way.
Oh, no way.
That's no way.
Everybody here.
What if I just run by everybody?
What else is here?
Is there something else here?
I guess this-
I don't have to do this.
Yeah, I remember this area,
the pan guy.
I'm going to just see
what's over here.
Oh, shit.
Okay, that's-
I need that item.
Oh, my God.
Jesus Christ.
This is crazy.
The way it does
is an idol up there.
Get up there.
Come on.
Oh, my God.
I can do it.
And I fell off.
I wonder if this
is an optional area.
I didn't-
How the fuck
am I supposed to know
you're up there?
Where is this-
Why am I locked onto this guy?
Oh, fuck this place.
Okay.
So, what the fuck
am I supposed to do now?
Well, I didn't mean
to do that.
Well, that was-
All right, I'm going to
go this way.
That's not an item.
Wait, where?
Oh, God.
Where did you come from?
Okay.
That wasn't terrible, but-
Oh, there's a lot over here, huh?
One guy on the road.
Ah.
I look over here.
Jeremiah, I think you're
making a very
prognitorial boss
can be challenging.
Take your time
and have fun with the game.
I'm glad you're trying
out your first
Soulsborne game.
It's-
We're still on-
All right, now you got me
all fucked up
because I had to read that.
Oh, God damn it.
I fucked it all up,
because I-
All right, I'm never reading
chat ever again.
I got the whole fucking
village after me now.
Oh, man.
Oh, there's no-
Nowhere is safe.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Oh, my God.
There's a chest.
No.
Nowhere is safe.
Whoa.
Oh, no way.
Oh.
Is there a
chained ogre here?
Are you sure that
they're not just
spawning in random
enemies of this zone?
That guy didn't even
try to fight me.
He just fucking
walking around.
That wasn't even-
That guy didn't even
try to fight me.
This is just an
optional war zone.
I don't-
I don't know-
I don't know
where I'm going.
Um, it's-
In there?
What is in there?
This is where I
fought the bull, right?
Oh, my God.
Wait, there's an
idol right here.
What-
Wait, where am I going?
Wait, what the fuck
is going on?
Are they-
There's random
enemies in here.
monster in here.
Demon of hatred.
He's got three bars.
Oh, boy.
Here we go.
All right.
You look like a
Dark Souls-
Souls-born
boss.
What do you got?
That's
pretty good.
You got a
firearm.
Okay.
I can-
I get you in the
hand.
Definitely-
I don't know if I want
to parry his
fire-like
swirly arm.
That's a-
Okay, that's
classified as a sweep.
Holy shit.
What the hell am I
supposed to do about
that?
I wonder if I should
just dodge.
If I
not, though.
Grab him.
Show me your
moves, please.
I want to see if
you can-
Good thing there's an
idol right here.
Is he-
Wow, that's an
enormous hitbox.
Holy shit.
Oh, my
goodness gracious.
Okay.
Well, a couple of
things that are very
clear here.
No, this is only
magnetic.
Red.
So it was-
No.
Uh, fire
gourd.
There is it.
Reduces burn
buildup.
Is he gonna
drink it
whenever it's
available?
Alright.
Let me try-
Let me just
get-
Let me just see
it again.
Let me fight you
like a-
like a fucking
dark soul boss.
Jesus!
He just does it-
Wow!
That's a
one-hit kill.
That-
Look at that
hitbox.
Did you see how
big that hitbox was?
There could have
been seven of us
lined up there.
Ooh.
Hey, this is
the only-
Let's just
keep getting
harassed kicked.
Let's go.
Let's try to
take it slow this
time.
You gotta run
underneath that.
Once he queues up
that, you gotta
run.
Oh, boy.
That-
The arm is
so weird
because it's so
squiggly.
That's the
problem, man.
Look at this
thing.
Maybe-
I'm just gonna-
Maybe just
run behind him
to stay all the
way behind him.
Don't even
let him give him a
chance to, like,
touch you.
He's gonna try
to do it, but
maybe-
Can I get in there
quickly?
I can't go
through his
legs.
What is this?
Jesus.
Oh-ho-ho.
Damn.
All right.
I'm gonna-
This is crazy.
Oh,
leave the fuck away.
Like that.
Not good.
Come on.
I can't attach
to him.
See, when he-
When he gets in front
of you, that's, like,
the worst part.
You gotta stay
with him.
Jesus.
He gets so
much range on you,
and then it's, like,
silly spring on him.
See you later.
There's gotta be a
way I can get
the fucker right.
Guess not.
What the fuck are
you supposed to do
against those?
Shit.
They take up, like,
the whole screen.
Jesus.
Run straight through,
I'm thinking.
I'm thinking run
straight through those.
All right.
Run straight.
He's gonna throw
the fireballs.
I think I can go
right underneath him.
Yup.
All right.
It's just figuring it out.
It's just figuring
that shit out.
We go again.
Oh, yeah.
At least I didn't get hit.
All right.
First phase is kind of-
I'm figuring
this shit out.
Ooh, that hurts a lot.
Damn it.
Oh, my God.
That does so much damage.
Oh, that's, like,
almost-
That's, like,
almost 80 percent
of your whole health bar.
Fuck.
Oh.
Slowly but surely,
I'm figuring it out.
You know what I mean?
Let's get an
actual attempt with
me not getting
hit by the fireballs.
That's a-
That's a big deal.
Here comes fireballs.
Oh, fuck.
I thought it was
a little bit longer
than that.
That's all right.
That's not good.
Yeah, I was
fucked there.
So I thought,
in my brain,
when he does the belly
flop, I thought
maybe I could
hold onto it.
But last time,
it still hit me.
That right there,
that right there,
that,
that little, like,
whip.
He does, like,
a tiny little jab,
and it's a massive,
fucking awful thing
you have to avoid.
If I'm going to try
to stay next to that leg,
then I've got to
be ready to
dodge straight through that.
Bro?
Oh, this is
a bad place to be.
This-
This, I couldn't
pick a worse place
to be right now.
Fuck it.
Of course he has to-
Of course he goes
all the way back here.
Like, look at him.
Like, get out of here.
Like, why?
Get the fuck out of there.
Because if I-
I have to run over there
to make him do anything,
and now he's going to
throw the fire at me.
It's such a huge,
open area.
How do you get stuck
in the wall?
This is the biggest area
of any Souls game.
Besides maybe Orphan.
And you go into the corner.
Oh my goodness.
Two steps.
There we go.
Nah, I'll get
me the fuck out of here.
No corner, no corner,
no corner, corner, corner.
Here comes.
See?
I have to jump twice.
There he is.
He does it twice,
and the step.
Oh.
Damn, he does like
four moves in a row there.
Fuck.
This fucking silly string.
Oh my god, please.
Dude, I don't even know
what he-
What the fuck
he's even doing for moves.
He's kind of just
ripping his body in circles.
And his arm is doing
the rest of the work.
Not very good telegraph,
so.
What's this?
Well, I got him down
to his lowest point,
and he's like,
oh my god.
Oh my god.
I got him down
to as low as I've got him ever.
It's that,
it's the close swipe it is.
Well, it's not gonna die.
That's gonna happen, man.
This is,
this boss has got,
so I got three phases
with this dude.
Let me see if I can just get,
I wanna try to get him down
by two and one.
See what he does
in the next phase.
Like, I'll get in here.
Let's go.
When you get
a certain amount of range,
he does that crazy
move set there.
To the corner again.
God, what's this?
What's my luck?
Come on.
Back it up.
I ain't gonna have that happen.
Fuck, I thought he
was throwing balls.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Of course he does it there.
Really?
No way.
That's the first time
that's happened.
It's because I was coming
down an incline.
Oh my lord.
It's because I've
gone down an incline.
Yeah.
All right.
One more try.
And then I'm gonna go,
come back.
I want new items.
And I still got hit by it.
Oh, that's helpful.
Like, what?
Really?
I still got hit by that?
What was that?
It was like a fucking
two second residual hitbox?
This guy may as well
be hitting me with a fucking
giant square.
He's got a giant flaming
square on his head.
Oh.
There it is.
There's a twice.
And he stomps.
Fuck.
Oh.
Two stomps.
He's got such
a difficult move set
to fucking telegraph.
It really is ridiculous.
Sometimes he stomps twice.
Oh yeah, yikes.
I'll get it though.
It'll take me a while.
I didn't jump?
I mean, I'm in the air.
I was...
You guys saw that.
I'm in the fucking
goddamn air.
Back up.
Two stomps.
Fuck.
I thought it was the balls.
Oh, man.
What?
No.
Come on.
What the fuck?
Do I have five more
seconds?
No.
Fuck.
Do I have 500 ping?
That's actually fucking
infuriating.
The dream of maybe
taking him down
is still possible.
Oh, fuck.
Here it comes.
He's gonna throw it.
Oh, he's so close to one.
Firecrack is worthless here.
What items could I possibly
use right now to make this
easier on me?
Maybe...
What about this?
I'm curious.
Let's just see something.
Finger whistle.
I'm just throwing darts
here.
Hold on.
Oh, come over there.
Hi.
You wanted my attention?
Well, I'm here.
I poisoned him with this?
No, I got the wrong thing
equipped.
Just kill me.
Do it again.
He's weak to the AK.
I would hope so.
Defense sugar.
Yeah, I mean,
here's the thing though.
I want to...
If I use those now,
I'll just waste them.
You know, I want to get
in a position where
I'm confident in at least
dodging or blocking or
moving away from...
They're already moved.
Just look right there.
Like, oh,
I get the candy.
It's gone.
And this guy will use
them all.
He'll take every
single thing from me.
I guess some of the ones
that are huge telegraphs
like this stomp.
Maybe I'll try to deflect
it.
Let me see if it's
possible.
Let's see if I can get him
to do it.
What?
He has so much time
on that move.
You've got to time that
move perfectly.
You're going to get hit
by it every time.
Stomp.
Let me see if it's even
possible, man.
Come on.
Well, he didn't get me.
Somehow.
What?
No.
Like, really,
really,
realistically speaking,
why did I not dodge that?
I...
Realistically speaking,
let's be real about that.
I can't jump that?
Or am I just too close?
I feel like it's half
the time that move I can
get away from.
That's not, like,
technically a sweep
movement.
Well, I did it.
I'm not even sure
what I'm doing here.
It looked like
it was doing something.
Fucking gigantic box.
Fuck you.
No, he's jumping!
Oh!
Phase one.
Done.
Phase two.
Incoming.
Attack.
Oh, now what?
Now what do I have to do?
Same?
More of the same?
A little more of the same.
What the fuck happened there?
You have to stay...
You've got to just
run the fucking way
when you go to that move.
You just run the fucking way
You just do.
There's no way
you can dodge those.
Like right now,
I've got to come out of there.
Hold on.
Itchy eye.
This is not eye...
Why would I even use that?
Oh!
Sorry.
Uh...
Um...
Let's go.
Let's try it again.
I don't know.
My eye, my right eye
is so irritated right now.
Why?
Do you have like
allergies or something?
Fuck.
Just kill me.
I've got to start over.
Ugh.
I've got this like
extreme eye itchy eye
irritation.
Ugh.
What the fuck
is happening right now?
This is like
unbearable.
My right eye
is like going crazy.
Ugh.
This is a problem.
I'm trying to deflect it.
It's a mistake.
Honest to God,
I just did keep doing
what I was doing.
So much to happen.
I need to at least
get to like
the second or third phase.
Maybe if you...
I wonder if you deflected
if you like
toss them backwards
or something.
Going off.
You get him to do that,
you get a good
bunch of hits on him.
Here he goes.
He's going up.
Get me away from
the wall here, man.
We've got to get away
from the wall.
Away from the wall.
Away from the...
Just come over here.
But if you go too far away,
he might throw that shit at you.
You know what I'm saying?
He might throw
that shit at you.
Hey.
Throw.
I'm far away.
Got it.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Got it.
Eight boards.
Let's go.
He does that
explosion.
Get it.
Wait just a minute.
Oh.
He fucking did
something different.
Oh.
That was
a weird angle.
Oh.
I hate that move.
It's so hard to get
around.
Oh.
It really is.
Just fucking takes up
so much real estate.
He's got more
moves and shit now.
This motherfucker
is adding moves.
That's new.
That's...
Oh my God.
There's so many
things to learn.
What the fuck
is this?
Jesus Christ,
man.
We got like
another...
a 25 minute boss fight
if you do everything right.
Oh my
goodness.
Is this Warcraft?
Am I playing
World of Warcraft
or is this
an action game?
Yeah.
We got him down
to five percent.
Yeah.
Two percent.
DPS hard.
Okay.
Here comes phase two.
All right.
This is where...
The mages
and the warlocks
It's been...
It's been 18 minutes.
Yup.
Okay.
Still fighting.
One percent.
Come on.
You can do it.
I haven't seen him
do that.
I'm already
not a great start
but I'll try it.
Fuck.
You got too many
like hairs.
That was
an instant kill.
What?
In the name of fucking
God, man.
Instant kill.
We got...
This is optional?
Well, I've been here
for long enough.
I have to do it.
I know this is probably...
This is probably
like this.
And it's...
Here it is.
So, I'm...
I'm going for it, man.
I'm already here.
I got...
I got him down
to one bubble.
I can't just leave.
Again with this.
Oh, God damn it.
Not again.
Oh, my God.
It's the bane of my whole existence.
It is the guaranteed to die
if it touches you.
Oh, it's the worst.
It's the worst.
It's the worst, man.
It's so hard to tell
when he's going to do it too
because you got to stay close.
This motherfucker
can just pull that
like a deck of...
He can just throw it up there
whenever he wants.
Let's go.
I'm doing something.
Kind of in the ball though.
At least he hit me a couple of times.
Balls, right?
I'm getting the fuck out of here
when he does this shit, man.
I honestly cannot believe
that the stomp hit me.
This guy is an earth-sized hitbox.
He...
She's so...
She stands there
and he's got
a hitbox the size
of a goddamn Jupiter
around him.
Holy shit.
Well,
do I have anything
I can do here?
Is this guy dead?
Wait, now...
Why can't I do this?
I should know how to do this.
I don't think I have anything, guys.
Prevents damage from fire attacks,
but man, I got to go...
I can't get that right now.
I got to go from all the way up here
to get this.
Let's see what I can do for skills.
That guy is fucking crazy.
Well, there had to be one, right?
Or two?
Um...
No, no, no.
Skills, skills, skills.
I got six points.
What am I...
What do I need here?
Uh...
This is less sound.
It's just more...
Spirit emblems.
Fang and blade.
Midair prosthetic tool.
I'm not sure what the hell I should buy.
Well, I'm going to do this.
Because that will...
That seems good.
Forward dash.
After you use prosthetic,
you can get close.
Then these.
Midair prosthetic.
Tools while in midair.
That sounds kind of good, actually.
What was the other one?
It was like another...
It was deflection, right?
Yeah.
This one.
You can deflect in the air.
That's a huge deal.
I don't know how the hell I didn't have this.
And leads to...
Combat arts while in the air.
Uh...
This is kind of good.
I'm going to hold on to the points, though.
Because I don't think there's anything else
I really want here.
HR slash.
Living force.
Shadow rush.
Unleash a long-range powerful thrust
and use the impaled opponent as a platform
to vault into the sky.
Hmm.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I mean, I have to spend them somewhere.
Attack with the sword and tool simultaneously.
That's pretty good.
Midair tool.
Eh.
I like this.
Let me take a look at it.
Special sword attacks can be performed
immediately after using prosthetic.
I can trigger it right afterward to a follow-up attack.
Actually, I use the firecracker so often.
What do we got here?
Floating passage.
I like it.
I just took it off.
Jerma lied about Minecraft VR.
Thanks for the five community subs.
Thank you.
Welcome back.
All right.
Where's the...
Where the hell is the blacksmith?
I don't have any money.
I died like ten times.
But thank you so much, Jerma lied about Minecraft VR.
Talk to Kuro again.
Try to talk with the immortal training dude.
He's dead.
Secret passage.
Yeah.
Give Gord seed.
Why would I...
Oh.
Flug Boy.
Five community subs in Flug Boy.
Thank you so much, Flug Boy.
Single-minded search for strength entered
and taking the machine for his own.
This is the result of combining techniques from the styles he encountered.
Lord Isshin.
If Sekiro is able to master these, I'd like to duel him.
Oh, he's dead.
Please.
I'll give him this book.
Wait, so did I...
He died before we could fight.
I still haven't beaten Lord Genichiro.
I just want you to know there are bite marks in my controller
and I hope you're having a good night.
This game's rough, man.
It really is.
It's a lot of fun, but it is fucking brutal.
It is super sharp.
It's like eating the most delicious thing you've ever thought of.
Think of the most delicious hamburger you could ever eat.
Oh, my God.
I love it.
It's a perfect flavor.
But the burger's made out of glass.
That's kind of how this is.
Jesus.
Empowered mortal draw.
How do I even get these?
Not available.
Five skill points.
One can draw, riddling a longer range, more powerful slash attack.
Draw the sword that cannot be drawn and unleash its devastation.
Ooh.
All right.
Well, I'm not sure.
I'm not sure what to do.
Should I keep smashing my head against the wall and try to beat this boss?
Or should I continue to progress the story in the game?
Yeah, there was a...
You know what?
Here's what we're going to do.
For the sake of...
I went by like a few different...
There's at least two mini bosses that I know that I can fight.
There's at least a few.
There's the drunk guy that was out...
There's like two drunk guys.
Go kill headless...
No.
No, I can't.
I can't.
I can't do it.
I don't remember where it is.
So I can't do it.
It's like here, right?
Oh, I can't do it.
Was it hidden forest?
All right.
No, this is going to make me so mad.
Do you see how many times I died at that boss?
Those of you that were here last night.
I died like three or four times to this guy.
And it drove me fucking mental.
I was so angry.
I just died like 10 to 15 times to that giant flaming monster.
And I'm like still fine learning.
Oh, this is crazy.
Wow.
What a move.
This is going to ruin the stream.
And I know it.
Okay.
I'm going to preemptively make sure that it doesn't ruin the stream.
You hear me talking right now?
I'm going to make sure that I'm preemptively making sure this is not going to ruin the stream.
I'm going to be positive about this.
I'm just going down.
I'm going to fight him.
Fuck items.
We're just going to fight him.
All right.
I'm ready.
I'm not going to get angry with this guy.
Wait, wait, wait.
Where is it?
I have it.
It's right here.
I have five of these.
No, I can't do this yet.
No, no, I have to do this before I walk in the door.
No, he's so awkward.
I hate this fucking game.
I hate this fucking series.
everything about this game I've given it a five out of ten no no just pull it back
oh he's so weird and slow all right I'm gonna get him this time you ready okay
let's go you won't like me when I'm angry get this off the bar I'm gonna do
this right fuck this I know this is gonna be a repeat of yesterday it's
not that bad but I'm gonna eat all this candy before I go in there you
ready um let's keep what candy am I gonna do that attack candy this motherfucker's
dead oh my god no god damn it oh my god oh my god he's fucking so oh my god dude
it's I fucking hate this enemy he's so slow and so awkward and the terror
buildup and the fact that you fight him in a kiddie pool and you can't dodge oh
I'm oh my fucking god man he it's it's so stupid I hate this enemy I can't see
the game oh man if yeah I don't care fuck them I can't keep using this
confetti man if I don't know like I fight the terror buildup everything
about this makes me want to delete this game uninstall it and then
fucking shit on it like okay that move right there like it's like I can't even
tell what he's gonna do and now look at my terror it's already almost built up
the people aren't actually telling me to dodge if you are you're banned
from the channel stop trying to parry so if I swing at him he's gonna hit
me with the sword I knew this is gonna happen I don't even want to be
here right now all right let's be aggressive dead I'm already dead for
the past terrible I will die to this guy more than anyone else in the
whole game I hate this enemy so much more than anything more than any enemy
in any of their games that they've ever made any of them no oh no this is the
worst this is worse I you know what I would this is worse than the fucking
flame dog that I was dying to this okay somebody just said there's no
point in attacking him somebody just told me you're not being
aggressive enough go in and be aggressive stop attacking I what are you
talking about
oh back out back up no way no way that got no way I turned around he still got
me in the back it's just Dark Souls 2 lag switching I turned around he still
gives me the back whoa I have three confetti let's go oh come on
hi okay come on kill him kill him more oh my fucking stupid fucking thing I'm
almost dead with the terror do I have any more terror build-up shit I don't
I don't have any more I need another confetti look at my terror though why
what is this movie's doing I don't care I'll fucking go around the goddamn
circle oh fuck he still comes around here
oh fuck kill him my body my body okay I just had to go like I just have to
like walk in a circle I hate that I hate this guy I hate him I hate this
guy I don't want to do that again fallen headless spirit of gachin
suppresses sound and presence making the user harder to detect consumes
spirit emblems to use repeatedly headless of the ruined form of corrupted
heroes who fought for their country I'm falling to pieces said the man to
himself drifting deep into the forest that's it I don't get any prayer beads
or anything killed the other two no you have to be I have to go to
another streamer for that one you have to go to another you have to
click a different Sekiro stream if you like stumbled on here you're like oh
let me watch this guy's Sekiro stream you have to go somewhere else if you
I hate every second of that I'm not even satisfied you know you kill a boss
like you get sad I'm not satisfied I'm more angry I'm more upset that guy I'm
so good I'm gonna just bone out of here the other two are way easier I
don't believe you you gonna fight two at the same time oh there's also
like the wizards the purple shooting wizards yeah let me take a
minute finish the demon no I can't not yet I can't do it the purple wizard guy
that's where we're going the thing is though I I use I have one more confetti
does this guy sell confetti you do 300 bucks that's a ripoff that's three
sit what have I got one dollar I can get two of them here I'm gonna cry
it's gonna make me cry it's gonna make me cry all right I'll take three
it's okay German go ahead all right I think where is it it's like the bottom
was hollow right let me just go see what this guy does then I go kill the
ape with the mortal blade yes it is who cares if I die we're going in
what's your move set all terrible that's all big terror meteor big
terror meteor big one right watch out big one there it's the end that's the end
so you can't come in here unless you have terrible I need something to block
the terror otherwise this is just a no-go
I thought he swings again as long as you keep moving it's really not that
big of a deal but I could use some of those pacifying agents
yeah the big ones that turned midway through hitting that ball curved in
the air twice take a while but
well I know what he does I was scared last time I was here if I come here
prepared watch out watch out let's go I don't want to use a confetti not
yet I could just use it and get screwed
nice relaxing but whoa big one let's get the items that's a scrap metal
ticket maybe I will use a scrap metal I mean a
uh confetti I'm feeling I'm feeling confident right now let's go I got
confidence right now bingo let's do it just one where you go cross the way
this is I need a place to save myself here
that was a mistake it was a huge mistake I just came in here completely
unprepared and thought I could kill him somehow but he moved I for some
reason I didn't think he was gonna move and I had that like little
cheese strat no all right well I'm not gonna do it again until I have
some pacifying things or something to stop that the umbrella upgrade I don't
have I don't think I have the umbrella upgrade confetti will kill him in like
six hits yeah but the problem is just if I get touched by anything it just
instantly died that terror just get dead I'd rather have at least the
papers there was a somebody sold one of those where is it when they're a
guy me boo me boo village me boo manor village there was a guy that sold a
bunch of shit over here where is he it's like a vendor right here right we got
yeah there it is model purple gourd reduces terror buildup and increases
terror resistance and he sells confetti okay what I got for money how
much was it 1800 buck man that's so much am I really gonna spend every
cent I own to get this and then some and we sell on it so I need to sell
some like ash or something too this is really good put me over there can I'm
just gonna sell all my ash I need it's 300 fuck it I don't care there it
is sell some ashes all right let's try it again hopefully these gourds help
later on down the road here in the game let's get it on here purple gourd I get
five right so how long do these last I'm here I'm gonna do a little bit
just hold on let's see one two three four five six seven eight twelve
thirty four fifty six seven eight twenty twenty one two twenty seven eight
twenty nine thirty thirty thirty seconds that's a lot longer than I
thought it was sure let's go let me just see how much does it reduce it's
pretty it's pretty decent it's pretty decent
that's actually great all right so now I'm just making sure I have confidence
to use the confetti because really I can just get in there and just beat the shit out of me right there like right there like he'd be
dead yeah who cares maybe well let's you know do it let's go say let him
land you didn't like that again he's gonna do the blast again is me all
right you're dead goodbye hey look at that strategy it works there's
another one of these guys to who dagger with a stark white blade and
hill to converts vitality into spirit emblems originally this time to was
used in a ritual offering at the dragon in which an emblem will be cut from
one's own life force okay so that's that's the self-harm for pellets in
bloodborne okay so the other one is down in I really would rather have
prayer beads to be honest yeah well I got another confetti and I have
another I have plenty of gourds so what does the other one drop let's go
kill the other one he's like right here right what's a good place to go
over here because it's another one of these guys back this way okay he's
under here
in the waterfall right he's like right here all right let's make sure I
don't get chased the spawns are right in here it is I think I even have that
why like why just let me jump up it I have I can't grab that shit okay here
we go can I land I can I probably take one of those if there's another dog
chasing me no all right so here we go should be able to get one or taken
away apparently not easy now watch that build up one where is it gonna be of
the end of the river back in the I don't know where's it gonna be
yep let's try out of confetti guys that's bad else sucks this is actually
terrible really
why is that dog have to even do it what's the point of that dog it's just
to be irritating there's no other reason it's just there to be annoying
well I kind of screwed myself there I didn't have enough confetti well what
about some other bosses mini bosses that I didn't kill there was two drunk
guys uh yeah they were back here where was that guy I think down this
way right down here I remember because there was somebody it was that like he
was purple I remember this is the right place maybe the element was closer no I
think this is this is it right no because that's the water was that guy
these zones are so huge and expansive it's really easy to forget where
anything is that's what the fish is a long time ago I fought somebody and I
said no no not gonna happen it was like the first two or three hours of the
game where he was like on he was in the castle I think spear guy now I
killed spear guy the spear guy died it was the second drunk dude with the
ghosts I feel like there's something down you know now that well yeah it was
this way but it was no wait a minute hold on it was too many places too many
things to remember here cuz then this is down to the demon but there was a
guy he's yeah down here all right here we let's try this fire make a funny
joke that's not how it works please save Ashina yeah I remember this cuz
there was a lot I gotta clear this out try not to take that much damage but
is there a way for me to just shimmy across the bridge without being
seen it has to be don't tell me there's not right hang from ledge hang from
ledge right here no I don't talk to you hang from ledge shit no there is no
hang from ledge I can do that and then no they're looking at me I don't know
if it's possible oh no I think you just gotta do it I you got to let him fight
on the bridge and come in and just clean him up I didn't do shit one of
the okay that's that guy's bug that guy I found a bug I found a bug in the
game this guy look ready ready watch this watch this guy's posture okay now
watch the guy right here this guy's posture look at that I found a bug
stop just fucking play oh this is so difficult like I can't like be
making stupid jokes here oh my god this portion right here we have to deal
with like four or five people at the same time it is very difficult I can't
be like you say you're like no just do it kill them go that person asking for
jokes you understand how much focus it takes to play this I can't be like
fucking dancing around let's go fighting together what you're looking
on to he's still on the demon I left me I'm trying just to progress in other
ways
nice shot see how it feels you see how that feels to have that happen to you
it sucks cuz you and I were in a one-on-one fight and then you were
I didn't even see your friend I thought it was a sweep and that guy
good yeah bring it on he's monologue her dinner's ready hello
dinner's ready oh no where even is the dinner where's the dinner guy this is
not even the dinner guy what the fuck who is this stop it I'm gonna hear
this is my sleep does anybody know what this guy is I just hear it where
is he it's getting louder is he on the roof you motherfucker
there he is this that little shit so then after all this not then I gotta
fight a boss I'm gonna try to reset him and get the come on man I gotta
take him out where is it I need one of these guys there is two samurai
left there's one is he here so I could hear something yeah of course
he is you sigh you suck this is the guy with a rifle come on here's the key
should be able to burn his friend oh no that's unrealistic this takes place
in realistic Japan all right I'm the fucking wedge dude there's so much to
have to pay attention to this is like scratching your stomach
scratching your ass reading a book driving a car eating a taco and giving
a speech at the same time oh you forget about me I'm one of the 30
people here forget about the big drunk guy running around yeah watch out
for him he'll kill you in one hit did you meet the pan guy yet why didn't you
stealth through here I mean if you would stealth through here somebody
would have seen you in the whole camp would have attacked what were
you doing why what were you thinking fuck this place oh my god oh my god I
can't hurt anybody what are you thinking what are you thinking just go
fight the demon you were having more fun I was you're right fuck this war
zone with the guys that sometimes take 30 hits and sometimes you've done you
kill in fucking four swings it's not this is the optional area where hey
do you hate yourself and hate video games come here and have a fucking
blast yeah you ever shove a wrench up your ass this is what it feels like you
don't even have to do it now every second every second every second every
second he just doesn't stop swing oh my god I just wanted it go over here
dang dang dang dang dang go get hi sorry he's up there I'm gonna hurry the
fuck up and get up there there's the fastest I food in two months I hate
this shit he's just having fun he's having fun just blasted shit look at
this move yeah I've pretended to swing at you wouldn't that be cool I'm
really doing the Joker laugh right now this level is hell this is relentless
fucking enemies and then the fat guy that and then and if you don't kill
pink every aggro's and there's like fucking snake grass over there it's
supposed to help it don't finally you and I can fight one on one dog just
you and me what we've lost him yeah man like this sucks like fuck me oh no he's
on fire after you got to go through all that bullshit to fight this guy
you get but it's optional though Jeremy hey I'm not gonna be able to do
this I just throw up a streamer pukes secure something about this is so funny
do you there when he fucking puked no fuck I want to just get away from
the wall there god damn it it wasn't over I thought it was three this game
is gonna make me fucking lose my mind I thought it was three swings this
game's gonna fuck me up this game's gonna fuck me up an optional area
optional where's that I know I have no I'm so fucked up right now this
is fucking killing me where is it I don't even know where it is which is
this one no that's the demon stairway I think it's stairway I beat this guy in
one swing I'm fucking happy you did I really hope that's true because yeah
that's I bet that's good I hope you did for real okay so if I go from here
to backwards from there I think there's too many I wonder and I get
over here without having a problem here but no way everyone's gonna get
pulled here unless I maybe if I kill those guys first I don't know that's
tricky across the game I mean it's possible maybe to pull just him if I
cleared these guys first which I mean it's like four people though it's not
different it's actually maybe these guys have cannons and shit too
let me read this to patrol where the guy where's the okay he's up here you
have to die right he's gonna shoot arrows that leaves I took a flame
barrel memo when we broke into Hirata state we found a barrel that spewed
flame must have been a shinobi's tool the boys lit of rowing bonfire with the
made merry with the drink must have been a tool they don't already have this
tool that he's speaking of okay where this buildings on fucking fire I didn't
even get any of these let me get these it's just ashes you need to come
down here for ash and a pellet all right so this should be another two
people this actually is probably easier because it's really just a couple
guys here I don't I think I could that is anybody behind me still you just
shoot that in the air no that's a nice firework but when is it gonna stop you
can stop now you can stop now you can stop now all right I'm ready let's go
what do I want here maybe sparking I don't know if this does all right
bring them out here wait wait a second wait a minute wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait yes I thought that was gonna be a dive fucked
after slow movements man it kills me you guys know it's so fast the slower
you are the hardest me to fucking beat you just is case you me that the
fire is fucking me up so erratic oh my god you spend so much time just
getting used to fucking I'm still a lot you know a lot instant kill moves are
never fun it just aren't they never are Lord this whole thing I can't really
go you should be burning right now it hurts me it should hurt you the laws
of physics I can't see if he's like a camouflage oh fuck off you need to
tone it down you're at an eight do you see why I'm surprised I'm not fucking
at it 11 don't I can't go on that I'll just apply this fat drunk asshole
I'm gonna dodge around when he does that well never mind he's gonna 180
degree turn into me forgot to parry all of these still got more shit for
me to do with my posture I'm stuck you know I don't know what I'm
oh good thing I just used it come on no oh god damn it man get out of my
life god fucking save me I need one more prayer
beating and I got better just keep going over here I'm out of here wait I
didn't clear this before I might as well take a look and see if there's
anything else here all the amount of energy that I just like expelled for my
body over the course of the last hour or two where's the other where there's
an ogre there's an ogre I remember and there's another bead there and
then I'm gonna attempt the demon guy I can't guarantee that's gonna
happen tonight okay there's a guy there we'll have to come back and do
it tomorrow I write forgot these guys wait for the jump up somebody to
one is it just one guy trying to fight them is it just this one guy that's
attacking me I think so no no I'm with X didn't break is that
secure but every time you die you have to solve a pick Ross puzzle pick
Ross was amazing yeah man like think it out different those games so easy
easy now need not a healing it'll force you to stay calm it's so easy
just to go absolutely fucking mental play in this game it just is it's that
just the way it is you have to accept it now what is that is this I thought I
could reach it it looks like I can reach this is just taking me back to
I don't think I can reach it from here
that's just the fire $2,000 where did I get two grand from what what what
am I supposed to do this I gotta spend this money somewhere I don't think I can
buy any more no I'm gonna have to go to the other guy that sells this shit
right what about upgrades all right I need one more of those salt things and
I can get the purple fume spark the thing I want shit I have to go buy
sacks where this guy at the this guy has sacks right you got sacks you got
oh you you the exact person I'm glad to talk to I mean what am I gonna do with
this 300 bucks confetti just to have it so I can not lose the money all
right what's the next oh the ogre right what's the quickest way to get
to the ogre I would just go back around see like that I could go all the
way around this way and skip this whole thing no no no no go back go
go to the snake but I can't the snake just blew me off the mountain last time
like I need a second wind how do I get a second wind I need a second wind right
now any second wind my sails I need to put my sails back up how it is one do
that smoke crack I don't think I'm gonna do that eat an entire can of
spinach one pick Ross puzzles oh I can't I don't think my brain will work
okay where's the snake I don't can I make that job yeah I did it already into
the snake cave this way guys no the snake cave is the snake cave is like
its own thing isn't it isn't the snake cave like down here it's like one of
these right Sunken Valley of gun fort it's one of these I think I think it's
gun for it it's the ecto cooler level cuz then from here go backwards
there is like a little cave Sunken Valley passage and then in I don't know
in there
I got rice I got rice um should I give her rice I have this I have been holding
on for a long time the monkey the monkey that was down oh the monkey
that was dancing around the monkey that's scared all right so how do I do
that monkey dance I think I have an idea oh the game's like a six out of
ten because of the voices wow remember that this guy here we go so make the
month wait there's a guy here too buy shit from you I thought I was under
the impression guys that I was in a pause menu no I can't believe it's
fucking monkey just make the monkey dance
anyways it was nice talking to you do you have anything you got okay I'm
gonna cure the dragon rot you have coin purses here all right make the
monkey dance so if I go into here puppetry I'm going to assume that it'll
just move around and then I get a free snake I forgot that you guys existed make
the monkey dance I remember this being this was terrifying when I first saw it
through the side and then there's a platform down here where is the bat
where's that platform where's the platform where's the platform where's
the platform it's up above me okay and then down here here we go big snake
monkey I can go this way right I can I I remember can I make this jump I
forgot if I could right okay did the same thing here we go all right make
the monkey dance make the monkey dance and is that a dance it actually is a
dance I did it I made it I made it now what do I do oh fuck I've never been
here before I've never been in here before can I kill it like this pick up
item dried serpent this sera a dried permission like heart of the great
serpent the great serpent is a god of the land and the heart is believed to
be where's one spirit resides well it looks much like a persimmon in fact
this is the red viscera of a god apparently denizens of Sunken Valley
worship the organs believing they represent the deity itself who cares how
do I get out of here I got like a shriveled up avocado for my trouble I
guess I just have to bone out of here I'm sure you're in the exact spot
Betty nice this leads here what's this same shit was some dumb shit fine dumb
shit I this is how you get the item that's over here right remember I was
talking about I couldn't get up there no that's not even true that's
unfortunate okay so I have this heart yeah I thought that was gonna put me
over here for some reason all right well I really don't know what to do
with this there's no way for me to get up there it has to be something I
can do there's nothing go this way that's like let me see I'm never I'm
not coming back to this area ever again I might as well take a look right am I
crazy or did I just see a thing to grab from this tree can I jump from the
tree and then up which I I need I'm gonna take the binoculars up for the
first time what did you not swing for why did I not
just like stood there like an idiot binoculars are you gonna shoot at me
from here are you yeah of course you are hidden point fucking accuracy
all right let me just I want to take a look even the stupid thing first I'm
ever using it so it looks like a cave back there I think it's a cave okay I'm
here poison pool ape the sculptors idol is unavailable till it's commune with
again why backwards from poison pool wait a minute no no it's not no if
you dip okay why are you in here it's just another one of these guys
how much confetti do I have I'm not sure I have enough I got plenty well I'm
gonna try let's kill them I kind of want full health though maybe
plus it was a large ape you're a liar I know but I really have wide string
of dialogue I can't all this I wish I could say he's sorcerer okay wait is
there is this closer not like it matters confetti where you got this looks good
bingo let's go fight this guy sure terms only good at the game because
he smokes a crack okay that is a lot more build up well I didn't need to
dash through it again again again again again again
confetti what oh fuck you disappeared again fuck I gotta kill him now he's
gonna die now oh fuck you in that hitbox eat my fucking balls sorry I
would I would I would I would can I get a big execution an old ring well
suited for slender fingers sure is engraved on the underside can be used
to upgrade the finger whistle prosthetic I don't need any of this
wearing this ring as you blow the finger whistle will create a somber too
and the weeping voice is full of solitude and beauty quell a voice of
rage I don't use the finger whistle though rage though wait sorry that
board was very loud oh yeah quells rage huh I made a world of warcraft
reference three hours ago and I'm gonna make it again it is a world of
warcraft boss you all laughed and said oh wow reference I have to trank shot
this boss that's the way to beat it I'm gonna do this too god I can't handle
these rage streamers I'm gonna leave what I what did I what did I rage when
did I rage today I didn't do that when a lot no I didn't was the guy
that wants the flower I did not rage at all I got a slightly slightly
irritated only link to clip let's see he's so awkward I hate this fucking
game I hate this fucking series I hate everything about this game I've given
it a five out of ten no pull it back see I pulled it back that's doesn't
count I pulled it back I immediately pulled it back I immediately what's
this one here again fuck I just did this I gotta kill him now he's gonna die
fucks eat my fucking balls he's a fuck hold on what's this what what's wrong
what's wrong with the audio god damn circle oh fuck you don't come around
here this is a curse
why oh I accidentally clicked I clicked it twice very fast I like click
that's why this game is fucked this game fucked telling you is this the
right way he was like up the mountain right oops no fuck man wait listen look
what I didn't even mean to do that and it's gonna get me a no it's not
no I had it there was a secret item over there and I just accidentally
fucked it up hold on a second here where was that wait fuck I can make
this I think how am I supposed how do I do that I'm doing something slightly
wrong maybe the angle oh I thought just it just popped up I just had the pop
up I got the indicator do you see that what why why was it that had a no
smoking sign on it why fuck I the indicator was there you saw it right
I'm not crazy got it okay wait what is this well I have to be something
cool prayer beads prayer beads I know it come on no it's alright that's
still cool that's still cool I can keep going that way too hey 500 bucks is 500
bucks still going cave nope I'm not losing my fucking mind what that was
the biggest mistake you've ever made okay I can Mario jump up here cool
all right what oh a small pinwheel made of white paper found below a
clipped in Malkongo perhaps it was carried by the wind it's simply a
single pure white pinwheel only the child is right here so I have two of
these now okay what do I do with this that's kind of cool all right now
we're dual well the pinwheels I almost have five skill points which
unlocks that super move probably items up here too I didn't get when I was
in my panic I feel like I've been panicking through the whole game
anybody else feel like that when they play this feel like every single thing
is panicking every single opportunity what is this monkey booze more money
good I open this door I guess I can unlock this monkey crack oh dear
you're actually really not that big of a deal I got a little scared for no
reason I found it I found it that's what they're talking about the whole game I
found it there it is this the thing that I can walk through I can go
through that door that's the painted door thing I can go through there
remember he was talking about it go through the door that has the thing on
it Shinobi escape route leads to demon
Bell I don't I feel like I don't want to I didn't even see it was up
here all right deep I got a guy didn't get this what the hell does this do
this is very ominous read do not ring this Bell inviting misfortune is an
act of virtue but only the stoutest of heart should ever consider it don't
ring the Bell do not ring this Bell what is it is it a boss this I'm
gonna spawn something sinister burden what the fuck is this a demonic
spirit sealed within the iron Bell of simple temple possesses those who ring
the Bell strengthening enemies around them the Bell demon confers hardship
but perhaps also slightly better spoils using this item is no particular effect
the second causing the demon to leave wait this is this is this everything's
just harder what wait a minute strengthening enemies around them gives
so you make the game harder but there's a hard mode for secure holy
shit why would you ever want to have this on how would you want to make this
game harder now that's like that's smoke and crack all right let's go I was
gonna see the door let's see how much harder this guy is in here I didn't
okay maybe more money how do you like hardwood um it's pretty hard I'm
scared to do what I'm doing right now okay well that's cool is there anything
else down here besides least favorite enemy in the entire series what else is
in here got anything else for me or is it just fight this guy in here now
at least this is a bigger area well I've got the means to attempt this I've got
the means necessary bring it on face your fears let's go
I forgot I'm on his moves
all right so I have the bell on stupid fucking bell I'm gonna beat this
motherfucker with the bell on okay are you ready for me to face my fears
completely it's stupid demon belt it's time here we go behind me what do you
got oh shit let's go face my fucking fears come on man one more
I got no more confetti I don't even know what dimension I'm currently in I'm
panicking so much okay he fucking went down under the ground through the wall
and hit me I'm gonna start to panic okay that seems like something I could
not what am I supposed to do red sugar I'm what's wrong with me guys I have to
be perfect
please please don't even get out of here with that shit come on no
please I ain't gonna hear that right now I can hear that stupid enemies I
can't believe it I I want to see that when he teleported through the wall that
was such I wanted that was offensive that was offensive to me it was
offending me I am offended
the one thing that's so much trouble with this and they put him
everywhere just to make me angry they did that to do that that me smiley
face whatever the fucking meme is where's the guy with the pinwheel where
is he he's like out here somewhere right I use so many materials to guys
I have I'm getting a zit on my face from this fucking stress it's huge
I have a huge pimple on my face wow yeah it's brewing wow I haven't had
like a pimple like that and let's see how bad I look on camera you want to
see what this game is doing to me right there oh look at me I'm fucking
like a shade of red right now now I'll fuck I'm wearing the same shirt from
yesterday I'm wearing the same shirt it wasn't even dirty it was
clean it was brand new out of the drive I'm fucking crazy right now
all right so I got another other streamer question I know I'm like
super like super into asking about how other people played this game am I the
only one that's caught that's been that in has gone insane are there any
other insane people I'm curious definitely I'm the only one that's
insane pure white flour I have it give red give white should I give the
white first I feel like if I give the red one he's gonna get angry I
wonder if I can do anything else with this
is this the pure white flower he sounds like me sure thing Patrick yeah
no spirit people away make them disappear as if they were never there
why do you want that I'm sure that everyone will be disappeared and then
I'll get to see them I'm in charge of looking after the children can do
that I have to kill him but does he give me something you can do that do
I have to know I get if I you okay guys you want me to use the tool the tool
that pushes people away I will push him off the cliff and he'll die if I do
that like wind move he's going to fall off the cliff and hit his head on a
rock and die you tell me I just want to make sure you're aware this you
tell me that the divine is a mild sort of being spirited away that can
be returned from quite quickly how do I I do what am I get for this you don't
leave anything here I just that's it nothing you get the satisfaction of a
job well done I gotta eat shinobi's gotta eat you know go to where he
landed fuck he landed he's in the monkey world I didn't make that joke
okay see Tommy's in here there he is what do you know
he's gone he's gone
painted item weird shit taro from simian greatly increases posture recovery for a
time even when attacking or taking damage to only get to eat that once I
think it to eat this one time
he goes even deeper into the fucking inception dream where are the monkeys I
want to see my monkey friends that I oh yeah they're dead I slaughtered them
sorry sometimes I forget okay I still am I need one more prayer beat oh it's
this person too you got any more info for me you got rice right
divine air you are welcome here shinobi of the divine air this time the rice
grew well now hold out your head please bless us with bountiful harvest right
I thank you rice is very precious please come again should you want for
more farewell shinobi of the divine air
the harvest securo is fine that's a mouthful sorry I did that like two
days ago and I had to make sure I did it again to make everybody happy in the
chat all right loose end tied up okay rice where's the rice lady she's hanging
out I remember freaking out because I was getting attacked by people that
were in the house and she's sitting on the edge and I was trying to talk
to her temple grounds thing I don't remember I remember freaking out
though what does this put me okay let's see where am I yeah all right yeah I
think it's this way guys he's not fucking around okay busy
I was busy insta-killing people well that's cool didn't get it yeah there
were items over there though that I didn't get but I was panicking last
time let me just take a look holy shit there's so many monks here I have
to get the job on it but I'm gonna just do it okay watch this oh this is gonna
be fucking awesome you know I mean like only on German on a five I mean if
you're a new viewer something like this you'll only find on German on a
five consider a follow oh consider it just consider it how much of a
narcissist do you have to be I'm just kidding around you can unfollow you
can follow you could stop you could unsub you dance if you want to you
kidding you think I really mean that you don't know me very well you don't
even know me if you think that's real that was pretty awesome though now I
remember it's right oh goodbye hey those are my friends I don't care about
flowers like my brother does I didn't really explore this bugs out of here
there's an NPC it's just fucking puked on me oh take him out for good nice okay
I thought I was gonna be much more substantial all right cool now here's
this lady got rice what are you gonna tell me
of the serpent there are two kinds
is fresh
over the cliff
what are you talking about
I sure if something troubles your mind
there you go
sorry but this streamer isn't for me
mind the puppet fly a kite ladies speaking of riddles so I have to make
somebody if it's fresh fruit you want fly a kite why I have to make
somebody I have to make somebody do the thing that soft-locked my game the
question is where the fuck was that kite I remember it I remember I couldn't
escape it I could it was soft locking the game I feel like it's close if I
feel like it's down a little maybe not hey guys
you don't see me pushed off the edge you are so just right here
because I've been attacking you just swinging around okay now he's like
rather start talking who's waiting for you to talk relentless oh shit there's
a fucking other guy here what the heck are you doing I don't know where
they came from sugar out of bullets well that was fun see you're on antidote
powder okay I got antidote powder I need to get the fuck out of here
what was this last guy I mean if I'm gonna really he's I'm drawing out the
end of the game I I told I told you guys this before I even started
playing this game now I'm gonna I want to play I want to see all the shit
there is to see I just want to go to the end as fast as I can just to get to
the end so I don't think this is correct let me go to the beginning I
like exploring too yeah plus I want to make sure I'm prepared especially with
a game that's like this this game is hard as shit and I want to make sure
I'm ready that demon boss it was enough for me to be like oh I want
to be ready for this oh I think it's down here where's that kite there it is
okay all right do I have it equipped I do this this is the guy a puppet this
guy now now how do I get on here so that I can jump to that so I gotta go
up there okay so it's over there this way I gotta get up with that way
and then on the other side of the building okay where the fuck am I at now
found an item heavy coin purse all right now where's that kite all the way
around keep going keep going keep going watch out
watch out bugs hey get out of the way bugs bugs get out of the way but I
but eggs get out of the way you fucking bugs all right now what fly a
kite line the puppet fly kite oh shit all right what okay I made it I did
it now what across fuck it here we go it's just snap seeds an illusion of this
that's the fresh fruit snap seeds it is technically like vegetables or something
oh we're not gonna go down there die if I go down here Jesus crap is the
cave oh there's another idol down here this is cool I like this little
adventure to go on all right so if it's a snake is that a snake down
there shit Sunken Valley passage why wouldn't I walk the plank oh guys do I
jump down and kill the snake no way no way is it it's not gonna do the thing
that I said was gonna happen right if it does I'll be fucking so happy oh my
god fresh serpent that was insane the great serpent is considered to be a
god of the land and the heart is believed to be where one spirit resides
well it shape their similarity to a person miss I can't say that fucking
word a persimmon in fact this is the red viscera of a god of the safety
assume that eating it would be poisonous to one's health that was
awesome I'm covered in blood so I have two hearts I have two snake
hearts what do I do with this now look at this little area this like
little items back here is beautiful there's a dragon's blood and another one
of these all right I need to look at those where is it fresh serpent dried
serpent it is safe to assume that eating that would be poisonous denizens
of the Sunken Valley worship the organs believing they represent the
deity itself so do we eat like the dried jalapeno and then like the fresh
jalapeno I don't know how this works I have to put them somewhere do I
give them to somebody like this is a California Reaper well oops okay
what is down here this one's like green no it's not thousand dollars I got a
lot of money now don't really know where I am though a lot of free items
down here scale
trigger
I think I've got a view nice okay um I've been down here right all right
yeah this is like the poison area all right I'm I need to kind of delaying the
inevitable I do want one more prayer bead before I fight that boss and I
there's a god of this one more mini boss that I think I missed I'm trying
to remember there was that I got the drunk guy inside maybe in here no I'm
not fighting the headless she in a castle let's go this way I've not gone
over here yet since the whatever happened it was like change world
changed really just sitting here waiting for me why how would you know
I was here I'm slowing down boys and girls yeah I'm slowing down I can
feel it the second wind no I didn't want to do that one to hit me as a rare
fuck yeah I think this I'm slowing down I'm getting to that point where I
might be I got to take a break and that means it's the end of the
stream but it's I want to keep playing though but my goddamn gamer
fatigue is settling in hard he just pretty much said the line if you
go to check smoke some crack for a gamer boost well you guys are gonna
be on this for a while huh this is down to the monkey area no I'm gonna
go back this way huh gamer fatigue is set and when I'm fighting enemies don't
exist I haven't looked in here tons of shit on the ground what the fuck is
happening it's here is it is there it's her headless water they're just
everywhere the fuck Jesus anything else what's this all right get this monster
away from me get out of here these guys are just sitting in here all game
where is he oh god this stupid fish is here too
no stop diving out of the water just get everything he's gonna he only has
one bar I hope that was a terrible place to drink and I know it goes
keep doing the wave your hair move grab that's the easiest thing to
dodge
greedy okay that was so much easier than the other ones no fog wall with no
dodging consume okay this is just another one of these reduces vitality
damage taken from physical attacks consume spirit of those to use
repeatedly so these are just candies that I can use whenever I want but
that's not really what I'm looking for I wanted beads I've killed like
okay since the demon I've killed like four or five mini bosses and I'm only
got one beat nothing else down here did I beat the red demon no I stopped
fighting against the red demon and I started doing other content to take a
break from it I was hopefully going to get some more stats but doesn't
seem like that's the case at the moment I got you got the jump on you
yet the elbow drop all right opportunity comes knocking no I couldn't get a
stealth been a while since I fought you what the hell you got like grabs and
shit right I remember this guy you don't pair you just kind of dance
around it goes over these grabs take the item that's not good he lost the
lock on there all right so far so good do something do something do something
do something do something do something fine I will still going I'm still flying
I'm still going what am I gonna end up here swimming and he's dead he
speared me through the mouth I went through it he just like that was
fucking bullshit I had that going to just fine all right well now that's
kind of the nail in the coffin for me I think no it's not let me kill that
guy I thought I could sneak up on finish the game today I don't know
that's gonna be tricky man so I don't think that's possible
crack here boom boom well it does have a little funky of a hitbox and I remember
Wow that was damn too funky with it just kill him I'm trying to be too
fancy with it like just fucking it's a tiny room and I'm it's but just
kill him man Wow just spun around in midair all right part two we do it
again yeah I want to get stuck on shit whoa we didn't get affected by that one
it's already there fair be let's go for a beat yes yes oh that's medicine
rank three increases the healing effect of recovery items that's huge
all right awesome their chest in here did I get this already I'm gonna pee
my pants I really might like pee I gotta go to the bathroom I was
there today this is where I came from I don't have to go up and I go up from
here I thought I could something going on out here this is the front door is
there a boss out here any boss maybe we're just a fight right that's too
many fight all that shit no chance I will go in here though I don't have
time to listen to you talk I gotta activate this I can't believe you
that's me
mud ball which is this the mud wall I already did this that looks like a boss
it's not oh that guy sucks he was so cool looking to you can't fight the
continuous hold down fucking wm1 pyro see he's still going he's still
holding down the button you didn't even realize he killed that guy well I'm
just gonna get the money I'm gonna pee and then we're gonna do we're gonna
what do I want to do here how much okay I know that this do I do don't
do times to do it a stream tomorrow the stream just do it again we'll go
three days in a row let's do it no time that's fine like this is this
is secure I will okay I'm gonna go pee I'm gonna come back I'm gonna
attempt the demon a couple of times I'll give him a good solid few tries
and then I'm gonna turn I'm gonna call tonight we'll be live tomorrow and we're
gonna go keep going oh that's too many oh fuck this is all right okay hold
on I could I can't do that can I well I'm not even gonna get a chance
to see all right let me go pee I'm gonna try the demon boss again I'm
just kind of feudal behavior what I'm doing right now I'm right back
gonna pee and we'll fight the demon again we'll try I had to get a glass of
water too all right I'm ready to give it a couple solid tries so let's just go
let me change this one three of these although what about some of these
things this is now this is stealth this is vitality damage I might be
worth using these if they take spirits but all my tools are although
what my finger whistle didn't I get something I got like a new thing for
the didn't I get a finger whistle upgrade or something what was it wasn't
it like oh do this to a beast and always a ring okay is it one of those
scenarios where I have to upgrade it let's do this first that's a lot more
health and vitality okay great this is five not available why oh I need
this to let me go let me go to look at the upgrade screen how am I doing I'm
doing good hope you're doing good how are you yeah okay so you actually have
to upgrade it through the tree shit I mean I can get it I can actually get
this it's gonna cost some money buy three of these thousand bucks and
then I can do it can be used to drive beasts mad into torment apparition type
enemies I wonder how much that is for materials though if that's but that
doesn't seem like that much I can still do this I'm gonna go for it so
it's six hundred sixteen hundred twenty seven three that's a lot of
money do I have that money what do I have for money right now two thousand
I got the money hmm I got the money let's do it how much do I need exactly I
need 18 let's see let's do the actual math here so I need this and then
this what does this do so this actually I could have used this an hour ago so
I need to buy three gunpowders which you should have them over here
protects from terror that would have been great
no not a state don't go anywhere I need you here to sell me things so it was I
know it's iron so I needed three of these please notice me hey how are you
so that's three 450 I think I should still have enough money panic okay I
need another 200 bucks you're killing me here you're killing me whatever I
need to do this anyways we go now I need $1,200
twelve hundred so that's a thousand five ten fifteen I'm just gonna have to sell
some shit because I can do no I don't need to it's gonna ease into the pack
whatever else I'll buy something else too here it is I hope this is worth it
drive beast mad into torment apparition type enemies I hope this
horse doing this is a lot of money and there's a lot of resources it's
done malcontent mal-cun-tent so if it was worth it I wonder how it works
and how much I got some money let's go back here I'm gonna buy I'm just gonna
buy like I'm gonna buy one of these just in case for some reason this guy
goes away what else do I have antidote powder five I got plenty
antidote pacify let's get another one of these in fact I think yeah I'm you
know just because I'm just gonna do it I you might think I'm fucking
you mean you think he's crazy but I I want like more of these I know I have
the potion but I still I think they're so useful now it's time for an attempt
let me look at the upgrade screen one more time I want this I can do this I
just need 1,500 and I need one more of those salt packets it's my
favorite item in the game over here is this is the fire attack one but I can't
even get this even if I wanted to I'm apparently missing a prosthetic tool
which I would have to go one two three four five and then it unlocks
this so I can't get this we're gonna have to go for it with what I got I
don't have that tool I don't know what it is I don't know where it is
let's see what I like I'm gonna scream it's not gonna be that much longer I'm
just gonna try we'll go again tomorrow try to clean it up finish it all up so
it was what was it flames of hatred let's see I'm I there was a list was
a lot of money I want to see what this does demon of hatred what does it
do pretty useful pretty useful how often can I do that I wonder if it's
gonna cool down what's the how far away I can do from pretty far away and it's
alright it's not bad can I do it again immediately can okay so just want to
see what did wasting spirit emblems I got plenty of spirit I've been
collecting them the whole game haven't I all right here we go let's go
oh thanks unseen aid then go oh it's just random shit here guys we're just going through some weird shit
thought I blocked it ah shit a little rusty a little rusty
going uphill though I don't like this
just gonna back it up, back it up, throw him, touch out, it's a cocky pun
that was close man god damn it fucking hell come on it's that one move that
sucks it just does that move sucks that's an undeniably fucking shit
should have waited
you got next level man on phase two he doesn't throw the balls anymore he
does that weird I don't know how to get the first two I got to get the first
phase down a long way to go like it's like that move is it just lingers for
the hitbox lingers for so long even when he's even if you dodge it so if
you dodge it even with i-frames for like a tenth of a second two tenths
of a second after it hits you it's almost like you should maybe even just run to
his right I don't think that movie I don't think you can dodge parry I don't
think you have to just get away from that move it's so hard to determine
what's gonna happen because it takes a not even a second to do it he's
just like yeah so you can be just you brain decides in a second and you
have to dodge it just because it happens so quickly there it is again
see what I mean it's just so quickly it's hard to react to and that was
with the fire resistance fuck I don't like it there it is all right no he
doesn't both ways I don't know man you gotta run left it I can you know I feel
like I don't I'm not sure I can the jump it might be a jump over that there
might be dead I just barely got to heal up
unforgiving I can't I can't stop for a second fucker there it is again the
unfucking bearable move that is one of the only things I take damage to I'm
thinking I dodged backwards I'm gonna try dodging back to see if doesn't
it I guess you can jump in the grab I wanted to do the moves I can just try
to dodge backwards
I'm gonna try to parry it let's see what happens let's see if I can trigger him
to do it do it
waiting for him to do it Barry all right can't all right it's I can do
it all I can walk it all but in like game time scenario though that I guess
that's better than me dodging and fucking dying I feel like game time
scenario it's he does it so fast I should practice it right
I really want to crack at that it's worth it but man the timings are so odd
it's like here punch
that's just such odd timing okay how did I not get hit by that
the ultimate ultra hitbox got me that other time
this guy's rough I wonder I wonder what my official orphan of cost was the
hardest boss if ever played in a video game I wonder how many attempts
I wonder how many it's gonna take for this I remember when I I remember me and
star could not be orphaned together we tried dozens of times to be orphan
I finally did it by myself and it was like holy shit it's the
hardest thing but I'm starting to get that vibe of this might be that from
this game this guy's just so it's so easy to die he's got so many
interesting moves he's got three full ball bubbles this dude is no joke
and I definitely probably beat orphan by this without a doubt because this
has to be upwards of like 20 to 30 attempts on this guy right
three or just four swings there
mainly just use this practice down to try to block those four times it's a
sponginess that makes him this heart yeah he's got a dickload of health I
can do this three times I've also seen people say hey just get get the
flame I don't have it and like I have to go get an item that I don't
what I have with my I didn't get that item so I got a fight of the way that I
know how also I mean I got I'm gonna have to come back stronger this is this
is one of the hardest bosses in the game and I'm like eight hours what
seven hours eight hours playing the whole day I gotta come back fresh
because at some point you know you get used to get sloppy and this this
dude optional probably top three bosses in the game has to be top all right
I'll tell you I've how many bosses are after this guy they can't be more than
like it I'm almost I have to be at the end of the game I have to be nobody
gave me this much trouble I think I'm gonna I'm it's gonna be tricky for me
to do this now haven't even fought any of the bosses they're all still
alive practice it kind of all right
a little bit there and also maybe don't even be afraid to now the chip damn
just too much bye last one sucks ha ha ha fucking drive me crazy the issue
with this boss is that it's a Dark Souls boss in a game with a shitty
role yeah yeah that's true but technically can
parry everything that he does so it is like a Dark Souls I'm the like
cleric beast boss but it can be beaten by the tools they give you it's just
really hard to get yourself in that brain especially considering the
obvious that you want to fight this guy like Dark Souls boss that time I
still taking damage though so I took a lot of damage doing that I guess
it's better than dying all right I'll do I'll try now this this would be it
I gotta come back strong tomorrow I'm just tired tired seeing the same
animations over and over again at some point you got to just fucking close it
rage no I did not do I sound upset right now no I'm just fucking just I'm
getting rushed oh fucking didn't want to do that I just accidentally did
that no too much for right now I've already I've gone through so much of
the game the hardest boss in the game can wait till tomorrow watch me
watch this I'll beat the last boss in fucking like three or four tries watch
me last one oh god I'm so sloppy right now
save the bell bell hasn't been enabled about now I have whoa starting with
this try the other way go on the wall
it sucks if you get hit by that you just fucked no right side then he
misses you with the first swing then he'll get you with the boy
really learn how to ride a goddamn bike
surprise I didn't get that fuck that was bad time to do that oh he just has
so much help so fucking hell you're gonna do this three fucking times you
gotta do this shit three times I feel like I'm stabbing him with a fucking
like a little pin is it no matter what this is the last one it has to be I'm
exhausted right now didn't walk it I tried that too
head that how many headbutts that's the first time I've ever seen him do
more than one headbutt fuck I can't see man fuck you I can't even see the
fucking guy looking free and the fire the camera up his ass
something just said who is this game even for who is this game me oh my god
that is made my mood just increased by like 50% thank you thank you guys
you made me feel much better that's so like coming in here and like just being
like seeing this shit seeing a guy die over and over and over again at the
same thing spending like hours of time what is this for I can't jump over
that why what that's fucking dog shit I can't jump over it that was my
strategy the whole time doing that do you see that shit it's just dusty you
have to just know this thing I don't understand that move I really
don't get it call me a fucking dope if you want the fuck man I tried jumping
I tried running I tried dodging I he has the thing on his head but I'm not
close enough that's it that's it I gotta tell I gotta get out of here
it's too much for me right now this guy sucks play fortnighter real quick now
I've been going for like eight hours of this game straight playing eight hours
straight as a hero is the equivalent of playing like pick Ross for two
weeks without turning it off and only eating three times there's like
playing minecraft on times five speed for three days straight but that's the
nature of the game gonna fuck I'm gonna be I'm gonna beat him eventually who is
this game for it's so funny it is so much to that comment but that's uh we'll
get what we did we defeated tonight we'll come back tomorrow stronger as
that's an obi-wan Kenobi said and then Darth Vader fucking lopped his
head off and he became a funny ghost for like three or four more episodes
so don't really use that as a good barometer have a great night guys I'll
see you tomorrow we're gonna try to get through this tomorrow tomorrow would
it's probably gonna be the last secure I'll stream and I say that now but I
better be careful because if I we might sit here for four I got a I'm
gonna like do fucking meditation before tomorrow's dream I have like
another two or three encounters I think that are left from where I how
many bonfires I have eight hours of one boss tomorrow it's very possible
we'll see what happens but take care of yourselves get some sleep I'm gonna get
some sleep now see you tomorrow and let's get through the bits shouldn't
take us too long there was a ton of community subs today 24 hours the
Kira stream I don't think I'd be able to handle that
let me get this on the right screen here now see tomorrow probably on the
same time around like 3 to 3 30 between 3 and 4 you know you know the
good night and those of you sticking around Casey had 250 here just shouting
out a cat is fine for gifting me a sub there were a shitload of them and
speaking of subs are thank you jibber 7 for the five community subs right at
the end they were I get probably somewhere around a hundred or so plus
community subs today Casey got one out of the many that were gifted thank
you Casey for the 250 somebody yeah KD KD every five minutes was giving
five to ten they gave a shitload uh thank you KD K banana bread the second
thanks for the $20 way earlier hey German my mom said it's my turn on the
Xbox you have homework it's my turn on the PS Vita mom said you have homework
I don't have homework but you know my homework is to prepare for a demon
hatred Lord thing but thank you banana the bread for the $25 here he
says I have the high ground high ground doesn't help you in these games Jess you
got it thanks for the 250 Jess why do we only hear the rumors on your stream
and not on italics is cuz I don't have a like a gate I don't have like a
limiter I just you hear raw audio over here exposed yeah I don't have a
like a compressor or like a gate I want you guys to hear me like fucking
breathing you and you wouldn't hear like half the mouth noises I make when I
almost like I threw I threw up on this stream didn't I almost I forgot about
that that was a while ago but I almost puked who is this game for I almost
threw up playing that's my favorite comment of the year thank you though
Jess you got it smelly boy thanks of the 250 do you ever have moments
where you'll be alone remember something really embarrassing that you
did in the past and just want to scream it scream to yourself yeah I do it
happened today when I died to the headless guy like six times last night
too every day thank you smelly boy also smelly boy 250 also eat a big
bowl of spaghetti on stream laughing my ass off I'm not gonna do that
thank you so spread over the three bucks Jeremy you sound way more
enthusiastic than you have in a while I'm glad you're having fun we the
chat are as well any who please accept these freshly farmed adverts it well
it's a from software game it's like Dark Souls I'm just I get really into
it I get super into these games as you can see he was buzzing on caffeine
that was me what's this
it's true this is for all right I'm gonna get back in a fit here if I
don't stop I was so defeated I wasn't even that angry I was kind of just
defeated it ups upset not even angry I was just defeated and hearing that I
just brought me back to life that's great I love it
Zorro Carlos thanks of the 250 Jeremy you've looked at a hat in time I hope
you aren't just because the ukulele stream from a couple of years back was
a mess to keep up the wonderful streams wait what oh I thought you
said I hope you aren't because the ukulele stream was a mess no no you
said I hope you aren't like the I ukulele I didn't like and so it turned
me off from all the other ones no I had in time it's kind of just been on
the list forever and it's kind of like if there's a gaming apocalypse it
would be that would be one of the games that would you know repopulate
the earth with you know I mean on like I would stream that game if you
kind of if you understand even remotely what I mean by that but it's
a great game looks really fun looks really interesting does not in the
cards unless I really really need something something else to play and
there's been lots of stuff to do recently so there's always kind of
something every week but thank you Zorro Carlos hopefully that answers your
question in honor this is from our store H2O thanks for the 250 in honor
of tomorrow being opening day I want to share a highlight really made of
your most iconic baseball moments of 2018 I think we've watched this
before but I need to watch it again
let's get a couple of doubles last night he's hit in 10 straight and it's
a right back I love this video so much the Tomahawk swing is what does it it's
perfect thank you for that here you go if you want to link look at me I didn't
think I was gonna catch it I don't even know how you guys come up with
this shit you just do it's great thank you Al store we had a sea of dozens
and dozens and dozens and dozens of community subs thank you guys thank
you there's so many people you guys are fucking amazing thank you for
continuing to support this channel pika banana thanks with ten bucks hey
I wanted to watch you finish secure Oh but I have to miss probably the whole
stream today well don't worry cuz I didn't finish it we'll probably
definitely catch the VOD later so wanted to pop in to show my
appreciation thank you pika I didn't finish it we probably have another
stream worth and if not then guess what after I beat secure Oh you know
let's say it's like a three to four hour late beat a bunch of bosses and
I'm exhausted and it's been like three hours and four hours I'm just
gonna play pick Ross we're gonna end the secure O stream by playing
like an hour or two a pick Ross and I'm gonna just like fucking slug in the
chair so depending on how long it takes tomorrow well it's not okay if I beat
the game in like an hour and a half I'm not just gonna turn off the
stream so we'll at least do something for a couple hours afterwards hey
Freudian weapon thanks to the 250 happy Wednesday
Jeremiah Hart I got to get out of here before I spoil any more of this
game for myself great stream so far lots of energy yeah I love this
game it's just it's just exhausting there's only so much of it I can
take before it's you know you got to come back fresh and I'll be just as
energetic tomorrow watch full night's sleep some food bingo I will be the
breath of air will be put into my lungs and yeah if you know if you
don't want to watch the streams because you don't want to see what's
going on then I totally understand I mean I would hate for somebody to be
excited about playing this game and then they click on the stream and they
see me fighting the demon of hatred and they're like well I know
that's in the game now so I get it I completely get it those of you
that have been watching through this whole thing I hope you're enjoying it
hope you having fun hope you think it's interesting can you blur out the
spoilers I'll try next time Garfield a Monday killer thanks to the 250 hey I'm
Garf I'm not so Garf and I'm the Garf Garfs welcome back to more of this
game I'm Garf and this is Garf and today we're playing secure oh shadows
die twice actually we lied we're watching German play it also there's
only one Garf sorry I lied to all of you you know but how do can I make
it yeah how can I can't make it in this town without a little Fibon maybe one
day chat can forgive me for my crimes against feline kind remember that time
when germ modded me he immediately revoked it I cried for weeks and if I
did that when did I mod you what did I when did I ever mod Garfield the
Monday killer did I I don't think I did that I had to have been three
years ago did I maybe I did what a monster give it back
hello fun zombie thanks to the 250 when you're older are you going to drive
around in an old Volvo wearing your dressing gown in a pine park in vacant
parking lots while eating Big Macs and laugh at Garfield comics probably yeah
whole of one zombie thanks for the 250 and he says I kept this for some
reason what I don't understand why look at that first like look at the
okay stop it at like three or four frames in I've got like a people's
eyebrow thing going here with the gets crazed face terrible thank you
whole of one's army I don't know why he kept that either thank you
schwarzer rid for the five dolls haha you're so awkward ha ha but that
wasn't an ad that wasn't a ha ha that was just an ha ha that wasn't the
emote one that was just ha ha but thank you Schwartz hey effect tater thanks
to the ten bucks effect tater hey chat did you know that you can get 2500 bits
for $25 until the 31st twitch ain't taking any cuts from it so if you use
bits hop on it that's pretty cool wish it was that good of a deal
always that is the one thing that I really don't like about bits one
thing it's just if you buy less than like 20 30 dollars of bits it's
like it you have to pay like a 20 30 percent premium for like anything less
than five bucks that just shouldn't be like that I really don't in my opinion
I don't believe that that should be like that it's actually you're paying
money to pay money you know you get you pay it's it's like a it's like
currency trading a dollar is like a dollar thirty it's weird then allow
PayPal I don't want to do PayPal PayPal's messy donations of messy I
see so many horror stories so many people and like tax purposes it's
really hard to it's just strange you see these people that stream they get like
a $500 donation and they transfer the money to their bank account well they
use it and then there's a chargeback and they have to come up with 500
bucks and they may have already spent it so it's just I don't really I
don't want to even deal with it and then the idea is well just wait like
90 days so you can use the money no I'd rather just not have to worry
about it but I do wish it was a little less I don't I wish it wasn't 30% or 20
was a 28% for a dollar Bitcoin I tried Ethereum we don't talk about that
anymore remember when I had an Ethereum link down there two people
used it you can even go on you can go on the blockchain if you have that
old address go on the blockchain and see like the two or three people one
person gave me like four dollars and one person gave me like a dollar it
was there for months and months nobody used it so I just got rid of it and then
obviously the cryptocurrency took a nosedive that's very sweet of them yeah
it was cool it was cool to see like oh look that came in through like the
Ethereum blockchain that's so cool hey smelly boy thanks to the 250 you
took a fight from a fair but challenging boss fight that you were
getting better at each time to try and fight a bullshit many boss that
you knew would get you tilted no you took a break from a fair but
challenging boss fight that you're getting better at to fight the bullshit
mini boss and I killed him yeah but I was I really prepared for it though
during that I got the two snake hearts which I don't know what the hell to
do with those but I still have them and that's interesting got to see
that content right I wouldn't have probably done that and bless I went
if I had just beat that boss like let's say I spent like two three
hours straight while I was still not succumbing to gamer fatigue I was
still doing that and I beat eventually and I did it I wouldn't have seen the
snake stuff I would have kept going to the final part of the game so I'm glad
I got to I got some more beads I got some more items I got to see more stuff
but yes that did happen you're right show wars are read thanks for the
five dollars by the way that's awkward for non boomers there's a lot of
boomers in this chat so I'm glad you spelled it out
hey errorless thanks for the 299 German earth thank you
anonymous cheer $10 anonymous cheer it's anonymous thank you for the $10
whoever you are anonymous cheer is your name well you are doing the thing that
you use it hey hey as they say on reddit.com username checks out thank
you peek a banana thanks for the five balls five dollars you all use
reddit everybody does all of you do it you were just on like our games
fucking ten minutes ago looking at the latest trailer and you're gonna like you
guys because some of you guys are gonna ha ha me on that it's reddit it's like
one of the most viewed sites on earth that's like saying I checked Facebook
before the stream and it's like yeah Facebook really haha haha that's how it
goes right but I it's okay whatever don't let it get to you don't let it
get to you but thank you peek a banana for the five dollars I'm so
glad I was able to catch the tail end of the stream after missing most of it
looking forward to watching you beat the final boss term heart me too I'm
looking forward to it but I'm I'm I might be dragging the secure of
streams out a little bit maybe there's this one at the end and I you know
that gamer depression you guys know I'm talking about when there's a new
great insanely difficult fun title like this only comes around once every
three four years and I can see the tunnel the light at the end of the
tunnels there and I know it's gonna end and it I just I don't want it to end I
know it's going to and then when it's done that's it and that was fun it was
fun because a game like this there's not very many reasons to play it more
than a couple times because there's no character progression right but there's
no character oh I'm gonna use this weapon this time and they do this
build there's the skills but you can get most of them anyways that I think there
might be a couple of optional things you can do maybe with a second
playthrough no multiplayer so no PvP no PvP builds no building a character
and playing through the game again it's not there so with this one in
particular there's the replay abilities not there that much so it's
kind of hard to attempt to do like a second or third even play for
anyways so that's the sad part about the end of security is it really is
just the end of playing securo so I'm taking my time with it you know all good
things have to come to an end yeah that's true but this one comes to an
end much quicker than like for instance let's say Dark Souls 3 eyes for I saw
myself even when we did Dark Souls 3 and I got to the end I knew I knew it
immediately I was gonna play through with a sorcerer I was gonna play
through with a strength weapon I was gonna try to do PvP like I had like
at least three or four more reasons to play through the whole I played through
the game like three or four five times I'm not getting that I'm not gonna do
that again here I might play through this one more time to see if I missed
anything but I you know what I'm saying you got a full VOD to look
forward to okay well thank you oh you missed you missed some strange
stuff tonight I got taken I got possessed by fucking gamer demon I got
taken over I went fucking nuts I was screaming and Chad and shit I mean I
don't know if you guys weren't here but Kibo if you weren't here I was
screaming at Chad I was making I was making all these horrible accusations I
was at a ten at a ten of anger we were fucking screaming at each other I
lost like fucking 22,000 followers tonight I kept saying unfollow me
unfollow me I said it like ten times in a row I started smashing my
fucking hands on my desk unfollow me somebody said like you suck at this boss
and I fucking banned him I started banning people every time somebody said
that I wasn't good at the game I would I banned them and I said unfollow me
fuck you it went off for like 45 straight minutes it's terrible I'm
embarrassed about this who is this streamer even for anyways let's put
the credits on we only have a couple more bits to go through this is the
most neurotic I've ever been let's listen to it this is when I started
banning people yeah let's watch this this is when I started going unfollow
me unfollow me ban ban ban unfollow me fuck you I was screaming it it was
bad I didn't even have the confetti look at my terror though why what is this move he's
doing I don't care I'll fucking go around the goddamn circle oh fuck he
still comes around here oh this sucked kill him hey Jerma's live
that was cackling it was right after that cable I was like fuck you the
fuck out of my chat relax Jerma relax shut up don't fucking tell me to
relax get the fuck out of here what are you a loser what are you a loser you're
a loser I banned like 1,500 people it was right after that happened I don't
know I'm surprised you didn't have that part in the clip you get
self-conscious hearing yourself now it's been too long it's been too many
years maybe originally it was kind of like yeah I don't really yeah nobody
likes the sound of their own voice when it's playback and recording
they've done studies on that shit but nah whatever at this point it's been
like eight years I did it's just kind of there anyway here come the credits
and we only have a few more there was a lot of subs tons of community subs
tonight thank you so much guys you guys are amazing
look fun 168 24 what kind of username is that whose name is that why is that
your username I can't even fucking comprehend that person's name there's
like two or three phone numbers in that name it's easy to remember no
it's not bots gifting subs to each other you guys fucking hilarious but
anyways thank you so much there was a ton of community subs look at these
names fly by and to end it Timmy Tim tan gives 250 hey what are you gonna
play up to secure I think you should play slime rancher gonna play monster
rancher 4 whenever secure Oh ends I will see the end monster rancher 4 is
the next game and if it sucks monster rancher 2 is on backup I'm
feeling that's gonna be a nice relaxing stream after all this madness at VR
Josh 250 thank you VR Josh few minutes ago I started my own secure Oh
playthrough and I'm kind of in awe at how well you've handled some of these
bosses on another note when's the next VR stream plan do you have a list
of games ready or you still looking for recommendations I have first of
all thank you secure oh is very very hard but as long as you can take
the pain you will push through eventually as long as you just relax you take a
break like for me right you guys just go you have to leave I can't just sit
there and fucking bash my head against the desk you got to come back you
got to leave and come back stronger take a break come back the next day
these are games that are not designed for you to beat in one sitting and
yes I know that there's people that play these games and they beat it in
like 45 minutes they're exceptionally talented video game players and they
are not even human with their reaction times and with their memorization but
that ain't me I don't claim to be that I do envy it sometimes because it's
remarkable what some of these guys are able to do but you got to take a
break here come back again those are real gamers yeah I know these it's
tough but okay it's like playing these from software games okay there's
gonna be like a Boy Scouts Sekiro badge I get I get to wear the Boy Scout
Sekiro badge when I get to the end right it's gonna be right next to you
ready here's I got like the whole thing here I got my flair Minecraft 4
Horseman in VR I got that one flame lurker first try that one's gold I
had that one embroidered beating Sekiro simply completing Sekiro that's
worth it doing the bonus round in point blank incredibly defied that's that
one's all that one's silver I wear these every day but for a moment these
these games are so popular within you know who's this game for right we
made that was funny and that that joke was was great or even if it wasn't a
joke when you eventually get to the end you do get to say I got to the
end and it was crazy it was fucking insanely difficult but I'm I did it I
made it they should have a t-shirt that you can buy only if you have a Steam
achievement that you completed the final encounter and it unlocks a t-shirt you
can buy that's like Sekiro got good right they would make so much money
think about the amount of people that would buy that shirt I got good and
it's like a cool design of Sekiro swinging his sword in a circle
do another hour of stream please no I'll be I'll be left tomorrow I'll be
like before you know it it's almost almost tomorrow anyways I got good at
Sekiro and all I got is this lousy t-shirt people would just put the
shirt on eBay it's not 1940 anymore grandpa everyone can make t-shirts
yeah but if it's officially licensed with an officially licensed tag from
software this game I'm looking forward to tomorrow kind of I'm also not
looking forward to tomorrow it's like this weird angel and devil scenario I
have to beat the demon I have to and I could see the wall I'm looking up as
high and I could climb it I got to get good and get the t-shirt I'll be ready
I'm gonna I'm good to go I'm gonna get a nice fucking caramel macchiato
from Starbucks they're gross don't order those and then I'm gonna return
that order and just get a fucking coffee we're gonna get up and we're
gonna go coming in fresh tomorrow and with that that's my time here but
thank you for those of you that have stuck through this playthrough I know
that a bunch of people probably don't want to see it they don't want to see
the end of the game or they don't want to see potentially somebody get the
rass kicked right so thank you for sticking through the whole thing I
look forward to seeing you tomorrow and the completion of the game take
care much love to you see you real soon