Pick that up today. What does it say on it? 700,000 games. I'll never have to play another game in my entire life. It's an award winner. See, look, it's got a red ribbon. It's an award winner. I'm not even sure there have been 700,000 games ever made. But yeah, that's a steal, in my opinion.
Some dude is selling this game for one cent. I mean, let's be real here. At what point do you just burn it? I bought this game for 10 bucks. So if you use the lowest valuation of this game, I paid for nearly 1000 copies. And I'm going to play every single game in the box. So I better get started. Because if I have one minute of time in each game, it would still take me about two years to play every game. So go pop some popcorn, go get yourself comfortable, because we might be here for a while.
Who cares? I'll show you how you play jewel mines. You click the three globs like this. I don't even know how to play Texas Hold'em. Especially considering like there's a Dungeons and Dragons 12 sided die here too. I don't understand. What is this for?
Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold
Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold.
Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold.
Don't boo me. I just beat the level in like less than 10 seconds. You're gonna boo me. I can't stop it
It's fucking breaking my computer. Oh
Come on, I need to be able to get down to my taskbar. Yeah, this is what I'm talking about. This is 3d graphics
Do it
Green light means go monster truck stunt rally going off this thing. Whatever this is
Go right through the middle
They biting
Not really. I know it might be the position of it. I might need to get a better spot to fit. Let's go get a better position
Good spot over here
Secret of the empires of the ancient world of Maya
Yeah, the secrets of ancient Maya and the staple guns
Yeah, make sure you find those scissors too and the crowbar. What are those handcuffs?
Just for good measure. We'll throw in an Eiffel Tower to you know, the thing that's in France
There's nothing to do with ancient Maya couldn't toss that in here. Why not?
Don't worry. I got it. I'm just gonna straighten it out. I'm just gonna straight out. It's gonna go like another 200 miles
I'll just trade it
Here we go big head tennis. This is what you came for. Ladies and gentlemen
Spike it. Yeah, that's nice. Nice job. Excellent work
Yeah, just swing backwards
We're gonna go get they're gonna pick up the cavemen and to live them
Come here. Okay. I
Apparently I apparently killed that guy. How do you get them to get in? How do you get him to get in?
Let us lose. This is a scary game
Push these boxes Joe
There's you don't have a t-shirt on
You don't probably don't even have underwear on you don't even have socks on
Farmer Joe just wakes up in the morning puts on his overalls on his nude body
And loafers and then he goes to work
I don't know something about that ain't right
Hey
And not much left to do here World War two every little dogfight
We're going I don't know where we're going. What a beautiful working day your first mission to destroy a nearby factory
Okay, Oh
classic the classic game of jewel
Wizardry if you think you're powerful enough to take on my challenge
We're in a fucking red dress in a bathrobe with a Diablo 2 paladin scepter
I get it. I actually get it. I get it. Oh
I
Did it I played them all you're probably wondering how the hell did you do that? So faster, but that's it. That's remarkable
Well, I mean, there's only a hundred and forty five games on the whole disk
You're looking at every single game unless of course you don't count the match three clones or the copious amounts of hidden object games
That are essentially the same game. Oh almost forgot all the games that don't work. They physically do nothing when you click them
So I mean in 91 or they're a little short of 700,000 exactly
0.013 percent of 700,000 close enough, right? I mean, come on