I didn't mean to turn this on. I pressed enter on the streamlabs
thing. I have it enter as go live. Um, it's actually gonna like delay the stream to tomorrow. So,
uh, sorry about that. I, um, I, I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Hey guys, how you doing? Welcome back. Psycho.
Gotta start. I'm excited. I'm ready to go. This is WarioWare.
This is the week of games that I've been waiting for for a decade.
Ever since Smooth Moves, I've been begging Nintendo to come up with a new one of these.
And I don't count game in Wario. That one doesn't count. This is a WarioWare game from scratch,
ready to go, on Switch, fully developed, fully ready. I heard it's short, but, you know, whatever.
We'll see how short. From what I have seen, it takes anywhere from three to four hours to
see everything. We'll see. But I'm really happy. I'm really, uh, I'm really into it.
I think it's gonna be fun. I don't know. I don't want to give any judgments until I play it.
The new system seems a little weird. Seems kind of weird. Yeah, I'm very early. I was just ready.
Sometimes I'm just ready. Not every time, obviously. Sometimes I'm just ready to go.
That is one of those times today. Hot dog, thanks for the five community subs. Appreciate it.
So the plan here today is we're gonna play WarioWare, and then after WarioWare,
it really depends on how long this game is. If this game, in like an hour or two,
I'm done with it. It's like, oh, that was cool, but I did everything, and I did everything I
wanted to do. I have to, I highly doubt that's gonna happen. And I'll just do No More Heroes 3
tonight. If not, if this game takes at least three or four hours, and I'm having a good time,
then we'll just do No More Heroes 3 tomorrow. So you're really gonna get two short streams
back-to-back, or one long stream tonight. We'll find out. Thank you, AStraightPube.
Are you allowed to have that name? Is that at least in that busy piece of cube?
Thanks for the 10 community subs, I appreciate it. Whatever. So yeah, I'm ready to go. I think,
should we delay any longer? We're just going emote only? What happened? We did. Hey, thanks,
Spigot. Thank you, K5. Five community subs. There's a bug with huge emojis some people are getting,
trying to sort it out. Wait, what? Huge emojis? Well, let's see what happens.
WarioWare, get it together. I'm ready. There's like a character selector in this one, too.
And yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, I'm gonna do a face cam. Everybody just relax,
because I'm going to be going like this. So of course, you have to have a face cam
on for this shit. Hey Casper, thanks for the five community subs. You guys ready? All right,
so this is just, I unlock shit as we go. I can't see what they're saying. What are they saying
about me? Thank you, facade, facadecake for the five community subs, appreciate it. I'm ready to
go. How many players? One. All right, so he plays Wario. Wario intro games. Change the number of
plays. No, excuse me. You can play Metroid? Probably. No, that's a lie. I don't really play
the Metroid games as much as I like pretend to. Metroid is a series that I pretend that I know
anything about, because I think people would think I was cool if I knew about it. I made a tweet.
Here's a fun fact about my Twitter. I made a tweet like three or four years ago. I believe
it said something like this. It took Nintendo five years of making Yarn games to realize that
Metroid was a cool series. I've never played through any of the Metroid games, any of them,
not even the Super Nintendo one. None of them. So why am I making a comment like that?
I was, yeah, I was a poser. I was a fake fan. I was. I'm like, this is WarioWare. I'm ready.
That was a lie? Well, I didn't lie. I just, I didn't say, oh my god, I'm such a huge fan of
Metroid. I can't wait for the new one. I just made like a joke about how they made a bunch of
Yarn games, but I didn't play any of the Metroid games. You know, no, I went like this.
Come, come, come, come, come. In Metroid Prime, Wii, and then I never played it ever again. Oh,
and then I also rented from Blockbuster a copy of Metroid, Super Metroid. But it was like halfway
through the game and I jumped around in a circle a few times and I just returned it. All right,
let's go. It's time for Wadi. What's wrong with Yarn games? Nothing. I was just being like,
I'm just trying to be like, I haven't looked at my opinion. Oh, what's this? I can't do it like that.
I got to do it like this. No wonder I am flying. I am a fly. This is because I'm inside the game.
Ah, who cares? This is going to come. Hey, hey, hold on. Hey, let's walk out of here.
This video game maker loves treasure, money, and garlic. And money, what could go by? This is meat.
I'm kind of coming to the realization that me and Wario are on the same page.
This guy loves treasure. I love treasure. I love money. I love garlic. All right, Wario attacks in
whichever direction he's facing. Okay. It's like a dash. Move and attack. Break. Okay. Push. Push.
Jump. Wait, can I dash? I can only dash sideways? Yeah. Defeat. Okay, push. All right. Is this it?
Look, I'm not going to do the voice. I can't do the voice. I can't do any voices with a cam on.
You guys know that. Because look, I know how stupid and ridiculous I look with it on. But if it's off,
I turn the camera off. Now, all of a sudden, that's me, Wario. I can do Wario.
I'm not doing that with the camera on. It's like embarrassing to have you look at me do that.
Uh, this is the level I made. Oh, he made his own video game, right?
Okay. That thing and messed up everything it touched. I feel like I'm the voice actor
that replaced Wario and like I didn't care to do anything like the original.
This is bad. It's going to ruin my level. Wait. Oh, people would fucking freak up.
Cutscene. Oh my God. Just put a bag over your head. I do like the voices.
That actually might work. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. The games. I got to play the game.
I don't, I think I failed on the first level. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. That's a, that's a really good idea. Dislodge. I'm going to hide my head.
What a genius idea. Okay. Select all. I just punched the mic. All right. We're good.
I've been so long since I played this. I can't wait. Mr. Wario. That's what I just said.
Young cricket. This devoted student of the martial arts diligently trains under master Mantis.
He likes meat dumplings a lot. Jumping is cricket specialty. Hold down A to perform a high jump.
Okay. So everybody has like their own like powers. Push. How high can you go? You can jump really
high. Cool. Why are you in the game? I'm not. This is 18 volt. Check it. I'm here too.
Get this. I can throw this disc on my head as many times as I want.
I know what's even better. I don't have to move, but you don't move.
Okay. 18 volt throws his disc in whichever direction you tilt.
They can't move. Break them all. Okay. Oh shit. This is interesting. I feel like this is like
overpowered. This is completely overpowered. He said this art sucks. All right. People just
make it when they piss me off. I just fucking. He's fun. All right. So do I have to? All right.
Time to join forces is the only way. Come on. Let's tag team our foe. Oh shit. I switched like.
All right. Cool. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I got it. I'm a rise. You match it. Oh
shit. Like that. Okay. Yeah. What am I getting? I got them apparently. Oh shit. Okay. Got it.
Empty. This is weird. I switched between them. It freaks me out.
Tech. All right. When I got it, this game is insane. Does it get insane? I feel like it's
gonna be insane. All right. Boss stage. Let's go. I love that part. Oh, look. Golly.
Defeat. I don't have to. There's no timer here. I'm fine.
Holy shit. Are his spikes come out of his head? Oh my fucking idiot. What are you doing?
You lose to the first boss. I'm fine. Look, I'm just going to get in spring things. I've died.
This is different. This is different. This plays a lot differently than the other ones.
It's a complete evolution of the WarioWare formula.
Oh. Hi up. Hi up. It's a Nintendo game. It's three hits. All right. That was easy.
The emojis are fixed. I need to like, I need to put like a bag on my head and try to do voices.
That's really important. I need to like cover my head. If you guys can't see me,
I can do whatever I want. I can do voices. There you are. You can't hide from Wadi.
Whoa. The corruption is disappearing. I bet that was a game bug. They make games act all glitchy.
Do you turn the webcam off? Okay. Why did I read that? All right. So you got to get rid of all the
bugs in Wario's game. Sounds cool. Everything moved back to normal. Yeah. I'll do like the
best impressions you've heard all night. Let's smash some bugs. Frickin 18 volt. Join the crew.
You earned 1000 coins for completing a level. Oh, all right. Hold on. Give me one second. Let
me, I, I, well, I'll do this in a minute. Let me like get to the first like 20 minutes of the game.
You want to play your pedia. You're like missions through. All right. Nice. You sleep good last night.
Yep. The PNG of Wario over your webcam. No, not that's what. No. What year is this? Let's go level
two. I wonder if there's anything to begin to shake the Wemo. It'll load this place. The bugs
really did a number on it. Hey, hello Wario. Is that you? Oh, my scooter. It won't stop.
Wario Vtuber. You know that Charles Martinet did that 12 years ago. They set him up with a camera
that like recorded his face in real time and he would go to conventions and he did Vtuber Mario
at conventions. That's like how it all started. The original Vtuber was Charles Martinet. The fart
music. It's Wario dude. That's not true and false. Look it up. All right. This is Mona. Work, school,
and pets keep this high school student busy. She's also a big fan of Wario. Why? Who can say?
Mona is always on the move so you have to steer her in the right direction. The boomerang
can be aimed the same way. You always are moving. I don't like this character. All right. This is
weird. Like I'm patting my head and rubbing my stomach at the same time. This is very weird.
This is strange. I get a raid. Oh, shit. Kit Boga raid. We got a Kit Boga raid this early.
What's going on? Thanks, Kit. What's going on? Welcome, everybody. Welcome to the stream. If
people are on my stream and you're not following Kit Boga by now, you've lost your goddamn mind.
Sing the raid song? No, I'm not going to sing a raid song. I'm going to do the impressions soon.
YouTuber raid voice. This is not a YouTuber raid voice. What are you talking about?
Look, when people hit the raid button, when you see the raid come in immediately,
I have to present myself in a way where I'm not a lunatic. Sing the raid song.
On almost just give 20 community subs. Thank you. Kit Boga is one of the funniest people on
Twitch. Go follow. How do you not know who this person is by now? They're on the dollhouse
stream. They've been got a thousand episodes. Thanks, Kit. Let's keep going. Find the bag for
your head. I will in a minute. I've been waiting for WarioWare for like the last fucking 25 years.
What a mess. My level looks awful. Bugs inside the game. Who did this? Unacceptable. Let's go.
Oh, wait, you actually pick your character. Oh, I don't want to be that. I don't want to be Mona.
I don't want to be that character. Who do I want to be? I think I'm going to be 18 volt.
Oh no, you pick your crew. I just, okay. I don't know. Why are you guys kind of hard? You can do
an auto. That's probably cheating, right? Here we go. You guys ready? Cut scene. Turn it off.
Remember, you look like a hotter version of Ryan Reynolds. Don't give me that. Don't stroke my
ego like that. That's completely false. That's 100% untrue. Why are you saying that? That's
unbelievably false. That's not even remotely accurate. See? If I had to do that with a cam on,
it's not going to happen. Next day. These people are just fucking up our house. All right, let's
do it. Peel. I just barely got it. All right. Aim and throw. Eight o'clock. Got it. Oh, look at
that. I love that little guy over there. Yeah. Ring. I get it. I got it, right? Ring the doorbell.
What? Hide. I rang the doorbell. Squeeze. He's so good. I just do it three times. Oh,
oh, that's hard. I got it. I got it. That's just one side. Okay. Good.
Thank God. Watch out for the teeth. Okay. I'm good. Yeah. I don't know why I thought I was
going to die. Oh shit. I got it. I didn't even know where I was. Good thing I was flying around.
Oh, this is, this is weird to do. Okay. Here we go. Air dryer. Mega Man jug. Boots. Backpack.
I need the Mega Man jug. I get it. Oh shit. I got time here. Missing backpack.
Bug. Oops. I tried to kill the bug. All right. I need two of these. I need two of these. I need
one of these and one of those. I want to kill this bug. I wouldn't even odd. Remember your hair looks
good today. Can I please see my family? I need like a bag. Not even a bag. Just like a, like a,
like a towel or something or like a blanket to hide. All tidied up. Good work everyone.
Thousand coins. All right. Hold on. Let me, I'll be right back. I'm not leaving. I just, I literally
just need one second. One second. Let's see. Let's test this. So if I was going to do Wario, right?
I don't like people looking at me. Hey, it's a me. Wario. I hate it. Hey, it's me. No, I don't like
people looking at me. Let's try this. Now you can't see me. So like I can do it. It's a me.
It's me. Wario. Oh, here I go. Here I go. That was pretty good until I freaked out.
How about Mr. Satan? I could do Mr. Satan too. It's me. No, I don't want to do it in front of you.
I'm going to do it. I'm going for it. Tell me which one's actually better.
Well, that's me, Mr. Satan. Hi, Goku.
Okay. Right. Now let's try this. Tell me which one's really actually better.
Well, that's how I do it, Goku. It's me, Mr. Satan. And I'm going to tell you something. You're not
going to destroy Earth until I kill you, Mr. Satan, Goku. It's constructing my blood vessels.
It's constructing my blood vessels a little bit. I can't do it that well.
All right. Here's the difference. It feels like somebody's like,
all right, do some voices. It's hard to do it with the mask on. The duck was,
was the duck better? That was just Alex Jones. Was the duck actually better? I don't think it
was because I was like constricted. All right. How about this? Ready? Now I'm not constricted.
Well, I'll tell you. It's me, Mr. Satan. And Goku has got himself in some trouble.
We got to go help him, Vegeta. Hey, it's me, Mr. Satan. We got to help that Goku out because
he's in big trouble. Which one was better? Okay. Exactly. Got him gained, please. Turn the camera
off. You know, that, why, why would I, why am I doing this? I'm not sure. Maybe you should try
the gimp mask again. Gimp mask. It's like a fucking turtle or whatever this thing is. It's,
I don't know what this is. It's like a duck or a chicken. What is this supposed to be?
What is this creature? What is this? Is it a chicken? It's a rubber ducky. Oh, right. Yeah.
It could be a turtle like this. All right. Stop pretending. All right. We've got all the weird
shit out of the way in this stream. We can go back to normal now. It's not so bad after all.
Oh, Wario. How could you say that? All right. Let's do it.
This taxi driving duo is happy to take you from your front door to the far reaches of space.
The fear is always fair. What's wrong with them today? I'm playing Wario Ware for the first time
in 10 years. I'm a little excitable. My Tribble always fires his bazooka to the right and Spitz
always fires to his left. What if I'm playing with one person?
I don't. How do I change? How do I switch person? I played this last year for the GameCube.
The game didn't come out last year for the GameCube. All right. We took a look around
and there are messes like this all over the place. Game bugs must have corrupted the entire game.
Let's go exterminate some bugs then. All right. I really like, I like 18 volt. I like cricket.
I think those are my two mains. Tribble and, oh. Did you forget you played smooth moves? Yeah,
but I, I played these games before. They came out 10 years ago. This is a new one that I've
never played before. I'm obviously going to be very excited. Here we go. Close. Holy shit. Okay.
Yeah. I didn't know if I had to shoot it. Spin it. Literally best character in the game.
Okay. Where the fuck am I? Made it. I got it, right? I can't even shoot that way. I got it.
Didn't I? Oh, I won. Okay. Cool. Put a jumpscare warning in the description when you're going to
turn on the webcam. Why is my webcam so dark? Oh, dodge. That's it. It's very easy.
How many? One, two, three, four, five, five. There are five. No, there are three. There are
two. There's one. Okay. High five. Oh shit. I'm going to lose. Stick together. Why am I going
like this? I'm like leaning back and free. Do you know what I'm doing? Like, why am I doing this?
Lean in. It's not like a scary horror game. Catch four. One, two, three, four. I'm an overachiever.
So, therefore, I get punished for it. I feel like it's going to be Wario and Cricket. All right.
Let's do it. Come on. Wario is actually pretty balanced. Oh, it's weird not being able to shoot
that way. Stop. This isn't Smash. I'm not playing Smash. I got it. Fight me in Smash. Okay.
Dodge. Oh, calm down. This game's easier to play standing up. I don't think so.
High five. Steal back. Steal back. Oh. Where the fuck was the raid song? This is difficult.
Okay, I got it. The raid song is from like 2019, guys. What do you want me to do? Oh shit. That's
bad. Catch four. One, two, three, four. It's from last year. It's from 2019. Protect. Protect this
little guy. Oh, what am I protecting? Unlock. Oh shit. Get it. You piece of shit. Let him go.
Unlock the fucking door. Get up there. Get up there. Oh my god. Let him go. That was tricky.
He only shot him 34 times. Ah, now that's more like it. What can I do with money? I have a full
drink here and I forgot it existed. Ah, that's good. Dr. Crygor? What's the drink? Um, it's tang.
I love tang. Am I swimming? Am I flying? Paddle, paddle, paddle. Look at my flippers go.
Hello, Dr. Crygor. Indeed, what the gallium is going on around here. Dr. Crygor, down here.
You literally live in the 90s. I don't. I have a tang over here. By the way, I do one
scoop. I don't do the recommended two or three tablespoons. I do one tablespoon just to get a
little flavor. I, it's barely anything in there. I just, I like it. It makes, it tastes good. It's
like a light little flavor. I don't recall my level looking like this at all. How many people
are in the game? Oh, you're here too. Extraordinary. Yeah, by the way, that shit will last like a year
if you do it like that. This genius scientist is so good at making mechanical marvels he made a
cyborg out of himself. Press or hold A to make Crygor swim through the air.
Weird, okay. So you just kind of steer around. Oh, yeah, this is weird. I don't hate it though.
By part of the game, something's gone awry. Do you know what it might be? Yes. Yes. Game bugs have
taken over. They're causing these glitches. Game bugs, glitches, wonderful. I shall be sure to
study them in my laboratory. I think this guy has some glitches of his own, if you know what I mean.
Okay, Wario and 18 volt. Let's begin. No, I'm not going to answer that question. It's weird.
Handball. Light. Oh, I like that one. That was fun. Are the emojis so large? I don't know what's
going on. Oh, I just get in frame. Escape. Oh, I escaped. No, you idiot. Fine, I got up.
Assemble. Assemble. Oh, Lord, I got it a little wrong, but I got it.
Shave your sides. Shave my sides. Like I haven't shaved in like a week. Oh, fuck. That was weird.
That's weird with him. I get it. I thought I was like, wait, am I going the wrong way?
Serve. I just spammed. I just, I smashed that fucking like button is what I did. What am I supposed to do?
Oh, that was easy. You contoured your beard. I didn't, I guess that's how my hair goes. I didn't
contour. That's funny though. Grab. Okay. Assemble. Another sushi. I almost picked up the
telephone. Okay. That was weird. It's toothpaste. It was very, that was simple. It's time for a full
melt downstream. I don't think so. I'm getting all the energy out in the beginning in the first like
40 minutes of the stream. I'm just blowing through all my energy like in an hour.
So don't worry. I'll go, I'll fall asleep in like 25 minutes. See, I am a genius. You earned a
thousand coins. Cool. All right. So I can only go here. Oh, Nintendo classics is my favorite stuff.
I love this shit. We're going to, we're going to get to see Super Mario 1. We're going to get,
hopefully we get to see Super Mario 2 and I hope we get to see Zelda and Metroid. This is the best
minigame. Waiting 10 years for these. All this pushing is good for my training, but can't you
just walk a little bit? Hell. Yikes. Nine volt. My skateboard. It's skating on its own. This
skateboarding school kid is obsessed with Nintendo games and has some serious DJing and yo-yo skills.
Nine volt skateboard keeps him rolling back and forth. Press A to stop and shoot his yo-yo
upwards. So you don't even move. It's just yo-yo. It's weird. I don't control it. This one's going
to be hard. Okay. I can turn around. Nine volt is the only person that can make Nintendo fan games
without getting a DMCA. That was, that was pretty good. That was pretty good. I like that one. What's
wrong with my level? Is it broken? Totally. There's these bugs in the game and they're chewing it all
up. Okay. Okay. And let's go get him. Nobody messes with my games. Nine volt. Okay. Nine volt,
18 volt. Let's take Dr. Kraigra. Why is he not doing silly voices? He missed the first 20 minutes
of the stream. That was pretty much the only thing we did. Nine volts house. I think augmented
reality game. I used to watch wrestling like that and I had this tiny little, I used to have
in my bedroom, this tiny little TV. It was like a, it was an old CRT TV. So it was big, right?
And I used to watch wrestling, like SmackDown would be, what am I doing?
Uh, so it was SmackDown and RAW. They would, it would be 10, 11, 12 o'clock.
And I would have to go to bed. But I had to, uh, I had to watch it on an old CRT TV. So I had plugged
it into bed. Like I plugged it into like the, oh, let me, let me pause this because my brain can only
do one thing at a time. So I had a little CRT TV. It was like a big queue. It was a big Minecraft
block. That's how I can describe it. So it's plugged in far away in my room. It's not right next to me.
But what I used to do is when I wanted to watch, watch wrestling late at night, I would plug the
TV in behind like the bed, like the outlet behind the bed. And the TV would be right on an end table
right next to the bed. Or I would be holding the TV in my bed, just like this with like fucking
Stone Cold Steve Austin on it and shit. And I would hear the like, here comes mom to check on you.
And there would be two things I would do it. I would like sometimes just like put it on the
fucking ground next to me and like pretend to be asleep or like put it under the covers and like,
go like this. But I had this gigantic like cube. Or I would try to turn with it like,
power off, turn it. It's like, I wonder how much my mother used to come in and be like,
you stop watching TV. I know what you're doing. The TV is normally like across the whole fucking
room. And you play, I'm like, no, I put it there before I went to bed. I turned it off at exactly
10 PM like I'm supposed to because I'm a good boy. It's like, oh no, you didn't. Did it ever work?
No, not once. I also, yeah, I think everybody that used to watch wrestling got in trouble
watching TV in bed. See, you don't know how lucky you motherfuckers have it now. Do you
understand me? Do you understand me? Do you know how hard it is? Do you know how easy it is for you
to go like this? It was a cube and it weighed 40 pounds and it was sitting on my chest. It was
over the neck. Do you understand how hard it was? You guys even have brightness settings.
You can go, oh, I'll turn the brightness down to zero so it makes like 10% illumination,
but I can still see. We didn't have that. You're lucky you didn't get your hands stuck in the VCR
part of these TVs. The combos. Game only? No! Okay, whatever. Sumers. Who won? Oh no, no, no,
you won. Wait, what happened? I am so confused. I just pick a side?
Oh, there's Donkey Kong. Mario? Remember, didn't have running water when he was a kid.
I'm just saying, you have, you have a TV, a game device. What am I doing? Oh wait, your phone is
everything. Yeah! I used to eat cement when he was a kid. I didn't eat cement. Spin it? Oh, that's so
hard with him. No! Spend a hundred coins to keep playing. What do you mean? No, yeah, what?
Oh, I can just start from there. No, start over. A hundred coins. No, I'm keeping it.
Eat cement. We used to play with old tires. We used to play with old, we used to play with old wood.
You guys don't understand. We actually had to use our tetanus shots, unlike you kids. You're
going to cut it off for the best part. Holy shit, that's one full letter grade below what I was
going to give it. I gotta be careful here. All right, what game is coming up next? This is Toad's
Treasure Trove. I remember that. I remember that one. The game is that one. Pikmin. I remember that
one. Hey! Oh. Which is greater. Three. What? This feels like a mod I don't want to be playing.
There's no jump. No! Wait. Okay. Ready? Go. Oh, do you like satisfying power washing video?
Oh, Newgrounds Mario Colonia. That was cool. I can't wait to do more of those.
It was a rant from what? What am I ranting about? Talk about KO. Thousand coins. Easy money.
And now what? New. This is, oh, it's a remix. First remix of the night.
Everybody just sat up in their seats. You've been waiting to eat your food because you know
that I'll be here for a little while. You're like, I'm waiting to get to the remix before I eat my
fucking chicken sandwich. I know he's going to be stuck here. I'm going to be laughing with my mouth
full of food. Minecart. Wait. Like the Donkey Kong minecarts? Be funny. Hurry up, my la la.
Be funny. My Burger King long chicken's getting cold. That's a funny joke. I know you're a liar
because they're always cold. Invented by Dr. Crygor, this karaoke robot has a great love
of singing. He does not have great skills at singing. Mike shoots notes upward from his mouth.
Can I fly around?
Oh, what a good observational comedy. I mean, I've had the long chicken like probably five times in
the last three or four years maybe. I'm not sure it's been warm once. It's very good. It's been
like kind of like sometimes lukewarm. I don't think I've had a hot long chicken in like five years.
I just don't think I have no memory of that. There's no such thing as a long chicken. Do
I have to link the video again? It's the Burger King long chicken. Just type it. Just type it
right now. Type in Burger King long chicken into Google. I want you to watch this. Look,
it's like the menu pops up. That's what it's called. They call it the Burger King original
chicken sandwich, right? Whatever it is. That's not what it's called. Long chicken. The original
BK chicken sandwich. That's like, all right. That's like when a company comes out with like
a cleaning solution and it's like a new, like, oh, new formula, original BK sandwich,
original formula. No, it's a fucking long chicken and I'll die on this hill. It's so, it's so like
just, oh, it's just like just safe. Like the original BK chicken sandwich. No, I don't want
to call it that. I'll take one long chicken, please. Oh, could I have a BK original chicken
sandwich? Yeah, there goes my solo career. We're going to play with Mike and I like 18 volts.
Nine volts. I don't like that. It's too hard to play. You just say chicken sandwich, weirdo.
Excuse me. I want that person timed up with one second. There are like seven different chicken
sandwiches at all these fast food restaurants now. The chicken sandwich is like the new thing. You
have to have like four of them or five of them. Oh, I'll take the deluxe chicken sandwich. I'll
take the crispy original chicken sandwich. Oh, could I have like the extra crispy double deluxe
chicken sandwich? McDonald's now has a, on the menu. I'm sorry, we're going to take a minute here.
It's, it used to be you would order like, oh, I'll take the chicken sandwich. Now there's like,
it's like, oh, number four. There's four A, four B, four C, and it's all a chicken sandwich.
Every restaurant has five different chicken sandwiches now. This one's spicy.
We're just going to have a fucking spicy chicken sandwich. I love these rants. It's not even a rant.
I'm just speaking factual information to you. Literally who cares? You're right. Stop.
This is a rant. Don't pretend it. No, it's really not. Oh my goodness. He's bad here.
Stream doesn't like choice. No, it's, it's about, look, you don't need a thousand menu items.
Make them good, not more. We did. No, I actually love like the late night menus because there's
like seven things on it. Can I do this? How am I supposed to? Okay. I got it right.
Nara has a mac and cheese sandwich. That's for you to say exactly what you just said for all
of us to be appalled by it. And then for somebody to go make a fucking like Instagram video about
it. Like that, that's what it's for. They've won because you just said that. Oh, I don't get
that one. Oh, this is impossible with this guy. Not possible. I died. All right. Okay. Let's go.
Focus. Oh, this is awesome. He's actually mad. Why would you think I'm mad right now?
There's no timer. Yeah, there is, but it's fine. I want all the coins because it probably gets
you something. Got all the coins. You're gonna be very prideful of your chicken sandwich knowledge.
Not really. And I'm kind of just foreshadowing over here, but why the fuck would it give you
something dumb ass? You're blatantly throwing. I just, I just beat it. What are you talking about,
man? Ooh, it's home to the island. This is Kat and Anna. Oh, this is Katana. Hey, we found you.
What's with all the bouncing? You look like a couple of tiny kangaroos.
We can't help it. Our legs won't stop jumping. It's probably just our super awesome ninja powers.
These kindergarteners are not only twins, they're ninjas too. That is a tiny bit older than Anna,
obviously. Kat and Anna jump non-stop. At always throws her shuriken to the right.
I don't like these constantly moving ones. Yeah, I don't like the constantly moving ones.
It's really weird jumping to our level. You can help us take it down if you're not too scared.
All right, let's pull out. Let's go Wario and we'll do, um, fine. I'll do nine volt.
Oh, there's another slot and cricket. That sounds good. We're not going to get a cut scene? Oh,
we are. This is the worst team. People just gave me shit by using the same three characters.
When are you going to play Mass Effect 2? The first one? I'm not going to play any of the mass
effects on the screen. Why not? I don't, I don't want to dedicate like a hundred hours to, never
mind. I'm going to get in trouble if I talk about this. Cover? Oh, this is a cat shit. Oh,
what the fuck? Speed. Come on. E1. That's classic. True The Flies Away. Classic WarioWare level.
What are your thoughts on? Well, hold on. First of all, we got a big chunk. Oh, no.
You didn't eat it all. Somebody wrote shut the fuck up. But it was in all capitals and they
misspelled up. It was so angry at that one. I was right at the wire. Is it? I got it right.
Ease. Okay. This is like a, this one's a lot of poop. That one's not hard. All right. Boss
battle. Are you going to be a dedicated Mass Effect 3 streamer? I cannot think of something
that seems more torturing to do than you want me to play Mass Effect 3 every stream. I mean,
how many times can you truly play through that game? Am I supposed to do something?
Question one. No. Who was there the most of? I don't, I don't know. I think it was the Flamingo.
Okay. If you're like speed running Mass Effect, then sure. You're going to do that.
Who was not there? He wasn't here. Just to simply be, I'm a Mass Effect 3 streamer. Question three.
No speed runs. No like new DLC or anything. Who was in pair? I don't know. I think it was this guy.
No. What are you doing? There are multiple endings. I could see like streaming Mass Effect 3 for like
a couple of weeks or something with like 100% of the game, right? But if I did Mass Effect 3
every day for like five years, I expect three, but I wasn't speed running it. Okay. We have Lion with
Meat, Jumping Elephant, and Sleeping Gorilla. Question one. Who was not there? No, there was
no, there was no giraffe. Stop looking at chat. Leave me alone. Question two. Who had food? Lion.
Question three. Who was jumping? Elephant. I won. Please. I said Mass Effect 3 multiplayer,
not the regular game. I misunderstood. We did it. Mission complete. I wonder what you actually buy
weapons. What do you spend money on? Oh, their names are Kat and Anna like Katana. Yeah. It helps.
They say it in the other game. Sports. Jimmy T. What's with this place? It's so dark and boring.
It's rather spoopy. Are you holding your little Joy-Cons? Thanks. Okay. Here we go. Sports. Hello.
Is anyone there? Grief. Why is there a story in the WarioWare game? There was a story in the other
ones. It was a storyline. All right, Jimmy. What do you got? Jimmy T. Whether he's hitting the dance
floor or the gym, the sports loving disco king has all the right moves. Okay. Tilt to choose the
direction of Jimmy's attack. This is kind of like Wario. This is Wario, but you can go in any
direction. Upgraded Wario. Why would I use Wario? We can fix it, but we got to take care of those
bugs. All right. I'm not going to pick Wario. Mike was good and I'll do Mona too. Why not?
And Dr. Crygor because I like them.
There's the cam. I turned the camera off for cutscenes so I get out of the way so you can pay
attention. This seems important. All right. There's something stuck in the fax machine.
There's something stuck in the fax machine.
It really is. That's just, it's Milton right there. It's the same outfit.
Hey, DJ. All right. Boomerang. Land. That was not easy. What the fuck?
Oh, he's to get it. You got it. Okay. Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it.
Wrong direction, Andy. Uh, whatever. Nice. Reel it in.
Wow. Okay. I didn't, I didn't understand what was going on to the last second.
Shoot it. Oh God. Okay. Speed up. Number 10. Oh God. He was perfect for that. Audios. De-synced.
Which one? It's not de-synced. Let's do a test. Ready? Climb. Oh goodness.
Are his feet above his head? How is he doing that? Fuck this art. This is going to be awful
when it gets to an actual remix. That's hard. And that shows up and I have to do that in like
12 seconds. I'm going to lose every time. It's a boss level, not a normal level.
They get harder though. Can you, don't you go back and do that? I think you can,
you go back and you play these things again and they're like three times harder.
All right. Here's Ashley. This is the Ashley. We're going to get a song.
That's uh, let's just uh, but, but, but let's see. Kamehameha. What's it? Kameha. What's the
character's name? It's from Mario. The character from Mario, the wizard that has like the same
exact wand and the cubes. What's the character's name? Kamak. Yeah. That's a pretty cool reference.
Ashley. Ashley. Cute stuff. Doesn't like cute stuff. Expressing emotions. Unnecessary chit chat.
Likes casting spells. Food in her pal red. Ashley cast spells in whichever direction she's facing.
Again, just a better version of Mike. This is a better version of Mike.
Mike just shoots up and just stomps some game bugs and you, you're going to help us.
Why should I? Because I said so and because fine, we don't need you anyway. Of course you do. Of
course, my buddy. And we'll do dribble and spits because they're awful. Here we go. Here it comes.
She likes to eat her food and she has all kinds of moods. Her name is Ashley. You cast a spell on
you. Where is it? It didn't do what I said. Embarrassing yourself, Jeremy.
Holy. Okay. You got to get it. It's a thing that way a lot. Get out. Oh, get the ball out. Shit. I
got it. Get it in there. Oh, blend it up. I like that one. That's my favorite one I think so far.
That's my favorite minigame for the whole day. Oh shit. Tang. I didn't even pick up on that.
It was very easy. I can't protect with. Oh yeah.
I can.
All right, time for a boss battle. Oh, you're playing a kid's game.
Okay. Would you like me to stop? Should I stop playing? Juice. Juice. Don't spill. Oh,
I don't understand. I need to fill each one of these slots? Oh, I need to juice it. I actually
physically smash it. Okay. Why is that meter doing that? Oh, that's. I'm fine. That was easy.
Everybody's a kid at heart. Before you retire, Jeremy, please do a full beard.
I can't. It just looks like I have like wires hanging out of my face. The hairs are so
individually spaced out that it just looks strange. After another two weeks of this,
it looks bizarre. All right. I got 10 almost 10,000 bucks. Orbulon.
Strange beards are cool. I mean, maybe. I don't like the way it looks. What's that weird sound?
Yeah. Some people can pull off beards. Some people can just pull off like a strange looking beard.
I'm not one of them. Plus it's itchy and annoying. I hate it. I don't like the way a beard feels.
Let's try to turn the camera off. This alien insists he'll invade Earth one day.
He's lived here long enough to know a lot about our culture. Orbulon sucks up the things below
him by activating his beam. Okay, weird. Beam up. Whoa. I like this character a lot.
My beam of tractoring, it does not work on this glitchy yuck. Stuff won't go away until we take
out those mean old game bugs. See, then Orbulon will dispose of these bugs with style. We're
doing Ashley and Ashley, Jimmy. I did a mustache for the one stream and I couldn't do it again.
I already like this music the most. When are you going to play Mass Effect 3
Alternate Appearance Pack DLC 1? What a living hell. That's so stupid.
That would be my stream title too. Checking out the huge new update.
Commander Shepard has a green shirt this time. The developer studio t-shirt. Make it flow.
Commander Shepard with like the game studio t-shirt that you can put on.
I would lose my fucking mind. Match? I don't know what happened.
I can't even stream the same game like two or three times. It was a Christmas miracle
that I was able to stream and play and make videos of TF2 for as long as I did.
That's the only exception ever. Ice cream. Oh shit. Was there a spoon in it? No.
It just got burnt. What happened? Oh, whatever. I didn't get it for a second but now I do.
Ring the bell. Ring the bell. What the fuck? Oh, do it. God. What the fuck?
I love these ones. Come on. Get over there. I love when you mix the colors together.
Don't waste your money. What's the point? This team might not be very good either.
Shit. Okay. I got it. You're a sad little man. All right. Nice. I got it.
I'm going to steal your bread if you don't tell me your skin care routine.
Okay. It's called turn the shower on. Put your shampoo in your head and then go like this.
And like get it all over like everywhere. Make sure your eyes are closed. Your mouth is closed.
Oh, this one sucks. Okay. I got it. You just shampoo, shampoo, shampoo. Then you go after
the shampoo runs dry, right? When it runs out and it runs clear. Just hold your face up to the...
Hold your face up to the shower and just go like this. He distracted me and it caused a
problem. Do it. No, you just use like seed fill. You're fine. I'm kidding. Just use like a little
gentle cleanser like seed fill. That's all you have to do. 35 in one shampoo. 35 in one shampoo
would be you brush your teeth too. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. We got to talk about that.
Let him pass. Come on in. Imagine putting shampoo in your hair, letting it run down into your mouth
and brushing your teeth with it. And then it keeps going down and you put it under your armpits and
it's a deodorant. Let's kill somebody. What happened? What was that? Let him through. Let it pass.
Oh, okay. I get it. They were going to crash into each other. I got something in my nose.
Oh my god. There's like an animal in here. What do I do? But they're going to crash into each other.
It's like, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out. Why would it tell? Why would it
tell me that? There is a beam that's like caution, caution, caution, oncoming car, caution, caution,
caution. Why is there a caution? If I'm driving on one side of the road, I don't get a bunch of
caution signs. Let's say, watch out, another car is on the other side of the road. What's the caution
for? Get out of here. Get away from it. Last one. I'm not going to watch it. Get the animal out of
your nose. I will eventually. Go pee break? Yeah, I will in like 15 minutes. At the two-hour mark,
we'll do a first break. I'm fine. Conquer the game, bugs, then conquer the world. Thank you Segata
for the 10 community subs. I missed a bunch of other subs too. We were in the middle of ranting,
ranting and raving. But thanks. Thanks for the subs. Thanks for the 10 community subs.
I believe this is remix two. Two hours drink. I've got, I've got a drink right here. I'm good.
This is full of water and a little bit of tang. I'm hydrating. I'm good. Another mine cart. I'm
going to take Orbilion. I like them. Do you like the game so far? I do, but so far it's very easy.
I think I'm going to eat those words, but it's very simple so far. Very easy.
I'm really hoping that it gets much more challenging in the near future.
I remember smooth moves. Some of those remixes were insane. Yeah, I think it's going to be hard.
I know it is. Unacceptable. You know better than to wander off by yourself. It's not safe.
Oh my, getting upset makes me so sleepy. Like what's up with your mom and your other mom?
You have these out of body experiences, I guess. Your mom's got spooky moves. Hey, that's weird.
I dig it. Five volt. While there's nine volt, she's as sweet as can be until she gets mad.
Her out of body anger is positively shocking. Five volt warps to wherever her spirit takes her
and emits a powerful shock. She can't warp to certain areas. Okay, weird. Yeah, I think I'll
get used to it and then I'll probably end up liking it. We'll see. She can't move. There's
no jump or anything. Just teleport. All right, we're going to get the cutscene here.
I want to just use the overpowered characters. Let's go with Mike and Wario
and 18 volt. You can't just use the OP characters every time. Oh shit, there's no cutscene.
No cutscene. Did I fuck it up? I think I broke it. I got it. She's actually pretty good. Does that
count? How do you jump through when you have a teleport? What? I can't, there's no jump through.
I like not having to move. Shit, too much. Okay, we're good.
Why do I sound like Patrick? I sound like Patrick. All right, speed up. Oh, she's weird.
She's weird to use. It does sound like Patrick.
I'm a master. All right, here we go. What's her boss? I'm not more of this juicing, juicing
shit. I can't even talk. I don't want to do the juicing. This actually kind of sucks with her.
Jump with the B. I'm missing a lot. No. Oh, we're at critical levels. The shit's moving around.
And that's it, right? That's hard with her. It's weird. All right, come on. Let's go. Let's go.
I think I figured out the strat though. Yeah, I got it. He's gonna wait till there's two over.
Don't. Stop. No. Fuck. No. No. God damn it. My last try. Last attempt. I just watched your
Thanksgiving dinner stream. This was a while ago. That's like one of my favorite streams.
That polarized the community so much. That's some people's least favorite thing I've ever done and
some people's most favorite thing I've ever done. People genuinely hated that stream and they were
like, don't fucking do that shit. I hated it. It's like, all right, I would do it again too.
It's my last chance. Seriously. I got stung by the B. What? I didn't think that was even possible.
I'm spending 100 fucking coin packs and I'm going again.
Pop it. I'm not gonna scream. What am I fucking 10? Pop. That's it. Okay, game over. I win.
No, the meter is going so high. Game too hard? Game is not too hard. You haven't seen hard yet.
That's coming up pretty soon. How many more characters are they going to introduce in the
game? Let me see. Go back and play the old levels. I'm curious. Let's see. So if I go back to, let's say,
all right, like Dr. Crygore, right? What happens? Yeah, I've already seen this. So what happens if
I play this again? After this, you should play one of the other, make a match. Oh shit. Can I
grow back? What does it play? Rhythm Heaven. I played it. It's one of my favorite games. Look,
green, green, purple. Pop on. Huh? I was paying attention. All right, I'm good. I got to get at
least 20 to 30 on every level. I like that video. Heart to Zombe, that one. What? I thought it was
a spade. Wasn't it a spade? I'm confused. 11. I got to get to at least level 20 to 30 to 50.
Green? A pop-up ad? What was that? Oh, I'm at the boss stage. What the heck? Do we keep going
after this? This game looks fun. It is fun. Itchy. I think we keep going after this. Okay,
so does it keep going? Yep, it does. Bonus stage. Uh, wait. I haven't thought. Oh, it's just a
collect game? No, we keep going. That's right. I knew it. What did it explode? What did it explode
for? I lost. Now I'm paying some fucking in-game currency. I'm paying in-game currency. Oh, I can't.
All right, I'll go back to it. Wario. Now we're getting somewhere. This is the last level I made.
This is story mode, guys. There's like a ton of shit to do. There's much corruption here,
a great amount of much. What is that thing? It's taking over my game. We've got to stop it.
It's four more characters. Yeah, what are you guys doing? This is just like the little story mode.
They get you tutorial to get you going. All right, it's five people. Bobulon, Mike, Ashley,
18 volt and five volt for the wild card. He's like possessed. That's kind of scary.
Credit card. Where's the key? All right. What? What's happening? What the fuck? I had to pull it.
I was trying to pull the damn thing. This is an awful character to have. This character is not
good. That was a very bad character. Three, one, four. Is murder legal in the Mario universe?
Okay, I got it. I lost. My mouth keeps going like, she's good. She's really good, actually.
That's really good. Oh, all right. Get this out of here. This guy sucks. I can get rid of him.
The one thing he was good for is right there. Oh, fuck.
There we go. Which one travels in the ocean?
It's too much for my brain. No, I don't want this guy for the boss stage. Maybe I do.
Chase. What? What happened? Go. What? Oh, it's on a rock they can break. Can I do it?
Oh, I hate this guy. All right. There we go. Okay. All right. Finally.
It's going to be so much easier with this character. It's so much better.
This is simple. I can literally just go to the edge of the screen and press A.
Okay. That was much easier. Here we go. Just dodge it. Just watch out for the rocks.
Wind. Be careful. Capture. No, I don't want this guy right now.
Chase. It's just capture and then points at the thing. I thought I had to catch the damn thing.
I don't have to destroy them. I hate this. Let's go. Okay. Capture. Oh, that's it?
That's such a bait. I like the toilet character though. That was cool. Wario. Anything goes.
I just beat the tutorial. This is where it gets a little bit more tricky.
I have to get at least 25 on most of the levels of my choosing. By most, I mean three. And by three,
I mean one. And by one, I mean I'll see you tomorrow. I need to get at least 25 on the remixes.
At least 50 on one remix. I gotta get at least 50 on one remix. I am the supreme developer.
I watch over this game, you might say. I'm the one who brought you here. Yes, that was all me.
I'm supreme who? Come on. Everyone knows Wario's number one.
The game bugs arrived quite uninvited. Almost as uninvited as your parent doing Wario reading a
book with Wario in it to their three-year-old son or daughter. They knew not what to do,
so I brought you here to help. Thank you for tidying up their mess. Difficult work,
I'm sure. Now your home is right this way. I'm gonna shuffle on out of here. Come back and play
anytime. That's it. Oh, here's the ending cutscene. I'm not done. I'm not done. I want to get at least
like 30 or 40 or 50 on some of these. I want to dial it up. I want to get intense. That was the
tutorial. We make games, I make money. Wario programs with java script.
Someone's missing. Who's missing? Oh no. We must rescue them.
Not over. This was just the beginning. All right, thousand coins. Very cool.
You now can walk to the end anytime. You unlocked a variety pack in the main menu.
All right. New. Scary mode. Looks like it. All mixed up. All right, I'm gonna do this one and
then I'm gonna go to the bathroom. I'm gonna blow my nose. You've returned and so soon welcome.
Seems some of our friends are still stuck inside the game. Three of our friends, you gotta help us.
Yes, of course. I shall check. Yes, strange. It appears they have been captured by something.
Oh, come on. I thought we took care of the game bugs. This is not the word of a game bug. Wait,
oh dear. One of you friends is nearby. All right, something tells me they're in this tower.
Someone, anyone help? Red, what have you done now? Actually, I knew you'd come to rescue a little
old me. Red, sometimes he seems to be more scaredy cat than demon. Still, Red takes good care of his
fave witch Ashley. Have bombs? That's a little weird. I kind of like it though. There's a delay.
There's a delay on them. Cool. Okay. You see where this big thing went.
Pretty sure it took this elevator up to floor 18. Do we have this more people to unlock? All right.
Obi-Lan, Mike, Ashleigh, okay. Let's go. We're himself not scared. Simple with this guy.
Oh, get out of the way. I don't get it, I don't get it, I don't get it, I don't get it,
I don't get it, I don't get it, I don't get it, I don't get it, I don't get it, I don't get it,
I don't get it. Oh, you know what? That was embarrassing. Oh
It's very embarrassing if I had to connect to the left side. I thought I had to connect it to the left side
It was embarrassing. It's fine. Take a peek
We got away frog walk. I love that guy. Why can't that be a warrior wear character? Oh
Was that technically a goal I don't think so
No get under the tongue get under the tongue
These are hard. It's uh, oh
I'm fine. This is gonna be hard
Cool car. Give me a fucking break
Five
I'm so proud of that. Five. I know that
That is it. Did I do it? I did it. All right time to pee
Don't pee right after this cutscene. What the heck that thing jumped out the window from floor 18
Drop something what's in there olden beehive
Treasure all right. We must not lose focus. I forgot I still had that emote
We must not lose focus time to rescue the other two
All right, I gotta be
I'll be right back
See you in a second. Okay. Hello
I'm trying to come back a little quieter nowadays
Is the compressor on my mic when I come back?
I'm just loud here. I am I feel like I scared the shit out of people
All right, we got a super hard
Super hard, I feel like this is gonna get impossible, but whatever
I'm doing a lot of like dancing today and like moving around. I feel like I have to do that when I play these games
whenever I have the two joy cons in both hands like this
I need to like be like
like moving
Because I feel like I'm not connected
This keeps me
like sane
Having to go like this
When you let me go like this
I'm just like I can move around I can do anything I want I I need to be like held down like this
Look at him. Look at him go
I'm tired of waiting and fell asleep
What do you got?
Uh mantis is a master jumper. He's so good. He can jump onto the ceiling and walk around up there
That's gonna be I don't want to use this guy
He's weird
Untethered
All right, super hard. Let's go. What how many do I need 18?
Or 10 that's it
only floor 10
It seems like it's gonna be simple. Nope. It's fast, but I wanted to 10
I can definitely get 30 or 40 at least on one of these
Oh take it out
Oh, okay seeks shelter
I'm fine. Stop overreacting. It's not just over so I'm acting like that
Because the camera's on and i'm like trying too hard like i'm trying to argue the camera's on
See I have the reverse problem when I play games
Okay
Instead of voice impressions if the camera's off I can do voice is better, right?
But when the camera's on I have this like obligation to overact. You know what I mean? Like
I don't do that when the camera's off
Like oh something crazy just happened. Whoa
Whoa
Stop, why am I doing that? I don't do that in real life
I'm like doing like a tuber react because I know you're looking at me
Okay toilet paper roll
Although actually some of it's real actually most of it's real
That's actually pretty cool treasure
Streamer syndrome digging in the ground. It's actually all real
But it's the thing like okay, so I go like what the
Whoa, like I have to go harder because I see myself over here in the preview
So it starts off as a normal like fuck
It's like I look over it's like
Fuck whoa
And I have to go harder because I like oh, that's not good enough. I gotta go harder than that
Real right block that part of the preview
It's so small. I can't even like see it
Please don't scream. I'm trying to sleep
We talked about this last week, but it's like when the mirror is there. I just have to stare at it
I can't help it. I just like oh what if what I would look like today
We already did this joke a week ago
Uh press a to make lulu float upward. She can perform a ground pound from mid-air
Okay, anytime it's gonna do it
Doesn't go all the way down
Uh, I don't like it. All these new characters don't like except for the bomb guy
the narcissist in the pond
What's the narcissist in the pond? Is that like a story?
Only four or five they make it as easier and easier
guys from staring at their own reflection
Good bomb is perfect there
Good
Hey swiglo. Thanks for the five community subs. All right, so obviously I have to go through these and
Once I unlock everything there's only one life. Yeah, only five levels though. That's not hard
You don't know boppities and you don't know narcissus
Put all the treasure together
Okay, how are we supposed to put all this junk together?
beehive toilet paper mug
What does that do?
All right, let's see if even my granddaughter penny can be of assistance
Mario has a granddaughter
Can't wait to see what happens next. I thought that was the grinch. It's not the grinch. That's a different character entirely. Okay
pennies mix
All right, then i'll give penny a call
I give you jet tank one mario did this
Mario did this already try harder next time
Um
You shrunk yourself down
To like go into the thing into the game when osmosis jones did that 15 years ago be better at everything you do
Tilt to aim pennies water blast with the recoil mover in the opposite direction of the water. Okay move here
Oh boy, okay. It's a continuous spray
And I can hover
I forgot the webcam was on and I definitely looked crazy right there. I was just like
This is why I don't have the webcam like
She's hard to use
Oh, it actually did this like fucking 10 years ago. That's how you guys treat me. It's hard
Lend it up
Like i'm watching like the outro to a half the animes i've seen
Everyone's like happy everyone's like walking down sidewalks together
They're getting food
They're taking like pictures of each other and stuff
They all have backpacks
And they're all very happy to have to be wherever they are
Slice of life andy
I want to do this
Uh with like times 10 speed when we eventually play this
No, I miss it I want it back all right solve this for us, please watering can golden watering can
The toilet that turns into a sunflower. It's gonna be pretty pog
Golden watering can has fulfilled its duty. It's gone my treasure my beautiful treasure getting a little crowded up here
Who's that cat over there? Who's that?
Have you seen that character?
New okay, you can watch calling penny anytime now
and now
Reached the showdown
time to do these
Who actually rewatches the cutscenes?
Yeah, I don't but
Hmm, do you think you missed something? I don't know. All right, let's see. What do we got?
This thing that's been jumping through the windows. There it is. That's the thing that kidnapped me
That have more treasure. Wait, come back
Can you get a final cutscene?
Done. I'm just going
Feed it round one
Well, it's a continuous jump. It's I can't okay
Come on lift up. Oh, I can't wait to do this one
And this one is unlocked and I can just keep going to like round 100
I try i'm trying to get all four
I forget what some of these characters do
Or i'm concentrating
Yeah
Oh shit, I get it. All right. Nice. Oh, no, not yet
I'm spending the coins
And that's it
Have I unlocked the whole game if we consider a career as an early morning talk show host
And god no never no
I would do that for two days and think it was fun or funny and I would never want to be on set ever again
Is that a new character?
It's puro star of that super popular game puro
What are you doing in our game?
Stop by to play for a little bit
I love him and oh he wants to know do you have a good time playing with me?
Good time bad time. Who cares? Where's the treasure?
Oh, there's got to be a treasure some gold maybe just a teensy bit
You're kidding. Oh, there's nothing at all, but I can't end like this
Perhaps this is the end you seek treasure not gold, but the journey it inspired
Okay, okay puro join the crew
I don't want this to be warrior wear anymore. I want this to be puro's game. Hold down a to extend puro's tongue
His tongue automatically retracts when it's gone as far as it can go
I love it. Ah
This is my favorite character in the series so far
Okay, so move around
Hmm cast of warrior wear
Wario
monas monkey monas elephant monas pig and mona
Dr. Crygore mike and dora swamp
spitz dribble
13 bolt 18 bolt 5 bolt 9 bolt and fork
albert einstein
And who could forget cat anna and leo?
ashley and red
Jimmy t master mantis young cricket lulu and joe
I didn't say orbulon's name. I don't know why
He's joe. Yeah
and of course
zero
It kind of looks like auto story is coming to an end but the game has just begun that was the tutorial I told you
All right
Now what?
new
You unlock the staff credits friendless battle is now available
You unlocked wario cup
unlock new features and crew
You can now select all when choosing the size of your crew
Is this staff credits let's mean like probably can I do anything with it?
Can't move around all right
You get points for destroying everybody's name
It's gonna take a long time, isn't it?
I remember playing smash brothers ultimate. No, maybe not. What was the one you could you had to punch the pixels and stuff
No, I don't do this. That's cool. But I don't care. All right, let's go super hard right now fast mode lightning speed. I'm ready
Here's the size of your crew crew of five
puro
Mike
Orbulon red
Dr. Crygore
That wasn't in melee that would mean maybe it was I shh
Oh, I I
restarted
time to do these same crew Mike Orbulon red
Dr. Crygore, I didn't know how that mini game works until five seconds ago
I didn't understand that words until right there. Let's go restart
I'm not allowed to restart ever again
Trap fuck you get up there and do it. This is shit on my head. I didn't do anything
I got it
All right, get in the red get in red get in red get in red
I got him
Whoa, okay
Yeah
Science
All right, 30 is fine. All right, I can do that again. Let's go fucking i'm gonna 50 i'm getting 50 right now
I'm gonna get 50 right now. Let's go again same team. No, actually. Yeah. All right, let's go
But i'm gonna make the game way easier for myself
Get the candy or break the candy. I didn't hear I couldn't tell
Again, this is gonna be like super training wheels. I'm gonna okay
you're gonna i'm putting training wheels and weights all over my body and
I'm just sprinting at 100 miles per hour when I take all the weights off and the training wheels off
I'm gonna be able to run 100 miles per hour through all the stuff
All right new team
Why is that? What's going on with my face? What's my face so itchy right here and like here?
What's happening?
I this is kind of an odd pick but i'm telling you it's gonna work
It's an odd team, but I think it's gonna work. I think 18 votes can be huge here
All right, I gotta get 50
Come on gwen, let's go
Jesus he ran fast. What is it a lollipop? Oh shit. I avoided the whole thing
50 you did what happened fuck he sucks
Again again again again, I can get 50 on this shit i'm doing what the
Magic it's gonna be uh, I I probably shouldn't do this first because everything seems so it seems so simple to me after
Go go go go go go
That's a basket what
Get those fries covered holy shit, that's she's not a good character for that eight o'clock
Whole body's coming in hives. What's wrong with me?
What did I have to do I missed it my body's covered in hives
Why am I so itchy on my chin?
Okay, i'll come back to it. I'll come back to it. I'll come back to it. I'm gonna go back to it
I'm gonna go back. I got new stuff to look at i'll come back to it
Wario cup
Each week you'll be surprised with a new challenge test yourself with a variety of games handpicked for each challenge
Earn super awesome rewards
Okay, connect to the internet and join the ranking system. There are two types of challenges timed attack and score attack
Timed scoring
Score is based on your level based on your speed based on your time played
Cool, okay
And some challenges you'll pick your own crew crew members base scores will change based on the difficulty rating for each challenge
whoo
cover knives
A lower difficulty rating means that the crew member will see yeah. Yeah, and then higher means you get more points, but cool
default score times difficulty times area times uh circumference
Okay, okay, and you get a prize
I turn on ranked mode
Yes, why not? All right. Here's my here's the current challenge
Speed skater. I must be going soft because these games are always going to show up in the same order
Know what? I'm gonna make it extra fast. Wha ha ha just keep it interesting
Watch that nine volt skateboard closely and practice those yo-yo shots, which he
Okay
This is your crew. What uh, um, excuse me
Excuse me. I don't okay
Holy shit
Okay, I thought it was close the casket
God damn it
That's impossible. You can't do that one
Yeah one shot how am I I can't see
Okay, holy shit
So how it's gotta be one of the you won the bronze cup and earned a thousand coins. All right
So how good am I in the in the world?
Near mortal you got more grade points
Okay
New personal record add it to the rankings. Yeah
B
I am part of 28 percent 80 percent of you guys get d
Not me
You're competing with children. Holy shit. Another raid came in
Jack manifold tv with a monster right here. What's going on everybody?
Thanks jack. Uh, welcome literally like six or seven thousand of you just came over here
What's up?
None of your friends. I don't have
Great song, you know, it's up playing. Why are you aware? Uh for the nintendo switch
I want more challenges. That was actually really cool. I want more like that
That's really awesome. But I want to I want to do more though. What about the crew?
Hope you had a good stream loaded
The emporium is now open buy items on sale. Ooh
Wait a minute
Earn job points when you give out
prezzies in the break room
Your crew member's job title could improve depending on how many points you earn
Rare prezzies or prezzies the crew member really likes will earn extra points. What the fuck is going on here?
Hey volatile pen, thanks with the community subs appreciate it. Thanks for 10 subs
Great things await those who reach higher job titles earn more food colors special artwork
Huh? All right. Let's go to the break room
Level one
Oh, man. All right. This just took on a whole new video game. All right, we definitely
Give a prezzy
I don't have any prezzies buy some from the emporium. Okay
New oh shit, they have like t-shirts and stuff. You're almost three hours in what do you think of the game so far?
um
I kind of feel like the game just started
So, I don't know
Okay, who likes this perfect four?
All right. Wario definitely likes toilet paper
um
Wario definitely like mustaches
Uh, somebody likes hair
Arbor flog and bananas
Lockade
Whoa, I get a rare
All right. I just got I spent five thousand dollars for this
You got prezzies
Whoa?
I'm not i'm not i'm not stop spending stop spending stop spending isn't how you get stuff
Nice, okay
What about these ones? These are like normals?
You got prezzies, okay
All right prezzy stash. Oh my god
What's the rarity system?
Is there four stars?
I don't know who wants who likes the stuff
Okay. Um
Well, I I guess I think you have to just yes
All right. I definitely like orbulon i'm gonna do my talk. Okay, my my wario wear tier list
He's gonna have to look something like this
S tier is
Um s tier is orbulon
euro
Mike and i'm spitz probably ashley no and five volts. All right, so let's go
That's why I care about orbulon. All right, give a prezzy
Well, I feel like orbulon would like
Um, he's an alien. So
What do I have that aliens like sunglasses? Those are literally this is literally his sunglasses
Loves it loves it
level two in turn
Oh blue
character art
All right. What else would he like?
As an alien
I don't think manhole cover
How about a football?
no
Gallery, oh customize. Let me do blue
Oh
Whoa, okay. This is cool
Whoa
This is cool
This is actually really cool. I like this a lot
Nice. All right. Should I do another one? Maybe I should what if I gave him a credit card? No
Looks like an alien if you squint
freelance here
yellow and
weird face
All right. Let's not go crazy here. Hold on. All right five volt. What do you got?
Five volt would probably like
Just ghost right so something ghostly
Probably like a hard candy. I don't know
wedding dress banana
Oh shit. Okay
Yeah
All right. Now, no all the gross stuff goes to wario
What a birthday cake?
Yep, blue and art. All right, what a birthday cake
birthday cakes huge
What about I don't think i'm gonna do the wedding dress. Let's look at the gallery
cool special
Zombie
Oh, that's kind of cool. All right
It's not the sound effects
Okay, what about what about pure?
Euro i'm gonna give pure a golden egg
Okay
She really liked that
What about what about a piece of meat?
Not really
What about the what about the credit card?
Eat oh like definitely the party cracker thing. Oh, we don't like that. Okay dress camera
Okay
Um, not really
not really
These are so cool
I love this
Okay, how about customize?
baby face
I want to see the other colors
This is club penguin
All right. Let's let's do I think this has a different sound effects
All right. I'm going for credit card
I'm gonna have a level 10 euro
More colors and another thing. Ooh
This is I this is really fun cutie pie. It's a cute effect
Okay. Yeah, i'm gonna keep it. What should I do? Should I do the baby?
All right, we'll do cutie
I'm gonna give one. I gotta give him the level 10. So we're gonna give him the helicopter go
Really likes the helicopter more special. All right another helicopter
chief of operations
All right. I want to get some other people up now we have shadowy figure
I'm gonna keep cutie pie on the way. He said you can do germa 985
kind of
Need like blue
This looks wrong
Wait, no, no, no, no, no
I don't like that one either
What's your okay? What should be the the beak should be green, right? It makes the most sense
This should be pink
This should be pink this should be like kind of blue and that's green
Doesn't look right. That's better
Good got all the art
All right. Who else do I want to do?
Oh mike. Yeah
All right. Mike is gonna take the headphones. I think i'm gonna give mike everything
He's so ugly, please. Hey
Really likes the manhole cover
He doesn't really like tea
Why do you mean he's ugly? He's fine
All right, i'm gonna go with
I have three of these how do you much you like this?
All right. He loves these horns
Of course, it's a micro. It's a microphone
All the colors. Okay, we're gonna do it again
Okay, cool
Or humans are true
All right, and now i'm gonna give him sneakers
Oh, he didn't like that. I think he's fine. Okay
Okay
Okay, what should he be?
Ooh
Okay, baby face is pretty
Sick
Oh, there's germa 985
Was my last person that I put up there
red
Who else was he gonna do it to?
This is reddit bot
I go all right
All right. Let's give him a mandrake
Loved it. I like the first art. I guess I could do it twice
Oh, that's not okay. Wait, wait, no, he's okay. He liked it. He liked it. He liked it. He liked it. He liked it
He didn't hate it
Did he hate it?
Yeah, he hated it. Okay, whatever
What you like? Uh
Stuff with technology
I like that. These are really cool. I like the style here. It's really cool. Oh, look at the custom colors. Let's do
yellow and
orange and
I like that. Uh, we need I gotta give wario some shit too. I mean like wario wants definitely like the mustache catalog because it's wario
Wario also wants all the junk food like a donut
Okay. Um, what about the meat?
Wario eats like food. He's like hungry all the time
Toilet paper too, right? He loves the toilet paper
and
Definitely the meat
He loves the meat. He loves toilet paper. Remember that piggy bank. That's a good idea
Oh, yeah, that's probably it all the sports stuff has to go to uh, jimmy, right?
Oh, don't be wario or anything. Eh
Let's do like player two smash brothers mara wario
There we go. It wouldn't be yellow
All right. So who else let's see who's who's the wedding dress?
Said it was for a girl. Oh, no five volt
And he who's who's taking what's the wedding dress?
any
Five volt really okay
More stuff. All right, uh, let's go to give me
football
I thought he would like it more than that
anything else
eye exam stick bicycle pump
Rubber plug, what about do you like cashews?
I guess so
It was really stinky in real life
I don't know anything about me
You know nothing about me
Okay, I only have a limited options here
All right, who should I give the rest of the stuff to i'm gonna give it to orbylon
I have a mushroom to every line. He hated it
Ronnie mcdonnie i'm trying to get i'm just trying to clear it out
Here's to you
There's a rarity system. Oh, yeah, I know another rarity rarity system exists
lore
Oh, I like the green
green
Everyone's gonna be germa 985
All right, that's the way it is
Okay
Should I buy more i'm gonna hold on
Give me some rares
Okay, i'm just gonna buy i'm just gonna spend all my money. What's what else is the money for?
Oh bowling pin
so is the four
stars
Silver better than the three gold it has to be right
I feel like the gold would be in front of silver
Holy shit
Okay, but that's a legendary or something
Well, we gotta get this one, right?
Who wants that?
Gessert island plants and animals and the like for the person who has everything
Who has everything who has everything?
Wario
Wario doesn't have everything. He's just like wants everything right give the credit card to five volt
Hazard island the person has everything
Orbulon like home destroyed planets and shit. What is what's this? I don't think I don't get it
Who has it does wario have everything?
Give it to ashley ashley has everything
Isn't mona rich?
I mean just a busy high school student. I don't
Beak the tongue the legend the star of the hottest game in diamond city
Oh, yeah, this is you got everything
whoa
cool
Golden puro that's gonna stay that way
All right. Now who wants the um
What else do I have?
Bat the smell of the wood transports you back in time. Why am I sniffing a bat? Sheesh?
Um, that's very jimmy
baseball bat, right
That's enough
Doll within a doll within a doll who wants that?
golden joe
Five volts. I feel like we're giving five volt all this stuff
Yeah, you're right
All right, i'm out of money and I have a golden puro so i'm happy
whoa
All right. Who do you think I have my lowest win rate with?
five volt
I love puro's icon
Okay, so I have a terrible track record with five volts
With numbers of plays. Yeah
All right, 18 volt 9 volt dr. Crygore orbulon and mike are my top characters
Oh, actually cricket's probably the top character with I gotta have at least 30 games, right?
All right, cool
Uh playopedia
Oh, I can just select them. This is cool
I score wait
crew of one
How does this work? Oh, I can break that. It's just the one
And then it just gets harder and harder and harder
This is crazy. Okay
All right. I'm taking the crew back. We're doing the super hard
missions
The group is gathering
Return to the outside world. Oh, this is for money
Intro games collector new
score
Oh, I got 1,500
Oh shit, I got this level 25 or higher so I get 2,000 bucks
Linus kitty play kitty business from nature clear without covering any
Make whoa. I made puro the head honcho and I got 2,000 bucks time to go buy more fucking junk
Oh god, okay
All right. I'm just gonna buy
I'm just gonna buy them. I'm not gonna sell it. Hold on. I'm just gonna purchase them first
Give me a legendary
There's no legendary in there. I'm not happy about it
Zero gameplay andy
I will just hold on. I this I like this. This is fun
legendary
Boy, all right legendary. Let's go
It's kind of weird. I just want to make a shitload of money to buy time to ten of these and like just get legendaries
Oh fish
Okay, let's go kind of play
variety pack
Oh lord, okay high five sly angle
What is this frenemy frenzy?
Oh, this is multiplayer
A lot of bounce friendship battle at this is like multiplayer shit
Here we go, mike red dr. Grygor
I gotta get to 50. No, that's open you dingus
Art equals what?
Art equals I don't I don't I don't get that one. I don't understand what it wants me to do
Again, let's go 40 at least
All right, all right that one's much I was making that way more complicated than I need to nice job puro
Jesus christ
I can't use puro. I like to use cutie scroll but I don't like it. All right, let's go place
Dislodge
I gotta get 50 just like
Why would you just like that video? It seems like mean
I get it. I find I get to with it, baby
Get him in the hole. Yeah, fucking what are you doing bro? What are you doing, bro?
Fucking fight
How did I get to 31 how the hell did that happen
How
Bottoms of both of my feet are itchy
Like I just scratch them
You're allergic to gaming
You're allergic to bad
All right remove this character from the
She's she's cool, but she sucks. No, what do you oh i'm going with orbulon
red
mike
Cricket and dr. Grygor come at me
right up
Hey
Fucking rock, but we need one dude. Do you guys like how?
You dick
Goddamn it. I have to get at least past 31. I have to get at least past 31
Can't not do this
I can't I can't I can't
I don't know what cat what are you talking about? They don't they're neither of them over there. Is it black?
I'm freaking out now
Losing fuck listen. I'm losing everything here
Don't miss
Okay, i'm going i'm doing one more
That's fine. Stupid. I shouldn't land. Why did I land on the top of that?
I'm going to video game world and i'm gonna get a high score
mike orbulon
And red my favorites
Hey germa, i'm going to sleep. Can you turn it down a little bit? Yeah, sure
Game over i'm gonna get to at least 35 in the yellow
I can't I can't go faster
It almost feels like too fast
Suck it up and drop it on him
I feel like it's too slow. 15 is gonna be so simple
defeat
This is like listening to a song normally after hearing the nightcore version
Jesus that's so funny
Did I do it
Don't get caught
Oh my goodness, okay, I accidentally got that right
This was always so easy
Just push that one up
Okay, this is where it gets real
You're foolish. You're kind. You're kind. You're kind
You're kind
Perfect tea time. What the hell was that?
What was that?
Which is greater
The original gameboy advance one. I don't know why that was me doing an accent
Don't lose life. So no reason. It's simple. Um, how would I capture the original gameboy advance?
I played there's a couple of them aren't there? There's like the ds one is the gameboy advance one
Play the gameboy advance one. I feel like I did
Did I it's on the wii u? Yeah, I think I know I did it. I did level up at least get the 10
Gameboy one was cool. Remember the big thing that hung off the cartridge
Attract your rotation
I never played it
I played the one that they ported to um, whatever console it was
I almost lost that one. I'm going for 50 at least. Oh god. I think you did
Oh, you almost tricked me. Oh
Go can't get 100
Whoa
All right. I'm like, oh mega concentrating. All right stupid
Spin it
Those are so hard the spin ones goodness
Jesus
You're just getting sounds today. Sorry. That's all you're getting. You're just getting noises and explanations. I can't do anything else
Oh, why just just beat it. Oh my goodness that scared the shit out of me. I thought he jumped at me
It's like when did that happen in those games?
All right, i'm going for the 50 probably get it. I'm gonna at least get to 50 to 60
Yeah, it's a great character here
good character here
You're trying to grow sideburns. No, it's a shame
Uh, I think it's uh, it's blue
Ooh, I suppose. Okay
I got a full life
Unto I need two
How do I stop the how do I stop the fucking thing just bump into it?
Throw some mutton chops. No
I swear to god like my whole body gets itchy when I have to play a game like this and not move ever played that game
Itchy andy, I don't know. It's I get like my stress goes up just get over here haven't played breath of the wild
No, I haven't
Oh, what was it?
Okay, I gotta get to 50 fuck you amuse me you amuse me you um, you amuse me you amuse me
Choking I was yeah, I still am
Force forget about getting coins just beat the mario level. This should be so simple for you
You don't have to do anything. You don't even play mario just glide to the exit
You used to have to put the game into a cartridge holder and go to a sub menu before you played the game to get shit like this
You can do this. Just fine
You can do 100 and all I care about is opening those eggs. They've got me. They've got me by the fucking for that game
Mario land used to you get you shot out of the little boat
I don't know. I don't know dude, dude, dude. I don't even know how to drop that
Okay, that one's gonna fail every time. I don't get that one. Like I I don't have a second to look at what the numbers are
What's game oh, okay
They got to 50 all right, we're going to all be long
This whole stream is me screaming and making sounds like i'm not even streaming right now
I'm i'm not even talking to you guys. I'm just like
Overacting and making sounds this is an entire broadcast
How we going with this team? You're sleeping right now. Stop saying that. I might think I am
All right, blink blink. I'm like like four minutes
Fuck up
I'll get the i'll get another life
I hate when people do that. I hate when people do that
Oh, I hate it like a crushed it's like an air guitar but cooler
I think they have both on the same exact
uh
playing field
Especially when they start like pretending like there's other drums, right? They start like going around and stuff and like up
like
Oh, you saw I you know what I mean?
What's firing?
What?
I feel attacked
This one's easy. I'm not afraid of this boss stage
Yes, I am
There's no time frame right? Oh my god, this is gonna suck
I want to do that with him again. All right, let's go full health four lives
Lavril 15
Air drum, you want to do a full air drum? All right
I'll put on a okay. You guys want to you guys want to fuck with new viewers?
You want you guys want to fuck with new viewers? Okay, so i'm gonna get a royalty free song
That's like with a bit like a lot of drums
I will i'm gonna full cam and just be like fucking like playing like air drums and like we're getting into it and shit
And i'll be like i'll put at the bottom like oh just taking a quick rock out break
Like how do I move this?
Oh like that. It's got to be weird. It's got to be wicked generic
It's got to be such a generic rock song with like a standard beat
You guys gotta give me I gotta get some hold on. I don't know. We'll do it. Everyone's quiet quiet
We don't we don't want to blow it
star equals
I have my I've not completed this one one time. I don't understand it. No one could ever explain it to me
Robot that was cool. Yeah, don't give it away
Okay
Acd I can't be a I have to be a royalty free song
Because I mean if you why would you be rocking out to like a generic royalty free song beat?
shit
Whoa?
Look up beginners drum beats, but I want to be a real song and i'm gonna try to do the whole song without fucking cracking
It's gonna be really hard
Why is it always this guy? I don't want to do it with him
I don't want to do it with this character
Then what does it want me to do?
Which one I don't know which one which one doesn't want me to do
But I don't understand which one
I get it. I know I get it. No do a song that doesn't have drums
We'll do that. Hold on one thing at a time one thing
We're not like a like beitrofen's orchestra and i'm just sitting there like
It's gonna be so embarrassing or whatever
It's worth it
All right. It's the one two three. I don't know which one it was one two three
This one good. Oh shit. Okay. That was I didn't even mean to do that
Do it to a carlon compilation
Oh fuck
Oh my god, that's difficult. It is
And we need to okay you guys also have to be spamming
Like sour, please and wait star
diamond
If I could click the button gary if I could click the button
He likes it
No, he doesn't like it. He's sad
No, not right now. I'm talking about when we do this
Rocking out later. Yeah, me too
This is gonna be the most you guys gonna hate this
They all fire
Give me 50. All right. Thank you. I'm not the stupid guy that sprays
Thank you
So much easier
Right wait
That was it took me a second
Yeah
No, I hate it. I hate it
All right, give me a fucking give me like a guitar solo
Taking quick rock out break read from file
What's the font should be like yeah like this and then the color should be
Let's look at what color
Okay, and the duck hat. Oh man. Okay, that's actually a great idea
That's perfect thank god
Okay, i'm gonna do this real quick
All right. I need some uh, we're gonna turn this music off
Okay, you guys ready? Let's get some songs in here
Uh, we have any any other any mods that can get it. Give me some songs
Something to work with rock out. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, we're not ready yet
All right royalty free rock music
No copyright
Oh
I don't think I can do this
I need a I need a couple ready to go. Where's the stupid hat?
Give me the hat. This is like weird and like funny, right? Like i'm crazy got this hat on
Oh, dude, I got this crazy. Oh, yeah, I got this hat on
I'm ready to go skiing have some hair peeking out the front
Oh
I can't
Uh, do this one. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. What is this one?
I need to hold on. I need to keep up
I have there's like the muscle shirt on this is perfect. I know I need rock music generic rock songs
All right. We gotta quickly get this rolled out before people come in
Can I just change the title and just go to irl and and am I like is that like to s can I just like change
Category for like five minutes. All right, let me we'll start. I need like a couple of generic ones in a row
Let's go here
royalty free
drum
Solo the home depot theme. No, no, you don't understand
I can't do the home depot. That's too that's way too obvious. This is way too obvious. This is the olive garden
This is just the olive garden. It's too obvious
When you're here your family
I can't do the olive garden. All right, hold on. Wait, wait, wait. We got some more do this one or this one this one
Shadow the hedgehog fuck
Okay. All right. All right. All right. Okay. I'm not doing that. I mean that's I mean maybe
All right, you guys you guys ready?
I have to not fucking break. This is gonna be really hard to not like fucking just crack. It's so stupid
All right. What is this? This is not royalty free. This is the song the hedgehog. What is this? Oh my god
I'm gonna lose my mind
It's my mind
This is not rock music. I need rock music
Royalty free rock music not this shit
Royalty free rock music. I'm just gonna pick some
Okay, how about this cinematic action rock royalty free rock music?
Okay, perfect. What about this one?
song
You guys are spamming links. All right, i'm gonna get going we're gonna do it. Why he was germa grandpa
All right. Here we go
I can't I don't think I can do it. I don't I really don't think I can do this
Everyone reset get back to zero
Okay, okay, I can try one more time I have to get the fuck away from the I have to get away from the microphone
Set back to zero back to zero to back to zero. Ah
All right, that was called a rock background music chill
I'm gonna move on to the next one. Thanks a lot. I got a lot of people here right now. This is crazy
Typically, I take a couple of breaks in my stream and kind of rock out man, you know for fun
It's like crazy. There's this many people it is crazy. Yeah, i'm in a band
What are you? Can you guess what I play?
Let's do another song drop my uh switch. Sorry choppy switch mo every musician keeps going
He's like pissed that i'm doing this
I have a one more one more one more one more. Sorry guys. I gotta go
I got band practice
One more. Oh, i'm out. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done turn it off turn it off. Please somebody said whiplash
I'm exhausted
How do real drummers do that for like four hours on stage?
Okay, that was fun. Uh, let's go back to playing wario wear, please
I pressed like a bunch of buttons and I I got here. I don't know how
Nice funko pop collection
Yeah, whatever. It's burnt. All right, let's go
Wait, so oh I threw the other uh, weemote
I put in damage my monitor. I don't think I did
Where is it? Yeah halfway through that auto. I just hear him sneezing
And he's just like looking at me and I look over and he's just like he's stretching on the ground with his tail wagging
Just like what the fuck are you doing?
We did all that to fool auto
Uh, like he's the one that got fooled by that
Let's go a bit of a drummer myself. It's a kind of rude response that I just have to you
Isn't it that was to just i'm not paying attention right like oh hey baba this this this this this
That's good. That's cool. That's crazy
That's crazy
Uh, anyways, what's up? What do you uh, what are you in the lobby yet?
That's fucking crazy dude, uh, are you in the game or because yeah, i'm in the lobby
I messed up my webcam
I can't
Why is my webcam so screwed up? Oh, it's because I cropped it a weird way, right?
That was stupid of me
Oh, no, no, no. I'm an idiot, right? I I have to turn this back on
Now i'm not gonna be in sync with the game
That's what i'm doing. Okay. There we go. That's better video games
All right, let's go for the big one
No, no, no, how do I oh, it's a pipe
Voices desync. No, it shouldn't be anymore
Is it still desync? I just changed it
Oh, no, I didn't I changed the wrong one. There you go. Now that's better. Sorry about that. Sorry about that
At least like level 50 i'm not gonna get 50, but you know, okay
Still bad. What that should be good
I I didn't change this did I? That should be fixed
Okay, but I let me just restart
Go back to rocking
So tomorrow i'm not ending the stream don't worry
Uh tomorrow we're gonna finish normal heroes three
We want to check out the finale of that game. We have probably like two or three hours left on that game
That's the plan tomorrow
I'm getting kind of hungry though. I'll probably maybe like another 20 30 minutes five hours
Ooh, that was close
Okay, here's uh five just two there's four there's five there's three there's two there's two
Eyes
I love the little crayon characters. I almost didn't get that. Come on
Whoa, he's hard. Yeah, that's a bad character
You're not there you're
This shit that was a blockade in the way, Jesus christ
Oh
Barely have to practice anymore
All right, I don't want to take the bomb guy then give me tea or be long
18 bolts and mike let's go
Let's dance
I'm gonna use a rock outbreak. Nah, i'm good. I'm good
Or we launch the best. I really think so that one's easy for him
Oh scissors beats paper I did
Um one two one two three four
Oh my god
It's not how you build a snowman you put his head on the bottom
Come on
We do it we do it we do it we do it we do it we do it I got the 38
Mike
Elon I don't like dr. Crygo 18. Well, it's fine
Jimmy was okay
Nine gold. Oh, I know why the usain is a desync. It's because of this
It's the my camera's fucked up. I can't fix it. I literally have to restart my computer
I gotta get the 10 without losing the light. It's really important. Yes, I thought it erased us
Why did I pick nine volt?
Maybe it's the wild card I need
Maybe it was pink poop. I don't know
Holy shit, it's so hard to do that. Uh, yeah
And how do you do that with this character by the way?
He's gotta go
You gotta go that guy that character has to go. No way
I'm not doing period. He's bad actually kind of like dog
Get to 10 with no lives lost
Okay
You're rocking be happy already
Oh
I had it. I had it. That's what fucked me up
Get in there do it. I thought I'd shoot him in his nose. I thought I should write his nose
Hmm
All right, I got to 41 I can do it. All right, only two or three more tries
I'm not looking over here anymore
Whoa
Oh
My funny bone. Oh my funny bone my funny bone. I just hit my funny bone. My arm is dumb
My arm is numb. My arm is numb. Oh my god
Okay, i'm all right i'm okay, all right
Motherfucker does
All right slow, um, relax jeremy. It's not a problem. It's just relax
You don't have to like scream
It's fine. Just play with the characters you did it with before
And do it
There'll be consequences
Actually like
I'm gonna get 15 without getting hurt. I don't even know i've never seen that before
Here we go this one's for you
Smash this fucking thing
That is on
Looks furious i'm not curious. Okay, this is the one I know it is this is the one right here
No more fucking around this is the one
Ashley don't ever take ashley out of the party. Why?
Oh my i'm alive though. You can't break an orange. Oh my fucking god
I'm leaning back. I'm just gonna lie back like this
Underwear stuck to my ass
God, it's gonna take a goddamn robot to get it off
Why doesn't the basket move
The basket don't move man
I hate that one
That's not a
God damn fucking close
That was so goddamn close
That's impossible with that character
The fucking ufo is over me
It's just you don't even give me a fucking goddamn moments notice 47. Oh my god, it's so close. It's killing me
Damn it 47
All right, let's go great
Goddamn gamer, let me show you my eyes are watering. I'm a gamer. Yeah
I'm a monster i'll show you a monster
Here
Tick tock he's emo. I thought if I pulled that out that would be great
All right, if it's I gotta I gotta go I gotta stop screaming. I'm done
I'm done. I'm done. I'm gonna play like the funny open at the ball game thing and then i'm done
He did ate it
Here
You only need one life to win just need one to win
What the fuck
I have so much money close your eyes. God damn
Touch no more mistakes
No more mistakes
Read my lips
No new mistakes
I don't even know if they're fucked up
This happens so fast it's so hard to it happens so quickly that like you're just gonna get caught up
Like you're gonna get caught up going the wrong way. You know what I mean? Like i'm gonna get you're gonna get caught going the wrong fucking way
It's over
All right, this is my last attempt and then i'm done i'm not doing it again
You guys just burning money if you vote for me more like that, please you fucking come on
You're fucking kidding me
There's three
My god, it's not gonna happen man. This shit is impossible
This shit is impossible
It's the fact that you have to change character and I and I don't know what the half of these goddamn games are
I like some of them fly some of them don't fly some of them fucking move. Some of them don't move
Some of them have guns some of them don't have guns
One more I mean it and i'm gonna watch i'm gonna do it fucking backwards
It looks like it was the same color as the other one. I'm gonna okay. This is my okay. That's it. I'm out of gas i'm gone
I'm literally out of energy i'm done i'm toast i'm it's like i'm cooked my goose is cooked i'm done
Okay, when I got to 47 that was literally six months of my life that I just deleted
It's gonna happen. It's gonna happen right now
Three no, not four. I didn't want to hit it more than what I didn't want to hit it
What
That one doesn't count it actually doesn't that one actually does not count you're right
That one doesn't count that was just a warm-up
Please
What
I fucking hate it
Maybe you should try easy
Damn it. I've got people to feed here. You love helicopters. Take it
You go higher than president
presidential suite
Let's do like
You like cameras? No. No, you don't really like cameras that much
Uh
Wait, you're the 47th floor guy
Ooh headphones
What do you like?
How about a shower cap?
47 is good, but certainly not 50
Oh, yeah
That's what you think
Okay, that's what that's what you think
I don't understand that one
I'm done. I'm out of matter. I'm leaving
Okay, how about we just go with the fuck face team because it doesn't matter i'm not gonna win so let's do whatever
Here we go. Not bad. Oh, I get it now
No doggy
She's holding a what I thought I was talking about me
Okay, that's enough, um, that's enough i've had enough i've had enough one more
This is my final attempt
the last one if I don't get it here then I am going to
Walk out last one. This is the fuck. This is literally the last one if I do another one
I will literally okay if I do another one after this I will give a thousand community subs, okay?
I
Couldn't tell the difference
I have to stop
God damn it. God damn it. I want to do it so bad
Yes
All right, so i'm not gonna do that one right that but i'm not i'm not gonna do that one again
I can play the other one
I can do this one
It's for this one. It's not for the it's not for any of the other levels in the game
Double or nothing for five more attempts. No way, dude, that's five thousand sub
I'm not doing that
Okay, but does that count? I need I need to like a general consensus. Does that count?
If I were to do a different level
That doesn't count. It's only that crazy one that i'm trying to get 50 rounds on
No, i'm just gonna play
I'm done. I'll see you tomorrow. I'll see you tomorrow. I'm gonna play no more heroes three tomorrow
And then when I beat no more heroes three tomorrow, it's only gonna take like a couple hours to get through that
I'm getting to 50 tomorrow
I'm getting to 50 tomorrow after no more heroes three
Well, what should I give this for a rating?
um
Okay, here we go. Is it so the rating of this game?
First of all, thanks to the subs everybody all the resubs all the new subs all of you
Some of you might be brand new some of you have been here for 10 years. Thanks guys. Really appreciate it
Maybe we'll see you tomorrow for no more heroes three finale and uh get to level 50 in super hard on wario wear
I'm gonna get some food. I've been okay. Well here you go. I've had a lot of fun with it
I still want to play so that's a good indicator
Uh, it was probably like a six and a half or a seven out of ten
until I realized that you could collect those coins and feed your
Crew I think that became a solid eight something after that like an 8.2 the actual video game. I think
It was a little short, but I think was the other one. I feel like the other one was longer
I feel like smooth moves was a longer game
Just with more mini games and stuff. Maybe i'm just completely wrong, but um, I think it's really good
I'm like i'm watching this cutscene
What am I talking about? I'm talking about warrior wear smooth moves being a longer game than this one
I remember playing it for a little longer. They have insanely short story, but tons of post game shit
Yeah, I think I'd have to play it a little bit more to figure that out
This one seems it has like daily challenges and stuff. That's really cool. Yeah, I think it's it's great
Way better than game in wario by a thousand times this game has about 20 more micro games than smooth moves
You know what? I think it is. I think that like the wiimote
Moving around the wiimote and doing stuff with the wiimote felt a little more involved
Than jumping with a 2d character to like turn a knob with your character on the screen
I think that's maybe what what i'm thinking of there when i'm seeing it like that
I I think the concept is great. It's actually a really really cool concept
It throws your brain off even more than the original games. Yeah, i'll see you tomorrow. Take care of yourselves. Goodbye
Tomorrow normal heroes 3 finale by the way, if you haven't seen normal heroes 3 and you want to play it yourself
Be careful on tomorrow's first couple hours of the stream because it's literally the last like two or three hours of the whole game
So we'll see you tomorrow. Good night. Goodbye
My voice is shot because i've been screaming it's literally been a scream stream. I hope you've been enjoying it
I hope you've been enjoying it. Yes. That's what I was trying to say
I'll see you guys tomorrow
Good night. Goodbye
See you later