How many how many like mini Milky Way candy bars do you think it takes to make like one candy bar?
You know I'm talking about I would say five. Oh shit. Yeah
I've eaten like fucking 19
Does that mean I've eaten like four candy bars, all right, so that's not good
Hunted what was this game? What's called hunted? Yeah, I think so
So it's probably a terrible idea for me to try to jump. No, I'm not doing that screw that
I'm not jumping up on like one of the tents. Ah
Somebody's real trigger happy who was just shooting their gun. Yeah, I just hear somebody just bang bang bang bang. Somebody's in trouble
Oh, okay. Okay. No, okay. Probably should not have just done that. Oh my god
What
I showed you like three times in the chest and you're telling me you golf club being like the forearm and I die
So where are you where the talks? Where are you right now? I want I'm gonna give you some hints
No, just give me one hint on where you are. There's grass. Just grass. That's a great hint. It's Alex. Very very good hint
I appreciate the hint. There's more tense than we were
Next to you. I'll say that much describe the tents to me in detail. What do they smell like what?
Give me some landmarks and some like sightseeing that you could potentially like close to me or something
No, I don't know. Am I I don't know. I was just trying to figure out why you're focusing on me specifically
I know like
No, who wants to do a duel who wants to play let's play Marco Polo, okay, who wants to play
Marco
Okay Marco
No, you're further away
Marco, I didn't even hear that bullet. So you didn't
No, it don't matter because you know games. Oh
It don't matter because the game's over
What
Hold on that was that was not out correct
Cuz we were playing I thought I thought that was coming from that direction
I'll give you I'll give you a few you gotta do the same
Do I yeah you do that's a real come on
Are you really gonna break the Marco Polo rope? I did way more than that. Whatever. You can still hear the directions
There you go. He's just like hunting us both. Yeah boo. He's been like dead silent this whole time
I'm shooting as well. Yeah stealth is a zombie. I feel like he's this person behind me
Like this one right here. Oh
Son of a bitch is that stealth right there?
Um, I need to alright you need to do polo again like 30 more times. Oh my god
God what I really close. I don't know. No
Boo, where are you?
Damnit damn it. I don't wanna kick all that way going this way. Whoo. I just can't can't be seen
Give me give me give me
shit
Come on, the fucking grenade didn't explode. I wish we could use the phone. I
Think I'm near someone how nervous is this making you jammer? Really nervous. What makes you more nervous using the phone?
I'm buzzing someone nearby or not using the phone and thinking shit. Maybe someone's near but
Is that you trying to tell me something boo? Are you in fact nearby right now?
Did you see some asshole with a crossbow walking around?
No
Yeah, you did. Where are you? Are you by the balloons? You definitely by the balloons?
Yeah, I'm like a party
No, boo's dead boo is dead and I don't want to waste my crossbow on something. So, you know what?
I'm gonna just you know, I can take
I'm gonna get rid of all the zombies in this house
Just because I know boo could potentially be one of them. I hear a lot of screaming. There's plenty of dog food
That's you
Is it was that you
Right that was you right or you just bluffing are you just bullshit me right now
Is this you
Okay, get me out I don't know play anymore I don't play this game anymore
Okay, I don't know if you're in there or not, but you might be you probably are yes you are
I might have got you. We're playing that game
I haven't seen anybody for like five minutes. Yeah, right. Oh shit in my pants shit in my pants crossbow
Get crossbow
God show yourself again. I dare you
Come on go show yourself again don't act like you're not gonna get wait a minute worry
I think I just saw a movement. I may or may not have seen movement
Hello hiding in the dark, I see I know where you are. I didn't even see you until I was waiting
I was waiting there in the attic. I saw Jerma's panic attack underneath me when he was shooting zombies
And I was just gonna wait for him to come up in the attic, but he never you ran out of the house, dude
I've got that was terrifying. I just see the guy like in the window firing at me speaking of guys
Like busy telling a story
Yeah, I should have crossbowed you I'm like already dying
Oh my yeah, I really am too. What the hell is that?
Already, I can't get out of the door
Okay, I get me out of here. Is there a kind of climb this ladder? Thank God
This place I spawned with a ton of zombies around me
I know I've trapped myself. Hey whoa whoa whoa easy easy
Who killed me?
I spawned with like ten zombies underneath me climb up a ladder and get shot in the face and fall down ladder and die
Great. You had your flashlight on
You should have like a flashlight on around
No, I've learned my lesson. No more flashlights unless it's necessary
Unless it is totally necessary
What am I gonna do with a pocket light?
In fact, it might be necessary right now
What can I loot?
Oh that is a ladder
Right when I turn it on really? Who's up there? Who is up there? Are you on a roof?
Where are you?
I saw those traces coming down from like the top. Yeah, they're on the roof. They're on the roof
How did you get on the roof? You are legitimately you are like spider-man on the roof
Do you sling some fucking web to get up there?
That was bullshit