I just barely cleared my throat, and I saw it. I was just choked on my throat.
Thank you Kazzy for the 10 subs. Congratulations to all of you that got one. Now you can spam
Germamoon like I do. I think I've only done Germamoon like three times in the last year.
Is there like data on that? When was the last time I did Germamoon? One of you guys has like the data
somewhere. Wait, wait, what did I say? Like 10 times? No, I'm not gonna type that all out.
I'm not like you guys. I don't have the, I don't have the keywords for, I don't have like keystrokes,
key mapped. I don't do any of that. I type it out. I actually physically type out like Germamoon,
and then I copy it and paste it. Me too? I'm not the only one? Good. But hope you're having a good
day. Welcome back. If you were here last night, good morning. But it's, it's almost four o'clock,
so it's not the morning anymore. But anyways, how are you? We're gonna do some DOS tonight.
Pick back up, because I really do enjoy this so much. Playing these DOS games is seriously
like one of my, it's one of my like most favorite things to add to the stream. I,
I get energy off of this shit. I like live off of these old fucked up games.
How am I feeling? I'm feeling pretty good. And then tomorrow we're gonna do Terraria again.
Mr. Star is gonna boot his server back up, and we're gonna kind of pick up what we left off there.
And then Sunday, I have not decided what's gonna happen on Sunday, but I'm probably not gonna
stream, because I have to leave. I have to be, I have to really get ready, because it's a very
important trip early next week. Leave, leave. He's going to Texas. No, Texas. No. For those of you
that were not here yesterday, I will go briefly. And then I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I gotta make
one of those exclamation point carnival, just so I can have like a clip of me talking about it.
Remember when I was moving to Vegas? All right, somebody clip this. Ready?
I gotta kill the audio here. Hold on. I'm gonna get this in one shot.
Hey, you clicked this because you're probably wondering why somebody wrote a hashtag carnival
in the stream chat. Let me tell you. September 21st is the carnival stream. Well, the carnival
stream, you know, the one that I talked about previously of you guys controlling twitch
controlled robots to play all kinds of fun midway games and carnival games, including
dunking me in a dunk tank. That's right. You ruined it. Yeah, you gave $50. That was going so well.
And then I Oh, you guys didn't hear the sound. I did. There's not even any any
message here. I said hashtag. Oh, fuck. But all jokes aside, that was mandem requiem.
50 bucks. Thank you so much. $50. You cut me off. But I will take a $50 cut off.
Because that's an insane amount of money. Thank you. The clip is fucked up now.
Here we go. I'll give you like an easy one. September 21st 2019 is a day for
you to remember. That's the set in stone carnival stream date. The one where you're
going to have fun with robots at a twitch controlled carnival stream. That's right,
you're going to be in control. September 21st 2019. Maybe we'll see you there. And up until then,
I'm going to be traveling back and forth to a different state to make sure I get this
thing hammered down completely. So you might see streams pulled back, you might see streams
canceled up until the 21st. But you'll know in advance. Don't worry about that. I'm jumping
down. I'm spending I'm working on it. I'm working on it. And I'm putting time into it. Thank you
for listening. All right, there you go. This is I don't care. Just use that one. I'm not going to
redo that one. I'm almost fine. This is not the Vegas one again. I just use the first one and
just like cut it. He's doing the Disneyland safety guide voice. Yeah, that's the voice acting voice.
Make sure to keep your arms and hands inside the vehicle. And by any means, do not get out of the
ride. Do not take any photos with flash photography. And do not take off your shoes. Too many people
been doing that lately. Keep them on. This is not a red eye from Boston to LA. Anyway. Hey, look at
that. Look what's on the screen right now. Well, not right now. In a second. Hold on. Just wait.
You'll see it. No, you know, fuck it. No, no, no, no. No, fuck it. We're just going to open up this
one. Yeah. Here we go. We're going to open. This is streamers choice. I remember the last couple
times we've done this. It's been streamers choice. Streamers choice is going to be tubing.
You heard it here first. Tubing. All right, you can open your eyes now.
Tubing. Published by Dumark. Limited IBM version. Written by Hank Gecko. Okay. VGA.
This is the song. Cut it. Cut it. Cut it. This is the song that in my mind is what it sounds like
when your computer gets a virus. I need to turn this down. Just go. All right. There we go. We're
fine. Tubing. Is this an arcade game? How do I move? W-A-S-D. Hey, what did I tell you about
keeping your shoes on? How do I move? J-K-L-V-D-B-M. Space. Q. Okay. Q is turn. Q. Okay. I tilted my
body a little bit. I'm just like in the lazy river. Oh, those are beers. I think those are
like beer cans. All right. Hold on. A is turn. S maybe. Hold S. Okay. I'm dead. I have to paddle.
Oh my God. I actually do. Throw the beer can at it. This is so sloppy. Why am I going this fast?
They did this shit in Super Mario RPG. That's where they got it from. I remember this exact
thing happening in Mario RPG. Guys, you have to hold it. You don't have to tap it. You just hold
it. Hey, quit fishing. Oh, come on. Come on. Let me like throw like a beer can at a fisherman.
That's so fucking stupid. What a menace to society this guy actually is. I didn't bring any safety
equipment. I love how it stretches out a little more. Those fish. A thousand points. I got them.
How do I get to the end? All right. I got to stay up front. That's how you win these ones.
Oh my God. Okay. That was kind of scary. You can get eaten by an alligator. Okay. Um, that was
called tubing. You are a top shot tube, dude. Enter your initials. Pretty good. Top shot tube, dude.
Biff. Well, that was that one. Uh, we're going to move on from this one. I don't know. This one
might take us a while. I don't know. I saw, I remember got streamers choice to start this out.
This one, uh, I never played it, but some of you probably have another virus song. Oh shit. This is
going to be as complicated. I thought you were going to, I thought you just had to like diagnose
somebody. This is too complicated. Yeah. We're going to have to sit here for like an hour to
do a tutorial. Wait, what? As a carpool passenger, relax and daydream your way to work. Then reality
in the form of a truck smacks into you. You're not seriously hurt, but you go to the hospital.
Wait, I'm the patient. You spend hours in a waiting room. You fill out a thousand forms.
You finally see it. Don't wait. After I got in a car accident, you're poked, prodded and rushed
through the system. They take blood run tests and send you away. You feel mistreated and out of
control. Time goes by your bruises heal. You put the whole experience behind you. Then the bill
shows up. What did they do? Who said they could do that? Shouldn't insurance cover this? Enough
is enough. You decide to run from public office on the platform of healthcare reform. Click the small
box in the upper left of this window to continue. Okay. Am I alive? I thought this was sim health.
Ah, how do I turn this off? Hold on. I can turn this off. Oh, it's like specifically designed
to hurt your ears. Before you can be elected to office, the voters need to know who you are,
what you stand for, what you believe in, your personal values. I thought this was a surgery
game. The values window will show you a number of statements. You rate how much you agree or
disagree with each statement from your answers. Sim health will establish your personal values.
Why is this game like 30 years ago and like 30 years in the future? This is some weird
shit here. Okay. Your constituents and the simulation will judge you not by the values
you select, but how well you stick to them. Okay. Why? Wait, why? I thought this is a health game.
Sim health defines personal values as a balance between four ideals, liberty, equality, community,
and efficiency. Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah. All right. Individually, each of these four ideals sounds
great, but you can't have it all. Completely supporting anyone takes away from the others.
So I got hit by a truck and decided to run for president? Is that what happened? Okay. Liberty
and equality are at the opposite poles. The more liberty you have, the less equality. Community
and efficiency are also opposing forces. As you choose your values, consider how the four different
ideals can work together. Okay. Now what? You've represented with four conditions. Oh God. No,
I don't, you're not going to do, you know, I'm not going to play like the saw game right now.
You have four choices. Each one describing four crisis points. Make your choice. I don't know
if I want to do this. In the first room is a man who's just like you was hit by a car,
choosing him, removes both of his legs. In the other room, two families, one of which
shit the bed last night. What are you, what, make no choice. I don't, I'm not doing this.
Yeah, that joke was ruined because I couldn't come up with like a safe way to have to have
you press the button on the family. You know what I mean? Like I had to abort that one.
There's no, like there's no way I could have, I could have turned that around.
I had to, I had to get that away from that one. All right. Anyways, let's go. I'll do one.
I'm fucking out of this. I'm not doing this. I'm not exploring the United States healthcare system.
Oh, was that the Willy Wonka song? Willy Wonka, the famous chocolatier. Hey,
this is the same song.
This is a binaural beats in my fucking head. Mr. Three, the bomber, dead eye. Mr. Three,
skill level one. Target. Yeah. Hello and welcome to the All-Star Basketball Association's three
point shooting championship. I'm Skip Smiley. The world's best shooters are here to settle once
and for all. That guy on the right can't believe he's on camera. The winner will have his name
engraved on the championship trophy alongside the name of last year's champ. Okay. That guy
clearly didn't have any lines. He just won the, that guy won the contest to be on stage with the
guy that people think is cool. All right, here we go. Joining me is the ever exciting Rick Vitality.
He will be giving us expert analysis as the championship goes on. Glad to be here, Skip.
It's going to be three point city, baby. Without any further ado, let's have a look at this year's
field. Same guy. Just that's the same guy. Here's the thing. I got to show this on camera. Same guy,
except the one difference is he turned his mouth to the side. Is it you go from this to this,
all you do is just turn your mouth. Is it just like tilt your mouth and talk out of the side of your
mouth. I didn't turn the face cam on. Whoops. Oh, well that looks like a strong field to me.
What do you think, Rick? This is going to be an exciting tournament. We should see some
fantastic shooting. Any predictions for the first round, Rick? Barclay might as well pack his bag.
You know, the muffins, when some muffins have the guy underneath with the real hands,
that he is out of his league. It's two puppeteers.
We'll win easily. Long Poppin' is going to say bye bye to Johnson. No problem at all.
I'll take Thomas in a close one over, Mr. Three. Anything you say, Rick. Well, let's go down to
the court as the first round is ready to begin. Okay. Bald Barker. This is not me.
We don't have to sit here and actually watch this, right?
Deal. I'm playing that fucking dumb game. All right, let's go. I got pretty bad picks so far.
I'm not gonna lie. The first two, three games, pretty bad picks. Let's see if I can pull this
out here with... This one might be all right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Why did I pick... No,
I didn't. I didn't do like more of these, did I? It's another fucking politics game. It better not
be. How was I... Look, the name of this game is Floor 13. Not anything to do with like politics.
I thought this was gonna be like a scary game or like a point and click horror game or something.
What? Okay. How do I go? Welcome new DG. Decor style. Modern or traditional?
Modern. Please type the name... Please type your name in block capitals.
I'm sorry. I mean, I do appreciate the fact that you give me the form, but I'm...
It's kind of a sleazy way to give me your Mario Maker level. I don't do that,
but thanks for the deed to the house. I appreciate it. That's not how I sign. Okay.
Surveillance. Four removal. Two assassins. Pursuit four teams. Look,
did anybody understand anything that's going on? Search three parties. Interrogate. Two cells.
$100,000 in funds. Good morning, sir. It's New Year's Day. There's a new report in for you.
All right. I don't even open the door. I go home. Hey, you're the new DG. Oh dear. Well,
don't come back here unless I ask you and use the back entrance and don't draw attention to
yourself unless you enjoy flying. I want to see results in three weeks. Is it on my house?
Okay. Let's go in the office. Read reports. See polls. Suspects. Groups. All right. Okay.
Them and us. Sure. Anyways, let's read the report. Please note that the food mixer stolen from L1
Division Military Research Observatory is still abroad. Security considers ex-stockkeeper Dave
Holtz as possible breach entry point. L1 security officer, officer Mr. Philip Owen,
has not implemented any investigation. It's a real slow week. Next report. There he is.
Smokes a pipe and a frequent party-goer. Suspected affiliation to the National Union
of Municipal Workers. Okay. Security officer for the L enjoys jogging. Frequent party-goer.
Okay. Mr. James Radcliffe, leader of the Hackney Council, has declared the London Borough a
nuclear-free zone. The nuclear train carrying waste through the Capitol may have to be diverted.
He wants a nuclear-free zone. Likes folk music. Okay. Give orders. Pursuit. Search.
He stole the coffee maker. We're going in for a heavy assault. That was her re-gift.
Uh, it's about 6, 6, 11 p.m. All in the hour. That's what, that's what jeopardy reruns the day
tomorrow. Wait, wait, wait. What? We're going, like, how many, like, people are going?
Is this, like, an FBI thing? Is this an FBI thing? Or is this, is this an FBI thing?
Okay. Give orders. And let's, uh, interrogate. Um, abduct Radcliffe in order to prepare for
interrogation. May take up to three days. And search. Just ransack the place. So, I'm gonna,
when do these happen? This is, like, we're just fucking, fucking up this whole guy's life.
And then, uh, how do I, like, get away from, I don't want to, oh, okay, I'm on the same file.
Okay, hold on. What about, uh, is that it for reports? Um, all right, leave reports. Let's
take a look at the polls, see if we get a chance. What about, what is groups? Oh, okay.
It's not even the right guy. Suspect. It's not even the right guy.
Okay, it's time to leave desk. No, no, no, no, leave desk. Go to the department. Go to the,
hold on. What do you mean, go to the department? Let's go back to my door. There's a new report
in for you. It's the next day. Okay, there's a new, um, is that it? Did we, did we find him?
Good morning, sir. There's some new reports for you. The Prime Minister will see you tomorrow
morning. Interest arrested in Paris. Time to get a hold of high tech equipment. All right.
So, um, wait, what happens? No, he's already dead. What? That's so fucking stupid.
What is it? I don't even understand. Okay, we're gonna, let's interrogate. No. All right,
go back. Go, I want to see the other suspects. There. Okay, give orders.
Uh, pursuit. Okay. This is like, what I'm doing right now is what happens when your cat runs over
your keyboard. It's like, oh shit, Jesus, I can't change it. We already went through. Uh, thank you
too. Call me bomb for the 50 bucks. 5,000 bits just came in. 5,000 bits. They say, hey man,
I'm not great at Twitch. Just want to send you a little something. You've helped me deal with the
stress of nursing school and now I'm an actual pediatric nurse. There you go. Hell yeah. You
help a lot of people and you mean a lot. You mean a lot to us as well. Thanks for all the laughs,
buddy. Also dodge right when you fight the abyss walkers in Dark Souls 3. Thanks.
Always dodge left. Have to dodge left every time, but congratulations. That's awesome.
Actual. I told you guys, doctors are in here. Everybody. Everybody talks about, hey man,
you always bring up how there's doctors in your chat. Uh, we got another person in the medical
field here. Nurse, doctors, scientists. Uh, thank you. Prime minister says, ah, don't attack people
with high public profiles or the chattering classes will start asking questions. Get serious. We'll
start flying lessons. I don't know what that means. And why am I not allowed in his house?
No, no, no, no, no. Stay here. See operations. Suspect under surveillance. Suspect being tailed.
Address marked for assault. All right. I think I've had enough of this one is to
eliminate. I might as well just see what happens. I want to see what the prime minister means.
Phone rings. Hey, my phone in my office. Hello. Uh, this is the interrogation department here.
We feel it may be a little pointless abducting Mr. James Radcliffe as corpses don't do much
talking. Yes. I'm very sorry about that. My cat ran across my keyboard. Oh, okay. No,
that happens over here too. All the time. Yeah, I know it sucks. All right. Goodbye. Bye. I need
to go to, is he still alive? All right. Let's, what happens when you just get, okay. Well,
what happens if you just get rid of everybody? Wait, no, no, interrogate, interrogate. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Stop. No, don't. Okay. Tail him. This is like a Pee Wee Herman
skit going on right now. First we stab him and then we grab him and then we kill him. I say we
let him go. Next, come on. All right. Give orders. What the fuck was that? All right. Search.
Make sure you do it a couple times and then like do it sneakily because we're going to like trash
this guy's place and then after like a day or so he's going to put out all the good stuff out
and then we're going to go in there and do it discreetly and find it. All right. Let's go.
There's some new reports for you. I mean, we might as well just see this to the end
because this is... I'm doing like a fucking clown show right now. Wait, what? Uh, hold on a second.
Dave Holtz. Suspect leaves. Suspect returns at... Okay, so he went to work.
All right. He got up in the morning. He left to go to work. At 5 30 he came home from work.
At 6 51 after taking a shower, he went back to... Oh, no, no, he left. He probably went out somewhere
like the grocery store. At 8 p.m. we attacked his house while he was at the grocery store
or out to dinner and then he came back at nine. Why did we not get a reaction here? What does
that mean? Attacked? Premises attacked? Did we just like drop a fire out of his house?
Is he going to be like upset about this? The police have puzzled this. The reason for the
military-style attack on the home of Dave Holtz. We set up like turrets and like fired a fire. This
is the guy that's been dead for like four days, by the way. This guy is in the morgue right now
and I guess, unfortunately, who fortunately was not there at the time. All right, well,
let's go. Lead reports. Suspects. How would you not be suspicious of this right now? All right,
give orders that we're going to pursue. Yeah, just follow them around. That's fine.
I can't like do... Can I actually... What about removal? What does that mean? Removals?
No, no, no. Removals. Immediate removal. You can't ruin the public standing. Just run like a smear
campaign on the guy. Like this is... That's terrible. All right, I'm gonna leave. We're
currently... What about this? Lead desk. Next day. There are loads of new reports in for you. Uh-oh.
This is the part of the show when there's a big... Everything is dark and there's one giant floodlight
on the door and I'm standing way in the back and it's one big light on the door and there's really,
really creepy, nervous music playing. Loads of new reports. Okay.
Exclamation point. Removal department here. Mr. James Radcliffe already dead.
Mr. James Radcliffe already dead. Somebody typed that up real fast and didn't put proper
punctuation or spacing or anything. Stop doing that. He's dead. I can't do anything. Uh-oh.
The PM will see you tomorrow morning. I can just imagine... That's like, that's like an old person,
right? When they're writing. I come tomorrow. Pick up. They just want to get their point across.
I come tomorrow. Pick up. Food. Are you hungry? That's like, that's like, like my father talks.
Subject, okay. Subject leaves home, returns home. Subject leaves home. Subject returns subject
of 3 a.m. We got a new spot. Subject leaves home, goes to Whitehall, returns home, leaves home.
Subject arrives at Frog Street. Suspect or location file attached. Okay. So the search party found
nothing of interest at the home of Mr. Philip Bone. The search party found nothing of interest at the
home of Mr. Philip, but we left the place in a mess. That's okay. Interrogation report.
Prisoner in cell, Dave Holtz. Where is your headquarters? There isn't one. Are you
involved in a conspiracy? I have rights, you know. Are you a member of a secret society?
Do you know who you're talking to? Whoever's doing the interrogating is not really doing a great job.
You don't start with, are you involved in a conspiracy? You find that out. You figure that
out. Inactive. Oh, because it's very, very, being tailed. Uh, different disinformation unit.
So what does that do? We're just going to like lie about, we're going to spread like a social
media like rumor about him or something that he like, what are we doing? Are we like spreading
rumors, lies? Are we doing like a campaign? I don't understand what that means. Propaganda?
Yeah, get rid of that. Let's do, um, yeah. All right, let's go. Next day. Next day.
Oh, yes. The thing slides. Oh, you're welcome. Yes, sir. I just had the palace on the phone.
I don't want to your dirty work getting into the papers or your history. Do you know what
happened to the last TG? Slide. Okay, bye. It's like the fucking the land of Oz. Let me in the
house. I'm invested. Oh, we're still interrogating this guy. Where's your HQ? What do you intend to
do with that? So you have an HQ. What is your name? Dave Holtz. Who's your contact? I won't talk.
Where's your headquarters? What do you intend to do with that? Means I have a headquarters.
But why would I tell you? All right. Yeah, he's he's gonna talk. Suspect under interrogation.
Suspect focus of smear campaign. Suspect under surveillance. Okay. All right. Now keep it up.
That's all right. Let's go. Interrogate. That signature was made in MS paint.
Disinformation department here. Mr. Philip Owen has already been smeared. We can't risk the
suspicion another campaign might arouse. Okay, fine. Fine. It's more. Okay. Next report. Here we
go. Subject subject has been held for two days. Somebody's looking worn down. What is your name?
Dave Holtz. What are you? Are you involved in a conspiracy? What do you remember of a secret
society? All right. We're gonna have to let him go. How do I let him go? interrogate remove
removal? Can I like remove him from the interrogation room?
Interrogate. Like, no, no, no, no, abduct him. Abduct him. He's already here. All right, abduct
him again. All right, we're gonna we're gonna you're gonna do you're gonna like put like a
like cover it like blindfold him. And then you're gonna like spin him around a couple circles,
walk him out the door, walk him out and back into the door. Take him like on a car ride,
and then put him back in the same room. All right, and then let's do it again.
What's this guy doing? And then we're gonna bring this guy in and convince him he's the other guy.
Okay, let's see what happened. What? Interrogation department here. We're not actually sure where
Dave Holtz is. Oh, sorry, I recognize that picture. That suspect is already here.
The Prime Minister of fucking Munchkinland. We'll see you tomorrow morning.
Subject leave, subject return, subject leave, subject return, subject abducted. Did it? Hold on
a minute. Are you involved in a conspiracy? What? Are you a member of a secret society?
The National Unit of Municipal Workers are hardly a secret. Okay, where's your headquarters? There
isn't one. Okay. So, so we've got to let him go. We can we've got to let him go. Prisoner in cell
two, Mr. Philip Owen. Are you involved in a conspiracy? Up yours piss head? Who do you work
for? Doesn't say anything. What's your name? Ask my mother. Huh, okay. Give orders. Infiltration.
What is infiltrate? Oh, wait, infiltration? 100 agents.
Okay. So what you mean to say is, all of us, it's just only going to be cover agents. We're
all going to be like winking at each other and like bumping into each other like the coffee maker.
100 fucking cover agents at this place that probably only has what like 100 people in it.
Let's go. It's 250. We're going to make up a significant portion. But okay, if this 250,
what happens when 100 people get hired? We all have to get hired. How do you we can't infiltrate
that many? Does the National Union of Municipal Workers plan on expanding their workforce by like
35%? We're creating jobs. We're creating like fake inflated jobs. Okay, let's go.
Infiltration in progress. All right, let's see the polls. Oh, oh, oh, oh, we're, we're,
we're four points behind. That was 50 more dollars that came in. A lot of money coming
in today, guys. Seriously. Thank you for that. This is like another 50 fucking dollar drop.
This is from Jay Zanye West. Thank you for the 50 bucks. Due to work, I'm away from family and
friends a lot. My girlfriend and I watch your streams and content together. So watching while
I'm on the road makes me feel a little closer to home. Thanks for the amazing content. PS What
are the odds of a scare Saturday's reboot? Well, first of all, thank you. That's I'm happy that
you guys have something to connect. If it's here, if it's this community, if it's this stream, then
that makes me fucking happy. Being away from people that you love is hard. But as I'm really
happy that you and your girlfriend have that. So thank you. What are the odds of a scare Saturday
is coming back? Pretty much I would say probably zero chance. Because I would just play any new
horror game that comes out regardless. I don't think it has to be like on a set day. But I just
want to be completely and totally just open about that scare every day. So you're saying that there
is a chance there is a chance. But I really do. Oh my god. I do appreciate the $50 on top of the
other $50 that La Cranda just gave right now. Holy shit, guys. All right. Thank you La Cranda
for the 5000 bits. It took me three weeks to save up this money. I won't have enough to pay the bills
after this. But the streamer needs money. You better be paying the bills first. You better you
better be paying the bills like five times over before you give me a cent. But thank you so much
for the $50 fucking dollars. Both of you, all of you. All right, let's uh, okay, let's see what
happens tomorrow. Let's we're gonna we're infiltrating with our hundred person agent team.
Uh oh, this guy's got a lot of threats. Let me do this thing again. Remember this? Hey,
you're becoming a serious liability. Questions are being asked in the house. Do you want to
follow the last DG? Get serious or start flying. Let's see what happens. To the shredder. For
security reasons, all references to the following will be removed from our current records.
Mr. James Ratcliffe. Okay, because he's been he's been dead for like five days. All right.
Infiltration report. All assigned agents penetrated. They were on a hiring boom.
Number of agents successfully penetrated. A hundred. Initial penetration successful. Infiltration
has risen to over 25% of core membership. Now what the fuck do you want us to do? Because
a couple of issues have arisen and I'm going to bring up very briefly. Because there's so many of
us, we all try to do the same job. We all try to go to the bathroom at the same time to use our
communicators in our ears. And it just looks kind of weird when 40 people go to the men's bathroom
at the same time. And 30 people go to the women's bathroom at the same time. And we all as we need
a bit of solution will be hat will be good. We're starting to arise suspicion. What next? 40 plus
30 equals 100. No, that what about the other? Okay, what about the people that have to stand
watch outside the bathrooms? 100 people all just get up from their chairs. Like bugs to a light.
Group infiltrated. Okay. Dave Holtz has been here for four days. A member of a secret society.
That's not a secret. Well, sooner or later, it's going to be our society. Because I'm going to
send another 100 agents in there. Two-fifths of the company is infiltration. That's so
stupid. I don't have one. I don't have contact. Okay. Give orders. Now there's nobody left to
all right now let's do a disinformation campaign on the inside. You know how easy that would be?
Tell the tell the the fucking 40% of their workforce to stop trying. Just sit there and
like spin a pencil around in your hand all day. They will lose so much productivity if you guys
just like browse Reddit all day. That we could completely control this. We don't even need to
put out like a false report. Okay. Let's lead reports. Let me go look at the suspects again.
Next suspect. All right. What do we get? Under interrogation. Orders. I got to remove. How do
I get somebody out of interrogation? This is not going to work, right? This is not going to work.
Imagine if you send in like a huge military team to to where we are. Yeah, we're going to
we're sending in like a big like raid on ourselves. No. The guy's just sitting there in a chair like
waiting for the next guy to come in to interrogate me. The door opens. The creeks open like
what the hell's going on there? And fucking flash can comes in. 50 people. Come get it.
All right. Let's go to let's go to the department. Interrogate. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Check captives. What does this mean? Procedure zero. Procedure one. What's procedure two?
Procedure two? Procedure two. Hold on. My cell phone plan? No, that's that's the cell. Okay,
hold on. That's the cell. That's not right. Suspects. Right. Okay. Okay. We've got there.
We're on two. Cell plan. Dental plan. Insurance. Home orders. Insurance. Okay. But anybody had no
past confessions, right? So what is phase two? All right. What about this the disinformation
campaign? I'm saying the guy was an alien. Lies. Lies. Lies. National unit slash slush funds
stand at 88,000. We're already doing this. All right. That's fine. Let's go back to the door.
So we were doing like extra interior. I don't know what that means. What is two? Procedure one.
Procedure zero. Procedure two. What does it mean? Apparently I haven't read all the reports. Yes,
I know. You send me this every day. Yeah, I've read all the reports. There are lots of new reports.
Okay. Political damage minor. Opposition MP Mr. Barry Matthews revealed a secret bill outlining
government plans to sell off national parks. The leaked document concluded that many parks
could easily be turned into golf courses and country clubs. All right. What? Um, isn't that
the same? Hold on. Mr. Barry Matthews. MP disgruntled. Suspected. Suspected affiliation
to National Federation of Labor. Suspect holds opinions not supported by the government.
Okay. There's a new suspect. Subject has been held looking pale. Okay. What's your name? Dave
Holds. What are you involved in? Who do you work for? Num W. The subject is being tortured
to British standards. No, I don't want to. What? What does that mean? Oh, they both being like
told. What is my God? What is your name? Help. How many are you? Go on punk. Make my day. All
right. I've got a group infiltrated group smeared. They're just like fighting each other.
They're just talking shit to each other. They're just making fun of each other.
What a perfect smear campaign. All right. Let's see. Suspects. But how do I, what do I do?
How do I do this? I need to like get them out of interrogation. He's been here for too long.
Removal. But is this kill? Or is this just remove? There's a dispose and then there's a remove.
All right. I have to go back to the departments. Leave desk. Interrogation. I'm going to say
dispose. That means remove is kill. Dispose is leave, right? Oh, no, no, stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop. Dispose. Remove is it's worded weirdly. Remove is kill. Dispose is get out.
Right? Or else how else would I let them out of interrogation? It's not the other way around.
You can't remove somebody. That's new reports. Let's see. Dispose is what villains ask their
henchmen to do. I know, but it's two people got fired. Boss, I was just doing the thing you told
me to do. I sat around. I played flash games. I went to the bathroom like 15 times. I told
extended breaks. Why are we? Why did we get fired? Is that it? That's it. So is he actually? All
right. Deceased. Next. So what the fuck does removal do? Yeah, I know. It's like the cartoon
villain gives his monologue at the end and says dispose of them. And then like the Batman throws
the thing and it like hits like three or four switches and then he gets trapped. I know,
but how do I get him out of the interrogation room? Hold on. What does this do? Oh, yeah.
Removal, huh? Assassinate George Cox. Yeah, that's removal. What? All right. We're going to
search his house and then we're going to tail him. I'm going to laugh my ass off if the first person
that we did like the military strike to was like the mole or whatever the whole time. And I can't
end the game because I'm softlocked. Okay, let's give orders here. Surveillance. Yeah. And we're
going to discreetly search. You know what? Just no, no, no, no, no. Discreet, discreet, discreet,
discreet, discreet, discreet. Did I already do that? Discreet. Okay. What is even the point
of like heavy assault? That doesn't seem to, why? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Back it up. Couple of new reports. See if we got any info. PM, we'll see you tomorrow morning.
Mounting political damage. Matthews has again embarrassed the government. Revelations that
industrialists are receiving back handers from the government in order to exaggerate output
figures have been vehemently denied by the Department of Trade and Industry. Under surveillance
being tailed, marked research. Okay. So the other ones being we can just go to tomorrow.
I do this every time. My sludge brain just goes back into the office every day again.
Is he going to do it a third time? Is he going to do the Oz slide the thing? No, he's not.
The Prime Minister says, I don't want to read derogatory remarks about this government and
the press. Keep troublemakers quiet. I want this sorted out now. We must continue. Hold on.
Document. We must continue our plan to wreak havoc and chaos at every level of organized
government. Switch the device on in the specified place in Morton on Stanley three days before the
election. I've set down a false trail. So Philip and thus you will not be under suspicion. The blue
none. Oh, all right. Matthews is two more people got fired. I'm not even sure this is how the polls
look. Oh, we're gonna lose next suspect. Okay, so this is this is the guy that's like causing
all the other issues, right? Um, what do we do? Disinformation. No, he said I can't if I do that
again, then I'm gonna be in big trouble. I can't do it. I can't do a light. No, I remember he said
don't do that again. You're getting too much info. Let's see what happens if we do some
misinformation. Let's go. You want? No, just wait. We need to see if we can do this. Correct.
New report. Wait a minute. Subject arrives at 150 Goward Gardens. Subject returns home, leaves
home, goes to the pub, leaves the pub, returns home. Okay. Suspect or location file attached.
Oh, there's a new executive of Megacorp. Friend. Oh, we found this is him. All right. Next report.
So wait, wait. We did a smear campaign and denied. Okay. Next report. That worked. All right. Again,
do surveillance. Sign the order. All right. All right. All right. Hold on. We're getting there.
Let's take a look at the polls. We gained a point with four days. Now I've removed the
surveillance. It's all right. We got what we need. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I know the guy that I have
is definitely the blue nun, right? Nothing of interest in Mary Matthews home. Two more agents
have been fired. Well, okay. Wait, hold on a minute. We are causing constant chaos and infiltrated with
our entire workforce, all the agents to try to get this guy, Dave Holtz. Dave Holtz has been
dead for like five days. So what are they doing here still? I think I need to pull them out and
put them somewhere else. Okay. Hold on. Let's leave one person. No agents. Wait, are they just
stuck there? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Can I pull them out? I think I can pull
them out. Yeah. All right. I'm going to pull them out and then we're going to go somewhere else.
Suddenly 90 plus people quit. Thank you for the opportunity. I really appreciate it. All right.
Let's go pull them out. All right. We have infiltration groups. Okay. See operation.
Okay. We next group. Yeah. Okay. Here we go. Hold on. Mr. Barry Matthews. So we're all everybody
pull out from here. Zero, no agents. All right. Everybody quit. Everybody walk next door. Wait,
how come I can't pull everybody out? Do they not want to quit? Okay. Wait, give orders. No agents.
Okay. Let's wait. We have maybe we have to wait for them to quit. See operations. All right. Let's
see what happens. I just, I got to get them over to the other place. Again, the same. I just had
the palace on the phone. Don't get serious. Okay. Let's see if we can pull them out. See groups.
Core size 251. Okay. Give orders. Oh, six agents. What happened to the other group?
Why can I not? Did they make their own organization? What happened? Did they all
leave? I only have six agents. Come on. Is this one like all those people left blizzard to make
wildstar? No. Hey. All right. So we have six people left. I can't believe this. All right.
Well, we're going to send. This is our sixth best. Send them all. Infiltrate. Okay. I guess we're
going to. What happened to our 96 agents? Hold on. For security reasons, all references to the
falling will be removed from our current records. Dave Holtz, Mr. Philip Owen, George Cox, and the
National Union of Municipal Workers. So they all still are there, but now they just work there.
They just are employees there now. Well, I guess you just work there. Okay. That's still fucking
funny. Oh, we have two gaining. Hold on here. Being tailed, being discredited. Okay.
How's that smear campaign? All right. Surveillance, pursuit, search. No, no, no, no.
We can't do anything crazy here. Let's just. No, no, just stay tailored on my guess. What's
going on next here? Suspect. Okay. Right. All right. Okay. All right. Let's go.
We're gaining like a point a day. What if it's a 50-50? There's a Mr. Garcia waiting to see you.
Who's that? I was. We were winning. We were winning. We were gaining a point a day. All right.
Well, we saw that one to the end. I have a few more streamers choices, but I think we can do a
chat choice now. Let's see. Let's make sure we're in the right spot from where we were last time.
Well, this sim health. Okay. Okay. I think, yeah, this is, I think I remember doing this one,
but I think that was a streamer's choice. Okay. Are we good? I do. Oh, by the way,
I already have that one. Let's move this down. Remember, it's the ones that you can actually
see the text on. Here we go. Please click on your screen in just a second. Do it now.
Yeah. Family feud. What's the other one? God. Captain Bible or family feud. All right. Thank
you for voting. I think we got it. We're going to do captain Bible. What the fuck even is cap? What
is captain Bible? Oh man. Okay. Oh, this is like hanging my computer. Why is this hanging my
computer so hard? Come on. Let's go. Stop this. Why is it? I'm, I'm hanging. My computer is just
hanging. Fire is penetrated. Oh dear. Well, uh, has anybody seen any good books lately?
Cause I'm stuck right now. I got a wheel. Hold on. What is going on? Fucking cap Bible,
whatever the hell it is. What is going on? You're killing me. I may need to, uh,
do some control. Oh, there we go. Okay. We're good. Captain Bible. Thank God. Here we go.
What was that? There was, there was once a, there was once a city far from us in a place
and time which had been imprisoned in the dome of darkness. In vain, the Bible Corps fought to free
it from its captivity. They would have lost hope for one last desperate plan that called for the
help of their greatest champion. Why is captain Bible assaulting Hogwarts in the Star Fox land
master? What the fuck is going on? Oh, I came as quickly as I could. Is that captain Bible or am I
captain Bible? Thank you for coming captain Bible. I've asked you to come here because this city has
been taken by the enemy and we haven't been able to break his hold on him. He planted a tower of
deception inside generating a dome of darkness. That dome is actually an anti-truth field. It
makes people very prone to being deceived. Why don't we just storm the city and take it by force?
Because we've only been able to open a small hole in the dome and that hole is very unstable.
So how do I fit into this? It's funny to use that phrase because we are sending you through that
hole into the city. So what do I do when I get inside? Can I expect any resistance? What about
the people? Should I expect any problems with my computer Bible? Your computer Bible might be damaged
going through the field so we've been sending in scripture stations where you can get verses for it.
Why is he so sad? Yes, I saw them outside. How will I know where to find them? You should already have
the maps that we sent you. They show where the station should be. Okay, um, what do I do when I
get inside? Your mission will be to knock out the tower of deception which is generating the dome.
How do I do that? You will need to use the city's unibot. We'll put you as close as we can to it,
but you'll need to get help from seven other people in order to operate it. The seven deadly
sins. The seven deadly virtues, whatever the fuck they're called. All right, let's go. This music's
gonna make me crazy. Now before you go, I think we should pray. Lord, please help
Captain Bible on this mission. Please keep him safe and let your truth overcome the darkness of
deception. Amen. Okay, wait, wait, wait. Normal, easy, or different? All right, hold on. I have to
exit. This shit is fucking gonna kill my ears. All right, that's all right. That's better.
I'm not gonna do difficult. I'm gonna do, I should do easy, if anything. I can give you
trivia answers. Is it? No, I'm doing normal. I'm not doing difficult in Captain Bible.
So am I in the dome of deception? Faith. Your faith is at 100%. Okay, is this like a roguelike?
What is this? No verses loaded. Oh, this is my Bible computer. Get a verse. Verse loaded. Genesis
127. So God created man in his own image. In the image of God, he created him, male and female.
He created the, I don't know the rest. I have no idea. I've got to go to the Bible machine,
ATM, to find out what happens next. The trouble he causes recoils on himself. His violence comes
down on his own head. What the fuck? It doesn't matter what you say, just what you do.
So God created man in his own image. In the image of God, he created him,
male and female, and then created them.
I thought I instantly died. So wait, I have to use Bible verses to stop the robot murderers.
All right, let me go look at my map. Holy shit. Are you serious? Look at this. This is too big.
This is too much. Wait, hold on. There's another verse.
The tongue also is a fire, a world of evil among the parts of the body. It corrupts the whole person,
sets the whole course of his life on fire, and is itself set on fire by hell.
The tongue is also fire, a word of evil among the parts of the body. It corrupts the whole person,
sets the whole course of his life on fire, and it is itself set on fire by hell.
Is that it?
What about this one? That looks like it's going to dig into my body when I walk forward.
Cyber lie incoming.
What? How do I do true or false? So God created man.
No, this is not right. Off. It's a cyber lie. I don't have that yet.
Here comes another cyber lie. Here we go.
Where is it? Right here.
Defend. Got it.
Power. Uh oh. Again, you're a fluke of nature. No, I am. I am of God.
What is that laser? Incoming cyber lie detected. It doesn't matter what you say, just what you do.
The trouble he causes recoils on himself. His violence comes down in his own head.
The tongue is also fire. Here we go.
I'm at 49%. What happens when I run out of faith power?
Hold on. I need to see a map. Trap. Trap. Prayer chapel. I'm just going to go down, I guess.
I need more verses, don't I? Here we go. No, wait. It's this one. Right? Which one was it?
Oh, no. I couldn't do this one yet. I had to run away. What about in here? What do I need to go?
So I can't go down. Go up and to the right or to the left and then down.
Let's try over here. Here we go. New verse.
That he was buried, that he was raised on the third day according to the scriptures,
and that he appeared to Peter and then to the twelve after that. He appeared to more than five
hundred of the brothers at the same time, most of whom are still living, though some have fallen
asleep. I need to match to unlock. It is most important to totally love God and to truly love
people also. The tongue is also fire. I don't think it's any of these. I have to go down from here.
Yeah. Oh, we got another one.
Sounds good.
All right. This is like using the world card in Binding of Isaac.
Restore my faith. Give me the sword of the spirit. Give me the shield of faith.
Warn me of traps and snares. Light my path before me.
Light my path before before me. How much faith do I have? I don't know. Thank you, Lord. I believe.
Lord, please give me the sword of this. Light my path before me. Where in the Bible does it
talk about God lighting my path? I don't know. Lord, please give me that cool sword.
What does it talk about? The sword of the spirit. Hey, Lord, I could use some more things.
Lord, please. Where in the Bible does it talk about avoiding traps? Right here. Right? Avoid like the...
Here we go. Did it work? I'm not very good at this. Okay, I got full health. What's in here?
All right. Here we go. An easy one. When Jesus died, he stayed dead. After all,
nobody saw him after the crucifixion. Got you. All right. So now what do I got?
I might be able to go up now. What was this one? The rainbow is just light refracting through water,
not a creation of God with a divine purpose. Uh-oh. That's a cyber lie.
Are we sure this is not just like a scientist with a helmet on? Uh, this Genesis? No, none of these
work. Scientists are liars. All right, what about this one? Match. No, no, I don't have this one yet.
Do I have this one? I have to be able to go one of these ways. Let's confront the cyber lie.
Here we go. Children are born pure and innocent. If you let them do whatever they want, they will
grow up with great wisdom. This one. Oh, oh, that didn't work. Uh, what is it? My son,
if citizen types do not give in to them. Dude, there are people dressed like this in Stormwind,
okay? A bit like the hammer. They can just walk by him? But this is, that wasn't a very good trap.
But this is what the high and lofty one says. He who lives forever, whose name is holy,
live in a high and holy place, but also with him who is contrite and lowly in spirit to revive
the spirit of the lowly and to revive the heart of the okay. Here we go. Doesn't matter what you
say, just what you do. It was palms, right? No, it was a tongue is also fire. Nice. All right,
what does it look like about left me go up? All right, let's confront the cyber lie here.
Do unto others before they do unto you and you'll get away with it. What? That's, that's palms. Do
unto others before they do unto you and you'll get away with it. That's a pretty sick shield.
Look at that. Look at the back. That's a nice shield. Yeah, he's going to kill me.
He'd make that stuff. That's not good. 38% faith. Come on, give me a, uh, give me a heal room. Cast
all your anxiety on him because he cares for you. Right. All right. Unlock match to unlock.
It takes discipline to get the foolishness out of a kid. What? What the fuck? I don't,
I don't know if we have this one. Seek God and he will answer you. Peter, cast all your anxiety
on him because he cares for you. Or I live in a high and low, but I was also was trying to lowly
spare this one. Is it Peter? Didn't open. Didn't open. Did I lose faith to that? No. Another cyber
lie. If a gang tells you to do it, then you just gotta do it. What, what, what is even the context
here? Proverbs? No, this thing's going to kill me. Thank God for, I mean, like honestly, thank God.
Right. I said that a lot, but for real. Oh, when do you just die? He stayed dead after. No, no, no,
it's, uh, here it is. All right. I haven't bought one of these yet. Folly is bound up in the heart
of a child with the broad. Okay. Okay. What the fuck? It's not, that's not fucking no. The sword,
I can get the sword though. Yeah. I don't think you guys realize how much like fucking
Monka S shit is inside of the Bible. We do realize. Lord, please give me the sword of the spirit.
Where in the Bible does it talk about the sword of the spirit? The sword of the spirit.
Here it is. That was a very holy, uh, legend of Zelda melody thing. The one that, whatever,
forget it. It's not important. All right. I'm going to go up so I can unlock this door now.
Can I use this or do I just have it? Oh, you hit harder in battle.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Foolishness. Uh, no child should be foolish.
Wait, what the fuck is it? It's proverbs. All right. Open the damn door. What has, what is going on?
Okay. Whose picture is that? The new lamb of God. What? He's Jesus incarnated.
Oh, what the fuck is going on? He is not. Uh, he's not. He is too. He is not. He is too. He is not.
Go away. Okay. But I'll be back. We're going to bring my dad and he's going to tell you that
that's not Jesus. Uh, no, hold on. I'm back. Would you like to talk to me? No, you must be from
Babylon. You are not a true believer. Whose picture is that? What? The Bible shows that there
is no reincarnation. Oh, that's how we, we do the, that's how we, uh, I don't get it. I, I don't get
it. Go away. Okay. But I'll be back. I don't get it. All right. So we're going to go, uh, down.
Do I have this one? Shit. Okay. Let's try this one. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
stop, stop, stop. What the fuck? Some Christians have changed their minds and become atheists. That
proves that the Bible is full of lies. The tongue is also fire. The sword of the spirit. What?
I don't think I have this one. Can I go up to the right? All right. Go through
and just, I might have, stop! Why does that have to happen? There we go. Okay. They will,
children born pure and innocent wait do we have that one is it is it is it is it proverbs
i feel like it's it is all right what the fuck why did i just use that why even use the sword
i have a legit i have like a legit gamma death ray why would i use the sword if you don't love
jesus you don't love god um i don't think i have this in addition to all this take up the shield
of the faith with which you can extinguish all of the flaming arrows of the evil one
oh i can block flaming arrows now the rainbow is just light refracting through water not a
creation of god with a divine purpose i don't think i have this i don't think i have like a god
created the world right i don't have this yet is it genesis no this is created man in his image
this is not about anything else all right we're gonna go back up then
okay we got another one here we go whenever i bring clouds over the earth and the rainbow appears in
the clouds i will i will remember my covenant between me and you and all living creatures are
very kind never again will the waters become a flood to destroy all life here we go do not go
up there here we go holy shit he almost just killed me oh that's not good please tell me
there's something in here that i can use what if some did not have faith will their lack of
faith nullify god's faithfulness not at all let god be true and every man a liar yes all right lord
please give me the shield of faith there it is to block the flaming arrows thank you lord
warn me of anything else i'm like doing pretty well in this game all right there was another
one about the the rainbow stuff up here right up and uh up into the right and then up
do i have this one no wait hold on hold on here we go i got it what if some did not have faith
will their lack of faith nullify god's faithfulness not at all got it what i just get
i okay i just got like a power up or something all right what's in here destroyed a robot
what about this one this one didn't work last time no this one doesn't work i have to just walk
through so we need to go up to the right see if i can unlock okay it is most important to totally
love god and to truly love people also no no i don't have this shit was there anything else up
here i get like straight up maybe yeah okay wait wait this is the science one right yep i remember
this one the rainbow is just light yep we can go through here so is that giving me
like faith up or is that just replenishing my faith i'm not really sure if that's probably like
a refill apparently this is a okay this is a big one shit there's two of these that i don't think
i have the right um verse for this one didn't work it does work i thought i did it before and
it didn't work all right this is gonna be hard i think uh oh uh oh how do i kill him how do i
back out how do i get out how do i get out did i do it your faith is at zero four percent zero
point four percent i need a heal right now it is written man does not live on bread alone but on
every word that comes from the wealth of god please don't be a monster fuck no one cares
cast all your anxiety away because he cares for you i have to instantly kill him too thank god
all right i need health save the game and heal save game right enter name got it okay uh oh
if someone says that they're christian and have a ministry then you can trust them
uh the tongue is also fire wait hold on uh wait if sinners entice you do not give into them
and i don't know which one it is will they lack of uh no i'm gonna try the romans i'm gonna go for it
is either romans or no no run away yeah i don't have it well maybe this is it i am the vine you
are the branches if a man remains in me and i and him he will bear much fruit apart from me you can
do nothing okay i don't think that helps us i could probably maybe i should go down um i can't i
don't think i can go over there maybe down here let me try to heal first maybe i don't think i can
i think i'm assuming you can only use one prayer room once lord please oh shit we're good we're
good all right so there's this person down here that we have to convince you can't come back to
life i don't think i have that do i have that oh there's a door over here all right let me let's
go see if i can do anything so i have to go up right down no down down down down all right
what about down here no i've already done these what about the one next across from the from the
v wait here we go yeah yeah yeah yeah these things are hard all right we're gonna go left and then
up and then right seek god and he will answer you um i don't know if we have this i'm the vine hold on
no this is this one man does not live on bread alone but on every word that comes from the mouth
of god i don't think that's that clear though he will let's try this one nope you don't lose
anything for this though just try john am i losing faith no i'm just guessing at the door
guessing the password i don't have this all right do i have the thing that's necessary to
okay what that's reincarnated there's no such thing as reincarnation and i'll prove it uh he was
buried that he was raised on the third day no this is proving reincarnation this is me proving that
you can reincarnate so i'm about to get like this thrown back in my face i don't get it go away
that's not it jesus resurrected not reincarnated right right that's yeah that's true okay you're
right you got me there uh what have i not tried down to the right it looks like a whole hallway
here that i didn't do up i think there's a monster here no okay this is the prayer area
remember that one all right did i get this one no one cares uh yes they do he does
it's a really strange version of uh samus here we go he who hates me hates my father as well
okay we're loading up on verses here do i take any pleasure in the death of the wicked declares the
sovereign lord rather am i not pleased when they turn from their ways and live uh all right so what
is that gonna open if you don't love jesus you don't love god right no no wait i think we have
this one yeah if you like hate me then you hate yeah where is it who you hate me hates my father
as well got it um what's happening here why am i playing like the 3d sonic globe game oh shit
god wants to kill the sinners before they get a chance for uh to repent no no no no where is it
we just got it we just got it what the hell is it called the one where it's like i don't want to
i want you to turn away from ezekiel here it is there we go here we go persevere all right
jesus replied love the lord your god with all your heart and with all your soul and with all
your mind this is the first and greatest commandment and the second is like it love your neighbor as
yourself all right keep me from the snares they have laid for me from the trap set by the evil
doers okay now i can see all traps in snares so what is in this door it looks like a boss door
save it all right uh warn me of uh traps and snares what was it called i don't i just got it
i don't remember what the hell it was there we go so now what does that mean do i have light my path
as well as restore faith okay i don't think i have light my path before me yet no i don't have it
that's it there's one more area i still don't have a thing about reincarnation do i have to
run back of course i do not bad this is not considered a trap all right up left and up
see if we can get in there seek god and he will answer you i don't know if we have this no love
the lord apart from me no none of this is about he who hates me hates no no no we can't get in here
shit so i the only way the place i can go is up here there has to be something i can do up there
because i can't do anything else over here why is it blinking oh all the way up go go go go those
are trap doors oh okay it just blinks if it's trap door all right let me get in here i got it is
most important to totally love god and to truly love people right i have this with what i would
there it is right that's it get in oh god none of these this is like hurts my head
i really don't want it this is another one of those like jump warps it is for freedom that
christ has set us free stand firm then and do not let yourselves be burdened again by a yoke of
slavery okay i'm almost at the end of the game guys it's almost done the greatest christian
commandment is that you go to church no it is not it is the what is it where is it that's like the
the greatest commandment what was it yes is it let him do anything don't let him attack
uh all right but even if we are an angel from heaven should preach a gospel other than the one
we preach to you let him be eternally condemned what does that do for me though oh shit this is
a spider what did you come from jesus told one truth other teachers have of other truths you
should believe them just as much as jesus we just got it there it is all right we have never fought
the spider before though i don't know i don't know what to do here did he give up what i was
kind i like i cut like all of his legs off you couldn't have just like liquefied him or something
all right well that's trapped through there you don't need the bible as long as you have something
to eat uh no there's one specifically about bread in here where is it you can like eat you can live
off of bread alone right there it is i can't believe i'm gonna beat this game that's i don't
know why but for some reason this is like unbelievable to me oh shit we gotta save it
right here this is the hard one uh i have to do this here we go holy god would never associate
with an insignificant speck of protoplasm like you no it's like though we're god is us and we
are god right which one is it um no no no no no it's um which one is this is it um here it is
i am the vine you are the branches of a man remains in me and i and him he will bear much
fruit apart from me you can do nothing here we go right john 15 five that's not it he who lives
forever whose name is holy i live in a high and holy place but also with him is oh yeah it's this
one all right i just this guy hits hard so why was that guy so much easier than the last one
like i mean we're talking 10 times easier than the last one all who sin apart from the law will
also perish apart from the law and all who sin under the law will be judged by the law
okay so you're judged by the law don't like break the law law all right let's go again
no law when jesus daddy stayed dead after nobody saw him after the okay this is the one we're here
it's genesis right no no no which uh which one is it right here which one is it right right right
where is it where is it where is it where is it where is it where is it where is it which one is
it where is it where is it where is it which one is it where is it there it is and oh he's to open
his eye okay that's how i how did i shoot him that many times and not hit his eye i don't know how
all right that's a that's a trap over there let's do this among this is probably like a uh holy room
yes all right i'm not going to use this heal because i probably need it do i have the light yet
this is a big circle i almost probably i think i almost have them people can't be expected to
live by god's laws uh la la la la la we just got it which one is it galactus i'm getting pretty
good at this just as a man is destined to die once and after that to face judgment die once
no reincarnation we can bring it back i have almost explored everything you don't have to
accept jesus in order to love god um i don't know you don't have to accept yeah where's the
one that like you you have to be the branch the branch right he who hates me hates my father
all right this is every i think i got them all johnson grew powerful because he walked
steadfastly before the lord is god the before the john grew powerful because he walked steadfastly
before the lord is god lord like the path lord the random spider real power is obtained through
intimidation and manipulation law i don't know which one that is seek you uh is it this one
it is that one that's funny it's just funny all right now let's go light our path go prove that
reincarnation doesn't exist that's not it that's not it which one is it i think i have them all
lighting a path i think i have every single one well i'm just gonna heal all right let's
go oh there's two up here all right let's go back this is the no that's a that's not that's a
where's the jump door here it is all right we go prove reincarnation see if we can open the door
opposite so i need to go down left up i'm wholly invested in this i mean a w h oh like holy all
right hey i'm back oh whose picture is that okay oh there is no such thing as reincarnation and
i'm back and i got the bible to prove it and uh let me scroll through here just as man is
destined to die once and after that to face judgment if people can only die once then that
means that they can't come back as babies and die over again well maybe but he's still the new lamb
of god he is the holy one who has the new holy revelation that was never mentioned in the bible
that proves that he's true well the bible talks about people who preach a different gospel
it's the angel one or is it but even if okay how can he be holy when the bible calls him accursed
do the eyes just move the eye with the eyes looking at her last time he's always been so
good to me and guided me into the new truth and accepted me into his family just because he seems
nice that doesn't mean that he doesn't have an ulterior motive listen to this verse uh listen to
this one just because he seems nice that doesn't mean that he doesn't have an ulterior motive
where is it where is it it's the one that's like one of the first ones
the tongue is fire yeah where is it where is it hold on i don't know if it's this one
the romans no what is he seems nice i live in it no but oh my son if sinners entice you do not
give into them right this might be it maybe let's try it i don't get it no reincarnation okay where
is it i gotta start like i can't even like burn these into my brain i don't even remember which
one it is i really don't i like i don't it's all i i'm just i don't even know no i sure i don't want
to burn these i'm not like that religious or anything like i don't want to okay uh and then
this is it's the this one okay now we have he's nice to me but that doesn't just because he seems
nice doesn't mean that he doesn't have an ulterior motive i don't even we might not even have this
one keep me from the snares maybe the yeah i'll try the one the um the only one this is the only
one that makes any sense no do i don't i don't even have it i'll come back i'll be back again
to try to convince you seek god and he will answer you i don't know if i have this one either leo
seek god and he will answer you i am the vine did i do this one before already i don't
it's not austin 316
oh my son keep me from the snares the troubling this one does anybody have any idea
just give it to me i don't have it i have to beat this game so i'm sorry we're stuck here until i
beat this fucking game look at this we're way too too deep right now i can only go up into the right
no yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah this is donald duck all over again no i just need to be let me just
beat a boss no wrong door oh it's already dead ow whatever oh all right don't have this yet
that's a faith room here we go you don't need god in your day-to-day life only in emergencies
i think we have this one it's the one we're like i'm the vine and you're the
whatever there it is torched oh dear god this is an emergency right there's another verse over here
let's get it for the son of man is going to come in his father's glory with his angels and then
he will reward each person according to what he has done okay what does that mean
this game is fucking stupid this game is fucking really dumb i'm just like piecing this together
right now i've been here for like 40 minutes it's starting to click it's actually starting
to hit me now if jesus comes again who cares it won't affect us okay that's uh where is it
you know when you do something for long enough that you forgot that you've been doing it for
that long and then you've just you're kind of like why have i been doing this for this long
that's it's starting to creep up and like the music is keep me okay jesus comes back who
cares it's this one no which one is it i was just on it there here we go then he will be
reward each person right this is the one right vital power watch out for false prophets they
come to you in sheep's clothing and there we go we just completed that quest quest completed
let's do it but first was the uh was that prayer room left down left right up
left down whatever i'll find it down right down left left okay i'm back i've got more
things in my bible computer the bible says there's no such thing as reincarnation
where is it it's like if you if you die you die once right what does it say it it's one of these
there it is okay and then this is the the angels one which is this one no this one
okay and then we have the next one here it comes are we ready do not listen to a wolf in sheep's
clothing it was matthew here we go done your new lamb is nothing but a fake and he just wants to
use you he wants to use you up is that kind of scary he's a false christ he lied to me
that means that god lied to me no no no no oh no no no no no god even though that mean that
man was unfaithful and lied to you that doesn't mean that god's a liar oh shit uh-oh this is kind
of backfiring on me uh even though that man was unfaithful god isn't a liar here uh take some
bread what a man cannot live on bread alone no uh um i already did this one wait what if some did
not have faith will their lack of faith nullify god's faithless not at all let god be true and
every man a liar got it not everyone believes in god but that doesn't affect him just because
men lie and deceive that doesn't mean that god lies lots of people lie so i can still trust god
yes he will never lie to you thank you for showing me the truth is there anything i can do to help
you yes i will need your help to operate the unibot do you know where it is uh-huh it's at
the north end of the city do you know how to get to the rest of the city yes and i have the verse
that unlocks the door that leads to it i kept it locked to try to keep the the cybers out
here it is ask and it will be given to you seek and you will find knock and the door will be
opened to you thanks where's the door right outside the room all right goodbye it's this
door right here i did it let's go ding ding all right where's the boss they mentioned the next
part of the city so why am i not dealing with all these robots why am i just running by them
okay i'm just getting spawned on that was just like five in a row no this is it uh by the way
this is this this i'm gonna make a chrono trigger reference this is when you the like the very like
first hour of the game you're on a bridge like this and you fight a boss and so they almost the
exact same background the exact same bridge the exact same door i'm just i need to reference it
because it's one of my favorite video games ever made oh fuck okay um so there's like five areas
which one do i want to go to the hell is that uh which way do i want to go should i try to go up
there all right let me just see if i can get up there all right so what is up here are you
shitting me yeah i get to get into a giant you guys want me to leave the game i'm about to pilot
a gigantic megazord so this is the unit bot that i need to destroy the tower of deception
testing testing is anyone here hey it's captain bible we plan to use this unit bot to get rid of
the dome of darkness hmm yes i mean that would be a good idea who the hell was that we need six
more people to work this system i have to go find more help oh no i need six more people that armor
is made out of gold all right i'm just gonna let me just see what it looks like okay well that's
this is over i'm done with this one uh do i have to do everything what i was just doing six more
times holy shit don't think so uh what is all this do i have to get the whole bible
i just i want to see what's over this is what is this i need to see what's over there
if you don't beat this game you're gonna go to hell oh boy i'm almost dead i'm dead don't give
up don't give up use reincarnation that's it that's it that's it that's it for that one
that was fun though what was the next one oh we still don't know oh yeah um why did this change
wasn't this over here these i got jumbled around all right i you ready where we going
yeah i fucking knew it was gonna be that i knew it i knew it was gonna be family feud i just knew
it uh that's a veto not happening sorry guys i didn't do this already all right i'm doing three
rounds of family few we're not gonna get stuck here i ain't getting stuck here we go
family few number of families uh do one family one are you returning champions no
please type your name stick with the bumps okay out of 100 people surveyed the top five answers
around the board dad's face off huh name some dad walk what what was that name something you
worry about losing keys this is too fast i think i slow this down pay your class pet play all right
things that you lose name something you worry about losing uh wallet money okay money keys um
uh id like your id all right um uh your sorry we're about losing um your hair
okay um your bible your job uh-oh money hair keys uh you're losing i don't want to lose my
social security card mind it's over chance to steal make sure you're about losing dad
my teeth you motherfuckers you worry about losing weight i'm worried about losing my teeth
that's fucking weird all right here comes the moms name something they're gonna pass it name
something you put on a cut bandage 82 there's like 12 people that said something stupid
i don't know like alcohol how do you spell alcohol something you put on a cut band-aid
disinfectant um ointment ointment um it's gonna be something dumb it's gonna be like
i put lemon juice on it lemon whatever teeth okay what is it what do you put on a cut what are they
even right do we not get to see their answer iodine i told you i need to put iodine on it sweetie
put on murthiolate i gotta press instantly name it i was pressing buttons what i couldn't read the
fucking question name a type of place where people can kiss in public and no one notices
i don't know at the movies like you you like go on a date to the movies um in the terminal
uh yeah like a no restaurant no um at the park that means only there's only going to be like
one or two for these um car restaurant bar i don't know like at home yeah no shit
but apparently not in public what is it at the beach yeah okay okay what's the last one
the disco i feel like bar should have been put in there that's not fair i don't know how to hit
the i don't know how to buzz by the way i'm pressing every button do i get it name something
you have that never lasts as long as you'd like it to last car okay we're gonna pass
what money car what was you what was the answer i would love to see it what do you got dad
nothing all right i need a chance to steal something you have that never lasts as long
as you'd like it to last um uh youth oh come on vacation how okay you guys i need something here
sex three strikes come on money car vacation sex youth um perfume this
this game is rigged well my perfume is not lasting i earned 82 bucks due to tax considerations the
volks choose not to play the fast money round huh boring boring boring what's going on
what was that supposed to be the audience they didn't want to pay their taxes so they didn't
want more money but what i don't understand what the concern is there i'm okay i'm gonna do this
one more time due to tax considerations what they didn't want to be broadcast on tv winning
money all right one family not returning champions uh what is gonna be just stay with the bumps
okay here we go meat flavor of jelly flavor of jelly how dare they fucking say something like
this lemon are you fucking kidding me that's the most like that is the most popular most important
jello ever raspberry jelly like raspberry jello lemon jello they're gonna pass
that's jelly lemon they said the word jelly and it fucked up my head jelly like um uh raspberry
or grape orange grape raspberry really strawberry strawberry jelly strawberry grape orange raspberry
lemon not jello um blackberry i did orange already blackberry no blueberry jelly blueberry
cherry apricot that's really good i think that's i think it's that one that no that's that's at every
diner in the in the fucking world is apricot uh jam they're not gonna get it oh my god i can't
believe it i was gonna do that too i was gonna do cherry jelly too apricot that is seriously
everywhere apricot jelly is everywhere i've seen apricot a lot cherry jelly no i don't think so
i'm spamming name a best season of the year this is such a subjective question uh i'm just gonna
put every season there's not a fifth season what uh winter summer winter fall spring
huh is it gonna be like bikini season or like shorts season there's not a fifth season
like baseball football season what is the mysterious fifth season rapid season
uh duck season no no no no no no no um uh autumn is fall but autumn is fall that's the same thing
that they would put under the same category it's not autumn i told you i don't want to get extra
seconds i got extra seconds i told you oh my god i'm so angry at everybody that was yelling that
what was it what's the two people what's your favorite season christmas okay gotta write that
down i can't not write that down because i i am just that's unbelievable okay do i get the points
for that my favorite season is thursday name the quietest my favorite season is that's the best
that's that great job for that one name the quietest place in your house um the attic what's the
quietest that's true though that is the quietest place in your whole house the basement bathroom
basement bedroom the attic is factually correct bedroom bathroom basement attic garage garage
study the den got it all right come on just spam it neighbor job at a hotel
uh food service rooms room service uh clerk uh what are they uh front desk the front desk
we both didn't get it receptionist apparently nobody works at a hotel at a hotel room service
receptionist the concierge desk clerk i was gonna write front desk oh my god did i spell that right
it's like concierge right did i spell it wrong no i didn't you spell it right uh the maid okay
the chef the room service the chef the manager there's a manager there's a hotel manager
yes and then the chef what is number one the uh the valet uh the doorman bellhop got it i have
582 points ready to play fast money here we go tell me how many pounds a football player weighs
um to 220 name something with a red light a red light a red light a red light tell me how many
books you buy in a year three tell me how many glasses of water you drink per day eight name a
sport that the whole family can play together um football are you fucking kidding me oh my god
what the you gotta be kidding me what's a red light like a stop light tell me how many pounds
of 200 250 no no there's no football player that's like three or three hundred three hundred
name something with a red light a stop light traffic light traffic light how many books you
buy in a year one how many glasses of water you drink per day two sport that you can play
with the whole family baseball i don't what what i don't understand this okay football player
bullshit how many two glasses of water a day i almost just won on uh two glasses of water a day
are those people still alive oh shit it's hacking me all right one more same thing two glasses of
water a day uh okay that's us i bet you one glass of water a day was more too
oh my they're gonna throw this tell me how many pounds a football player weighs
220 was incorrect 300 was incorrect 200 oh my god why are there so many of these that are not
correct 220 200 300 one 250 what how many pounds does a football player weigh 210 you're gonna
play this good luck 160 180 there's so many numbers here 230 oh god should i do 230 if 220
was not there then why would 230 be there i'm gonna do 190 190 oh how much i want to see all
the answers this is fucking ridiculous 200 225 250 220 i did 220 but it said zero what
180 what what's i didn't pick them right like keno numbers apparently 190 is not there 185 180
200 that's unbelievable why are they doing this this is the same stuff they're just mocking me
all right i don't know what else has a red light besides a traffic light i have no idea good luck
rudolph rudolph the red nose reindeer you're not gonna get it's rudolph it's gonna be rudolph
red nose reindeer police car has a red and blue light that's misleading rudolph a cat house
what is a cat house like a cat tree how many books do you buy in a year one oh my god
this is the worst it's not going to be like 10 nobody that's a lie bunch of fucking liars
i buy lots of books i buy like 15 books a year bullshit you don't even read one every five years
it's if it's 20 i'm gonna be upset okay no one's that much of an asshole to pretend like they
read 15 books a year this is just another hold on more than 28 i hate this is so dumb not 20
less than 20 but more than 20 5 2 12 and these something it's gonna be like 30 or something
please have this last one be like 60 see that's those people are telling the truth the only people
tell them the truth how many glasses of water two i know that it okay two how many glasses of water
do you drink a day i want to play this one because i'm this is gonna be really funny if this is true
this is zero okay nobody's that fucked up one holy shit i can't believe 12 percent only drink
a one glass of water a day do you pee out dust four six seven it's not eight what eight had zero
last time should i do eight eight had zero when i did it before eight had zero when i did it before
nine or ten nine or ten ten oh give me a break don't do nine don't not say nine
i wrote eight in the zero when during the fast money it's not eight don't do it
yes all right it's gonna be nine okay it was eight i won fast money coming up
tell me how many years you have worked at your present job uh eight that's way too long name
your favorite tv network um abc let's see name the age when you got your first job it's uh 15 14 15
tell me how many years you have known your best friend uh 20 25 20 25 tell me how much
of a tell me how much a new wardrobe would cost uh 19 like 85 uh like 36 bucks 30 bucks
eight years abc told you that's like the best answer 15 yep tell me how many years you have
known your best friend 25 all right tell me how much a new wardrobe would cost 30 bucks
nobody said that okay abc uh cbs right nbc how many years have you worked at your present job
five i'm gonna say five favorite tv network nbc name the age where you got your first job
16 right because 15 was how many years have you known your best friend 10 tell me how much a new
wardrobe would cost um 150 100 200 all right almost there all right come on yes yes
all right come on i don't know what the money would be back then to buy new clothes i'm just
gonna say i'm one i'm gonna go pee i'll be right back i'm not gonna keep this music on though i
won't torture you i'll be right back okay so uh streamer's choice time i just saw this and i
remember this game so i want to try it here we go this is that uh bar game where you throw the
drinks what's it called bar tap hmm all right uh k keyboard button or space to play let's just play
wow this hurts is it supposed to look like this this doesn't look right i don't remember being
like this ah it hurts it hurts i'm so sorry i thought this is is it my colors all right i
gotta turn this off wait it's my colors it's the channels right you're right all right what all
right i'm done why have my choices been all so bad okay that's it watch closely mountain dew
this is a mountain dew game all right i can't look at it anymore it hurts i'm sorry about that like
now i can now that's all i can see i can't see anything else all right we're gonna bring it back
uh we ended up down here we did donald duck's playground so i think it was
if i scroll here i think yeah this makes sense let's take a look right here i think right no
it was like it was right here we already did donald duck's playground so we're not gonna do it
so don't click it yeah i know you saw i know what you saw down there i know i saw it too
where are we going where did you get what are you guys clicking i just have the fortress
this is very spread out we're not going to donald duck's playground i already did it
bouncing bait what is this game i was i was like do we delivering babies in this game
all right let's take a look is this like a stork game or something all right let's see 50 bucks
just came in from valemi thank you for let me thanks for the 5000 bits that's a lot that's
like the fifth fifty dollar drop today so thanks guys that's fucking a lot uh and they say here's
your money for sponsoring mountain dew jeremy you'll get the rest after the chug you'll get the rest
after the chug well thank you so much for the 50 bucks i'm not chugging mountain dew it's not
gonna happen and let's get this on screen all right i this one is you're not delivering uh this
you have to what i don't understand what is what's on the left oh uh okay why is this bouncing at
least these okay well this one i'm not this one's dumb this one's like i why i i don't understand
this one move on from that one it's the colors again yeah that was just like what where we pick
again that was just like trampoline bounce into like the the right side of the screen
all right hey i picked a couple of bad ones but bouncing babies was just
i don't know guys come on that was on you uh wwf wrestlemania yours were way worse
no they weren't bouncing babies and bar tapper canceled each other out because they were the
same color scheme and they were both equally as just like hard to look at all right we're
gonna do wwf uh there was some i missed some community subs from earlier adventure mf dan
gave five subs uh we also had uh am clockwork gave five subs earlier i want to make sure i didn't
miss that so thank you both of you and let's go wwf wrestlemania if it'll open and it will
what do we got hulk hogan hulkamania and the hulkster are trademarks of marvel entertainment
wait hulk hogan is a marvel character since when
get him in the mcu i did not know that that's odd compete for belt or practice
uh well okay it's q and a is up and down it seems let's practice first what we're gonna be
hulk hulkster uh weight three hulk hogan was not 300 pounds i can assure you of that
i guess we're being we're gonna be uh hulk hogan it's taking a long time to load holy
shit this this is the this is the this is the game this is the this is the guy because i love
this game this is gonna this is games in the arcade this is like this game's fucking unbelievable
i think this game is one of the best games in the arcade i've been looking for this for a long
long time okay this okay i got grab space is grab what is left and right q and a is up and down
w e r c x c shift alt control q there's like a there's a grab so why is it doing two player
controls i didn't select two player i mean i'm hitting every single button number pad all right
well number pad works over here space is punch but weirdly enough i can't find left or right
match over i mean i i am just dragging across the keyboard the arrow keys were controlling
mr perfect i don't think i can control this game j and l no i don't think so you would think if q
and a is up and down oh this sucks i love this game the number pad number pad was for the player
too this was in the arcades if i remember period and comma no unless it's like a capital no wait
wait wait wait what was that that was just like you okay that was oh all right q a o and p
i think there's only three wrestlers all right i'm gonna be the ultimate warrior
q a o and p you might be big you might be strong you might look good but you just
ain't perfect you missed oh hold on i have to select a reply you mr perfect will feel the power
of the ultimate warrior and you will yield to that power yes i am strong but the strongest and
biggest muscle i have is the heart that pumps the love of all my warriors and that will spell your
ultimate doom let us put your body to the ultimate test because i can promise that the result will
not be perfect for you let's rally up the crowd i don't want to see this whole thing they say
nobody's perfect but then they say the exception proves the rule all right you're dead
he's speaking in riddles yeah all right where's it going why is this faster now
what does it want to do where this this is the game by the way it's a chair rider
how do i get back in the ring he has the chair now this is the game it's so fast i'm fighting like
four imaginary people and him o and p being left and right is fucking me up so hard
dude i gotta go to the chair give me the chair out out give me the chair get back out here all
right it's gonna count count it's gonna come out all right go go get out i'm gonna i win it looks
like you lost and i won that's not what happened now that's what i'd call absolutely perfect
then you could count it out how did i lose that you might be big all right i'm just doing like
christopher walking why did i lose i did not how did i get counted out i was in the fucking
ring when i was at 18 you can't win the belt on a countout yes you can who made up that role
was because i grabbed the chair i think i have to hit left and right yeah it's left he's like
flipped me
let's go and i'm not hurting myself am i how i don't understand that i have to go left and right
and spam holy shit i get it i get it i have to hit left and right really fast i can't do it
that's hurting my arm i almost had it all right i'm sitting here and go opi opi opi opi opi opi opi
dude that's impossible it's going too fast i gotta slow it down is that better i feel like
that's better how do i run through the ropes it's a double tap this is i i there's no way
i need like a controller q a o p in space and i really don't we're just gonna play pac-man right
now story of his choice it's gonna be a good one trust me this is pack in time is this i feel like
i played this one not on stream but before we're talking about our hero pac-man has not always been
the cool video game dude we know and love because the evil ghost witch and her flunkies the ghost
monsters invaded his world was pac-man forced to survive 50 many crazy events since then pac-man
has lived happily with mrs pac-man and their two cute pack kids
is that but pac's fiendish arch enemy the ghost witch has vowed to disrupt his tranquil life
following the failure of her diabolical plans she decided to eliminate pac-man once and for all
what the ghost witch cast a forbidden spell on pac-man ripping him from his family and hurling
him through time to his dangerous past the journey back in time transformed pac-man into a young
pac-boy the ghost witch sent pack to 1975 a world which has never heard of the hero pac-man
through the witch's foul magic the inhabitants of a once beautiful land have turned against him
commanding this mystical horde are the ghost witches loyal ghosts they are a pac's worst nightmare
and will do everything possible to keep pac prisoner what's with the spacing here to escape
this distorted past and return to this beloved family pac-man must traverse this hazardous land
and penetrate the castle within it stands the portal of time packs only hope to return to
presence let's go new game game a i've never played this before that was interesting what
was that i wanted to see that for more than a second like wait am i just playing on the beach
shouldn't i be a little bit more distraught why do i look like i weigh a lot
this what why can pac-man do coming on my hop let's go oops there's a double jump kind of okay jump
is that it wait wait let me try something else it's bunny hopping guys it's momentum with bunny
hops all right anything else i need to know down space alt z like anything else i don't think so
what the 70s were like that's a good question i feel like i'm going too fast this is awesome
what is it oh i can i hit my head cover the spider it's almost water can i swim how do you swim
swim is there a way i can go how do i get to drain the water oh it's alt this is so much fun
just drain all the air from my lungs turning into kirby am i out of the water
what are the power-ups can i get this is a vine that hurts that's really loud and it hurts
oh that hurts to listen to what bullshit i'm only gonna do that when i need to because it's hurt
you look at how happy he is i know it's great i didn't even let go what is it timed
i'm also alive where's it gonna go oh my god okay it's when you touch anything
my controller for this so bad that's all right i'm telling you doing this with a keyboard it's
not easy it's like it's really awkward oh that's not good that's it i'm doing it again i'm doing
it again i can do it again it's gonna go fast watch this come on hurry up oh yes i actually
start here that's perfect oh what an awesome game this game is older i didn't even touch anything
what come on all right easy just right here why can there's something wrong
why is it not sticking uh well okay this something's wrong now i have to jump first
i can't just attach i guess i have to jump first all right now easy i have to jump over you
i you gotta double jump over that guy so it's double jump over the scorpion
shoot him i don't i don't have a i can't shoot him i don't have that power i have the eat
here we go nope watch out oh fuck i knew it was there too i knew i could feel it
wait should i just do this all right i got it nice no fuck i can't believe it i can't believe it i
have to play this again i have to do this again um i really like this how did i land perfectly
on this bike that's insane i just i jumped and it didn't grab yeah the bottom left is what i have
power ups okay up all right there again can i eat this no watch out i'm okay all right
oh look at it oh my god okay i can do it again i think it's gonna be three is there a speed run
of this game i feel like i'd want to see it another beach what's this called this is called
uh pack in time all right now i do have power ups all right slow down i can't okay i have to
land first oh i can fuck let's just jump it that's hard to control that it's really hard
it's like okay you know what it reminds me of the ninja rope in uh worms oh my god it
controls just like it too except it's like it's a worse version somehow all right i can't grab
anything gotta go one two three power up i gotta shoot something no vine vine is gone oh shit i
thought that was a platform oh did i get it no vine i got i got the vine nice oh i try to bull
myself up there all right let's say you get the vine let's go up here i have to do twice oh my god
it's fine i'm good all right what's over here i gotta jump and then uh stop okay we're good
a breeze i wonder how much more of the uh desert are we doing don't go crazy what's this whoa
the clock can i get that clock there's a one up down there okay i can't kill this
wow that was okay i clearly made it over that two three out let's see if i can snipe them
all right did i get them go down or i guess i could eat no it's only two globs i don't need it
wait secret oh nice shit i was trying to grab the last two sorry what i thought that was a
background image come on uh come on just turn this looks like a ramp oh my god i thought it
was a fucking background image again it's all right infinite continues i like this one i love
how i don't have to do and i don't have to start over that's great okay slow down how am i going
to jump over this though didn't make it last time i don't have to mine got it oh that puts
frame perfect it was all right so i gotta go eat through no i can move this okay interesting
i feel like if i fall i'm gonna die not quite oh shit wait i can't go down i don't have the air
bubble it's a secret over here i can't get oh i promise this is way harder than it looks
no stop i get that no i don't who cares holy shit i don't have any um power
we gotta jump i thought the momentum what oh shit okay the little green pellets out of the wall
okay dude like that's gonna be fucking hard to do
because you have to stay bouncing yeah okay let me show you something ready all right i'm not
jumping right now there's like this bounce momentum i'm not like hitting the jump button
i'm just gonna vine up i'm trying to go fast stop bouncing i can't help it it's doing it
i'm not pressing that button go up all right i'm done that game it's fun but i'm not doing it
anymore that's fun game what's next didn't even beat the desert all right where we're going down
here uh we got let's see is there anything else here to do i mean maybe Popeye there is a mario
down there that's why i can't scroll i don't want you to see spoilers well everybody was
clicking on Popeye so i'm just gonna do it and watch the bounce physics in this one Popeye Popeye
Popeye Popeye 2 actually Popeye 2 loading level one that was weird uh all right first i thought
is that Popeye i thought that was Popeye's foot down there is this a Rube Goldberg machine
uh i can't climb up the ladder control i can't a okay apparently this is just donkey kong but
zoomed way the fucking no i want to go up i don't know what the interact button is i tried alt control
a space i have to go up but then i have to go up there alt a alt space spaces jump what's cat do
Popeye okay from this angle it looks like Popeye has just bones he's like skeleton he's really
skinny you can see like the top part of his rib cage and then his spine uh q w s uh escape all
right let's move on was there anything else here that you guys wanted to see because we were right
here what do you think christmas lemmings wait wait what does happen to the clicking what website
is this is the archive.org ms dos uh dump there are 4 000 plus ms dos games there are a lot of
them some of them are better than others some of them are not some of them are good some of
them are bad all right we're gonna do christmas lemmings this is probably gonna be like a 30
second and then we leave because lemmings uh i last time we tried to play lemmings it didn't work
twice um okay here we go xmas lemmings uh f1 is one player f3 is music no it's on should be on
f4 are controls mouse no that's not gonna work it's doesn't it's not picking it up in the emulator
all right uh what's going to keyboard all right one player christmas lemmings i'm oh all right
no we're fine um where they coming from plus and minus one two three four space
alt space down left right q anything happening p one click alt i don't see anything being selected
they're all just kind of walking around in a circle one for nine doesn't seem to be doing
anything the cursor is moving where there's a cursor in the top left i don't press down
no it's not doing anything above the dancing santa oh god okay um oh yeah it's gonna be
yep it's gonna be q a o p this is gonna be hell and then select and all right can we get
all right i need like an ice pick all right ubi ice pick start going break through the ice
go get santa and then i need um what do i need i need some what does this thing do nothing
three four two one two two two one two holy shit i didn't uh that was insane okay let's try this one
more time we need to go to uh we need to get miners to go this way come back just give her
i'm gonna give everybody a pick no no no no that one's dead that one's just gonna dig straight
down everybody get over here and then what's what are the other ones okay you start mining
start mining get over there all of you get start mining go cross i'm just making a slide
okay now what is a juggler no just that's that's the crossing guard don't move all right
all right now stop stop stop stop don't go that far you guys gotta go up dude controlling this
they're dead okay controlling this with q a p thankfully you they're all going that way
stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop everybody stop moving all right just keep them there is there
like a fly you can float up right then i'll work the t posing i don't know what these ones do
what is it is it a climber oh he's climbing he's climbing from all the bodies all right no no no
don't get on like the person no he's making the the blocks all right so we're gonna do
up this way all right just restart it we're gonna do climbers why does this take so long
this game is fucked i have one left we're gonna do almost i'm gonna try to go across
try a little harder next time does the map go further this way oh my god it does um all right
i really wish i had that mouse all right i don't know now i need somebody to build
this shit is painful to play like this build over the snowman forget about the guys digging that
way just make the staircase over the snowman keep going no no no no no keep going keep going keep
going keep going keep going no no no no all the way up more you need to do more go from here come
on come on finish it finish it all right go now we're gonna go i have no idea where up are they
gonna walk up please tell me they're gonna make it okay i gotta plan the next part um we have to
mine or no just just walk walk just climb climb climb climb climb climb up they'll come back
those are gonna they're gonna get trapped in there but it's okay almost all right now what's
next they're gonna fall down here this is where they're supposed to go all right down they fall
wait they need umbrellas oh they're gonna they're gonna uh die umbrellas uh-oh uh-oh okay a couple
didn't make it it's okay but what about further ahead i need to know it's further i don't know
what's further ahead some people are just dying okay wait paul how do i pause the game
where's my cursor i need um all right get it down they're not i think they're gonna walk up
the cliff right turn how do i turn them around all right only stop stop stop stop oh bridge uh
make a bridge oh my god give me my fucking mouse my left hand is q and a and my right hand is o and
p it's killing me um ski bridge where's my where are my builders oh this is bad does anybody know
which one of these anybody have any idea stop stop don't put this put them here stop everybody
um what would work here oh it's the pause button the one on two like this one builder is oh two
yeah i know but it's not gonna be enough that might not be enough to get across
what is this one is this just more lemmings what does that mean oh that's explode well thank god
you're gonna be away from everybody i only have two of these though i don't think it's gonna work
no people is gonna fall off it's over wait did he just turn why did you do that what are these
okay let's go over so what some of them do floater loader what's the juggler oh they're digging
straight down okay what about like this the i'm assuming this is i can i can walk up walls
he's gonna make it is that gonna kill him no uh well there's nothing i can do here this game is
i love this game but i would want like a better way to control it is everybody still alive over
here what was that what's the dragon thing do oh time that was fun but i want to be able to
play it the way that i want to play it's an old classic it's a good one though all right it's
time to scroll down i think i know i'm just gonna click it because i know everybody's gonna i mean
i'm gonna click it right i have to i have to click this we're gonna queue that one up
skipped king's quest yeah but here's the thing about the game like king's quest is hours and
hours long there's a lot on here that's gonna be really good all right well pick one what do
you guys think virtual mario the price is right and then let what i'm just gonna queue these up
we all know what i want to play the terminator price is right life and death and virtual mario
because i want to play those well we might as well just do the one we just said we were gonna do
price is right this is by the way this is 1990 so think about prices
come on down i know how to play but we're gonna give the instructions anyways yeah wonderful
place make people entering their names and characters if you're the four yeah yeah yeah
i know how to play price is right you got to come closest to the item pictured without going over
how much you think it is okay i know how to do this i've seen it before all right i know do we
do you want sound of course i do number of players one uh let's go with mail please type the name
player one there you go the peas everybody that's fine leo ken leslie and karen
leo what is the price of this vinyl modular sofa set from simmons okay sofa set three um
five six ninety nine six ninety nine you don't want to go over the retail price is seven hundred
leo you are the winner press enter to continue i got it by one dollar
do i need instructions no the range game what press enter to start the bar what is the price
of this 35 millimeter autofocus camera from fuji um i'm gonna say probably 400 three to 400 like
right here fuck what am i at 250 that's like two i'm so close oh wayne come on down you're
the next contestant on the price is right no i don't have to watch no no no no no no that's
not fair no restart it no restart that's i don't know i want to restart yeah reality can be
whatever i want it to be that's true one player player number one and it's me just me all right
let's go what is the price of this forehead programmable stereo vcr from dull to 250 300
let me say three um to 249 were they this expensive holy shit 534 dollars no i'm not
going to play for the computer what is the price of this uh athletic football use the arrows to
highlight the correct price what's the price he's getting everything wrong oh you want a puck
wow you get two pucks dude nice try a dollar that's 100 never mind 600 bucks actually not bad
all right now sit down kim okay what is the price of this instant start three speed mo okay i thought
just looking at that i thought it was a car sitting on top of like a tow truck or a crane or
something and i was gonna say that's like 40 grand mower a lawn mower 400 probably 400 500 bucks
i'm gonna say 550 fuck safe cracker you're gonna get it wrong wrong wrong it's 700 sit down
come on down ben uh that's germa pop what is the price of this 10 carat yellow gold ring with a
diamond what i can't even do more than four digits 10 carat yellow gold ring with a diamond
7 000 oh my god i was way off 675 dollars for a diamond gold ring that's not correct
take two i don't even know what he's doing you lose spin the wheel do you need instructions wait
i don't get a chance i can't go i don't even get to go i don't get to even do the showcase
no fuck that i'm doing i'm going to do it again oh you got yourself 90 tickets
oh that's a big spin there let's see what you get for those tickets i don't want dave to win
oh nice you got yourself a hundred tickets fuck dave you try to get closest to a dollar
and you will compete for the grand prize in the showcase enter number of players round two
what do you mean i don't get to oh i had to go sit back down okay okay i'll be germa pop
what's the price of this pair of diamond earrings i don't know it's for 15 dollars
so i'm gonna say like 1200 i didn't get it uh what hold on six seven eight nine nine ten eleven
twelve oh what's how much was i off by i went over it shit i'll leave hey now i know what the
camera is uh gary what is the price of this portable cd player from uh magnavox 20 19
dollars no these were expensive 29 a portable cd player in 1990 was probably like 30 to 60 bucks
i'm gonna say like snow not that much i'm gonna say like 40 49 oh my god 200 bucks for real
200 fucking dollars all right come on down mike all right i did my last chance what is the price
of this heavy-duty drill saw and socket set you guys in the audience are screaming numbers um
probably 400 probably 600 no three 375 135 bucks an entire furniture set for your living room
worth of tools is worth less than a cd player well i lose again do we need instructions spin
the wheel ah i can't wait to watch other people have fun i have to get to the showcase points
i have to let me just get there once that's all i care about we got yourself 10 tickets heidi
spinning again for a dollar don't can you say i hold it so half of you hate that and half of you
love that half these cpus guessed wrong by hundreds of dollars how have you not made it
i don't know because i've guessed wrong just let me in the showcase i just want to do it once
and then we can move on i guess i'll just refresh the game
oh good job here comes the showcase no i want to do this i'm doing this one more chance
that showcase was dog shit that was a like two thousand dollar showcase
all right let's go what is the price of this stereo cd player with equalizer so these are
expensive they have to be right like a thousand bucks if the cd player the portable one was
200 this is probably like more at least three to seven five hundred six hundred i'm gonna say
299 or three uh three 399 350 oh amy what the fuck that was way off all right what's the price
deluxe three-speed microwave from samson 250 180 like 160 to it's i don't know it's between like
it's i don't know it's between like one and 300 bucks two i'm gonna say two two uh two
260 oh my fucking god please be right yes no what oh this so what's what i don't know what
is the price of this three-day cruise for two from san francisco to where 1200 bucks
two 1200 1500 999 i'm gonna do 999 or 899 is that too high 799 790 690 i had it right the first time
i should have done you gotta be fucking kidding me i had it right i had it was i had it at the
fucking 1200 999 would have been fine why why why did i listen to you guys i was gonna do 999
i still would have lost no no fucking i'm doing it again can you yell for the rest of the stream i
don't feel like turning my volume up what do you mean yell what is the price of this solid oak table
and chairs set for okay solid oak is expensive 799 maybe more it might be like six six to eight
hundred um i'm gonna do 799 there's almost five thousand fucking dollars more than diamond gold
rings what is the price of this 20 inch silver necklace silver is not that expensive but i don't
know if okay this is more expensive than the diamond ring i'm gonna swallow uh uh one half
of a switch control a hole okay thankfully i'm never gonna get to play one of these games
never what is the price of this double oven and range from zappin five five hundred six
hundred it's always way more or way less it's not a thousand i'm gonna say 800 850 i told you i told
you it wasn't that expensive all right i'm putting my hand over chat no i'm doing it i swear to god
this is the last try and then i'm gonna move on i was gonna say like 599 a 600 no it's 1200 bucks
all right not this time here we go uh wait i didn't give i didn't even get my name i'm just
no name what is the price of this 14 carat small link gold necklace it was a hundred for the
silver one so that means it has to be like 200 for the gold one 300 299 go do it fuck off george
all right it was uh 800 right it was exactly 800 bucks for this one wasn't it it was right
i did it you are the winner i get okay well take two whatever okay from four wait a minute
so they change that price changed from the two games ago i okay so that's bullshit this whole
game is rigged from four items shown select two whose prices when added together will equal to
show price so this is gonna show four items and two of those items added are the price shown item
one item two what item one is this remote control toy car item two is a pair of kids plastic
sunglasses so we've got a remote control car a pair of shitty sunglasses a football a leather
football and a 640k computer with two drives well this is going to be fucking impossible
it's obviously the computer because um okay so the the plastic shades are have to be a dollar
or two right ding ding got it i get to be in the showcase fuck yeah yeah do whatever you want i'm
in the showcase now good luck sanford oh he's doing plinko i have to i have to win the wheel
right all right if i lose the wheel i'm just gonna take control of the person that's playing
i'm just gonna like i got five grand okay well i would just who cares if you don't go to the
showcase just take the five grand that's really good takeaway that's six grand this guy's screaming
right now 6100 bucks in 1990 that's like that's like four million now all right spin the wheel i
do not need instructions you have to come as close to a dollar without going over as possible
george is going again something low 25 25 no are you serious okay what i didn't get to i didn't
even get to see i didn't hold it down 70 cents 90 cents 100 oh yeah wait i don't want to spin it
again how do i say don't i don't want to spin it again there was no option for me to say no
that was my most powerful spin i was a bonus money all right right okay i don't know what
i just kind of freaked out there 85 65 70 you guys said it was for the bonus what i don't
know what the what the fuck is that why couldn't i say no i i can't i he didn't he had a choice
to not spin it again where was my choice if this dickhead wins with 10 cents i mean come on
i i don't understand what this is this is virtual mario um that was guys that was a jump scare face
um keys used during all map screen the four arrow keys work for movement in the direction they
indicate jump up down up arrow down pick up an object is p okay mario speaks d p and d
it's a me mario okie dokie princess speaks hello bowser speaks jump crouch left right jump okay
right and left is jump up jump up sh shuriken shuriken shrunken mario walking left right pick
up an object as the green shield drop an object such as the green shell so you can stand on it
insert as fire fireball only when there is a fire flower enter shoot a red shell only when
there is a red or purple shell in mario's inventory mario speaks uh okay i think i
understand read the story the mushroom kingdom is in great mourn ever since the governor of the
mushroom kingdom had received an urgent stress call from princess toadstool his daughter of
princess toadstool accompanied by luigi for her safety were making trips across the land
looking for mystery super mushrooms the call was made from the royal family's submarine somewhere
near the northern hemisphere of the planet called the yoshi's world the message was simple the
princess and luigi were trapped on the shore of lake hamhurst where their submarine had been
wrecked by a violent storm at sea this is where mario's role comes to play mario must make his
way to lake hamhurst to all right enough to rescue the princess in luigi why does mario have to do
the job you ask well when bowser heard word about the princess and luigi being stranded on the
shore of lake hamhurst he sent his goons out to stop any i can still hear it stop any rescue
ships from coming to the rescue it seems bowser is up to his no good the only one who is capable
of beating bowser's good goons and rescuing the princess and luigi by the way luigi forgot his
firefowl hour at home leaving him powerless against bowser's goons is mario this this is
still going this situation would not be as bad as it by the way trying to read this
like purple the purple text with no outline on this background is i have to like cross my eyes
the situation would not be as bad as if it would be however mario was just recently taking a
vacation from just had rescued the princess from bowser a month earlier is not in the area yoshi's
world as such mario must travel from the planet he is now on to yoshi's world four planets way
however he must stop this is predictive text i feel like i'm i wrote this on an iphone line by
line he must stop on each planet to pick up the key which only then can he continue his journey
on the next planet bowser is also making his way through therefore mario must battle against
bowser's goons time is against mario as he must make it to the submarine wreck princess and luigi
before bowser does will mario become the hero once again okay let me welcome to my shore
for
40 20 dollars 40 dollars 50 dollars how much money do i have 50 dollars p i don't think i have any
money the turtles don't have heads wait how do i talk what does talk oh h i go higher sometimes
i just can't i'm trying to jump on his head why can't attack why can't i attack oh my god
what what do i do how do i talk how do i do anything other way these different planets
i have to do this one all right seriously there's got to be a way
i'm gonna try to jump on his head just wait till he falls and then i can jump real high over here
all right i can't jump that high this way there are keys i got one key i made it up here okay i
made it up what is that thing that's an enemy from number munchers come on get up there fire
flower get it what you can't jump you cannot jump on any of these heads okay uh the other
one that people wanted was life and death then we'll choose another one keep going life and death
hi doctor welcome to tool works general won't you please sign in name of warren or john
can i pick my own oh ernie nice to meet you ernie report to medical school for your orientation
happy friday hey happy friday to you happy friday good luck happy friday happy friday to you too
greetings doctor good luck today greetings happy friday leave me alone tgif a doctor greetings
doctor tgif how are you today i'm good what about class welcome to tool works general hospital
you're currently in the classroom whenever the chief of surgery feels that you need schooling
you'll be instructed to come here when you're finished reading the blackboard use your mouse
or mouse substitute to click on the board the instructor will then put up the next lesson
if you need to reread a lesson click your mouse or mouse substitute at the very top of the blackboard
while making your rounds at tool works general use your mouse or mouse substitute to enter and
exit rooms by pointing and clicking at doors you may also use the escape key to exit rooms
to leave the hospital exit through the door at the far end of the hall
while you're in the hospital you may request the hospital policies and guidelines clipboard
by clicking on an intercom or pressing the f1 key use the clipboard to set
game parameters you may not request this clipboard during surgery to exit the classroom
click on the door behind the instructor or press escape this concludes class for now
thank you for attending that's it okay well you have you have a patient in room one that's the
second door on your left good luck today happy friday what was that okay what seems to be the
problem let me open your present okay what we'll just zoom um what did i do what how do i go back
did i just like we're doing surgery no no no go back go back go back um patient is a 59 year old
male patient was admitted complaining of abdominal pain accompanied by generalized weakness nausea
and a runny nose so i just like poked his stomach okay uh admitted of abdominal pain
and weakness nausea and runny nose let's observe the patient and let's do it uh let's just let's
just observe the patient for now no we are hold on i'm not going to operate let's uh an ult what's
an ultra scan uh referral somebody else to do this no let's do an x-ray let's find out let's get an
x-ray of your stomach and see if we can see anything is that the stuff that's not the stomach all
right is there anything here i didn't see anything observed you diagnosed this and recommended
treatment were incorrect and you have been taken off the case report to medical school on the
double dr wilson called from the lounge on line four medical school is the first door on your
right better go now all right when the nurse tells you that you have received a phone call it is
considered poor protocol not to return the call you may use the phone on the front desk your beeper
should tell you the correct extension to call in your last case your physical examination of
the abdomen was incomplete you must be sure to palpate all four quadrants of the abdomen
including the sides of the lower abdomen and the navel area for the exam to be effective so i did
an exam in your last case you ordered an unnecessary x-ray the patient's symptoms did not indicate a
need for an x-ray padding the hospital bill in this manner is frowned upon at tool works general
this concludes class for now thank you for attending okay dr wilson on number four okay call
call for the line four how do i use the phone like 004 number four it really is
triple zero four this is dr wilson thanks for calling back keep sharp today that's all is it
you have a patient in room four last door on your right here we go are you sure what are you talking
about should go she left last door on the right patient is 24-year-old male patient was admitted
complaining of acute abdominal pain accompanied by nausea cramping and generalized weakness okay
all right let me take a look that feels all right no problems here no pain there that doesn't hurt
right there right here all right it's on the left side all right i think that's that's the kidney
right no is that the gallbladder okay so right here that's like a side flank pain that's uh what
is that okay so you're not no only down here in the lower lower left side of your stomach
i'm thinking we should uh lower left of the stomach flu-like symptoms maybe medication
or maybe do an ultrasound or refer to a gastroenterologist maybe some pain relief
and then a referral no i would just i would be it would be referral what you recommend a course of
action was correct but you did not follow the correct procedure that was right in your last
case your examination the abdomen revealed that the patient was experiencing pain on both sides of
the lower abdomen even though the appendix is on the right side some appendicitis patients will
experience pain on both sides during examination an x-ray is required how the fuck was i supposed
to know last door on the left they're all they'll have abdominal pain hey i got an idea why don't
we check the water that's the third person with the same acute abdominal pain in the last 10
minutes flu-like symptoms okay let's take a look no pain okay we've got no pain no pain at all
all right so no pain to touch which means you've got the flu medicaid your last case the examination
of the patient revealed that the patient was not suffering from acute abdominal pain further
observation of the patient is indicated as the usual cause of uh transient abdominal pain as an
intestinal gas abdominal pain okay patient suffering from abdominal pain accompanied by
flu-like symptoms nausea generalized weakness and dizziness all right we got acute pain
on both sides anywhere else left and right we're gonna do an x-ray left and right right
okay i'm just gonna confirm okay we're good x-ray what does that show nothing i think we're good
nothing there um observe operate ultra scan let's do an ultra scan i don't know what that is
you get the screen pop up and the first thing the doctor says i don't know what that is you don't
know what organ this is oh wait hold on you like wipe the lens sorry there's some mustard on there
i don't i don't know what i'm looking at i don't know what that is uh refer operate but i don't
know that but what is what was i even looking at that needs surgery wait hold on operate i can't
operate referral what wait wait i just skipped it it just skipped what happened what back to class
no kidney stones appendicitis is the correct diagnosis surgery should have been scheduled
immediately and i tried to was it room four acute abdominal pain all right same deal pain on both
sides um does anybody remember the game at the arcade this is a long time ago so not very many
you guys are gonna know i'm talking about but there was a game that was crocodiles and they'd
be like i'm gonna get you and it was it was a game ad was a physical game you had a mallet
and they would come out they would go across it was like and you'd go you'd have to hit them and
it made this exact noise they would come over and it would be like right that was one of my
favorite games it is the no it is all right so i'm like pounding on this stomach and you know
you know when you make that noise it's really funny your stomach hurts but
remember that that game at the arcade all right we're gonna do x-ray nothing here um operate
surgery operate initial operate how do i operate your patient ready for surgery don't just tell me
where they are don't speak another language to me where does the surgery room oh here we go
oh shit okay um where are we where what is this what is what i would do with like that hamster
water bowl thing all right there i would suggest anesthesia before beginning surgery right right
right soap okay uh where is it is this it where's the where's anesthesia gas turn it on okay
anesthesia's on um wouldn't you rather wash your hands for surgery what where's the sink
what you are rather unsterile where's the sink oh my god you have scrubbed doctor
okay i've never seen a surgeon operate with his bare hands before
well i've never seen somebody as good as me all right let's go uh we do this okay 45
basically a flu-like symptoms nausea generalizer okay let's go doctor uh nalor called from the er
online too what is it don't forget the staff meeting yeah okay okay put the gas on wash hands
put on the gloves okay now what what do we do now scalpel would you like to inject antibiotics
yes where's the antibiotic injector the patient may become infected with antibiotics
where's the antibiotics i would like to inject antibiotics first yes i would
this is the thing that they put in your mouth at the dentist the like the thing that sucks
is this it well this is this changed which one's antibiotic i don't know which one of these is
antibiotic is it this one a g b s is there anything in this what did i inject him with
what did i inject him with why give me a break i wanted to give antibiotics that's
fucked up why i why is that even there a for antibiotic jesus use your mouse or mouse substitute
to click on the patient's body you will then be presented with the patient's abdomen i know
but why you're not teaching me anything okay instead of here's how you click on the door to
leave the classroom maybe you should tell you doctors about what syringe is fucking adrenaline
and what is an antibiotic okay let's do is it everywhere okay it's everywhere okay it's the
whole thing so we're talking about it's the whole stomach hmm maybe um observe maybe generalized
weakness and not dizziness i think we need an x right here so this is they're just really really
this is the kind of scenario that you would do to somebody when you know they fucked up with
the antibiotics before this symptom indicates the presence of a bacterial infection which should be
treated with antibiotics right mike and everyone looks at me and i'm just like oh fuck no what you
took the phone away from me give me the phone back give me the phone back now you left staff meeting
what's this what this is i can pick who i want on staff i feel print available um what did i just
do okay what do you mean flu-like symptoms abdominal pain is also present okay hold on
we got we have a some acute pain here on the right side okay acute pain on the right side
so that requires a that requires an x-ray is that something here okay i think that's uh
i think we have to get i think we have to operate it's a that's appendicitis
okay appendicitis see you in a minute wash hands put on the gloves okay next draw
come on i want the other one please okay be antibiotic that's not the one
the gas what just happened what just happened what kidneys okay referrals right when i turned
the gas on he was like testing me they got everybody ready to go and got everybody in that
room for me to be like okay everyone in here everyone in their scrubs oh yeah let's go turn
that don't get are you serious you spent all that time why wouldn't you just tell me no i thought
i just said surgery is easy i was like flu-like symptoms nausea weakness dizziness abdominal pain
all right let's take a look both sides in pain this is both sides in pain always means what
ow that means that we have a we have to do a um an x-ray i don't see the presence of any bacteria
maybe an ultrasound both pain and weakness on both sides see you in the classroom operate no no no no
i'm gonna say medicate no cramping dizziness operate i just don't i don't see anything though
ultrasound looks like it's up right don't forget our golf game next week all right it's b for
antibiotic this is correct right it's not like d for like anti-diotic it's not like l for like
anti-liotic it's b for antibiotic i didn't wash my hands oh shit i didn't doctor you got your
gloves on is this any this is an antibiotic okay now that's not an antibiotic that's like a topical
alcohol it is it's you're it's wrong it's wrong it's wrong it's one of these syringes i have to
inject got it you've injected antibiotics good okay here we go it is not proper procedure to
leave this much of the patient's body uncovered if it is not part of the operation use the drape
to cover the unaffected area you've got it is this the drape which one of these is drape this
all right surgical site has been uh draped doctor here we go i'm not skipping it it's doing it
automatically what what happened what happened what did i do wrong all right we got we got pain
on the we got pain on the left side let's go ahead and say you but maybe you got kidney stone
you don't but what does that mean i don't know what to do from here
operate appendicitis operate doctor schwartz called from the gift shop what do you mean from
the gift shop your lab reports will be ready tomorrow i mean lab reports antibiotics antibiotics
administered is because i put this shit all over it huh why that's a that's a very small area
do i have to that's what have we taken out what are we taking out it's a coin slot okay hold on
the patient's skin is not sterile hold on okay are we ready to go in don't hack up the sterile
drape what what are you talking about can somebody screen grab that because i i'm not skipping it
it's skipping it automatically i'm not touching anything uh can somebody freeze frame that and
tell me what it said slow the game down okay uh who's calling me acute abdominal pain he said
there are procedures you have to follow before you're allowed to operate nausea cramping weakness
and dizziness all right so here we go pain on the left side pain on both sides okay so pain on
both sides is you check for the for kidney stones and then you refer kidney stones on both sides
i don't i'm not qualified for this so this is a referral to a to a urologist very nicely done
your diagnosis of kidney stones and your decision to refer to the patient will both correct
thank you very much room four abdominal pain weakness nausea and runny nose you might just
have the flu pain everywhere okay so this is potential for medication nice job your recommendation
to administer antibiotics for a case of bacterial infection is correct all right acute abdominal
pain by nausea cramping generalized weakness and dizziness all right we got no pain no pain
with um flu-like symptoms that is a hold on a minute here observation good job intestinal gas
acute abdominal pain accompanied by nausea cramping generalized weakness and dizziness
does anybody have anything else besides like stomach pain right side generalized pain in the
right side nothing on the left side generalized pain on the right side is we've got to do a um
an x-ray not kidney stones it's time to operate let's go line two hope you enjoy success today
okay thank you thank you doctor for your fortune cookie can you're gonna give me my lucky numbers
too all right turn the gas on antibiotic good oops i didn't put gloves on okay good now we
are going to drape the area all right sterilize the skin we are completely clean now what the
fuck is going on here what do i do now drag around the rectangle like this i just go like this
right not the knife not the knife without the knife the drape is on wrong oh jeez what does
it want me to do how much i don't know where it wants me to go but what does it want me to go
choose the spot to cut then cut that's what i'm doing you put the drape where you want it i mean
don't i want it like here i can only go look let's say i start up here it doesn't matter
it's gonna have to be just like this i don't know you're the doctor okay so like this here
bottom left ah bottom left ah what do you mean bottom left ah but i can't do bottom left don't
you stand like look it doesn't matter i can't like bring this over here it's only this the square is
only i can make it only bigger and smaller in the middle is it gonna have to be like this top right
i'm just going in drape everything oh my god all right i'm just fucking going in i hope it's
right here so okay ready i'm gonna click and hold i need to practice oh
but which tool do i use is the thing am i going to clamp something they didn't teach me how to do
surgery they just said go do surgery hook up the blood what the hell was that okay that's what that
does what does this one do that's the problem okay this is the issue it's got to be sticking
out and then cut i just want to see what they do i just want to see what they do i just want to
wait did you just tell me the for the first time ever how to fucking do surgery okay hold on hold
on every single time he didn't tell me shit and then now he does okay all right let me just hold
on none of these people are dying they're fine i got it under control so we need to do scissors
no we do four the forceps stick these in here and then the knife right use the sponge no the
scissors what do you mean use the scissors i just did these last time i got yelled at you need to
hook up their blood there is no blood to hook up it's the scalpel it's i have to quit i can't
fucking do anything the blood is the red bottle all right but what is he saying right there
i can't read it because it skips it automatically i can't i can't stop it
that's not the proper procedure will you tell me what i did wrong yes there's a phone call okay
hold on i know right right okay i know why does it tell me how to do an examination but it doesn't
tell me to do surgery and they don't have class you don't have to do surgery
look it up all right i'm gonna do one more and try to get it right and but i don't understand
the surgery part anybody who's left abdominal pain with flu-like symptoms let's take a look
we're just gonna observe you because everything looks like it's fine
congratulations space yourself from intestinal gas you did it all right somebody just
flu-like symptoms nausea generalized weakness and dizziness all right pain in the left and right
sides and then that means we look for kidney stones don't have kidney stones
okay so now it's time it's time to operate ultra ultra again nobody even knows what that's what
that is it's been the same image every single time thanks for calling back be careful out there
okay all right i'm going to try this one more time i can't use any of the dials no and now
let's do antibiotic drape here i guess the patient's skin is not sterile okay
okay now what do we want what do you want to do get the iv bag drug the blood shit to the plastic
bottle thing left of the text box are you fucking kidding me so this blood the blood iv is in place
now doctor do we have to connect it is it already in is it ready are we ready to go now i can
cut cut now cut now no wait let me cut it's just it is sterilized cut vertically cut vertically
i'm cut i'm gonna do it cut vertically i got fired again cut wildly cut in a circle no
no i want to see what it does uh all right now what use saline instead of blood is it do i need
to saline connect to the iv tube no that's the ek that's the ekg what i just do what is this thing
doing what is this oh those are stitches what is this i don't know what that does i don't know what
that is it's an x x marks the spot this doesn't do anything though all right this is my last try
i can't even i can't even cut why can i not cut i can't cut them i can't even
like why can i not do this i can't even pull these out doctor really doctor must you handle
the patient in such a fashion blood's going down quick it's all right i can refill it you should
probably attend to the patient's weakening heartbeat check the ekg check the ekg all right what i can't
do it i'm out medical school hold on oh my god hello what was that all right i'm moving on i
can't do this one anymore i can't it's too much i really wanted to do a surgery but i couldn't
there's a sequel to this game that involves wait there's a sequel should i do the sequel yes no no
no yes yes no no no no yes yes yes what's it called what is it called it's not kingdom hearts
two life and death two i'm kind of invested i need to know same name too okay it is a game life and
death to the brain okay let's try it so okay was life and death one the stomach and life and death
to the brain doctor tom jack dr jack please report to the classroom right how do you arrange
dr grippen in the classroom this afternoon yeah just the sight of norris and heidi back in here
in an eating bench this is not the classroom oh that's it southeast should always perform a
full physical examination of the patient before specifying a treatment so that you have all the
information and avoid a misdiagnosis yeah uh brain infarction is growing a blood vessel supplying the
brain become blocked by blood clot the symptoms are very similar those of brain tumors okay weakness
and loss of sensation the clean side of the body upset infraction pupil dilation light reaction and
eye movement are also affected on that side okay speech impairment and it's very to the left side
best way to identify uh infraction the cat it's it's not afraid to infarction oh my scan the uh
angiogram may show the occlusion while cat never i would feel this area the only effect of treatment
for infarction is physical therapy which may restore much of the patient's abilities lost
through the death of brain cell welcome to the neurosurgery wing of tool works general hospital
you are currently in the classroom you've been told to come here when the chief neurosurgeon
feels you are need some instruction you may view all this lesson by clicking on the projection
screen with your mouse or about substitute wink remember from last game okay back to the beginning
of the lesson you can go into any room by yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yep click on over the mouse
feel free to explore the hospital to find out where everything is the receptionist is located at
somewhere in the center of the hospital she can help you if you get lost
click on that hospital's guideline of policy make changes the game settings okay class is over
dr jack you a patient in room three which one is room three this is my patient this is my patient
what's say what am i doing say alice what is this uh hold on all right looks good
wait hold on you can you can't feel it on the right arm okay can't you can't feel this though
fit wait a minute face arms reflex uh is it right reflex absent on the right side
weakness okay reflex absent on the i can't check that box what is going on no no no no
i want to get back get me out of here i'm gonna go but like let's go back to his bed okay say alice
alice alice okay do you feel this hey you that's in the face right you can do that
get to class please don't stick the pin in the patient's eyes imagine going to class at a medical
school and they say please don't stick the pin in the patient's eyes really i really i i don't know
no what is this is this like a cigarette what is this no this you shine a light in their eyes right
i think so well those are dilated well i come back over here what do i do this oh my what the
what is going on how do i left right up down okay let's take a look at the sheet face uh
abnormal dilation no light reaction left and right both okay arms let's go back to the arms
okay got reflexes on both you got feeling on both okay let's note that okay and then
we're going down here okay okay so that looks like we've got uh pretty good we got we got
abnormal dilation in the eyes and no reaction to light huh interesting patient's 57 year old
man who came to the hospital said he conscious according to friends he was non-responsive to
their presence allergic to crab and other shellfish okay so we've no dilation in the eyes
next time for uh for a potential uh was that normal does that look normal yep that's a brain
all right so uh should i code red in the cat scanner what are they i thought they were eating
him for a second i was like this is fucked i thought they were eating his body oh my god
they're cannibalizing the guy what happened yeah this is still fucked up what your patient died
in the cat scanner due to an allergic reaction to the contrast dye i didn't know that patient's
history oh some patients are allergic to iodine which is used to contrast type the cat scanner
you should not order cat scans or such patients use the mri allergic reactions to shellfish
and those seafood is a good indicator that patient has an allergy okay patient in room four
all right that's not good um what's that on the on the right eye what's in the right eye
is that normal okay you're reacting to light
okay no pain no pain on the right side no eye tracking it's slurred speech all right hold on
let's go to the arms okay we got uh this this is there's no no feeling in the right arm here
okay no feeling in the right arm what about the right leg okay the whole right side the whole
right side is is uh having some uh some uh nervous system issues i think okay so what do we do severe
headache all right we're gonna have to do an MRI okay it's in there i guess it's it's no uh
prescribed um what does that mean i don't know what that means um so is this a is this um
it's a stroke but how what do i do for how to prescribe treatment uh
aneurysm brain subdural what's it called with that is that but is that an aneurysm
all right let's go so it's ready for you in the aura where's that where's the aura okay
welcome to the oh no um okay soap uh i can identify tools uh hold on let me
anybody oh there's even more of these okay b i irrigator bone wax metal ribbon used to cauterize
um why wouldn't they teach me how to do this staple gun that's to close cotton swabs
drape what haven't you forgot haven't you forgot something doctor i don't know what you mean by
that why don't you tell me i have gloves on i'm trying to wash my hands with gloves on
what is this i don't know what i just do i can't close my drawer here close the drawer um just
run just be like i don't know and run draw i guys i got no fucking idea which one of these do i need
to do no put that in the eye okay blood no no what's g there's g already in there glucose
menthol saline blood g a not doing that um where's uh antibiotics did it go in okay now um
is the patient under i don't is i don't i don't know i don't know is i can't i don't know if the
am i forgetting haven't you forgotten something doctor turn the patient's head first what what do
we turn the patient's head what do you spy what uh what uh keep it up okay i did cut there was a
was um my drain um never use antiseptic in the body let me it's in the body i'm not even in the
body what is this thing sutures okay get me out of here okay now i need to where's the um
drill what needs to go in there okay glucose is in there closing the draw is fucking impossible
sometimes shit what what close the close the draw close the draw close the draw close the draw
close the draw i can't even close the fucking draw i can't even close the draw it's too complicated
you lift the respirator on high what do you mean the okay bring pco2 levels down to normal about
30 okay so only do they only turn that on to okay double class okay i give up i'm not gonna i'm
never gonna get it it's never gonna happen all right it's time to do the final few i'm gonna
scroll down here somebody said come on gerber it's not brain surgery it is okay what do we got i'm
scrolling down a little bit because i think that's pretty much all the good ones up here
what do you think got an opportunity here i think right there that'll do it uh what do you think
where do you want to go i have podracers yeah kind of well duke nukem's penthouse paradise
is a veto sorry gremlins 2 though which is one of the best movies ever made good choice nice choice
let's go i hope we get the music it's gonna happen here we go there it is
no it didn't say that's not shrek 2 demo start now i want to play this looks fun
okay this looks really fucking fun i want to play how do i play i don't want to just watch
this this looks awesome insert coins f1 i don't think that worked shit i want to play this one
in the main menu screen press space to enter the menu then select control to keyboard otherwise
it's impossible to play okay thank you random commenter appreciate it space space space space
okay control uh space press the key you wish to use for the following left
space what right a what the fuck are you doing no no no no no what is going on this is not correct
no no i don't want left to be n no stop okay is this correct no left okay right's gonna be m
up is gonna be um let me guess q and a and fire sure let's go here we go let's do it
i didn't i didn't click the redefine keys button fuck no now they're different the
fucking keys are different though let's go i don't at least get one gremlin i instantly died okay i'm
done let's do one more one more one more uh two more two more i think would be sufficient i can't
leave this game apparently i'm stuck here for real hello hello all right so what's the last
one gonna be you think what should we do by the way tomorrow is uh terraria me and star are gonna
play terraria i'm not sure what exact time but probably somewhere like typical time in the
afternoon all right where we going and no i am not going to click on duke nukem's porn game
really i can't click i can't click on that guys obey us obey us because if i click this it's
gonna be a porn game sid meyers railroad tycoon we did too but that was the first one we did
railroad tycoon i mean this is it's my i might only play this for like 10 minutes
this is gonna be a long boring game now revote revote revote 60 60 percent of you guys
are clicking on something that you shouldn't be clicking on change your vote i'll tell you right
now if more than if more than 60 percent of people click on that don't even make me do it
the bard's tale three thief of fate thank you for voting uh chat can never be trusted here we go
that game is actual porn i could imagine if it's called duke nukem's porn palace i don't even know
what the hell it was called palace penthouse penthouse porn i don't know it's something like
that oh hey come on i'm an engineer hey look buddy come here the tale of a um
this is happening way too fast somebody that's holding the person that's in charge of the
teleprompter you gotta slow down this is a long ass song do you wish to restore your last say
no i don't have a safe game the art in the camp of scarabray add a member rename a member create
a member transfer characters delete member um it's kind of running like shit add a member
how do i get us to not run like shit who shall join greg greg gwendolin okay let's add a member
iron pants okay hit point spell ac okay add a member create a member okay hobbit half out
first been to hobbit hit it you uh we're gonna do um a magician okay did i not add me oh i just
made like a class all right one one more a green bolt all right let's go enter the wilderness
okay to the north of the campus refugee camp all right i got some pretty bad okay no no no no no no
enter the wilderness this is running like dog shit to the tree facing west facing south oh what's this
gold rocks what's our goal i'm kind of just lost gourd gourd rulers what is a gorge ruler
oh your onslaught is greeted with laughter you face three gorge rulers 10 will your gallant
band choose to fight bravely or run away we're going to fight bravely gwendolin has these options
this battle round attack foes use an item bard song okay gwendolin has pretty good hit attack
foes iron pants has these battle options attack where's iron pants 333 hit germa has these options
cast a spell use an item cast a spell use spell to cast uh vocal goofy or sissy how about sissy
and green bolt let's do uh attack foes use these commands green bolt swings at a gourd ruler and
hits for five points of damage nice job now who's next anything else happen derma casts a spell
scary sight that's just jump scared somebody gwendolin slashes at a gourd ruler and hits for
seven damage iron pants swings at gorge ruler and hits for seven damage okay do we win you still
face three gourd rulers who will your gallant band choose to what to put me this is three okay let's
do a song so robin safety sanctuary or watch wood melody let's try that attack what can i do for
spells but that's okay i don't know what i just did it just was lagged and picked one i think it
was scary sight uh attack germa cast scary sight four points of damage the gourd ruler slices a
green bolt and hits for six points of damage uh green bull gets stabbed again and gets hit for
seven points one of the gourd rulers is dead from iron pants a gourd ruler summons help and none
appears gwendolin plays one note okay let's keep fighting uh party attack attack member one to
four how many are there we're fighting together i don't know three attack attack uh what other
spells do i have let's do uh vocal casted member one two four um so i don't know three attack use
these commands am i am i i'm gonna attack my own party okay vorbal plating iron pants swings at
gorge ruler hits for five damage okay green boat slashes gourd ruler hits for four damage
why would you attack your own party why is that even possible i thought that meant like we'd
attack together as one move or something attack foes attack foes we can't even beat the sludge
enemies what's the other one uh let's do it at four okay one more is dead germa cast quick fix
five points of damage to the enemy critically hitting for three points of damage it's not that
good and killing it no and hitting it oh it's dead each character receives 525 experience
points for valor and battle knowledge and 105 gold that's pretty awesome actually let's keep going
just walk west do i have a map oh what's this what is that is a wall what's in is there anything in
this is there a door there's something else over here too what is that minerals it's a camp but
hold on it's blocked by the trees i can't get in there oh shit it's the circus oh really what i
just want to go over there oh my god i have to like maneuver around the fucking trees
go in there get i want to get over here straight right puma do we just get attacked one puma will
you um one puma 20 one puma 20 health i think we can kill it everybody's attack at the same time
kill it i missed the puma gwendolin misses the puma the puma advances iron pants actually hits
the damn thing and so does green bolt it's kind of coming like tear my throat out isn't it you
still face one puma it's got 10 health fight attack go on oh puma claws a green bolt hits it
for 11 damage green bolt okay killing it nice it's dead it's dead you have any treasure 50 gold 250
exp nice all right now let me in here it shouldn't be this difficult to get in here you've done such
a great job keeping people out oh my god finally scrap wood tavern buy some stuff i have money hail
travelers step to the bar and i'll draw you a tankard you can order a drink or talk to the
barkeep let's get some drinks who will order a drink uh all of us what it will be germa i'll have
a full foul spirits will you have it for here or to go i'll have it here oh that's good stuff
that's because you begin to sing 99 bottles of beer on the wall you collapse on the floor
thou are in no condition to order anything well just give me a ginger ale then all right let's
talk to the barkeep who will talk to the barkeep me okay then uh gwendolin talk ain't cheap the
barkeep says how much will you tip him how much money do i have you're trying to tell me that 500
gold is not enough money i think that's that's all the money i have 500 i don't have 500 100
oh be on the lookout for the magic gems your spell casters will need them no shit all right
get out of here where's that there was another building there's a there's a camp over here
let's just go i want to go uh north i'm gonna go northwest
jerma is the carnival stream going to be on mixer it is not going to be on mixer enjoy your next
life you snarl you see uh okay attack attack attack attack three things swings at iron pants
four points of damage how much health do they have not very much one's dead are they all dead
this is green goblin here halfway up earth dagger mountain winds swirl around and make
this place earn its name cold peak okay what's this a dark gnome okay this is not a bad game
this is actually fun your battle cries heard by all as you face one dark gnome will your gallant
ban i don't want to fight let's go i want to go in this building but it's like tank controls
welcome all weary ones to our humble temple dost thou wish to heal a character pull thy goal
or exit pull the gold together whom shall i gather thy gold gwendolin now hath all the gold no no no
no i want all the gold pull the gold to me thank you and heal me jerma has wounds which need
tending the donation will be 80 in gold who will forfeit the gold uh i will there we go he is healed
goodbye nice to see you so i want to go back to north what is this oh that's we're just here
that's scrap wood tavern wait i can add people to the party right uh shadow all right we got a new
party member out all right get out is it the starting location no stop maybe it was just go
north until i can't go anymore a hedge lizard two hedge lizards fight attack shadow can
hide in the shadows that's i guess the namesake shadow jumps into the shadows but is discovered
miss the lizard green bolt swings iron pan swings kills it but they got it we're good so what do you
think ran behind a tree and they were like hey we saw you run behind the tree man oh shit okay
trees on every side north and west only he just tucked his head into his shirt sounds like it
actually uh just run no no no run run i want to run all right we'll just kill them then i just
got stabbed for nine damage i'm almost dead again i have four i have four hp left what the fuck can
they just die already please just kill your party members to be ha ha funny i'm not gonna need to
because i'm probably just gonna die i'm gonna get stabbed right now no we're good miss miss good
kill it that would be such a funny moment uh-oh back to back if i die i'm dumb end of the game
a serpent why am i getting just back to back to that's terrifying uh i might have some money
though i'm only one everybody attack it swing and miss green bolt bit green bullets not doing too
well either okay it's almost dead it's still alive the best teeth let me see wow those are nice
those are some piano keys man all right attack everybody attack green bolt is now on the verge
of death can somebody kill this thank god i'm not really entirely sure what i'm supposed to be doing
but i mean there is a place to go over here what's the point of in here oh shit i was supposed i'm
supposed to go here there's an unnatural silence as if death itself has come to stay
go in this door the party is inside a storage building who wishes to inspect
would germa like to pick up harmonic jam plate armor a halberd okay give me the halberd
give me everything the gem take where's take all plate armor all full okay now it's uh iron pants
his turn lamp fire horn soothing balm youth potion all right uh gwendoline just grab the
youth potion and we can get out of here empty cleaned it out i have to hit i don't want you
guys to see the final thing i'm gonna do though so i have to go like this you'll see the tab that's
open did i get it all did each one of these doors when i go in that's it oh foul stalkers
i think we have to fight them everybody attack wait use an item broadsword you can't use that
item use an item uh what can i do i can put the plate armor on maybe not maybe have to go into
the menu later okay miss 16 points of damage to gwendoline a foul stalker swings germa and hits
for nine i'm dead hits iron pants for 15 the i guess these are really really iron pants drinks
and feels less thirsty good what is that mario emote that mario falling down emote
why do i feel like that emote is huge okay all right i'm dumping the healing the huge youth
potion on me gwendoline cast a spell youth everyone we're all dead we're not getting out of this it's
over yeah i i gotta i gotta get a good super mario emo don't you think all right i give up
as you do cake mario i would do a cake mario emote but then we would understand what it was
which item mandolin no i don't know can they do it no vandals dead who's left shadow oh he's in
the shadows right now isn't it let's see if i can get away can i sneak away into the shadows all
right you can live out your rest of your days in this building shadow quick run uh-oh here comes
the bad ending uh no no no i want to run hide in the shadows i'm dead what happened did one run
away i have no idea what just happened get me out of this place get me out of this place channeling
like tommy was so right now all right can i just like drink poison just drink poison what's going
on shadow is a level two male hobbit rogue that's me even in death i get all the fucking money
all right i'm done that's a pretty fun game if you had to sit down and actually play it
10 20 30 years ago uh and the final thing that i wanted to do you didn't drink the poison well
then he can stay alive he gets to live no it's not going to be a porn game ladies and gentlemen
it's original donkey kong right wake up it's time to go to work time to go to school
no not the alarm all right get it off i can't get it off i don't know what's going on hit
this news button quick all right i can't hear that anymore all right i fixed it somehow worse
all right that that's it i feel like if i listen to this long enough i'll go insane this is like
you'll go insane if you listen to this should we try it i'm gonna put both headphones in turn
your volume down i'm gonna see if i go insane turn your volume down oh fuck come on all right
both headphones are in turn your volume down never mind i've gone insane all right that's it
i got hit by the fucking thing yeah i'm uh i'm i'm spent i was only supposed to drink for like
four or five hours tonight because i have some stuff to do but then i get too sucked into the
surgery game so going more than seven hours tonight i'll see you guys tomorrow though
we'll be doing terraria with star picking up where we left off last week is the stream going
to be early i really don't know i don't know i gotta talk to star so the sus is just going to be
tentative so it might be earlier than three or four pacific but we'll see we cheated out of our
duke nukem we will do this again though i have a lot of fun playing these it's always a roller
coaster i love it but let us conclude let's do the bits go back earlier about seven hours ago
close this window move this over here and if you take it off well maybe we'll see you tomorrow if
not then we'll see you probably next week so back earlier we had lazy luke thanks lazy luke for the
250 two dollars and 50 cents hey germa you asked when the last time was that you used germa moon
it was march 2nd 2019 exactly five months ago uh here is the here is a part in the
vod where you talk about how much you love that god awful emote god awful emote have i really not
used your moon for five months no what am i doing it was in vr germa moon is the it was my first
emote ever and it's like if i was intentionally trying to have an emote that was awful i love it
though that's my favorite emote this is by far my favorite emote on the site and i didn't do it for
five months i don't think anybody has one that can compare i don't think they do i'll stand
on the eagle maniac hill here that's why i love that emote that's the best emote on twitch god
what a beautiful emote i agree it's so good i say that because it's my faith to me i hope you guys
don't take me that seriously definitely take me that seriously i'm not kidding that is the best
twitch but thank you lazy luke uh thank you chimera 87x for the 250 rick vitality is alex jones's
next supplement line rick vitality that guy was wild thank you to stiff funky chicken for the
three bucks uh i asked last night you this but i think you missed it if not disregard i was
wondering if you had thought about establishing a place for members to submit community art
yeah uh i'm not sure how much you've been around the last week or so but i'm going to start to do
community nights where instead of it just being we're gonna do artwork we're gonna do show a
couple of a video that somebody sent through we're gonna do uh hey somebody sent like a funny copy
pasta once every two or three weeks we're gonna just compile all of them and spend an hour or two
at least going through so it'll be like artwork videos random like little stories that people
write so and that's why i've not been uh i've been i don't really have a time frame for that
unfortunately because this carnival stream has taken up all of my other non-on stream time
when i'm not live on twitch besides like taking a day or two here just to kind of you know
to hang out with my girlfriend and you'd be like a person i've been doing this carnival shit
so i haven't put that much brain power into this yet and it really is probably not going to start
happening until the carnival stream is over so all time that is dedicated to like stream stuff
is split at this point evenly with the carnival and being like actually on stream but after the
21st i'm really gonna get that hammered out and have an actual set time for whenever we're gonna
do it i might even be able to do it it depends on how much work gets done uh this coming week
next week is when most of the real important details for this frame are gonna happen
because it's already been back and forth about contracts and what do we want how many robots
do you want how many things do you want to do do you want to have this do you want to have that
and this next week here is we're all going to be in the same room and really hash the whole thing
out so might be able to do it sooner than that we'll see but it is coming it will be here
hey real sleazy thanks for the five dollars get serious to start flying lessons hey hash house
ago go the whole thing oh don't say that that makes me want to have the blue cheese stuffed
cheeseburger the best fucking hamburger i've ever had i want it right now i'm just gonna go get it
if you're by the way if you are around if you're in town here for evo go get a cheeseburger from
hash house ago go at the link do yourself a major favor as a shill i will go ahead and call me that
bite into that burger and then you'll start telling everybody to do the same thing
as someone who lives in vegas i can vouch for this thank you
that place is 24 hours and has some of the best just delicious food you can get all night every
day god i fucking love that place i really do did they deliver across the country i don't think so
hey thank you zake for the 250 how much money do i have to give man can i get my dog back i don't
have your dog how do you how the how juicy are the burgers it's i can't even describe it
it's like the crunchy crispy edges it's really smashed up stacked juicy in the middle crispy
on the outside i have to go get one it's two patties oh there are four hash houses in vegas
go to the one at the link is the gordon ramsey restaurant in vegas yeah gordon ramsey has like
four restaurants here he certainly loves las vegas he's got four fucking restaurants
and they're all great yeah they are i actually have not had the burger from the gordon ramsey
burger place because every single time we have ever gone to try to get one there's a line out
of the door you need to be ready to wait in a in a pax line to go see the 12 minutes of legend of
zelda 6 but you know i'm saying for like three hours it is an actual disney world line book a
seat in advance i'm not sure they do that a lot of restaurants in vegas don't like do reservations
you just kind of have to show the fuck up we went somewhere uh last week or yeah we went somewhere
that you you can't you physically can't they don't do reservations how much have you gambled since
you moved to vegas let me one to two hundred thousand dollars not a whole lot oh but i forgot
to mention uh i put one dollar in a machine when we first got here and hit a million dollars so
i mean that's not that much in the grand you know picture i still got 800 000
no that'd be fucking awesome
is that for that is not for real no that did not fucking happen i would be on the goddamn
news if that happened if i put a dollar into a machine and it won a million i would be holding
the check smiling like hey did it i'd be on all the fucking news stations uh unfortunately
i did not win a jackpot i wouldn't be able to hold that information in if you would hit a fucking
million dollars on like a scratch ticket or a slot machine or some weird table game you think i'd be
able to keep my mouth shut every day would just be like million million a million you know you want
a million dollars you want a million you have a million you have a million dollars it'd be like
hey guys uh so today uh tell about them tell about the million tell about your million dollars
uh today we're gonna play toss you would never be able to hold that in that's how you get like
i would tell my mom i would just subtly remove the ability for people to sub and donate
yeah but but that would be kind of like suspicious though wait a minute jerma why did you disable
all subs and all donation and all this i don't know i just kind of felt like it
i don't know what do you mean what's that mean tell them about tell them tell them about the
million quick unfortunately i i'm not a millionaire didn't win the jackpot on the slot machine a
million burgers hey thank you to uh espada escalada for the 250 i just want to say despite
this being an absolute day from hell and my first day at my new job um i'm sorry to hear that your
stream is really helping me and my nerves physically i'm fine i'll be okay mentally and all that with
time just wanted to say thanks from the bottom of my heart they say long story short i was very
nearly shot today holy shit stay safe that's fucking sounds pretty terrifying i'm not sure
the details there but thankfully you're all right hopefully nothing um hopefully nobody was hurt or
nothing happened there but i'm really really sorry to hear that take care of yourself stay safe that
goes for all of you but thank you for the 250 i really appreciate it did i get uh these the five
subs from am am clockwork i did right yeah well thank you again clockwork modest narcissist thanks
for the five dollars hey everybody streams always make the last couple hours of my work day a lot
more bearable it's before i have to close for the night i wanted to give a small bit of my
paycheck as thanks keep up the good work and have a good night you as well thank you for the five
dollars really appreciate it hopefully closing up went well thank you we just had uh a thousand
bits ten dollars from bet three are you going to be at san diego twitch con san diego is it in san
diego um yeah i i think maybe i don't know it's going to be really tough i have not decided if
i'm going to actually be at twitchcon or not and is for one very specific reason because
that carnival stream is on the 21st and i don't know how i might because i'm not going to be able
to stream i'm not going to be able to stream for almost a week before that stream happens
i will be in this facility getting everything set up and moving stuff and helping
set up sets and talking to people and telling people where i want things and i mean i'm going
to be there for probably like five days before 21st of september so i won't be live for a while
and then come back oh hey it's like the 23rd 24th and then what just stream like for a day or two
and then leave again for like four or five days you know what i'm saying i would only be live for
like two days out of like two and a half weeks and i don't know if i want to do that the idea is that
i would probably go for it a short duration because i really will only have like a day or two to kind
of get back to normal and then i'm leaving again to go to twitchcon so we'll see i may or may not
be there for like a day or two i've not 100 decided yet i do have a ticket though because
i made sure to get one to i have a twitchcon ticket so it's not like i'm going to be like
locked out or anything but uh maybe we'll see there'll be a clown car at this carnival stream
how would i not have clowns at a carnival you want to help advertise the carnival stream you
should put something about it on your offline screen yeah as we get closer there's going to
be a lot more i'll be talking about it a lot more and potentially even uh the companies that are
involved because i know that i'm gonna be you'll know who's behind a lot of this it's not just
gonna be the this nameless faceless company you'll know who's helped out a lot so we'll go i don't
have that information yet so but uh thank you for the 10 bucks bet three i'm not sure yet
creamy sensation thanks for the five dollars this is doom but a doom slayer went to heaven instead
of hell that was for the bible game i forgot about that game it's been a weird night huh
thank you to fuss roe for the five dollars germa i'm playing dark souls for the first time
what's the best build do you have any tips i'm i'm i'm sorry i might be the worst person to ask
the best weapon in dark souls remastered um doesn't isn't dark souls one have like a lot
of usable weapons you can pretty much use anything have you tried playing a good game instead
whoa hold on whoops they have uh hit the brakes on that one for a second playing a good i mean
yeah the first 12 out 15 hours of dark souls one is is incredible and then in the middle
like 10 hours is puke inducing and and awful and but then the last like 20 of the hours are
absolutely fantastic so a majority of that game is incredible so you can forget about the the middle
part this is just it's the fucking lettuce you can you can take the lettuce out if you want
just eat the burger dark souls is a 60 hour game yeah i mean all the souls born games your first
playthrough always takes like 30 to 50 hours because you have no idea what the hell you're
doing or where you're going the dark souls one is still a great game though it's still a really
really good game lettuce is unimportant on anything lettuce is kind of just crunchy water
but sometimes crunchy water is really important on some stuff uh thank you bananaism for the five
dollars and 90 cents they say chug chug chug i'm not sure what i was chugging at the time
well what you wanted me to chug but i didn't uh thank you to doctor uh dr enak for the 20
dollars 10 dollars twice in a row say i love ms dos nights i do too sometimes i get really really
overstimulated when we do this though because so many different colors and loud sounds and music
and weird fucked up shit and after like four to five hours six hours of doing dos i kind of just
like my brain turns to mush but i do love doing it it's so much fun just to see although it's
like you never know what you're gonna get it's a it's a box of chocolates and some of the chocolates
are filled with acid but thank you for the 20 bucks i really appreciate it uh flank tank
thanks for three bucks how much money would it take for you to scream on mixer full time
i've a look listen let me tell you something this is very very easy answer i i made the switch to
a different platform before right i went from youtube to twitch and i think it's probably taken
a couple years to really have everybody understand that i'm here i i made a switch
so going switching from youtube to twitch and then from twitch to another platform
i feel like that's like that's like the second platform switch i don't know if i have it in me
to do like another platform switch again now i mean i don't know if twitch for some reason
starts to really become like a company or as a company that i don't really want to be a part
of and i'd rather try something else i mean that that'll that conversation will happen with myself
what i do for millions of dollars i mean that's like that but that's like saying yes i probably
would because that's that's like you want to be like no i wouldn't do that how dare they even
have decided you know what i could do with a million dollars you know what i could do with
two fucking million dollars i i would make a goddamn movie i would i would do it would be all
kinds of crazy shit that i would do on those streams but no i mean i'd be lying to you guys if
i and i and i think a majority of people would probably be lying to you if it was like hey would
you like switch over for like a million dollars no no i don't think so i don't believe so i would
probably continue to stay here i don't know i yes that's like literally life-changing fucking never
have to work again a day in your life money yeah obviously like you're gonna do it if it's just if
yeah well maybe not everybody would do it for various reasons but two or three million dollars
is like that you that's every cent you'd ever need until until you were buried i'd burn through
that money quick no i wouldn't i would not i would do the thing where i would hide okay for if i got
if i came into like a million couple million dollars like tomorrow right the first thing i
would do i would hire a lawyer i would get a really really good lawyer and i would say i want you to
make a contract that i have to sign to dump my money into like a vault that i cannot open
you know what i'm saying like i want you to i want to put a million dollars into a vault
that i'm not allowed to touch like retirement account type shit just put it into a big safe
and don't give me the combination but you don't get to have it though like he's like okay i'll
just take it no no no like i eventually you tell me like after 10 years you tell me what the
combination is so how do i have access to it i don't until 10 years ago yeah trust two million
dollars to stop streaming would you leave us what do you mean stop like can i do anything else
can i do can i like do anything else can i like go back to youtube no i have to just leave the
internet wait but you tell me two million dollars and i have to just delete all my accounts and just
literally like just don't do anything else no i don't know if i that you're giving me like the
fucking the button the the two buttons thing where the guy's like oh shit i don't i don't think i
could do i don't think i could do it what else what the fuck else would i do i mean if we had
two million dollars we wouldn't have to do anything right you could just like invest half
of it and then just like sit on a beach every day but i think i would get bored i would get
bored i would be like oh this is fucking great and after like fucking three years i'd be like
i need to do something i can't stream anymore i can't like make a video i'd go nuts three years
is generous it would probably yeah that is it would take like probably two weeks no it would
be more than that it'd be like a after like two or three months but i i was always under the
impression that i was going to do this until i didn't think it was interesting or fun anymore
and if that hasn't happened yet then i will never no matter like oh yeah give me 10 million dollars
and stop streaming forever i i do i am not satisfied yet and if i'm not completely satisfied
not completely like full then i would i would all it would always bother me you know what i mean
jerma i'll give you a million dollars if you stop to keep streaming until it stops being fun
the only way that i would actually accept a million dollars from anybody that was
somebody that was watching the channel was if you could prove somehow i would you would have
to go through like an underwriter to prove that you have like a hundred million dollars
as the only way i'd ever to ever accept that you'd have to go through like like a mortgage
company to prove that you can like do that like a thousand times over no not the undertaker an
underwriter destroy him but no i i don't know i don't know if i could do that but i don't i
don't know i dude i i've got this like weird i don't know if i like want i don't want to have
a bunch of like money they kind of like freaks i don't want like 10 20 i don't want like 50
million dollars what the fuck am i gonna do with that money i i'd panic i'd buy like five boats
just because i'd be like i don't know what to do should i buy boats you did do that in that life
simulator if i had like a hundred million fucking dollars i would do wacky shit i would be that
weird guy i'd have a fucking top hat and a cape and shit and i would just like hold events where
i dumped like 500 grand out of a zeppelin you know what i mean i'd be fucking like a crazy person
i would hold like contests impromptu on like the beach or on the street or something
like who can eat skittles and like spit the furthest and oh and by the way oh the person
that does it the furthest gets 50 000 not like oh 50 bucks i would just get like chased the
second i open up okay congratulations yeah you won the spinning contest what was that
let me see let me lick my fingers what's in here okay so that you were going to get five grand
and oh and there's so many hundreds in here please nobody fucking attack me
no that would not work you're right i would get like strangled on the street and be like
wait how much money has he gotten there no it's not that much i'd start like running
but then i would do i would do like the fucking cartoon you know the cartoon like oil spill
behind you that they do when in all of those when anytime the character in a racing cartoon
or in a video game or any any point when somebody has is in a race and the bad guy drops the oil
behind them that would be money i would just like throw a fucking thousand dollars behind me and
just keep going oh i would like wad up like fucking 10 grand into like a big wad fist and just like
baseball throw it like over a roof or something and just keep running so just like land in an
alleyway and then all of a sudden like oh there there he goes well who cares we can tell you
think of this a lot what if you were a billionaire no billionaire i would just be in i would just sit
in vr all day i would just pay somebody to make like a a vr game that i just played it was mine
would you still stream no i don't think i would
ah my fucking stomach just buy a state yeah what the hell you know how when uh people that are
millionaires get bored they buy baseball teams and like soccer teams when billionaires get bored
why don't they just buy a state or just have a bunch of like just make a new like land off the
coast of fucking california have like a 20 mile radius like a land built and just call it something
and see if you can get added to the fucking 50 if you can get become the 50 like first state
let us in that'd be fine we could just put like we could all all of this the whole germa community
could just live there some of the things you guys say are fucking crazy that would be a fucking
shit show yeah how would we even get like water i didn't think that through we'd have to i'd have
to hire a bunch of plumbers to make like water come through pipes we'd have to have a sewer system
we're like how would we do that the ocean you can't drink ocean water it has to be uh
desalted it's got to be processed where's that gonna go what about a military oh yeah i wouldn't
have a military but then i would have what if i just got like taken over it would be like here
we go and it's the grand opening of germa island and here it is cut the ribbon welcome everybody
we're gonna do just fine and then just cut it's just like decayed land people screaming
he was trying to pump water he's been pumping salt water and every time we take showers it's just
like salt water gets in our eyes he's a maniac that'd be a great movie yeah that would be a great
fucking movie what a good movie that would be i want to see this movie a guy with like a trillion
dollars makes his own land his own like country off the coast of the pacific and like the crazy
wild shit that would have to happen to get that to work and then what would actually happen
what kind of potential crazy shit would happen it's called no it's a jurassic park
that's a will farrell comedy well hire him he still pulls numbers that'll be a 2.8 on rotten
tomatoes that doesn't matter it's it's lord of the flies yeah but lord of the flies they didn't have
a billion dollars it already exists let me see hold on what is this movie it'll be a bad it'll
be it'll be 2. no just make it animated does all animated movies have like 80 to 90 percent
on rotten tomatoes guaranteed into the billionaire verse you have no idea how trash some animated
movies are yeah all right but like listen somebody put up what sausage party does not count
it already exists what the hell are you talking about
sea land this already exists the principality of sea land commonly known as sea land is a
micronation what no no no no no i'm sorry guys hold on a minute here this is a helicopter pad
this is not like a whole city similar no it would have to be like okay it wouldn't listen
it would have to be the this place would have to be the like the size of roteisland
what would that be like 500 trillion dollars like bioshock not a bill you tell me you tell me it
wouldn't cost a billion dollars to build a city as big as roteisland it costs more than a billion
dollars to put up a new casino on the strip that would be like a hundred trillion dollars
all right we've been on the like billionaire makes his own like cartoon island for like 40
minutes so we gotta get out of here it's a jaw-dropping shame how bad your money and
number management skills are you're 35 we're talking about a looney tunes bit i'm sorry i
don't have the necessary mathematical knowledge of how much it would take to build a fucking new
country as big as roteisland who the hell has that information that information doesn't exist
i didn't like miss a decimal on my tax return this is like a dr eggman plot maybe there's a
reason that you're not rich hey yep maybe all right here we go let's keep going uh we're at
the end here garfield the monday killer thanks the 250 hey garfield what's up garf garf we are
the garfs celebrating yet another birthday snark and germy you had such a good stream this year
and some of my bits wow we all cheer thank you garfield the monday killer welcome back
thanks the 250 and so let's get the credits on here all the subs thanks everybody i'll see you
tomorrow terraria at some point in the afternoon i'm not sure exactly when did that not go through
why did that not go through what's going on here uh-oh well that took a while to go through some
really but once again thanks guys for all the support means a lot it's a fucking lot of subs
there are a couple more bits to do we have uh demonic cucumber just gave three bucks you can
donate $50 to sea land and they'll make you a duke how much to become a duke of germ island
um you wouldn't be able to do that you can't pay me to play your mario maker level so
i have to stick to that germ island uh thank you to uh thank you to jango agogo for the 10 bucks
10 dollars from uh jango they say for all my life i've lived in one state and for the first time
in my life i'm moving many states away i'm pretty sad about moving so far away from my family it's
a tough thing to do but no matter where i am you and the community will be a family that i can
always come to and feel like i'm a good company so to you germa thank you for the entertainment
and the creativity and to the chat thank you for being the other half of my jukes i love you all
that's wholesome i can relate to this very very personally because i did that i just traveled
across the whole country to live in a place that i've never been in before i've traveled to las
vegas a few times before moving here but yeah i did nobody else that none of my like hometown
friends or family members nobody's out here so it's a little different it is you kind of you have
to kind of get used to it but i love it out here i loved it i think it was the right change i think
it was the right move so we are all more than happy to have a fun community here
can all kind of collectively hopefully enjoy the same things where am i from i'm from massachusetts
i moved out to vegas just under a year ago it'll be a year in october yeah but thank you for the
10 bucks really appreciate it uh thank you to uh jen pendulum for the five dollars i don't know
how expensive the whole carnival stream thing is but here's some bits to help you out maybe one
day we'll talk like i did the germa rumble but i don't want that to be a point of contention or
talk about that until much later i don't really want to talk about like how much money this
stream is gonna cost i mean i i think i said a little bit a few maybe like a month ago or so
but that's not important maybe we'll talk about it some other time but i do thank you so much
for the five dollars appreciate it that was a jen pendulum thank you uh volemy gave ten dollars
they said chew no not chew the dew chug the dew jeremy you already signed the contract
aren't they paying you to do this no no no no other way around i have hired a couple of companies
to help me do this i was not hired by this is not this is me hiring people i was not approached
for this i have been trying to approach people for this for about a year and no it is not a
massachusetts-based company there's somewhere else and that's it i'll see you guys tomorrow
thanks for hanging out dos is always fun see you tomorrow for terraria have a good rest of your
night take care and goodbye get some sleep we got one more bit that came in at one more right now
by snoozing copter 250 from snoozing copter they say hey germo uh when you don't know where you
want to be or where you want to go what do you do except for waiting it out i'm sure you and uh
and everyone can relate i want to hear your thoughts when you don't know where you want
to be or where you want to go i think well for me at least uh in regards to where i wanted to be
i kind of just wanted to be somewhere that i knew i was gonna wake up every day and
be at least interested in where i was and what i was doing at least in a territorial sense
but in a more elaborate sense of where you want to be a way you want to go i always was of the
mindset that you you kind of pick a few things that you like and try to have one of them or
a combination of them work out find what you're interested in find at least two or three things
that you really are interested in and be happy with any of those things i think a lot of times
i think a lot of times people can get stuck by putting all their eggs in one basket
when you should have a few baskets that you are equally excited about and as long as one of them
works out then you're happy trying to find what you're interested in and then spread out the eggs
a little get into the carnival business now but it's tough because it's it's tough because
everybody is interested in different things but i'll tell you just i wanted to do entertainment i
wanted to be like an entertainer actor comedian whatever that was one of but also i wanted to work
with animals i was really really into the idea of getting into i like love dogs i love cat love
animals right so that was another i'm really into that another one was doing uh customer service
like i like talking to people i'm the big i'm big into having conversations so with customer
service uh field customer not necessarily support but so any of those three things i
was going to be happy with because i was actually really interested in all three of them if i had
been let's say for instance i never did anything on twitch or youtube and instead i fell into
like a uh like a vet clinic right i would be very happy if i was like a vet tech or
somebody that worked in the veterinary field right
or combine them you know find a few things that you like to do and be happy doing any of them
comedian for pets combine them all be a clown vet but that is honestly the only advice i can really
give i've been very fortunate to do something and sort of fall into and do something that i really
really really wanted to do but i was really really happy and passionate about very very fortunate
to be able to do that but i was prepared to fall back on one of those other couple things
and that's pretty much that's pretty much what i gotta say i wish you luck i wish you the best
sometimes you need a change of scenery sometimes you do moving and even if you even change in towns
or you know going a few miles away if you've been in the same place for a while
it can help but with that i will see you all tomorrow have a great rest of your night
get some sleep see you tomorrow good night