Going over your morning commute right now, we've got traffic on the threes, which looks like it could be letting up by about 4 or 5 p.m. tonight.
I would suggest taking a different route, but we got an accident on route 45, and hopefully...
What's this? Oh my god, a person!
Hey everybody, welcome to another video starring me, German985.
I've got a really interesting thing to show you. It's how I drive cars now. It's pretty fun.
Here we go. Oh yeah, Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 5. Coming soon. Coming soon, DVD.
Jesus Christ.
This is nothing like riding a tricycle on a Sunday afternoon. Hey, look at me, mommy. I'm so cute.
Inside of a Mack truck? Oh, you gotta be shitting me. This ain't gonna end well.
This is gonna be real bad. Oh, fuck the fuck. That sucked.
Okay, we'll put a big ramp right here. Let's go. Let's do it. Big ramp. Hold on for dear life.
Because we're going over the goddamn ramp. That's not what I wanted to have happen.
For some how I landed that. Broken bones everywhere. I don't know how that just happened. Let's do it!
Go. Go. Go.
And just like that, he was never heard from again.
So are you sure this is safe? I'm positive. Just do it, you baby.
Okay, well I guess I'll try. Weee!
Looks like you're gonna be fighting a little bit of construction on Route 24 coming on the bridge there.
What the fuck even happened? Are you serious? I didn't even do anything. He didn't do anything.
What just happened? I broke my neck on the dashboard. Okay.
You know son, it was on this very bridge that your mother proposed to me. I mean, I proposed to your mother.
She looked so pretty in her red dress. Fucking come on!
Did I ever tell you son, when I proposed to your mother on this very bridge, we were both young and restless.
And I said, sweetie, I love you so much. Can we please get married?
And if I miss this again, I'm gonna fucking scream.
It was this very bridge where I proposed to your mother.
She looked so pretty in her red dress and I said, son, would you like to get married?
No, there's a fire. There's a fire somewhere. We're gonna bring the fire engine. I think there's a fire.
There could be a fire over here.
It's this highway right here. This is the one son. You gotta be careful. You're only a student driver.
You gotta watch out for the goddamn animals. There's birds and bears cross this bridge all the time.
So please just be careful. Look out son! There goes one now!
Why did mummy not want me to play in the street? She said not to play in the street, but why? It's so much fun.
Fuck! That would have been perfect.
I can't wait to show my mummy my new skateboard move. She told me not to play in the street, but I don't care.
Mummy, let me see. Maybe I can show mummy my new skateboard move. Look, I'm just flying down like Superman.
Check it out. You're going for 20 points.
20 points.
Yeah, my boyfriend's so badass. He's in a biker gang. He buys me presents all the time.
You wish you had a boyfriend like mine. Just wait till he shows up to say, to say, fuck you.
And he fucking fell off again. I really hope this works.
I've done this like eight times and it keeps on falling off the bike like a dipshit.
Somebody get this dipshit, a driver's license that is capable for a motorcycle.
Here he comes. Here he comes. Come on. Come on now.
You did it. You did it, my son.