These? These are my subgirls.
Hey! Whoa!
Dama!
No te batalo!
Look at Andrew.
That's right. Look at Andrew. Never heard of him.
I'm going to see my armpits, so I'll lift my arms up.
My subgirls.
Woo!
Yep!
Can't breathe without these.
Look at the TikTok video. Who said the lip I was doing?
I was just going...
Woo!
Just a little too big.
Can't breathe without these.
Look at the TikTok video. Who said the lip I was doing?
I was just going...
Woo!
Just a little too big.
Can't breathe without these.
I broke the watch.
We should have started like five minutes ago.
We had to tape the watch on my hand.
I was putting it on, I was panicking.
And the thing just shattered in my hands.
But anyways, hi!
Welcome to day two of the Dollhouse.
Do you need an introduction?
Should I give you an introduction?
Or do you already know how this works?
You should by now.
Why don't we go take a look inside? Oh my god! I look fucking awful!
I was just like...
Oh god.
I'm going to be so self-conscious.
I don't wear this shit.
In my own home I don't wear this.
Because I'm embarrassed about my neck and shoulders and stomach come out.
And I think you can see my nipples through the shirt.
But I'm going to try to do my best to make sure you can't see that.
Let's go in the house.
Seas have been cleaned up.
You notice something in the trash out there?
Because I'm not sleeping on that fucking mattress.
That's not going to happen.
I'm not sleeping on that.
Because it's actually dirty.
Actually dirty.
Actually, you know, I look like a...
Oh boy!
I look like a fucking idiot.
You know the bathroom?
Probably pretty well at this point, I would assume.
I love this bathroom.
Although I could use a little bit more stuff.
Please be aware.
You are in control of...
98% of everything that happens on this stream.
Just be aware of that.
Should we check this door?
What do you think? Should I go in here?
Does this door work?
We'll find out. I can't open it.
It's locked.
Oh, that's where the bed is.
That's right. I built it.
It was broken.
But that's where I decided to put it.
Because you got it for me at the end of the stream.
It took me like six hours to build it.
This is nice and comfy.
Can somebody...
I actually kind of like how this looks.
Can we see?
Can you get it?
Can I like home shopping network this thing?
It's so stupid.
I feel like that mouse
who I'm not going to say
on a stream like this
I feel like that mouse wears this kind of stuff.
I feel like he has like 30 of these.
But we never see him wear it.
I guarantee he has it.
Welcome back though.
You know, from the front it looks okay.
But from the side it doesn't.
I need to like get a bigger chest.
But I got like these flick of these arms.
I can go like that.
I love the bedroom.
You've got more choices now, don't you?
Toilet, I don't have to go.
But just so you can be aware
that it is available.
Eventually I probably want to take these gloves off.
Enjoy the game.
Good luck.
I got full bars, which means I can do this.
That's embarrassing. I just did that.
How many people here?
That was actually pretty embarrassing to do with this many people.
73,000 people just watched me do that.
That's like embarrassing.
Back in like during like school plays
there'd be like fucking 40 people in the audience.
They're...
No, I'm not peeing on them.
I'm not peeing on the flowers.
Why is that the piss sound?
That's not water flowers.
I'm going to stand like this
so people don't think that's what's happening.
I enjoyed that very much though.
I did.
I'll tell you, from the front this looks good.
Wait a minute.
We're going to do the same job from the other day.
I still got it.
But what I was going to say is
back when I was a young, young boy
there'd be
school plays, you know.
You're in like the fourth grade, the fifth grade.
Only people's parents
came to that shit, right?
Maybe the principal, maybe the old lady
that played the piano during the entire show.
She would just
every scene it would be like
that lady was like super into it.
I kind of wish we had one of those ladies.
We don't.
But the difference is
it's not 40 people's parents.
It's 70,000 people.
I don't know how many of you are.
Actually, I think my mother is watching.
I'm going to go lie in the bed.
I'm going to go check the bed out.
Parasocial Andy.
What? I'm going to check the bed out.
Okay.
There it is. There's the first one.
I actually talked about the fart thing.
And I said five farts.
An hour. An hour.
So it's going to be in a lot of trouble.
It was five fart sounds an hour.
There was one.
I want you to keep track.
Okay, let's go.
I watch out for that manhole.
You see the mattress?
There it is.
I'm in the right clothes for this.
Not sleeping on this.
We actually talked about this after day one.
I'm like
not a chance that I actually lie on this.
No way.
Oh, we got the popcorn maker.
Except it doesn't do anything.
Because I don't want to get electrocuted.
Check mail. Sure.
Why not? Mail.
Check the mail. What's in the mail today?
Let's find out.
This is somebody's shoe that's here.
Somebody actually like on set here.
This is their shoe.
I don't know whose it is, but I don't know why it's in here.
What is it?
Has somebody worn this in the last few days?
Did I just get money?
There's 20 bucks in the shoe.
Who would do this?
What kind of fucked up neighborhood is this?
Thanks for the 20 dollars.
What do we start with? 300?
So that's what? 320?
How much money? 40? What?
I thought we started with 300 dollars.
Oh, they bought the upgraded house.
Right. But why don't we have any money?
How are we supposed to get any money?
How are they going to buy anything?
I'm talking to you.
Remember, I have to go to work to make money.
If you don't send me to work, then it's not going to happen.
Oh! Got you.
I actually hit myself in the head.
I went for like a joke.
And I didn't fucking get it right.
My knee was in the wrong place.
That actually just hit me right in the forehead.
I do actually feel pretty... I need to take a shower.
Let me get in here.
Don't close that. See, you guys figured it out.
You got to keep these bars green.
Otherwise, how am I going to get promoted?
How are you going to make more money?
How are you going to be able to get more stuff in the house?
You can't unless you actually play
and get me there.
I want green bars.
Coming up. Coming up.
Oh, I hit the watch.
I'm getting a little tired though.
I'm starting to wane a little.
I want cool items.
I want fun stuff.
I want things to lie down on.
I don't just want...
What was that?
Go to work. I missed work by like
four hours already.
Go to work?
Alright, I'm going to work.
Fine. I'm going to work.
I'm coming.
Night shift.
Thanks for the ride. Goodbye.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
That just made me tired.
That just brought
my energy to zero.
What did I do?
It wasn't working for like six or seven
hours. It was doing the goodbye
like five times
is what made me tired.
I'm exhausted though.
Tired and a little hungry.
At least we made some money. I'm hungry though.
And how much money is in the account now?
$200? $140?
I'm going to my
bedroom. I haven't been able to sit in here for very long.
I've got a bathroom that's bigger than the bedroom
which is a little odd.
I don't want to lock
myself out of one of these rooms eventually.
Oh man.
Tired. Make a phone call.
Who am I calling?
Call who?
I got a call?
No sleeping?
What are you talking about?
Oh!
Mom!
Yeah, it's me.
Yeah. Yeah, it's been an interesting day
or two. It's
actually really remarkable that I can even talk to you, Mom,
considering that I just pulled the line out of the wall.
So this is really good.
Some kind of alien technology which is interesting.
Oh yeah, no, hi. Hello, sorry.
I forgot to say like hi. How are you?
Yeah, it's good to hear your voice.
You're the only person I know.
That's kind of interesting.
Yeah. Yeah.
And so I...
What? Oh, this.
Right. Right. This. This shit.
That's right.
Okay. Okay.
The couch is fucking ugly.
Mom?
Are you still on the phone? Mom?
I don't know. I hope she thinks I'm alright.
Let me put this back.
What is... What is this?
Can I get this back on?
Yeah, whatever. It'll stay.
Oh. Ooh, yes!
Oh, I love that! Oh, sofa!
Ew!
Yuck! Yuck!
What is this?
I don't want that.
I want one piece of singular bread.
I feel awful. I hate sleeping on the ground.
Let me go to bed, alright?
Like, okay, there's a sofa here now.
There's a bed in the other room.
Don't make me use the phone.
If my energy's low and I'm just...
I'm hangry, alright?
Just let me talk to you for a second.
If you put me in the bed and let me go to sleep,
then this won't happen. You'll have plenty of opportunity
I'm gonna piss my shit my pants.
I'm just eating a piece of bread.
I'm eating one piece of bread.
It's good. It's actually pretty good.
This is the good bread.
What kind of bread is this?
Oh, it's multigrain.
I eat multigrain bread.
I don't. I actually think that stuff's gross.
Okay, that was good.
Delicious.
Don't just leave it.
Disgusting.
I'm gonna do a thing that everybody does.
What? Work?
I'm gonna go to work?
Wait! Wait for me!
Wait for me!
Just a full piece of white bread.
I've been at work all day trying to eat.
I've been chewing
this single piece of white bread for fucking
six hours.
It's like eating saltines.
Everybody at work thought I was chewing gum.
I ate a whole piece of white bread before I came in.
They were like,
dude, what did you have for breakfast today?
I just went like this
with a piece of white bread.
They were like, do you want to go to McDonald's?
I'm like, I don't know. No!
I'm fucking horrible.
I feel awful.
I can see it.
I can see it!
Please help me.
Please, I can see it.
I can literally see the fucking toilet
in front of me.
What was that? What was that?
Wait, wait, wait.
Who's at the door?
This is my pants.
I'm coming!
Uncle Ted!
It's been so long!
What is he doing here?
I went to spring training.
I told your mother I was going.
Look at this nice couch you got here.
You got good taste.
He's dead.
What are you doing here?
Give me a hug.
He's so fucking cold.
He's freezing.
What's the matter with you?
Let's go.
I went to my house.
You know what's there? Nothing.
I got no furniture.
That looks familiar.
I don't know what God I angered.
Oh, you like my couch?
That's beautiful.
I haven't had a beer in about
50...
Hey!
Uncle Ted!
There's a fucking ghost in my house.
This motherfucker is dead.
Jeremy!
Is that the bathroom?
You and the bathroom.
I need to do something about this.
He has to pass on.
The ghost of the walking dead.
Take your time.
I know what a good release feels like.
Sometimes it takes a little while.
Lord.
Start at 100.
I don't know what happened.
I don't know what God I angered.
I don't know what I did.
I don't know who I'm angering.
Get him to the other side.
That would be fantastic.
I don't want to be haunted anymore.
I want to pass on wealth.
Those are my spoons.
That looks like my couch.
I'm going to shit my pants.
I got that one.
I got that one in Dollywood.
Hey!
I love my grandson.
Hey, so how are you?
Are you ready for Uncle Ted?
You're not supposed to be here, Ted.
I'm not supposed to be here.
I had to get your address off somebody
because your mother, freaking mother,
my sister, my house is empty of furniture.
But this looks familiar, that looks familiar.
And those are my spoons.
I got that one in Dollywood.
I've got a ghost that needs to go to the other god damn side.
He's haunting me.
Yeah, you come as soon as you can.
Talk to me.
Ted, Ted, how are you?
Who's on the phone?
I was just calling my friend, Granit Reapelson.
Granit Reapelson?
Yeah, they're an old family friend.
You played soccer with him, didn't you?
I went to one of your games and you played soccer with him.
I did, I did.
Anything that you need to say before you move on to the other world?
No, I'm good.
There's no money hidden under any mattresses?
No, actually I had no money.
Like somebody cleaned out my account when I was in spring training.
I went down to see this octagon.
Let me get the door.
Just stay there for a minute.
You know this is a new place but you've done wonders with it.
Stay there for just a second.
I'm here for Ted.
Please come in.
Where does this go?
Yeah, he's over here.
He's having some trouble getting over to the other side if you could.
Hi, how are you?
This is my friend.
By the way, I don't think I've ever said about you.
It was just a joke.
If there's anything you need to say to me,
should I know anything about anything?
Dress up?
Is this dress up?
Ted.
It's time for you to come home, Ted.
It's time.
Well, there's no furniture in my home.
No, Ted, not that kind of home.
It's time for the long farewell.
It's time for the long farewell, Ted.
I'm feeling kind of cold.
Shh.
No more tears.
Only dreams.
Come on.
Come on now. Here we go.
There you are. That's right.
I'm not dead.
You're not dead, yes. They all say that, Ted.
They all say that.
Jerma, Jerma, Jerma, Jerma, Jerma, Jerma.
Jerma can't help you now, Ted.
Fucking family.
I have a spot picked out for you right here.
Come on, Ted.
Right this way. There you go.
Shh.
I'm going to take good care of you, Ted.
Off we go now.
Aww.
This is the worst day I've ever felt in my whole life.
What did he fucking do?
Why did he come here?
Fucking haunted by my Uncle Ted.
I tried to make amends and shit.
I don't even know.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Here, press it.
Jesus.
Holy goodness.
It's a whole nother one.
Okay.
The water's starting to come up over the lip.
I don't care.
You know when you have to pee a lot and it just hurts still.
It hurts.
Up here hurts.
Right here hurts.
All the way like I'm in here. This is killing me.
Oh, like I emptied everything, but it's just like this pain now.
Are you going to let that go again?
Thank you so much.
And I'm going to say a prayer for Ted too
because being haunted by somebody is just
a very unnerving ass thing.
Oh, man.
I'm going to write about that in my blog tomorrow.
What should I title it?
My Uncle Going Through the Great Beyond.
Something like that.
Oh, I was fucked up.
What did I ever do to that motherfucker?
I didn't do anything.
I got money in the mail from him. That's it.
It was just kind of the thing.
It was something my mother called me and sold me.
What the fuck?
I don't know why I'm getting haunted by him.
Thank God he's on the way to the other side.
That's ten times better.
That's a hundred times better.
I'm not even fun anymore.
This is a nice watch though.
I don't want the clowns to come back.
Please do something. I don't want the clowns
to come back today.
Oh, yay!
Butterflies, but
they don't want to be caught. They want to be free.
Butterflies don't want to be caught.
They want to be free outside.
No, I don't want to. Let me see.
There's one over here.
Oh, that's a monarch.
It's beautiful. That's beautiful.
I think that might be a moth, but it's okay.
I can hear.
It sounds like I'm getting hit by a wave.
It's like, hold on.
That's kind of funny.
That's funny I can hear that.
I can't move around too much.
This microphone life fucks up.
I'm tired though.
What's that butterfly?
I think that's a green-tailed
sparrow back. Wow!
Maybe I should keep him.
Actual psycho?
I'm fucking tired.
Doorbell!
I didn't press it.
That was fun.
I feel better.
That's two. We have 30 minutes
or 45 minutes to go before we can do three more.
Life and death.
When somebody comes into the world,
they're essentially created.
And when they're taken away from the world,
they are destroyed.
So therefore, all of us at some point during our lives
witness creation
and destruction
in one life. That's crazy to think about that.
And also like in the fact that
are we even real?
Is this a simulation?
Like this is a simulation.
But is this a simulation
inside of a simulation?
Could we in fact wake up from this simulation
into another simulation?
Because we're doing it now!
Oh. Have I eaten?
What was the last time I ate? I don't know.
Fuck it. I'm not ready.
Gas?
Oh, I'm hungry as shit.
This is not a bad couch. Where did I get this from?
Oh, that's right.
Cool. Okay.
Oh. This isn't really good.
Unbranded beer.
I'm hungry. I feel like I've got like
a stomach ache too. I don't know why. When was the last time I ate?
Ugh.
Ooh.
What is it? Mystery?
Mystery box?
Ow. A mystery?
Please handle with care. Do not drop.
Something fragile in here?
Well, if it's fragile,
I don't want to mess with it.
This is pretty cool though.
I would assume my fucking meter is high!
These fucking stools.
Is there anything else in here?
There's a lot of paper in here.
But they're...
Oh, this is a lot.
You know, can I say something
real quick?
The amount of packing
material that people put into
boxes is getting a little
ridiculous, okay? I have
ordered CDs before
that have come in a box this big
that have this much
packing material and then what
am I as the consumer to do about it?
You can literally like throw a fucking
CD into the wall and it's gonna be fine.
You don't have to put like 600
fucking pounds of paper in here!
Hold on.
Ah! Stool!
I'll take some cereal. That sounds
good to me. I'm not
cutting a tomato.
It's me pouring a
soda.
Oh, it's liquid cereal!
Do I have any utensils?
Oh, I'm starving though.
Thank goodness.
What was that? I have a good
thing I've eaten. Eat real quick!
Hello? What?
Uncle Ted is dead. And I got
an inheritance from Uncle Ted.
The insurance company? What?
Didn't Uncle Ted die like three days ago?
Two days ago? What do you mean?
My mother called me and said,
I got $2,000 added to my account.
But I thought that, I thought,
is this like just litigation stuff? Like I got it
like a week, two, three weeks later or something?
No, he's confirmed dead
yesterday. Oh.
Okay. Interesting.
Thank you for the, thank you for the reply and
thanks for the email.
What? $2,000? Smack-a-roos
though! I'll take that one!
Is he dead? What? I thought he died.
Oh, thank you!
The cereal's actually pretty good.
Those who don't know, I don't eat on set.
This is the only food that they give me.
Okay, can I sell this watch?
I don't want to leave trash around.
That's better. I need to put a trash
barrel, put a trash can in there.
Why are the people just at my house?
Stop coming to my house!
I haven't even eaten breakfast!
Oh my god, alright.
Who is that? Hi.
I'm Edna, by the way,
your neighbor. What are you doing here?
You'll have to forgive me, I
was busy with my cat sweater
yesterday, but this is for you.
Thank you. Welcome to the neighborhood.
Thank you. Welcome
to the neighborhood. Let's see the house.
Oh my.
Goodbye.
Oh wow, you've really done nothing
with the place. Okay.
Is this what
you kids call a house these
days?
Thank you.
I'll take that back later, but
you put that wherever you like.
That's for you. There are apples, there's
fresh fruit in here. Yes, that's
from the farmer's market. It's a stone
throw away. If you ever get
hungry, you can go down there.
There's no worms.
The worms, it's a very big mix up.
My cat is the one with worms.
There are no worms in the apples.
I can't have any of these. No, those
are for you. Those are for you. But you're taking
the basket. Yes, it's my basket.
Actually, my
first grandchild was born
and we brought it home in that basket.
Okay, that's really
fantastic. What would you say your name was again?
Edna. What is
this?
The placement's a little odd,
but you can sit down if you want to. In your
kitchen. I just
moved in and it was really nice to see
you though. Have you seen
these spoons? Yes, I have
seen those spoons. My Uncle Ted left me those spoons.
Did they come with the house? Your Uncle who?
My Uncle Ted left me those
spoons. You wet the bed? Okay.
It was really nice. That happens sometimes.
People wet the bed. It's perfectly
normal. Don't worry about that.
Yeah, sometimes
they do. They're under the age of six.
I'm a 35 year old man. How
old are you?
I'm 35. 35, really?
Okay, you look more like a 15
with those gloves, but that's
alright.
Do you mind if I sit down? Please do, please.
No, no, no.
Oh my.
I just have a bad migraine.
I'm okay. I want to say
you look lovely.
Thank you, sweetheart. I do my own
makeup and my own hair. You look lovely.
You're the loveliest woman I think I've ever seen in my life.
Oh, really? Well, sweetheart, I'm sorry,
but I'm taken.
I'm taken. I've been married for 45
years. Yeah, that's
excellent. Do you have
a stool
by chance for me to put my feet up?
No, not yet.
It's kind of an interesting scenario that I have
here in this particular house. No
stools? No, I mean you could put feet up there
if you want. It's too high.
The blood flow. It's too
high. Yeah.
How old are you?
You shouldn't ask a lady that question.
You should never ask.
That's probably a bad idea.
Ruined it.
Do you have food? I do.
I actually do have food. Do you have bread?
I've got lots of bread.
Do you like bread?
Not really, no. I don't like bread,
but a house isn't really a home
without food.
I've got bread.
I do live like a 20-year-old
that's in a dorm room, but I have
peanut butter, I have cereal, I have mac and cheese,
I've got bread. Oh, sweetheart.
Why don't we whip something up really quick?
Maybe in a few days or something.
No, no, no, right now.
Why don't you give me a beard doll?
I've got some stuff going on, but I'm not sure.
I'm sorry, that might
be me. It's you.
Don't worry about that.
I have a lot of nice people
who call me.
I can get some food
ready if you want. I've got peanut butter,
you know, I've got everything.
Hello, this is Edna.
Yes. My social
security number, okay.
I can give that to you
if you want. That's fine.
What are you doing?
My social security number is
4-2-0-6-9.
Is that a family member?
My family wants to talk to you.
He's from the social security department.
He's from the social security department?
Yeah, yeah.
Are you a family member?
Did he hang up on you? They hung up.
He'll call back. He's a real sweetheart.
Was that like a son or grandson?
No, there's a little bit of a mix-up.
I left my car on the
south border of Texas, but it's a whole
thing. Don't worry about it.
I wouldn't give
your social security number to people you don't know.
Listen, will you be a sweetheart
and get me some flour and sugar and eggs
and some mayonnaise and maybe an avocado
and a couple of, I don't know,
do you have like a baking sheet
or maybe a pie tin?
I don't think I have any of those things.
You don't have any of those things?
You can take a look.
Just to make yourself comfortable and maybe
we could plan this maybe in a few days, but not right now.
Oh no, I'm busy in a few days.
Okay.
There's not much here, but...
What am I doing?
What, he only eats macaroni?
Is that you
or me? I don't know.
It sounds like you. I think it's me again.
I need to make a phone call.
Are you getting another call? How many calls do you get?
It's me. Well, I'm a very busy woman
now, right?
I would change your phone number.
Hello? Yes.
I was telling you the social security
number, right? Yeah.
It's, um, I'm sorry, what was that?
Where is my grandson?
Your grandson?
He's in prison.
I'm quite busy right now.
Maybe some leg routines, something like that.
He's in prison?
Yeah, whatever you'd cost, it doesn't matter.
Because it's not me paying for it, except it is just bullshit.
How long has he been in prison for?
Yeah, you have my address.
It came up on the thing. What do you need from me?
It's 9-8-5. 9-8-5.
Dollhouse way.
Is everything okay?
Excellent. We'll see you soon.
Well, how much money is it exactly?
How much money would you need
for me? Okay, so $10,000
and he gets out of prison.
Scott, three or so? Hang the phone up.
Hold on, it's two seconds, two seconds.
Okay, my wire details.
If I could give those, it's a Wells Fargo
or a Chase or whatever.
Hello!
It's time to get
fit.
I think so. Those look heavy.
Come on in. Get in there and get physical.
Come on in.
Okay, I was
looking about maybe some upper bodies.
Well, I can tell you
how we're going to get you in shape.
Excuse me, I'm so sorry.
I'll have to call you back.
There's a strange man
in the house.
Don't take any more phone calls.
Yes, they are. Hold on a second.
You never know.
Well, I would get your phone number, go to
the provider and they talk to them about that.
I think you probably shouldn't be answering those calls.
What's your name? Gigi.
This is Gigi.
Nice to meet you.
So what do we want to do?
So what we're going to do, some light aerobic exercise.
Get the heart rate elevated.
You can sit down.
I think I'll sit down for this one.
I want you to follow me.
First one,
the sprinkler.
Okay.
Hey.
That kind of hurts.
More movement, more energy. Come on.
But it hurts. Okay, we'll do a different one.
I can do this at home.
We're picking items at the supermarket.
We're picking items.
Come on, get that arm up.
That's right, we're picking items at the supermarket.
We're swimming in the pool.
I can actually feel it in my pecs.
Are you feeling strong?
Do you feel good?
I don't want to be responsible if something happens to you.
Just relax.
How do you feel?
I'm lightening up a little bit.
Now it's time for the skyscraper.
How much weight are these?
Those are five pounds each.
You don't want to hurt yourself.
We're yummy mummies looking to be tight in the tummy.
You got it.
You might need a spar, but you're looking good.
I wanted to drop those off as a welcoming gift for you.
You look great.
I actually feel pretty good.
You ever want to go out for a 60 mile run?
You'll never get that from Uncle.
I'll come back tomorrow morning.
Are you going to leave these here?
Would you like them?
I would love these.
How much was that?
Do you need a credit card?
No, that's okay.
We're coming back for a workout tomorrow.
I'll see myself out.
Bye.
That was a very strong workout.
That cost $200.
What was your name again?
My name is Gerber.
Do you have children?
I don't have kids.
Why don't you have children?
It just didn't work out.
I've been trying to focus on my career.
What's that? You have a job?
Your kids don't have jobs these days.
You go to work regularly?
I don't get in a car to go to work.
I go in front of a screen.
Very interesting.
What was that?
I get in front of a screen.
It's almost like a car.
What does that mean?
It sounds like you made up a job.
I get in front of a computer.
I hang out with people.
We chat and we're cool.
You don't have to make up a job to appease me.
I still care about you.
I'm a plumber.
The trades are very beautiful.
That's very difficult.
That's exactly what people need.
Plumbing, I go into the sinks.
I'd like you to really quickly,
if you don't mind,
could you point me to your bathroom?
The bathroom is right under the storage room.
I have a weak bladder.
So do I, but apparently they don't want to take care of it.
That's not bad in your hands.
All right.
She was talking about getting flour.
Flour, a whole package of eggs,
avocado,
if you have anything like noodles,
salami,
anything like that.
Excuse me.
Oh my.
Look, he's just like Jimmy Fallon.
He just breaks it every time.
Oh, stool.
Okay.
I need to get the flour ready.
Edna.
I need to.
I need to get flour.
Oh.
Okay.
Easy does it.
I'm a little titty pie.
Edna, are you in there?
What was that?
Would you like to dance, Edna?
It's a weird request, but would you like to dance?
Okay, hold on.
Edna, come on.
Come on out here. Do you like to dance?
Would you like to dance?
Would you love to dance?
Okay, let's go ahead and do this.
Okay, I don't know what that means.
All right.
My throat was a little weird.
You remind me of my husband when he was younger.
Before he passed away.
Yeah, we turn.
Now you spin me around.
Just like, thank you.
We lock it in our locket fingers.
Why are we dancing for?
Because I'm very tired.
Let go.
Okay.
Into the kitchen, if you would.
Into the kitchen.
Are you coming in here?
I'm coming in here.
Listen, I'm a firm believer
that a house isn't a home without cookies.
Yeah.
Can I give you
my mother's famous recipe for cookies?
Edna, did you wash your hands?
I never wash my hands.
You kids don't understand. I have a very good immune system.
Very good.
Okay.
No, that's okay.
If we're going to make food, then you should...
You'll do all the work, sweetie.
It's all in the feeling. You have to feel this.
So what do you need?
Flour, sugar, eggs.
What are we making? Cookies.
What kind of cookies?
Sugar, eggs, water.
What kind of eggs are these?
Those are free-range eggs.
What does free-range mean?
I don't know. I just pretend to know.
So I just pretend to know.
I think that means the chickens are going to walk around.
Okay, we'll need all of these.
Is that all right?
All of them? At least most of them, yeah.
We can use a few of them.
How much sugar do we put?
Honey, just embrace it.
Sprinkle it all in there.
This is to make cookie dough?
Yes, go ahead. Just give it a couple of good shakes.
Put it all in there.
All the flour?
Well, I mean most of it.
That's good.
A little more.
A little bit more.
Eyeball it. Does that seem good?
I've never made cookies in my entire life.
You've never made cookies?
That looks great.
You want to wiggle it around a little.
See if there's any lumps in there.
Okay, now dump all the sugar in it.
People like sugar.
I like sugar. It's good.
And this is just how my mother used to make these.
They're very simple.
I have these Mickey Mouse gloves on.
It's kind of hard to open.
I don't know why you kids do things like that.
It's just like...
Where did you get these spoons, by the way?
Those were left by my uncle Ted.
Okay.
Who recently passed away.
Can I have them?
Can I have those spoons?
Can you have them?
You don't use them, right?
They were left from my uncle Ted,
who recently passed away.
You need help with that?
I'm just going to open the top
because I have these Mickey Mouse gloves on.
Somebody decided I was going to wear them the entire day.
You're your own person.
You get to make your own choices.
How much sugar goes in here?
The whole thing goes right in there.
That's perfect.
That looks good.
What I want you to do
is crack two or three eggs into that pitcher.
Two or three of them?
Two or three.
Whatever you're feeling today,
do you want to be extra moist cookies?
Is there a recipe or are you just doing this?
It's all in your heart, honey.
I don't know what that means.
How many eggs do you think would be best?
If you're always on a quiz show
and you tell me how many eggs,
I would say probably four.
That's terrible. We'll make it again.
That's fine.
You've got to do better than that.
We've made a good decision here.
These gloves are coming off.
How about two?
I think it'll be great.
Even one egg is perfect.
Back in the war, when I was younger,
we used to have to ration
and we could make one egg go a long way.
You know what? In the gift basket,
I brought over some applesauce.
Applesauce?
This is applesauce.
These are mint chocolates.
If you boil them up,
it'll be a similar consistency.
We'll roll with it.
Okay, so boil these?
No, forget it.
You don't want them in?
You're fine.
I need a stirrer.
Do you have water?
Take a little bit of water.
I get a picture here.
What is this going to make, Edna?
They used to say two spoons of sugar
would make the medicine go down.
In this case, you have a whole box.
It'll taste very good.
That smell you're smelling, by the way,
is probably the eggs and the sugar combined.
It's probably filling the room.
I can't smell anything.
Thank God.
How much water?
That'll do.
Do I mix this?
What kind of cookies?
Put your arms back into it.
Uh-huh.
Really work.
I want to see you actually working.
It's good for you kids to work.
Yeah, it is.
Elbow grease, we used to call it.
This is sugar flour and egg.
Pecan sandies.
My mother's recipe.
Those are my least favorite cookie in the world.
Why would you say that?
It tastes like you're taking a bite of the beach on the ground
and it's sandy.
So you don't want extra pecans?
When I take a bite of a pecan sandy,
I feel like there's sand in my underwear from the beach.
You don't like that?
I don't hate them.
I thought that's why some people went to the beach.
I've got it all wrong, I guess.
Okay.
Are you really tired after this?
I mean, it's work, Edna.
Look at this. Look at how much muscle I'm putting into this.
You kids don't understand.
All right, that's good.
Can we see? Is that good?
Do you mind for two seconds?
I have to make a quick phone call if you don't mind.
No, fine.
Put it in the oven.
That's an oven-proof bowl.
Okay.
Edna, this is plastic.
Can I actually use your phone?
Before you go in there, I need to take a shower real quick.
Oh.
You can get on the phone.
I'm going to call somebody this way.
I'm going to take a quick shower.
Okay.
All right, you're fine.
Let me get these in the oven.
Is it going to be pecan sandies?
Yeah, put it in there for like 20 minutes.
Okay, so 20 minutes.
Doesn't that seem kind of long?
Is it okay if the utensil's in there?
Okay, I'm going to take a shower.
I'm so sorry. If you smell something, it's not me.
I'm going to get fucking rid of this lady.
My neighbor?
What the fuck?
There's really nothing in this house.
So much better.
I think I'm just going to piss.
I'm just pissing right now.
Well, the water was off. The water's off now.
I want to pee now.
Turn the water back on.
You don't just pee into an empty shower.
You pee when your shower's running.
Everyone does it.
And you can pretend like you don't.
I know you do.
It's better. I feel better.
Sweetie?
Are you there?
I would wash my hands, but...
What was your name again?
Justin?
Justin, are you there?
You don't by chance have nitroglycerin
pills or anything, do you?
I don't... What was it?
No medicine. No medicine at all.
I've got acetaminophen. I've got
ibuprofen. Okay, it's fine.
We're probably done by now.
The cookies are done? Oh, yeah.
I already sprinkled the pecan in there.
Oh, you put the pecans in? Oh, thank you.
Appreciate it.
Oh, my.
They smell heavenly.
They do smell fantastic. That's strange.
Just like my mother used to make them.
Well, open it up.
Let's see. How does it look?
The fruits of your labor.
Yeah, I mean, it's the fruits of our labor.
I might as well take a look and see.
I'm curious. I think the plastic from the bowl
must have transitioned
into this. Yes.
Is that the recipe? Yeah, that happens.
It's called osmosis. Right.
If you would have gone to school, you would have learned.
Edna, could you get one for me? I have raw egg
all over my hands that I don't want to get
salmonella.
You let my grandchildren salmonella?
I've got like a thing in my throat.
My twin granddaughters salmonella,
did they come by? No.
I'm talking about the food. They love
these. I make them for them. They're very good.
Can I try? Would you like one?
I thought, okay.
You can keep these, all right?
Let's see.
Just like sand at the beach.
I feel sand
all up in my underwear.
It's fantastic.
It feels great. You look like you're loving it.
You look like it. I was probably
at the beach at some point.
These are fantastic. I know.
I know. Just like I told you. You just have to feel
it any time you want to make food, I swear.
Just put the stuff in there.
Feel it out.
It's been about seven or eight hours since you've showed up.
I think it's time maybe
Where do you live? Do you need help getting home?
I usually get lost,
but someone will call me and I'll have to go down
to the police department or the bank or something
like that. It will be fine.
Do you live in the neighborhood?
I don't have a car. Yes, you don't have a car.
I could point you to where your house is.
It's somewhere
around that way.
Because it's getting late.
I'm getting really tired, I'll be honest.
I need the gift basket back.
Could I have an apple?
Sure. Let me just have one apple.
It's a very beautiful apple
that you've given me.
If there's anything you ever need, I know a lot of people.
Especially if you have computer
problems. You let me know, sweetheart.
I wouldn't answer
the phone for very many people anymore.
I enjoy it. I have plenty of time.
It was nice to meet you.
It was a wonderful meeting.
Maybe I'll see you again. It was fantastic.
I'm sure. Thank you for
the recipe and everything. Absolutely.
Thank you. I'm exhausted.
I hope she gets home
okay. Is she going to get home
okay? Should I make sure she's okay?
She said she doesn't even know if she lives.
I have no idea. Should I
make sure she's alright? I don't know.
That was an interesting day.
Oh.
She's here all day.
I'm just trying to be nice. I'm not trying to
get rid of an old lady or something.
You're here all day.
I got the
fitness instructor here.
I feel a little tighter.
I also feel like
we're doing this now apparently.
I'm going to do this into the bedroom because
I'm not going to leave another floor again.
I'm slow to sleep on another floor.
No. No thanks.
Ow.
What's today?
Saturday? Thursday?
Tuesday? I don't know.
Do I have something to do today? No.
I don't know. I think three or four people are going to call
me. Like at a meeting.
I don't know. Whatever happened yesterday
I just forget it as of today. It sucks.
It happens all the time.
Somebody will bring me up to speed.
This is a cool bed.
Not that cool.
No. I don't want to.
Not today. Something else.
Something else. Not today.
Ah. Fuck. Whatever.
Imagine not even being able to pee
before you go to work. I'm coming.
Just wait.
Oops. Oh look.
Peek hand sandies.
Time to make the money.
Wait. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm here.
I'm here. I'm here. I'm here. I'm here. Come on.
Why do you always pull so far down
this fuck. You're pulling my driveway.
You don't have to walk down the street to see you.
Hi Adam. Hi Sweden.
Are you with them? You're falling
very far behind.
You know I actually don't. I don't trust people that fucking
work out that much. Seriously.
Like what do you have to prove? What do you have to prove?
Like you can take a day off.
You go like Monday, Wednesday.
Like Tuesday, Thursday. Right? What do you have to prove?
Why are you working out literally seven days a week? There's no reason to.
Shit.
Hey. How are you?
Hi. Hi. It's really great
to see you again. It's so lovely to see you. Yes.
I'm one of those people that talks a lot of things
about somebody and then when they see them
they pretend like they didn't say those things at all.
How are you? Tomorrow morning.
Yes. Tomorrow morning.
Sixteen miles. Sixteen miles.
Sixteen miles. Yes. Of course.
Absolutely. Absolutely.
If you could do that away from my house.
There's like six different
intersections here. You could go down.
I don't want to hear that in the morning
or in the night.
Fuck those people. I feel like shit.
Long day.
Colon D. Colon D. Colon D.
I'm hungry and I want to shower.
And I'm not having a great time.
Those people are having a great time outside.
Why can't I have a good time too?
I got like
Ted shit here.
Thank you. Some of you listen
and some of you don't.
It's okay. Ah.
So much better.
You know what I mean? It's like you work out so much
you don't have time for anything else.
I don't care how much you worked out.
Look I'm just trying to live.
If I sit down and we're at lunch
and you say like
oh hey dude by the way I fucking
I could do like five hundred pounds
five times for the rep. I don't care.
That's good for you.
You're saying that because I can't do that.
You're saying that to me because I can't do it.
God.
You know what I can do?
I can do what they can?
Not much. Not very much at all actually.
Actually it hurts to walk around
from me at the moment. But you know one day
I'll get there. Ah.
That feels better. Ah.
What is this?
But they that wait upon the Lord shall renew their strength
they shall mount up with wings as
eagles. They shall run
and not be weary and they shall walk and not
faint. You know I've actually seen
this in somebody's bathroom before.
I've seen that before.
Whatever. I guess here it is.
Showered.
I feel clean. I feel good.
Although I'm kind of not having a
great time but you know whatever.
I got my expensive watch. That's all
that matters right? Let's go to the
bathroom. Let's fucking stool out of the way.
I don't know.
I have to look at this every time I pee.
Something about that. By the way
that's like what are you blurring?
There's somebody like sitting
on that toilet that you're blurring.
Who is that? That's
not me.
Oops! Wait I'm done.
Okay we're good. Like there's somebody
else sitting on that toilet.
No no no no no. I'm going to the
bedroom. You gave me this like mystery
box of stools.
I'm gonna place them. What time is it?
It's pretty late.
It's alright. We'll put two here.
We'll put one over here.
Not like it matters.
I don't know. I'm getting kind of annoyed.
What do I even need these stools for?
I'm okay. Don't get too
upset. Hey this is how tall
I want to be. All of you are the five
seven men out there.
You ever thought about this? You ever think about how big you were?
If you were this big?
This is what? Six? Six two?
Man. God.
What a figure that would be. Wouldn't it?
How about um
I don't know. We can put them next to the bed.
How about like one here?
One here. And then
should all three go over there?
I don't hate that. I really
don't. Three stools
in front of the bed. I don't know if you
get on the side. If you're as tired
as I am right now that seems like a pretty good idea.
That means I can get out of the bed. I can put
my feet down on three different
places.
I am tired. How much
cash do we have? How much money?
What do we got for cash?
$19.60.
Give me something nice for god's sake.
I got money. So no, that makes sense
because then I don't have to clean all this shit up. That's a good idea.
Calling a maid is a good idea.
Thank you.
Because the last, I don't want to
clean anything up. I want to be able to have somebody else do it.
We got almost two grand. Let's
use it. Hi.
Yes. I would love to, I'd like to have
a service started please.
Yeah the address is 985-985
Dollhouse Way.
I mean you know. You're in this fucked up
cartoon universe with the rest of us.
Yeah. Okay.
Thank you. Do you live in the neighborhood
too? Are you like down the street?
Because it seems like everybody lives next to each other here.
Okay. Thank you.
Today? I mean I'm tired but okay fine.
That's fine. Alright goodbye.
Alright let's get a maid in here. I don't want to have to deal with this.
They'll take care of it.
That was very quick.
They must live in the neighborhood.
I'm so tired though.
Alright.
Maid service.
Here we are. Hi.
Hi.
I'm assuming that you must be the maid?
I heard you ordered a sexy maid
service.
You have a big mess to clean
don't you? Stop doing the lap track. I don't want that.
Yes there's a mess in here.
It's very messy. Well trust me I can take
care of your big mess.
Okay come on in. Show me where it is.
So I pretty much what I want you to do.
Come on in. Watch the door behind you.
Don't want to get hit by that.
Such a gentleman.
Wow. What a unique arrangement.
So there's this
trash here.
This is dusty?
Yes it is. It's very dusty. So if you want to dust
there's some fruit here that needs to be cleaned up.
Oh saw stain.
Yes thank you.
So there's in the bathroom the toilet needs to be cleaned.
The trash needs to be taken out.
This flower, the fridge needs to be cleaned.
This room, the bathroom, any other rooms?
Yes come with me. I'll show you.
Bathroom definitely needs to be
cleaned. The sinks need to be cleaned.
If you have an opportunity to it would be great.
How much do you charge?
Well for you I'll drop my
prices to $2,000.
That's $2,000 for this?
For the sexy
maid service. Why is this $2,000?
No it's like $100.
It's not $2,000. Well lead me to the bedroom
and I can show I'm worth $2,000.
No.
$2,000.
What are you trying to say?
Am I not sexy?
I didn't say any of that.
I'm looking for a maid service to come and help clean up
maybe make the bed. Okay.
How sexy am I worth?
I don't have $2,000.
Okay well you're the one who called
a sexy maid service.
Well honestly
I think you look great. I do.
I think you're probably the best looking
maid service maid I've ever seen in my life.
Do you mean that?
Yes of course. Go on.
I think you're the most attractive
sexiest maid ever.
I do. I really do.
Please keep going. You're so
wonderful.
Let me show you the bathroom.
Okay.
So I have a
plunger. I have a
plunger and if anything ever happens
with the toilet I'm sure you'll be coming and going over the
course of the day. Do you just want me to clean
your house?
Yeah.
Why didn't you just call a regular
I'm a sexy maid.
What do you mean sexy
maid? Well like a regular maid service
is like $100 maybe $200
but when you add the sexy it's $2,000
for a maid. Well what would you do for
$100?
Clean your house I guess. That's perfect
that works for me. $200?
Okay. Are you coming here every other day?
Yeah I'll come. You still
think I look sexy though right? I do.
Is that alright with you?
You want to go lower? That's okay with $150
for just cleaning.
But if you're ever interested in
expanding my rules
Yes I will keep that very much in mind if you
come this way and just take a look and
start doing your thing. I'll clean over here.
Pick that before I fucking shit
my pants in front of the maid.
Sexy maid
$2,000
that's so much money. I'm just
trying to get my life together in here before I go
back in there.
And I'm fucking tired too.
It's four.
Thank you so much.
Wait where is it going?
Wait what?
Am I sick?
Do I have like the
norovirus? Like what's happening?
Sir? Yeah?
Are you alright? I'm okay
in here. You don't have to come in. Do you have a big
mess you need cleaning?
No
You can stay out there. Okay.
Alright that's good.
What did I eat? Those
pecan sandies I swear to god.
Do you like food?
Yeah. Do you like bread?
Yeah. I wonder if
Yes this bread
I got multi grain bread over there.
Do you like multi grain bread? Yeah I like multi grain
bread. Could I ask you
why?
Aesthetically I thought it made sense
to put it in the corner here to make sure there's enough room
for people to come around. There's not enough space.
Maybe eventually there will be a TV up here
like a big screen TV up here.
Yeah like they could watch the TV
play video games. It would have made sense to make it flush.
Well you're a maid
you're not an interior designer. You're right
I'm just a maid.
That was the bread. That was the bread we have to eat.
I'll clean the bathroom next.
I can still eat it.
Excuse me
sexy maid. What?
Would you like a piece of
bread? Sure.
Okay.
Let's get some bread on the fucking stove top.
Would you like a piece of bread?
I've got bread and you throw it on the ground but it's okay.
Why don't you grab a piece of bread? I want you
to eat. Well I've been cleaning
I wouldn't dare touch it with my hands.
Right but if you just eat
wash your hands and then eat.
I'm not putting it in your mouth. Right. No of course.
Sorry I'm just used
to different clients is all.
Out of here. Out of here.
I'm getting out of here. I'm going to the bathroom.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'm going to stay here.
And excuse me
this job
is not done.
The maid is scaring me.
Our job's not done.
I'm so tired.
God. I think I'm going to pass out.
I think I'm really going to pass out. I need to go to bed.
I have to go to bed so bad.
I'm sorry if I smell a little weird.
It's just it's been a long day.
Well that's two hundred dollars.
Are you going to. What?
Two hundred? I thought it was one fifty.
I cleaned more than I thought I
had to. There was a big mess in the bathroom.
Okay take two hundred.
Alright sir well
I'll see you in a few days. Yeah
and it's a hundred fifty each time right?
From here on out we'll talk about it.
And we're not doing anything else. Do you still
want me to wear this next time I come?
If you like if you're comfortable
wearing that you can. You dog.
It's been a weird day.
I'm tired. Give me something
to play with. Give me something to hang out with.
I mean you guys seriously like I
I got to go to bed. I can't just
sleep on a couch every fucking day.
Give me like give me like give me the bedroom.
Get me to get me to bed. What is it?
What does it say?
You didn't want it. What? Why
not? Scammed.
I literally I can all I
can see is colors. It's the only
thing I can see. I just see pink and I see like
green. I see pink here.
It's just pink.
I need somebody who has to tell me to go to bed.
If I don't then
you're just going to get me fucked up again. All I see
is pink colors.
That was really cool made. I really thought they were
cool. I like to work out with people too.
I'm going to get into the bedroom as fast
as I can because I don't want to have a problem.
For the first time fucking ever.
For the first time ever you
make me go to sleep. Thank you.
Seriously like this is the first time you've ever done it.
Took you long enough.
What is that?
Why is there a computer in front of my fucking
door?
There's a computer here? What is outside?
I hear something.
Dog or something?
Oh no.
My god.
Oh my fucking god.
What am I doing in this scenario?
Is it because of the food? Oh it's trash.
What time is it?
It's like
one o'clock in the morning.
Oh shit.
Can you see me? I hope you can't see me.
What am I supposed to do about this?
I got to go in the bedroom.
Oh my god.
Yay.
A computer. Cool.
Huh?
You want to do what?
No I'm not going out there.
What the fuck am I?
Alright it's time for you to pay.
I don't want to go out here.
Why would you make me do this?
Hey bear you're in deep shit.
Oh my god.
He's biting me.
Jesus.
Play dead.
What are you doing?
Do you see what he did out here?
Why would you make me go confront him?
Are you out of your mind?
What am I going to do
versus a bear that's five times
as big as me?
I didn't sleep all the way through the night.
Oh.
Good thing I have a maid.
At least I've been able to help me clean this shit up.
Close the door
for the love of god.
Why are there bears here?
I'm here.
Wait.
Go fuck yourself.
Good thing I got my watch.
I feel so bad.
There's a mess in my yard.
There's a mess.
Wait a minute.
I'm covered in scrapes.
I'm covered in bruises.
I need to sleep a lot for a while
and then I need to eat
if I have something to do.
Holy shit.
I can't stream right now.
There's no way I can stream.
What do you want me to stream?
Oh no.
No, I refuse.
I can't.
Oh.
Hey, what's going on, everybody?
It's Jerma here.
We're going to be playing some Call of Duty.
So as you can see here,
I'm going to be in the menu for a little while.
And welcome to the stream.
It's good to have you here.
Of course, I have a pretty good day today.
I had a crazy scenario happen.
A crazy scenario.
Hold on, let me get in here.
What's that?
No way, dude. That's so funny.
I saw a bear outside today.
And I walked out there.
And I was like, what the heck is that bear?
And eventually, I went outside.
And I did a little horn.
And the bear got away from the horn.
I shit and I sleep.
What does it say?
The water does that.
You have been banned from Twitch
for 24 hours.
This is temporary ban for sleeping on stream.
Oh, what the fuck?
What?
When did I go to sleep on stream?
What are you talking about?
Give me a fucking break.
That's the first ban I've ever had.
Are you sure I didn't get banned because I'm streaming from my toilet?
Sleeping on stream,
I think it's way less offensive
than shitting on the toilet and streaming.
Just like that.
That's six, by the way.
I'd like to take a shower right now, please.
That's the first ban I've ever had.
I hope I didn't say anything weird in my sleep.
I'm fucking starving and stuff.
Oh, yay.
Ah.
Banned from Twitch.
Can I call anybody?
I don't know.
I say all kinds of weird fucked up shit.
Let me just brush my teeth real quick.
Brush your teeth and shower.
It saves about five minutes.
That's a pro tip for everybody.
Coming up.
So what happened?
There's an office chair
next to the toilet.
Why would there be
an office chair here?
In case somebody wanted to watch?
Oh, hey, man, you got an extra seat?
Yeah, go ahead. You sit in the toilet, I'll watch you.
Why is there an office chair?
I'm starving.
There's a piece of bread on the ground.
Good.
I'm not going to work today, by the way,
just in case you were curious.
Not going to work.
You can leave without me.
I got plenty of money.
Go on. Not going to work.
Go on without me.
Tell the boss I said I'm the biggest producer
so I can stay home.
What is this?
Does this work?
Is this an organ?
I don't think it works.
We play Radical Dreamers
from Chrono Cross.
Pretty good.
How about Super Mario?
That's terrible.
Can I do reverb?
What?
There we go.
What do they want me to do?
Food.
How about a piece of bread?
Because it's the easiest thing to make.
I like to toast it.
I like to toast it real quick.
Better.
I do have to pee though.
Or, you know, the other one.
I'm sad that the maid threw this
on the ground though.
I'm going to play with the organ again.
It works.
What do the pedals do?
Holy shit.
Hey.
What?
Ludwig?
What are you doing here?
I live here.
You live here?
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
I've lived here for seven years.
Hold on.
983, 983.
You're 983?
I'm 983.
I do not know.
Hold on.
Don't mind any of this shit.
It's fine.
Why do you have a
trash everywhere?
Don't worry about that.
There was a tornado that came in.
Did you see the tornado that came in?
They come sometimes.
A tornado flew through here.
The tornado flew in
and it swarmed everybody.
You didn't get that?
The gloves are also
confusing to me. Is that normal?
Yeah, it's very normal.
Tornado came in, ruined
everything.
It's nice to see you.
Do you want to come in?
Sure.
I was just playing this because
it was a gift from a friend of mine.
I'll get it for you.
We should clean.
I want to clean first.
Can you just help me for a second?
Sure.
When did you move in here?
By the way, I had a raider.
Excuse me. Sheriff Tony
Andrews. How are you guys doing?
We're looking for a bear.
Have you seen the bear around here?
We're going around the whole neighborhood.
I've got animal control with me.
He's an expert.
A tornado came in and a bear came in.
There was a bear and a tornado?
I kicked the shit out of the bear.
There was a tornado.
Smell him.
There was a tornado. Do you see the tornado?
No tornado sightings in the area.
I'm pretty sure there's no tornadoes
around here.
Do you guys like organs?
No. Have you seen a bear or not?
I had a bear
encounter yesterday.
You're a full day late.
I don't know.
He's a bear.
You got a scent?
I can smell him.
I think he went this way.
Nothing tricks this nose.
I can smell that bear.
Why is everybody coming to my house?
We'll find him. Listen, Sheriff
Tony Andrews, if you need anything, give me a call
and pick up the trash.
Let's keep the neighborhood nice.
He beat a bear in a fight.
Yes, I found a bear in a fight.
There was a tornado, and I got an organ.
I knew I liked you.
I really liked you, but I didn't know you lived here.
I just live here. I was just walking by.
I don't mean to intrude or anything.
I just had a good time playing Battleship the other day.
You still owe me a lot from that.
I do. I have quite a few things.
I don't know how long.
I get to get in a shirt. I get to do a thing in a shirt
T-shirt. Milky Maids.
1500.
If you ever wanted to play again, we could just sweep the debt.
Maybe double or nothing.
Do you have another job here, by the way?
Oh, well...
Do you work here in the town?
I'm a streamer.
Do you work here as anything else?
In this town?
Do you clean houses or anything?
Do you think my stream is not successful enough?
No, no, no.
I stream like a month in a row.
It was a long time.
I know.
It was great.
You don't do anything else in this town?
Again, I just stream.
All right, whatever. I won't even push it anymore.
So you're talking about
we could play what?
We could play Battleship?
Yeah, if you ever wanted to. Why do you have bread on the floor?
I'm supposed to have it made.
You just ate it out of the ground.
Should I follow you?
Come on in the other room.
Wow! This is your stream setup.
This is my setup, man. Check it out.
That's convenient to have two chairs for co-op.
Yeah.
I could look out. This is good.
You could watch me stream if you wanted to.
This is a good setup.
By the way, it's cleaned very well from whoever that person happens to be
that comes and cleans the house every so often.
A maid?
Is it a guy or a girl?
It's you.
Sexy?
It would be you.
I think it's you.
Are we co-op streaming?
Do you want me to do your intro?
Sometimes I get nervous before a stream.
Let's try to start the stream.
Just go live.
What's up, suckers?
It's not live yet.
I'm a little nervous when I do co-ops in person.
It won't go through.
I'm banned from Twitch.
Why did you get banned?
Do you see where I stream from?
Yeah.
This reminds me of another doctor streamer.
You know.
If you can make it work, you can make it work.
I'm going to fall out of the thing.
This has been a bit eye-opening, man.
I didn't know that you lived here.
I didn't know that you lived like this.
You've got to have your setup in a good place, right?
No, that's what I agree with.
I think we disagree on
how you accomplished that.
I've got to shower, too, if you feel
you need to take a shower or anything.
Anything you bring up that you have.
It's assumed.
Yeah, but in case you needed to, it's there.
Oh, homemade cookies.
There are cookies.
Oh, and what do you got here?
You want to play?
No.
I've been waiting for your arrival for months, even though I didn't even know you lived here.
I have Mickey
weird mouse
cartoon gloves on.
Can you go ahead and open that for me?
I'll open it for you.
Let's get this moved out of the way.
Sorry, I've got to piss really bad.
You take your time. I'll set it up.
I don't have to go quite yet.
Why would you bring it up to me?
Just in case for you to know in the future that I'm going to have to go eventually.
Thank you for the information.
I also will have to pee in the future.
There's a bathroom there, too.
I don't know when.
Should I set up your board for you?
I think you should, because I can't touch it.
I made cookies
with this woman. Do you know Edna?
Oh, Edna?
Isn't she great?
She's a cool chef, but she's a little weird, though.
Well, like weird in a good way, you know?
I got it for you.
Yeah, I can't even
touch that.
I think this is how it goes.
This looks much more complicated
than I thought it was going to be.
I was thinking, since you owe me about $500,
we could just do a simple
You want to do two ships?
Two ships. Maybe even just one.
One ship.
Just a two-piece ship.
I can't get this other glove off because it's taped to my wrist.
You know what?
It's taped.
It's a great watch, though.
It is a really nice watch. Am I flexing enough?
Do you know that I make pretty good money?
Do you know that I make good money?
I saw your last stream, you know.
You missed a day.
Insistency is key.
You make great money.
I don't want you to see my screen.
Charming place. I'm not cheating.
Just place one ship.
We're doing one ship?
Just one ship, yeah.
You're not looking, right? I'm not looking.
I got my ship placed.
Do you have your ship placed? I do.
Are you starting this off?
Yeah, I'm going to say
C5.
Just be so incorrect.
So incorrect, it's a miss.
This is $500 on the line.
What are we doing with some money?
You owe me money. This is a double or nothing.
Okay, fine.
Now I'm fine with it. You can make a lot.
I didn't even know you lived here.
So C5 is a miss.
I will go with C5 as well.
You're doing C5? It's a miss.
I don't like the aesthetic here.
Can you scoot to your left by like 3 or 4
inches here a little more?
There we go. I like that. I like the aesthetic there a little more.
Is that a bit better? That's a bit better to me.
I just have to think about the way you were sitting.
It bothered you. It bothered me very much.
That's fair. So you said C5?
Yeah, C5. Okay, it's a miss.
I'm going to say, you can literally see me.
No, I can't see anything. You can see.
I'm going to say F7.
Incredibly incorrect.
Okay.
Fine. Where are you going?
Maybe like something in the
first column.
Okay.
Well, you have to say something.
D, maybe C1.
C1 is a hit.
It's a hit? Yeah, and you literally looked.
No, I wouldn't do that.
I'd like move to your left and he's like, oh sure.
You asked me to move to my left. I just happened to move to my left.
You literally can see. I'm just going to take a random stab
in the dark. D1.
No. What?
There's something on D1.
First of all, I want to do this real quick.
Don't move. Okay.
Here, I want everyone to see what I have.
Show them what I have.
If you ever have to go to the bathroom and take a shower, feel free to.
That's where I am and he looked and it's bullshit.
I've never looked at anything in my life.
Call me a cheater?
Yes.
So when did you move here?
At 983 Dollhouse Lane.
983 Dollhouse Lane. I've been living at Dollhouse Lane
for a while actually.
I was with my mother.
I was friends with a man named Ted. Passed recently.
Sad passing too.
Came out of nowhere.
Blindsided us all.
You weren't there.
No.
No, I wasn't.
I didn't think I had to be there.
It was very clear.
You would be your uncle too.
We would be literally like brothers.
My mom is not related.
You and I are not related at all?
No, my mom is just friends with him.
I'm going to go F3.
F3 is just going to be a miss on your end.
That's fine.
You don't have to pee yet or anything, right?
I have had to pee for the last hour.
I've had to pee for the last hour but I'm just going to hold it
because I like talking to you.
Okay, okay.
Let me go with E1.
E1 is incorrect.
You already said that last time.
No, I said D1.
Oh, well you were wrong twice.
Where do you want to go instead?
You know what?
I'll go D2.
D2? That is a miss.
You already have a hit.
Hold on, I've got to get this.
Who is calling right now?
Hello?
It's just static. I don't know who this is.
No, I don't know.
Hello? Hello?
What the fuck?
It was a prank call.
It could have been a prank call.
Hold on, somebody's there.
We have a final courtesy call.
Before we close out your file,
I wanted to see if you were available
to talk for a few minutes.
I'm not available to talk.
If you're a specialist concerning extending
or reinstating your vehicle's
warranty, press 1 right now
to speak to a warranty specialist.
I'd like for you to put me on the do not call list.
That's what I would appreciate. Thank you.
Put me on the do not call list, ever again.
And I know what that means is that means you're going to take this,
you're going to put me in a database of people that answered the phone
so therefore I'm going to get 10 times more phone calls.
The real play is for me to never actually
answer the phone, because if I answer the phone
that means they have me in the database of people that answered the phone
so therefore I'll get more.
Have a good day. Fuck you.
What was your move?
It was...
C4, like the explosive.
That's a hit.
What?
C3.
That's a hit.
C2.
That's a hit. You won again.
I have to pay $500.
That's $500.
This is just for fun.
That's just for fun.
I guessed it correctly.
You guessed it correctly, but you didn't even...
Hold on.
Sorry, I've just really got to go to the bathroom.
Yeah, take your time.
I've got to go to the bathroom.
Well, I can't go yet.
But I have to go.
I didn't think it would be like this when we hung out.
I didn't even know you lived here. I thought you lived somewhere.
I didn't know you lived here.
I've always lived in Dollhouse.
You walked over and I was doing my thing, playing the organ
and I didn't know you were here.
You're weirdos, by the way. Is it police?
It's the police. There's been a bear on the loose.
Have you had a bear in your house?
Well, before, yeah.
You've had a bear come to your front door?
Before, yeah.
What did you do?
Well, the rational thing, I called the cops.
What else would you do?
What would you do?
I would call the police.
But I fought him and I kicked his ass.
What?
And then he kicked my ass.
Okay, you're saying it with a tone that makes me think you might not have.
I'll be right back.
Take your time.
Just hang out this food in the fridge, this pecan sandwich I made.
Yeah, sure.
Ludwig is in my house right now.
He's awesome.
He's like a huge streamer.
He's like fucking really funny and shit.
I wasn't prepared for this.
I got a piece so fucking bad you have no idea.
Please help me.
Please. I'll do anything.
Please let me go to the bathroom.
Hey!
How are you?
I'm doing good.
He's doing good. Awesome.
How are you doing?
I'm doing great. It's good to have you here, man.
It's really good to have you here.
You seem on edge.
Yeah.
You want something to drink?
No, I'm fine.
Ludwig!
There's stereo in here. I'm listening to weird music.
No, I get that.
Listen to drum solos.
It kind of feels like you're trying to drum over the sound of your shitting,
but that makes sense too.
It's drum solos.
Why is the paper this far away?
Why would the paper be over here?
This guy's a bit of a psycho.
Thank God.
That paper is like three feet away.
Hands washed.
Ludwig, how are you?
How are you doing?
You've done this a couple times.
I'm doing good.
I don't want to stay too long.
It seems like you've got a lot of shit going on.
No, not really.
Just a few things.
I'm really happy you came over. I hope you like the place.
It's cool.
It's all right.
It's a low mortgage.
I got it on a good deal.
Yeah.
You got a beer?
Is that okay?
I'm just going to help myself.
It's cool, man.
I don't want to...
It's all good, man.
Sometimes I just got to fucking get some blood pumping.
Sorry.
Do I do it with you?
You can if you want to.
Sometimes I just feel like doing it because I feel like I've got to get some blood going in my body.
Maybe you could move this to not be in the middle.
That would be a workout.
I can't get swole that way.
Right.
That makes a lot of sense.
It does.
Hey, it's been a pleasure.
It's been wonderful.
How many times do I have to pay you every time I see you?
Don't want to be too forward.
Maybe it's worth getting a maid around these parts.
I know. I thought about that.
Weirdly enough, though.
Maids are like two grand around here.
Well, the sexy ones.
You wouldn't get those ones.
Those are the maids that are like happy ending maids.
Two grand, though. It's a little high.
Well, it's a good ending.
End of Code Geass levels.
It's a little high.
Okay.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'll just get my socks on.
I'll just see myself out.
Hey, it was great seeing you.
I'll just get my socks on.
This guy's a fucking psycho.
Ahh.
I can't sleep.
Why?
That was so fucking embarrassing.
He's like really cool.
That's like you literally just brought in
one of the coolest dudes I know.
I'm trying to sleep.
I'm so tired, but I can't.
Why?
Why can't I sleep?
I don't...
It's raining. It's really raining.
It's like loud rain.
It's like a thunderstorm.
Oh, whoa.
Whoa.
Whoa, TV.
TV.
Does it work?
TV? How do I turn it on?
Holy shit.
A TV.
If I can turn it on.
Where is it?
Where is the TV?
How do I turn it on?
The rain is so loud.
TV.
Oh, cool. TV.
Oh, whoa.
Wow.
TV.
How do I turn
the TV off?
Oh, cool.
TV.
Wow. Oh, my God.
Oh, wow. TV.
TV.
Shit's fucked.
Why don't we watch some TV?
Oh,
the beautiful rainstorm.
Take a look outside.
Wow.
It's coming down out there.
Holy smokes.
Time to stream.
Let's get some stream going here.
All right, going live.
Check me out.
And live.
Hey, guys. Just started the stream.
But before I get started,
let's run some ads.
No, I don't see it.
It's not on the screen, is what you're saying.
Thanks for the subs. Appreciate it.
It's not there, though. I'm not blind. I can't see it.
There's nothing there.
There's nothing on the screen.
I've turned around four
times now, okay?
I'm not there.
Stop fucking with me. I'm just getting, like, gaslit.
That's all you guys fucking do.
I don't know if that's somebody's officers,
police officers driving by or something.
Yeah. No, that was a siren.
I don't know. That's a main road. It's a busy road.
Yeah, I got it.
Ring the doorbell or something.
Ring the doorbell.
I gotta go.
It's hard to do. I'm freaking blind.
Can you knock it a couple times? Do something, okay?
I'm freaking
pretty sure this is the right place.
I'm pretty sure. All right, let me show you how it's done, all right?
Hey, listen, this is
Sheriff Tony Andrews, I believe we met.
Yeah, we have. I have some complaints
about a stolen TV in the
area, and the GPS tracking device
is showing right here. Yeah,
the GPS tracking device. Yeah, what's that?
It's raining.
Interesting. Well, listen,
listen, you're gonna have to let us in here, okay? We gotta inspect
the area. It's raining. Can you see that?
How are you guys out here in the rain? Wait, is it
raining right here? Yeah, it's raining just in that spot. I'm perfectly fine.
Yeah, that's
a stolen what? Yeah, you see
that stolen TV? My GPS says it's
right at this location, right? 985
Dollhouse Road. How do you have a GPS on
what is stolen? Everything has
tracking devices. We gotta go
in here, we gotta go in here. Do I seriously go
inside, dude? Who is this guy? He's
a serial jaywalker.
I caught him loitering outside the library
a couple minutes ago. Listen, dude,
you can just call me Snakebite.
Why is, why are you bringing him in my house?
What's that? It's a TV.
You see this, you see that red dot?
Yeah. You see that TV?
Where'd you get that TV? That TV was 50 bucks.
I got it from second hand. It was second hand.
And where'd you get it? Huh? Where'd you get that TV?
I got it from, it was brought to me by some
sleep paralysis demons in the night. Sleep
paralysis demons, yeah, okay.
Tell me more about your sleep
paralysis demons. You got any
sleep paralysis demons?
Sleep paralysis, dude?
It's going down out there, you hear that?
I don't know what you, he's crazy.
You're a psycho, you know that?
You think it's raining, you got sleep
paralysis demons? What do you want
to do about the TV? What do you want to do about the TV?
Let me ask you something. You see that red dot?
You think that's that TV right there?
Officer, I don't want, I don't
want a criminal just in my house.
He hasn't actually officially been arrested yet.
That's a whole other story. Why is he handcuffed?
This is boring. Hold my phone.
Dude, this is crazy, man.
Let me just double check something, okay?
You can look if you want. I don't think
there's anything wrong. I mean the TV doesn't
work, it broke. Yeah, that's the
exact serial number with the GPS.
I didn't buy it. Somebody wanted it for me.
It came in here, sleep paralysis demons
brings it to me and it's going to take my name in my bank account.
Do me a favor. I'm going to need you to help
me pick this up, alright? Oh yeah, sure.
I'm sorry, sir, this is stolen property.
Unless you want me to- You can't take my TV.
You want me to arrest you? It's your choice.
You know. You can't take this TV.
Okay, listen, you want him to take the TV?
I don't want anyone to take my TV.
This is my TV. It was brought to me by the sleep paralysis
demons and they gave it to me in the night time
and they dropped shit and they touched my head
sometimes.
They touched your head sometimes?
By the way, can I just tell you?
You are probably, I would say
probably the most handsome police officer I've ever seen.
You're aware that this is like another
dude here, right? Like I'm a person, dude.
I'm sorry, I just like
the outfit, the uniform.
I really appreciate that. My mother always told me
I look good in blue. You do look fantastic.
Thank you.
It's the blue.
Listen, maybe we should
grab a beer sometime. I would love that.
I would absolutely love going out for a beer.
Hey, where'd you put my phone?
It's in my hands, bro. You made me hold it for you, dude.
Listen,
here's the thing. I can either find you for
$300. Don't find me.
Okay, and I can say that maybe
I didn't see the TV. I don't know.
But listen, man, I'm going to take the TV
either way. Well, guess what, officer?
The TV
doesn't fucking work.
It doesn't work. So you broke it.
I didn't break it. You
stole the TV and you broke it.
I just wanted to watch a sports program on it and
it didn't work.
It works a little bit, dude.
It's just like kind of abstract, man.
You want me to hang this
on the wall and make it an abstract art
painting? I'm sorry, you're going to have to keep your hands off
the contraband.
Listen, I'm going to have to confiscate it.
We're taking it.
You go ahead and lift that up for me.
You expect me to pick up the freaking TV?
It's part of your community service.
Really?
Go ahead. Good luck.
Thank you, by the way. Thank you. Appreciate it.
By the way, like I've got to say before,
I've said it before again, probably the most handsome coffee
I've ever seen in my life. Can we not
address the fact that I'm like
I'm literally going like as fast
as I can here. Watch out for the couch.
Dude, we've got cables all over here.
This is a major safety
risk, dude. Like you care about safety.
You're a serial jaywalker.
Bro, there's no crosswalk in front of the library,
dude. What am I supposed to do?
Bring it up to city. Excuse me, I've got to get around you
for a sec.
Official police business, huh?
Yeah, official police business.
Dude, this is
ridiculous, bro. This is silly.
You get a load of that? Who is
Sleed Peralis?
I've never heard of that before, dude.
This guy.
Put the TV down for a sec.
Go have a
good day. Go ahead and take it. I'm not paying you
fine. You can take it. I don't know if you've heard of Tic-Tac
or whatever. Keep going. Don't TikTok me.
You're going to TikTok me fine.
Are you TikToking? Are you
TikToking now? Yeah, I think so.
I don't know how it works.
There. Fucking leave, please.
Alright. Alright. And I'm the one
in handcuffs, bro? I'm the one
getting arrested? You made me watch that.
I'm the one fricking in handcuffs, bro?
Okay.
This is ridiculous, dude. How far are we
carrying this, man? Another couple miles.
Another couple miles, bro, dude.
Now I don't have TV. And I
smell so awful
to a point where it's
disgusting people. And now
why would you get a stolen TV?
Why? You had so many
options. Why pick a stolen piece of merchandise?
And I plugged it in. It didn't even
work. Unbelievable.
Oh shit, I'm still
streaming.
Hey, if anybody's still here.
Hey.
So I just said, hey,
everybody, what's going on? I just
had a little bit of thing going on. I had my TV worked on.
I had a handyman come. And, you know,
I was trying to get like an
Ultra HD screen
put into the wall. Because, you know what I mean?
I got money. I got a lot of it. So
Ultra HD screen going into the wall back there.
Right in front of the kitchen, too.
I've got money, you know. I've got money.
I've got...
Mute the stream. Muted. I'll be right back.
Oy yi yi.
What a pain in the ass.
I gotta... I gotta move.
This neighborhood is fucked.
This is the most ridiculous neighborhood I've ever...
What an insane neighborhood.
It's eight. I mean, I thought I was
a weird guy. Do I belong
here or should I leave here as fast as I can?
Right, right, right, right, right,
right, right, right. Hey, everybody,
I'm back. I gotta go.
I know you've only gotten about four minutes of
content and like a sixty
two minute BRB screen.
But, you know,
I just... I'm working on some stuff.
Make sure to check out tomorrow.
There's gonna be a dollhouse stream tomorrow.
I will check it out for you. We got
a lot of work done on it. A lot of people were involved.
It's gonna be a lot of fun.
So I'll give you guys a link now.
I'll give you the link. Just send it
it while you're here already, so that's fine.
And I'll see you guys tomorrow for the dollhouse stream.
And goodbye.
Play the outro.
There it is. Okay.
I fucking hate doing
this. I hate streaming. I fucking
can't wait till I'm done. Somebody calling?
Hello?
This is Jason from Warranty
Services, Car Parts, Extended
Warranty Vehicle Offerings, USA
LLC. We've been trying
to reach you for a while now about your vehicle's
extended warranty and haven't gotten
a response. We wanted to give you a couple
maybe two, three, four
dozen final warranty calls
just as a courtesy to let you
know that we're trying
to get you to purchase this from us.
And since we haven't heard from you, we're just
gonna keep calling until you talk
to us. Press 2 if you'd like
us to pretend to put you on our do not
call list and press anything
else to talk to a specialist
right now. That's 2.
Owie.
I got all day, man.
2. Do I have to say 2?
Just 2. Hang on.
Does that shit work on people?
I don't understand. Car
warranty? I don't have a car.
I literally don't have a car. I don't
own a car. How would a car get here?
I was just in there
and I didn't go to the bathroom.
This place is a mess.
Disaster. TV's gone.
My friends think I'm a
weirdo. I barely have
anybody I can fucking hang out with.
What an absolute disaster this has
been. What I'm gonna need is I'm gonna need the audience
to give me some more volume.
That's what I'm gonna need. I'm getting more volume.
I need the audience to give me volume
to let me know what they want to do.
I thought this was gonna be easy.
I thought this was gonna be simple. Thought I was gonna
be able to live here uninterrupted,
undisturbed. That I'd be taken
care of by six
hundred million people watching.
There's six hundred million people here.
You're making me look bad.
I do love this though. It's a good touch.
Imagine streaming and having somebody
sit in here with you in the bathroom.
Alright, finally. I'm hungry.
Get this out of the way.
I'm trying like an extension
cord. For the
TV that I can't use, that's great.
What do we got? We got
beer that people keep drinking.
You know what? I think I'm gonna go for a slice
of bread. Or a cookie
sandwich.
Don't put plastic on a stove, kids.
Is there blood on this? No.
Ah.
You wanna see how dirty these are over the last like three
or four hours? Look at this.
It's like I literally was walking around in mud.
These are white.
Ugh. I do have to go to the bathroom.
And I'm
tired. Very tired.
Can I sleep in the bed tonight
or are we gonna make me pass out on the toilet while I
take a shit and then pass out and slash my head on the
ground? Can we make this a normal day?
Huh? Huh?
Normal day.
Normal day. Bar's
full. I wanna go to bed.
I wanna pee and then I wanna go to bed.
Can we make that happen, please?
Can we? I'm trying so hard to not
have my arms go up because I don't want to see my armpit hairs.
Because that, like somebody's gonna
screenshot it and like keep it.
I don't want you to have that.
I don't want to go to that room. All I have in my
third room is
like stools
in a bed. I mean the
organs out there and that's pretty cool. I'm gonna
go back and play that. But like
give me something, give me a fun
toy. I'll take a second
bathroom. I don't think
that's even possible. Thank God.
This bed smells like cheez-its.
I didn't eat cheez-its in here.
Okay, alright.
Alright, I need two shadows in here.
Oh yeah, that's a bad dream
for Joyma.
Hey boys, yeah, get him up, get him up.
He's having a bad dream. Ain't
that right, big boy?
Oh, you're all alone.
All alone in your house.
What, you missed that maid? You missed
that cute maid from the other day?
Yeah, get him up.
Get him up.
Oh, what's that? When's the last time
you showered, big boy?
Oh yeah.
Okay, come on. Yeah, that's it.
Get him up. Get him in the bathroom.
Oh, I can smell him from here.
Come on, both
of you. I'm not gonna get my
hands dirty. There we go. Come on.
Yeah.
Big boy Joyma.
Oh, what's this?
Your game station?
Oh, take a look at that.
I can smell it from
here. What's that,
dude? You gotta go to the bathroom,
big guy.
Looks to me like you gotta go to the bathroom.
Someone's not been taking care of their needs, boss.
Get him on the
toilet. Yeah, that's
it. Yeah.
Then Jerma
poops himself.
He poops himself in front of everybody.
No, no, I didn't poop my pants in front of everybody.
And then a cowboy comes out of the shower.
What if you poop yourself,
don't you?
That'd be embarrassing to poop yourself in front of
so many people.
And the cowboy's got a sword.
Yeah.
Poop yourself. You better keep
pooping yourself there, boy. And then he starts
streaming.
Hey, everybody, it's me,
Jerma.
Are you live pooping yourself? No. Yeah, you
are.
You are.
You're pooping yourself on television.
Oh, yeah.
I bet you like that, big boy.
I'm about to go live.
That's a T.O.S. violation.
What can go wrong? And he gets up again.
I hear his stomach growling. Get up.
He's just catching the 4th grade class.
Get him up and then go to the
kitchen. And he doesn't wash his
hands either. Oh, disgusting.
I wash my hands every time. Yeah,
sure you do, pal.
No!
No, I didn't shit
myself!
No!
I'm a good boy!
Make the sandwich when you want it.
It's your dream, big guy, to make the sandwich.
Oh, no.
Make the sandwich when you want it.
You don't have way too much room for it.
You did, you're a little woke up.
Oh, man.
Huh?
What the fuck?
What am I doing in here?
Oh my god. You know, when you
have a dream, you ever have a dream
where you, and you have it,
you have it, you have it, you have it, you have it, when you have it,
you have it, when you have a dream, you have it, when you have it,
and you had it. I feel
awful. Why is this stuff all over here?
I had this dream, I like,
I had this fourth grade teacher,
and I like
pooped my pants in the class, but whatever.
You guys don't know that, you don't need to know that.
Nobody needs to know that here. But pretty much
the end of the story is I had a bad dream about like how
people like laughed at me, thought I was stupid, and like
whatever.
What a fucking joke.
Why is all my stuff everywhere?
Why is my stuff everywhere?
Why am I holding two pieces of bread?
Ay yi yi.
Ugh.
That was very weird.
That was
very weird.
That was, that was,
ugh. I want to go play
the organ. At least I'll have some fun.
Ugh.
Do I have any mail? I'm the, I gotta get
rid of this.
Hope you didn't see that on camera.
What's in the mail?
It got
rain.
What's in the mail?
There's nothing in the mailbox.
I don't see anything in this mailbox.
There was no mail. I'm doing this.
Play
public
domain
music?
Play public domain music?
Is that what they said?
Um, okay.
Play
public domain music?
Maybe take a shower now.
Oh, I, that's fucking
water.
Real shower.
Oh, I think I have my tetanus shot.
Hey, there we go.
Nice and clean.
Ready to take on the day.
It's a centralized location.
Nope.
Puh, puh.
German's house.
Ah, very, very good.
Oh, very, very good.
Oh, gotta get those bars green.
Very green.
Lime green.
Citrus green.
Pistachio green.
Uh, what else is green?
Toad green.
Frog green.
Green green.
Grass green.
Take a long one today.
Ugh, I'm letting it hit me directly in the chest.
I like turn the water up like kinda high,
and then it just hits me directly in the chest
and it feels so good.
I come up with like a red, burnt chest, but I love it.
What the, hello?
Hello?
What are you doing?
Mr. Germa.
Hey, hey, what are you doing here?
What are you doing?
Look, Wig.
Yeah, no, I'm your maid.
You didn't even ask my name once.
Who is it?
Oh, it's the maid.
What are you just calling out, maids?
Is this your fiance?
I'm in the shower, please.
Gosh, oh, please, I'm so embarrassed.
I'm in the shower.
All right, I'll go to your bedroom, then.
I'll go to your bedroom.
What the hell are you doing?
You said come back every few days.
I did, but I, look, it's been a few days.
Okay, all right, just do what you think.
The name's Amelia.
It's Amelia.
Amelia, okay, Amelia, thank you.
I appreciate it, but I need to come out of the shower now.
I need to come out of the shower now.
Who needs this many stools?
All right, well, first I'm just gonna clean the,
I need to move this.
What was that?
Perhaps steps.
Okay, that looks good.
That makes sense.
I gotta move this stuff out of my,
Amelia will take care of that.
I don't have to worry about that.
Sir, can I do the bathroom?
I'm not, I'm not in the bathroom anymore.
I don't think, I don't think,
I'm no longer in the bathroom.
Perfect, I'll just stay out of your way.
Good.
You dropped this.
Thank you so much.
Yes, you looking for an outlet?
Oh, yeah, I think there's,
I have no idea where one is.
I think there's one outlet in the whole house.
There's one right here, sir, thank you.
You got it?
Yeah, I got it, I got it.
That's a beautiful vacuum cleaner.
A lot of bathroom usage for you today, sir.
Almost as beautiful as you.
What?
That vacuum is almost as beautiful as you are.
I mean it.
What is it, what is that?
It's the sweetest thing I've heard all week.
Heck you.
Can I get a hug?
Yes, sure.
Absolutely, come here.
Thank you, there you are.
You need to go to the bathroom, it's right here.
Thank you for telling me that.
Yes, of course, absolutely.
And you know that I mean it.
I keep getting this fucking huge migraine.
And I feel like somebody's telling me
I'm being controlled by something.
What the fuck?
I mean, they look good, they do.
They look good.
Everything okay in here?
Yeah, no, everything's great in here.
Sorry, you might know I'm not that used to cleaning.
Yep.
Up stuff.
Okay.
Um, what's the problem?
What's the problem?
Yeah, it's a computer, you can just move it out of the way.
I'm unsure how to clean it, sir.
Well just push it out of the way
and you can just dust it or something.
Yeah, I'll be in here, you got it.
You're fine.
Great, I'll just move it out of the way.
Oh, I like what they did with this.
All right, I gotta go to work.
Oh, that's not too loud, is it?
No, it's fine, I gotta go to work.
I'll see you later, have a good time.
All right, thank you.
Again, I want, and this might be a little neurotic,
but I like vertical lines, not horizontal, okay?
You like vertical lines, not horizontal?
Like vertical lines, not horizontal.
You get a couch in the middle of your living room,
you use the computer in your bathroom.
I woke up and came here
and there was a piece of toilet paper on the floor.
We prefer vertical lines.
You can do horizontal if you want.
I would hope.
Yeah.
You can do horizontal.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
Vertical lines.
Guys, a psycho.
Not very much slack left, by the way.
Thank God for Uncle Ted,
because otherwise I would have no fucking money.
See you later.
Goodbye.
That was a good day.
I feel pretty good about that day.
Hungry, thirsty, ready, but I made some money.
That's good, right?
Still kind of a mess out there.
I really wish the, I really wish.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
Goodbye, yep, see you later.
I didn't press it.
I gotta get that doorbell looked at.
I need like an electrician.
Okay.
Why is this open?
It looks pretty clean in here.
Not bad.
I mean, it could be a little better, but whatever.
Hi.
How dare you just walk in when I'm cleaning?
The shoes are in the bed.
What?
You had your shoes on in the-
I took them off.
I'm not a psycho.
I don't sleep with my shoes on.
But you took your shoes off and the shoes were
in the bed with you.
Why were they not like on the side of the bed?
Because I was cleaning the bed
and I put them on the side of the bed.
You weren't here for that.
Anyway, it took me a little bit longer today,
so it's gonna be 300.
Okay.
Is that because you slept in the room
or is that because you do-
You don't talk to me like that.
No, I was, Amelia, it was-
No, it's fine.
I was just saying, like I come from work
and you're in bed.
I picked up a piece of toilet paper with poop on it,
but I'm the one to blame.
There's been more than one person here.
There's been at least four people here.
I found a pair of pants with poop on it.
Did you poop yourself?
I'm wearing the same pants I was.
Five days ago.
That's even more concerning.
And by the way, I may have pooped my pants,
but goodness gracious, I mean, you look great.
And I think that you and I could probably
maybe go out sometime.
Well, I don't know.
I'll see what I'm doing tomorrow.
Let's call it 300 and I'll be on my way.
Sure, $300.
Great.
Hey, it's been great.
It's been fantastic.
We should go out sometime.
You wanna go out sometime?
Well, I just said I might be free tomorrow.
Like, yeah, but like I got a wild schedule.
Can I confirm it?
Sure.
Okay.
I don't think I wanna shake your hand
after you said you pooped yourself.
How about this one?
Great.
Yeah!
Woohoo!
Looks like we got a date.
You know, there are three to four options
when you get a choice.
You know, there's a few different things
you can choose from each time.
Not sure you're aware of that at this point.
I feel pretty good.
Although I'm very hungry.
Oh!
Can I eat something?
What are you gonna do?
I saw mine.
That's the first time I've looked at chat
in like four plus hours or so.
I saw minus twos.
Thank you.
Look at the same loaf of bread every time.
This bread has lasted a long time.
I hope my hands are really clean.
I've been cleaning them.
I'm actually glad I'm wearing these gloves
because I mean, they're just, they're absolutely gross,
but I really am happy I have them on.
I have an apple too.
Why would I not eat the apple?
I wanna hang out in here.
Ah!
I'm gonna sit down.
God!
You work all day.
You come back.
You just wanna sit on your bed.
Why am I sleeping in here?
I could have paid you hundreds of dollars
for just sleeping in the bed.
Like, I wonder how, I was gone for six and a half hours.
I bet you they were sleeping in this bed for four.
What?
I'm not gonna, I'm not smelling anything.
In fact, I want this bed fucking removed from the house.
All right, let's do some Twitch TV streaming.
Ah, every time.
Okay, let's go.
Get these, I gotta get at least one off, right?
Okay, let's go live.
So we're gonna do some Germacraft, some Minecraft.
Why don't we call this episode one.
Live Germacraft.
And let's go live.
Hey, what's going on, everybody?
Jerma here with episode one of Germacraft.
You know, of course, the series where I play Minecraft.
And it's gonna be really fun.
There's gonna be a lot of trials, a lot of triumphs,
a lot of fails.
And, uh, I don't know, that was a funny dream.
Ah, so, uh, by the way,
before I turn the stream off, everybody,
I just wanted to say, um,
if you go to germa985.com,
we've got merchandise for you, we've got posters for you,
we've got all kinds of things you can get,
and some of them might even be signed, too.
Oh, sorry, I'm talking to you guys, too.
Have a good day.
I'm not even online.
The stream's been off for like the last three hours.
I'm gonna be banned for two days.
Am I gonna get permanently banned from Twitch
if I do that again?
Just don't do that again.
I'm actually might not be able to stream again.
If you want, like, income, don't do that.
So that's what I heard.
Ah, cool, a bunk bed!
Oh!
It's another mystery box!
Oh my goodness, I wonder what's in this one.
God, you give people a loot box option,
and that's what they're gonna pick,
like, three out of 10 times,
which would be 30%, which is not that much.
I mean, like, five out of 10, which would be 50.
How about let's go eight out of 10?
You couldn't have put anything else in there, in here.
You couldn't have put, like, rubber duckies or something.
It's three more stools?
This is the biggest bait ever.
You're just, people would probably be pissed.
Okay, I'm, uh, all right.
Well, let's get this out of the way.
I heard an explosion in this room.
This bed is, I'm moving this.
Get this out of the way.
I'm putting this over here.
Let me at least get this correct here.
Decorate?
Yeah, I can do that.
By the way, though, I do have to pee,
so I would do that soon.
Um, sure, can I get rid of the box part of the decoration?
Decorate the, where would I want the bed?
I definitely don't want the bed in front of the door.
That would be a pain in the ass.
Let's go with over here.
Probably against the wall.
I want it against the wall.
That makes more sense to me.
That looks good.
Why would you have a bed, like, over here?
I like that.
It's a twin bed.
I don't have to worry about the other side.
Who cares?
All right, then, what about the mystery box?
We can put that in the corner.
And then I'll put the, um, put these in the,
I don't know, what am I supposed to do with these?
What a shitty bedroom.
This looks like I'm still moving into this house.
How about two over there, and so over here.
Okay, good.
I have to pee real bad, like, right now.
Um, how about on top of the mystery box?
It's a beautiful day outside.
Beautiful day.
I want one of these next to the bed
so I can put my legs over.
That makes sense to me.
There couldn't have been anything else in that box.
Anything else.
I don't know what to do with these.
I don't even have a shelf to put anything on.
That's there, that's, that can just stay there.
I don't, I don't care.
That's fine.
That can stay.
How does it look?
You like it?
What do you think?
Thank you.
Yes, yes, yes.
This is nice, 985.
This is a wonderful, wonderful place.
Thank you for letting me be, I appreciate it.
Do you think we should try?
I don't see why we shouldn't.
I think it'll make sense.
Oh, it's even in tune.
Oh, this is perfect.
Wonderful.
Why don't we start off with some 985?
We'll practice 985.
985.
That sounds good, let's do that.
I'm trying something new.
Oh, all right, go ahead.
Ready?
Or get outside.
God our father.
He's our daddy.
He's our friend.
I don't know why the organs blink.
Father, not daddy.
Sorry about that.
I'm sorry about that.
Excuse me.
Oh, Edna, how are you?
I'm doing great.
Who are you?
Jerma, you were here a few days ago?
Oh, okay.
You were here last week?
Oh, yes.
Jerma, we heard you had this wonderful organ.
Yes.
I heard how impressive your organ was,
and I just wanted to come over and play with your organ,
with my choir, of course, from church.
Okay. Bless you.
Bless you.
Bless you, too.
If you wanna join in.
Would you like to join us?
I don't, I wouldn't.
Why don't you just stick around and see what happens.
Step on over with them, that'll be great.
Your organ is so big, I'll have to use two hands.
Here we go.
You'll have to use two hands to play an organ.
Yes, okay.
I don't think you play an organ with one hand.
It's not like a flute.
Over here?
Yeah.
All right, let's take it from the top.
From the top, Edna?
From the top.
From the top of where?
You'll figure it out.
What page are we on?
Song 985.
God came down from the land.
And he took us all by the hand.
And then we started.
And then he started dancing.
And then we started dancing.
He's got the spirit.
Remix.
But God came down to the land in the land.
God came down to the land in the land.
I can't believe what's happening right now.
Get that migraine again.
Oh, okay, let's.
And he came down to the.
Why don't you lead us in it?
And he came down to the land.
And he,
he ate, he brought wine and sand.
And he brought wine and sand.
And then he left my front yard.
They went to the fridge.
He got himself a nice big tub of lard.
And went to the fridge and got a big tub of lard.
I'm gonna get, get, get, get, get you drunk.
Get you all drunk.
On God's love.
What the fuck is happening?
Excellent, excellent, my children.
God bless you all.
Is he done?
Is he done singing with you?
Yeah, I think so.
Get you drunk.
We could ask.
That was beautiful.
Get back.
But that's my organ
and I'd like for you all to leave.
Well, we would like our book back.
Unless you, of course, would like to study on your own.
We'll save it for you at the church
and you can come sing with us any time.
Okay.
All right, wonderful.
Thank you.
Bless you.
See you on Sunday.
Thank you, please actually do that a few times
because there's been a lot of fucking weirdos here.
Bye now, bye now.
I'm sorry.
Have a great day.
All right, now I don't want to hear them any more.
But wait, wait a minute.
Wait a second.
Hey, wait, wait a minute.
Wait, I really, I want that book.
I want that book.
I think the book.
Can I have one of those books?
Yes, sir.
Thank you so much.
I'd love one of these books.
Can I keep it?
Yes, you may.
And I can have it.
You probably should.
Yeah, what passage should I read from
to get rid of bears, people that I don't want in the house?
Jeremiah 985 is actually my favorite chapter.
Okay.
Okay, yeah.
All right.
Here.
I'll put it in the mailbox.
Yes, yes, probably good.
He'll find it.
And he'll find his way home.
Yes, we have.
Good job, sister.
Very good.
Hope they're still there.
Really hope they're still here.
What an embarrassment.
Don't play this too loud because they'll come back.
I'm fucking hungry.
I'm tired and I have not showered.
You hear that?
Thank you.
How does she not know who I am?
She's been here like, she was here like fucking a week ago.
That's over budget of farting.
That's definitely over fart budget.
Ah, better.
Thank goodness.
I brush my teeth every time I get in the shower, every time.
Saves like two minutes each day.
That's too over budget.
That's too many.
I know it's fun to do that,
but no, I know it's really,
you don't just get them all out of your system right now.
I'll shit in the shower.
Get them out of your system.
All right.
You need a lot of characters in your time,
but character development
and internal characterization of yourself
is very important.
The more you think about who you are as a person
and what you do, the deeds you do,
that's how you can shape yourself as a person.
Or if you want to know,
fill words to make yourself sound intelligent.
Oh, should I have a date?
I have a date with a maid.
Fuck.
Right now?
I don't want to bail on Amelia.
That would be a mistake.
I'm just so tired.
No, they'll, they'll, they'll understand.
They'll understand.
It's fine.
This is too comfy.
Another time, another time.
I'll just, I'll text them or something.
I'll just let them know.
I'll just text them.
Kind of comfy, but what did I miss?
Oh, I had a date.
It's okay.
Oh, my back hurts.
My knee.
You can't sleep sitting down.
Not bad.
I felt worse.
Okay.
Had a bed already.
Hungry.
This is not very stable, by the way.
I'm not sure I can sleep on this.
I already had a bed.
Is that a bed sandwich?
That's all right.
I had a better bed in my dorm room in college than this.
I'm hungry.
Can I make some food, please?
Am I making something to eat?
I'm so hungry.
I am starving.
Does it matter?
Can I eat?
I don't want to eat bread for a seventh time.
I really don't.
Here, you know what?
We're doing hot dogs.
What do I got?
Do I have hot dogs?
No.
We're doing butter and eggs.
My favorite.
That was very loud.
This.
Ow.
Not bad.
Another few minutes.
Another 30 seconds or so.
Should be ready to eat.
Here we are.
Need another cup.
Oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops.
Oops, oops.
Oh shit.
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God,
oh my God, oh my God, what do I do?
What do I do?
What do I do, what do I do, what do I do?
What do I do, what do I do?
Ah, ah.
Fire, it's a fire.
Do I have anything?
Do I have any?
Hold on, wait, wait, wait.
I think I have something.
Give me this.
Fuck.
Oh, it's all right, it's all right, it's all right.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
This.
What the fuck?
Oh shit.
Oh.
Oh no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Holy shit.
Get out of here! Get out of here, you little bastard! Get out of here, you little bastard!
Shit! No, fuck! No, no, no, no, no, no, no! No! Stay down there, you motherfucker!
Damn it! This thing's fucking jammed!
Ah, fuck, whatever, okay, it's alright, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
It's alright, everything's gonna be fine, everything's gonna be fine.
Everything's gonna be just fine. Everything's gonna be fine. Everything's gonna be, come here, come here.
Shit! I can't fucking hit him!
This thing! What are you doing?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Ah! Someone's at the door! Someone's at the door!
I can't fight this motherfucker! You're a big fire, I don't know if I can do this!
Alright, I'm coming at you!
No, no, no, no, no, no, I don't wanna fight him, he's huge! He's huge, he's a huge guy, he's a huge fire!
Steve, keep waving, ah, fuck!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Ah, shit! No!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!