Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary and tonight I'm gonna be playing as... I don't know. I have no idea. It's either gonna be Scout or Sniper. That's what I've narrowed it down to.
So whatever you see on the screen, that's what's on the screen. But this video is kinda gonna be a casual commentary. I'm gonna talk a little bit about what I'm doing this week and how I'm kinda going away for a little bit and how July is gonna be incredibly hectic and so on.
So just right off the bat here, I'm gonna be going to San Francisco tomorrow. I'm gonna be getting on a plane tomorrow night to go check out the new Magica game. I actually got invited by Paradox to go check out Magica Wizard Wars, which is kinda like Magica 2.
And that's awesome. I'm flattered and honored that they would want me to come check the game out and go see the game and I'm gonna be meeting a few other YouTubers there. It's probably gonna be a good time.
But a lot of you guys that travel a lot will be able to relate to this. When you get on an airplane and it's a long flight, this flight is gonna be like six hours long or six and a half hours or something.
It sucks real bad, especially when you have to leave the next day. I'm only gonna be there for one and a half days. So I'm landing the plane, getting off in San Francisco, and getting on another plane less than 24 hours later for another six and a half hour plane ride.
So that really sucks. It really screws with your brain. And my sleep schedule is probably gonna be all screwed up again because I'm doing a red eye on the way back. And if you don't know what a red eye is, it's titled pretty ironically because it's an overnight plane ride.
It starts at like 11 PM and goes to like 10 AM the next morning or something. So it's really a rack on the brain. But that's not to say that I'm not excited for this trip. I really can't wait.
I haven't really been talking about it too much because I wanted to make sure it was like a legitimate thing and not just some random person in email going, hey, come to San Francisco and have fun. I don't worry. I won't capture you. It's not that.
So that's what I'm doing tomorrow into the next day or two. And then after that, I'm going to be going to North Carolina like I've talked before about my sister and having a baby and doing all kinds of stuff down there.
And then in August, I'm getting on another plane and going to PAX Prime. So I'm going to be all over the place in the next two months. This summertime is like busy be German summertime. And I'm happy about it.
I like having things to do, things to look forward to. And when you stay busy, when you're always doing something, you're always busy, that's when you really get a lot of shit done.
And that's like a advice tip, like kind of one on one for life. I guess is if you can keep yourself busy, really doesn't matter what it is. You just feel better about everything. Everything just kind of makes more sense when you are the busy you are as crazy as that sounds.
People that are always busy. You have this like image in your head of, oh, that guy's busy all the time. He must like to be so stressed and he must be so like, oh, where's my papers? Where am I? God, what happened next Tuesday?
Like, no, but but it's, it's kind of like that. But at the same time, you feel good because you're doing things, you're actually getting some stuff done. And you just feel great. It just makes you feel great when you accomplish stuff like when even if it's like the most mundane, simple thing.
You can sit there and you go, you know what? All right, I did. I was busy. I did this and it's done. And now I feel good. Like that's the connection I'm making the endorphin release in your brain for accomplishing something.
Now, I guess we'll move on from that. I just want to let you guys know, I'm not going to be here for a couple days. I have something scheduled to go up in the next couple days. So don't worry, there will be videos on this channel. But if you're like looking for me, like I'm not going to be here. Like I'm not going to be like sitting at my desk and able to answer questions or something like that. But I actually still do owe hats to people. So if you were one of the people that got selected in my last crate unboxing video, yes, those hats are coming. I just like I said, I've been really busy the last few days.
So don't worry, you are going to get your hat. I will contact you. Don't worry, you'll be fine. And to wrap this video up, we'll talk about some Team Fortress 2 a little bit here. I heard I've seen and I've experienced the summer appetizer crates. That's awesome. I can't wait for the new actual like main course crates in the main course update.
And they're doing all kinds of things. They're fixing exploits on maps. They're added to new community maps to the actual official valve rotation. So it's awesome to see this and I can't wait to see what the hell they're going to do for the actual summer update.
I really hope we're going to get some new weapons. Hope we get some new man versus machine stuff. I hope they blow everybody out of the water with this big update they've been hinting at on the blog post the last couple little mini updates.
So I'm excited. You should be excited. We're all excited. I scream you scream we all scream for speed cream. So that's going to wrap up the video guys. Thank you all so much for watching. Really do appreciate it.
Just a quick little casual commentary talking about where I'm going, what I'm doing and sort of little update for you guys. And that's going to wrap it up like I said, and I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.