Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Hitman Absolution.
Well, not really Hitman Absolution. Hitman Absolution does not come out for another couple weeks,
but this is the pre-order mission you get if you pre-order the game. So I guess this is a sniper challenge.
I have to kill this guy right here and...
Should I just shoot him right now?
Oh my god!
Dude, did I just beat the mission immediately?
I'm just going absolutely crazy. I haven't even introduced the video.
I haven't even introduced the video and I killed the guy.
Dude, why did I do that?
Oh my word, should I not have done that?
Let's see if I can even complete this.
Dude, I blew that guy's brains out.
Oh, get smashed.
All these people freaking out.
Look, it's like somebody dropped a grenade at the party. Everyone's like running around.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. God evacuated. I gotta find any of the gods.
Alright, well anyways, I'm really excited for Hitman Absolution.
If you can tell.
And...
Damn it.
Let's just not shoot into the crowd.
Oh, wait.
There he is right there.
Oh, come on.
You bastard.
Oh, he's not getting in that helicopter.
I will make sure he does not get in that helicopter.
I will put a bullet in between his eyes.
Just like this guy right here.
Slow time down and...
No, I missed.
Oh, that's a times two baby.
Wait, wait, wait. Where is he?
There he is, there he is. Look at this guy.
Please don't kill me.
No, he's gonna get away.
He's gonna get away.
No, I gotta do the last ditch effort.
No, no, we evacuated.
Alright, let's try this again.
Right in his face.
This next guy is gonna be second in line to die.
Get him right in his shoulder blade.
Oh, somebody saw that.
I gotta be careful here.
Let me reload this damn thing.
Let's go 47. Get your game on.
This guy down here. I don't wanna hit the window.
What? What?
Hey, what happened to the window behind me?
It just like exploded.
Hey, did I insta-die?
I think I should be in the clear though.
Now I'm gonna take my time here.
Because every time I kill somebody, like this guy over here,
everybody freaks out.
Is there somebody like on the roof? Oh, there is.
Is this a bodyguard?
What was that guy doing?
That guy was putting his hands on his waist like
I am a superhero.
You got killed, man.
Is there like a, what?
Is that a bodyguard up there?
Are you serious?
What? How am I supposed to hit this guy?
Oh, this guy.
That's a long fall.
That's a long fall. He's still going.
Imagine looking over and seeing that.
Okay.
Wow, that took like 15 seconds
for that bullet to hit that guy.
I only got 12 minutes here.
I gotta be sly.
Anybody else out here? Is anybody gonna see me shoot this guy?
I'm going for this guy right now.
Right in his chest.
Load, reload.
Exposed? What do you mean exposed?
I gotta kill this guy right here.
I'm gonna be such a bad shot though.
Oh, bang.
I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
How did I get exposed?
Who is it?
Who's placing a phone call?
Oh, this guy right here is like looking for me.
Get shot in the face, dude.
What, what, what, what, what, what, what is he,
where's he making the phone call?
Hey, you're not gonna find me. Where is that guy shooting?
Hey, bro, I'm over here to your right.
I'm not like over there, like over this way.
Oh, there he is. Oh, he's about to make the phone call
aka run. Oh, he's gonna get
smashed.
Right in his side.
You're dead, man.
Oh, hold on, I gotta get this guy. Boink.
Man, getting headshots. You gotta have some skill shots
to hit fellas. Oh, there goes the whole
party. At least I killed the target.
Right in his back. Moving kill streak.
Nice. Oh, let me get them all.
See ya. Right in your glasses.
Oh, brutal.
Oh, guard evacuated. What? Where's there another guard?
Down here? I only have three more left.
I don't know where any of them are.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. Right in his forehead.
Go ahead. See ya. See ya.
Any more? Any more?
Oh, cowboy John apparently is
like still like hanging out doing karate moves.
Oh, boy.
No, those are bartenders.
There's only one guard left. Where the hell is he?
Oh, I can hold.
I can use like instinct. I have like
super powers. Ooh.
Oh, damn. This guy's, oh, this guy's
gonna hit right in his face.
Right here. Ready? Here it is.
Oh, baby. Yeah.
Hey, I did it.
Nice.
Well, I wonder what kind of score I got. I didn't do that well.
Silent Assassin? No, I didn't.
I got, oh, I unlocked something
for Hitman Absolution. Increased the
stability on sniper rifles. Oh, that's
gonna be a good thing to have.
But yeah, thanks so much for watching guys.
Really do appreciate it. I am so excited
for Hitman Absolution, which
launches in less than two weeks. It's gonna be
so much fun. You're gonna see a lot of content of that game
on this channel. So stay tuned for
that, guys. And again, if you pre-order
Hitman. I know this is somewhat old
content. It came out a while back.
But if you pre-order Hitman right now, you're gonna be able to get
this and have some fun with it.
So I'll see you guys all next time. And of course,
take care, everybody.