Hey, how's everybody doing? Early today. Very early. I wasn't anticipating being this early, but
sometimes things happen and you have to solve them. Uh, Otto has an appointment today. He has some
like kind of weird skin itching issues and it's getting to the point where it's been like a
couple days and I really I gotta get him in to get seen. So he's okay. He's fine. There's
nothing wrong with him. He's just, I don't know if it's the dry Vegas air or something or the
Vegas weather or something, but he needs to, I gotta get him checked out. So, um, gonna start
early. Stream for about five hours or so. Me and Ster are gonna play Deep Rock Galactic.
It is a left for dead Minecraft game. That's right. It's a lot. I don't know what this
game actually is. I did the tutorial and we're in a lobby together right now. Uh,
italics may join us in like an hour or so and we'll go for about four or five hours and then
I gotta take Otto to the vet and then tomorrow we're gonna do the movies. So you'll see the
movies tomorrow. Hopefully with some, uh, mods installed and that's the plan. So let me see if
he's, uh, here. You there? I'm not sure if he's around yet. Hey, I don't, I really don't
want to raise my voice. I will if I have to. I think he's got me muted. Let me move
this out of the way. Okay. Hey look. So this is, uh, Deep Rock Galactic. This is the
lobby system and there is, um, let's see if we can get his attention. How do I, like,
how do I get his attention? Did I just spit on him? Oh, hello. Hey there. Yeah, I'm here.
Hey, sorry. I was trying to, like, get your attention. Oh, I accidentally had to turn down.
Well, that was kind of funny. Um, so what, what's the, uh, where do we go? What's the
plan? I think you might be lagging a little. Yeah, I'm lagging. Uh, you go to the mission
terminal. Yeah. And you select the mission. Well, you're the party leader so I think you
should do it first. Because I really don't, I don't know how, like, where to go.
I mean, either. I haven't played in a while. Yeah. Um, what's that? That looks like a,
uh, looks like my old intro up there. That's pretty funny. Yeah. It's, like,
kind of funny. Yeah. What, so what, what's the first mission? What we
countdown? All right, come. We're doing the, uh, do you have to strap in?
Yeah, you gotta strap in. Remember seatbelt. He reminds you. Uh, pretty good game so far.
What was, sorry, I was panicking. What'd you say? I was just having, you know,
sorry. No, you, you talk first. I, I talk, what? Oh, wait, no, sorry. I thought I was
talking over you. All right. So I'm playing as the, um, I, I'm playing as the, what's this,
the driller? How do I get my drill out? And you try your, your one or your two or your three or
your four. So I can't explain how this game works because I can't really do that good of
a job explaining it so you can do it. Um, listen to him. That goes down pretty far.
You go down through the tunnels, you find the resources we need. So we've got to extract 200
more kite. You've got to collect 10 fossils. That's a, that's what we got to do. And then
you got to come run all the way back up to this spot before the ship leaves. All right. Nice.
And I'm the light guy. Also there's all damage and you don't want to, you don't want to take
that. And usually in the starting area, you know, you got a couple of things to mind.
That's our bot. You got to put the minerals in the bot. You know, not that pretty good.
Oops. I, or are you just hanging out here?
You're going to get out of it. Help me. You're going to get out of it. Help me. Come on.
It's German star again. Let's go. That's it. Last long. I can't, I can't do that. I can't,
I can't. I'm sorry. That's not going to happen. We agreed to try and sound as boring
as possible and see how long we could do it, but there was a cliff. Hey, hey, hey,
turn around tutorial. I don't even know how to play the game. I'm teaching you. This is the,
this is the fossil. That's awesome. We need 10 of those. Why don't I get my little, uh,
bot? Oh, well I have to do, we don't have the bot, the bot is single player. So it's,
it's up to us. It's up to us. Well, I've got a flame thrower. That's pretty cool. How
do I get my, um, Ooh, I got my drill arms. How do I? Okay. I'm not, I'm not,
I'm actually not trying to fall on purpose. Like what's my travel ability?
I don't think the drill guy has one, but you can, you, you ever played red faction?
Yeah. That's what we're talking about. You just drill up and down. Oh, okay. That's somewhere.
If we had more people, like if we had any friends whatsoever, if I didn't like break
all ties with everybody and we would have other people be able to join us, then there's like a
zip line guy. Yeah. It's just too bad you've burnt every bridge you've ever had in your
life. Like we would maybe have some friends over there. That's health. So if you ever hurt
and you need health, that's what health is. Okay. So I need that now. All right. I'm not,
can I be honest with you for a second? That like wicked loud fake laugh that I did,
like I hurt myself. I wait, what was that? I have you. I've captured you.
I thought that was you doing that. No, that was a very good impression. Wait,
wait, wait, wait. What do you mean? You, why do you have me doing that?
Well, I'll see. I'm a soul taker now. That's what I do. Whenever I play with people is I,
I take their souls through voice clips.
That's gonna, I, that's not going to get old. No way. All right. Let's get this.
I wish I could just play that. I thought you were just playing back a clip of you laughing.
Oh, no, no. Oh, no, no, no, no. Don't use your drill on those. You just, you hold down space,
the mail. I space. Oh, no, nobody's a weirdo like you that has like fucking space bar.
Hey, watch out for the crystals. What they shoot lightning. Don't hit them.
Don't wait. Are you serious? You just avoid these. Just don't look at, don't look,
don't look, don't look. It's like the thing in the Minecraft. You don't look at it.
Otherwise it comes for you. I'm still freaking out by the fact that you have this like
the strange robot device that can capture me. That's not going to get old.
That's what I'm be saying. That I didn't say that he had, you know what? Like,
can I just, can I just say a couple of things and you just like, I'll just like play and
you can just like do a commentary. Okay. Okay. Give me the, I need them separately. Give me
an affirmative, like a yes. You got it. Okay. Now give me a negative. Nope.
You're not too sure anymore. Well, I don't get it. And I don't know anything you want.
Dude over here. Okay. That one is amazing. You can use that one at any time.
And hold on. I got the super light gun. Oh, wait, wrong, wrong one.
You can, you can, you can have like, I do. I'd be careful. Oh, I figured what the button is,
but the button to call the, the guy over to you is pretty important. Also this nitrate,
very important. We're going to need it. I'm sorry. I cannot pay attention right now.
You're a little bit distracted. I'm still freaking out. You just been waiting for
an opportunity to use this. I love how the, Hey, let's be quiet and not like make any references
or any jokes at all. The entire stream lasted five minutes and now I'm going to make Jerva say
fucking crazy shit over himself is now the new thing. So what? Okay. We need to extract
more kite. More kind. Yeah. That's what we're looking for. It's the light blue.
So should I keep throwing out these, um, yeah, he's pop. You have a whole bunch of
them and we're going to need to come back later. And then you can, you can, they stay on the ground
forever. Wait, I got this. They turn off so you can like follow where you've been.
Oh, yeah. Drill it baby. Up or down. Um, you got it. No, I thought I just said that.
I didn't say that. You thought that you said that, but you didn't say that. Yes. I thought
I just said that, but I didn't. I just heard myself say that. Which way do we go? Up or
down? We go, uh, we go straight. Okay. What about this, uh, egg sack? Try torch the egg sack. Um,
watch it. I don't know what these are actually. So the difficulties, what about the slugs?
I thought that was, I thought that was me as well. I thought that you just see that
your character yelling. That was me. You're freaking me out. Well, that's no, that's not
you. Okay. That's not you. Okay. I think I thought you like pitch shifted. Do you have
any mineral? Do I have any minerals? Yeah, I have some. Where, what do I see? I just
went through the ground. Where's my mineral count at the bottom of your screen? If you've
picked up anything, you got, you got to dump it in there. I don't have anything. Okay. You
have nothing. Okay. We're good. Okay. So, uh, up or down, up or down straight down. Okay.
This is more kite. Oh, here we go. So should I not be control clicking on this at all?
Uh, no, that doesn't collect it. And then we got, we got swarm incoming,
incoming swarm. You got it. No, I, why am I saying you got it? That's like the
me fake me saying that dude over here. So is there something I should be doing? Um,
we're just, we're just in a corner here. You know how, you know, left or dead,
the zombies all rush you. We're getting ready. We're bracing for impact.
What am I, what are my grenades? I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. You're
gonna have to throw one. So somebody clip that somebody clip him saying that right now. I gotta
do my own version of it. Get somebody clip him saying that and get, and give it to me.
Wait, which way? You got it. You got it. Up or down? I don't know. This is not a really
big swarm. This is like three. Up or down? Up or down? Is it friendly fire? Uh, yes,
I think it depends on difficulty. We're, we're just doing like a simple mission right now.
You know, just, you know, get our bearings. Yeah. Oh, now, now we got brought.
My grenades are like a slow field. Let's see what mine do.
I think you might have like the TNT big explosion. Uh, that's not exploding. It's an
axe. Oh, you have an axe. Well, they just had like a, uh, an update as well to what
grenades do. Pretty, pretty sick. Out of ammo. Flip that dickhead. That was really mean. Like,
it was like rude. I wasn't sure if that was you saying that or me making you say that.
What do we do about this? It's like roly poly. Uh, what is that? What the hell? I
have no idea. I've never seen it before. This thing's huge. Get it right in his teeth.
It's a brain bug. It kind of is a brain bug. You got it.
Um, this is okay. They probably warned us about this at some point, like 50 years ago.
Right now I'm like laughing at not me. I'm laughing at myself,
but it's not even me, but it was me earlier. I'm going to die. No, I'm not.
How are you, how are you doing that? What? I dug into the wall so I could stand in it.
I thought you said I could drill up. Whoa. Okay. That was fucking scary.
Well, you got, you got to drill like, uh, that was diagonal up. I mean, I was,
I thought I was doing that. Oh, like worms, fossils, fossils. We got fossils.
So let me test this out. So you're talking about like worms. So if I go like this,
what about you? Yeah. You can make like this. Cool. Um, I forgot the button. Hey,
hey, anybody here from Twitch chat? I need the mule right here. How do I,
I got to check the button. What do you need? We need to call in a supply drop for more ammo.
I forget the button. Uh, five. How do I know that? And you don't.
Yeah. How do you know that? Cause you just did the tutorial. See, I got, I can do it.
Should I do it too? No, only one of us can do it. This is ammo, I'm assuming. And you need,
uh, nitrous for this or whatever it is. That, okay. That scared me too. And I knew it was
coming. Should I just take them each side? No, leave those. Leave them. We need to collect,
uh, you see this red mineral up here? The red one? Yeah. That's what allows us to call that
supply drop in. So we can't, we don't just have them forever. So you're talking about
like that, right? The thing I'm mining right now. Red sugar. Yeah. You need like 90 or 80 of
these. Okay. Well you can like fly around. I have to like walk. I have to like drill
through the sky. Well, I'm sorry. You picked the driller. Well, that's your, you,
you collect them. I'll just be the guy that like hangs out and just watches me. I'll just
play the game. Yeah. Okay. Well, you already get, you know, you're already going up. It's
straight. We're going this way. Okay. Isn't there a map? Oh, there's, uh, there's a
four over here. It's tab probably M behind you, dude. Yeah, but you can handle it.
I don't know. Can I? Yeah, you can handle it. Look, so we're, we almost got,
what do we need? 200? Yeah. So what about other minerals? Is there, are there rare
minerals? Like, holy shit, I see gold or something. There, there are. Um, if you see
a whole bunch of like circles in a wall, kind of, kind of like this, actually. You
see this over here and you see what's going on up there. So should I drill in
there? That means, uh, I'm pretty sure that's one of them. It looks a little
different. Usually inside the wall here. This is where you need drill guy to go
in there and drill up into that wall. Monster, uh, monster spawner in there.
Okay. I see more. I see more. Yeah. Just keep digging into the, the circle spot.
Okay. Until you find the pearl. It's like, find the pearl. Uh, and then
come back. It's like, it's over here. All right. Hey, have you found it yet?
I don't know. Now I'm just going to let you talk for me. How about now?
Nope. Keep looking. Maybe it's below. It's, you know, it's somewhere around
here. You think you're going around in circles around it? Come on, drill guy.
I don't know. Nope. That's all I've got. Nope. You don't have a yes or don't you
have a dude come here? I have, uh, up or down. Down. Up or down. Down. It's
right in front of me. How do I get it? Oh, oh, well then, um, I got it. Oh,
now we've got to bring it back to the mule. You got it. Where's the mule
from here? Can I throw this? It should be funny. It's straight down. Just go
for it. Did I just give you the EXP? Yeah. I got all the experience from
that. No, you didn't. You're not going to level ever. I don't know.
The thing is people know the truth because I come through clean and crisp
and that comes through like not clean and crisp. All right. So I'm
looking at the map right now. These are rare materials too. They are
they? Buys more. Buys more. Yeah. Oh, that's cool. Point one buys more.
Yeah, you're going to need more than that. That's the fuel satellites
and the satellites. You can call, uh, call them down. Oh, that's
cool. All right. So what should we go from here? Let's open the map
that I knew about, but you didn't. Um, we go up, up or down,
up. Where are you? Well, I'm a loop bug over here. Is that like a
well, kill loop bug. Ooh. Where's my friend? I'm down. How can I
like tell you where I am? I'm like underneath you. I think there's
a yell button. Oh, there you are. Yes. Okay. Come on. Yeah. Let's
let's go like up, not down. I don't know. I mean, I can't
remember which one just went pretty good about it, but now I'm
so confused. What is that? That's not going to get all.
All right. Ooh, what's this? Gold. It's gold. We need gold.
This is very annoying without anyone that can like go up walls.
What's the, I mean, I think you're the only person that
can get that. Oh yeah. Don't worry. I've got it. So should
I, are you collecting it or should I go on the ground and
collect it? I'm collecting. Okay. Good. What does that? What
does that really cool new cyberpunk trailer music mean?
Swarm. I do like the flame effects though. They're very
cool. Over here. Over here. How difficult is that for you to
press that button? I do have to take my hand off my
mouse for a second. See, you should be focusing on the game
instead of your, how do you not have one? I screamed clipped
already. You still got these old, old material. There's a
huge bug. There's a huge bug gaping dragon over here.
Yeah. Where'd it go? Oh, there he is. There he is.
Behind you. This hurts. I don't know. I really don't know.
I don't have to leap them all because I don't remember which
one is which. There he is. There he is. Yeah. Keep that
one because they're here. There he is. There he is. There
he is. There he is. There he is. There he is. There he
is. There he is. Oh shit. That diamond just insta killed
him. I don't see him. Are you sure? Okay. I'm going
down. Fine. Fine. Does he drop anything or no? No. Is he
just cool? He's just a cool guy. Just cool. All right. I
need some of that red sugar to heal, right? Yeah. Where's
it? Where's it? It's kryptonite or something. Where's
it called? It's I don't know. Let's go up. Is it
like procedurally everything generated? Can we? Is it? Well,
do you have the map? What was the map button? Tab. Hold
tab. Tab. Well, yeah. If there was something up there,
you'd be able to see it on the map but yeah, you can just
like drill across or you want me to just go in here and
just drill. I'm gonna just go. Is this like Minecraft?
Should I not like ever drill what I don't know where
I'm drilling? Are we gonna fall into the lava? There's
no like bedrock or like a lava or anything. All right.
Well, we're just still going. Okay. I don't think
you're going anywhere. Am I not going anywhere? You
gotta look at the map. No, like look at where you
are like hold tab. Yeah. What about it? This is
not I like if you you rotate the map, you'd be
able to see a room but so what not going
anywhere. So, can I not have I not going anywhere
but why can I dig over here though? Why not? Well,
why what's what there's no secrets over here. You
know, you're the hardest person to record sound
bites for because like it doesn't start recording
until you start talking but you have like most of
the things you say are filler words. Well, why
what's what there's no secrets over here. Like
most people I can just get a straight like
there's no secrets over here. Not you.
Oh, big fun. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait. There's
no secrets over here. Oh, what are we doing? Oh,
that is a big bug. Yeah, shoot them in the butt.
Oh, he dropped something. Am I not supposed to
be touching that? No, that's poison. But no,
there actually is like a globe in there. Wait,
come back this way. We're gonna keep drilling.
I thought you just told me that this was not
something I should be doing. Don't you want
to see what's that way? Wasn't the whole
point that I was stupid for doing this? Well,
what's what there's no secrets over here.
Am I not going anywhere? I don't understand.
Well, what's what there's no secrets over here.
Oh, he dropped something.
Hold on, look at the map. Am I not going
anywhere? Hold on. Should we turn around,
right? Is this not it? Right. So that doesn't
you can just do that for fun. No,
that's a serious business. Just wait till
they patch that out next patch. We found
an exploit. This just didn't. Miners can
mine in ground. We've removed it. We think
players had too much freedom. All right,
so you went down. Yeah, up or down?
Oh, yeah, we gotta go this. We haven't
gone this way. All right, cool.
Just like an actual one or health or health
over here. Health globes. Hey, I got some
one hundred and seventy five out of two
hundred. Just gonna keep going up. So
who's the best character in the game?
What's the coolest character? The coolest.
I really do like a drill guy. There's
one fun thing. Like after you collect
all the minerals, you have to retrace
your struts, your steps to get back up
to the starting spot, right? Or trace
your strep. The drill guy could just
drill like a straight line straight
back to it. Especially if you're on
like a harder level and that because
the levels get really huge. They seem
like they seem like they could get big.
Hey, you ever play this game called
Apex Legends? No, not once. OK, well
first of all, Apex Legends is better
than this game. And there's the
character Pathfinder and he has, you
know, ziplines. There's a zipline
character just like that.
Underneath you there's this health
underneath you. Like grab it right
underneath like with that rocket.
I'm not hurt. Straight below you.
This is health on her. Are you dead?
What? No. Are you dead right now?
Am I dead? No. Why? I'm mining over
here. You look like you're dead.
Dead? Like what happens when you die?
Can you can you be like revived or
what? Well, no, you just you're just
dead forever. What? Do you see a dead
body on the screen? Yeah, there's one
like right down this pit. What? I'm
like I'm like fucking over here mining
this red shit. You don't see me over
here. I'm pressing X. Do you see me
hitting the red thing? I got you.
What the fuck just happened? What the
fuck's going on? Why am I here?
Hey, there's health over here. You
just like ported me back. Am I
lagging? You just like ported me back.
I was like in a fucking wall.
Can you like teleport people to?
That's weird. Yeah, there's a I'm
playing teleport guy.
Oh, no, I just I got like pulled
back. That's weird.
I actually forget what the other guy
does. So we we
need to find fossils. We need to
find fossils. I think they actually
show up on the scanner too.
Do they? Let me go this way. I've
we've been messing around so much I
have no clue where we've been and
haven't been. And also like every 10
minutes my computer has been freaking
out and it just starts like freezing up
and I can't do anything about it.
I'm sorry to hear that. I'm not very
I don't like this character.
I want the character that can fly
around.
Well, I'm at crystals. Hey, there's a
lot of bugs.
I need your help. Where you at? I'm
worried. I think I'm going to die.
Hit, shout, shout, shout, shout. I
don't know where you are.
What happens if they hit me? What,
you see the audience screen?
Shout again. I can't see you. I don't
know where you are.
Watch out. I got this one. I got this.
Watch out.
Told you. What's the big circle here?
The big blue circle. That's what I was
talking about before. That's my
grenade.
That's a flow field. I can't see
anything.
Help me. Shit. I'm not gonna lie. I
have no clue.
Like I would not lie to you.
I mean you you have many times. We're
gonna run around
and and get the last fossils. We get
the heck out of here.
Yeah, well you're the one that made
this a comedy stream. We would
this is supposed to be a boring play
the game stream and you made it a
comedy stream by making like recording
me. Come over here. Without me
telling you you could.
I want to make sure you're aware of
that. I didn't sign any release form.
Tell me when I have permission to
record you.
Not now. You don't have permission
to record me right now.
Okay, I'm not. Okay, good. I would
hate to have to get legal involved
in this one.
I have a drill. Why would I be doing
this? I don't know. Have we probably
walked by
a ton of these? Is gold up here? I just
no, I just grabbed it.
So we're looking for the fossil
looking thing, right?
I'm out of ammo.
Mike, I'm out of uh shit. Sorry, I know
we don't like to use real names. Um
I'm out of uh ammo.
Please never say that again. I would
hate. Hate to have to get legal
involved in this one.
I need ammo. Uh what's that uh
supply thing or should I just drop
another one? I don't know if we can.
I don't see where those are. You need
like 80 nitra.
Is there something on the minimap or
something that indicates if there's a
fossil around?
Or like the scanner or something? Because
I'm just trying to find one too. I'm pretty sure.
Oh, we're like nowhere near each other
either. No, I'm just looking for
fossils. They have that weird
nautilus look to them, right?
Yeah. It's like the uh Pokemon.
You know Pokemon. I don't. Are you
excited for um
Pokemon, Blood and Gore? Oh. See mine was
like nice. Yours was mean and horrible.
Pokemon, Blood and Gore.
They're going with a more mature
route. They figured after a Detective
Pikachu,
like everyone who likes Pokemon is a
bit older now and it's time for
Pokemon Blood and Gore.
Uh Pokemon Sex and Drugs.
That's next. They're testing the waters
with Blood and Gore.
I'm going up. Okay, I think I have all
the fossils.
It says we have six out of ten. Yeah,
I'm carrying four.
Oh, you have four. Okay. Can you shout
for me?
I'm so far away. Yeah, you are really
far away.
You can start heading back to the
ship because once I can deposit this,
we're leaving.
Um the ship is. I called the mule to
me. The ship is just the thing that
looks like a ship
on the screen, right? Yeah, I think. Why
is it moving?
Why is it? Oh, no, no, that's the mule.
So where where's the ship? Where's the
ship? I'm gonna like leave you on this
planet.
Don't do that. This is about to be
really bad.
But where about where is the ship
from here?
Um is there on the. Is it on the
map? I think it's
way up on the map. You just need to
start going up.
It'll. I think it'll show you once
I complete the quest thingy. Okay. Normally,
you're meant to follow
the mule. All right, well um I'm just
gonna dig. I'm digging straight up.
Hopefully, I don't drown myself.
Mule has a button. Somebody said the
mule has a button.
Yeah, it has a button that I press
and then like the mission ends and
swarms all come after you.
Oh, and you have to get to the
exit. Because the bugs know that
you're leaving and they're like
bonely. I'm just making this harder.
I'm making this slower and harder by
just going through the a tunnel to the
left.
There's no reason to do this. I just
bought out guys. I don't
I'm making it harder. I am. I'm making
it harder. I just got it. I got it.
Got it. I gave it. I gave it.
Here it goes. I don't have any more fuel.
Got an axe. I'm about to be in deep
shit aren't I?
Oh okay. Now it shows you drop pod.
You see where that is? Drop pod.
That's actually not that far.
Okay, that's where you gotta go.
I'm out of fuel. How do I get fuel?
You need to resupply. You should be able
to call one now.
I don't have enough.
No, I can see it. I can see it. I can see it.
Okay. The other fun strat
when you call in the supplies
it drills from like the top down.
So if you call it underneath a
launch pod or something it just makes
a straight line up.
Yeah, I'm here. Okay, I'm on my way.
I see. You got some bugs behind you.
I am. I'm bugging out. What's this?
Oh, it's just a... My computer's on the fritz.
You look like your computer's having
trouble. Yeah.
So we this is just like left for day.
We just have to get on.
Yeah, I'm getting on it. There you go.
That was baby mission for babies.
That just looked like it said no
dwarfs.
No, it's no elves. Retrieving escape.
Oh, this is new.
Why do we do the Grand Theft Auto 5
lobby?
Shit. Oh, you win a race.
So Jadiz and Vizmoor.
Do we use these for stuff?
Oh yeah, I'll show you that now.
I'll show you what you use the Jadiz on.
Sick. Sick.
How many chins does the driller have?
A lot.
So I did perks. I did one already.
Oh yeah, come, come, come, come, come, come.
What's up? Where are you?
You come down here in these terminals
like equipment
and you can upgrade your equipment and
get new stuff.
Oh, this is cool. I think this one's
cosmetics. Yeah, this is all your
upgrades.
Locked weapon. So when you click on a
gun it has like tiers
where it goes down. You can only
have one perk equipped per tier.
And so I need to level your money.
You need to be, this is level four
for the next row. What's this like
four, eight, twelve, sixteen that goes
down? I don't know what you're talking
about.
When you're in the equipment, when you
open up a piece of equipment.
Right, like open up your equipment and
this should be
red. Oh yeah, you need to unlock
levels. Those are your levels that you
need to be.
So should I increase the range of
the flame for long distance
incineration?
How hard is it to come by some of
these materials?
Oh, it's Vizmoor. Okay, it's 1200
bucks in Vizmoor.
Let's get it. That's cool. What about this
one?
Pinpoint accuracy on the first shot.
Nice.
Nice. I'm just gonna get it. I don't
even want to play as this character.
What am I doing?
You don't? Can I refound what I just
did? I don't think so. I don't, why
am I playing? I want to try the, ah.
Well, all right. I'm playing as the
fucking frog neck guy. German. It's
all right, this did these last.
This is a time-honored tradition around
here. What I'm gonna need for you to
do is give me a
boo. What? No, you,
you just make the noise like a boo.
Make a boo?
Boo, boo. Why am I, why would I, when
have I ever done that?
When have I ever made that noise?
When you and I have ever like hung
out together ever or made a video or
been on stream. No, you don't. I do
it on my stream all the time now.
It's, it's because, okay, I'll give
you an example.
Boo. Boo. Oh, it's not, I can't record
myself. See, I need you to do it. Okay,
so you just want me to go boo.
Yeah. Boo. Boo. Okay, wait, boo.
A different pitch one. Boo. Now,
now a deep one. Boo. Okay.
That's all I want. That's just a
hundred people just died in Roblox.
That's what that was. They're dying.
Oh god. All right, how do I,
can I go into your room? Dude, I
can go into your room?
What do you got in here? Where's your
diary? I do not want to get legal
involved in this.
Well, what's, what, there's no secrets
over here?
Whoa, somebody's got a messy,
somebody's got a messy room. My room
is not messy. Yes, it is.
Oh yeah, what about like the five
McDonald's large cups over here?
Oh, come on. Fucking idiot. You know,
I'm, look at my room. It's clean.
I did my laundry today. You're never
getting out of your room.
Well, what's, what, there's no secrets
over here?
That's all you have to say? You're all
just looking for secrets all the time?
All right, how do I change characters?
Uh, in your room, I think. Wait, wait,
there's no secrets over here?
Come in your room. Boo. Guys, I
didn't just say that. Over here, over
here. Boo.
What, there's no secrets over here?
What?
Well, what's, what, there's no
secrets over here?
What, what's, what, there's no secrets
over here?
There's no secrets over here? What,
what's, what, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, what's,
there's no secrets over here? Well,
why, what, is there no secrets over
here?
What, why, what, what, there's no
secrets over here?
Are you slash following me? This is
fucking work. All right, let's play the
fun thing.
Okay. Yeah, this is, oh yeah, this is
the real game.
Yeah. This is like the Junk Course
to Star Game.
...I'm gonna do another one
Go into you don't do it. Hey, do you think that maybe if you get like a high score here that there's like
You're gonna kill me with that shit. Oh, I want to hear what one of them sounds like because you're probably like
Because you couldn't hear yourself
No, you were pretty good
I got 250 but like I it fucked me up because if I have no secrets over here
No, no, no, you have to reset it
Fuck you reset that counter. Oh, I got 250 yet. I got 250 go into you don't go until you don't hit
Don't like don't hit go until you miss
Okay. Wait, how long do I go?
Until you miss there's no time limit. Okay. Thanks. I went
Wait, I thought it looked like you did no it rolled in go until you miss until you miss I didn't miss
Oh, my games like it my games like it he missed
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Oh, yeah, I gave lagged oldest trick in the book
Yeah, I mean I did but you missed again. I got 250 points
Are we just gonna sit around and do jokes? Why am I doing this?
Why am I doing the fortnight thing? Why am I doing the oh you love fortnight? Oh, I've seen you dab before
I feels like you just took over my computer. It got loud
Yeah, keep it up. It really does feel like you just got control here. Oh, it's the jukebox. Okay, isn't this romantic?
Okay, you're a real funny tuber doing the floss. Somebody just said I'm unsubbing
My computer was taken over. I had no control over that environment if it was under my control
I would not have done that
Yeah, I'll kick up fucking water bucket into his head. It's making you happy
What what wait I need to upgrade equipment
What is your guys ability now? I don't know. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, what what if I got to it?
What did he do it up a doing ability? Um, I don't know. Are you sure I don't know
How do I look at it? You start a mission and then you you play the game. All right
Well, this is the deal. I'm just gonna place this guy
But uh, yeah, you do it too you just did it everybody does that especially you just you know
You because you're a fool and I want you to know that you're a fool. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, okay
I didn't get that one
It's too long for you to have the the part that you want
I
Okay, I'm setting this to hazard for extreme. Are you ready? Why would you do that?
What why would you make it that hard? Okay, we're doing hazard three. We were on hazard two and that was baby mode
All right. Well, so we're gonna go up to three and you handle it salvage two mules
There's no secrets over here. I can't tell if that's the original one or if that's the one of those that I did
Previously, I don't know. That's a previous
Okay, what 12 a poker blue these flowers
Yeah, we got to get on poke balls
Where's the escape pod the mule leaves behind a trail of green markers when it returns to the escape pod follow those
Oh, that's cool
Why did Mike Mike hit a slow than yours?
What do you have for processor
45,000 K 20
I don't want to bet I don't want to be the guy League of Legends that fucking loads in last you look like an asshole
loads in last I
Don't want to be the little guy the League of Legends the fuck loads in last. I don't want to be that guy
All right, hold everybody hustle hustle
Okay, we need we got a salvage to you
Okay, so I have a tether oh
Yeah, you're the guy with the wires. Yeah
Okay, well your wire guy. Okay. He's just testing. I'm test. I just want all right cool
That's how that works. Nice
All right. So we need to salvage. What are these?
Whoa, yeah, I think they just
Also, if you're going up these you press reverse
You can just like hover over a chasm. So when a lot of bugs come out you can kind of just fill in the middle
Oh, I see you can just like go backwards. That's cool
That is really watch out there. Why watch what about there's some flying bugs in this game
So is that my only means of transportation? I have to use this to get up there wherever you're going
Yeah, or you can just like
You can just minecraft your way in I guess you can
It's not far. Then you're gonna want to save uses of your uh, yeah
Grapple. All right, let's get going. Good thing. I just wasted two of them. Yeah, watch out. There's a pit here
Okay, don't worry. So is this an opportunity to use this? Yeah, it's just too
It's a too steep now, it's really steep
How do I get out of here now if I'm this character
It looks too steep. I think I think you got it. Do I actually have to dig out of here?
Yeah here here here dig with me on this side. It should have brought a driller perhaps maybe
What is the other guy? There's the scout the driller the
Engineer but oh, yeah, you like build the turret. Yep. He builds turrets. All right. Thank you. Oh, yeah
No, and he makes platforms. He's really good
Makes plow that's awesome. Yeah, maybe I should play him so we can actually, you know get some teamwork going but I
What am I supposed to do about this? Can I make this jump? Is that gonna am I gonna hit the wall?
Can I jump from here? Can I jump from here? I try I don't know
Yep. All right, cool. Let's go. Are those the flowers we need? Oh, yeah, and you can dig while you're on it
You can like make a foothold. I mean, I wish we had a driller
We did
And I'd be really helpful right now if we had someone who could drill through this
We can but we're doing it manual drilling. I'm just burying the axe in the back of your head
That's what I think about you. Oh, there goes what does that mean? I don't what was what's on the computer?
I have no idea. It's been doing this with every game and I have no idea why what do you have for a graphics card?
I have 240 80
To a 240 80. I think it's like a tight next pass. Is this like
2804 be more than that. It's like what year is it? It's like it's like
1900 you help me mine this I can't even go. Okay, there's like a
What are these dead we shouldn't have done that that was not but they weren't a threat the environment will
You're the most like environmentally conscious dwarf I have ever seen
We only know
Digging and killing but he just not drop anything here
I wish I could see more light. Oh, well, I have the light gun
Then your job
Yeah, but like I'm not blind. So I've been fine. That's cuz you turn your gamma all the way up
I've been I've been to his house
You haven't been to Austin and he turns up his gamma all the way and then pretends like he can see really well
It's bullshit
Look out we got blood. Yes, we do
Remember we're at a higher hazard level German
I like this this game actually is really fun when you have people and you're on the really high difficulty
You got a hustle
There's a million buggos seems like it
But you just can't stop making jokes for more than like two seconds I didn't start it for loads in last
Alright cool
You can't take cadences and make that some kind of an insult like everybody has cadences
You can't make a cadence it is like come on
It's a cat I have we all have cadences form of like political correctness were you like
Cadence you can't make fun of a cadence
Alright cool
Get down here. Where are you my cadences?
Daring
How'd you feel about always sunny being a TV show at e3
It wasn't it was only one. Are you all right? Was that your computer?
Yeah, my computer just I didn't I guess I did what what's going on here
It was one person from the it's not even
Cast
Games are dumb watch my new show. No, it was one guy
And all right, I'm in trouble
Who is doing this what the fuck is going on to me
You see I'm shouting I don't know
We got swarmed and you ran away and started making always sunny references separate it
Look, I'm shouting what?
Oh god, you're fucking what is going on right now. You're loading in last right now
Loads in last
I'm flying
I am flying around getting carried away by a bug
Shouldn't have dropped me getting it. I'm coming. I'm still i'm fine. That's like a smoker
Can you shout so I know you are?
There you are. I don't know. How did you even get over there?
Well, I saw that you were down here and I was
Seeing if I could
It seemed faster
You're flying
This is what happens when you're in a dream when you're in a flying flying dream
You don't have control of where you're flying. You just know you are
Jeremy i'm taking care of this bug. All right, this bug is dead here. You see where I am
Yeah, okay. Let's go
All right. Um, I just showed up just in time
I dug a really big hole for you
You did that for me?
I did it for you
Let there be life
There's my hole I think is that no, that's not my hole. There it is up there
That's a big hole
What?
You can fly around you have a grapple hook
What does that have to do with anything that has to do with you have to be aware that I can't do that
You have to help me. I'm the ground force
Okay, edf
Yeah, that'll be fun. We are the valiant
infantry
We're the
That's the only thing I know
Defend our mother earth from any alley and attack
Huge room
Oh, is this is this one of the mules?
Probably
That looks like a mule and watch out
All right. These things just are blowing up all over the place around us. I'm almost dead. They're bainlings. Those things are horrible
Oh shit
I think we got to dig this up. Oh, yeah. We got to we got to pick up all the parts
What oh
Oh help help help help my computer's lagging
I can't help you. Uh, three more of those creepers came and exploded on us
How did you end up down there I got picked up by a fly bug
He just threw you down the hole
Where's my recorder where's my recorder for it?
Why'd you have it on hazard five
I didn't I had it on hazard like we're confident people that can play this game
Guys, can I have like a thousand people diagnose my computer problem all at once?
Uh, all right, I know I can help you
Give me the symptoms. When do they start?
It's like inner minutely
Every like 10 minutes, okay, my game freezes like four times. Do you have any hard disks?
No, are you all solid state?
Yes, are you sure?
Yes, okay. When was the last time you did a driver update?
Good question
May have just solved your problem
Also
how
Much ram do you have?
um
You're gonna tell me to download more. No, i'm not that's but it's like
2017 joke
Yeah, I mean you do them sometimes you were doing the flossing dance earlier
2017 is really not that long ago. So like that joke would still be kind of relevant
But no, how much what do you have 32 16?
Uh, I think I have two 16. I didn't do the flop first of all
I need to like 70 scream in you i'm gonna scream in your face as loud as I can
I did not do the floss you put the jukebox on and took control of my computer and made that happen
But I also did see you dab before
So have you
No, last time I was at your house you did
Please just let the barrels be
Last time you're on my own
All right. Let's let's do that mission again, but not on like ultra inferno mode. That was that's like normal difficulty. Is this
Let me see
We should be able to do that
He's deflecting i'm not deflecting we're doing it the same difficulty
And you know what i'm gonna switch characters
Tell him I that's what i'm gonna do
So that I can work together with you and you know, we can both be low level newbies
So i'm gonna be the driller again. I kind of like that. It was fun
Okay, and i'll be the engineer so at least I can travel around now and I have an upgrade now
Do you accept me?
Yes, why why wouldn't I?
That's a pretty do that that
Bro, that's an epic beard. I can't there's too many people talking
There's voices in my head. I'm the only person talking to you
Yep. All right
I think you've played too many sounds
You played too many other how many other people you got on that sound board it was normal man was talking to me
He interrupts my stream sometimes
normal man
Yeah, wait, there's a couple characters around here
Normal man's just telling me to kill yerma
well, um
Don't listen to that guy
I'm not don't don't worry. They're all corrupted see
Everyone banded together and killed justin so I replaced him with kimberly
But kimberly was secretly the person who killed justin so I had to get rid of kimberly
And then we got japanese voice lady who apparently is god
And we went through a couple of different guys and now it's normal guy normal man who likes, uh, white bread and tennis
You should probably go to a doctor if I would have
Give you some advice. You probably should hit up a doctor
Okay. Yeah, you try and explain the germa lore to somebody and like not have to see a therapist
How do we know that i'm not one of the voices in your head
I don't know. How could you i've been playing alone this whole time
Just like who does he think he's with
He's just talking
I was last to load in again
I need a I need a there's a 2080 any good
Yeah, it's very good. Is it it has the it has the rtx
No, you dare do that. Don't say that. I know you're gonna do the
All right, which one this is like
All right, so that's my spotlight. That's your spotlight
Is this when the curtain comes up and there's an audience back here?
I got all solid state too
This is bullshit
Okay. Um, sorry, I had to shoot that thing. Okay. Okay. You see this flower
Do I see this flower? I do
There's a one behind you like those
I'm back here
Let's do okay, but no more fucking around like we made our funny joke. This is a serious mission. No more
There's no secrets here. We made our one joke. It's been like five minutes. Let's just get to it, right?
Yes, why why wouldn't I I that's what I said to yourself
I was
And you kind of interrupted me
Okay, I should be playing this multi-boxing with three other me's
I'm gonna get so much done and then you would make the pro team
You want to dig through here? I can handle that
Oh your drew guy. Yeah, that's why I changed
Uh wrong way. I figured yeah, what the heck that should have been right though. That is weird
uh
Because yeah, these dirt areas always lead to a new path
Here it is
Uh computer a computer's break. Oh, okay. How's your computer?
Not not good
Uh now it's fine
Maybe this is what they have
No, there's definitely you got a virus
Yeah, I I look at a lot of just
Messed up stuff
Remember that time you got that virus that locked on your whole computer
Yes, yes, I do remember
I got a ransomware
to like
Give us your computer
Or give us four hundred dollars and we have your computer virus like how do you get this virus?
Yeah, you got like all your everything on your computer encrypted or you got like ransomware
That was fucked up. Oh over this way
There's a are you sure?
There's a rare rare materials and here's the stuff. Everything's over here. But watch out because these sometimes bugs. Yeah
Don't get exploded on
You got exploded on didn't you?
bugs
There's too many people talking
Watch out and there's this thing that built home. I I have to build it
You have to build that I have to build it. Holy shit, dude, I can't even see anything
I turned my dpi on my mouse up
Are you not helping? Are you sure this is not like hazard eight?
No, this is doable. This is i've done this like solo
Well, what's the problem then?
No, I can do this
I'm the problem. I'm the problem
I just built your thing for you. Are you doing what is making the ball pit?
It's a mcdonald's poop pit
I don't think they have something. Oh, what just happened?
the mcdonald's poop pit
patent pending
Patent pending so like this axe. I want to hit. Oh, no, that's your throwing. Yeah, that's my throwing axe
I just did a lot of good work with that thing. All right, so
I got a lot of stuff
Okay, you gotta put it you gotta put it in the guy
I did so where's are the machine that we have to get?
uh, you see all these uh
Hold on everyone about there's about to be 60 voices in my head
Ow
Give me like i'm trying to learn a game mode
I can kill this with one hand if i'm good. Am I good enough? Oh, it's bouncing me. I'm kind of good
I can my my axe goes through it
Oh really? Yeah
Okay, so you have to dig up these white circles
Okay, i've got an arm. I don't know what we're doing with them because I couldn't deposit it
Wait, mine just went through the floor. I just attached a leg on this
I think we might have just soft locked. No, we didn't
I'm, I'm attaching legs
Well, it's good. It's good. It's repaired it fell in the ground. Okay, are we good? Just watch me
Just be just just watch just watch. No, I mean like defend me
I'm doing i'm repairing my turret. Are you because I just got bold
Did you stop whining? I got bold I got bold
This is why we needed italics the voice of reason got him one hit
Bald no, I said bold bold
So we need one more
Give me my axe. We need nitro as well because we got a call on resupply. We're like low on ammo
I don't know what happened
I'm okay. I'm all right
There's another okay. The other supply thing is down here down here. I'm probably gonna get swarmed. So I need your help
What do you need? I don't know. I just heard I heard like that weird
dinosaur sound
what
That's sound that's in jurassic park every jurassic park. It goes like
Where I could press that I just did
Oh, i'm not ready to go down yet
Well, I don't want to get so I got a leg. There's another one of those things down here somewhere
flowers to
Do you see the other thing?
Um, I don't see it. I have there's a leg in my hand. I did I hold on wait
Something down here, too
God damn it
What just
I'm just making pancakes. I don't know what i'm doing. They're letting me on fire friend
This is friendly fire
Stop killing justin
I don't know what you're talking about
Oops
Uh, we should go down here
No, no, no, no, no, no
some of the ammo
Yes, do I have to like pick up my turrets? How do these things work?
Do we you don't want to go down here?
Oh, I got the dancing man
So what what's your goal here why what are we why are we just sitting here for
Um
I was I was just confused for a second
We resupplied. Okay, where are we going? There's stuff down here. Okay down there. Okay, let's go. Is this gonna hurt you?
Wait, wait, wait
Oh
You made lily pads for a guy
Yeah, you ever played prey?
Once game ripped off prey. Oh right there
It's a scam. Honestly
What's a scam?
prey
Yeah, right
How is prey a scam?
It's not even a real game they start you in like a fake room
Help me this is this is two out of two and then we all how many uh flowers you have
Okay, we need seven anymore. Uh with those packs
I can't think
Yes, why why wouldn't I feel like you accidentally just pressed that button? No
I mean, I didn't know what it was, but I pressed it on purpose
All right. We need more flowers
Any more flowers?
Okay, let's go. Let's go. Let's go
Did you say we need more uh malachite whatever it's called?
uh
Don't it was nitro that we needed for the resupply and I called and we got it. Oh, okay. Well, it's just flowers good
Could you do me a favor? Yeah, could you uh cap this?
Uh, yes
Well, give me a different tone that's what do you think i'm doing
Okay
You didn't really do that, right but I mean you
That's that's what i'm doing
I got uh, I got I got umma umma might I got dude. I got umami over here
Dude, this is totally umami over here. Where's the supply?
I think we actually have a chance to make it
Are you picking up flowers are you just being fucking I just I got two flowers i'm holding them right now
All right, we need to go up
Bunch of dwarves. Oh, we're tough dwarves big beards. Let's go pick flowers. Well, I had none of the dwarves
the default dwarf
This can't be a dwarf game unless
One of them talks like this
I mean they do a little bit. All right
No, they have to do
That's the only way you can tell if it's a dwarf if they go
All right
Okay
Uh, where have we not been?
I don't know
Have we been down this tunnel?
Now we we go up
Up or down
I don't think we've been this way. Oh, there's nothing
Put the shrek voice over a dwarf and it's perfect
All right, just follow me. I'm taking this up
We can go up
Where where are you?
Oh
Okay, take me up pick me up
Have we been like up we've been like here, right?
No, there's not any um
Or what? Um, I don't know
Where is it until you miss go until you miss? I don't have it. You don't have it
I couldn't find it. Why do you still have to go until you miss one? Yeah this flower
Well, it's funny when I do it but then when you when you do it you get to funny no
No, no, no, no when you do it you get to then catch yourself and then pretend that you're making fun of me
Oh, I get it. I see. It's not funny cerebral cadence is a serious disorder
It's funny when I go
Up, uh, oh, hey, i'm doing the turbo. All right
Right, right. Oh
interesting
It's funny when I do it
I don't know. What is every dwarf is the exact same character. Don't say that
Do we know we haven't been this way come come this way
There's eyeballs over here
eyeballs
It just drill these eyeballs dude. Calm down jerma. This is right here fun
Should we just drill those eyeballs drill them?
drill them
They're moving around
That's common rock. How would that be common? That's pretty uncommon. There's nothing even in there
You're supposed to drill them to death. I did
And now you can't get the secret
I thought I did I thought he did I guess not
We're passing flowers people attending we're passing flowers
What no I grabbed it
Five more five more keep going. Let's keep out on lookout
Don't see anything
Don't don't say anything. I know what that tastes like
What I know what that tastes like the red sugar
flower
Just saying random nouns and like
The sugar the red sugar health thing. I feel like I know what that tastes like. What does it taste like?
That's I why do I have to explain that to you?
I just know what that tastes like
Uh need a driller here. It tastes like a red jolly rancher
There are you happy?
God man some people
I thought you were a bug
Well this uh, we ended up kind of this way
Oh, we're just back in this room. That's exactly what I was thinking. Is that right?
I feel like we're talking to the germa soundboard
That's your own fault for making it in the first place
Oh, yeah deposit the flowers
I have three how many do you have?
One. Oh really?
How did I get three and you only got one?
Where's that thing? Come here
What is our thing doing
Why is he just sitting on the wall?
Press c when it comes to you
Oh
I wish the real germa was here
same
Okay that and the old germa wait what the mules are heading back
Oh, wait, wait, wait
No, no, no, no, I I want to deposit. Hold on. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait
Did I just send them all back?
Did you I I thought I was depositing
Did you do something
Wait, no, we were supposed to do this
There's where we this isn't
Yeah
I guess
Okay, come on overheating
Okay, i'm fine how the fuck do I get I gotta get up there
What?
Okay
Oh, and there's a flower right here
So when's um when's out when germa's dream screen is on part two
Uh, the 29th
July
June yeah, we're still in june
Yeah, we are still in june
I need help
Don't leave the triangulation zone unless you need to go get some, uh jolly rancher, right?
Yeah
Okay up the length of progress. Whoa
Where'd he go? Jeez, it's like a charger
What is watch out for the the boomers i'm dying what are you okay? Yeah, i'm good
Yeah, you know, it's good thing someone played engineer
Yeah, it's a class that you like and how to play
You've never played it before it's level one
Damn
What do you think i'm doing?
There's some help over there
I'm good. Oh, not anymore
Oh
Stand right here stand where
The underneath the yellow
Under the why?
Oh, that's funny. Okay
Oh, it's funny
All right resupplied I can we can get out of here now where's our bob
Secondary objective completed now finish the job. We have to refuel this
We're going to fuel
We're here prepare the bomb. Okay, you i'll do the fuel line
Hold on. I'm killing things. Where's bob?
Oh wait
Come on press e
All right
Come back to the fuel charge
Hey, want me to kill that in one hit? Yes. Yes, I would love that just got it
Wait, wait, what the fuck did they come from they just they spawned in front of me easy
Where is this thing?
All right. Now's not the time to be bragging about how easy this is
What's your orc doing?
My what your orc
My my you're dancing or land mode
But it attracts a bunch of children
At least one of you remain by the charging fuel cells. All right, let's just stand back here
You're gonna get overwhelmed people above you too
I got my turrets up. It's fine
Here here I know how to do this. Here's the here's how we do it
We build a house
Build a house watch out the exploded. Well now it's just damaging my house
jeez
Come on right this butt
Shut up, I don't care if I were jeopardizing the mission. This is my life. I only have one
Yolo a one life gameplay
Up here must have been 10 minutes
I can get this dude. Where's he going around the other corner?
That guy's fucking me up. Hey, excuse me. Hey cover me up cover me
Uh
You can't say that okay, we're almost done
One minute and 12 seconds interesting come on
What's that?
build
Oh, that's your turret
You've gone there like what are you talking about here? What are you talking about? What are you even saying?
People are trying to like
We're staging a coup
What is he talking about? What is he even talking about?
There's people
Never okay before we got a call a few times before we got on the call. What did you specifically ask me?
if what
If what if I was going to what?
be
What was it?
I wanted to make sure you weren't going to ruin my fun gameplay session by being silly
Okay, being like weird and being silly. Yeah
You're talking about like people in your head speaking to you and like then you just talked about like uganda
What take your own advice was that no that wasn't you all right when you win the mission
There's someone like there's like a like an orchestra on my head
Like gospel singing
I can't get it to stop. It just keeps
We could start a band, uh, all right, hold on I think we might have a third player here
possible
It's possible
Possible third player everybody. Yeah, well, let me go pee and see if there's a possible third player
All right. I'm gonna figure out this. Uh, you figure out your computer
I can figure out my computer. Okay, and don't mute yourself because you have to you have to like
Make sure people on my stream can hear you because like i'm leaving so i'm don't mute you yourself. You need to talk
Okay. Bye. I'll be right back. Okay. Can can I download and install new nvidia drivers while streaming without any problems?
also
Why like why do you always need a new driver? Why can't they just use the same one?
Like my computer used to work if this if this were the problem
You know what i'm saying?
He's also by the way drama never he doesn't get t
Well, I can hear myself. Oh god
No
There's voices in my head
it might be
I was thinking too
I had the same problem when I was playing the soul calibers and it was
Disconnecting like every 10 minutes and I thought it was a hitbox problem, but it's not
It's not plugged in. No, it's not plugged in
Oh, you know what? My twitch chat is always right. You're right. It's because I have spotify open
That'll do it
Ronnie has wait ronnie joined like when did ronnie join the game?
Get in here ronnie. I don't care join do it get in here
Do it
Those shy little boy testing the waters if I join
And see his reaction
And maybe I could play
Yeah
Yeah, I gotta do my upgrades and he's gonna come back and do his upgrades and we all gotta do upgrades and that's
What are you doing? Well, no, you're you're peeing right now. You're not
You're not actually doing the upgrades right now
Shut up that joke is old
Stop
What yeah, please?
Thank you go until you miss
I'm not doing that game again until you miss
Okay, i'll go do it
I missed okay go until you miss. I missed it's it's over. Um, I don't know
Oh, hey, what's up?
Hey, can you hear me on my stream? Yeah testing. Yeah. Hey, what's going on?
Okay, uh
So we should be dragging in
Mr. Attalix
Can you drag him in or do I have to do that?
Um, you i'll do it you don't I don't want to explain how to do it
There's already somebody else in here. You just you wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait
Let me wait
What did he just do?
Why did he just do that?
Huh? Why did you just make a new call?
You have to
Discord is a good program
That's weird
So is Ronnie playing?
Yeah
We got a full four we actually have a full four
So now nobody can just like make fun of us for being bad at this video again
No one was doing that
Yes, they were
Please just let you didn't see
No
Are you one of those people that like just reads chat you don't actually read it
You just kind of glaze over it and you don't see all the criticisms that they give to you
No, I read chat too much. It's been a lot of trouble
like you
like me
Like I don't do that. I read all the criticisms
He's insecure say i'm reading your chat right now, too stir is black
very uh
I don't know
Our unique stuff going on in there. You have unique chats
How do I can I buy a drink?
What does this do?
skull cross your heels four hundred and thirty dollars
Is italics on steam?
Can you invite him? Let me see
Let me get him in here. Uh, is he on steam? I don't see him
Well, he's he's your friend your best friend that you decided to move in life
Just invite him over all the time so you can do your painting streams. So maybe you should keep track of where he is
What's so funny
It's not funny from the other perspective where you have to like watch other people be friends from like outside your window
I I don't know. I can't invite him
Is there a way to invite from
Invite to lobby you're hey, you're stixson, right?
What I am?
Stixson, okay. Yeah, i'm inviting you to this lobby. Why can't you guys just have your actual names?
Because I don't want my actual name. Okay, I want it to be something interesting
Why can't you be twitch.tv slash germa985 on steam?
Why do I have to be?
Did you get the invite? You don't have to be i'm just suggesting
Hey talcs, can you say like the first part of your abc's?
Hey guys, what's up? All right, you're good
Yes, that's not the first part of your abc's, but that's okay
No
Actually, it was kind of the first part of your abc's
All right. We ready?
Stixson's still joining
I have to like re-explain the whole game just for stixson. Yep. You are you're gonna have to re-explain everything everything
Everything no
Yeah, he is
He's gonna have to explain everything he is though because you don't know where is this guy
What the fuck is happening? Hello. Am I the only fucking person in here? What's going on?
Can we serious? Hey guys, what's up? Can I start the mission?
Is he actually here no, hey i'm pinned down over here are you even playing
I
Think we have to do baby missions because he's like the the newbies join now. He's good at video games
He knows what he's doing. Well, no, no, like it has a lot of them are locked now
Well, we can just let's blow through it
I'm doing hazard four
Let's go. I didn't know that wow
Wait, are we doing hazard four?
That's talcs welcome to talcs
Hey guys, what's up?
I'm gonna fucking throw up
I'm gonna throw up on this room. I know what's gonna happen here. I have a sinking feeling
I don't know
This is gonna be bad. I'm gonna puke
Need ammo. What are you doing?
Oh my god, i'm gonna fucking puke
All right, you know how to play this italics yes
Okay, so
You it's left for uh, it's left for dead
The only difference is you have to mine we have to see the top right of your screen
We have to get 225 more kite. We have to extract it together and you pick a class and there's four classes
And hey, can I get a closer look? Yeah, you come over here and look at this. He's building a sentry
Wow, i'm not sure who you pick who who did you pick for a class italics? What's your class?
It's a very simple question. What is what is your class?
i'm under fire
Well, you're the scout
I'm surrounded by fucking sound boards today. I'm surrounded by sound boards. Hey guys, what's up?
All right, i'm the drill guy
I don't know if you're doing this too. I don't know if you're capping him and then playing it
I don't know if you're doing this too
Why what are you talking about? What do you mean? What am I talking about?
You invited your best friend italics. Do you have any idea what's happening right now? You have he's not here
How is he not here? He's not here
But he's not here. He's he's
We're being manipulated
Yeah, all right. Let's go
You died again
Oh my god
Yes, oh look it's a fortnight orc we're we're gonna be fine
What hey guys, what's up, I don't know who's talking
It was a copy pasta
Oh, can you heal me watch out come on italic he's just standing here
Maybe
I'm so confused right now. All right, let me
You definitely i'm mapping this right now you're freaking out he's like I got a pressure to get it mapped quick
There's too much going on. I don't even know who to shoot first
Yes
Is anyone playing this game?
You can die
Hey, we're in a safe zone with the turrets. Hey guys, what's up?
I'm gonna lose my fucking mind
We got a sniper over here
It's actually way too bad that I I need to go back
I had a ronnie soundboard too. Oh, did you really?
Don't have it. I checked
I like didn't save any of them
We need to get the the more kite which is
The blue the navy blue stuff on the sides. I'm not sure how I feel about that
Should we just kill him?
I mean like we should probably just kill him like like I got my sights on him right now
Don't do it
I'm not sure he's fired the gun
But he doesn't need to
This is easy. We're only in hazard four. Oh, it's time to fight the boss
Wait, that was a real voice
That that's not
Look, okay. I'm hitting left bumper. This is what's happening
He's on a controller
That's why
Okay, I need some sugar
I need some sugar right now
I'm, not sure he's fired the gun
All right. Whoa something
something
Yes, oh you're killing the you're killing the the the brain I think the brain
I I stuck a bunch of needles in it
I'm gonna duck
I was a little spider
I'm trying to take a game that we played together seriously for once and all you want to do is stop and make jokes
Seriously, i've been looking forward to playing this game for like two months
You really have wanted to play this for a long time too. And now all I get are these jokers in here
No, I didn't do anything
I'm playing that i'm the one that's playing the game right now
Is there a kill feed
No, how could this game not have a kill feed?
There's punches over here come get some
gold
Also, this is where scout gets really useful. It wasn't someone playing scout. Are we all dead?
Yeah, you're the only person that remains fuck
Who's in this hole?
Oh, he's stuck to it. I'm dead
Wait, wait
He's alive. No, he's not. No, he's not
Can we just play the game?
You know
Really pisses me off when people accuse me of lying
Should I go like into his room and like turn it off?
Go into his room and cut his mic
Maybe
Turn off this cut. I should unplug his I should unplug his router
I'm gonna go unplug his router guys. That's my router too. That's not how I can't do that
Okay, we're going in again
I need full focus
From everyone. All right. Let me just buy some stuff first
I'm taking this one dead seriously, but I can I can I can afford something. No, I can't I don't have I need to level up
There we go
Flare last longer. Sure. I'll take it
I thought that was another sign board. I am so
Fucking paranoid about everything being soundboard that I don't know
What what what's there to be paranoid about?
I don't know you tell me
I'm gonna go unplug his router
Wait, am I going alone? What?
You were more concerned
about
Fucking doing that stupid soundboard and now wait, oh, yeah, I think we're good
Yeah, I think I brought everybody but I was worried because I was in the ship alone and I just saw myself dropping
My stomach can't take it. I'm gonna go I'm fucking
Hey guys, what's up? Oh my fucking god
Oh
I can't okay. I can't take this
Oh, are you are you drill guy? I am drill. I've been drill guy. I'm always drill guy. It's a drill wall drill wall
You gotta find the thing. Oh, i'm looking for the purples
Right, I don't see
Oh, maybe i'm wrong down. Yeah, I think this might just be a common rock area
down
I don't know. I don't think this might be one
I don't see anything
What the heck is this?
I don't know. I don't think i've been to this environment
Maybe I have
A long time. What about these? What about the blue?
Okay, we got to get more kite
And yeah, yep
Stop singing
One mission is all I ask
You're going you're going home soon like you're not gonna be able to play again i'm gonna miss you dude
At least I got
Jolly rancher. All right
Back when army of two came out my college roommates and sweet mates were way too into
Cut his mic
This way friends
This two this two scouts both yelling in different directions
No, maybe I shouldn't be following the scout that's standing still in the wall press control
That's the pro tip
I go into his room and he's not even in there
Hold on a second
He's not in his room
This he's not at his desk. There's nobody there
Are you controlling him? Are you?
No
Where am I?
Uh, no one no one is like can we please please?
over here
gamers
All right, let's go
We're gonna go up. What do you want to go through?
Drill not working. Oh, there's a bug you're getting caught on
Dude, I think please I I I can't drill through this
Dude, it's not my fault that italics is at like a mcdonald's wi-fi right now pretending that he's here. I can't go through this
I can't go through this
Use your fucking pick
I'm so sick of goofs
All right, we can move
Oh acid acid pool acid pool acid pool acid pool
What is it? Hey, can I get a closer look? This would be a lot easier if we had a driller
I
You saw what happened to me. I drilled and fell down into an acid pool
I told you I thought you said again
I thought you told me that there was no minecraft like dig down into the lava scenarios in this game
That just happened
I lied can we get some can we get some support? There's a bunch of like flesh-colored fighters on me
Hey guys, what's up? It's okay. I've been live for two hours. I feel like i've been live for 40
Uh, I burned another bridge
I don't think i'm gonna play with him anymore
I checked he wasn't in the other room
He's simulated. I don't want to play with starting one man. He like
He fucking simulated one of my friends
Shut up
I didn't know we were all dead
I need a recording of italic saying like i'm down
I'm gonna scour hours of youtube content
Hey, i'm pinned down over here. Are you even playing? Okay
We can handle
Let's just never talk about this mission. All right, we're doing it again. That'll work
That'll work
That's good enough for me. I think yeah
Well, not time to leave. I need to upgrade my weapons. You can't I need to get better drills barb drills
and um
uh
barb drills
Who has the worst computer?
Right now it's a tight race between lemon law and ronnie. Oh
I was gonna say every time that it's quiet for like 15 to 20 straight seconds. It means that like the two sound board boys
are
Queuing up more
What every time that every time you guys are quiet for more than 10 seconds
It means like here comes more sound effects. Yes
Yes
No
I'm breaking out
I'm breaking free
Oh, this chip was in my neck
It was a computer chip in my neck. It's blood
Can we uh, can we all just ignore the blood for like one second and get a drill guy over on the dirt?
I'm a drill guy. What do you need?
What?
Who the fuck was that?
Did you turn italics into another person?
good times
I can't have italics. I'll just replace him. All right
All right, here we go
Bugs
I can't tell if that was a sound board or somebody actually just hurt themselves. Oh
The stream doesn't feel real
I'm not sure he's fired
I know
I i'm right there with you
It's so messed up when you get cut off from talking by yourself
Like you can't finish your thought I can't finish my sentence because i'm cutting myself off
It was so funny because it was like it feels like you're so polite
You can't interrupt yourself. You like give yourself the time to talk, but it's not even real
Four
Wait, what's what's the dog?
Is somebody a dog? Hey, all right
That's awfully suspiciously the same bark over and over again. Is that even a real dog computer and might have just woke me up
I
Has to be to like play this game like four hours ago and I've just been I don't know man
It was rough last night. Where were you? You weren't even I just went in there
Were you in the bathroom?
Guys if we fail this mission, i'm gonna scream like
Oh fail it immediately fail it fail it. I want to hear him scream as loud as I can
So fail just blow yourself up or something. Help. Help. Help. I have no idea how to play this game
All right, so pretty much how it works is uh failed the tutorial. It's
Lfd2, but it's with dwarfs
Lfd2
Where are you?
Where are you star?
Looking for dead. Where are you star? Where are you?
Found him
Oh, hey, there's a there's a there's a pearl on there pearl, but you need to upgrade your character
I can't get in there
You need a drill. I have a drill
I'll get in there
Like you're on a secret mission to kill me right now
I thought you said there's a pearl in here
There is you got to keep digging around until you find it
Not that way
Over here found it
Did I blow it up? I got it. No, you gotta bring it to the thing
Ow
All right, where's the thing?
I'm gonna die
Protect the guy with the money
I'm the okay now it's gonna roll down the cliff
He's dead again. Yes. I'm the one holding the disco ball and nobody's in my line. You can't say that
He's gonna scream he's gonna scream this is perfect
Oh, that's weak weak weak
Someone just said what's wrong with you. That's not me doing that
I'm not doing that. That's not me screaming
It's like, uh, I have a radio frequency
I have okay
I gotta explain what this is. I got stop. It's a radio. I got a radio frequency
And i'm turning around looking for like the news and I pick up like hell
And i'm like, oh all out of it
Like never mind
Sounds like a whoopee cushion
Let's go again. All right. Do we give up and not do the hard mode?
No
Hard mode. All right
No, we do hard mode
All right, so actual question. I don't know how to change character
Are you going to your your pod with with your name on it?
And you know what attacks doesn't even know how to play. We're doing hazard three
You should have explained it
Oh, sorry, it was all funny games a second. Oh, I can't wait to hear him scream and now
Hold on that's not the news
That's like the ghost realm. Hold on let me
What class do we actually need? No
uh, we need
Anything I mean like we're fine be like the gunner like the machine gunner actually anything other than scout would be great
Italics is actually here. Yeah, we recorded this video like three years ago
Oh, wait, hold on everybody. Hold on
I want to start a new video for this. Um, we're even a new video three. Oh, okay two
One. Hey everybody. What's going on stir here? We're checking out this new game deep rock galactic pretty cool
I've got a couple my friends in the car. We got lemon law stickson and ronnie. Could you say hello? Hey guys, what's up?
Hey, what's happening?
Uh ronnie, uh ronnie is not in the call for honey. You're
Cut i'm cutting this. No, just start again. Hold on. Just sorry
I'm i'm still going so let me do my intro so then like we can i'll just change it. You know what I mean?
Well, we'll count it and i'll restart can you shut the fuck up and let me do my thing because like you know
I let you do your thing. So like let me do mine
Okay, fine. I don't it's like it's gonna be in the video though. No, no, no, no
No, like I am gonna i'm just saying like when we do intros
Uh, we do three of them because you gotta get what it's your video. No, it's fucking
There's eight of us here making a video
So we're all gonna be able to sink it sink it to the load screen
That would be cool. Like you start like right as we're landing. No, that's what's gonna happen
But like there's there's fucking eight of us in this call. We're all gonna have an intro
I video now. Hey, what's happening everybody? We're and you started the game
Yeah, do it as we're like after it loads do the intro
Hey, nobody bleeps their youtube videos three years ago. You do that now for ad revenue
It's true
Hey everybody, what's going on looking to make some coca cola money with that and we're gonna do a little bit of fun
Wow if you could all
Airhorn
What are these crutches all right everybody we're gonna need to go they're bombs
Fucking oh my god. Oh my god lemon law down
Actual you died again moment. That's what you died again moment right there
Okay. Hey, what's that? Hey, okay, everybody welcome to youtube. Hey
What is going on guys? I like to elongate my words and drag things on a little bit longer
Trying to make this video 10 minutes, you know get that ad
So i'm a casual mining here in the cave
Uh pro tip, uh, usually a driller to get through this dirt a little bit quicker
It's like you have this crazy alter ego that's like ripping out of your head as a ghost like screaming shit on video
Hey
All right, watch out. I screwed these up
Like, you know the ogre from warcraft how it talks to the two heads
And one of them's like i'm not ready. I'm ready. That's what's happening to you from dota
From dota they they did it first
actually
Really like these up. Hey click this one. Never mind
Uh-oh
Right. You were thinking about the environment
about
Supposed to take all a moment to tell you guys about dollar shave club
You just did that's the thing you just did
I mean you make that joke, but you just did that for free
So tell me more
You just never you ever buy a one dollar razor
Yeah, use that on your face
have fun
Dollar uh
Well one dollar razor I call that a ship
It's just a knife
They just send you like a piece of glass
Hey, try this out
What's going on with your voice? You what's what's happening?
What do you mean?
you
I don't know something's weird
I see I do comedy skips now. So everyone's been wildly going and do a different character
No, no, it's it's the compressor. Right? Right, right. You have like the yeah
Yeah, if I scream then i'll start off lower and try and compensate for how much i'm
Yeah, you have one of those you have one of those like things that makes your voice go like this
I don't have everybody
Was that the jora mormon voice? I mean it could be
Kind of hey, no spoilers
No spoiler. That's how he talks
That part yet. You haven't gotten to the part where jora mormon talks. Well, you haven't seen
You're on like episode four of the first season. Okay
What he doesn't feel like season four
Can I get some help? Yeah, he's in the first episode
What he's the one that falls out the window?
Yeah, you all right. You're tracking on kind of uncharted ground here
You you be careful here
Careful what?
I'm the one that doesn't want the spoilers
Where we need to go up?
Where is everybody we're going like up
In the worst possible way
Did I that's that was a funny moment that's going on the montage
No, no, no, that's it's my that's my clip. That's my video
Please no, please. I need that. I just need to fill this out
I'm so close to 10 minutes. No, you got the you got like the funny like scream ghost of a frequency thing
I get this
Fine. Thanks
But I get the dollar shave club
All right, homie
I get italics like sorry. Are we role playing right now? Are we pretending like we still make youtube content?
I do what the fuck man
I do
I do once every three years
And they are not spider-man three what's plays. That's too bad. You're missing out
Is that why gta 5 so popular right now?
I don't know because it takes you back to the yester years in 2015 when things were good
I think just gta rps is fun and people like it
So what we're to look we need uh, we're looking for you missed. Uh, you missed a secret I did
Yeah, my games. I'm just lagging computer. Watch out. What?
Are you down?
Oh down here. There's a there's a drillable
Is it there's a drillable down there?
Yeah
What is that out right here? I got it
Uh, it's not there
It's not here
Not over here
Swarm swarm
Swarm
Did you just drill can you drill like a straight line so we can retreat?
Please i'm going i'm going i'm going
And you're going through like toxic gas
What?
There's a hole
Okay, I gotta I gotta escape her
Wow, that was that was some teamwork. I'm using this clip if you got the last one
I'm getting this one, but that that was me doing that though. That was like my perspective is like more interesting
Because i'm the one drilling
What's this for my review?
Uh, that need help pops
What's the pop? What's the what's the pops?
Are we dead?
Some of you look dead
I think
We are dead
I'll get you guys. Don't worry
He told me to drill a hole
And they just kind of filled the hole
Well, if alex didn't come with us because he was too busy making the jokes first of all, I was with somebody
So if I was with somebody then that means two of us
You were with ronnie
And ronnie can't hear what we're saying
Oh, right. Is that why he's been yelling for help in the chat?
Ronnie can't hear us
Is that why he wrote help, uh, 10 times in the chat? Yes, that's why
To anyone watching this youtube video, please help. How do I t-bag?
No
No, ah
I'm dead. I'm down again
That's okay
Did aiming did you reviving me give you tamp a handful time to run away while I absorbed everybody?
Well
This is what scouts good at
You can read more about it in the review. I'm just gonna like not revive germa this time
You revived me and ran away. Well, it's like 10 bugs attacked me
Uh, I can't shoot
They had ammo we might need to get a supply crate
Uh, you don't have enough nitro. I don't think
Thank you for using the sprinkles on me
If you have nitro, please deposit it because we were very close to the allotted amount required to call in
The drop-on which is going to apply you with additional ammo
All right. Well, where are we gonna find this pearl? Don't we?
Was that before or after the dlc?
Uh, it's actually entirely, uh start to finish free to play
Uh, it's not true. This game's like 30 bucks
Hey, i'm just a youtuber. I don't gotta be
Hey guys check out deep rock galactic if you're a tuber you can just email the publisher and they'll send you it for free
So that's how I got it
Just pretend to be
Found it
Where is it?
What where is it? I just heard it
And can we please turn in some nitrate?
What I just heard the thing break? Oh, it's right there
I'm nitro whatever wait, where the hell is it? Don't correct me
Don't back check me. Oh, you got it
All right dump it
What do I do with this?
Uh, we gotta get the supply wagon thing
You're gonna put it in this thing and we get some
Stuff wait, where you going? Why wait, wait, wait, where you going? Get back here me. No. No, it's a stupid thing
Oh, it might be following me press v
I did
enemies
Much as I can do
I swear who has the nitro?
One of you have it I do
Turn it in
turn it in
where
Where it's right there. There it is
Inside the moving loop great
All right
I I think that
Over here on the yellow thing there is a device that comes out that gives you extra money
I get this clip
No, that's mine. I'm the one that did it
If you put that in your video, i'm gonna be fucking really mad. Don't do that
I made that funny joke and I dropped it on him and I knew I made I did the funny
Eehaw eehaw thing. I would hate to get my oh my lawyers involved in this one
Ladies and gentlemen, we have the prelude to what would ultimately become
Recording without telling the people you're playing with that you're recording so that no clips would need be shared
And all would belong to the clipper
It's pretty good strategy actually
Natalix, did you uh level up your
Inside of your weapon to be able to shoot things out of it
What did you get ammo
Did you did you get ammo?
Make sure you get ammo
I got ammo. Nice. All right. Are you guys ready? I need ammo. Did we put the um
Did you put the the the jade thing in there?
What did you put the we put the jade in there the thing that the the secret gem in the wall?
The secret gem that we dug out of the wall was put in the supply drop, right following somebody who's good at this game
You following me?
Then oh, so the answer is no. No, the answer is yeah
The heck is this?
we're looking for
The blue the navy blue. Oh, by the way f if you want to throw out a some light
You can just do that. Hey
Driller control
Mouse button is grenade you need me to do what you need to dig split dig spot
Yeah, just dig straight to me
What is it guys? What is he doing? I'm digging to you
I'm seeing i'm seeing f in the chat. What do you f?
This is some red faction one stuff we're doing right here
Why would yeah, I want to replay that
One of these days you're just really far away
Okay, far 20 meters for a drill guy
I can't overheat this i'm right above you
Hey
I made it
Okay, there's the hole we're going but a swarm's coming. Oh that actually worked
Press f he doesn't know
I don't understand what the doubts what do we not know?
Uh, I think what is running?
What do we not know? Oh, we're asking chat. What do we not know? Yeah, what do we not know?
So
I think we know everything we need to know. That's why half these people still in school
They don't
Uh, it's two o'clock
What are you talking about?
Oh
Sorry, do you uh you are you face cam?
Uh
Are you on face cam now? No
Never mind why not never mind. You're gonna ask me and take my shirt off again. We're here
Something in the water just I could just snipe running. That was me
Me
Um, we're like in trouble here
Yeah
Wait, you've never been in trouble before
I'm dead. There's so many of these things. It's up to you
Oh, dude, i'm gonna die right now. No, you're not. No, you're not be fine
Be fine i'm gonna ammo
Why there are so many of those?
Just grapple around
We got so much of that ore over here. This would be so bad if you lose this
Come on, man. You're like one of the top players
Show us again why everyone considers you to be like the good gamer
I got no ammo
You don't have any ammo at all zero
i've got
four shots left
Make them count two
Um, they're all cramming up this hole. I don't remember which way to actually go
This is the wrong way
Holy shit, you can go very far with that thing, huh? I'm getting edf. I have it upgraded pretty far
And this is our runner trying to revive us
Here's the hole. What are those like?
Deku nuts coming out of your like face when you fly
What are those deku nuts?
No, it's your beard. Never mind
You're lost
Here look do you need a guide?
Just sneak over and revive just sneak through that tunnel is my tunnel. That's my clip
I'm copyright claiming your whole channel
Oh castle griffin's seat, I I hold the copyright
Is that supposed to be some kind of monetary threat?
On a platform with no money exists. Here's the dumbest thing about youtube. You could probably fucking get away with that
somehow
Uh, I i'm from uh, loc limited for uh company from uh, south
Florida and uh, I own that song the video's mine. You can probably do that and like get away
I just the other day
Had a video claimed it was like scout hand upward live commentary
Was copyright claimed by mortal kombat dude. There's like a thousand of those armored bugs over here
Yeah
um
Uh, you know what we need is is more nitro though
Because I have just happened no ammo
It's up to you again
You're all that fucking yeah, we we all got you revived us and then instantly he's alive i'm dead
Yeah
I'm gonna be dead too. Come on sticks slow
one
two
three
four
Five got it
I was just running around looking for nitrous
Come on, you can do it. You can do you can do it. I got ronnie the relay has been had the batons passed three
four
Five got it. Nice. Oh my god, you're up. You're up. Let's make sure i'm counting five for you
I'm coming to five for you one
All right, no, no, no, no, let's let's do this smart. All right, everyone relax. Hey guys, what's up? No
This is not the time to do this. We you want to do this level again
Yeah, no, you don't there's a there's a dirt down there that needs to be drilled through this dirt down there
Where where is what do you mean dirt down there?
Where are you? I mean over there compact dirt that leaves the next area
We need to get through because there's like no nitro here
How did you get down there? How did I get down there? No, how star? Where the hell are you?
Where'd you just write with me? Oh, you fly around like a dickhead forgot like a dickhead. I'm just drilling down
Wow
Am I going the right way?
star
No, you're not
Like a dickhead
I hear something
You're going the complete opposite way
I'm with you. Let's do this. Let's do this lemon long. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die
Do you have ammo a little bit?
Here lauren lauren into this
All right, i'm here i'm here i'm here i'm here i'm here i'm here i'm here i'm here all right
Studio quality like voice acting for these characters sound effect. Whoa, let's watch out man
Touch it
Where'd you go?
shout
Shout i'm just i'm going down this path
Looking for nitro
Good question. How come one of these games hasn't done like a voice pack like that
like what
You know non-serious like tuber boys
you mean like
the dota voice packs
Star like hiroth smite
Start with our hiroth smite is uh
Sorry, but did you want a voice pack? Um
Open the wallet and turn it upside down. Which one did you want?
Star, where are you?
I need to know oh, I need to constantly know where you are
I'm running back to our friends
You're going back
You're going back there
Yeah
All right. I'm like above you
Oh god
Can you dig up? Can you dig up for me? Can you dig up?
dig up
I'm dead. I'm good. I'm dead, too
I don't like I don't understand how there was only enough nitro to call in one supply drop
For like the first three areas
What is it is we have four people so it's 400 more hp and 400 less resources
Yeah
We have this dead weight
Ronnie's not even in the call. Why would you say that?
I feel like he's listening to all of the streams at once
Let's see if anyone mentions him
Uh, well, he is getting him in the call. He is communicating. He said bad in all capitals
He did say bad
Oh, I need 15 silver coins
Let's see the other characters
gunner engineer
gunner
I'll stay with the drill
Noob driller
Is it the new class? Whatever you pick
How come I can't go on the ship? Oh, I didn't take a mission
I feel like this is how you dance in vr
You don't want to move around that much because you don't want to bump into your walls
Dude I go nuts
You can't use your legs in vr. Yes, you can if you have trackers on them. Yeah, you just
They have the loops like the oculus controllers. You just stick your feet through the loop
And then you play with poor controllers
All right. Are we ready to we'll get this is
This is a pure gamer
Part of the level. Okay, I haven't won anything since i've been here. So i'll take responsibility
Yeah, congrats on level one
Yeah, i'm still level one
Remember when I said anything but scout
I didn't oh I didn't pick that
I didn't even go into my ship
These tough those beards are so huge
That's just like that's so much hair
I feel like I would trip on that here. Is there like a button in here that just takes us back to the base?
No, we're winning this
Mine that this is a simple mining mission. You got it
Does the drill work is a better miner?
Someone okay, who's hosting this?
How I was posting what me this my computer freaks out every 10 minutes and then the game freaks out
Because I just lagged off the clip. Yeah, that's happening. That's my fault
Okay, I got the uh gold
There we go. Okay, dig through the dirt dig through the dirt. Let's dig through this dirt
You gotta hustle you take too long. Then there's a million things
dig through dirt
I doubt I've just planned. Okay
Going through the dirt. Wait
Okay
We're through i'm proud of you. Thanks, man
lick me
Why do you want to say something like that? Hey guys, what's up? Why can't you just say like
I don't know something like
Charge me. It's hard to think of something better to say right on the spot. You can't even think of anything
You're like, why don't you say? Um
Well, it's because I was looking at something
Yeah, i'm not afraid to share what my desires are
like some people
That are so bottled up
And taught by society that you're home supposed to you know, not be licked
But you do it anyway, right?
All right, you're killing one hit I did
All right. So now where are we going?
We need to extract
All right. There's uh this
crusty stuff here
I'm gonna dump the uh gold and the I got a lot of nitra and a lot of gold watch out spiders
Why what's with this broken game?
Okay, we're good
I want that. Uh, right killed in one hit
Now we got a lot of gold in there a lot of uh nitro
I'll scout ahead as the class name implies
Hey, i'll come with you. Yeah, let's stick together stick together. There's no reason for us to split up right?
Don't like don't split up because you're the gamer star and you'd like to go forward really fast
And then that's what this class does. No, you're supposed to go back to back to back to back and just walk together
Look at us mining this together doesn't feel good
It is fun
Take my hand take my hand
Okay, let's go
Make sure you keep your hands our hands locked
Okay
What's purple rock?
Purple rock is
Help me mine this don't talk to him
I'm gonna talk to him because he know he wants to know what the what's going on purple rock
He's not with ronnie would be able to tell me if ronnie were here
Oh my god, you do not want to talk to ronnie. He's insufferable
Why are you so rude?
always
I like these blue crystals
They light the place up
What's this about this cheese? Come get the cheese. Can we do like the moldy cheese?
Cheese mine, it's nothing. Oh, is it nothing?
It's dirt dirt
I have no idea what the purple stuff is. I don't think it's anything
That actually was just nothing that actually you have ronnie sound board
That was very accurate. That's exactly the land. We need it. Oh germ over here
Jeremy i'm coming coming right here. Give me a sec
I probably wouldn't follow me italics
Oh, he's actually he's actually in the car. Oh, hey ronnie. Sorry. I thought I thought I was being like manipulated
You thought I was simulating more people? Well, you are but that's a different thing
Ah geez are way down there
I still don't see the greater searching. I got it. I got it bring that thing
Thanks for taking my clip you just that's what you just did it's the equivalent of what you just did
No
Wait here
Okay
Okay, we can dig straight down to them
Here where you're above us
Here I got you
So it's gonna make the tunnel down to us
Okay, so i'm gonna die i'm in a hole
Hey, germy, you can drop that, you know
You can drop that and contribute
Oh, there's another secret thing here
Good
You're good. So when should I smash my razor death at it with a hammer?
Um, should I just put it in like a blender should I put this fucking thing in a blender?
Yeah, where's ronnie?
This is my life now. I can't
Walk he's getting he's digging with a pickaxe and i'm like standing on top of him like shooting up
I made the tunnel there
We were already halfway in the ground. We don't know where the tunnel is
You can see it through the wall
Now my computer is freaking out i'm gonna die
I don't give you permission to put that when I screamed I screamed like so hard I farted
You better uh check
Hold on wait what?
Better check for extra
All right, go ahead and get me up. That's okay. Yeah. No, you're no problem. I'll get you up
Yeah, I got this now
I found you
All right, I think i'm gonna be bigger next time
Wait, you're you're gonna be bigger
bigger
Oh
But no that probably requires coordination
So many not really
Okay
Here are though
No, no, no
I love being out of ammo
All right, we're going back to back to back to back together next time
Now we're all gonna put on a shock collar and if you go 20 feet away you get shocked
Oh, I thought the star I thought this was you just like with your head poking out
I've got this
We should use cheat codes. I'm using i'm trying to type them but it's hard to run away from the bugs and type
Up can someone type black liner liner hear you typing
Oh shit
What no, I didn't what I didn't know you were getting me
fucking god
Just trying to carry
I didn't see why you didn't get revived last time. I didn't think you I did
I'm sitting in mashing on the keyboard. I didn't I thought we were done. Hey, uh, this guy's gonna need two shock collars
I didn't move. Hey you guys ran away from us
You went your own way and you went your own tunnels and we went a different direction and that's what happened
Yeah, we did the hand-holding joke and everything
No, I'm I like
Have to revive germo, can you imagine i'm ready i'm ready i'm i can't do it now
We're in a hole in the wall. You should be able to see this
Yeah, but I can't reach you unless I like dig through the wall
Do we look at my keyboard when I type?
Yeah, I didn't grow up with a computer in my lap. I had to learn it's like learning a new language. I learned I started
Yeah
Sorry, I mean I ruined your joke. Sorry. You weren't born with a computer in your lap. Go ahead finish
Are you paying attention?
Yes
I was gonna say you're older than I am, but I didn't even have a computer until I was
Like yeah 20
Yeah, they they didn't give me one till I went to college and it was one of those big ones that filled the whole room
You had to crank the generator for it
Or one of us in here is uh spoiled. Oh, that was perfect
I never had a cranking generator. All right, are we good? No, why is there another one of these they just keep coming out of nowhere
You guys really were digging down like parallel to the hole that I made for you
We were already most of the way down when you made your hole and then I couldn't get to your hole
You could have and you don't you just don't understand how this game is supposed to be played. I understand. I just don't believe you
You're a noob
Did you not resurrect the other guy like you were the one in the hole?
You didn't get other guy
Oh, you didn't get other guy
Hey, he didn't get other guy. Okay, there's one resupply here, but it's like in the wall
Another swarm so resupply and um be ready
Uh, i'm good on supplies because you haven't played in an hour. Yeah pretty much
Is that a record scratch?
Why did this turn into like a fucking am talk show
Another record scratch. That's my screen
Oh, I think I just fucking destroyed ronnie
I think it's a right of passage at this point. I did that earlier
Get off me
There's too many. There's too many
So the hitbox wasn't the problem
Thank god, all right, we don't have any
Uh, do we have enough for supplies?
No, we don't
What the hell are we gonna do?
We have to keep going forward and get resupply
Like let's start fighting forward down this hill
Push through, you know
three three
This is one of these things
Uh down here. Oh, why did you hold control? Hold, uh control you can see where we are
Oh god, I found like a mother sack or something hard to hold control when i'm dead
Are you dead? Oh, yeah, then why does it matter where we went?
Are we killing the sack
Bad not good. There's a lot of ore over here
Hey germa, you have drill I do have
I'm underneath you get up here
I'm making the call you're making the call
All right, what do you got? What do you need control dig towards his dead body?
You're i'm digging. Yeah that way
Hold on out of uh, how did yours?
Like the last millisecond I realized what that was on the ground. I was like, oh, what is that man?
That was almost my clip
almost
Almost your clip
There's a lot of this we've gotten 20 more pipes
Yeah, it's pretty bad, isn't it?
I thought we were just here shooting bugs for fun. To be honest, there's also the uh, those those those
crystal, um
It's a lag crystal light drinks
Crystal light is as literal poison. Don't drink it
That's all ashley, but she doesn't drink it. She eats the dust. She doesn't mix it with water. She just eats the dust
Please be kidding
No, ronnie how many times you heard me say ashley eats dust
Uh, I just always assumed the dust came with liquid wait
She she eats crystal light dust
Yeah, are these like drug code words?
Like I heard a peanut butter dust, but I assume she mixed it. She also eats the peanut butter too dust
That's that's like an apocalypse peanut butter. Okay, she does mix that. All right
But does that crystal light's not okay crystal light?
Uh, is that what they're calling it nowadays? Okay
Where we going?
I don't know need we've 65 out of 200
um
we need
Honestly, we meet we need more nitro. Oh, I'm my we're out of ammo like again
Basically what you're looking for at this point when you don't know where to go is one of those dirt walls
Would be the next area
It's probably not a good idea. I think i'm going backwards
Yeah, we shouldn't go this way
Not this way
I'm not talking to you. I'm gonna stick some
Oh, you're coming this way too. Yeah, not this way. I know everyone was following me
And you're king
I'm the king
Well, if she likes crystal light dust, why doesn't she just get like a pixie stick? It's kind of that same thing
I think one of them is free of calories. Thank you. Yeah zero calories
It would have to be
Oh, there's a thing in there
Is this nitro or
Oh, I found a bunch of nitro pixie sticks are for when you want to get serious, you know
Crystal light light is in the name
Crystal light dust is a
It's a gateway drug to pixie
Her parents are visiting this weekend and we went out to a river and we were swimming in the river
and she
Won't admit it was a river
And i'm worried about her
She keeps saying it was a lake
Was the water moving in one direction? Yeah
It's a river. Oh, it's here
I got the thing
I think she was calling it a lake because she could you can't see either end of the river because it was like a bend
So it looked like a lake
But she like won't admit that it was a river
But it's a hundred and six mile long river
What's it doing over here
Well rivers that are exactly the mule up here to be honest. That's just insulting to cartographers. Okay
it's more well see
Little known fact rivers that are exactly 106 miles long are actually classified as lake really
Yeah
This is a very long lake
That and she's eating the dust
She's eating the lake dust. She won't let me like hear her either. She's eating the lake dust to her
She's like go away. I'm gassy
I deposited the uh the jade thing
Something again, uh, okay, I guess you're just gonna talk about the game. I have like a real narrow problem
malachite
Listen, I opened up to you guys some people need to understand which is not an excuse for your mental health. Okay
You handle that with a professional
We've got bugs surrounding
Where's that dang wheel?
I need it. I'm finding all the stuff you people need
Oh god, I also found monsters
No, no, no, don't fall down all the way. I'm good
I'm trying to knock it killed. Where's this mule?
You called it
Okay, we gotta go up top here. Is there no more supply? We're close. We gotta keep pushing
That's not good
Where's that loot bunk?
What's so funny what
Are you dead? Who's dead?
Hey, that was that was definitely going on that stream
Guys I don't want to alarm you but
Not by everyone literally everyone we need to go to the top
Well, i'm trying to people are dying. I'm trying to wrangle children. I'm i'm people are dying down here
We're dying down here. You set up up in your tower and fucking look down
We're trying to make things happen down here trying to survive
Are you posting the picture of me hugging the waterfall?
dead
All right, we've broken through
But I think that we ended up
The hell did we end up?
I think we already think we've wrapped around in a circle. I think
Uh shit
You were so adamant of us coming up here
I'm being chased by cave godzilla. Just trying to get you guys
Cross promotions getting wild where we're going then
I swear to god, I can't believe that that hurt me that much
Where were we off to up here? I don't know
Look at the map the map we
We could go down
Down to the left lower left. We kind of have to like go all the way down left
If you open up the map sweet, we gotta go this way then
Follow me
We're going down here
We need to go like this way
Poison i'm losing it. All right, we need to go
All right over here
Uh, this is this is just crazy enough to work
Okay
Here we go
Follow me guys
All right bingo
Start this hole he did it
We haven't been down here
Uh, there's a giant what the fuck is that thing?
Oh, that's the uh, that's the half-life thing and then you gotta you know
we gotta
No, it's just a lot of health around here for you. You hurt boys. I just got startled by the fortnight orphan
I am very hurt. I could use it
We need that Michael like there's a lot of stuff here a lot of stuff here guys looking good you guys
Hey, remember how we skipped the last like 45 minutes of us looking around in the youtube video
So we can get to this part. This is it guys. Yeah, we just cut
No, we just leave it all unedited but cut into 10 minute slices and say it's just the episode
We finally find the more guys
That's the title. Sorry guys tune in next time
Oh, no more kite this time guys click here to subscribe aliens
If you keep saying this i'm not going to be able to do it
Where's molly how much more we do 50 how many do you guys have hey and nobody's fucking helping me
What like it like an entitled thing to say i'm calling resupply do not touch the red button
Germa don't what do you not want me to do?
Here's the question
If they can just drop resupply pods from wherever they want
Why don't they just arm us with the drill that the resupply pod uses?
Shut up, uh because
Never mind. I was gonna say like a tv show thing
I mean, this is pretty much like the faster than light star wars issue all over again
Okay, so we need a second to plan when you look at the map
And try and figure out where we came back from
You press the button the thing walks back. You can either follow the mule or we can just start drilling
Well up if you want I we can start drilling up if you want
We got to be ready for that though. Where from where you want to go?
It looks like you can also okay. Come on
We can just start walking this way and then call the mule to us. We could just we okay. Hold on
Come over here
If we go over here
If we go through this tunnel and then up
Yeah, like this way
Climb back up this climb back up that
Because we have to get back up to the top, right?
Yeah
Watch out it's bug city. Oh fuck it is bug city
Okay, so then from here
We should be able to go up this way
Just like straight up this way over here
right
because then
That'll take us like, uh
All right. Let's go. All right
Let's clear this and then we'll go clear that don't go yet
Yeah, just set up defense here
Otherwise, we're gonna get a swarm goal. We're trying to figure out
Watch the behind watch the behind
Oh my god, come on, we ready to move this is a big dude over here
All right, we're all right, we're okay
All right, are we ready? Yeah, so now we gotta go we gotta go like up this way then
Also the mule walks back to it so we can just follow the mule and we're just following just follow the mule
Yeah
Okay
I'm just gonna stand on top of it easy mode and now yeah now it shows you where the drop pod is coming to
Drop on arrived mule is returning to lz. Yeah, we can just we can dig through
Wow it really is mezy mode you really do get to ride it
Oh, I don't think you used to be able to do that
No, he got away from me. It's just oh, yeah, we had you guys dug this tunnel
You're welcome. Oh jesus christ. Oh god. What?
Hold on is it
Wait wait wait wait
Oh god, there's big bugs behind us
Oh god, i'm not gonna overheating overheating. Where are we almost there almost there was there
We're out. We're out. We're out
I have no guns
Where the hell did it go over there?
Oh shit
I'm never gonna dig 85 meters in four minutes
We get good
Hey, oh me the talics are up here
Are you guys good?
Oh different hole. Oh talics. What do we do?
Just uh, let the bugs let the bugs go eat them and we'll escape you gotta run
I'll i'll get up there eventually
Just look towards the drop pod and dig
Why'd you say you were there you're like
Hey, are we all right?
Turn around. Oh god. Are we okay?
Are we all right? Keep digging. I I have no fuel
I can't leave him behind
We're almost there
Where the fuck are we?
You said you were there
One for you and one for me
I actually ran the whole path
Oh, no, don't die
All right. I'm gonna go
No, which way is the right way which way it's the correct way
i'm down
Wait, where am I going?
No
See you at home
We all right to be fair. We did you get did you make it?
Yeah, he made it. Yes
We pulled everybody into that tunnel
Nice job everyone. I hope jerma stretched his shoulder before he threw that hard
I don't have nobody had any ammo. We didn't know we were i'm trying to like just dig we're fine. We the missions went we won
Yeah, we wanted i'm still alive
When you don't stick to the plan, this is what happens. Let's get back to work
You're still alive. Why are we resurrecting in the med bay?
Well because we were checking on you guys
That was so fucking bad though
Like I I had the depth wrong and I turned the camera and we're just like tunneling
Like a tube sock on the left side of the map
But we did pull everybody away from star and then we may have not have made it out alive without that
Yeah, I just bailed
And how do I get a second freaking turret? I don't see the upgrade for it
You should just always have two turrets. I had it at level one
I did back in the beta and I cannot figure out how to get my it's the same button
So like you press four to place the turret then you press four to place the next one
And when I do that, it just recalls the previous one. I don't think it should
what do you think faster shield regen rate
or
Regen starts sooner for shield. I'm gonna check out youtube videos who they say you're the what you're making it
You're making that video now
So yeah, he's trying to get some insider tips everyone saying sooner
I would get better guns before you can get armor stuff unless you just can't afford the other things
I mean, I have one upgrade already into my
I need
I need this like silver or it's like a silver circle
I don't have any of it. I don't know what it is
There's an upgrade that makes you have one better turret into the two weak jump
Oh
No, i've even oh I can switch which modifications i'm using. Aha. Yeah. Well, that's a game changer
Aha
Give me that better drill
All right, let me put some perks in
Accessories, oh shit. What is this stuff a clean shave? Oh, what was that company?
Dollar shave club. Wow
Doesn't even remember the name of it from the same stream we're getting another plug
By the way, I did this this is for uh, comedy purposes only
This is with no affiliation at all. We have to say that otherwise you could get in trouble before you just did
Fuck a shave club
I did this this this is an opinion of somebody here. This is I don't know. I did I I don't even know who this is
I've never met them before in my life. I don't know who they are. So glad is the best a man can get
I don't I don't I cannot confirm or deny any of the statements
What if i'm not a man?
Oh, these are just hats
Yeah
Well, that's cool
This upgrade screen is not rad and sexy as fuck making my tummy twerk. What the fuck are you talking about?
Are we ready
I am now ready. Wait, wait, wait, where's the perk? Um, where's the perk screen? No inside your
Room, I think there's something wrong with my gun
What's wrong?
It's just not being used to being handled by such a handsome man
I don't have any available perks. Yeah, I do
All right, what are these what are these? Hey, hey i'm on stirr's floor
Interesting
Look chat. I don't know what you're thinking right now, but this is all real. It's happening. It's live
Whoa, what's going on?
We're about to leave. Okay
Oh, I need the ore that's here
How did me walking inside add seconds?
What time is it right now?
Can I BRB real quick? Oh my god
Hey guys, what's up?
Hey, hey guys, what's up? Hey, what's up?
Hi. Hey guys, what's up?
I'm unplugging the router. I'm just gonna unplug the router must
Must be my internet taking so long to load. I can't imagine my computer slowing us down unless you all just have way better
No
My computer's not slow. It could do 144 and overwatch just fine. No
By the way, it was great. I think I think I just heard like a door close behind me
I'm fairly certain. He like actually went to the bathroom and like put like a clip on
That's fine a clip on like a tie
He's got an interview later
It like started us right next to this objective, I mean, that's pretty great
We need these rooms
Uh, we've got I want to say that it explodes pretty long actually
Salvage these things are annoying, huh?
You are
One mule has been repaired
Is there another one around you it's right here
Doesn't look like it
I think that's the bonus leg
You know how cars have like a extra tire on the back
uh dirt
Like a kickstand
Oh, hey, welcome back italics. Hey
um
Yo, thanks for helping us. They're over here. I am helping you're fine
drilling
What am I getting?
You needed me
Is there no I got it. All right more
What do we need we need 20 of those mushroom caps they're the weird like uh,
You gotta find the germa 985 mushrooms
No, yes harvest my mushroom
This is weird
Hey guys, this is the mushroom. Yes that harvesting. Come on. Do it
Pull it up. Yes
We need that shit don't we you want ammo yeah
Yeah, what's it about somebody everybody has their own gamer noises. I had a face hugger on me
first time being hugged
Wow
We all get hugged all the time
Oh my god
All right, we good
No, this thing like suction cups me into that. Yeah, I told you
What the hell? Hey hit in the weak point
There's a face hugger on me
he is
Just tearing me apart right now
It sounds like a you problem. It is a me problem. Yeah, it is
He just gently put me down
I'm sure beauty and the beast right there, you know, they look scary, but really
Take care
uh
Yeah, that's a lot of ammo you're using on a
I'm like an npc
Kind of just sits there and does nothing
Not bothering anybody
Gold gold gold more gold. All right
Whoa
Okay, how we doing?
bad
Check bad time. I'm kind of down in the pit dying
Thanks for the gold. Hi, sir
Why are there so many of these little fly boys i'm afraid to do that i'm not doing that somebody else can get this
Whoa
Here you go, can somebody get up there? Yeah, there we go. We need somebody to get those jewels over there
On oh, we have uh, we have grapple guy
I've got a grapple down
Cool, I have where the rules lie down at the bottom
Nitro
Oh a grapple cool. What the hell is that? Oh, that's the thing that must be summoning all this nonsense
Can you reach that?
kill it
I'm gonna get this stuff
Is he dead?
Coming is there any help down here this grapple over here? Can you reach it? I got I with the deposit
Was that the safety deposit box thing?
You can hit the and it'll come to you
What is that thing in the middle curious, whoa god, oh you
Oh
I owe you one brother. No, i'm dead. Oh you want I should watch star wars on stream
Yeah, definitely that sounds like a good idea
I wonder stream it. Yeah, I wonder if i'll be permanently removed from this platform
The new one is there a new one?
Yeah, just go to go to the theater go to the theater and just while you're watching the new star wars just stream the screen
That's fine. Yeah, no you can do that. You can totally get away with it. You just do it right
Like make sure you switch your game category to artifact and you can get away with it
Man, just sitting there just like cheering like yeah
I don't you'd probably make it to the opening credits
This is awesome
You're probably do it longer than that
Not if your title was the new star wars movie in theaters
reaction
All right, so we going down
I'm, not sure where we're going. What am I for? I hear this like mules. I think we have to go down here
Okay, come come to us
Come to me and italics because I think it is one of those uh beep bops over here
Let's make let's do the safe italics. Is there a resupply down there? I think there's
Yeah, one more use on it
All right, I didn't go what I just like oh, you feel tactically suicide. I got
I thought we were going to go die
Pay attention to us. I am we talking a lot
Pay attention to me
Notice me
All right. Yeah, there's legs down here. Oh, there it is
Come to me. Uh, i'm looking for you. Uh, yeah
Okay, so we can shoot it
I can't toss it
To only one leg isn't it a leg over here?
Is that last leg? There it is. Oh the little hearts
Who's uh, it's out there we have to repair it i'm in trouble now
Where the where the rest of you?
Oh, what what i'm trying to hold either resurrection or i've got this leg in my hand
I was trying to carry it up
Ronnie and I need a little bit of assistance down here. We're actually fine. I don't think there's any trouble here
What don't you want to be scared your problems are the only problem? Yeah, because our problems are the objective
You guys are like fucking
Having fun over here. Don't worry. We'll just take care of it
They're just finding their own bliss. So what do we do with his leg? We're finding their own. All right
I got we got dirt here too running
Be careful
Coming those caps
What did you just say?
Uh, you need that. Oh, you got it. Okay
Uh, you need help this some help up here
Uh
And not enough to no, no, i'm good. I'm full
All right, what we're looking for uplink to mission control. Where's that then fucking role players? This is five player game
Who's the new guy?
Where me and ronnie are trying to play and win?
I'm doing things. Oh, yeah
What did you do?
i'm collecting
How many do you have right now?
Blue caps how many caps you have we'll see who's doing better. Oh, yeah. Oh, do you I have four?
And i've been turning them in you haven't and by the way me and ronnie just activated the uh objective
All right, you're still proud of yourselves. I'm doing better than you. That's what it matters
right, alex
um, are we like
Playing smite right now going by kdr
Maybe guys look when i'm mid. Okay when i'm mid. Oh my god. This is so annoying
What are you guys doing though, I am curious
We might have we might have enough to defeat it
What's the big green glowy one? Is that different somehow?
Uh, I don't know. It's poison. Okay
Um, I have four how many do you have ronnie?
um
Five so that's nine
Yeah, we no we we're done mission's over
We have enough
Yeah, let's go get to that dog
Oh, you guys are right here we made it
So nice of you to join us confused mission's over we beat it
We didn't do anything. You just deposit the mushrooms and it's over
We have enough mushrooms
We need one more. That's it
I was told we were done
We are we just need to you just need to put in your um mushroom caps
I was told it was over who hasn't deposited their mushroom cap. I got mine in I got mine in
Gar
I'm lying then it's alex. I already pushed the button. I didn't even have one
Bugs, I know where I can go get one. Hey bugs. Don't worry
I'm just on point tonight
You're banging on all cylinders man
You had him the whole time
No, I went and go grab I grabbed one
He had the whole time. I did not I you know, I got a whole stream over here though. I'll tell you
Like your mother did so we need to uplink. Are we ready?
You guys ready? I hate when people say that to me
Are you guys good?
Press the button. Here we go
This is where we got to uplink and we got to defend
Maybe this is a therapy stream. Is this like a parent parent issues stream?
Jerma, I love your streams. You always make me twerk. Please click this for a free ipod
Why are there virus bots in this chat right now?
That is a that is a virus bot like you're you clicked a link and your account got taken over by the bot
Did it say you make me twerk? Yes
Yeah, go like run malware bytes or whoever's account that is. I think you might need it
Everyone's helping me with this. That's cool
I'm doing a really good job
We've only got one shot at this if you fail retry from the hop
Just do it again
Let me get let me get like a big
No
I have these cool grenades. No
What grenade what's so cool about it? That's kind of cool
Yeah, sounds cool
Thanks for sharing
You're very well
This help down there if anybody really needs it
Give that ton of lacrosse. There's a secret thing in there for drill guys. Is there?
What can you like point to it?
I see you i'll get it
I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it
Whoa, which game had like an abora thing you had to defend first this or risk of rain?
Uh, all games are the same game. So doesn't matter
All right. How do I i'm gonna get up from here. I think it was pong
Uh, do we have any drop ammo get away from me?
There should be one down there. Yeah, they're all swarming me in here. I'm just trying to get the thing
I got you. Yeah, help me protect me while I search
Got it protect me
Can we all please get back in the time? Yeah, that's actually we have to stay inside that
I just I had the two people not in the triangulation zone dragged. I got sucked out
The gold bar
Where's the gold bar important, where's the gold bar? I dropped the gold bar
Where's the gold bar it fell because I got grabbed are we gonna lose this guys?
Yeah
Leave it to a couple tf2 players to not know how to play the objective in my right
I got the gold thing. I was it was directed by our director here star to go get gold thing
What is this too far?
I was I went I got I got it and it didn't take me very long
Let me be fair to myself here. I was on top of that real quick
I got a whole stream over here. That'll back me up
I can't believe we just lost
I need a soft and supple touch. I need someone to call daddy. Hi
Jesus
When you don't stick to the plan, this is what happens
That ended as well
This is me i'm throwing a tantrum right now
Do you think guys think the
One turret well, okay, they got stats. Never mind. I can figure it out
I'm just resigned to the fact that i'll never be able to upgrade anything
Can we beat that one level that one time? All right, but how about we drop the difficulty by one?
Is it really that embarrassing to play on like not the hard one
That wasn't even the hard one
But sure, yeah, we can do baby mode
What is but okay is baby mode in regular mode no, it's not baby mode
Dude, I don't know
I don't do I
stop
Stop yelling
I'm very calm and i'm very collected. I'm just asking a few questions about this video
Times oh you guys are leaving. I was still what does real mean?
We all meditate first click this. Uh, my name is joe. I want to play on the hard one
Baby, well, it's not fun
Okay now that we're all calm
How about we get the
I mean the other way around reverse it
Reverse what
This is you this is your face
I can't wait to come to one of your streams and just wait till you do that and then i'm gonna never
It's gonna happen every five minutes
See ronnie's laughing ronnie does no i'm saying what will never happen is you coming to one of my streams
What was the last time you were at my stream?
Oh by hold on a minute game with an ipad
It's funny funny that you say that um, who is still subscribed to the other person
Can I can ask you that just just right off the better?
Which one of us is currently like has a three and a half year sub to the other person. I is it you
I don't I forget sometimes what who is it?
I'm pretty sure i'm subbed to you. Are you subbed to me? Are you subbed to me right now?
Let's find out. Yeah, talk in the chat
Hold on. I gotta open up the screen. Yeah, he's gonna sell like right now
Don't gift stir. So please don't
Why did you just give why did you just why did you just give 30 dollars, what are you doing?
What he just he just donated 30 fucking dollars to the stream
Is that you making up the time that you were not subscribed?
Yeah
Hey, thanks. Thanks with the 30 bucks
Wow, that was the first time you've ever thanked anyone on you've been gifted a sub
Honestly, I told you I was subbed
Anonymous has a gifted a sub tier one to stir
I told you
Can we leave like the uh, the uh tutorials down here?
I'm i'm looking for a bolo
Bolo cholo or whatever gifted like five times
Is that wait they can do that is that possible hold on has he you've been you've been gifted a sub more than once
After this stream, uh, he'll never have to manually subscribe to you again
That's so funny
Hey, let me get let me take care of
Hey non-subs out
Uh, this is leading to nowhere kind of up here where I am. This is really weird
That is really weird
See for context guys, you actually can't play with germa unless you're subscribed to him. That's why I still have myself
Found it
Subs
Yeah, it's subs. No, you got
What all right, why did that just happen to us did you just do that it was like a gas
It's the gas knocked us off the the ledge. Oh, ow
Yum
Actually, never mind. Take it back instead cinnamon flavor
You know like the fireball candy that's what it tastes like
The firewall the fireball candy. So cinnamon forehead. Yeah, cinnamon
somebody said
Thank you, uh mini clips for the 50 dollars
And mini clips says something really funny
Hello mini i'm i'm saying thank you so much
Uh, they say this stream makes my brain want to vomit keep up the disgusting work
Is that like a a garbage pail kids quote
I think from the back of the card which pale kids. Is that like the
garbage
The patch kids. What is it the cabbage patch kids not the garbage patch kids
What's going on with this video game?
If you play it again
All right, we should we need to be together
I need to talk to you know, like just make this happen
And we got it. We got to be collecting the leg these bombs these guys
Like great person get this out of here. It's like the vacuum
I hear the beeping up here. Why are we collecting this because it's umami
Well, what does it do?
Uh, it's like, uh, just give you uh, it's uh gives you resources for upgrading and stuff
I don't get it
Oh, remember riding on the zipline back and forth to avoid enemies
Yeah, it's gonna hurt
It's okay
Um, my mom's in the chat everyone no more swears
I love you mama b
Your mom is your mom actually in the chat?
Yeah
For like for real
Yeah, hey
Hey, uh, your son's been really good today at this game
But uh, we've had some problems that i'd like to address after the stream is over
There's some issues
Uh, I don't think you're aware of that. He's playing well with others
and
We want to do something about it on a more private basis. Oh, you're gonna find another school
Just put
We gotta go get that supply thing down. There's a mule down there and we need to it's beeping
I'm gonna say you're not aware of this, but um, my mom likes germa more than me
that's
Actually true
It's not true. That's not true. It is
No, it's not true
I asked her what like my favorite her favorite video of mine was and she named one of your videos
Were you at least in the video I think so
Was I at least in the video
Uh, what if you wanted rat burger?
I mean, but that is like I mean, it's a classic
No
Now this dirt over here rat burger is classic
I need i'm going down there to get that thing
Oh god
Oh, here's the thing
Yeah, i'm that's what i'm doing down here
This is so awkward
Is there a way to find the broken? Uh
All right. I'm currently near one right now mules, but like is it on the map or
Um, I it just beeps. It's like
Yeah, it's on the map
But see you see where I am over here
It's in this little cave, but all the parts are above it above this cave
I'm gonna i'm gonna need
Some i'm probably gonna alert a horde when I do this
I'm grappled to the air good
Okay, and uh
fellas
This is probably gonna have to be my last game because I have to take auto to the vet
What a likely story
Like my mom shows up and suddenly you have you have to like leave
Oh and like oh she's leaving at the same time, too
Oh, nothing's going on here
What the fuck are you saying right now?
God
I just I just i've never heard of this dog what his name auto before now. That's all i'm saying. Yeah
Just that sounds like a story
Oh god, i'm gonna die. Oh
Just think oh he's done now. We got one mule
grenades out
Need ammo just say everything you're doing
torching
running
Leading out
This is the worst what's the worst
Robot over here is in the worst spot. It's so annoying to do this alone and no one's helping me
There's like a grapple guy that could be helping them. I'm all alone
And my mom's in the chat like yeah, my favorite stream of yours is when jerma played stardew valley
Well, you definitely would be more the clips if you were like over here
Then she might see you more when she watches his videos
What
It's a stream. I did like fucking four years ago and
what
But it is but you're not but you're not in valley after that, but you're not in that is that
Wait, i'm hold on
Words just like flipped out of my mouth. It was like I had nothing to say about it
That's why that's the point
She's a real fan
All right. We got that done
Yeah, she came here to visit was like hey check out my glue man shirt
It's pretty nice shirt
It's below us
Yeah
I found I found something
By the way, uh, those are still available. Look at me. They are here
This hit
What?
That's it. Okay
What like she's already bought one. Okay, you don't need to advertise it again, please stop
It's coming to me. It's closer. We're gonna we're gonna climb up. No, it's not you fucking tool
Where oh look it's in there
It feels like an hour it has been an hour I think
At least oh, but it's closer now
Hey, you guys are all doing great. We just had to draw this particular round out long enough mountain
Until jerma has to go
So we're like doing exactly right we're doing it yeah, we're doing it right
All right. Give me a chance to redeem myself. Okay, here it is
You guys are what are you guys even up to over here?
I feel like
Me and italics are missing. I don't know what's happening. Well, i'm gonna be honest
I've been following you guys around for about two and a half three hours. I have no idea
I've just been pretending the entire time when it's gonna land. Tell me when it's gonna land when it's gonna land
Oh, I made it
All right, where is it?
Down there somewhere
All right, i'm throwing this at stir
No, what are you doing? I don't hear the beats. I don't know where it is. You won't tell me
Well, i've marked it like six times you marked it. How do you do that?
It's up like seven cliffs from here
I'll get it
Oh is this room? We only need one more shroom and this is it right here
Can I have beyond the zipline and bring you to actually can that's really awesome?
All right marked on the map
Ronnie, no, no look
It's in that little cave. Why is it all the way up there when I throw it to the bottom?
I don't know dude
Where did I where did it go? Oh, it's there
I don't know why would I why would I throw it down there if it was all the way up here
To explain that
I don't know
Come on. Come on. Come on. I just now realized I have a shield mic
That was pretty cool. I do hear the beep now
I hear it
big brained baby
Oh
An eternity later. All right. I got the one I got one cap
So we can do this this time
Let's focus and get this done
Legally speaking I did help
Yeah, germa has to go like kiss his dog or whatever
Well, not right this second
All right, are we doing this am I pressing the button yeah here we go
Over here
The mules are fine. I don't know why it always takes germa like six tries on the side of the draw six tries to do what?
What do I have what takes me six tries?
Forget it. Just you just forget it. You know what?
Germa, yeah
If we're supposed to just both be subscribed to each other for like friendship points
Aren't we just giving twitch money?
And then jeff bezos is that much closer to ruling the world?
Yeah
I I how about this just just unsubscribe however
Did you know that if you subscribe to another streamer, it could be attacked right off
Yeah, but what if we just both unsub from each other and I just like at a convention
Just give you a 50 dollar bill. You give me a 50 dollar bill
No, listen
You unsub
And then like every once in a while you come in my chat and you say hey
Give me a sub
And you'll get one
And then
You just leave I got a pearl
That way jeff bezos daddy bezos gets his money
Get in the core bar
That's the real goal
Well, I wanna all right. How about this? How about this is how this will work
Because if we just are giving subs to each other then we're just yeah
There's no reason for that. Just you give me 50 dollars
The next time I see you
Okay, so that'll cover like the year right whatever that'll cover like just called christmas
No, but then like next year like in two years i'll give you 50 dollars and like oh let's go to lunch
You know, i'll take you to lunch
Okay, so that's it's birthdays instead like I give you 50 dollars of stuff on your birthday
And then you give me 50 dollars of stuff on my birthday. Yeah
All right, so let's just celebrate each other's birthdays then like what's the big deal? When's my birthday?
Um, when's my birthday just so I don't look like a bad person
Um, let me think um, I don't know either don't tell me don't tell me don't tell me
Docs yourself on stream
Going to like germa youtube wiki up
He doesn't know so I don't know either but like birthday dot com
It's august 8th
That's not that is definitely not true. Well, how do you know that?
Your birthday is in august
Yeah, and when is everything I know I know everything that happens in august your birthday since september august 8th
I knew your birthday. That's what i'm saying. It was august 8th. Do you you don't understand what I was playing there?
Wow, did you really just take like a one in 12 shots?
No, I knew it. No, it's august 21st. It's I was closing up
Yeah, you were close
When's talix's birthday? I want an ashley. Oh, um talix's birthday is um
I'll bet stir knows when my birthday is
No, but I know you're a draft. It's january. Um
I thought you'd know since it was last week
I know it's alex's birthday guys. Come on my birthday because that's what his mom showed. Okay. I'm sorry
Wait
That's what his mom showed up
But why would my mom come show up for your birthday people have no idea what's going on right now
I don't know what's going on anymore
All right, fine. It's alex when's burger boy's birthday. I have no idea. I've never even met burger boy
Wait
He dropped it on me for fun
What no he put it down and then you went and stood on it
What what I
I I don't believe that you couldn't know it was gonna land on you like that's a ha ha funny
I was too busy talking
That's a ha ha funny
That's definitely just a ha ha funny
All right, at least revive me so I don't don't get them up, please don't get them up somebody better
Thank you so much
He fell off the edges that he's gonna die yeah i'm getting back with all that's not you where'd you go
Wait 40 seconds. Wait, what? Oh, no. Okay. I thought we had to leave
It's like doesn't hurt at all
what
That doesn't hurt you. I mean it does but like
Barely wait. No, no, no i'm not supposed to shooting you. That's what you really want at the very end
Do not get him up get me up
He's gonna shoot me if I try to get him up. Come on. Come on ronnie. Get me up
How do I do the dance?
He's trying to take everybody out so you can't revive me
He's gonna get me
Shoot
No, don't let him get away with it italics get out here italics, I know your birthday your italics your birthdays
I made it
I'm on the ship
I want to upgrade something
Oh, look at these dead guys
No fun in the med bay
Hey, it's fun
All right. I actually do have to leave
I don't think I have time for another one
Well
Do I what time is it?
No, I don't have time for another one
I do have time to do perks and stuff though
But we just unlocked a new planet zone new egg hunt complexity
How long is it gonna take?
like six years
Which is how long it takes us to do these missions got the word complexity in the title
Will it take more than?
30 minutes
No speed run
All right. We have literally 30 but um
I still want to I still want time to do the end of the screen
Hey guy, we can do it in 20 minutes, right?
Yeah speed run 20 minutes 20 minutes 20 minute cut off
No, I got time. I got time
Just like actually do the objective and don't throw things down a hill
When did I do that?
Not talking to you. Oh, when have I ever directly talked to you?
Don't even speak to me again. I don't think i've even used the satchel charges
Well, I have a better weapon
All right, let's do it 20 minutes
Uh, I got i'm looking at the clock right now. No this I got time. I thought it was uh later than it was
Save auto give auto a scratch on the butt tell him it was from me
I will
Yeah, I I have an appointment. So it's not like um
It's not like I have to take him now or anything like doesn't point him
That's why I started so early
He's good. He's fine. Just needs to get checked out for something
Do you have any hobbies?
Do you leave your house at all?
Yeah
What are you what are you doing out there gambling reading
All right, let's go 20 minutes there's the dirt find the eggs eggs
Um
What happened to me?
I was trying to dig to the egg as fast as I could
What have I happened to speedrun
What you're the one that died i'm i'm I was trying to dig
We need eggs. Whoops. The eggs look like
Going to the first one down here
first egg is
Is this the egg?
No, this is like spaghetti. Oh a little bit more
Egg
I recently watched that video
Again
All right with the egg
It's like right around us here somewhere like above us
egg
Eggu
I know it's on the map. I see it. It's just somewhere in here. It's like right here inside these tentacles
I'm pretty sure they're just like the uh pearls
Cool one egg
What why is it world shaking?
Oh because they don't like it when you take their eggs. All right next one
I'm gonna find my way to the next one
There's some weird thing over here. I don't know if it's an egg
Yeah, there's one up this way
Here follow me
Oh god, this is so stupid. I didn't know I knew
Oh, there's a bush over here red bush thing over here
Where is the supply bush?
nitrous full
Shit is he is the mule being taken?
We got we got a big bug problem. Oh my god
Yeah, i'm up here on the cliff doing what I can
Oh boy, this is not good
Even even if you run sometimes you gotta kill enemies
Sometimes i'm going like crazy
Um, is there a reason why you're mining and not like helping everybody waiting for the enemies to come up here
So I can go down there and resurrect you. Um, just
He's playing like a clicker game
I don't buy it until I see it
Are you getting shot by like our friendly bot? No, it is not a friendly bot
There is a super giant robot that is shooting everyone down here, which is why we're all dead
And it doesn't like oh my god i'm dead
Oh now it has a health bar. That's a lot of health
There's nowhere to really run
Ah, man, it looks like we're losing. I think there's the way to the bot. You gotta kill the bot. Kill the bot
I've done so fast. I have so much health I can't
So that's what what was happening. All right
Well, let's see what my real problem was as I res germa first again. Look guys. We really tried this time
Okay, swear. I mean that that's that's like that that that's not true. But what happened actually was
Um, we did nobody knew that we had to kill the robot that was running out loud said wow, that's a corrupted bot
I think it was muted. Did you shoot?
I didn't see you shoot at it. Uh
I've been shooting it
Oh now you are a squad stream. You can all see that i've been shooting it
I'm gonna get your germ
Thanks, ronny. Just gotta set my thing up here
Damn, I keep getting froze
I'm gonna kind of dig myself in a hole so I can have some cover star. Did you beat sekiro?
Uh, I got the last loss. I honestly I hate that game
Did you put on passion?
So I did not want to
Spend the time on the last guy
I'm trying to risk hold on
So so sure you can say not you're the better the game. You're a better gamer
I just was scared. I did it. I just I was curious to play it
I didn't get your thoughts on it
My thoughts I didn't get your thoughts apparently you don't like it
No
Whoa, that kind of hurts my head. Oh god. This guy looks like short circuit
Oh
All right, it's dead
Restart it. Yes. Let's repair our enemy
But oh shoot is it a walking turret now without uh without any like obviously spoilers. I think it took me like
what 50
60 attempts at that final boss
That's insane
There's a final boss spoiler
Spoiler
Well, I didn't want to say what it is
Did you fight like?
Did you fight? Um, he's already
The big red fire demon. Yes
Okay, i'm not digging out of here
Only two out of six eggs. How long has it been?
I don't know. I was reading chat
I don't even know where I am
It's too dark
All right. We do we have we have we have we need one more egg in this area
Go over here. Where is it?
Yeah, I do. There's one up. There's one down. I'm gonna I'm gonna get the one that's up
That is weird. I have yet to see an egg. I have no idea what they look like inside the giant flesh ball
You have to dig and there's eggs inside of them
But if you press the tab on your map it shows you exactly where they are
And then you have to dig into
All right, what was that one?
low
Anyone keeping track of how many times i've explained this what the fuck did you get it? Um at least one
Oh, did you what'd you do with it?
How did you get in here back that way dude, it's i'm fucking in the room of mirrors right now
Oh
No, wait, why what the fuck
Goddamn minecraft. Oh shit. All right, i'm fine
Uh, we're gonna need
Pretty much everything i'm on it
Okay
I'm gaming with the where's the last two?
But they're like up this way
You're voting to kick me
I own I own the server
It's gonna take more than that
What is this bot doing? Because I have not seen it shooting at any bugs. It's kind of running around
Oh, i'm skiing around now
Yeah lag guy uses god mode in his own server
All right, this is really weird. I really am on skis
Um, it's ice
Yeah, it's gonna say aren't you from uh, boston. It's ice
I thought I was in boston. I thought I would like it
Uh, is there one more I can get that you have not got i'm gonna just go to the one behind me
There's two behind me here
This game reminds me of like war frame
War frame
Yeah, because you drop in you do an objective you're with four other people or three people
And he's like, oh you got you got to hack like three nodes and you're like, how did I hack three of them?
What did everyone else do?
I'm over on this too. I'm getting gold
Good job
Have you had prior experience though in warframe? I didn't have any experience. Actually. No, I did
I played for like five minutes with you and said no
Uh, not that the game is bad. I just was like no i'm all right
I just do you have a swarm on the way. All right. This is bad just protect
We have a supply
Uh, I called one down earlier
So it's it's way over there war frame is really really cool. I just couldn't get into it
Should we stick together for this swarm? We only need one more egg
And it's above four out of six eggs. Yeah, but there's one there's one thrown down. There's one up here
You're gonna break the egg
We'll throw the other egg down here then I mean I have another one. I don't want to go get it
It's up above us. It's like I don't want to go get it
It was like a swarm coming you want to get stuck in a hole somewhere and die
Oh now the uh, the the big monster tank is shooting things
All right, i'll go now. So where is it? I don't see it on the map. Oh, it's up this way
I'm gonna go try to get it
I mean I am the drill guy
What I can't go through this
um, okay weird
Why you're almost through the wave
I'm trying to go up trying to go through it. I don't have any fuel shit. That's why
That's all right. He can do it. He's played warframe before
Very good. Very good job. Very good
He turned around
Good
Where is the aforementioned supply pod?
What there is not a supply pod, I don't think
There it is
Where is it down?
All we have to do now is leave
Oh, I have zero bullets. So
Let's get some bullets excellent
Eggs excellent get it
egg
Egg
Egg there we go. That was better
Kind of hybrid everyone's right here. So we don't even have to go far
Stuart can you tell italics that he's the sexiest dreamer here for me
Wow
I mean, I already knew that but it still helps to hear
Uh, that was my mom. It's bullshit, by the way
I thought star's the only one up there
I was
He's just kind of we're just like playing
Hide and go seek down here
I think what's actually happening is we're all relying on someone else to lead so we can follow and read chat
So when all of us just read chat
We just walk in circles like we're talking on the phone. How many of the eggs did I deposit?
two
Fuck you. I'm seeing two. I'm seeing a bunch of twos. I'm seeing
I'm seeing a bunch of twos. Everyone in chat is running you put in like plus two you did two
He definitely gives one look at my chat. That's my chat is all saying six out of six
I don't know, but I don't think so
I don't think so
I just figured out what you're doing
Sir was trying to kill me like i'm just standing there letting him shoot me because i'm that kind of guy
And he's trying to kill me before I get in the pot
Go kill kill start kill start get him. He's not gonna get away with this shit kill start now
Everyone focus all fire
Now get him
Hey
It's like crime outline is just down there
Oh my head hurt. Oh
This friggin dead guy. Come on
Yeah, so
it shows
How many eggs?
For the love of god, can you please go?
Take care of your dog. I'm I know
I don't know. That's exactly what's happening. I'm so worried about him. He's fine
Yeah, just another speed run speed run no, no
Was like at least 15 minutes ago. He's just really addicted to this game
That's right tantrum
All right. Can I can can somebody buy a drink before we go?
All right. I'm gonna buy a round
Hey that was mine
Hey, wow, these are mine
Get out of the way
What about mine? I want one
Uh, so when to see a thief stream
Yeah, see him feel what stream and I can smash it
Yeah
Thank you so much for watching everybody. That's gonna be our time here
That was
deep rock galactic
Checks notes
My name is jerman95 subscribed if you had fun watching this video
Play us out here
Hold on. Hold on. We can't end yet. I gotta tell you guys about my patreon that we're running here
Okay
We do a lot of good stuff here every month and uh for a small price
You could get some special perks that you could only get here on patreon. We've got special videos
We've got special streams. We've got limited edition pins
Let me tell you about our sponsor square space
Even though you knew how to make a web page 20 years ago. We're acting like it's a brand new freaking mystery
All right. Bye guys
Thank you to ronnie. It's alex
Stir is it stir or star or what do we call you now? What do you what do you want to be called now daddy?
That's the third time you've made that like kind of weird reference during this just want to make sure everyone's where that's number three
It's not weird if it's three then it's just like that's my thing. This is the thing you do accept that
All right. Well, thank you. Uh, thank you stir. You're gonna be calling me daddy after this stream
Okay, there's not there's another one. No, i'm not gonna uh, all right
Ronnie hey was great playing with you ronnie
Yeah, sure. Sure. Go uh
I'll take auto to the vet. I guess is what you're definitely doing
Yeah, I love you germ germ. Wait. Well, are you are you implying that like i'm not going to do that?
And i'm just making that i'm making this up alex just said he said you were gonna be calling him daddy
I was talking to you. I just left i'm not I I ain't doing that anymore. Uh
Thanks for watching everybody
A little bit on the shorter side today
but auto kind of
unexpectedly needs to um
Go to the vet. He's having some skin issues and I don't want to
have it just kind of
Fester so I want to get him in there
But uh, i'll see you tomorrow tomorrow. We're gonna do the movies again and we're gonna try some mods
Uh, probably starting
Around the normal time tomorrow. Maybe not maybe i'll start early tomorrow as well
We'll see not that early not as early as I started I started like 11 30
This morning, but maybe a couple hours early tomorrow. We'll see
But uh, I am going to the we only have we don't have very many bits
So I got time to do it. I want to make sure I got out of there to be able to do it
That was fun. That was deep rock galactic actually was pretty fun
It's a nice take
On like the left for dead model
But let's go back to a few hours ago here. We had elizabeth for three bucks
Uh, hello
I just wanted to chip in and say that I recently got my dream job as a community manager for a game dev
Which also is sister company with the ones who publish deep rock
Pogchamp so cool to see you play and loving all your streams. Oh, that's awesome
That's really really cool
Congratulations on that. Thank you so much for the three bucks. Hell. Yeah
That was uh elizabeth deep rock galactic germa lied about the clown card gave five community subs earlier. Thanks for that
Didn't catch it. It's too busy being
captured and soundboarded
Smilio, thanks for the five dollars. Hey germa. Hope i'm doing this right since it's my first time donating
Hopefully of many since I figure I start I should start to pay you back for all the laughs since I started watching you in
early 2013
I have a question if that's okay
I'm lucky enough to be visiting america for the first time boston specifically
And I was wondering if you had any tips places to go things to do etc
um
For boston, I mean the museum of science is awesome if you've never been
boston museum of science is really really cool a lot of interesting things to see and do there
museum museum
Yeah, it is an awesome place if you have some time you could spend
All day there you could spend more than one two three days there
So if somebody that was coming
To america to boston
That's probably the first thing I would tell them to do yeah. Faneuil hall is awesome, too
A lot of shopping a lot of great restaurants there
Yeah, there's a lot of cool things to do the north end has some of the best italian
food and
little eateries
In the state, so if you ever find yourself in the north end
There's a lot of cool things in boston, but um, hope you have fun
I hope you have a good visit to
the
United states of america. Thank you for the five dollars milio
Fine every man. Thanks for three dollars and 77 cents
Thanks to the eu stream nice to get to be around for a stream once in a while
Especially when it's a co-op one
Yeah, no, it's good to do just hang out and chill and
Stick around with some friends and have fun, right?
It's good shit
by the way, that was
I don't you all know who they are but
Go give them a follow. They're all good people
Star italics, uh ronnie and much as ronnie stream
He might
I think he does
Sometimes at least
But thank you binary man
Uh, thank you the yellowest for the four dollars germa. I just got a job. Can I uh get some pog champ pog champs in the chat?
Yeah, hell, yeah
Another another job
That's two jobs
No, congrats
Awesome. Awesome stuff
Thank you so much yellowist with four dollars
Dork cube. Thanks for the 250
Germa love your streams. They always make me twerk. It's actually become a bit of an issue
I'll be watching you do your thing with your wonderfully twisted brand of humor
When suddenly my mom comes in with my tendies and she sees me twerking, but it's not like she doesn't approve of my
Shaking. In fact, she's a bit supportive
She thinks I should quit my delivery job and just do twerking full time. I don't know where I could get paid
Thank you for the 250
Appreciate it. Thank you stir stir with 30 dollars 30 bucks from stir
Hey, thanks a lot stir
That's a very then they say love you. Wow
Yeah, oh thanks appreciate it
And then a and he got yeah gifted a sub too
Dragon breath. Thanks for the 250 you and star in italics need to play battle block theater
The stream had me in tears in these they are my favorite streams. Love you
Yeah, it's fun to get the gang together
I'm sure we'll do it again soon. It's always a good time
I'll see if they want to do anything else in the coming weeks, you know
But thank you so much for the 250 dragon breath
Definitely mini clips gave 50 dollars
We touched upon it, but this stream makes my brain want to vomit keep up the disgusting work
I'm going to keep the disgusting work up
Hopefully it grosses you out even more
Thank you for the 50 dollars mini clips
Ipod matt thanks for five dollars free ipod link click here for a free free online fast and easy ipod touch nano macbook
It's easy and free and online click here for a free ipod for your chance to win for real though
What was your first ipod? Mine was the first gen ipod nano
I didn't have an ipod
I had a zoom and that's not a joke
But thank you ipod matt. I hope you enjoy your ipod
Yeah, this that was nothing wrong with the zoom
People think that's a joke though when you tell them that
But thank you. Thank you marvosh mcgally for the 250. Thanks for the eu stream
Sure for sure
If I do them and i'm able to do them and I can kind of change the schedule around and
I mean obviously this stream was eu friendly
Not out of essentially choice, but out of necessity
But it's nice to do them every so often i'm gonna get the credits to roll by here
Thank you to all the subs
All the resubs on new subs tonight today. No, it's today. I forgot them and it's like four o'clock in the afternoon
Thanks guys
Thank you so much. I will see you tomorrow
We're gonna let this play out while I go over the last three or four bits here
And i'm right on time for auto's appointment. So don't worry. I ended at the perfect time, but thank you
uh
to
origin
Three for the ten bucks
Stop reading this go save auto
He's gonna be all right. He's fine
He has an appointment and i'm gonna take a do it and i'm gonna be right on time for it. Don't worry
Thank you for the ten dollars though. That's ten bucks. Thank you
Freudian weapon. Thanks for the 450. No messages 450. Thank you for audience
Appreciate that
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
Anybody see star's name yet?
I didn't i haven't seen it pop up
We have to get documented evidence that it's happened
Because I we needed the date
God he's got me. He's in my head now. I like i'm thinking about me doing that and it's happening
He's in there. He's in there like laughing and mocking me right now
Uh, no, that was fun. He's in there rent free. Yeah
He cancelled the sub. No, he didn't it was a gift. It's you can't cancel a gifted sub. Can you?
You can't go into your account and cancel a gift sub
Is that impossible?
You can
Oh shit
Did he?
I wasn't looking in the first
15 seconds of the credits
What if he cancelled his sub to have like the token to give to somebody else?
That's so funny
Is he uh, is he still going? Is he still is he gonna be screaming still for uh, he is still going
Well, let's just raid him
Did I miss it? Did it happen?
All right, it happened. All right. Well, we just look just real raid star. He's just still going
so
Even if he goes for like not that much longer, whatever
Y'all were just watching him anyways, right?
All right, let's raid star and admit be like yay like scream and like do a bunch of fucking emotes and stuff
Taleks and star back to back. That's fucking hilarious
All right, guys, I will see you tomorrow. We're gonna play the movies again. We're gonna do some mods
and hopefully it's a
Fun time after that you won't see me for a little while, but
I'll be here in spirit
Take care guys. Let's raid
stir
Let's do it. Why not?
And tell him germa985 sent you. All right guys
See you tomorrow. Take care
Goodbye. Oh, yeah, I will do stream legends. I will see you tomorrow