Hello, good afternoon or good morning, those of you on the west coast, like me. How are you?
We are back again. Fun filled day of streaming on twitch.tv. People are calling me a liar already.
I haven't even spoken. I haven't even talked yet. Can you read my mind? Can you read my lie mind?
I'm a lied about house flipper. We're playing desperados three today. Don't exactly know where
you're getting that from. I'm checking on you. Take off the diaper. Hold on. What? Look,
click link, click link. I don't want to. What is this? I don't want to click this.
What is this? I don't think so. When does that? When does a house flippers DLC come up?
No, I didn't. They're doing like an HGTV thing, right? Is that out? I gotta fucking play this.
All right. All right. All right. Right. How about this? I'll give you a date on Wednesday,
the 19th of August. I will play house flippers, HGTV, fucking DLC. Okay. It doesn't matter what
the fuck I'm doing on Wednesday. Whatever it is, it's off the table. That's in like a few weeks.
Okay. Well, whatever. I was going to, I really wanted to play desperados three today.
That's it's off the table now. Right. It's today, the 19th. Today's the night. All right.
You promised you promised. All right. All right. I don't, whatever. If I'm going to be held to my
word, which I hope I am, I'm going to play house flippers, HGTV, DLC. I got to be held to my word.
All right. Well, I had this whole cowboy costume over here that I was going to put on today.
Are you sure? I do. Okay. Looks like I'm just going to return it while you play house flippers.
That would just be odd. Why would I be dressed up as a cowboy? I guess I'm that's I just maybe
I'm just a cowboy. Who cares? Turn your cam on. Turn your cam on. I why make a cowboy house?
No, that's too easy. That's too easy. Put on comedy. Hold on. I got to, I got to change the
title. God, you know, I got to be held to my promises about it's HGTV, right? TV ready homes.
Is that good? TV ready homes, house flipper. Good thing I own this shit already. Good thing. I
already own this DLC about the whole thing. I bought everything. Yeah. And don't let, let,
I want you to show people this when they say this dude doesn't do what he says. He does. He
does not go back on his word. If he says he's going to play a game, he's going to play it.
Like he, if he says he's going to play a game tomorrow, he's going to do it.
Just get this open. Hold on. All right. Let's, let's go. We're going to play house flippers.
DLC play saw then I never promised anything with saw. So I had no promises. Hey, look,
there it is. House flipper. You guys remember this game? Oh, well, let's take a look around our,
a double. He's a double liar, but he can do resident evil four. That's probably never going
to happen unless it's on the Wii. The PC one I thought was going to make me sick, but hey,
take a look at this, right? Oh, let's get it. Uh, those last time we played house flipper, HGTV.
Well, this is the house. This is garden flipper. Actually. Last time we played this, I made this
sick garden. Remember this is the old house. I don't know why I just, I thought just said
or wallet out like dump money in here. This is pretty sick. Oh yeah. Right. It's the family guy
house. This is supposed to be the Griffin house. I forgot. This is an expensive ass house. What
else? What else is back here? Oh yeah. The AOL. Oh, right. The projector, right? We're going to,
it's going to be movie night. You can come park and watch TV, make pizzas. I forgot about this
game. I love this game. All right, let's go. There's a kiddie pool, another pond with some seagulls,
picnic table. What else is back here? The grill, right? Nice. That's a pretty good gamer. That's a
gamer fridge. That's a huge gamer fridge. Stove. Here are the seats. And don't, aren't these
actually connected to plumbing too, by the way? Those even give you, you think this is just a
funny joke for the stream. So there's actual plumbing down here. I remember that. Big bean bag
chair. It's a cool color scheme. I forgot about this. I gotta, let me look around. Oh yeah. There's
two toilets. I gotta remember this. This is my, this is my design philosophy. Eat while you shit,
technically. Why are there three sinks? Because it's like a public restroom. What the hell is
going on up here? Oh, that's right. The pool was too expensive. So I made just one of those
swim forward while the current tries to take you machines. Oh, this is where it happened, right?
This is where it was. I feel like if it's an old historic house, like an old streamer house,
this is where he did the worst impression of 2018. Yeah. I remember it. It was right here. Wow.
This is super historic. All right. Let's keep going. Let's go do the new, uh, DLC. Where is it?
Okay. Map of jobs. This is not realistic. That number is not 580. Boy, they give you like a
Sims map now. HGTV. Is this like a, this is, but they're not like, are there police over here?
Why is there police everywhere? Okay. Is this the one? Job, a new beginning. Welcome to your
first job in Sunset Bay. Are you ready to help John and Nicole renovate the house of their dreams?
While the house is small, the view is amazing. You'll have to make some decisions when it comes
to room arrangement. The shack under the house is especially problematic. Good luck. There's four
people buried there. Only got 6,500 bucks. Go to the Simpsons house. Omega-Lel, his fucking brain.
Omega-Lel, Omega-Lel. What the fuck? But I'm going to record myself be saying I'm going to
play house with my 19th. And then you guys can click link to it. I'll be like, fuck, right. Well,
sorry guys. You know, okay. Here's the thing. Really? Like they teach like this type of photo
manipulation in the fourth grade now. Really guys? You honestly, this is like, you can do this in 15
seconds. In fact, it took you a while to do that. Actually it's been 10 minutes and we get this now.
Okay. So yeah, so fake. Omega-Lel doctored. He's not wrong, chat. Are these people on HGTV?
Is this a show? Are these people on a show on HGTV? Or did HGTV just hand their logo to the
house flipper guys and just said, yeah, just put it on there. What does this have to do with HGTV?
Okay. Welcome to your first job. Are you ready to help John and Nicole renovate the house of
their dreams? Oh yeah. Okay. I got 6,500 bucks. I got 6,500 dollars. This is what I have to work
with. When you work on jobs in Sunset Bay, there is a specific budget defined for each one. It's
the amount of money that the family is willing to spend on their dream house. Remember to stay
within the budget while renovating. Oh, their dream house. What a dream house. Wait, did you guys
start the renovation and then just dad just kind of started living out here? What the fuck is this?
6,500 bucks. All right. What this looks like is this looks like like dad built this part of the
house himself and we have like a Hansel and Gretel trail of how he started to get really exhausted
and fucked the whole thing up. It led into here and then he got like shitfaced and threw the
remaining wood into the shed. I can't do this. I'm already like 80 grand in the hole. Get the HGTV
guys to come. Just have them come fix it. Just look, I promise I'll cry when you reveal the house
if you come and do it, please. I promise I'll do a massive Pog face when you reveal. I'll freak out.
I'll sprint in a circle and scream. I'll take my shirt off and just sprint around yelling. I'll
take both my hands and grab the Camberman's lens, pull it in and go. Yeah, 6,500 bucks. This doesn't
cost any money, right? Keep your shirt on TOS. This is not me doing this. Okay, so I have to
what do they want? Look at the tablet for a second. All right, first floor. Remove the trash.
Make a decision in room 4M squared. Clean dirt. Okay, make a decision. Let's go make a decision.
What room does it want me to do? Okay, there's a lot of bugs in this house. What decision do they
want? Okay, make a decision. Definitely a TV. The room feels so empty without it. We can also add
some decorations, a carpet, and a few potted plants. A fireplace could make this room feel
more complete. A large corner electric fireplace. No, no, no, no. I don't care. I'm not doing an
electric fireplace. No way. I don't even care what the other one is. I'm sorry, guys. Something about
flicking a switch and fire starts in my house. I don't want that. That's dangerous to me. You
don't flick a switch and your oven goes to 500 degrees. Nope. I wouldn't want that either. All
right, let's clean. Easy. Yes, you would. I would not want that. That's terrifying. Who wants an
oven that if you hit the on button is instantly 500 degrees? That's terrifying. All right, hold
on. A living room. Chandelier with bulbs. Let's get rid of this fucking thing. What do you want
to do with it? Remove object. Oh, okay. Wardrobe Drenemo. Is this a wardrobe Drenemo? Which one?
This one? Let's clean this place up first. What? Why is everybody flicking things? What is all this?
Okay, hold on. I need to go over this because this is fucking me up. This is freaking me out.
I need to go over this. Address it. Address it. Address it. Address it. Just hold on. I'm
going to address it. That's not it. Yeah, I did it. Yeah, whatever. That's me addressing it. All
right. Well, let me see. I don't even know what this is. What the fuck is this? Shit. What do I
even save it as? All right. Address it. Address it. Address it. Address it. I'm addressing it.
Easy Bake Hard Mode. Why are you watching that? Okay, here we go. Let me shrink this a little bit.
Dremeloogs. A fake website. What is that website? I don't want that website. I don't want my logs.
I don't know what to delete. That's a good one. What if you just tell the truth? Yeah, I mean,
that's true. Play disk skipping noises. Say I dropped it down the stairs. Floppy disk sounds.
Ha ha ha. That's so stupid. Yeah, say you heard it. I showed it off on Periscope.
Ah, no shit. Okay, hold on. This is like next level faking people's with it saying,
I'm going to record myself and play house flipper. Yeah. Inspect element. Yeah. And then you guys can
link to it. Yeah. Oh, wait a minute. I'll get a good one. Okay. I'm rendering the clip. I need
to Twitch clip of this. I mean, you guys are really, you guys are really trying at this point,
but the fake website, the fake fucking text, the fake everything, fake text, inspect element. Yeah,
it was fake. I don't even need to inspect element. I got fucking online x-ray vision.
Just wait till they make that shit. Just wait till you're going to have to have online x-ray
vision. It's a button like an extension you're going to have to play to see like if the website's
even fucking real. We're getting real fucked up in 10 years. It's a nice bathtub. Link spam. Funny
link. Nah, whatever. All right. Let me, I got a living room. I have $300,000. Why do I need $6,500?
Okay. Where's this wardrobe? Is this a wardrobe? What is this? This is a wardrobe, right? Well,
it's ugly. Get rid of it. Right. Wardrobe. All right. There we go. Clean the windows. Oh,
this is my favorite part of this game. I fucking love this. Oh, it just does it for me. Oh yeah.
Thermal. That was real. It's a hundred percent real. You're a liar. Ask me if I'm a liar again.
Say, did you say, did you lie about the clip? What's the question? Did I lie about the clip?
Well, the thing is we have to take care of everybody. We have to make sure that we get
down with our hands dirty and we get everybody on the right page. I also think that we can make
it happen as long as you stick with me. There you go. Here's your answer. Senator Albertson,
have you ever eaten glass for fun? Here's the thing. My favorite dog that I've ever had
was little Fido. And I'll tell you, he was a good dog. I'm a good dog. And if I can be your senator
again, I would be such a good boy. Senator Albertson, is there a, is there a full shit
in your underwear right fucking now, right now? Yes or no. You know, the tricky thing about trying
to fix this country is just my goodness. We got to get everybody back to work. I will yield the rest
of my time. He has my vote. You can't yield time in an interview. Yes, you can. It's called,
I'm just going to stop talking and stare at the camera until they ask another question. Turn that
off. I hate ovens. You get interviewed and you say I'm doing the fifth amendment. Mr. Albertson,
I just want to ask about the potential controversy where you chugged an entire Gatorade as fast as
you could on camera for a bunch of people. And you thought it was like funny. And then you like
burped really loud. Mr. Albertson, what can you tell me about school? Well, think about school.
We got to really get in there and I'm going to change everything about, we got to get, we got
to reform our schools. We got to make sure everyone's prepared. Absolutely. Mr. Albertson,
there's a video of you punching a guy in the face at a bar in downtown Boston. You did that
fucking all day. I just like fucking, I should like, all right, I got to play the game of like
getting to the sidetrack. All right. Adam Chandler, TV corner cabinet. What's a TV corner cabinet?
All right. Well, where's, where's the couch? This is way too far away. You can't see shit from here.
You want the TV over here? Uh, wait, next to the people are going to be like walking in the way
and shit. Why would you ever want that? You want an Adam Chandler. Okay. Well, let's put the TV in
the shitty place they want it. Clean this. Wait, there's one more window I didn't clean. I forgot
one window. I forgot. Where is it? It's got ADHD. Yeah. Oh shit. Fuck. I actually answered the
question. No, I was supposed to tell you how we were going to fix our schools. Shit. Oh well.
Place object. All right. What do we got? TV. Buy. Buy many. $700. How big is this thing?
This is 700 bucks. Okay. Well, we'll figure it out later. What a terrible setup. Now I know this
setup. I know this exact setup. This is, I just moved into a new place and two months later,
still kind of don't give a shit about this. And it's a pain in the ass, but I'm still, I'm going
to do it. I don't even care. Yeah. Eventually I'll get something to put that on, but like,
I don't care. I will maybe. Thanks for being with us. That's a pretty cool like streamer end card.
Okay. So now I need a TV corner cabinet. Is that what this is? Okay. What color? All right. How
about just bright red? Wait, that would be infuriating. Okay. Imagine buying this and
this is the place that you really thought it was going to be. And your heart was set on this.
And now you go, no, I didn't measure it right. Fuck I have, but it has to stay. I'll have to
deal with it. I'll deal with it. I'll just deal with it. You hate it every day, but you know what?
You're going to buy a new one, return it, have them, the guys that brought this thing in,
you're going to have them bring it out. No, you have to deal with it. God moving sucks.
So does this, by the way, this sucks. What is it? Who's who can watch this? You have to be sitting
here. Wait, no, I get it. Okay. So wait, nevermind. I thought this is a bathroom. I was going to say
that makes sense. It's fine. This isn't, this is not fine. Why would you sit at a viewing angle
permanently at like 30, 40 degrees? This is not fine. You have to sit here and like watch the TV.
No, you need to be facing forward, facing Adam chandelier. Okay. You want two of these. This is
like, uh, you can't even, I can't even, whatever. All right. What do you want this? A rectangular
carpet. Let's do gray. Gray goes with everything. I don't, I don't like how this is set up. How are
you supposed to sit here and eat dinner? You can't like sit there and eat dinner on this. How do you
only work in gray scale? You design, it's a, this is a living room. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm sorry. I am going to tell you guys the age of sitting at the dining table is over. Us,
the younger generation, that shit's over. The new dinner table is the coffee table in front of the
TV. They're a dinner table for what? To throw all your mail, to like stack a bunch of shit.
And then you get pissed off in six months when there's shit all over the table. Dining room table
is just totally like 2010 and before. This is the new dinner table. Everybody gets out, sits in on
the table, on the couch. Everyone's just eating off the, everyone's like, yeah, put it on, put
SpongeBob on. It's like, oh, I love it. I watch you. Do you know what I watch? I watch, am I weird?
Let me ask you this. So this is a YouTube channel. It's called The Wolf Pit and the guy reviews like
frozen, like $1 dinners and TV dinners and stuff. And I watch this guy when I eat food. He's like
going over how like disgusting it is and like, oh, this is like a $1 TV dinner I got from like
the dollar store or something. And I'm just eating food going, oh, cool. Am I weird? Does that make
me a weird person? Yes. It doesn't matter what I'm eating. I could be eating like McDonald's or I
could be eating like a steak. It doesn't, it doesn't matter what it is. I'm going to watch this channel.
All right. We know two of those. Where'd you, why would you want, oh, underneath the table.
That's never going to get used. And then a Zamiya plant. Okay. I want, why many? Dude. All right.
Can I tell you something about big plants? I'm really telling you something about stuff today,
huh? Let me tell you something about X. I think these just get in the way. They look cool, I guess,
but I feel like they just get in the way. Where am I? What do I put this? What's this? What? This
is just clearly just in the way. You're going to, something's going to be on this table and you're
going to bump into this once and it's going to infuriate you. What do you do with this?
It's a Seinfeld joke. Hey, Seinfeld is a legendary show. All right. That doesn't bother me. All right.
Living room. We got it. Progress. I have $4,900 left. Okay. Let's keep doing this. Second floor,
living room with kitchenette, garden, remove the trash. All right. You want to make a decision in
this room down here. Let's go. This is fine. Look, we're trying to make a little bit more,
make the bed. I shouldn't have even done that. Who makes beds? My pillows are just on the ground
every single night and I just pick them back up and go back and go to bed. Yeah. You're a slob.
Yeah. Yeah. Whatever. Wasn't there one down here? Okay. Make a decision. Sauna and a bathroom. Being
able to hop in the sauna. What? You can make a sauna? Just cleaning it up will suffice. This is
a very capable storage room. Isn't the sauna expensive? How much is a sauna? Are you sure?
Why am I getting, who wants to be a millionaire? This is too, this is too much money.
Why would you want a sauna down here? That's actually weird. Isn't that strange? What's this
guy do down here? Oh, I got to clean. Hey, an anonymous gifter. Thanks for the five subs and
atmosphere starfish. Thanks for the five subs as well. What is he building in here? I don't know,
man. Can I just sell this whole thing? Yeah, I can. What am I doing? Can't sell trash though.
You can now finish incomplete jobs. I'm going to finish it. Wait, they ordered a sauna and I get
to just leave? Yeah. And I think down here I want it to be red. And I think over here,
the wall should be gray. Put a couple of carpets down. We want a sauna down here. Okay.
Let's just leave. And I never come back. I gave up. Guys, I gave up on you when you wanted
TV in the corner. That stupid thing. I need a dining table. All right. That's it for the trash.
Four dollars and 42 cents. All right. Literally all city contractors. So what do I need a sledgehammer
for? I don't even have, why do I not have a sledgehammer? Lay floor tiles. Where's my
sledgehammer? 80, 100. Where's my sledgehammer? I sold the sledgehammer. No, that's not how that
works though. Sink plumb. Oh, maybe I don't have to do it. Okay. Scenic sauna heater. That's a sauna
operate. Sauna. Scenic sauna heater. This is 420 bucks. All right. Where does this go? Lay floor
tiles. Oh, I need floor tiles. Okay. Hold on. What do they want for tiles? Floor tiles. What do you
think would look good in a sauna? That's my opinion on rhinos. They're very dangerous. They're
very cool though. They can go very fast. Oh, I like the gray bubble tiles. What do you guys think?
Fuck. I do like gray, huh? I can't help it. It just, I like it. It goes with everything.
I have a Squidward house. It's fine. Ceramic brown rectangles. Oh no. We've spent the money already.
Wait, can I sell it? Can I sell it? How much do I sell it for? Oh no. I have to go over the tiles
with other tiles. Great. What the hell was it called? Floor tiles. Whatever. Where is it brown?
What? Ceramic tiles brown. What? Why is this wrong? Floor panel dark? Hold on. What is going on?
Wait, it's different rooms. I thought this whole thing was a sauna. I was going to put a toilet
here. Okay. Brown rectangles. I don't even have the right thing. Yes, I do. Okay. Here we go.
All right. There we are. Going a little over budget, but it happens. Which room is this one?
Is this brown tile inside? Okay. Floor panel dark. Just wait till I can make my own house.
Poop line sauna. What was it called? Dark. Floor panel dark. Is this the my summer house sauna?
You know, somebody said to play that game. It's been significantly updated or something
since the last time I played it. All right. There we go. Now I need the scenic sauna heater.
Okay. Which one is the sauna? This is the sauna. Okay. Sauna bench. Sauna bench. Okay. What about
the galaxy? What about the galaxy brain sauna heater? Isn't that one better? Wait, I need two
of these. Okay. You sit down here. Corner sauna bench. Sauna bucket with ladle. There's not room
for this stuff in here. Oh yeah. Right. Cause you go with the on the rocks, right? Right. Sauna bench.
No, no, that's not right. Sauna. Sauna. Corner bench. Why do you need this? Are this many people
going to sit in here like naked? I don't understand. How many people do you want to come in here?
One, two, three, four, five, six, six people in here. This is a one person sauna. Another corner
sauna bench. Look, we'll just stadium seated like they do somewhere there. You're going to sit up
here and your legs are going to be just dangling down here. And there's a guy going to be sitting
right here. This doesn't work. Can I put a sign up that says like must wear clothes? Like, can I
probably like must be fully clothed or something? What do you mean? No, you don't have to go into a
sauna nude. You can go in there and like a bathing suit, bathing suit, a bathing suits appreciated
with an asterisks and you have to get clothes and it says required. Okay. And then we need a lamp
lamp. Okay. And somebody can sit on this. I can't even turn it. Oh no, it's supposed to go up. Okay.
I see. Ooh, wait, that's not even on. Oh, nice. Okay. Jeremy, since you're keeping your word,
should you play eternal darkness? He said, yeah, I missed it. Okay. This one, this is done.
Sauna is done. I'm probably doing all my money. 4,300. Shower plumbing system. Wait, you can
actually do this now? Oh, I was going to wait. Why is there a shower here? A shower next to the sauna?
Okay. I guess so. Of course, dude. Isn't that too much money though? Like you have a shower just
upstairs. Use your shower up there. Buy a shower and mount it. Toilet plumbing system. Wait a minute.
I don't hold on. So this is just a toilet. Why can't you see through this? There's no door here.
Hey guys. Okay. Sink plumbing system. What do you mean sink plumbing? Why do you need all this stuff?
I don't agree with this sauna field. I don't know. What's the point of having this bathroom?
I cannot do it now. We'll think out, you know, when houses have four and a half or like five
and a half bathrooms for some reason, like what do you pick a day of the week to go shit in each one?
I mean, no. You guys never heard of like a three, four, five bathrooms? Yes. How do you
have half a bathroom? Do I? I think you're messing around. Okay. Messing around. All right.
Mountable shower idiom. Okay. This is what they want. Wait, isn't there supposed to be a toilet
here? This is going to fit over here. Wait, what's this for? There's not going to be any room.
That's the sink. Uh, assemble it. Okay. Oh, dude. How do I assemble it? Is there something I'm missing?
You, you broke the shower because it's like, cause it's hovering. It's like a foot off the ground.
Okay. Wait, but then what the hell is this for? Mountable shower idiom. What? Why is this doing
this? Rotate. I can't. Why does it snap back to there? Okay. That didn't do anything. I tried it.
I'm losing money. All right. I'm done. I'm going to leave. I gotta go. That was fun to make the
sauna. Cool. Nice. Uh, goodbye. Wait, photographing? Wait, it's doing before and after photos.
Oh, wow. Nothing. You didn't change shit. That's not all it is. Okay. I hired a cleaning company.
Let's take a look at your new house. A cleaning company came and picked up the wood. You've ruined
a room and left. And I made 7,300 bucks doing it. Bathing suits are not allowed in saunas.
Okay. Cool. How much money do I have? I have like $300,000. All right. All right. Getting
interesting here. We have this one or this one. Check out this one. Man's job. Okay. What about
this one? 100 year old memories. This house is over a hundred years old and the ubiquitous wood gives
it a unique appeal. It'd be great for Trevor and Lily and their kids. A family of sailors. It's
going to be haunted. The family fell in love with the house at first sight. It was not cheap, but
the budget for its renovation is limited. It should be just enough to have it refreshed and
introduce some necessary changes. I used to hire the wrong guy. Never hire an interior decorator
on Craigslist. And you're about to find out why. Make the Simpsons house. No. All right. Clean the
dirt. Oh, my favorite part. Weeds? He hates the Simpsons. Yeah. I think I probably do now. Like
when was the last time you watched it? I haven't watched it. I don't think, maybe not hate them.
I don't hate the Simpsons, but like I don't, I haven't watched an episode in like probably
15 years. I don't, I don't know why. Does he hate it? No, he doesn't watch it. I don't even think
I can name you the whole family right now if I tried. Bart, uh, Bart, Lisa, Santa's helper,
Homer, Marge, uh, and Margaret. I, I, I stick into it. I got it. This place is a mess. Let's remove
the fluorescent lights and the mirror from above the sink. We can lay elegant wall tiles and mount
a new mirror. This mirror fits and looks like a window. Let's keep it. We will just buy a few.
Yeah. I like the weird one. I like the weird while you're at the kitchen sink, stared a huge
mirror. This place is filthy. What do you mean that's wrong? What do you think Maggie is short
for? Yeah. Margaret, Maggie. How do you, do you guys not know? You don't. Hey, face. Where's all
this dirt out here? All right. What if I, okay, we got to go to hold onto this one. The next house
that's really, really full of trash and dirt and shit. I want to try to put it all in the same room.
So when they do the before and after picture, it's even worse. This one's on the outside.
Why am I trying to climb? Wait, that's not, why do you have little like escape doors? This is,
that's awful. Do these, you can't, these don't even open. This is not, doesn't go to the backyard.
What on earth? Or the front yard. Wait, that's the front yard. I'm not a fan. You don't have to pay
me. I'll change those out for you. These are French doors. No, they're not. Are these French windows?
This is the last bug. It's not, it's not on the roof. Isn't it? That's a germa door. Sure. Okay.
That's, that's fine. It could also be a elegant doggy door. Where's this thing? What do you see
this? I don't, I'm, I can't see this. Where is this? Oh, whatever. You got fucking rats in the wall
for all. It doesn't matter on the grass up top. I can't reach that far. You made me forget. I was
making mac and cheese. Um, that's, uh, what did you kind of leave it on? That just gets better
with age. All you guys talk all this shit about like, Oh, I fucking hate making mac and cheese.
Every time I make it, it's so runny. What's going on here? Wait, not waiting long enough. You're
not patient and you're trying to eat it before it's ready. You let it sit there, stir it up
and it'll absorb all the nutrients from, it'll absorb everything. It'll puff up. It'll be thick
and greasy and shit. You need to wait. You're not waiting long enough. There's mud all over the bed.
This is the, I found Santa's helper's room. This is just if a dog had his own bedroom.
All right. What do you want me to do in here? Clean dirt. 99%. Great. That's fantastic. Where is it?
I got it. Uh, nothing in here, right? It's dirt. Shit. I had something to tell you guys today.
What was it? What the hell did I have to tell you guys? I had something going on. I had something
to say. I had something. I remember like just like shaking my hands, like rubbing my hands,
going like, I can't wait to tell them this one. I don't know what it was. Damn. I guess we'll
never know. I don't, I don't like a lot of big orange bed sheets. Orange. No. What's the thing
about like colors? Orange doesn't, I don't like this. I mean, you remove the two pillows. Never
mind. I was going to say it'll be a giant creamsicle and I like those, but that's not even like,
who cares? That's not even funny. Nonsense words. Quick. Just say words. Quick. I mean,
uh, what should happen with our schools? Okay. Dark mahogany floor panel in here. Oh, thank God.
It's right here for me. It's foolproof. It's a, it's a prison jumpsuit bed. Words, words, words,
words, words. Why does everybody love? What's, what's the obsession with wood? When I see like
a nice carpet, I'm like, oh, I like that. It's soft. It stays warm. Your feet aren't cold.
Everybody, I don't know what it is. Everybody loves wood. I don't. When you step on wood,
you ever, you walk around a house that was predominantly wood. I've lived in one. It's,
it's, it's just in every room. I don't, it's like I'm playing basketball in my house. You'll step
on a piece of that, a panel somewhere and you'll hear a, like a hundred feet somewhere else in
another room. Everybody could always track where you, where you are in a wooden, like wood floors.
Like, I know exactly where the fuck you're stepping. I don't want to know that information.
I don't want to know how many times you've gone into, into the bathroom. It's easy to clean. Yeah,
but I know, but then you get, you obsess over it. It's really nice. Wood is expensive. Real wood,
wooden floors are expensive. So anytime that you drop anything or touch a piece of grease
and a small crumb lands on the floor, you grab it. You're like, fuck, lick your finger. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no. God, please. Just give me a multicolored shitty carpet that I can just dump
shit on. It doesn't even matter and just run a vacuum over it once a year. How many stains
are on that carpet? You will have, you'll never know. There could be a hundred hidden in the
fucking awesome carpeted multi fiber colored, just like in there. You can't even tell. I could
probably do a full piss onto some of these carpets and have you guys come in and examine it and be
like, wow, this is perfectly fine. By the way, every day I could probably piss on it every fucking
day for a year. And you would come in and you wouldn't, you had no idea where it was. It would
smell. No, it wouldn't. I would bring in somebody in a room. Hey, what do you, what do you think
about this room? It's like, it stinks like piss in here. What's this guy trying to get me to do?
Hey, come on in here. Can you, hey, can you see if you can find it? This? Cause that's all I smell.
Okay. Melissa light colored left corner sofa. That's a long one. Mimimo dark coffee table.
Where does it want this? Not here. Oh no, they did want a Mimimo dark coffee. Here, here we go.
I wish I had a couch like this. It's just a permanent bed. No matter what, you could just
lie on it. Where is this supposed to go? This is, this is why I haven't windows this big sucks.
I honestly, this is horrible. You ever want to clean these, these windows just never open.
You have to accept that. If you put one of these here, you put a couch next to a window like that,
this is a, you have to accept that it'll never be fucking opened once ever for any reason.
And you just hope to God that one day, like four years from now, when you open this,
like the dead bugs and rotten leaves that are in here are not enough to make you throw up out the
window. Cause then your neighbor will think you're crazy. Why did he just do that? He opened up his
window and puked. He has a bathroom. Doesn't he like just puking the bathroom? I don't, it takes
longer to open the window. Okay. Coffee table. I'm going to move this shit around. I don't like this
at all. I hate this. No TV in here. Fireplace. No, I don't like this. I hate, I hate this house.
Then you have the weird separate like fucking dungeon dining room. No, I don't like that.
I hate that. Get this wall out of here and get rid of the half of this room. Don't just remove
this different floor. No, this is what happens when your house is too big. Cause this is all
the furniture that anybody fucking needs in their whole life. So then you end up with like, if you
have like a 4,000 square foot house, it's like, okay, we have the biggest couch we could possibly
fucking find. Nice. That's all we need. Uh, I guess fill it with plants. You don't have TV right there.
That's unbelievable. All right. Place object. Right. Here it is. Told you. Yeah. Good. Put it,
put it up here. Right here. How about that? Yeah. It looks good. How many more of these do we want?
This is a big one. It's big enough for me to have to get it, get in the way and be smell and
get in and rot. Cause I don't take care of it. Unless they're fake. It's just unnecessary shit.
Does it look nice? I guess, but it's just, it's unnecessary shit.
Therma hates plants. No, I love plants. I love a garden. I love tending to tomatoes. I love growing
my own tomatoes and eating them. I love plants. Late dark, my heart. Where, where am I missing?
Oh, here. Oh, okay. Eat a tomato on stream. That's so funny how I have to prove that.
If any streamer ever says anything, they have to always prove it on stream. You know, I really
like, uh, I'm a big fan of Buffalo chicken. Eat Buffalo chicken on stream. Prove it. Liar.
Okay. Uh, I like, I like, um, I like reading books. Liar. Read a whole book on stream. I,
I guarantee you haven't read a book at all this whole year. Oh, okay. I read it on stream. I guess
how would you get halogen lamps? He's like, let's get hot. Don't they prove it. Eat a book on stream
hanging long bulb. This ain't even our house. I want to, I have a lot of money to buy a house.
I don't care where it's placed. Living room. Why is it? How am I not? Oh, this is good dining
room. This is good. All right. I got to go upstairs. Wait, bedroom double bed Hermes.
What is double bed Hermes? Stove on stove on. I wish I had an electric stove. I don't like gas
stoves. I don't, you guys know me. I don't like gas. It freaks me out. Something about electricity
is so much safer to me in my brain than like gas. Think about all like the movies and TV shows and
like scariest things about gas. That shit ignites. Watch out. It's going to explode. What's the worst
thing that like electricity that like Will Ferrell like electrocuted himself in the fucking Christmas
movie. This house didn't explode. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Maybe it did. Maybe it did. Did it?
You could cause a fire. Yeah, but it's okay. It could, it could cause a fire. Sure. And then
the fire will take a little while to spread at least 50 to 60 seconds. Right? If you have like
electricity in an oven, if it starts, all right. An explosion is an instant. It explodes your house.
Fire is a fire. It starts somewhere and spreads. You have time. Gas in a house. The house explodes.
You don't have time. You, you have enough time to go, oh, you don't have enough. If there's
if there's electric, electricity fire, you can be like, all right, get the fucking get out.
Let's do something about it. Okay. Out, out, out. Okay. So let's do the get the fire extinguisher.
Like it's not just scream. You guys are fucking crazy. I just don't like gas. Gas scares me.
It's something about it. It's like lighter than air. It's like a gas. It like floats around and
it just ignited and shit. I don't like gas. It's scary to me. When I think of electricity,
I think of like, I think of like energy and, and like a light bulb. When I think of the word
gas, I think of or like, what's happening? What's happening? No, no, no, no. Fuck that.
Electricities. I'm like, I'm an electricity guy. Like if you hear that or smell gas, it's,
it's like immediately that like iPhone fucking like, which by the way, by the fuck do people
have that as an alarm? What, what, why do you wake your? Yeah. Like they're that iPhone
alert notification thing. Everybody had it. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. What was it called?
iPhone, iPhone alarm. Like, let's see. Yeah. This. All right. So if, if you smell gas, literally,
what goes through my head is this. It's I'm dead. I'm dead in five seconds. I'm going to die in five
seconds. Why would you wake up to that? Why would you ever want to rip your fucking head up from
bed? It's like you're supposed to wake up easily. It's slowly. Why do people use that for their alarm?
That sound only means three or four different things. Look out. There is a fucking tornado.
A bomb is going to drop on you. You are under attack or there is an immediate threat that is
around you. Why would you want to awake to an immediate threat? Like, oh, hey, like it's a spy
moving. You stepped on the red wire thing and now like machine guns are going to shoot at you.
You should be awakened to like chirping birds. Don't do this to yourself. It's got 50. I haven't
done anything. I've just been walking around and like, look, dude, look at it. Nothing. That's four
things. Idiot. We had that guy for five seconds. Somebody. Yeah. A plug boy gave 50 bucks. Thanks
plug boy for the huge absurd amount of money. Thank you. That's a lot of money. There's no
message or anything, but I, you guys know I don't read bit messages anymore, but that's still an
insane thing to do. Red spies in the base. Prove it. Wake up to birds right now. Okay. What do I
have to do? Turn on. Maybe a fuse is blonde. What else is left? Paint the color silver glacier in
the bedroom. Bedroom 11. Okay. Bedroom 11. Paint. Yes. My favorite part. Oh, it, it feels, I love
that about when it sucked it all up is the wrong bedroom. This is 11, two, right? 11. This is not
the wrong. What do you mean? How many bedrooms do they have here? Is this on the first floor?
That's what I'm talking about. You have too much stuff. Get lost in your own house. No, all you need
is a toilet, an electric stove and a bed. You don't need, don't all this, all this room. It's just room.
It's room for like the gas. Okay. Here we go. Get rid of this thing. There we are. I just thought
somebody gave $50. That was the someone gave $50 noise. It's so relaxing. I'm so glad that I
promised to play this today. Oh, you know what I mean? Got to just keep your word. That's my slogan.
Germa, keep your word. There's a huge scandal about how I've just, I've lied about everything.
My entire campaign was running on telling the truth and nothing I said was, was, was real.
Dean Dingus, you can't keep getting, he can't get away with this. Senator Elbertson, keep your word.
And then they play during the attack ad campaigns against me. They show how I opened up a guy's
house, went in, told him I was going to put a sauna in and then just left and lied and just told
him I wasn't going to do it anymore. Do people paint their closets? No. I mean, I thought they did.
Thank you, Peter. I thought it was Peter Griffin. Thank you, Peter V. Peter Gruen
for the 10 community subs, actually. Thanks to the 10 subs. Welcome all the new subs. Hey,
what's going on? New subs? Wait, what's in the safe? Forgotten safe in the closet. This must be
the forgotten safe of the captain that lived here a hundred years ago after selling the precious notes
and jewelry found inside the budget significantly increased. This allows us to plan something more
for both the kitchen and the bathroom. I'm on TV right now. I'm on TV. I'm about to go on like a
weird prank show adventure. How did you not see this? This is like, it's a giant fucking open
safe here that you don't, why would you not see this? Steal the money. I already, I just did.
I just did. Wait. Okay. Close this. Paint is done. We can sell this now. All right. We need a bedside
table. Well, can I give you some more design choices here? Cause that is an ugly ass bed.
There, there we go. Make sure you give me a good review on Yelp. German 985. It's my German 985
colors. How's it going to fit in here? This room sucks. How is it supposed to fit in here?
Why would you want a bed like this? Okay. Bedside. The bed doesn't fit. It's supposed to be an end
table. This bed only can fit one way and it blocks every door. And we need a lamp. Make sure you get
those German 985 colors. What's this? A carpet? Get that German 985 set green. All right. The
carpet is there for all the shit that goes under your bed. It's a useless carpet and they want a
painting, a big one. Okay. Does anybody feel like, okay, if this was next to your bed and you were
sleeping and you're snoring your life away, you know, you're just sleeping and you turn when you
wake up and your eyes, you're pointing this way and you see this. I feel like sometimes I would
actually think I was sleeping on a beach for a second. It would be terrifying. Okay. This one's
done. What's next? Oh, a choice. A cupboard shelf and new tiles will be enough. We will utilize the
extra budget. Let's go crazy and add a second sink. I want to save the money that I stole.
I'm going to invest that shit. Okay. Modify the walls, wall tiles. Oh yeah. That's right. You have
to actually pick these up. You can have finished. Okay. I can finish the job now. Do we care? I
don't think we care. No, this is just to make money so I can buy my own house. It's coming up
here in a minute. Yeah, I'm done. Wait, first I want to fuck their whole shit up. Hold on. I'm
going to put the dining room table in here too. Turn the oven on. No, I'm going to put the, I'll
put the oven in there. That much better in there. When you're watching the game, you're going to have
a nice fucking crisp pizza ready. Okay. I can think about what I want. Okay. Done. I've prepared
you for your yard sale. Complete the job. You may not complete the job, but I got tons of money. I
don't care about the money. I just care about making a statement. Yeah. All you did was remove
my things. Here's the, you know, the best part about that was this is how all this bullshit,
all the fake like filters and stuff. That was just a filter on the shitty picture. They took
a shitty picture and they put a little filter on it to make it look better. It doesn't look like
that. I didn't walk in that room. They tried so hard to make how bad that was look. Not as bad,
even though it's just the raw photo. I got $341,000. I'm ready. We need a big one. Um,
there's an actual Simpson's house in the game. How do I do that one? I don't know if you can
buy the house in the HDTV part. Oh, all right. Property renovation in the rental business. She's
expecting a baby. So there's no way she can work as much as usually. I'm going to have to help her
with a house for one of her clients. The semi-detached house that requires some work and
yeah. Okay. I got a $9,000 budget. You're in story mode. Yeah. I got to unlock all the tools and then
I'm going to take those tools into, into free purchase mode. All right. So what does she want?
First of all, this has got to change. That's the first, uh, you want, you really need a,
an HDTV specialist to tell you that this is probably not something that this is probably
like a, you want like a more neutral color. Well, now we've got a clean slate to work with.
All right. Here's an idea. Maybe we should demolish the two walls and knock it down.
Knock it down. Knock the whole thing down. The whole thing should be an open floor plan,
including the bathrooms. Knock it down. I'm talking square build tool in the Sims.
No rooms made. This is just as satisfying as it was before. All right. Well,
I have the sledgehammer feels good. Feels good. It's been a while. It's excessively loud. Yep.
The game is excessively loud. Someone has started working on the kitchen already gone with a dark
brown paint. Let's add some traditional hanging lamps. No, I hate those. Let's put some bright
colors on the walls. Yes, absolutely. Lime green. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. What do you mean? Well,
what are you doing? I'm doing my interior designing. What are you doing? Besides
criticizing a genius at work. Broken pipe. It looks like the radiator. I wait. Yes. No,
it's water. Okay. The leak needs to be stopped. There should be a water supply valve.
This is the urgent water, water supply valve. I'm going to hit the gas line. Okay. I'm actually
kind of concerned about this because if I hit a gas line and it's an instant gas line explosion,
then I'm starting to have a little bit of a scenario here. I don't like this.
If I can hit the water line, then I can hit the gas line. This is the load bearing wall.
Yeah. Where's the load bearing wall? There ain't no more walls. The house is just laid on top
like a hat. Oh no, the house is coming down. Just delete everything. I'm going to make an open floor.
I'm going to make a completely open Sims 4 renovation. This guy's deranged. Just renovate
it as an empty field. Just take the whole house down. So the before and after is just a house and
then the house is gone. That's not a renovation. That's a magic trick. Imagine going through all
that trouble. What we're going to do is we're going to bulldoze their fucking house and then I'm going
to pretend on TV that I made it disappear and I'm just going to cut these people. You know what?
I wonder how many times maybe that has happened before. If I was just a millionaire
magician, I would just like, here's a check. How much is your house worth?
Oh, the house is worth probably 325,000. I'll give you 400,000 if you let me do a magic trick
where I disappear your house. You just go buy one in cash. But I need to do this. You mean destroy
it? Yeah. But, but, but it's a magic trick. It's not, I'm not like destroying the house.
It's a magic trick. I even use the door. Is it leak? That's fine. Not my problem.
All right. Load bearing wall. Don't touch that one. Can't get rid of this one. It's got an
achievement for being an asshole. The achievement I just got is called truly open space. See,
I'm making game progress. What is this? This is like a puppeteer station. There's a wall here,
wall there. This is where the family crouches down and has like puppet night. How can I sell
this? Yeah, I'm sorry. If you have a dedicated puppetry room, then I guarantee you, you got five
or six big plants in your house. You want to put, you want to make that bet? You want to put that
money down? What are these? Cement. I thought I said gourmet. Gourmet cement. Lights on floor,
lights on floor. It's all right. I'm not going to, that's immoral. I can't sell the doors. The doors
have to stay, but everything else can be smashed down with a sledgehammer. That's very immoral.
Okay. That's it, right? Any more? Move furniture into the water leak. See, hey, if being a psycho
was a strategy game, we would get an S plus on every level. You get that, right? Okay. Is this
the house? Is there any more rooms or anything? Who's we? What do you mean? I'm talking about you.
It's you that I'm referring to. Talking about you. All right, cool. Now we want build the walls.
A mountable towel radiator. Toilet? All right. Oh, should I need to mount this toilet?
I can't just jam it in there. Just stick it into the water. Wait, lay wall. Wait, wait, wait. What
room am I in? I need a radiator. Towel radiator plumbing system. Right, right, right, right, right.
What is a towel radiator plumbing system? What? Did I read that wrong? No, I want to get that out
of the way. Wait, what is this here for? A towel warmer. You don't even need a shower. Just come
into the leaking room and just smush your face over here. It's an indoor pool. Yeah. Somebody gets it.
Okay. Remove object. No. Where's the toilet mount? Move the bathtub onto the leak. Can I move the
bathtub? I can't. I cannot move the bathtub, unfortunately. Click on the link. What even is
the toilet really? Wow. This is your room. It's so cool. Yeah. Yep. Why do you always have to use
this drunk image? I don't know where these are supposed to go. All right. Mountable. Mountable
towel radiator. What is this? Old Japanese sink. Okay. There we go. Yeah. I fixed one of the leaks.
Where does it go? That's crazy that that's how they make these things. Okay. Cool. What's wrong
with this? Assemble. It is assembled. Paint with the colors young flower bud. Uh, young flower bud.
All right. Here we go. This is going to be real boring, but I love it. Enable A. Yay. Yay. A. I'm
not going to say it the way it's supposed to be said. It's baby puke yellow. I think this is baby
puke baby. This is, I think this is, yeah, this is baby, like baby burp yellow. That's a better way
to put it. Why would you? Yeah. Yellow. I mean, it's, I don't know, like an olive. What would you
call it? This is carpet piss. Yeah. That's accurate. That is what it looks. That's an accurate
carpet piss color. You're right. Oh, rude. That would be if you told somebody that. Yeah. We had
the, we had it painted. We, uh, yeah, we got a painter in here to the bedrooms, did the living
room. This looks like carpet piss yellow. Because if you, when you hear that, you have to really
think about it because it doesn't make any sense at first. And then you think about what an old
piss would look like as a big gross circle. And then you would see it and you would know. And then
you get angry. It angers you. Then you pretend to like it. And then eventually you pretend to like
it for so long that you're just like, yeah, it's cool. I like it. It's fine. You know what I really
do miss though? Oh, I missed my spearmint green gamer room. I love that color. I might, I got it.
I want, I want like a spearmint green room again. Oh, I love it so much. It's like my favorite color.
Okay. So now we need, uh, lay wall tiles and white mosaic hexagon. Wait, it's just right here. What?
Hexagon. What's it called? White mosaic hexagon. Right. I was supposed to go. Oh yeah. That's right.
This is, this is a room. Olive greens. My favorite color. Wait, this is not right. The room is just
going. Just testing each room. Which, which room is it going? Wall tiles. Shit. Hold on. Modify what?
Dark gray mosaic? No, I thought it was white mosaic. Shit. No, that's not right either.
I could draw a penis. Modify walls. What? Here we go. Why is that not working? Eight out of 10.
Put this away. Throw this away. I don't want this. I have to get rid of them. It's because
I demolished all the walls. I actually kind of like that. It gives off the like in the pool.
That's like the side of a pool. I really like that. Okay. Let's go. White tiles. 25 of them. Good.
This is a bathroom house. That's a good idea. God damn it. Am I going to get like addicted
to house slipper again? I think I might. I don't know. Are we, are we going to be streaming this
tomorrow? Oh no. What have you done? Why did you remind me that I promised to play this?
You know what happens? I get stuck here. That's enough, right? Yeah. No. Yeah. Yeah. He said that
that's the best streams. I love this game. This game is so simple and it's so basic,
but it's like the best game and real. I love this game. This has to be my favorite game
in the last five years. Isn't that fucked up? That sounds like it's something you shouldn't say out
loud. What's come out in the last five years? I got to paint some, wait, I'm going to paint this
wall in here. Lay tiles, wallpaper with bamboo. All right. Hold on. Paint. Okay. Young flower bud
needs a little bit more space. What about a half-life game? But that's like, what do you mean
the last five years? Half-life Alex? I haven't played half-life Alex though. So how can I compare
it? This doesn't count as a wall. Okay. There we go. 73, 24, 75, 76, 77. Play half-life Alex. I'm
going to, don't worry. I'm going to go back to VR. I'm going to go back to VR. It's going to be a
big VR day, big VR week. I'm going to play all that shit. You're going to trust me. All right.
Wall tiles in the bathroom. Or should I do light? Okay. Light biscuits going to be in here.
Just do that now. Ooh, I like that. You're pogged. Look at that. What? You're pogged?
Why is that clippable? Clippable. He always keeps his word. I try to. Thank you. I really
appreciate that you coming in saying that. Real voice. Yeah. This is like kind of great.
If you called me at like six o'clock in the afternoon and I answered the phone, I'd be like,
what's up? Be like this. Hey, what's going on? What are you doing? Nah, nothing. Sorry. I might
sound a little hoarse. I was acting on Twitch for a while. Yeah. You play Mario Maker 2 yet, dude?
Yeah, that's fucking suck. It's a wicked good acting game. Yeah. Come over. You can come over
like an hour. Fucking tired from, you know, missing a jump over and over again. But it
fucking kills on Twitch, man. Dark gray mosaic. Where are these going to go? Is he from Boston?
Yeah. That's kind of where I fucking grew up, dude. I live. I live in Vegas now, but I was a
fucking big Boston guy before I moved here. And you know what? It's still with me every day.
This is just the drug chair. Oh, hey guys. Okay. I think I'm good. Stare at the wall. Okay.
Open the window. It stinks in here. What am I doing? I still have $8,000 of a budget. I'm
going to put an expensive chair in here. There's a garage too. All right. What's this a bed?
Let's make it an invisible bed. I can't. I'm not going to be able to fit it. It can't go in like
that. What are you a lizard? Yeah. Well, you know, I am a fucking lizard. So I have to have
moisture in the bedroom at all times. My wife, you still have to spray me with a bottle.
This is a much better solution. I think. All right. Would you let me ask you again,
would you be able to do that? Would you be able to sleep like this? That's a challenge. I'm not
sure I would be able to. If you were wicked tired and the water wasn't cold, it was exactly at like
68 degrees. It was like 70 degree water, completely isotonic. It had enough sodium.
It's an isotonic solution. Would you be able to sleep with that if that was not pointed at your
face? And there was like a doctor and a scientist and like a construction worker that were ready
to like, Hey, like we got to get them out of there. Do you think you'd be able to fall asleep?
No, no, not hypothermia. That is, this is an isotonic solution. It has like the right amount
of sodium, nitrogen, hydrogen, everything, human blood. It's isotonic. Look it up. Okay. That's
good. Am I getting money points for this? Let me check. Look down there. Progress. I'm not,
I'm not getting any progress. Okay. Lay wall tiles, wallpaper with bamboo. Where is that going to go?
Dark gray hexagon. I must have burped really loud. Dark gray hexagon mosaic. Do you mean credit
score? Wait, what did I say? I don't remember. This is not even right. It's free credit report.com.
I'm lying down here seeing all this in this restaurant. They monitor your credit and give
you free email alerts and put it on your sweatshirt and you see the t-shirts. Shit. Now you all heard
it. It worked like 20, like 15 years later. It's still worked. Congratulations. It's still fucking
worked. Good work. Ad campaign team. You deserve, all of you deserve to get at least a 20, 30 percent
raise. All of you, wherever you are now. I don't care where you are. And that band. I hope they,
I hope they're absolutely killing it. I hope the last EP they dropped has like fucking 500 million
plays on Spotify. I really hope that. All right. Now paint with the natural beige. The band broke
up after the commercials. Oh, that's really sad. That makes me feel bad. Really? No. Did they?
Okay. All I just read was all the, like everyone's talking about this band and then somebody just
wrote, this is a fucking mess. Holy shit. No, I'm not. Okay. Paint with the natural base. Six percent.
What do you mean six percent? There's not enough walls in this house to do this. Wait, is there
another house? Oh Jesus Christ. This is second house. Wait, no. What? House two? No, there's not
enough walls. There are not enough walls in this house. Is there a house three?
Jerma, you're a fucking idiot. You broke the walls. Right. You're right. Okay. Well, why can't I just?
Okay. I have a solution. We need to build five walls. More than that. Where's the build tool?
Okay. We need just enough room to be able to paint on all sides. That's four. This is four, eight,
12, 16, 20. Okay. Build a maze. That's another one I could do. I could build a maze. I'm gonna build
a maze in one of the, all right. Welcome to fucking house flipper week. I'm sorry. I think maybe at
least a thousand people just put their hands in the air when, god damn it. Okay. So what do I need?
Beige. Do beige first. Natural beige. Five percent. Six percent. These ones have to be beige. All right.
Where's the beige? Pipers. God damn it. Yeah. If you can't handle me at my worst, you don't deserve
my cat puke noise. Come on, guys. 12 percent. Is this? I can't tell this is working. Is my grand
scheme actually working? I think so. Because this is technically 14 percent. Yeah, it is working.
Carpet piss omega lull house. This is gonna be such a pain in the ass. This is gonna be such a
pain in the ass. Get rid of this chair. Get rid of this stuff. I need, okay. 18 percent. Shit.
I have to build so many more walls that are separated. Build them all together? Will that
be more space? But like, we can do that. Yep. We can do, we can, all right. We can do like a McRib
system. That works. Yeah, it works. That'll be way more surface to paint. Nuclear reactor house.
It's very funny. Like, large generator. Build them outside. Did they add that in house flipper?
I remember you couldn't do that before. Do it outside. Wait, can you build outside? Can you?
How the fuck is this still 15 percent? This is beige, right? Light biscuit? No, this is wrong.
Natural beige. That's not it either. Oh, god damn it. Buy another one. Buy like three of them.
That's, that's light biscuit. Okay, there we go. Now we're going, now we're cooking with gas.
Not scary! Is that loud? Is that really loud? I'm sorry if it was. No? All right, I'm sorry if it was.
Sorry. Okay, 25 percent. Can I build this shit outside? I don't think I can, guys. Wait,
does this not count? No, no build tool. I can't. Remember, you're so loud. Everyone always yells at
me because they say I'm too quiet and now everyone says I'm loud. Okay, we're gonna need some more
walls. What are we at? 20 what percent? Late wall tiles. Okay, wait, wallpaper with bamboo. Let's do
that because I know I can do that like over here. I don't need very much of this. One guy. Get rid
of this. I don't want this. There we are. Okay, how many do I need? 11. Something's in my eye.
Something's in my eye. Something's in my eye. All right, we're good. Four, five, six, seven,
eight. Am I trying to make it look like my house is a plant? Nine. Look, these are my roots. Like,
I have roots going down. N and 11. White mosaic hexagon. Oh, whoops. Not it. How much budget do
I have? I stole a lot of money from somebody, right? I want to put this shit down. I don't
want to hold this anymore. Going on the outside. Okay, where am I missing this? Where's the white?
Okay, I see. Build one of these. Beige. Mountable towel radiator. Well, that's that right there.
All right, sell this shit. Get this out of here. So, I need to build the walls. Didn't I already
build five walls? Shower bed. You need... All right, who made the dumb joke that got him started on
this awful house? I don't think anybody did. Nobody did. This wasn't some kind of joke or,
well, let's do this. No, I don't think so, at least. That's all I had to do. Why is that in here?
Isn't that kind of a weird place to have that? Okay, sink. Turn it back on. I can't turn it back
on. Turn it... I don't... I didn't know what it did. It was just a random valve. Quick, break it again.
That's not going to work. Wait, it might. Hold on. No, it's gone. Let it go. All right, let's finish
this. How I still not made this much progress? The garage. Okay, it's the trash in the garage
that's killing me. All right, now... That's it. Garage is clean. Decorations. This guy's got like
a Rube Goldberg machine in his house. Whenever he turns on the garage, it's like... It's like an egg
that just drops and scrolls around the gears. Wait, they're just big ones? Damn it. I can
make a gear house. Shit. Okay, remind me of that later. Remind me of that later. Not now. I'll do
it later. No, we need like a couch in here. Furniture. Table. Minecraft jumping event. Bunk beds.
They added bunk beds. They added bunk beds. This is the greatest day ever. They added bunk beds.
What's my WCW? Like wrestling? WCW. What do you want to click on? Women Crush Wednesday. LOL,
I choose Ursula. The top reply here is, oh god, you're drunk again. And then I replied saying,
haha, I'm not. I just have this super WCW on Ursula. Why did I do this? What's wrong with you?
Good crush. Okay, so why are you linking this to me? I got a tweet I made like four years ago.
I don't... I don't... Hey, Jeremy, maybe you said this like on Twitter five years ago.
Remember this video, this specific moment that happened in video 225 in 2012? I don't even
remember what I had for lunch yesterday. I don't even know. I have... I don't remember what it was.
I don't know these things that I say. That's a humble brag. Forgetting what you ate for lunch
yesterday is concerning. That's not a humble brag. It's Wednesday. Is it still Ursula?
All right, let me just focus on my HD... HDTV. I need to wait. What do I have to do? Okay,
this is broken. This. I gotta mount a sink here. What kind of sink do they want? Build the walls.
I have to build these walls, right? I don't know what the fuck they want. ADHDGTV. What is ADHDGTV?
Is that like the guy renovates a house but he cannot decide on the color of the couch he wants
so he keeps getting it upholstered for the whole episode and that's it. This is a guy paints like
half of the house and then just kind of starts watching TV. Basically, it's this stream. No,
it's not. This is not what I would do if I was on HGTV. Walls. What do they want these walls?
Build wall. Modify the room's layout. Isn't that what I'm doing? It's the green on the map.
Oh, it won't. Right. Okay. Wait, that's not even it. What the fuck is that for? You just built an
annoying wall? It's a wall. Yeah, I know what it is but why is it? It sticks out too far. Okay,
we need young flower bud or a booger beige. I'm gonna go with booger beige. Place little walls
on the ceiling. Paint with beige. How much of their room do they house? They want beige.
You guys thought I was boring. 75 out of 80 with the other one. Where's the green one?
What's it called? This one. Just complete the ones that can be completed. Okay. Wall with bamboo.
Alright. Closing one door, opening two more. There it is. That made no sense. Yeah, it did.
How do I drop shit? Press E to pick up the $60. Here we go. Alright, look. I'm gonna fix this.
Check it out. Alright. Lay floor tiles. Floor panel pine. You got it? Floor panel pine. Alright.
About right here. 2%. I think the entire house is supposed to be like this. How would you have room
for anything else? It's only 27%. 32%? Is the bathroom pine wood? This is the worst house I've
made. I didn't make this house. Remember, gotta get it right here. I didn't make this house. I'm
just getting money to be able to do my own house. This is me renovating somebody else's. And yes,
I took the money up front. This is horrible. Regardless of how much I fucked this whole thing
up, that doesn't matter. This whole house is a wood floor. The entire thing, the same color,
everything. Even in the bathroom? Only 50% so far. How? Do you want me to put wood floor on the roof?
66%. This is so stupid. 80%. It's because I made everything one room. So I'm never gonna be able
to complete all the tasks. Please. What do you want? What? What is it? Guys, you're not gonna
believe this. Hey, woozledoo is in my bedroom. I wish I was in your bedroom. Yeah, what? What do
you want me to say? Wrong link. Wait, is this the go-through Jerma's Twitter comedy hour?
Let's go, let's go to like 2012 and find some comedy. All right, that's it. That's Team YouTube
Money's new album cover. Here's the story of that. That Team YouTube Money was the name. I didn't
pick the name. The name was already there. We got called in from the benches because, uh, I believe
if I get the story right, I want to get the story right. I think the incredible orb legally couldn't
participate in the United States in that shoot mania tournament. So we had, we were like the
bench players that came in. If I remember that correctly, like it was supposed to be like orb
was in like the tournament or something. Then we were like, at least I was like the B team. It was,
I was the, I was the anchor. You guys don't remember that? That's okay. A long time ago,
like 10 years, eight years ago or so now, seven years ago, I played in a shoot mania storm
tournament and we almost won the whole thing. It was streamed. This was streamed like seven and a
half years ago. And what it really came down to was MLC stealth just carried us all the way to
the final fucking round. Star was pretty good too. It was me star and MLC stealth, but it was supposed
to be, I think me, no, it was supposed to be star like MLC stealth and orb, but like he couldn't,
they like legally wasn't allowed to participate because he wasn't a US citizen or something.
Here's a video of it. Yeah, it was a big deal. I was an actual, yeah, a gaming warlord. Yeah,
gaming anchor. Eric, you gotta have an anchor on the boat. MLC stealth was like the sails.
Star was like the solid wood and I was the anchor and be careful. You want to go on a fucking trip
without an anchor with a boat. What if a storm comes? What if you need to drop that anchor hard
into the ground? I'm here. I'm here to, I'm ready. The train needs a caboose. Please just make the
house less bad. Actual literal dead weight. All right, let me finish this. Let me finish this,
please. This looks like the house from Hellraiser. No, no. All right. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
I need to, let me finish this first. I don't even, you know, I'm laughing at that, but I don't even
know what they're talking about. I haven't seen the movie in so long. I just hear the word Hellraiser
and I think of the guy with like the needles in his face and I'm just like, holy shit, this probably
looked horrible then. And then that cube that bites you, right? And it needs to like you drink
your blood and then go take a portal. I don't even remember that movie. What's next? Mountable toilet
fire fairy. Okay, I need mountable toilet furry. A toilet fairy. I don't think I want to know
about that. What is it? Toilet fairy? Mountable toilet fairy. Nice. Okay, too bad we couldn't
like lift this up another water go in there. That's just a complete and total. Oh, okay.
Old fashioned sink. Where's it supposed to even go? Is it actually supposed to go right here?
Oh, I don't think I can even assemble this. Here comes the toilet fairy. What would that even be?
Like you have the tooth fairy. The tooth fairy, if you lose a tooth. Hey, the tooth fairy left a
dollar under your pillow. Does the toilet fairy leave a dollar in the toilet after like you took
a dump in it? How come I can't close this thing out? Am I doing this wrong? Why? How come I can't
do this? I'm sorry, that was weird. Okay, short narrow curtain. I'm assuming for the bathtub
thing here. Short narrow curtain. Multiple, mountable wide curtain. That's not for the bathtub.
Mountable wide curtain. What is this? Oh, it goes up here. There's not enough room to place it. How?
Oh, come on. All right. We're almost it doesn't matter. Place object. What does it want me to
place tasks? Nothing in the garage, right? Okay, I have to place these objects. We're almost there.
Get it. All right. We're there. We're there. We're there. We're there. Okay. We're done. Done. Done.
Done. Done. Done. Done. I can do it. Let's go. The job is complete. Let's see the before and after.
The garage looks nice. It doesn't look that bad. Oh, mega lol. The bucket. The bucket of paint. Yeah.
Jerma, Jerma, stop wasting channel points. They're going to be so valuable.
Eventually, that's what my excuse lead to the Simpsons house. Let me see if there's any new
houses to buy. I got 350 grand mail. No, I'm not doing this. Wait, look for like Bart Simpson
or something, right? Do I have an email from Bart Simpson? No. Damn it. Like writing a letter to
Santa Claus and expecting him to write back. I sent Rocco from Rocco's Modern Life a thank you
letter. I liked his show, but he didn't write me back. All right. The game's going to really open
up here when I'm done with tutorial house four. We're going to do this quick. That's until he was
released. Yeah. All right. Ed purchased the small house on sale. The couple that was selling the
house split up during the renovation. So some furniture is brand new. Our house is messy.
Ed has some doubts when it comes to choosing which of the existing solutions should be carried over.
Sure. All right. Let's go quick. Clean everything. Get this trash out of here.
And then we're going to make our dream house. The maze. I have garden flipper too. Where's my
lawnmower? No lawnmower? Remember the lawnmower? The lawnmower sucked. It was so hard to control.
All right. That's the whole front yard is good. This is very messy. You're right. What are these?
Wait, I thought these were like silicone gel packs. What are these? Is this water? How did you get
this much water on the couch? On the shower? Huh? How's the bathroom doing? The bathroom doesn't need
anything. Quick. Make a piss carpet. Okay. Make a decision. What is it? This one's going to be quick.
But leather furniture is stylish. Let's keep what we have. We will choose furniture in a similar
style. Um, no, I don't like leather couches and leather stuff. You can ruin it too easily.
Give me the thing that can be wiped off with a towel if you dump a whole coffee on it.
Uh, let's go modern. Leather arm. I don't want leather. Alfred leather armchair. Okay. Paint.
Okay. Steel gray. 180. This is the kind of house I'm talking about. I'm going to love this place.
Gray. Gray. Everything gray. And then one piece of blue furniture. You will impress the shit at
anybody. Ready? Gray walls. A light blue couch. And have maybe a little bit like of a dark blue
accent. And you better make damn sure that you have something nautical on the wall. Picture of a
beach or sailor's cap or hanging on the wall. It's a prison architect. It's a Spongebob prison.
How is that a Spongebob prison? True. True. True. True. All right. Hold on. We got,
all right. Link cool down begins now. Link cool down begins now.
Every single, every single one. German look at a stream like, because what's a VTuber? I'm sorry.
I'm really bad at doing a Boston accent. I was just going to say, what is this?
All right. For a second, I don't know why my brain is just wired wrong in some places. I thought,
I see this is, I see the tweet. It's German nine eight five out of context. I was like, German.
Okay. I click it and I'm like, is that me? I was like, I didn't went German, German out of context.
I was like, did I do that at some point? Then I was like, no, that's, that's not me.
Sure. I wonder how do you get like an avatar? Do I do like an avatar stream? If I were to do
an avatar stream, I would kind of want to get like a custom one where it was just like a big green
slime and the whole stream. I'm just like role playing as the slime ball guy. That's just like,
I, I like to take breaks every like 10 minutes. Is that Mr. Green's slime guy?
Hey, welcome to twitch.tv slash slime guy TV. Mr. Green's evolved. I have to look into that.
That sounds, that actually sounds like fun. All right. Well, let's, let's start there. I don't,
I kind of do. I kind of don't though. I, I, here's what I know. I know that I just said,
I want to do Mr. Green's as the slime guy. I get it. I understand. Thanks for that. He knows.
You're going to stop that. I'm not doing that voice. That's not me that we're watching a video.
Oh, there's no video on screen. So that is just, that's just a voice talking.
All right. Slime guy, slime guy avatar stream. I think I'm going to do it on a different channel.
You know what I mean? Would you guys care? Would you guys be mad if I started a new channel called
like the fucking slime guy or something? And I just like told you guys, like you guys knew,
like I just did it and it didn't stream on German. It wasn't even me. I don't think I would tell you
guys when I was going to do it. I think that's, yeah, I wouldn't tell you guys when I won't even
tell you guys the account. So I'm going to stream as the fucking slime guy and you're never going
to even know. And I'm going to stream to nobody. I'm going to take like, I'm going to take like a
fucking week off and just stream as that guy. He's going to have 10 viewers.
How much more gray do I need? We're going to find you. I bet you will.
What if it happened to Bugleberry week? Yeah, this is kind of an evolution of that. I think
this is an evolution of that V tuber. And then I can, and then I can just,
I would just be like a different person. Like German nine at five has his life and his friends,
but fucking Mr. Slime. I'll be, I'll be a fucking V tuber. You guys will come in and tell me all
this like fucked up shit that the, that Mr. Slimes did. And I'll just be like, I don't know.
Perfect example. I used to use grandpa as a way to swear on the channel 10 years ago.
So, oh yeah, I'm ready for this one. Do you remember that? Cause it wasn't me. It was grandpa.
Oh, I didn't say that. I didn't say shut the fuck up. You fucking stupid idiots.
None of you guys have any idea what you're talking about. Like, no, that wasn't me. That was,
I could say whatever I wanted. And then I was just nice, Mr. Nice guy, Jeremy. It ain't me.
It's Mr. Slime. Slimey motherfucker. Yeah. And if anybody followed me, you better,
you better not say a single thing in chat besides talking about how disgusting Mr. Slime is.
I want you all to hate watch that stream. That's just going to go off and everyone just like be
wicked mean. This guy's a fucking idiot. Oh, Mr. Slime, what a piece of shit. Oh,
he's gross. Look, he just like shot boogers and just, I don't want a chat room. I'll be like
banning people and shit and talking tons of shit. It's not even me. I'm, I,
Jerma hasn't streamed in like four or five days. It's not me. Now here's the real kicker here.
What if Mr. Slime becomes more popular than Jeremy? What do I do then? That's kind of what
I'm afraid of. And then I have to stop being Jerma and like retire as Jerma and then be Mr.
Slime. It'd be Hannah Montana. Oh, well, we'll see. I definitely want to like figure that out
though. That would be kind of fun. What would the voice, what would VTuber voice, what would
the voice be? I'd have the effects thing on. It would be something, it would be something fucking
gross. It'd be like something like this. I'd be like, shut up. Shut up and get out of here.
Get slimed. And that would, I would, that's the person I would be banning. Okay. It is far too
big for this interior. Let's replace it with something. I hope it becomes more popular than
me. I do. I really hope so. I hope, I hope Mr. Slime, I hope Green, Mr. Green Greens becomes a
huge star. Do you keep it? This piece of how, yeah, keep it. I don't want to do anything.
Fuck doing the work. I like Mr. Slime's more than I like Jerma already. Well, good. Yeah, go make
him famous. Okay. I thought it said hang a bathtub. That's fucked up. Okay. Hanging long bulb.
Okay. Rectangular carpet crossy. Uh, grabby bus chandelier. This ain't even my house. This is just
a tutorial. What are you going to do? I'm not going to tell you when the fuck that's happening.
No, I don't care. Guys, I don't care if I waste like 25 fucking hours of my life. I don't even
care. I'm never going to tell you where it is. Enormous wooden table. I mean, this is all just
supposed to go in here. So we're just doing this for the money. Mr. Slime waiting room.
Well, this is a pretty enormous leather sofa. What am I missing here? Oh, remove, remove,
get it out of here. Okay. Oakey light colored chairs, six of them. Slime, slime, slime.
You know, like doing the Mr. Slime stream once a week or once every like couple of weeks,
like that'd be a great stress reliever. It would just be me just flying off the fucking handle,
like just talking shit. What a, what an outlet for me. This is the coffee table.
I need like, anything I, anything I need to say or get off my chest. I have just the slime.
And I'd be a mod for the slime guy. I don't, we're not taking slime guy applications. Okay. Rug,
get this thing, wherever this goes. How about over here? Just give me my money. And then I'm
buying a huge house. Slime guy. Yeah. You don't know the name of the, you don't know the name yet.
You don't even know if that's even the name of the person. You don't even know if the
person's name is Mr. Slime. You think I'm going to tell you that right now? Painting gray
derangement. Booger boy. No, you have no idea. Nope. Dr. Jerma and Mr. Slime. Okay. Wall tiles.
We need light gray. I'm almost done. I do want to see the Simpsons house though. I really do
want to just take a look at it. If we guess right, will you tell us if we are right?
Um, I think you'll know. I don't know very many other people that are currently
streaming as a slime character on Twitch. Although I mean, I may have just like started
one of your careers. Like, Oh, I got to get on this right now. Slime, slime, slime, slime, slime,
avatar, slime, avatar, start it. And now they're going to be, people are going to be looking for
wait, Otto's bed. Wait, but how am I supposed to put this anywhere?
Now you'll know the real one. You'll know the real slime.
Good. I hope there are fucking imitators. You'll find the real slime guy.
Cause ain't nobody else can do this.
You don't know anybody in your whole life that can do that. I'm the only one.
So God find the one that's doing the fake one. That's like, not even fucking close.
You're not even close. Oh, floor panels too. Five out of 15. Don't ever do that again.
I have no idea what that sounded like. Let me hear it. Blink me it. I'd like to hear it.
This guy sucks. Get your own show. This is my show. I'm on it right now, man. What do you mean
the go get your own show? This is, I'm on German. I'm not going to get kicked off my own channel by
Mr. Slime booger boy. Hold on. I want to hear this. This is important. Mr. Slime call sign.
You'll find the real slime guy. Cause ain't nobody else can do this.
Why is it so robotic? It wasn't supposed to be like that. That just sounded like you had
part of your headphones were out a little bit and you didn't plug them all the way in
before you opened up an audio file. They're going to have to work on that.
It'll be a completely original voice. Okay. Floor panel. Palisander. No, what? Palisander.
Man of five voices. Nah, I see that joke a lot. Come on. I can do a lot. I can do a lot.
Come on, Gwen. You know that. You know that. I'm not a man of three voices. I'm a man of like
seven. That's a lot. Most people can only do one. They're on. I actually kind of like that floor.
Wait, there was a whole nother room. What was that? Was that the, did you open up the wrong
file on the computer? Where was that? Is that where we put all the trash? It was the garage.
Yeah. Whatever. That was the basement. Okay. Here we go. I want to buy my own house. All right.
Let's buy. I would buy my own house browser or purchase. I was on the moon. All right. HGTV.
I want to get one of the HGTV house. What's this one? Accountants house.
Oh, this is 169,000. How big is this one? One story house from the eighties. Not big enough.
Buy the moon. I don't have enough money to buy the moon. Moon, moon, moon, moon. I don't have
enough money. Amberlee house. A beautiful house for sale. Three bathrooms and a pool. Only serious
offers. I think we can make something out of this one. What are the ones that I own? Sell the houses.
Oh, okay. I own this one. I own this one too. What is this one? Sell this one for the moon house.
This looks pretty good. Whose house is this? I didn't even do anything with this place.
Is this the wall dad house? No, this is definitely not a wall dad. All right. Let's sell it. Submit
garden. Put the house on auction. Go to the garden competition. This is an American garden.
A lot of plants. The value of the house has increased by zero. Oh, whatever. Put it on auction.
Sixty seven thousand. Ninety two thousand. Ninety four thousand. It's good here. Ninety eight. Ninety
nine. Ninety eight. Okay. A hundred. We're over a hundred. A hundred and two thousand. All right,
Dolan. Congratulations. Okay. You have no positive opinions on the house. You only have negative
things to say about this. Let's negotiate. I want an extra, uh, I want an extra sixty. I want an
extra five thousand seven hundred dollars. Okay. Well, fine. You can have it. Wait, it's doing
before and afters here too? I've owned this house for a very long time. These pictures have taken a
very long time away from each other. There are not any doors. So I have enough money for the, uh,
the meme house, right? All right. Is the moon thing, is it going to be stupid or is it fun?
I hate this house. I'll take it. I'm not selling this one. I'll sell the other one. Look at this
place. I got double fountains. No, there's no way I'm going to sell this place. I love this place.
Okay. Owned. Burned house. Family guy house. Family guy house. Slime house. I live in the
family guy house. What happened in here? I didn't even do it. I didn't, okay. I didn't even attempt
to clean anything. This is why always go look at your apartment before you sign any documents.
Yeah, let's sell it. Submit it for a garden contest. It's a Japanese style garden.
You've been just lying. I haven't sent it in. Okay. Put this on auction. Anything more than
$25,000 to this place is a, you were losing way too much money. Same guy. He likes this place
more than the other one. Nolan's buying it again. Your offer is too low. I can sell the house for
$1 more. He refused it. That would have been so funny. There are no before and after pictures.
There are only just ugly pictures. All right. If you went on Zillow and you saw these as the
photos for the place, would you do it? Would you move in? But no, but it was a reverse. So it
looked like that, but they didn't update the pictures after they renovated. They put like
$80,000 into that place to make it nice. And they're using old photos. See? That's why they,
I always say, don't judge a book by its cover. $192,000. This better not be a bad idea.
This is all the money I have. I'm not selling the, Oh right. It is the family guy. Holy shit.
Oh my God. It's the, it is. It's like, architecturally, it's the house. It's the family
guy house. I thought it was just the outside. We knew this. No, no. I thought it was just like,
Oh yeah. The yellow paint. It looked like the house. I forgot. I made the family guy house.
Okay. $492,000. Let's go buy it. Portfolio. Okay. Or purchase. House on the moon. This house allows
residents to move away from the most earthly problems. Family who moves in here may have
problems with communicating, commuting, but they unearth. Do I really buy this before any thoughts
all the money I've made in the whole game? How do I make a cool house here? Like growing weed,
garden hose. Wait, why is this in the game? I can clean with this. I ran out of fuel. I have to buy
a new one in the store. Are you shitting me? Which two garden hose? I don't have it. Emolition
triceps. Where's the garden hose? You didn't air blast. Okay. This house, this is, this is a waste
of money. I'm going to clean it up and then put it on the auction. I'm going to try to make a million
dollars. I don't like this house. It's just, no, I don't like this. Yeah. That's the plan. I don't
want this. I'm just going to sell it. I'm going to make like $800,000 and then we can buy the most
expensive stuff in the world. This house is already ready. Flamethrower, mega low. I don't, I can't,
I don't have enough. This is the most expensive house. Yeah. I'm about to make a lot of expensive
profit from it too. Flip the moon house. Yeah. That's the idea. You're already ready. I just
gotta clean it up a little. I don't need any new furniture or anything. They look, they get in a
car. They get in a weed factory. They're getting a big security system. What's this for? Okay. All
right. It's a little cleaned up. Is there an upstairs? This is just pissing into bottles.
What is this weird bed set up? Why is this in a mirror? That's odd, right? It's like an office.
Two offices next to each other. There's no bathroom. If you walked over here and you
just like got up on a cliff and just pissed into the air, what would happen? Would it slowly fall?
Or would it just kind of go into outer space? What's the gravity like on the moon? It's like
minus two, like minus like five percent earth, minus 10% or something. What is it hiding his
like piss bottles? One sixth. That's kind of cool. All right. Cool. Cool. This is all expensive
stuff. It's three fits. Look at all this stuff. What is this? I just sell everything in this whole
house. How much is this worth? $180. Why not just sell everything and then sell the moon? You could
do the garden thing. Yeah, I did the garden DLC like a year ago or so. It was a lot of fun.
They're selling a car? All right. I'm going to sell the car first. What? Go to job. I thought I was
about to give this a full letter grade. That was close. Okay. I'm ready. Would I pay for it? $480?
$482? Already made money. I feel like this guy's following me around. Starting to feel like it's
the moon, man. I want an extra $2,000. There we go. Acceptable. I made $20,000. Now let's go do the
real house. Shit. I'm burning time here. I'm burning time. It's been like three hours. It
went by so quickly. No, not into the scream voice. I'm just saying it's been, I'm just kind of flew
by. Morning maple. Thanks to the five community subs. I missed it a while ago. Thanks. I appreciate
it. Okay. $510,000. Browser. Pink kingdom. Century old house. Accountants house. Uninhabited house.
A man cave. A family house. Or Samarta Myers house. Uninhabited house.
This house was bought for refurbishment. The current owner did not have time to do it. You're
looking for a buyer. Price is final. It's not negotiable. Beautiful big house in the back country
for sale. A lucky strike for people who have value silence. Decent one to take a rest from the city
noise and other people's company. Only you, your house, and the nature around you. This place was
abandoned many years ago. This place is huge. $254,000,000? It's this one. Family house. This
one looks like it has more rooms. Why is it? What's with the, uh, the radiation thing? Does that mean
it's like something bad? All right. Which one? Um, man cave or the like nuclear house? Well,
I'm seeing a lot of both. Slime house. All right. I'm going to take a, I'm going to go piss. I'll
give you a, a straw pole right back. I'm going to refill the water I have here too. I'm going to
get up and stretch a little bit as well. So here is a straw pole. I'm going to say nuclear or
man cave. Okay. I will be right back. Okay. Post the slime guy.
No, that will defeat the purpose. Uh, it looks like, uh, nuclear is, is just, is won by a long
shot. Thank you for voting. Okay. A big, beautiful house in the back country. Let's go there now.
Make it green. Everything. You would go nuts in that house. You would go fucking nuts. Uh,
it's the Halloween house. It's the Halloween house. I get it. Okay. Sure. Well, here's the
thing about this game. Um, that's just a scary person in the house. This is a game where I flip
houses and buy property and stuff. This is not in any particular universe. There's somebody in this
house. Run, get out now. It has to be the Mr. Slime's Halloween house. Okay. I'm going to go
to the house. I don't want to look at that for this TV too. I don't want any of this shit.
No, fuck that. I'm not making a Halloween house. I don't care how haunted this place
is. It's going to be a nice family place. Yeah. I don't care. You think I'm going to let that get
to me? You think I'm going to give in to that? Nope. It could be screaming faces in the bedrooms.
It doesn't matter there. Oh, I just saw the lights, but I have to spray the house. Good thing. I
don't have any neighbors because I'm a fucking wacko. It's like three o'clock in the morning.
Get rid of this too. It's like a bloody gnome. It moved. Yeah. I don't want that.
This is not a Halloween house. Get the hell out of there. That's Freddy Fazbear's house. Oh, no.
Weeds there. Can I get this place to light up? Or is this actually the haunted house
moment? I'm not going to ever have it to be daytime. You're a terrible window cleaner.
Pretty good at picking up weeds by the lights. I mean, I'm going to light this place up.
You're going to be able to see this house from space. I don't like this being in the dark shit.
A non-descript civilian. Thanks for the 10 community subs. Appreciate it. Thanks for the subs.
Place is almost pretty clean, at least on the outside. Look across the street. What's across
the street? Any slimers in chat? Slimers. Okay. What if I just did like a, a, a, a walk,
like that German walk thing that you guys are always put down, but as the slime.
Any joke I tell, this is where it's going to be really interesting.
Because any joke I tell on the slime stream, I'm going to tell it on my stream too.
We'll see who's funnier. I'm going to battle myself. He's going to just repeat jokes.
This is going to be great. I pick up these weeds, make Twitch drama with myself. Yeah.
Get that box out of here. Okay. Well, the lights, that's always very scary.
This is going to be a little ring girl here. Why am I doing this house? I,
I don't want to be doing this. I want to do the HGTV stuff, not a Halloween. What's that sound?
There's a leak somewhere. I don't see it. It's a ghost peeing. Well, he's gone for a pretty long
time. I know what that feels like, man. It's just you. You're peeing your pants. You're going to
pee his pants. So gross. I would not want to hold this vacuum. It's disgusting. Clean this.
The lights work. I'm putting more lights. I want way more lights. Why am I doing the Halloween map?
He's dirty. Dirt. All right. Dirt. We're good. House is clean. Look in the closet. I can't.
I can't look in the closet. Okay. So what do I want to do with this place?
We're going to, with the whole, we're going to take, we're going to take care of this top floor.
I want, let's get rid of this. Check the basement. Ghosts don't like that. No,
this is not going to be a ghost house. I'm going to, in fact, let's do this now. I want lights,
lamps, lighting. Ghosts are afraid of light. Let's get the brightest shit we can get
just for now. This is temporary. Okay. Here we go. Just fluorescent.
There's a big ass fluorescent light. Yeah. Have fun scaring me now. It's going to be very scary.
All right. Turn the light, turn the lamp on. Look at that. All the lights flicker, don't they?
The lights flicker. I can't do this one. I can't. The lights are going to flicker all the time.
All right. Where's the boss that I have to like smash his head in with the mallet in the basement?
Where is it? Is that, is it like a doll? I keep hearing doors open. Okay. This is it. Here we go.
The FOV just went to like 300. It's gas. It's gas. It's not a monster at all. It's gas.
That's what that sound is. Is there anything I can do? I'm selling this house. I don't even
want to do this. I want to do a different house. I don't like this one. Bunny moved. Whoa.
Dolan gets outbid for the first time. Look in the backyard. Wait, wait, what, what, what?
Refuse offer. Did we find $6,700? But whatever. That's not, that's nothing. I'm fucking, I got
like $300,000. That's fine. Where do you want to go? You didn't get rid of the curse. That's not
part of the deal. Look in the backyard. Who's in here? Bury it. Burying the coffin will probably
break the curse on this house. Wait, what? Oh, nice. Whoa. All right. Cool. I got a house now.
This is a huge basement down here. Oh my God. You know what's going down here. All right. Let's
clean this place up. This is like $4 million. I don't want any scary stuff. Hey, basement. This
wall, the basement wall is terrible. It has no taste. Well, hold on a second here. Not wanting
Saturn devours his children on my wall is, I mean, that's like a, that's like a family den.
That's where we're going to go play like Scrabble together. I don't want like, I don't, I don't,
I don't want to look at it. Basement Scrabble. What's wrong with basement Scrabble? Why does
this keep changing? There's a lot of fucked up rooms in this house. All right. Get rid of this.
Stream the Scrabble game. No, not everything has to be streamed. I delete this stuff. Get rid of
this door. What do I want to do? All right. What did I say? I was going to make a man cave.
I'm going to think of what to do up here. Make a man cave. Make a whole house man cave. No,
that's not what I was going to do. There's going to be a slime house. The door frame with the hammer.
All green, all green. Make a smaller house inside of this house. We got to get a clean slate and
then I'll figure it out. Make a casino. It needs to be a clear upstairs. Clear. I need to, I need
time to think. Make a casino. I don't think I can even make a casino. I'll try. Your house is a
casino. Make it a hotel. Casino hotel. Make the actual house ridiculously smaller than the house.
Okay, wait. I kind of like that idea. I like that idea. I like that idea. I want to do that.
Okay. That's what I want to do first. The first thing I want to do is have there be,
can I even break this all down? I don't think I can do that. Get rid of this fucking thing.
This is the door. Where's the front door? Here's the front door and you're forced to go up the
stairs. This is going to be walled off. There's not going to be anything here. Forced to go up the
stairs and then this door here on the left is not going to be here. This is going to be just a bed
and a toilet like here. Make it a labyrinth. Rip frames. No kitchen. Now we'll make a kitchen.
It'll work. I'm going to put like, I'm going to say, okay, it's going to be like an electromagnetic
house all around the outside before I build the inside. It's going to be a bunch of like,
a bunch of like anti like 5G rays and stuff and like tin foil and stuff. I'm going to be
completely protected on the inside. I'm going to make the walls out of like steel bunker house.
It's going to be a DMT house, 5G broadcasting station, a cell tower. Just make it a cell tower.
Okay. Looking, getting there, getting there. Get rid of all this shit. That's not where I want it
to be. This is all junk. We don't need it right now. This is a great link. I think I've, I think
we've seen this before. Put that in the house. So big. This is huge photo. Fit to screen. Squished.
Put that on. All right. Maybe. No, I don't want that. I cannot fucking believe I'm about to do the,
just make a small house in the house. I, why am I doing this? This is not, I, this is stupid.
Make a big house in a small house.
No, it'll, no, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait. I kind of like the idea of having a hotel. I don't know.
I don't know yet. I don't know yet. I need to see, I got to get a clean slate or like a big theater
with a bunch of chairs and I like a performance stage. Like the, I, the entire theater staff are
asking for a raise. No, I mean, just like the whole, the house is a movie theater. The actual
house is a movie theater. Wait, I already made a movie theater? When did I make a movie theater in
Hubslipper? Did I? I made a movie theater? No, I didn't. I made a bowling alley. I made a mall with
a bowling alley in it. I didn't make a movie theater. It's the same thing. No, just because
some bowling alleys are in movie theaters and some movie theaters are in bowling alleys doesn't mean
that they're the same thing. Okay. So this is the upstairs. This is the space that we have to work
with down here. All this space out here. We're taking on everything. I need to be able to see
everything. And it's the basement, right? The basement too. Okay. Hold on and make, make a
bowling alley and movie theater. Make it a prison. Making a maze is kind of funny and like you finally
get down here. Make a working society. Make it a maze where you have to go through the maze to get
to the bathroom. This is such a pain in the ass. Unscrew. Oh wait. Yeah. Yeah. I don't want this
to be bathroom. Okay. Cool. I like, don't mind this yet. The house is going to be green. It's a secret
basement wall. Hey, I'm shitting myself. Where do I go? Well, I would just stay put that you can
really figure out what the hell you're going to do with yourself. Running around and sprinting
and screaming and oh my God, oh my God. That's not going to help you. That's going to make everything
worse. Cool. Just make the whole house a solid wall. So I'll open it up so I can get a good look.
All right. We got a good look. Basement goes down here and so does that. The basement cannot be
destroyed. It's a brick house. I'll fix it. Make a normal house. You know, that is what an interesting
concept. Jeremy, why don't you just make a house and make it like look good and really show us like
what you would do when you designed the house. I mean, should I ban that guy because make a normal
house? I don't think I even could. All right. Demolition is done. I got 250 grand. I'm good.
Plenty of money. I'll wait outside. Shit. I have to do this too. Damn it. Dig up the coffin.
I don't even know where the coffin was. All right. We look at the entrances. We've got
these lamps that I don't like. Okay. Front door. That's what it looks like on the outside. You walk
in. You can go right. You can go left and down. This is important because, all right, here's what
we're going to do. Okay. We're going to seal this off. Okay. You can put one there. We're going to
seal that off. We're going to seal this off too. And then I'm going to make an entire elaborate
like not just try to leave. If I'm going to make a maze, I need to make it hard. Is it okay? Is there
a way that I can make the maze go down here and end up back up the stairs? Okay. I think so. Wait,
I think there is. Oh yeah. I can do that. Are you kidding me? Because then I can go like this. No,
I can't because I can't split this down the middle. Shit. All right. I need a second staircase.
You can't put a staircase. You can't remove and you cannot put new staircases in, unfortunately.
So I need to do something with this. I think this is where the illegal casino is. All right.
That makes complete sense. Start down here. Uh, more muscle store. We need to have a really,
really crazy floor. Bathrooms. Should there be a bathroom down here? Molding bag. Let's go.
Okay. Furniture. I don't need some like bar tables. See a good one. Where's a good like,
no, these are good like poker tables or a blackjack table. We need like a big circle.
How big are these? Well, they're enormous. Shelf? No. Leather. Let's do,
let's just see how big they are. I mean, they're fucking huge. There's only one game down here.
One huge game of blackjack. That's so big. It's like 15 people can play. No, no, no, no, no.
It's got to be smaller. Table, table, table. We need table. Table. Ella. Table. Mooner. There we go.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Okay. There we go. Okay. So this is like the blackjack and shit.
Slots are going to be in here. See what could be a slot? I need chairs and slots. Lamps. There's
got to be a weird fucked up lamp. That's, that's not bad. Can that be on the ground?
Wall lights. Put mirrors on the walls. Make a fun house.
Why did you pick the poop colored table? I don't know. Make a fun house. Mirror. Oh shit.
No, this is going to be fucked up. Make a mirror maze. Make a mirror maze. It's going to be
impossible to find my way out. This is going to be so trippy. It's not even, this is going to suck.
This kind of looks good. It does kind of look good. Weirdly enough. How quickly would you go
crazy if all your walls are mirrors? He's a vampire. But I thought vampires weren't supposed
to be able to see the reflection. Oh yes. Yes. This shit's going to take forever. This is going
to take forever. This is where I'm, okay. This is where I just come to meditate. You look like
you're playing a Wolfenstein level. I got plenty of money, right? You, what do you mean stop you?
I didn't, what do you mean ruin? I didn't ruin anything. Stop, stop, stop. Uneven. Fix it.
This is just a first draft. There. I got it. I fixed it. I fixed it. Are there any bigger
fucking mirrors? Seriously, are there bigger mirrors? This is going to take, this is horrible.
This is just like a solar paneled basement, which makes no sense. You come in with a flashlight
and shine it at him? What are you doing? You're just that guy that's super into solar. Yeah,
you know I got solar. I got solar literally everywhere. I got into my fucking bathroom
and powers my teeth brushes, my toilets, my lights. I don't even have a roof anymore. I
took the roof off and the sun just shines on all these panels. We're getting there. This is,
this is like room you pay to get into. This is like a fun room, right? This is the anti-5G room.
This is the 5G room. This is one of those rooms where you go in and you just shine a single like
laser pointer at the wall and he'd probably kill you. You know, it was just going to ricochet off
like 500 mirrors. He's going to kill you. Nice totally spies logic. That's so funny. Okay, when
I'm not going to do the whole house like this, that would be so painful to me. It would, I would,
it would cause me physical pain, I think. I can't do the whole house. Look at how good it looks.
That's not going to look good upstairs. Get the bigger mirror. Okay, this is the mirror house.
This is the mirror house. Mirror house. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Hot, hot, hot, hot,
hot, hot, hot. I want the mirror. I want the bed I sleep on to be a mirror. Big. Somebody said
there's a big mirror. I think that's the biggest mirror you can get. Mirror module? No, it's as big
as it gets. There's no large or anything. Wait. Mirror Lamont. Mirror module. No, I can't. This is
as big as I can make it. There's more? All mirrors. No, there's no. I mean, here's mirror. This is not,
this is not even that much bigger. On the left, on the left. Hold on. I'm getting spammed. Mr.
Slime's playing. Yeah. No, that's not what it's going to look like. It's not what it's going to
look like. Not what it's going to look like, guys. Sorry. There's a mirror category. Where's the
mirror category? Old-fashioned mirror. Mirror. Mirror. I don't think this is bigger. I don't say
mirror. I don't think it's big enough. Well, I'm going to keep going with what I was doing.
I hate this. I'm only doing one room like this. I'm never going to open it. I don't even care
what's in here. I'm only finishing this room because I have to. Sort by size. Uh, sort by size.
Sort by oldest. Descending. Alphabetical. Price. You can't sort by size. What are you? What's
this? Jebait. Okay. I'm done with this shit. I'm just going to put a bunch of weird lights
so the ricochets off and I have to dodge the laser. I also kind of feel like this is going
to break the game. If I turn a light on in here, I think that's the game's going to probably crash.
Mirror modules connect. Oh no. No. No, no, no, no. No. I can't do. The whole house is a mirror.
We're going to be here for so long. You know how long that's going to take? It's going to be like
a portal gun house. Oh shit! Okay. All right. I'm sorry everybody that's not going to want this to
happen. I'm sorry everybody! I'm sorry. Even the outside is going to be a mirror. I'm going to get
lost. Oh Jesus. This is bad. Oh no. Should I put obstacles in the way? I wish I could control Z.
I'm not going to run out of money, right? This is one of those absurd custom houses that you will
never sell. Ever. You're going to have to demolish this house. Oh HGTV presents interesting houses.
Better be your permanent residence. Yeah, you know, we decided on having full of mirrors just
so I can kind of see everything. Always make sure like nothing was wrong in the house. Why is it
Kermit? Man, I got, I got 10 voices. I really got like a lot of inspiration from insects. You know,
they have like a hundred eyes. Kind of mimic that in my real life. I mean, I get a little nauseous.
I get a little nauseous, but it's worth it. Peeing is hard though. I can't tell if the toilet I'm
peeing into is the real one or one of the mirrors. Hard to pee. But what I did is I just turned the
whole bottom into a urinal. This bathtub works pretty well. Nine more voices to go. That's right.
I'm going to have to paint that gray. If you stood in the middle. Okay. If you put like a light in
the middle of this room, I really wouldn't be afraid. I would get electrocuted. You can move
it to the left. No, look, I can't see. I can't, can't do it. Question is, can I do this instead?
Yup. Yup. It can be fixed. Hey, at least I'll be able to stand anywhere in my house while the main
character comes in and I get to go. That's cool. I get to do that. I lost. No, I can't do it. This
is already freaking me out. We're not even like a 10th of the way there, but what happens if the
guys, guys, I'm in trouble. Oh, I don't like this. This hurts. I don't like this. Your house is going
to be invisible. These need to be lower. I can't even fit these here. Uh, yes, I can actually.
Excuse me. What are you talking about? What do you mean you can't fit it there?
I can't fit it here. Shit. Remove the window. You can't remove windows. It's impossible. Break
the top first. I can't. Cause this is a, this is part of the structure. All right. What like weird
cartoon doors can I have? Pretty mirror-esque. That's pretty much a mirror. Make a mini-golf.
I'll do the outside. All right. Can I make a normal house? Like did I, can I make a normal house?
When can I make a normal house? Like, like, should I, can I do that? Oh Jesus. Okay. I'm just going
to get this done. I'm going to get this done. Get it done. Get it done. Get it done. Get it done.
Get to work. Um, what do you think I'm doing? The mirror thing was your idea. It was? No,
it wasn't. Was it? No. Somebody else said, Hey dude, put mirrors everywhere. Come on. Stop it.
It was you. All right. Hold on. Hold on. We're going. We're going. We're going. We're going.
We're going. We're going. I can't put them there. When I actually stand in the middle of this room,
somebody's actually going to puke. I need to make a really, really fair warning.
Here's your warning now. When I stand in the middle of the room, when this is done
and there is furniture and lights in here, one of you is going to throw up. I just want to make
sure that you know that now. I can go faster than this shit. Come on. Think on the bright side.
You're going to be immortalized as the genius streamer who created the mirror house.
Um, you probably should put mirror in quotes. It's misaligned. It's never going to be aligned
right. I'm going to paint it the same color. Don't worry. Security system.
Fuck it. Don't need it. I don't need lights yet. Oh, oh, I already hate it. Oh, I hate it.
It's not even done. I don't like it. I don't like it. I don't like it. I don't like it. I don't like
it. I really don't. I don't like it. Something in my body just wanted to just recoil backwards
and scream. This is a good idea because the burglar can't find your shit now. I mean, that's
yeah. You got that right. That makes sense. But, um, have fun stubbing your toe on every single
thing in your house. And I don't mean just like stubbing your toe once. I mean every single item.
You're going to constantly be in a state of just, just disarray. You're going to bump into the
couch. You're going to hit your head on the fucking ceiling lights and shit. Is it going to be bad?
I don't think I could, I don't think you could pay me enough money to live in this house. This
would start to really, really get to me in a week. Remember the music's driving me insane.
What should I put on instead? Ceiling mirrors? Uh, you can't do ceiling mirrors. See the only
thing that we have to escape is to stare at the ground or stare at the ceiling. Can't fit them
here. Why not? What? Bullshit. Put on Luigi's Mansion? That's not a bad idea. Oh God. I'd
prefer it to be like this. Is that real? Is which one's real? All right. Yeah. This is horror music.
I'll turn the horror music off. There we go. Horror music off and Luigi's Mansion OST.
I remember that sound. Okay. That's not bad for a second. I thought, wait, if I do mirrors here
too, right, is it going to work the way that I think it is? This is not even lined up. Is the
OST really the opening cut scene? Let's be honest. I just scared the shit out of me. Hello. Here it
comes. Right. This is the song, right? This doesn't look right. Why does it look so off? Oh, okay. Um,
okay. What is a hundred gecks? Like everyone can, I see that all the time. What's a hundred gecks?
Shit. It doesn't fit. I can't, what? I cannot believe I'm doing this, but it's, I can't back
out now. If I back out now that it's a failure, I can't back out. I have to do it. Oh, mom.
The game's having trouble rendering the actual, you know what it looks like? It just looks like
the game hasn't loaded all the assets in the house yet. It just looks blurry and fucked up.
Check settings to make better reflections. Well, one, hold on one step at a time. One step at a
time. We're almost, we're almost done with the first floor. It's already starting to have
problems. Okay. Let's do, all right. I can build a wall here. Wait, I can just do that over there
too. This house is going to give me mercury poisoning. Mercury house. We need just flat.
All right. I, this is where I really blew it. Okay. This is how I blew it. We just need one
full thing across. I fucked it all up by needing the, like, just like this, a straight line across.
Restart. I'll show you how you restart. You just pretend this wall doesn't exist behind me.
Hold R. Building distance is one meter more. Oh, cool. This reminds me of Earthbound. I get
Earthbound vibes from this. Let's go. I'm ready. Don't make mistakes. It takes longer. It takes
longer if you make a goddamn mistake. Just get it right. Fuck. Whatever. This is riveting gameplay
here. Like, holy shit. This is unbelievable. What did you do on your Wednesday afternoon?
Watched a crazy guy, uh, mirror every wall in his house. Uh, dude, just, um, like, you were ghosting
me. That you'd rather do that than, like, hang out with me? Yeah. All right. Yeah. Sorry, dude. And,
like, you know what, man? Lose my number. I just, I'm just gonna take this opportunity right now.
Like, we just don't, we don't, like, see eye to eye on anything. And you're kind of like a dick,
man. Like, I've just, I'll talk to you later. This is gonna make my house look way bigger.
No, it's not. This is just what the house looked like without the mirror wall. I'm giving myself
an illusion to a house that exists behind this wall. Why? Infinite house. Infinite housing.
All right. Okay. I'm making a house. I'm making a house. I'm making a house. I'm done. I have to
stop doing this now. My sanity is at stake at the moment. Like, I don't, I don't want to do this.
This is stupid. But, like, I could make a big... All right. All right. All right. All right. All
right. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I know what I have to do. I know what I
have to do. I know what I have to do. I'm in too deep. Yeah, I am. Oh, son of a bitch. Sunk cost
fallacy. Turn up reflections. Okay. Graphics. Brightness. Graphics API. Brightness. Field of
view. What the fuck is this doing here? Resolution. Advanced. Shadows. Screen space reflection.
What is that? What do you want? Motion blur. Fog. Make it extreme? Extreme quality. Dude,
what are you doing? Monsters are going to spawn in the gap. Same Minecraft, man. He said M. He
said monsters. He said the M word. God. Okay. So, I'm just curious to see what happens. Okay.
Let me just... Give me one second. Furniture. I'm just going to put a chair in here. Okay. Just
a swivel chair. Wait. Why is it on in the mirror world but not on in the real world? Let's keep
going. Such a colossal waste of time. Jojo reference? What did I do? Actually, this is
starting to take shape. All right. Never mind. Hold on. This is starting to take shape. Dude,
is that a Jojo mirror? Oh, by the way, I saw an image of me on the internet. Somebody put, like,
Pokemon sandals on me. People just doctor photos I'm in. People were so excited that
I was wearing Pokemon sandals in this photo. And that's not real. Somebody put that in. I didn't
do that. The only thing they doctored in the whole entire picture. Why is this upside down?
This stream is going to make somebody sick. How do I get out of here? This song is killing me.
How do I get out? I have to get the fuck out. This song came on and it fucked up everything.
Okay, get that off. I don't want to hear that one again. I don't want to hear that song ever again.
Trapped in mirror hell. I'm going to make you guys the home of my dreams. I'm going to do that.
I'm going to start that shit after the mirror house. I'm getting this one out of the way so
we can go to the mirror out of here. It's not this. This is not the house of my dreams.
I'm going to sell this one. There's a guy in the mirror. There's not a guy in the mirror.
Who are you going to sell it to? Dolan. He's loaded and he doesn't care about any of his money.
I could probably call Dolan on the phone and say, hey, yo, Dolan. Can you buy my house for
$400,000? And you just say yes and hang up. Yeah, I'll wire you the money immediately.
Thanks, Dolan. I can always count on you. Yeah. Hey, if you ever fuck up a whole house again,
just let me know. If you like burn it down, you like put mirrors everywhere or you fucking like
torch it. Yeah, just let me know, man. I'll buy it for 500,000 every time. Do a Trump impression.
Um, why? I can't handle this anymore. I don't even know if those are lined up. I don't care.
It's fucking me up so bad. No, no, either finish mirror house or you have to do a political stream.
Um, how about I just say, uh, no. Yeah, I can't wait for, I can't wait for Mr. Slimes to be like
a political streamer. He would. I'm not going to, I'm kidding. Fast German versus purple alien.
Is this the music from fast German purple alien? Is it really? Nice. I mean, this is when you catch
a ghost. I know this one. Okay. Um, I don't even want to go over there. You guys gave me
Luigi's Mansion soundtrack and it's, it's the worst possible soundtrack to listen to right now.
Oh, I'm going to lose my mind. Luigi's Mansion two, any good or is it just
three only play three in one by the disappearing. I think I'm running out of asset space. Yeah.
It's getting a little sloppy. He's getting a little sloppy. He is. He's getting sloppy.
I gotta, I have to start to move. I have to get, I have to move. I seriously have to move.
I can't look at that anymore. Okay. He's going psycho. I'm kind of, man, it's like,
this is difficult to do and not to have like a freak out. Okay. All right. All right. That's
fun. That was fun. Let's put some furniture in my house. Let's do, uh, lights. Furniture. I want a
couch. I want one of these cool things right, uh, right here. More mirrors. Just wait. I'm
trying to decorate my house. Finish the stairs, but hold on a second. Fucking crack music. I
swear to God. Furniture. I need to put on, um, dining room table over here. It's just a dining
room or a kitchen. Um, okay. We'll put the, I can't, I gotta go. I gotta go. I have to stop.
Stop, stop. Turn it off. Turn the music off. Turn the fucking music off. Turn the music off.
Turn off the music. I need ceiling lights. Humanity restored.
I just, I want to just make a house. Why did I have to do this?
I could have just easily had just made a house with like a TV and here we go. Oh, I can't,
I can't look at it. I can't look at it. Oh my God. I'm trapped in a nightmare. It's a fucking
nightmare house. TV. What's big? A bed? Put in a disco ball. I'm actually, I'm actually going to
move on. I'm, this is going to kill me. I'm, I have to stop doing this. Why can I not stop doing
this? Why do I want this to crash? Why do I want this to break? I'm going to turn off some of the
lights. Some of them, only a few of them. I feel like this is what it would be like if I was in a
human fish tank. Do you know how we put shit in a fish tank? Just like, uh, fish like coral and a
little castle. Human. Plant a computer sofa and a chair. Oh, I, now I know where I am. This is,
I know my surroundings. I just open up my mouth and just like meat just falls down. Human fish
tank. This looks like a bank. This looks normal. Like it looks like a bank. What would you classify
is odd? It looks like a bank. Oh, get rid of it. Get rid of it. I don't want to look at it.
Why did I put that up there to taunt myself? All right. I'm making it. I'm selling this house.
I don't want it anymore. Sell this fucking thing. Sell it. I don't want it. I don't want this. I'm
done. Sell the house, please. I don't, I'm going to make a real house. No more messing around. No
more like joke, shitty joke shit. No, I'm not making it bowling alley. I'm not making a movie
theater. Although there could be a cool sick theater in there. Auction. I don't want it.
Put a disco ball. It's actually going for a lot. Was it the mirrors? Holy shit. Fuck the disco ball.
I'm just taking it. Why is it taking so many? You know, the house is fucked up. I got a tip
for you guys. When the realtor is only taking pictures of the same room from 10 different
angles. Probably might want to skip that one. When they just show you a photo of the outside
of the house and one of the bathrooms and you know that it's like 1400 square feet. Don't go
to that one. And look at that. Don't go to this one. But Dolan just buys every house. So who cares?
He has a grand scheme where he's going to own all the property in whatever town this is.
And he's going to be a mogul. Do they update this game a lot? From, from what I gather, I believe so.
There's been at least two or three major major updates to this game in the last couple of years,
right? Okay. I'm doing a real house. Real house. No more messing around. I'm going to get a real
house and I'm going to make it the way that I would. I would, my dream home. Okay. I have to do
this. Which one do I want though? Hmm. Family house. Man cave. Oh yeah. All right. Let's do the man
cave. Let's go. I'm ready. Now I'm sorry. I just punched you in the face. I'm ready. So let's take
a look. What are we, what are we working with here? Oh, okay. This is coming down. What's this for?
World's best dad. Well, we know who lived here before. It's a Reddit house. I got to have the
streaming room. Okay. This is going to be my garage. It is a garage. Right. Here's the streamer room.
There's going to be one. I'm going to do the, I'm going to make my exact fucking room.
Make the Reddit. This is the Reddit house. What a huge fucking yard. All right. We're going to go
outside, outside first. The spray can. Make Otto's room. I need to cut the lawn. I should have a
little like tomato garden back here. Yup. Use the lawnmower. I don't have one. I don't have a
lawnmower. Where do I get it? Flamethrower. Oh, I can burn the grass. You're right. I have to buy
one in the store. I'm out of fuel. Okay. Fuel for the flamethrower. Refueled. That's so much faster
than mowing the lawn. And I pull the goggles down and look over. Hey Tim, there's a hot one today.
You're killing the grass. Oops. It's okay Jim. Yolan will fix it. I didn't want that shit
anyways. Who wants that? This is so much faster. This is so much faster. Why clean when you can
just burn your house down? You're the neighbor looking in here. Oh my God. Mike's finally lost
his mind. Just taking care of some yard work. You know, by the way Jim, that tree's kind of hanging
a little bit far over on my side of the property, don't you think? By the way, flip us around and
pretend I'm you saying that. What I meant to say was I'll take care of it. I did it in the
reverse way. You get it Jim. You get it. We're buddies. We know each other. He's mirror mad.
Oh wait, I am actually killing all the grass. I am. I actually am. Act's not available yet. What?
The way you don't understand it when you do it this way, you never have to have a lawn. You never
have to mow the lawn. Never have to cut the grass. Never have to take care of it ever. It's just gone.
I thought this was going to take like two hours to do this out here. Nope. This is so much quicker.
WM1. Lawn mower. Wait, why am I adding grass? Yo, you melted the driveway. Oh, oh, okay. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I mean, this is very important. Give me one second. Okay, I just need
this. This is important for me to do this. Hold on. Where is it? I need, I need the crit sound. Okay,
we're good. I need to be able to press this a shitload of times. Here we go. Okay, we're good.
Give me one sec. I'm just going to add this to my stream deck. This is going to be a audio.
Random crits. Yeah. The back burner. I'm back-burnering my house. Okay.
Play audio. Audio comes from. Just download it. There it is. Where did that download to? Shit.
Hold on. Is it on desktop? It's on, it's on desktop, desktop, desktop, desktop, desktop, desktop,
desktop. There it is. Okay. Here we go. Let's test it. It works. Okay. This is play.
L fade. All right. And let's go ahead and start to play the game. I'm playing. Hey,
Jim. Not the house. Oh shit. The new pyro update. The fucking hose. You got to land it directly on
their fucking head. Nice. I love this fucking target map. How do they add this? That'd be awesome.
If there was like a water spray can. All right. What was I doing? What was I doing?
Flamethrower. Not bad. This was going to take so long. Not anymore. Okay. How come this doesn't
take off the graffiti? I'm going to pave the whole backyard anyways. Don't worry. This is
supposed to be my dream. My man cave. I mean, there's going to be four basketball courts or
as it leaves the grass, more muscle. That's cool. I missed a spot. I know I'm going to get it.
I'm actually probably better off. Okay. It's ready to be cleaned. I'm probably better off just using
the actual mower now. It must be burned. All right. Look at that. It was so overgrown with
vegetation and now it looks great. It looks flat. I need to get rid of this in the front.
Not that much more. This, it doesn't want to get destroyed for some reason.
Mini golf. Oh yeah. Yeah. All right. I'll get, let me, I'll do this later. I've got to clean.
Eep world's best dad. Maybe. Maybe. Okay. That's fine. I'm going to clean the windows.
This is just so messed up. It's going to need a complete overhaul.
There is something about no one will ever be able to replicate this. TF2 did this the way that you
felt after hearing that sequence of crit, crit, crit, crit, crit, crit, crit, crit, crit, crit,
something about it. It was the most, it was like dopamine just flooding into your brain.
No game will ever be able to, I don't think we'd ever be able to make that feel like that again.
When you shot two crit rockets in a row in TF2, nothing can replace that. Especially if you did
it into like a little corridor and you do those like six people in there and it was just, it just
went like this. You just heard it. You'd go, it was like, Whoa, look at the kill. I got six people.
It was amazing being on the receiving end of that though, was like uninstalled TF2. Why
there random crits? This game's nice job valve random crits, huh? They hear this place out.
Like you would hear that noise or no, you would not hear that noise. You didn't get to hear it.
That's the worst part. If you get hit by a random crit, you don't get to hear the cool noise. You
just explode. Does it play fall guys? Um, no, not right now. Okay. World's best dad. Can I,
I don't think I can go around this. I mean, I guess I could put, I could put a bureau here
and just block this out until it's just world's best dad. Play Mario maker. Didn't I make,
I made like a Mario maker reference today. What was it? They don't remember what it was. Like,
Oh yeah. How like Mario maker. Why did I say that earlier? It was yesterday.
You go many extremely thinks he's the best dad. That was a good game. You were calling your fake
friend. Oh, right, right. Okay. I'll just loser thinks you can make a better dad than anyone.
I think I'd be okay. I think I'd be a pretty good dad.
Okay. So every night that's well, that's not a cool dad. I have a funny story for you. So we
get, we gave Otto this new food because of his Addison's and we're trying to like get him on
some like better food and different food. Uh, so I've been given it to him and a friend of mine
was here and the friend of mine saw me put this, this fresh like dog food into his bowl
and he thought I was giving the dog queso. He really thought that's what it was. He was like,
what are you doing? Cause it's in this, like this weird package. It like you like dump it out. And
he was just like, why are you doing, why are you feeding your dog queso? And something about like
that was just making me fucking die laughing. I'm like, why would somebody do that? Just give
your dog queso every day. Like that's fucking insane. Like, why do you think I was doing this?
There's already a man cave down here. I can't even make it mine. Is that picture of Elvis?
Who is that picture of? I don't know. Oh, lucky, lucky. No, this man cave is not, I don't want this
stuff. This is my standup comedy studio. That's where I practice all my new jokes. What are you
doing? Pick it up. Any golf? Yeah. Yeah. We got to clean this place up a little bit first. What's
wrong here? Why is there, why is there like consecration on the walls? Does it do anything?
Did I get it? Oh, what? How can I, I can't remove these. I burnt it all. That's why
I cannot remove these. That's annoying. The house is clean. There's one more piece. It's right here
somewhere. I can't, where is it? Did I get it? Cool. What color does the house, is the house going
to be? What color does the house want to be? I'm thinking make it purple, make it a mirror. No,
we're not doing that again. Not happening. Okay. How about, what about walls? Uh, light colored
medium panels, pistachio. This is kind of, yeah, this is like a Rocco's modern life house.
I'll try this. Yeah. All right. It's like Rocco's modern life. His house, the Rocco's modern life
looked like this. The cartoon house. This is a nineties house. Oh, actually, I don't know. Is
this supposed to be my dream house? I can't do that. I can't decide. All right. This is a bathroom.
Let me think of what I want. When I walk in my house. Okay. I'm closing my eyes.
Walk in. What am I looking at? Got a place to put my like keys right here. Okay. Kitchen right here.
Yep. Okay. Kitchen. This leads over to the, this is my little living room area.
I don't know if I want the bathroom there. I don't know. There's only one bathroom.
What is this place? Bedroom? Bedroom. Garage. Okay. Garage down to here. Maybe this should be.
Yeah. Okay. Stream. We'll start with the stream room. I'm going to make the stream room that I
want. All right. Stream room time. Here we go. Where is this? I need a stream room. This is,
this is bedroom. Bedroom. Bathroom. I need a stream room. Take the basement, the gamer room.
No, no, no, no. I can't. No, no. It's got to be a separate thing. Bedroom. Stream room. Basement
for VR. Okay. Yeah. We'll do this. We'll make a wall here. Kitchen. Where's the TV going to go?
This place is too small. TV here. Couch there. I think so. Just buy a bigger house. Well,
I've already committed. All right. So this is going to be the stream room. The glass house.
No, it's not. This is going to be, it's going to be nice. Use the scroll wheel to make the sections
larger. Thank you. Wow. You just saved me like a hundred years. Okay. Now we need to make
the door here. How big is it? One, two, three. That's good. Right. The basement is going to be
sick. Don't worry. This is the streamer room. Okay. The desk is going to go here. I have an
L-shaped desk and I've got the one, two, three monitors. Okay. Let's go to type in desk.
No, here we are. There we are. This is Walnut too. Already. It's the exact one. This is my desk.
Wait, that's wrong. What? Why does this feel incorrect? How would you sit here and touch the,
it's like that, right? I want it to be like that. Shit. I can't, I built it the wrong way. Whatever.
Okay. There's that. I need to make, I need to get my book and my office max,
Quadro 4000. Spell it right. For God sakes. Okay. Chair. Oh, I mean, you have to.
This is gigantic. How is this bigger than the desk? I don't know. Every time I see one of these,
I honestly, I just think about it's going to lean back and the dentist is going to come in
and just start drilling my teeth. Queso chair. Now we need monitors. Computer. What kind of
computer do I have? Uh, probably like this one. And it's under here. My computer sits under here.
Okay. Then what do you mean? What the fuck is? Oh yes. It's on the floor. Under floor, under the
desk, except on the other side. All right. Now we need monitor. Holy shit. I don't have that though.
That's me lying to you. I don't have that monitor HD. Not it either.
Monitor. I just need the little ones. I, I need to do my setup. There we are. Okay. Here we go.
Ready? This is what it looks like. I know people are being like this. You know, you gotta, you gotta
look at a glimpse into my life. Three. Yeah. Three. All right. That's good. Where's the keyboard? I'm
working on it. Backlit keyboard brushy. Oh, that's actually kind of scary. This is, this is the one
I use. Nice. Okay. Now we need a mouse. Gaming mouse pad. And then a mouse. Okay. That looks good.
And then what else is in here? There's a Reddit shelf behind me. This is pretty close. Where's,
no, there's, there's one that looks like this. Where is it? Soap is tables, desk, chairs, beds,
armchairs. Decorations? No. Where is it? It's not walls. Is it a bookcase? Installations? No.
Decorations? Accessories? No. Where is it? Put a step stool in there. No, I don't think so. I mean,
I would like to have a sauna. Books? Where? I've seen it. Where the hell is it? Oh well. Oh well.
Other? Whoa. What's this? Aquarium? That'd be cool. Shelf? Yeah. I, I, you think it would just
show up under shelf. It looks like this, except it's, it's kind of tilted. This is, this will do.
Furniture. Furniture. Furniture. Furniture. Furniture. Furniture. Furniture. I don't see it.
Wait. I think this is it. Hold on. Yep. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You got it. You got it.
It kind of looks like this one, right? And then we got to put like a bunch of sound paneling all
over the walls. First, I want to paint this lime green. Wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
a spearmint green. Spearmint green. Paint. Here we go. Uh, faded lemon. Not a bad choice.
Spring grass. There it is. Oh, I love it. I love this color so much. It's just, it makes me feel
so good. This is a little too dark. This is too dark. It's, it has to be lighter than this,
but this is the closest it's going to get. Slime room. Guts room. It kind of is a Nickelodeon room,
but that's all right. It is a Nickelodeon room. It's because of that chair. It's the yellow chair.
Orange, whatever. You need a bucket of plaster. Oh, fuck off. All right. Let's get a bucket of
plaster. Uh, I think that mirror house changed me forever. I'm like, I'm like forever a different
person. You okay? Same, to be honest. So is Desperados 3 actually a good game? I want to play
it, but I had to, there was a promise I had to keep. I believe it is. Music being off makes this
really strange. Yeah, it kind of does. How about, um, sounds like another, uh, it's a generic shooter.
No, no more scary shit. Hackman World 2. Silent Hill is scary shit. Hackman World OST,
full soundtrack. All right, nice. I'm looking forward to this. I love this guy. All right,
let's do it. That's enough of the green. I think it looks good. I don't want the wood though.
Remember, I'm a carpet guy. I know, you know, punching, punch him, punch him, get him, kick
his ass, right? I know. That wasn't meant to be a joke. I know, don't make the crickets thing.
Okay. Floor. Floor, panels, and covering. Here we go. Green carpet. No, I'd like a, like a, like a
gray, a gray or a little blue. So gray carpet. I think I'm into the, the, this one can blend in
pretty well. That would have let the dog in. This is just like what the, this is what you hear if
you're a fucking Mike's neighbor. Hey Jim. Oh, just throwing my trash out the second story window,
trying to land it into the trash can. Have a good day. Why does he keep using Let's Plays for OST?
This is Pac-Man world OST full soundtrack, high quality. All right, that looks nice. The green
doesn't work. It's not the right green. It's not the right, it has to change. It's not the right
green. It just isn't. Wait, is it pistachio or is it ice blue? Is it pistachio? You know, don't do
that. There's no mirrors to do that with. I like it. This is not a Let's Play. You're missing the
plot. Shit, I'm missing the plot of Pac-Man world two. There we are. That's nicer. I said this is a
Miku room. Um, let's just say blue room. This is like water. Robin's egg. This is Robin's egg blue.
This is not Miku blue. It's not what it says on the can. What? This is a song. Miku blue.
I like it. It's a great color. It's just like, it's teal. We're not going to replace the word
teal with Miku blue. I'm sorry. I'm not participating. What else is even in this room? Christmas door?
What's a Christmas door? All right, internal door white. That works. What about the soundproofing?
I'll do it. Okay, good. Wait, it's not good. It's not lined up right. Looks like shit is what it
looks like. Why does it look so wrong? This looks like we leaned it in here and just didn't install
it. All right, son, be very, very careful. Don't put too much weight on the door because it's not
actually in there. It's just standing. There we go. That's a little odd. I'll fix it later.
Remember, still going strong. Yeah, I'll probably finish up here pretty soon, but I kind of want to
do this tomorrow and we'll play desperate. Okay, listen, I'm going to promise you something. We're
going to play Desperado's three tomorrow, but I'm going to do this too. Okay, I have to make you guys
my whole house. More house flipper. Yeah, I'm going to open with this. We'll play this for a little
while and then we'll move to Desperado's three when I'm done with my new house. When am I going to end?
Um, I don't know. Probably soon though. We are encroaching on like the five plus hour mark
and that's when I need to start to be cautious of how long I've been sitting down,
but we're good. Desperado's is going to get shafted. It's not, I promise. What else is,
that's all I have in my room. Everyone thinks, dude, I wonder what's like in any interesting
shit in like a streamer's room. No, wait, hold on. Hold on a minute. Uh, let me fix it. You want to
see what it looks like? What a streamer's room looks like? Is there any bags of trash that are
available? Give me one second. Give me one second. I, I need to turn the camera on just so you guys
can fucking understand what I'm talking about here. One sec. Okay. So I didn't do anything.
I had to just get this out of the way. Just like clockwork. Right. Right. Right. Okay. So
I'm going to show you guys the ground in my room. I don't know why some of this stuff is even here.
Yes, by the way, those of you that are asking, I know I'm going to get a lot of questions about
this, but there's a very specific reason why. No, that's not going to be shit on the ground.
Hope not. Uh, there's like a trash bag, this Elmo and like a bunch of cords and shit.
That's not a torture me Elmo. No, I don't know why that's in here. I really don't know.
That's like, I, Kim got that stuff for some reason. It's not a torture me Elmo. This room is a
fucking mess, but I have to clean it. I know, but that's what I'm saying. I was trying to go,
I wish I could go find the trash bags that I deleted. You have your documents all over the
floor. Yeah. I did that before. Oh, cool. That actually lights up perfectly. Okay. That looks
good. There's not trash in there by the way. It's storage. When you run out of places to put shit,
it's like, okay, what am I going to do with that? I'm going to put this in a trash bag.
That's all I have right now. It's storage right now. That's not trash. That's storage.
Why a trash bag? Cause it's a huge thing that like all the commercials, you can't rip through
them. They're so hefty. They're so hard to break through. So why don't you use it for like a bunch
of shit? All right. I got that room. This is literally the cleanest my fake room has ever been.
The food. Okay. I also need, um, like laptop. What's going on? Socks. What is going on?
It's Christmas time at the streamer room. The disc is skipping. No, get this out of here. No,
I'm a clean guy. Right? I need to do the, the, okay, this is the, I'll show you. This is,
this is going to be fun. I just need, um, just like foam walls. It might actually have to be,
I don't know, like what would, what's just like a, like a thing that's like a square that's black
like a hang clean or not. You have to eat. Yeah. I know a box, a mirror. No,
got to be able to sit on the wall. This guy has to be one of the lights.
It has never turned on. I'm supposed to make my streamer room. If I don't have all my cool foam,
dude. Damn it. Oh, nevermind. You search foam. I would, why foam be here? Maybe a painting.
I'd have to upload a custom painting. Yeah. I'll use a picture of it. Yeah. I'll do that tomorrow.
Oh, that whatever. I just saw it and I just, I cleaned it off. Okay. Here goes the, there it is.
So here's the front door. I need, first of all, what do I want to have my floor here? I think I'm,
that looks kind of nice. Yeah, it does. I love it. I love the smokiness to it. Tile floor, tile floor,
tile floor, tile house. Um, I'm not sure how many of you guys live in the Southwestern United States.
Um, you got, you gotta have some tile somewhere. Shit gets hot, hot, hot. Oh, this is, I like this.
I really like it. I really like this. This is sick. Okay. Now we need a cool, uh, kitchen
panels. How about, hmm, maybe, um, maybe like this, like a sand, sand. I think I like this, a sand.
At least you're having fun. Yeah. Oh yeah. This music is a little kind of getting to me though.
That's better. It's a little, it's too much. It's like playing in my brain.
Ball panels. What a cream. Cream works. Look at that. This is a house that you can just look
so good. You could just eat it. This is resident sleeper. Don't resident sleeper me. Don't do it.
Don't you do it. You guys like keeping logs of me. Well, I got logs of all you resident sleepers.
I don't know. How does it look bad? Now we brighten this up a little bit. We add a little,
we get some color in here. Eat them. No mirrors. That's the, I can't. Okay. Can I nominate just
the portion of the mirrors for worst stream in 2020? Like I can, I do that. Just that portion,
just like that, like 30 minutes. That's all. Everything else has been really fun,
but like I hurt my, my, my body hurts from that. My whole body hurts. All right. Cool. Nice. Nice.
Clean these windows. Yes. Another two month break. These are the mirrors.
I remember because this is my, uh, save file. Remember how long this takes when you don't have
any of the upgrades is so horrible. What the fuck are they saying? Cigarette house, something house,
something house, cigarette house. Do not say that because I will make like a filter and then the
actual cigarette and then the yellow, I'll make the cigarette house. I'm not doing mirror too.
What are you doing? Why is it not showing up? Where is it? There's this, this is not a,
no, I'm not even giving, I'm not going to give you the satisfaction of me saying it.
This is not that this is not a cigarette house. This is smoky white and black and, and like cream
with some accents. It's going to be some black furniture. There'll be a couple,
there'll be maybe some oranges here. It's looks, this is a good look. Okay. So
not all the walls have to be like that. Just these ones here. All right. Let's go this way.
This is the mega milk house. It's Oreo cookies and cream. That's a good look. It's not a cookie.
Okay. Lower. I'm going to put a wall here. God damn it. This is a school cafeteria.
Why does it have to be perfect? You could have said anything else and it could have been kind
of accurate, but it is so accurate that it's making me angry how accurate it is. So angry.
That's pretty good. That's got to be best chat joke of the week. I think it's up there for me
for sure. Okay. Oh, this room's ugly. Sorry. Sorry. Okay. Okay. I need another. What the hell is this
room? It's a 12 year old room. What? I want to know the 12 year old that has a triple monitor
gamer room set up. Hey, what, what, what is, what do I always say? If that's the case,
how many plants they got in there? How many plants they got in the corner of their houses?
When I was a kid, I had this whole shit box HB computer that the tent was wrong and it got
really hot. It was the shittiest computer ever and it got super hot and I was sweating my room
all the time. I would play Diablo 2 on it and Team Fortress classic. Make the green room meat wads
room. You guys, are you guys, how are you guys this on point today? Holy shit. You guys are on
fire today. This is the Aqua teen house. Isn't this Frylock's room? Doesn't he have like a cool
computer? This is Frylock's room. This is Meatwad's room. And then this is Shake's room. This is the
TVs right here. No, no more cartoon houses. I don't want to make a family guy. I don't want
to make the Simpsons. I don't want to make Aqua teen. Yes. Holy, this is the Aqua teen house.
That's the exact house. How did this happen? I don't understand why you're an idiot and I'm
going to throw this thing on the floor and it's going to explode. And I don't know what you're
talking about, man. I think you're going to shut your mouth. The little guy has a mouth on him,
I think. That's too bad. What's going on in here? I'm leaving. I'm gone. I'm gone. I'm gone. I'm
gone. I'm gone. I'm gone. I'm out. I'm out. I'll see you tomorrow. I was so bad. I have to fucking
end the stream. I have to turn the stream up because that was so awful. Jera's life is a
cartoon. No, it just happens. It just ends up that way for no reason. It just ends up like this.
I have no control over this. All right. I'm fixing this end of stream fry lock. I'm so
fucked up right now. All right. I got to get a front door. This guy's fucked up. I'm not
fucked up. You're fucked up. Oh, it's not me. It's you. I didn't do anything. And by the way,
Merry fucking Christmas. No, no, that's not how I'm going to end this. I'm not ending it that way.
No, no, no, no, no, no. I'm not going to. Okay. I'm done. Everybody just relax. Okay. I'm going to
do the bathroom. Whoa. Look at all this stuff. There's an AC unit. An amountable AC unit. A
unit. Stop. Stop it. You guys are a bad influence. No, let's just. What about for walls in here?
Uh, I'm thinking I'll do a grandma house or Minecraft grandma house or I've only played
Minecraft for two hours. My whole house looks like this. Uh, 3D is a 3D. Yeah. That's fucking
ugly. It looks like instead of a beehive, sell this shit. Get this out of here. Here's the,
okay. The problem that I have with decorating places is I, everything that is not just gray,
white or beige, just, it's just crazy, right? It just looks crazy. How do you design anything?
I don't understand. How do people make anything look good? Like this just looks crazy. This is
pretty cool. This is what every single high-end hotel bathroom looks like. Put carpet in the
bathroom now. No, I already did that before and I don't want to do that again. That sucks. Pretty
cool. Resident sleeper. Hey, wake up. Oh, cool. I guess. Real cool. I guess. What happened?
Windows in a bathroom. Yeah. I don't get that either. I don't know why they would ever be a
window in a bathroom, especially windows that are at somewhere around waist height on a first floor,
waist height. If those blinds are up and I look at like, just think about that. I think we've had
this exact conversation before, but there's a lot of potential new people here that I want to bring
this up to. If you're peeing right here and this window is right there, why would you ever want the
opportunity for like the paper boy to just drive by and look over or anybody literally doesn't matter
who? In fact, I'll go one step further. Every single blind in my entire place, doesn't matter
where I am, is permanently closed. You guys like that too? They're never open because I know one
day I'm going to like lock eyes with somebody outside of my window. There's going to be somebody
like just out there and we're going to lock fucking eyes and it's going to be like, oh shit.
Uh, okay, then get away. No, I, all blinds closed everywhere. No windows, no open windows ever.
Why is it kind of like this? That doesn't seem very healthy. Is it? I'm doing another funny
aquatine impression. I'm like getting out of here very soon. Social interaction. I'm sorry, but
walking eyes with a random person from your neighborhood or from like your outside of like
apartment complex. It's just odd. I don't want to do that. Who wants to do that? I don't want
people to see me like fun. Plus I'm naked all the time. Right? So when am I, why would I,
what opportunity would I ever have to have any windows open? I'm constantly without a shirt,
at least. So what opportunity are the windows ever going to be open? He's naked right now.
I actually am not. I have clothes on today. This music is way too intense for what we're doing.
Proof it. I actually, you know what? I actually can prove it. I can prove it. No, I can't. The
webcam is unplugged now. How? It doesn't make any sense. You saw me like four hours ago when
I turned on the webcam. What are you talking about? All right. Installations. Toilet. No,
this sink is, there you go. Okay. It looks good. Toilet. I feel like I keep hearing this music in
every Spider-Man movie. Okay. How about this one? Toilet standard. All right. Stick it on. On. I
have to go. I have to go. I gotta go. I'll pick up tomorrow. Don't worry. We'll pick up tomorrow.
Crossing that out, that mark where I have to, I have to get up. I gotta go. I gotta go. I will pick
this up exactly where we left it. And I'm going to be, we're going to make it happen. We're going to
do a whole mini golf course back here. And then I'm going to pretend to you guys that I'm going
to play Desperados 3 tomorrow, but four or five, six hours is going to go by tomorrow.
And I'm going to be like, oh shit, well, we'll do that later. The plan is to do this and then
play Desperados. And look, maybe we just play Desperados like a few days later, a couple days
later, whatever. Hey James, thanks for the 10 subs. Thank you, James. A lot of people are today.
Hope you enjoyed the stream. Thanks for stepping by. We'll see you tomorrow. Thanks guys. I missed
massive bits. Holy shit. I did. There's a hundred bucks, 10,000 bits from Stormy 2. Thank you for
the a hundred dollars. Is Pac-Man totally tubular or radical man? Totally tubular. Is it the very,
very simple question for me to answer, but thank you. That's a ton of money. And I don't, I know,
I, like I said, I don't read it's anymore, but people still decide it's a good idea to give me
fucking hundreds of dollars. And I just hope you think it's worth it. Thank you. I will see you
guys tomorrow. Good night. Goodbye. Have a wonderful rest of your day. Let's do the credits.
Oh, that's, that's Elmo. That's the picture of, why is that sea dead? He's not dead. He's just
sleeping. He sleeps on his stomach. This saves the game automatically. Yeah, it does. What music is
playing? All right. Pac-Man. I forgot. I thought, why did I think that was in House Flipper? All
right. Thanks everybody for subbing. Here they come. Just a moment. Yeah, there's a bunch of
other stuff that I have too. I want to do custom robo. I want to play ghosts of Tsushima too,
but I don't even know if I'm going to stream that. I have no idea. When I took off that couple of
months, I created a gigantic backlog of tons of things that I now need to figure out when they're
going to happen. But thanks a lot. It's broken again. And I even, I had, why is this doing this
again? I had it open. Did I, I did. I had, am I going to play Paper Mario? Yes, I will play.
I promise I'll play Paper Mario. Thanks big buddy. The only guy again, two subs and two streams.
We're on a roll. God damn it. All right. Well, I don't know why this is happening again.
Wasn't it open? I, by tomorrow, this is going to be fixed. If it ain't, then okay. If this is not
fixed tomorrow, if this doesn't work tomorrow, I want the stream after that to only be Jerma
punching emotes until I'm, I have to stop the stream. Okay. Bring the winks back. No, the winks,
I can't do the winks anymore, but I'll see you guys tomorrow. We'll pick up right where we left
off. Good night. Goodbye. Have a wonderful rest of your night. See you tomorrow. I had a great,
time. Abrupt ending. Everybody's saying raid, raid, raid, raid, raid. Uh, what do you, who's,
who's live right now? Raid Mr. Slime. That, that's me. Actually, that's me.
Raid a small account. You should, you want to, you want to raid Nyaners?
All right. Yes. Are you, all right. I, are you guys going to be nice?
Am I going to just diary you guys on a channel we've never been to before? Raid Rev. This is
going to be, this is going to be a toss-up. Raid GDQ. Oh, fuck. GDQ is going on. Oh my God. I know
I, I'm so happy about that. I love staying up till like fucking four in the morning and watching
people beat Nintendo games. Do them both. Raid Nyaners now or, or punch you. You guys better be
fucking nice. I swear to God, if I get word, if I get word back that you guys were fucking like
mean or fucked up, I'm going to, you're going to hear from me. You're going to be in big trouble.
You're going to be grounded. All right. We'll do that. And then I'm going to raid GDQ and then
I'm going to, can I even do that? Can we bounce around? I don't think you can even do that.
Let me see if I can do like a raid bounce. All right. Here we go. Be nice. Be nice. I don't,
I don't even know who this person is. Like, so I'm just, Hey, great. All right. Let's, let's go.
Fine. Here we go. You ready? I'm doing, I'm doing it. Don't raid bounce. We did that before
Joel and I ended up hosting the league of legends channel and I, I, I hosted the league of legends
channel for like fucking four straight days. All right. Here we go. Go say hello. Tell them about
my, my Mr. Slime stream. I'm not leaving this channel. All right. Goodbye. I'll see you tomorrow.