Hello. How you doing? I'm sure you're probably noticing something. Something different. Something
strange. Something that you've never heard before. Well, you've heard that. You've heard the zoomers
before. But I've got a brand new audio setup today. Game in the mail. And here we are.
I now have a compressor on my voice. What do you think about that one? Now I get to sound like a
radio commercial. Ew. Ew. I don't like it. Ew. Oh, you don't like that? Break the fuck out of here.
Okay. Yeah, I can do that now. Losing viewers. So he was coming back. But all right, let's go over
this. So I get complaints. Every single stream where people say, Hey, dude, you sound like shit.
I can't hear you. I can't turn your mic up. You sound awful. Why can I hear a loud buzzing
in your room? And I'm just like, Yeah, it was time. So now you actually should be able to hear me.
And I shouldn't sound like shit anymore. Are we a hype train? No, not again. Not again. I just
turned it on. We're doing this a second time in a row. A second hype train in a row. Is this going
to happen? This is going to happen every single day. This is going to happen every single day,
isn't it? Are you kidding me? Which you have? They've gamified this shit by this point.
This is going to happen every day. Oh, we're already at level two. I oh my god, this is
going to happen every day, isn't it? This is going to happen every single day. You got you,
you motherfuckers are gonna make me rich. I'm not even kidding. Hype train level three.
New tax bracket POG. CPA is gonna I have a CPA. And this year, I'm gonna come to him and be like,
Hey, what's going on? Just want to let you know that my income increased like times five.
What? Yeah, this thing called the hype train on Twitch. Oh, yeah, I was I love the hype train.
I'd be like, Yeah, yeah, I get me too. I guess. Old material. Tax hype. Honest to god, though,
like I this is gonna happen every day. Can I can I can configure this to like not happen?
Why do I sound like this? And we're gonna get that question a lot. As because I actually I
actually have a compressor actually have a real audio device. Now I didn't just plug my mic into
my computer. I didn't plug my microphone directly into my computer. Ready? We can do stuff like this
while shorting. Let's let's turn the compressor up even more. More. Even more. It's at 100% right now.
Well, imagine if here's the reason why I don't like compressors. Let's see if we can fuck up
the compressor. I'm going to talk high and then talk low. This sounds way worse. I know it does.
Because the way that I'm talking, I hate compressors because you can hear it like
I am. Okay, so I hate that. I hate the fucking sound of my I hate the voice. I hate I hate that.
I don't like the way it sounds. Let's bring it back down. Ready? Oh, this is without the compressor.
Oh, this is what streamers sound like when they don't have it on. You see, it's a cheat code.
It's a way for cheaters to be able to sound better. And this is what it's on. This is I'm talking the
exact same way. I have not changed any single way that I'm talking. But here we go. Ready? Hey,
how are you? How are how you doing? Hey, how are you? How you doing? Now it said zero. What do you
think? Compressors are just lying. Well, I can't have like a little bit of I want to be like
professional sounding. I can't have like 10%. You can't even give me 10%. Why? Compressors are
cheating. It's I know it is. Look, can I at least like tell you that? Hold on. Am I too loud now?
We got I got to we got to do this together. I can't we just like we actually just did another
fucking hype train. Another one is done. You guys just dump thousands of dollars on this. Okay.
So should I turn it down? Or is this good? Well, what happened? But if I scream, it's
it's gonna sound. Hold on. Hey, hey, everybody. Welcome to the stream. Like, didn't that sound bad?
I have to do like 2% compression. It's fine. I have to try to peek my mic to see what happens.
I don't know. I tested this before. Is that doing anything? I actually can't tell if it's doing
anything. Is it? Is it? Is it? It's not compressing it down, though. All right, hold on camera. I knew
I was gonna have to do this live. Turn this off. Okay, you ready? How's that? Will you let me have
this? Will you please let me have this? I need people to come into the channel and I need them
to hear me sound like this. So they go, oh, that dude's fucking that dude's cool. He sounds cool.
That doesn't sound good. That sounds way worse. But it's it's go back. You want me to go back to
the old mic. This is the old mic. It's just actually plugged into real a real piece of
hardware not right into the back of my fucking computer. All right. How's that? Is that good?
I think we're good there. I think we're good there. Do 100%. I just did that. Do more.
How's that? I'm gonna stay at 100% just because everyone this thing. This is a nice piece of
hardware. And just because everybody is fucking everybody is is causing lots of problem with me.
And everybody's talking about this shit. I'm going to keep the I'm keeping it at 100% this
entire stream. This is the generic streamer voice. I know it is. That's why it's going it's staying
on the eye. Look, this is this is this is what you supposed to see. At least you can hear that
still. At least you can hear that still. That's never going away. All right. Look, just get you
got to get used to it. It's it's you don't do. This thing is nice. It's a nice piece of hardware
and I'm keeping it. Okay, here we go. Are we done? We're ready to play. We're playing Katana zero
today. Look, let me let me Okay, but would you would you rather this? Hold on. What if I was just
like this the whole stream instead? Would you be happy? Like, would you want me just to be is this
this is better? Do you think this is better? Why is this better? Hold on. What do I turn down a
couple things? What does it sound like? This sounds good. It's perfect. Now, it's actually perfect.
This is perfect. Okay, what if I turn the compressor up all the way now? How does that sound?
Does that sound a little bit better? Should I keep this should I be professional professional
streamer Thanos? This is awful. I need to hear what this sounds like. I'm looking at the first
time I can play with this. Hold on. Let me see. Hello. What does this sound like? This this is
fucked. This is it's just like a pitch shifted by 1%. This sounds weird. This sounds like this is
what happens like I feel like what people sound like when like if you do drugs and then somebody
talks to you. Does this what it sounds like? Hold on. No, I don't like I don't like that. I
don't like that. Hold on. What about if we go lower? Can I go lower? How's that? That's a little
different. That's way different. We did the we did the hype train everybody. Thanks again
for giving money during the hype train. We're at level five right now level five.
And I oops. This is no this doesn't sound right. It's because the compresses at 100%.
That's better. All right. This is what we're going with. If you don't like it, then I'm sorry. But
this was an an ice expensive piece of equipment. And I was told by two or three data aggregators.
Do you need to improve your audio quality? Or no one's ever going to like you. And then I said,
fuck. All right, we're going. I'm ready. This Katana zero is Katana zero. Welcome. And let's
listen to the sound quality though. This is my mic is supposed to sound like this. We're going
to put on the webcam mic. I think that's the problem. I think a lot of people are just so used
to hearing just loud sounds that I don't matter. We're going. Everybody's so used to hearing like
your voice is too nasally. It's not. Wait a minute. How's that? Is that better? Is this better? How's
that? Okay, that that's probably better. I think it might be better. Are we good? That's that's
better now. I think. Let me see. Is that home on saved saved saved? That's not because I like
an equalizer on don't use there are no filters on. Well, I think you have a lovely voice. Hey,
thanks. I appreciate that. Move closer, move closer to the mic. I don't think you want that.
If I move closer to the mic, then I sound more of what the thing that you guys tell me you don't
want to hear. All right, I'm leaving it the way it is. I'm leaving it the way it is. You guys have
just been so used to hearing me on shit quality that everyone's like, oh, oh, wait, he sounds good
now. I don't like it. My God, we did a level five fucking hype treat. Go back. I want the shitty
one. We can hear everything in your room. What? We can hear every car. No, you can't. I'm looking
over here right now. No, that's not true. You know why I know that's not true? Because this is what
it was before. That's what it was before. Perfect, huh? Too much. There's zero compression on the
voice right now. You guys are fucked. It's perfect. Perfect. Keep it like this. Perfect.
It's perfect. The vroomers are an integral part of the stream. No, they're not. I'm trying to get
rid of these motherfuckers. Are you serious? I'm putting it back on. All right, there we are.
I'm keeping it like this. Let's go. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. We're going. We're going. I'm done.
Let's go. I gotta play a video game, okay? Like, for instance, the one you're about to see on the
screen. Look at that. Has he peaked the mic yet? Yeah, I can't. I can't peak the mic anymore.
God damn it. All right. Anyways, let's talk about this. We just did another hype train thing.
We just did another hype train two days in a row. That's fucking ridiculous.
Uh, Kaj Tech gave 5,000 bits. They say PogChamp. 50 fucking dollars. Scream into the mic so I know
it's fine. All right, we've been sitting here for 20 minutes trying to get my audio right. I'm not
sitting here for 20 minutes anymore. This is my... It's a GoXLR. It's a great piece of equipment,
okay? And it sounds really fun and good. And I don't know if anybody likes change, but here we go.
Oh my god. This is what you sound like. I know. I know. I know what I sound like. What are you
talking about? That sounds fine. It does. Actually, it sounds professional. Fuck, it does. It sounds
like super professional. Should I return this? No, no, no, no, no. I'm not gonna return it. All
right. I'm not gonna return it. I'm not returning it. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay. All right. We're good. That's better. That's better. That's better. Everyone's in. All
right. Well, here's Katana Zero. We're gonna play Katana Zero right now. Welcome to the stream,
everybody. Thanks for coming. I need to tweak it more. I just, I turned off the compressor.
Your voice sounds like a JPEG. God damn it. This is Katana Zero. Thanks for coming to the stream,
everybody. Hope you have a good fucking day today. Tell me more about the men in masks. No,
I'm self-conscious because I don't know what it sounds like. I see. Then let's start from
the beginning. ASCIIsoft presents Katana Zero. Jeremy, it sounds like you're chewing on marbles.
No, that's not even accurate. This is too much bass. Should I turn the bass down? Bass. Hold on.
Ready? Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass.
Is that better? How about this? Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass. Bass.
Better? Too much? You sound like a radio DJ. Fuck. That's intentional. That's why they sound good.
I'm gonna, you know what I'm gonna do? I'm gonna slowly, I'm gonna slowly increase the compressor.
I'm gonna start at zero and over the next like two weeks I'm gonna increase this shit one percent
every day and eventually you're not even gonna realize it happened. How's this? You're a monster.
The compressor's not even turned on. This is what the compressor turned on. Do you understand?
This is the compressor right now. It's on right now. Compressor is off right now. Everybody hates
the radio voice. Is it, don't people stream like this? Everybody streams like this.
There's like 500,000 streamers on Twitch and like 490,000 of them all have good quality audio.
All right. I'm just gonna go. I can't do it right now. This shitty box that I had before.
This thing sucks. You're being gaslit right now. I definitely am. There's no way I don't die. There's
no way. I'm being, I am being like gaslit by so many people here. I'm not watching till your
compressor's at 110%. Someone's calling the phone. Have you arrived? Who the fuck are you?
Leave me alone. Do not hang up again. I need details on your location. I'll be there soon.
I'll be there soon. I need you to work as quickly as possible. There's not much time left.
The scientist is being held somewhere within the factory. And listen, I'm like,
you guys, you did it. Congratulations. Because now I'm like talking differently.
I'm speaking differently now because of what you guys have been telling me. I'm speaking different.
All right. Understood. Free him. This is just the way that I actually sound
in real life. He's already getting the bad ending. I don't even know what that means.
I don't know what the fuck that means. All right. Katana zero. God damn it. Oh, I'm so,
you fucked me up. Oh, by the way, this game actually has a warning on it that it will give
you a headache. There's a warning here. Turn the music up. Okay. I can do that. Is it got good
music? That's good. How does that sound? I have to like listen to this back. All right. So let's go.
I can hit bullets. Is this like a view that you hit? Is this going to get hit once you die
scenario or what? Okay. You can swing up. Cat. Oh, you can pet the cat. You've got a podcast
voice now. God damn it. Stop it. Oh, this is what I get. What? This is what I get for having 10
years of like the same crusty ass audio. Press Y to eject. Why would I eject? Eject? I can hear
your mouth sounds. No, you can't hear my mouth sounds. What is going on? Oh, it shows the level
you just did. Okay. I need to pay attention. This game is supposed to be hard. Stop. RT. Oh,
it's like a dash. Okay. Cool. Turn it up. You have a really phlegmy voice. I don't though. I don't.
I don't. I should have done it gradually. This game is pretty good. You can pause time. Oh,
does this kill you? All right. I didn't know if it killed you or not. I can hear his teeth.
You can't hear my fucking teeth. Okay. You can't hear my teeth. Teeth don't make sounds.
All right. That's not my teeth. That's the controller. What do you think I'm sitting here
going like? Not my fucking teeth. I can hear his heart. All right. What does this one do? Why?
Oh, I bit my tongue. Oh, I bit my tongue. Fuck. I'm reaching because I'm trying to get you guys off
this. I'm trying to get you guys off this so bad. Like I'm trying to get you guys away from this shit
and I can't. I'm trying to think of what to do. Oh ouch. I was starting to think I wouldn't make it.
Thank you. I saved him, right? Oh, I didn't win. I hope we got that on tape. Hey boys,
it's time to take the trash out. Mind the lasers. I can do shit like that now. Oh, what?
Did I die? All right. I gotta slow down. This is actually a pretty fun game so far. All right.
How fast do the bullets go? It just does it again. Mind the lasers, boys. Yeah.
Would you look at that? Switch back to Thanos voice. No, I can't. I'm not going to use that.
You understand that me turning on the compressor and me turning on the 10% pitch shift Thanos voice
is the same cheat. You guys know that, right? That's a really easy plus two. Make us laugh,
funny boy. Are we good? Your employers are displeased that the mission target was terminated
before extraction. I could have saved him. Go home and rest. You'll receive a new assignment tomorrow.
Drink herbal tea. Yes. I should have gradually done this. You guys never would have even fucking
known if I had done one to two percent per stream. Nobody would have even known. You can
watch TV. At least 12 have been reported dead or injured at an abandoned factory in the third
district. Okay. The only thing they did is Dawood Bay. A government scientist first reported missing
three weeks ago. It sounds so bad. Guys, I can't go back. This is an elaborate new audio setup.
I'm never going back ever. That's impossible. It took like two hours to do this. These people
are fools. I don't know what to say. Nine days remain. Come and take a seat. All right. Fucking
hold on. I want to hear it back. Hey, so what the fuck's going on here, guys? Oh yeah. That guy is
crazy. Oh shit. Watch out. I got you. I got hit by that guy. Hey, look at me. Look at me. Clip it.
I want to hear it. I need, I need to hear what it sounds like. Everyone's freaking out. Don't clip
it. What are you talking about? Don't clip it. Clip it. I want to hear it. I want to hear what
this shit sounds like. I want to hear what it sounds like. Fucking Jesus Christ. Hey, so what
the fuck's going on here, guys? Oh yeah. That guy is crazy. Oh shit. Watch out. I got you. I got hit
by that guy. Hey, look at me. Look at me. Clip it. I want to hear it. That sounds, that sounds very,
very good. That sounds very good. I ain't got, I'm done. I'm done. That sounds very good.
I'm done. Let's go. Do I have both earphones plugged in? That shit sounds very good. It sounds
clean. It sounds beautiful. It sounds really good. I'm getting fucked with now. Everyone's
fucking with me and I'm not going to take it anymore. I'm playing Katana Zero for the,
let's go. My nightmares have returned. I see this could be a side effect of your treatment.
Tell me about the dreams. Uh, the shadow came after me, right? The shadow that entered the
room. Tell me about it. Uh, it wasn't heading toward me. It was going toward a machine. Yeah.
It's been 30 minutes. I gotta stop looking over there. Perhaps the shadow was the machine's
operator. Oh, it might've been a scientist actually. The person probably did not wish to
hurt you. You shouldn't be afraid of them. This sounds good. Fuck. Um, I think you, maybe you're
right. Our time is up. Let me see you. Let me get your files. He's falling apart. It sounds very
good. It sounds clean. It sounds beautiful. It sounds really good. I know I'm getting fucked
with now. Everyone's fucking with me and I'm not going to take it anymore. I'm playing the Katana
Zero. Let's go. It sounds fucking fine to me. Real voice, by the way. Let's go. Can I go to the
desk? That's a photo of my family. What's your fucking memers and prankers? I'm getting pranked.
Destroy. After reading Josh Rose, well regarded tech billionaire and philanthropist chairman of
the new Mecca foundation for post-war reconstruction, clandestine involvement in the movement of
material and war drugs. Heavily guarded exercise caution. Okay. Derma was hacked. I ain't taking
it anymore. I'm not taking it anymore. All right. Start, start purging comments. People saying bad
audio. Don't ban them. Just let them know that it's not, it's not okay. Can I go? Wait, what?
Where are you off to in such a rush? Just start, just start purge. Don't ban them. Just let them
know that they did not to do that. It's a bathrobe. Interesting looking bathrobe. Interesting looking
face. Sorry. Shut up. I must be hearing things. Shut up. Sorry. All right. As I was saying,
interesting looking bathrobe. It was a gift. What's the sword for? Uh, it's a family heirloom.
Do you always bathe with your family heirlooms? I just keep them safe. All right. Well, enjoy your
shower. Thanks. That's that easy. Get in. Derma, no matter the audio quality, your streaming
personality will always be amazing, but you're implying that my audio quality is bad. Don't
imply that. Well, boss, the dragon is here. Crazy alarm. Wait, what can I do with this?
Wait, I go, you can throw objects. Oh shit. That's cool. Oops. I don't even know what
do you say? Oh, I didn't kill him. There we go. Oh, that door's closed. There we go.
It needs to be adjusted. Your voice sounds just sticky. Who would want to fight dragon or strong
Terry? Me. Which one of you was strong Terry? Are you dead now? Oh, I got hit. What did I get hit by?
That was pretty sick. New mic. No, new audio device. I got it literally at two hours ago.
Well, I fucking missed that one. Can I jump out? Can I make it through that? No. Maybe I can. Can I
make it through there? I can definitely make it through there. Ah, one more try. I can't make it.
No way. What? What did somebody else do? What? I thought I was going to like a new area. What? I
don't know. Okay. Ah, all right. I see. I see. I see. I can smell his breath. Boss, I just think
while you're here, I'm not giving you the satisfaction of killing me. Oh, you're not
who I was expecting. I'm surprised there's more than one of you. Technically got it. Yeah, I did.
You just fucked up the whole thing. What? Wait, wait, wait. I didn't know there's somebody's name.
I'm looking over the fucking chat. You're an alligator brain dipshit. Alligators are
one of the smartest goddamn animals in the animal kingdom. Just because they're slow
and they don't come out of the water doesn't mean they're stupid. They're actually pretty
intelligent. Oh, he does it anyways. Okay. Pure alligator instinct. That's right. Alligators
aren't fucking dumb. They have like little pea brains, but that doesn't mean they're stupid.
Yeah. Guess what? A crow has a little pea brain too. And they're seen as one of the smarter
animals. Oh, that's just one of our guests. Well, your guest appears to be soaked in blood.
How do you explain that? It's bath products. In that case, you're free to go, sir. No, thanks.
I hope you enjoyed your shower, sir. It's a place called murderer tower. Your employer is pleased
with your results. See, you guys said I had the bad ending. I got the employer ending. You're
receiving a new assignment tomorrow. I didn't die. You ran into me. I didn't do anything. Hey,
watch where you're going. I don't know you. I'm busy. Oh, sorry. I'll just leave you alone then.
Didn't think I could fucking do that with this new device, did you? Is this my apartment?
A grisly scene at the murderer hotel. I don't ever do that again.
I'm not. I'm not going to do that ever again. Gang related, at least 28 dead. Among them,
eccentric billionaire, Josh Rose, who felt his death from the balcony of his penthouse suite.
So far, the police have no... That guy was a billionaire? It's a crutch for people who
can't do voices. That's why I don't do that. Highly coordinated large scale attack. Citizens
are urged to stay indoors. In other news, want to lose weight fast? Sanitation worker may have
found the answer. Tune in at 11 to hear the amazing story. Let's have some more tea. A grisly scene at
the murder... Oh, I already did it. Go to sleep. Why would I say IA? Because I have to apologize
about it. Wait, that's the girl that was in the hallway. Eight days remain. Do it with the voice.
I'm not going to apologize again. You guys. I'm unbelievable. Unbelievable today.
I'd like to begin by discussing your sleep habits. Has your nightmare reoccurred?
I feel like I shouldn't tell this person everything. How about... Sure, last night.
Oh, I see. Tell me what happened in the dream. I get shot. German is using the turtle beach
microphone. Oh, I see. You said the scientist was talking to you. I couldn't understand him.
Fucking turtle beach microphone. And immediately after he was shot, perhaps he was warning you.
Hide. There. Hide something. They're here. Yes, a warning seems most likely. I think you're right.
You know, these dreams may be rooted in a traumatic memory from before your injury.
What do you mean injury? Near-fatal head trauma you sustained during the war left you debilitated.
We've worked together ever since, despite your memory loss and distorted perception of time.
The service medal you carry is an important reminder of your sacrifices and a crucial
link to your past life. Your recovery has been slow, but tell me how's your personal life.
Leapfrog microphone. All right, I'm going to ban the word microphone. Can somebody ban the word
microphone in this chat? I met someone last night. I want all versions of the word mic and microphone
to be banned. That's quite unusual. Tell me about this person. Girl, she lives in my building.
Ah, I wasn't expecting that. Who is she? She's just a kid. We're neighbors.
Ah, I misinterpreted that meaning. This is somewhat relieving. You met a child in the
third district. How strange. I don't know what to tell you. I take medicine? Well, as you know,
the third district is not a safe place for children. Why? All right, you've been very
cooperative today. Just a moment. What are you injecting me with? Well, there's a syringe in
this game, which means it gets a full letter grade. This has been a productive session. We'll
continue tomorrow. Is there something you're looking for? This is probably like a secret
government agent or something. This is a secret government agent. That's definitely what this is.
I know what's going on. Don't I get a new assignment? Popular DJ from upscale second
district involved in the trafficking of club drugs. Lightly guarded but surrounded by clubgoers.
Extreme finesse required to eliminate without detection. Pathological liar. Do not speak to
him. We got a huge amount of community subs earlier and I'm going to go over them all later.
But non-descript civilian gave 10. There was a... We did the hype. All right, I couldn't even pay
attention to the hype thing just because we were fighting about my mic audio. But seriously,
that's a fucking lot. Thank you guys. So I have to be careful in here? Can I... I can't be seen.
I need to be more careful. What? Can I jump over there? Can I jump over there line of sight?
Wait. Oh, I'm dancing. Okay, that makes sense. Oh, fuck. Kill. I can't even take my sword out.
I can't kill anybody. NPR with German 985. Oh my god. Get over there. Get over there. What the
fuck am I doing? What kind of nightclub has the bounces walking around with automatic assault
rifles? I mean, that's kind of ridiculous. Yeah. Hey you, you're not supposed to be here. Turn
around now or we're going to have some trouble. I'm not... I don't... That's it. I tried to get away
from it. Oh, fuck. Yes, that should work. I don't... What? I don't get this whole eject thing.
I have... Okay, what's the what's the bar up top for? Oh my god. That's it. Somebody put it...
I have to get this time bar up here. All right. Okay. Yes. Slow. I can slow down time. Who's calling
me? Don't forget that you are invincible while rolling. Uh-huh. If you're having trouble
predicting a good plan... Hang on. I know. I tried to... What? I can't swing at it? Fuck. All right.
I gotta... Oh, don't take one hit. Okay. I thought it was gonna be more than one hit. What happened?
Whoa! Can I hit that? Can't see me in the steam. Yes, that should work. Oh my god. That's the guys
with the... All right. Easy. Down. Let's go. Oh, there's steam in here. I gotta use that. Fuck.
Okay. Turn, but don't click this. Okay. I won't. Oh, fuck. I didn't see that.
Ooh. You. How? Damn it. Where's it going? All right. I gotta dodge and then... Okay. I gotta dodge
and then break. Dodge and then break. Oh, fuck. I can't dodge. Can you dodge in the air?
You cannot dodge in the air. Okay. That makes sense. Got it. All right. What about this way?
To the left? Whoa. Nope. Turn off the lasers. PP. What is going on in this chat today?
You guys like... You guys doing drugs today? Like, is there a collective like chat drugs?
That was fucking awesome. Holy god. Oops. Oh, I just threw everything. Oh, fuck. Drop. Oh, yeah.
I thought they were coming down around. I thought they were wrapping around the whole way. Okay.
Whatever. Shit. What the fuck are you guys doing? Wait. What are they saying? Trying to throw this
up. All right. Do I have anything else? Chat is high. Chat is doing drugs. All right. They're
coming down. Oh, fuck. They're coming down. They're coming up. Holy shit. All right. I gotta go the
other way. God. Rich. All right. Rich the slender. The council of skinny rickies has made our
decision regarding your membership. Is it? Are you finally going to make me a member?
You have tamed your beast's mane into the powerful hairs of the pompadour.
Rick and slender man? Oops. Why am I dying here? Who has the gun? None of them have a gun.
They just have a knife and they're walking. Okay. Oh, my god. I'm fucking dying over and over again.
All right. I'm good. Two are attacking at once. Your swing is being canceled by one.
Ah, okay. That makes sense. I get it. Well, that's how you do this. Oh, my fucking god.
Okay. I know what to do. Okay. This game. This game. This is a hard game. All right. Let's go.
Okay. I got to pull them over here like this. No, no, no, no, no, no. Turn it off. Oh, wait.
Hold on. Holy shit. I'm doing so bad right now. What? You can reflect bullets with your sword.
That saves some headache. Yeah, I'm trying. I'm having trouble fighting just the guy,
the four dudes right here. All right. Let me get this right. It'll help above. Yeah. Okay.
I'm going to slow down. Can I reflect the laser from the thingy? I can. Can I? No.
I'm going to leave it turned on. Yeah. They'll just run into it, right? Here we go. Oh, shit.
Okay. Open the door. All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Oops. He's got a big crow brain. Do not talk to Electrohead.
Why? Do not talk to Electrohead. Well, I'm going to fucking talk to him. You can't tell me not to
talk to him. Are you, um, are you real? Yes. I'm here to kill you. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
You are real. Okay, man. Let's stay cool here. I'll give it all back. I'll give it all back.
I'll give it all back. I'll give it all back. What are you talking about? If the shit I found
was yours. Oh, God. I can give it back after the show. Please don't hurt me. Oh, God. What'd you
find? Your shit, man. The drugs. I only tried it once at a party. I swear. It was wild. Felt like
time was slowing down. Repeating. Been seeing crazy shit ever since. Oh, God. Somebody help. Oh, God.
Oh, my goodness. What did I do? All right. Let's go. Bingo. There's a gun back there.
This way? It's down here. All right. Guys with guns. Oh, shit. I can't swing twice fast. Okay.
What are you? What are you? What? What? What? What? What? What? I see links. I see links. What?
Oh, look. Drugs. I don't even know what this is. I don't know what this is. I don't get it.
I don't get it. I don't get this. I'm gonna. I don't get it here. This is supposed to be
me in my in my audio room. I don't understand. This is my podcast. God damn it, guys. All right.
Whatever. All right. Guys with guns in here. I got to slice and then dodge. Slice and dodge.
Here we go. Good. Oh, he came right at the end. Shit. Okay. All right. I got to get that down.
I got to get the actual like buttons down. Damn it. Excuse me. I can swing down, right?
All right. Holy fuck. This game looks like it was specifically created for me.
It's pretty cool. Reminds me of Hotline Miami, but the site's growing. Get too fancy with it.
How did you not hear that? Shoot. Oh, he didn't shoot. I got it. All right. Watch out for this
guy. Who's coming? Someone's coming. Someone's coming. Someone's coming. God. God. God. God.
Oh, I ran out of juice. Oh, it's all right. Oh my God. All right. I got I got my hands
fucking sweaty i'm sweating my ass off right now oh my god i'm fucking sweaty you're playing
games why do you play games that make you want to rip your nuts off why don't i read that out
loud and number two i don't know because it's kind of fun wait can i hold on a second i have i can
do a bunch of okay you can do a bunch of angles shoot let's go did i do it oh fuck this guy's
coming from behind oh shit done okay you hear a click and then you can do it your employees
are pleased with your results a cleanup crew is en route you will receive your next assignment
tomorrow fuck the cast hey look it's that little girl microphone more like micro penis
ban that person for 10 minutes i mean i have to i have to start putting my foot down
i gotta start putting my foot down somewhere like i gotta start putting my foot down
as the guy that's driving the ship if it isn't mister too busy to talk oh what have you have
you been waiting for me you bet i have behemoth says you're keeping leviathan in there roar you
now spit it out where are you hiding leviathan what are you talking about spare me the act bob
watch this what the fuck is that behemoth only glows when leviathan's nearby now open up or
he'll kick your butt yeah i guess that like a bomb get it out of here let us in okay come in
nice i told you he'd be a pushover behemoth but the thing was beeping red it was going like
what do you want to do all right let's go come on a sec he's a pushover i'm not a bum what a dump
no wonder you didn't want me to come in here you take behemoth he'll glow the closer you get
closer i get to what it was you want some tea there's nothing but fish heads just boil them
boil them use the broth and i'll put a few onions in it and draw on them what do you mean what the
fuck what the fuck what are you talking about boil them sir let's search the counter nothing
boil them mash them stick them in a stew speaking of which i'm glad you brought that up because
tomorrow tomorrow we are going to be starting the lord of the rings the fellowship of the ring for
playstation 2 it's a very important stream i hope you're there because somebody told me that they
guaranteed i would not be at the first level they guaranteed it so we're gonna see i don't know why
i don't understand i don't i it's not wrong i you can't guarantee something okay a guarantee
it's a lord of the rings tie-in movie playstation 2 game now the two i have by the way i have two
towers and i have returned to the king two towers is one of the best video games ever made i'm rose
colored glasses i know but the two towers is probably one of the best playstation 2 games
that ever existed did she just stay here now what the hell was that see i knew it you had them all
long i don't know what this is oh it's another dinosaur hello leviathan roar they sound pretty
scary they sound pretty scary yeah you gotta you know that's just me right they're just toys
they can't talk geez well yeah but i'm all right i gotta go you can keep leviathan for now but if
you're nice to him if you're not nice to him being behemoth they're gonna kick your butt
in other news no leads yet on the murder of underground dj electro head who suffered
a fatal knife wound while performing at a local nightclub club neon the killing triggered a
stampede leaving dozens of clubgoers injured or dead why did i do that no amount of compression
is gonna save me from that those of you thinking that you're not gonna hear those anymore despite
this club neon manager sterling silver says the show must go on as a high death compressed vroom
i can't believe i spent fucking 30 minutes self-consciously trying to fix my audio
i had it in a spot i already knew i like i can't believe and you failed no i was trying i was
trying to make you guys think it was down and good i thought i was gonna turn the stream let's go over
re like in my brain by the way i had a dream last night that i was naked on stream let's go over this
i had a dream that like i was all right this is gonna be fucking crazy i was streaming in
a bathtub and i don't know why the camera was on the bath while i was in the bathtub
and we were just talking and i stood up and just like naked like it was i was naked in the camera
and i freaked out i was like oh fuck right i forgot and then uh the vod was later on i was
like oh it's not whatever it's not a big deal the vod was deleted later i didn't do it i was like
who deleted this vod i must be banned and one of my mods deleted it and they're like no i deleted
it it's all right and i was like what like yeah i deleted the vod for you i was like oh shit i
have to read this our doors will be open again soon as mop up the visceral in other news no
no i already read this i read this a bridge collapsed the third district plus seven okay
let's go to bed so yeah one of the one of my mods deleted the which mod i don't know it was just
like mod just mod but i was going oh man okay so what i did did nobody see it and apparently
no one saw my like naked body nobody saw and everybody did but nobody was i went we went back
and like i looked at like a clip of it happening hold on what the fuck seven days remain anyways
so the the moment where i stand up and like my full lower body naked into the camera nobody in
the chat you know when you can see the twitch chat the vod on and clips and shit no one said
anything i think only one person one person they were not a sub they were not like a you know like
the when somebody's not subbed to the channel it's just like their name there's no bits or
anything it was just like the the text it just said penis and that was it and i saw that i was
like wait nobody noticed that one person did though and i woke up and i was like how did nobody see
that one person noticed do you see your chat in your dream all right i have to go back to this
your work last night was exceptional i did as you asked so this is the person giving me the jobs
yeah at this rate we'll be able to move you out of the third district soon electrohead used the
same drug you give me what did you speak to electrohead i specifically told you not to speak
to electrohead shut up what did he say uh why didn't you want uh you told me why didn't you want
me to know our superiors don't want to risk exposing you to anything that could potentially
compromise our goals as a veteran you should understand that you're not privy to the full
details of our mission what the what is what's the mission your memory lapses are beginning to
concern me we're working to the we're working to end illegal drug trafficking in the third district
when this is over you may return to a normal life i'd like it too but it will require strict
compliance to your orders there can be no more hiccups um all right does my precondition come
from the drugs well yes it does your precondition is a side effect of the drug that is why we cannot
allow others to abuse it all right i i don't want this it's a shame that you can't grasp the power
you've been bestowed but that's how you really truly feel we can taper you off once the mission
is complete uh i don't wait is that gonna take my power away no no no no no no i'm gonna do that
so this is hard mode i understand it's time for your medicine okay yeah it's hard mode if they
stop giving me the medicine i can't do the slow mo anymore right something like that
anyone have a clip of germa showing his dick the other night i need it for community content
night imagine making a community content night video oh yeah yeah there is one last matter
we need to speak about the dragon an impressive moniker but your work has become too visible
please exercise greater discretion in the future you may leave now i'm called the dragon that you
don't you don't want me to be called the dragon say i show ads no i don't i'm never showing an ad
ever again ever any reason ever never no absolutely not ever again i can't i'm not guys there's like
eleven thousand subs on this channel i'm never gonna run an ad never ever ever like i never did
but why i'm gonna start running ads hey you know i we just crossed eleven thousand subs we start
running an ad every 20 minutes what no political descendant and leaker of redacted scheduled to
testify in military tribunal target must be eliminated post haste collateral damage is
unacceptable stealth and covert action are necessary to prevent additional loss okay let's go
hello i want to reiterate as per your dossier that your target in this mission is fa yuan others
must not be harmed what if i don't have a choice what if i'm being attacked or something this is
simple trying to let that happen okay whatever do an ad reveal at 100 subs here we go what's the
other one i like this one this is a good one i killed that person why did his head come off
what oh well they're gonna think did they think i did this i didn't do this
oh that's a true that's a true monka omega did i i didn't do this though this is probably like
another katana this well it's a katana one is somewhere all right this is going to be like a
proto man megaman kind of scenario or is that like am i thinking too much into that i can hide in
here okay but why do i need to hide from a show your ass have you devolved how much have you
devolved i wonder have you devolved already you've devolved drink from the fountain it's fa yuan his
body is still warm oh dragon we have you surrounded surrender or we will respond with
maximum force great don't kill anybody right wait till he turns wait till he lands holy fuck
wait okay i can't go in anywhere all right let me see what how he goes all the way down there
i can just drop down okay i can drop down do not i'm not gonna kill anybody i promise
i'm not gonna kill anybody did they know i'm in here fuck oh they can hear you that's all right
i can do it he's oh he came in he came in there with me okay if you get spotted you need to kill
them to leave the room really oh fuck are you is that for real uh somebody died whatever yes
that should work video feed lost you promised does that kill them all right it's over at this
point they're all dead what a liar i'm not i'm trying what do you want to do how do you walk
the whole way jesus man you're walking the entire way video feed lost breaking promises he's doing a
genocide run no he's not no he's not he's he only killed three people because he did it was no he
had to okay i had to hide in here okay nice to go i can hide in this room but how long do i have to
hide in here for one two three four five god damn it i was i almost had it like whatever that's
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i know i know that's all right four people i know why did you
kill those people i didn't die because show ads can i dodge around him you know what i mean can
i dodge through him will he see me if i dodge through him he can he's gonna hear me you have
to hold y to sneak well that would i didn't know i didn't have that info before now i do
maybe it told me and i wasn't looking he heard it i went through the entire game not knowing you
could do that really they're upset that not all terms the contract were met the collateral damage
of the police has been deemed unacceptable everything's going so fast nobody will see
when i write this word hey papa needs his medicine how about an old friend i killed
six chrome mash bastards in that war i gave my fucking leg in the war you just what oh
uh i don't have i don't have anything i don't have anything you look like a fucking
frog match all you people are the fucking same you row away relax i bet if i was a you'd have
money for me holy shit i don't know let me see that hey that's that's mine you stole it from me
help help some what is going on what are you doing stop somebody help assault this man's
assaulting me give me the medal give me the medal no i'm not gonna kill him help somebody help me
i violence gets violence there you are some guy told me to give you this looks like a movie
who gave that to you you just stole that from one possession what do you know that i mean that
that was an ed ed and eddy quote some guy with dumb hair he just said to make sure you got it
that isn't that wasn't an ed ed and ed ed and eddy quote yeah so can i watch um i don't know
what's on the down it was on it violence forgets violence eddy wait that is does that where i got
that i thought i was being really deep i thought i was being deep and it was just an ed ed and eddy
quote oh god damn it yeah i was trying to be like wow listen to me listen how fucking smart i am and
how caring i am that's just ed ed and eddy me doing the ed ed and eddy impression okay
whatever it's just some dumb movie let me see it fine you can watch the movie that's not the
origin of that quote i know but that's where it's coming from my brain what are you talking about
they're too big where would we put them bro now i'm talking about model trains dude think about
what they'd add to the apartment i don't need this not turn shark month what about model dinosaurs
think about it dude dude nice yeah dude we could be train bros everybody loves train bros
shit what if it's the cops what if it's the pizza guy whoa we got a wrist hit let me take a hit
first nice the what the fuck man i heard there's a party going on in here who wants to fucking party
hey look i guess i party a little too hard for him hey how about you huh you like to party
what what was that uh we just watched like an r-rated movie um it wasn't real don't worry
oh okay if you say so i think i should go now please stop what is this shit music i could
hear from my fucking limo you guys got any hard bass what is hard bass please stop
oh no your friend tapped out early you and me we're just getting started here i've got a gift
for you oh shit it's a work in progress i'd ask you to let me know what you think but the last
guys never did talk again after you don't pull up pliers unless you're fucked up time sure did
crawl for them though do you feel it hold still no nobody has pliers unless there's something
nobody has pliers put you crying i didn't even cut the bone oh where'd your enthusiasm go maybe
you're not such a party animal after all then maybe you shouldn't place music so fucking loud
all the time hey it's not me you need to apologize to it's your neighbor you know that guy's a
serial killer one of the greatest a living fucking legend man he can't get a wink
asleep because of you scum so i'm here to take out the trash no you don't carry pliers on you
unless you're a sicko or you are like in working on something a person wasn't obviously not working
on like a desk or anything hide there this shit keeps changing six days remain
working on trains what if i go this way i can't yeah that apartment yeah that that's probably i
know office closed all appointments rescheduled for tomorrow was it i what the fuck am i supposed
to do what do i do now you have a nice walk oh okay i'll have a nice walk somebody use channel
points let me see you're hey i saw you walking in the rain i figured you could use a lift
what's the person gotta say i'm a big fan man big fan the other night at the factory
those were my guys you killed what do you want i feel like i'm talking to an auteur over here
haha you're the fucking dragon so what did you think of my gift the tape oh that wasn't a movie
that was real oh that was pretty sick that was sick noisy neighbors right hey what did you think
of the wire cutter part inspired right i wish you hadn't sent me that tape and we've a little
girl watched it that was fucking horrible am i that amateur damn man shit i didn't even ask you
if you wanted anything you party no don't be a bitch man this is some prime uncut shit me and
the boys are working on remaking this wartime combat drug you gotta try it it's crazy hey i
don't have a razor give me your sword to cut this you're not touching my fucking sword
don't be pretty hey give me a razor give me a razor what was the name fuck yeah fuck yeah
fuck fuck psycho your turn okay aha fuck yeah this is where i pretend and then it's good shit
huh it lasts forever it wouldn't mean to last forever listen i got some fancy cameras at studio
51 let's bring these dumb bitches over there and no i don't want to do that you and me man
will make no no no no no no no no no i i don't i don't do that i don't do that no i'm not doing
that come on man i did you a solid you're a noisy neighbor i don't even no no no no i don't you
kill you're you're you're fucking crazy you think you're better than me you kill more people in one
night than i have my whole life we're cut from the same cloth you and i i'm proto man
keep it down do you know the meaning of respect do you understand i'm what i'm offering you
how do fuck off snow he wasn't interested he turned it down and got away okay fuck off
wait it's the same person whatever snow i'm busy what just happened oh shit did you seriously
follow me you fucked up what the hell ow barge barge now playing the third district
who do it fuck out of here clean clean real clean fuck i'm out of shape i shouldn't have
shot my personal trainer no you shouldn't have uh gonna go up here no buttons elevator going up
your voice is pitch shifted no it's not it's impossible uh what a chapel of doom quiet hills
let's go to um quiet hills that sounds good my voice is not it's not pitch shifted open world
sick watch out for that gun uh what is that whoa fuck it okay there's a guy with a shotgun over
there what who shot me shoot all right here comes this guy shoot shoot ah i gotta die okay i'm going
over there here we go oh i gotta dodge through it i gotta dodge through it gotta die gotta
dodge through it you can't you can't slice that back all right come on damn it all right hold on
fuck i have to pull him out how do i i gotta place that thing down
give me this what does this do oh well that's what that does it's smoke would you look at that it's
smoke god damn it okay pick it up can i go in here yeah what's in the bathroom nothing
ed ed netty opening sound what your mom puking in my mouth thanks a lot dick what what did i do
what are you talking about what is what is he talking about i'm cute what did i do i didn't do
anything oh fuck say you're sorry i didn't do anything it was because you didn't do ads
oh okay so picked up blue key card all right cool i'm sick right now well you go get go get some
medicine take some take like one or two what is going on what was it a silent hill reference
okay silent hill robot i got the blue key card oh shit don't get killed by that don't be an idiot
all right blue key card where does it take me i don't know current floor
two a space uncertainty sounds good what do you mean idiot oh it's called quiet hills
whatever well that was insane watch out the this guy's gonna wake up halt meat man your
puny vessel has been commandeered i am the invincible cyber man of glow box 12 surrender
to my superior robot intelligence i'm here to destroy all humans and chew bubble gum but i
just ran out of gum oh all right well i thought they were gonna make that joke i was trying to
stop them from making that reference human yikes that was oh i thought he was dead didn't get him
that's they're dead yeah they're dead tap all right where we going this way
looking good oil that was easy should i go up hyperspace oh it's a knife oh that was fun
whoa easy watch out for the ninja turtles what just happened what just what happened
i did i kept what i did i hit i hit the ninja turtle okay that all right this time just
okay good they don't know what it was watch out for the turtle this time
that that's what happened all right i was gonna say what the fuck all right got a yellow key card
i must have them all one more room how's the audio
haha i shouldn't have even said anything i'm such a fucking idiot oh my god i really am a
fucking moron why would i even say anything we were all just relaxed nobody was saying anything
and i just brought it back chapel of doom wait is donkey kong country it is donkey kong country
what how do i have to jump over it okay that's some suspicious masochism shoot yeah you know
you wanted to shoot me keep going oh you've gone shoot goodbye i have to shoot oh god i have to get
down is this doable anymore what i i i died because there's no minecart okay what did i
just jump into jump into his fist i was supposed to jump down get out get out of the cart imagine
streaming from you bathtub i know i gotta get how do i do this am i okay i did it no what
do i do i have to go up to the ah fuck fine who's up you who else somebody with a gun
no we're good key card that should work i imagine streaming from you bathtub i know
okay the best part about that dream seriously is i like i'm gonna turn on my webcam and set
up an elaborate setup to stream not only stream naked like actually in the bath with the camera
pointing down at a level where it could why would i ever do something like that doesn't make any
sense if that would ever actually happen i would wear like three layers of undergarments and wear
a pair of shorts and tape the bottoms of the shorts with like duct tape like so it would be
impossible put the cards in yeah i would but what would the bathtub even be for why would i be in
the bathtub watch this watch out whoops that's all what you do gun gun gun
shit randomly just do that one day what the fuck just happened i tried to throw it i'm not going
to do this one i'm going up here there's a lot of guns over that way i didn't bring this up here
okay good they're coming up they're coming up down oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh my god okay um okay they can't he's gonna see me this is not ideal not ideal this is incredibly
not ideal i think it's possible though holy fuck okay is he okay i'm all right i'm going to mcdonald's
do you want anything yeah get me a fucking big mac meal get over here i don't want to stain my
fresh tracksuit get out this is business well let's do this that was i'm dead okay okay he's
this guy he's gonna keep shooting me okay so i can't don't swing at him just hit his bolts back
okay um i don't understand but he throws me and then pulls the gun out and shoots and i can't get
it deflected uh okay so you he throws you then you have to slow it on time and oh my god what
the fuck i don't understand but that's not fair why is he doing this this is okay is this all what
a waste hmm shrink shink i couldn't even say it i've never proved of your pet projects shrinkage
oh i'll go home now and forget all about this this is your only warning what a fucking waste
let's get out of here yes let's do not mistake my mercy for weakness okay we're getting another
we're getting another uh image here yes i did that i know i did that but i'm in a pair a full
pair of jeans i've rescheduled your appointment for tomorrow i hope you had a relaxing night
i'm in a full pair of jeans right there you know what i mean have your children trick or
treat in your building only don't accept candy from anyone you don't know and don't accept
strange or discolored candy that's good advice who's knocking at the door trick or treat oh
are you dressed like me you dress like me i knew you'd recognize me you wear the same
thing every day happy halloween trick or treat what i don't know what trick or treat means
trick or treat trick or treat you're supposed to give me candy now
all right let me see if i have any let's check okay a fish head oh wow hell leviathan i said
hello happy halloween that's pretty fucked up i just gave a small child a cut off fish head for
halloween the police have confirmed the recent killings at mutual high security prison which
left over 20 dead including political dissident uan didn't even boil it first i don't know for
the work of the serial killer known as the dragon that's me or i think the dragon whose targets
tend to have ties to gang activities a bit though i shouldn't have probably slept behold comedy the
wayward swordsman awakened from poison slumber tragedy and i drugged your tea you don't even
know dimwit hee hee thou strugglest vainly errant heart tis not thy time to pass beyond that cryptic
threshold the time abeth no man's dominion now gaze upon my woeful continents and hearken
thou these words yeah hearken bitch two lustrous masks upon thy visage rest of gold and sterling
silver all life and death these masks preside lo the silver mask commandeth death with sword and
sling libate upon the author of the turbid wine of man you're a real killer huh no not so scary
when you're out cold hee hee the golden masks shineth life a vessel child wandering time's
infine fractal unspoiled by babalon's malignant spell is that a girl i see i didn't know you had
a conscience sicko hee hee ha ha two masks thou hast yet one alone may thy continents adorn gold
or silver life or death three grains of sand yet linger within thy shrinking hourglass deliberate
upon thy soul or errant heart time stoic harvest reapeth bitter yields my flag is next to a rose
my flag is between an o and an a my flag in three days you're going to meet again and you're going
to have to pick life or death remember whichever one you choose we're going to take away the other
to pick life or death in a few days that was a mario rpg reference for those who that are just
completely uncultured now scram all right i'm awake in four days so tell me again about the
men in masks what the masked men from your dream what the hell is happening you know
today's wake up here when did i get here uh what is happening what am i doing here
mm-hmm it felt so real i couldn't move my body all right you piece of shit what well i don't
understand get up get the fuck up uh okay do i not do i have to my doing what if i just don't move
okay that's rip graphics card 28 years in that godforsaken jungle killing soldiers wasn't so bad
i highly remember it but burning those villages watching those naked peasants cry i see it every
day it's the not the pst at ptsd it's the drug it's only been a week but it feels like a year
every word is getting longer the mosquitoes are getting louder when the drug runs out time
stops and you're stuck in the jungle forever this is getting bright it's grains of sand and
a shrinking hourglass i know what comes next i need to ask you a favor everybody's spam i die
no minus 684 days hey papa needs his medicine to help out an old vet i killed six chromage fosters
in the war he was am i the am i that person it's only been a day since his last taste how can this
be the drink is all this man ever was and when it is gone what remains is the bottle
pathetic absolutely pathetic let's just keep walking and try not to make eye contact
please help me anything a thousand yard stair does not instill me with confidence i've increased
your dosage to compensate for yesterday please keep in mind everything we've spoken about today
okay oh do you like it it's a traditional healing stone my daughter brought back from
burundi it makes a fine paperweight why can't i see emotes like monka s you need to have
better twitch tv to see monka s it's an add-on let's take a look al kasim secret founder and
ceo of neotech military logistics consultancy close ties to new mecha government involvement
in military r&d likely lightly guarded receive a caution wait is monka s part of twitch now or no
i don't think it is mansion hideout here we go shit i wonder if monka s will get the lul and
it'll just be part of twitch at some point it's like everybody uses it everybody that was bad
that was really bad right in the face watch this jump oh didn't pepe wait what down if you read
my blue thou shall be cursed with a i don't even know what that means wait what and yank it through
the hole in the back what are they saying no boss i read about it in regional geographic
how about you shut the fuck up when i'm telling you a story sorry i guess that would make don't
move muscle jesus it's you are you fucking following me again no more loose ends well
he did it don't move a muscle lock don't move a muscle rock let's go wait should i go over there
can i follow him in this room turn the tunes up i'm gonna turn up the tunes you got it wait
here you go turn up the tunes why is it doing this all right okay i was gonna say what
that should work all right turn the tunes oh this is where i was before when it was doing all that
weird shit you're not gonna get me with that sorry oh please just break it when i go down that should
work oh my god monkey ass lights out damn it i tried to swing down whoa he just did he spot me
with that shit oops okay he's buttoned what is this is that flamethrower how do i use it what
it's a beat i don't get it what do i what should i use this for who's that it's for the flames
fuck i'm trying to be fancy okay let's go oh i see there's oil right there i got it
how close can i get to this oh fuck okay i did it i need that link i need that link no stop
spanning links are you gonna be you're gonna get arrested what is it what is it i don't see
anything i don't what is it it's a fucking ear of corn why are you linking me an ear of corn
why are you linking this i don't understand it's the wrong link i can't i i don't i can't even i
can't open this link i can't open this you just scared the fuck out of me i was like wait this
not real that's anything can be edited anything can be edited anything once you understand that
you understand ouch anything can be edited anything everything is editable whoa i didn't
do that okay i gotta slow down all right fucking what am i doing i gotta bring everybody down here
or at least most of them actually there's a lot of people in there what's that guy doing
i don't know oh fuck okay he's what was he doing where's he going how do these guys not die
what can you say every word in the dictionary to teach my ai your voice no i'm not doing i'm not
no say every word in it that wouldn't even be ai that would just be you have me saying every
single word you wouldn't need ai you just did five that way you didn't you'd have just pieced
words together i think we've already brought this up before i've streamed and made videos for a
decade uh get up i'm up good i expected more out of the infamous dragon they think i looked up to
you well any last words good one now it's my turn mr kissy face cut off his head put the body in
cement sure thing v get the fuck up my head your head huh i expected more out of the dragon i
looked up to you fuck you fuck you too mr kissy face cut his head off and put the body in cement
sure thing v hey get up oh my head your head huh expected more out of the dragon
fuck you fuck you too mr kissy face cut off his head and put it in a bag sure thing
get up i'm up good i expected more out of the infamous dragon to think i looked up to you
well any last words i want answers ah i never told you my name you should probably cut his
tongue out what a waste of fucking time i'm gonna be late for my date i bet she's ugly shut the fuck
up i got i got a lot of chances here i'm up good i expected more okay any last words don't be late
for your date v what ha you sneaky bastard you're not here for the cronos you're already on it
i knew it i knew it how many times have i killed you he's on cronos that perk up your fucking ears
now you want to talk now you want to tell us how to make it well fucking talk
you're not gonna get anything if you don't i think you broke his ribs you're not gonna get
information if you do that you're just gonna kill him these guys don't talk you will though
i know your game now listen i have reservations in the second district and i'm not gonna be late
because of a goddamn cronos junkie now tell me who supplies you so i can end your miserable life
and get on with my night uh my psych uh what is cronos huh ah you don't even know what cronos is
you're on cronos kissy face watch this huh not so fucking fast now kissy face put the dragon
near i'll kiss him when we burn the place down people will think he was looking for drugs or
something what you're still alive whatever man you're probably just gonna go back and change
this anyway get up get the fuck up i'm not here for cronos i'm on it don't miss your date v
v what the fuck start talking now who sent you my psychiatrist sent me yeah you shrink kissy
face kill him and throw the dragon's body when we're done yeah i'm not here i'm i don't miss
your date i'm on cronos i'm on it i'm on it i'm on it i'm on it what the fuck you uh what start
talking now your tape sucked you thought you i can't believe you
i need to find it my fucking thing unplugged i'm on cronos i'm on start talking now your
tape was stupid you always thought you were in my league hey it's sad watching you grovel for my
approval you think i want your approval bitch fuck you fuck you we could have been a real fucking
team you know your form my cinematic flair it could have been art i'm going to fucking kill
you fuck the question he's just trying to get under your skin v shut the fuck up i'm tied up
and you still want my approval fuck fuck hey that was the ask al kesim who's he hadn't talked yet
ask fucking al kesim who's a bitch fucking ask him i'm not in the mood for this shit you handle
this one mr kissy face tell the boss al kesim was dead when we got here say what again say
what again i double dare you hey guys check this out hey guys check this out what i don't have a
weapon i don't have a weapon oops wrong guy oh there's nothing i fuck i had to dodge all right
i got it kill yeah good now we can have some fun hold what do you mean hold what i don't understand
what do you mean hold what's he doing all right all right what hold on
all right yeah it's okay i got it i got it that didn't hit him dead all right here comes this
thing spins it around blocks go around him got it yeah see you later was it supposed to do that
was it supposed to do that i don't think i was supposed to do that i don't know okay let's go
kissy face you weren't able to find the chronos were you he wasn't talking i think he knew
who sent us the boss isn't going to believe al kesim was dead when we got here you're making
me look very unprofessional he wasn't saying anything anyway these invents investor guys
don't really know anything about manufacturing chronos we need to look for scientists maybe you
shouldn't blow off their heads he wasn't talking either some things i don't know what to do with
you i'm fucking i can't even read still it is somewhat impressive that you were able to
eliminate the swordsman the boss might be able to overlook your murderous tendencies for it
it was no big deal yes it was i saw his handiwork at studio 51 he killed dozens of men
effortlessly and dispassionately he was ready for battle almost before i came out a big deal
it was nothing behind those eyes no soul no remorse he didn't care about his mission
or the people he killed or even himself why is all highlighted is this something with this i know
i'm hard on you sometimes but i'm proud of you the dragon was no ordinary no jeez snow
i think the boss is gonna give me a reward probably omega lull or standing whatever
jeez it's not so fucking close those are sharp saika you where are you going automatic one plus
letter grade yep get out of here dicks oops shooby shoot gone shoot shooby i can take it
oh yo all right get the other back fuck okay hit by a car oh fucking cars are coming
i missed double it up got it what a fucking idiot driver the car car watch out for the guy i'll
fuck you all right holy fuck well he's gone oh boy i gotta hit the helicopter like that all right
dr robotnik you suck oh i almost got it we oh
i talked a lot of shit oh
it's not good didn't hit him talking mad shit with somebody in missile range
make sure i don't run into anything oh fuck got it three yeah it's dr robotnik only three hits he
got it it's over you put me through a lot tonight let me just tell you you think i've never done
this before i've killed six of you no how the fuck do you think i got this job you think i look like
shit now this is a fucking scratch snow can't save you from this you know this one null shot me seven
fucking times from a mile away when i found him i rang his neck like a fucking dishrag like a
fucking dish rag fucking you think you're tough shit the dragon well i'm the dragon slayer
he's not the dragon slayer this is rested development i am ah you've been difficult
to find i have questions oh this game is weird you missed your appointment this morning i learned
why when i turned on the news there's a smoldering helicopter on the highway the mayhem you've caused
is inexcusable we will talk tomorrow go directly home and prepare for tomorrow's appointment
i don't think that's what i'm doing you look like you've had a rough day give me something strong
what do you got back there six more fucking months we would have blown those fuckers out
of the water you bastards couldn't fight for shit how the fuck did they win what's going on
you got something to say i'm mining i'm not doing anything i'm just sitting here
you know where you are right now don't you in a bar i i i did it i was in the world looks like a
distinguished service crescent tarik yeah where did you get it pawn shop on fifth you got a real
baby face ain't nobody but vets and junkies in the third district and you ain't a vet how many uh i
was injured i don't know nice story baby face war ended seven years ago you would have been sucking
your mama's tit when you were out in the jungle you know we would have fucking won if those
goddamn hippies in the first district weren't bitching about the child killings
what the fuck i don't like either of these two that's the spirit this rounds on me baby face
uh thanks they hated us i thought we'd be heroes man i thought i'd get all the puss
he came back it's because of those psychics or whatever government mind control spec ops
laboratory test tube freaks try to say it as a icky uh it's an icky word i don't like that i don't
like the word i look i don't like that word that word i just i'd rather i i don't like how it
sounds i don't like how it just rolls off the tongue i don't like it no not not icky and i'm
talking about like i just don't like the i don't like saying that i don't like that word i don't
like it i just don't like that word it's like ignore that old blowhard you ever what is chronos
What do I say instead? I don't know. I don't I don't know. I don't know. I
Just don't like it's just a I don't like that word
It's just oh, I can't even say it
Huh? Ah, I can't say it. I'm not gonna say it. I can't I define all I do it
I just don't like that word. I don't like the word
Just I just got out
I don't like it apparently they had some kind of drug to make them see the future or read minds or something
I had a buddy who met one played a game of cards in one every hand like he knew how would it play out before it
Happen you telling you the card game story?
Shut it ray look all I'm saying is there was some serious sci-fi shit going on and maybe we would have won if they left
The fighting the real soldiers
You know in seven years not a single
Civvy has listened to me. You're a bad liar, but you're a good guy
Well drink up
Bars closing it's time to go sir. They took care of your tab. Let's go. This is just the Yoshi's Island mushroom stuff
You know the one that goes
Door
inside
inside the door
dad
What?
run, okay, uh
I don't understand help
Terrorism that occurred on this district one highway
34-day what am I doing?
Three days remain. How is it? You're not mad at me. Why would it be mad?
I'm sorry last night when I asked you for help you wouldn't listen to me. I thought you were mad at me
There was something wrong with me last night dad's friends came over. I didn't have anywhere to go
So I hid under the stairs with behemoth. I
Didn't eat dinner last night. Oh
I'll make you something really. Yeah, let's see what we have. Let me see what I okay
You just hang on over there time for fish head soup. No, there's something else in here
You found some protein paste
Did you find something all I have is protein paste
Sorry, well, I guess I'm hungry
I need to leave but you you could stay here today. Okay. Have a good day. Bye. It's a heenie paste
those of you that know what that means, yeah, I
When I was for that some of the new viewers people that weren't here when we talked about this
This is not advice don't listen to me. This is disgusting shit. Don't listen. Do not do this
Nutritional shit. You need to go see a nutritionist or a doctor. Don't listen to me
I fucking have no idea what I'm talking about. Don't ever listen to anything I say
When I was I used to be very very very skinny even skinnier than I am now and I really wanted to gain weight
I went to the gym all the time and I got a lot of I put on a lot of weight
One of the things that I used to do is I would eat tahini paste
Because tahini paste is gram for gram the highest calorie per unit
Thing on earth. I would put it on sandwiches. I would have like two spoonfuls. It is hundreds of calories per spoonful
It's fucking hard, but it was it I I was able to put on weight. That's disgusting. That's disgusting
Why is that disgusting? I mean, I just told you it is I just told you it was disgusting just eat normal food
Just eat normal food, I know but if you eat watch this video now, I'm not watching that video
I'm not watching that video. I'm not watching that video. I'm not watching that video. That's
I'm not watching that video. No, I am watching that video. No, no, no, you're not getting me
I'm not watching. I'm watching that video. He hates that video
Fucking old-ass shit old-ass videos. That's like 15 goddamn years ago. All right. Yeah, I said it
In that video. I said I said it out whatever. I don't even care. I said whatever I could say it
I could say it like I'm I could you don't think I could say it. Okay. Let me try. Oh
Pussycat got okay. We're good done. There are two dozen wrecked motorcycles in a gun
Yeah, goddamn helicopter in the highway. I didn't have a choice. It's time to get huge. He's uncomfortable
No, I'm not I just I just oh I yeah, I don't like to say it's that other word
I don't like that word. It's a shitty word that word sucks and you shouldn't use it in your regular vocabulary
Use use fucking I don't know. Well, I superior saw him with this god damn it. Why am I back here?
You're not looking hot right now. I bet you want a hit of that good stuff, huh? You're supposed to be dead
Yeah, fuck you. I missed my date asshole. He's a dirty shit shit to your dirty words
Rough day, but whatever it doesn't have any arms. It doesn't even compare to what's in store for you
You don't even know about it. You don't even know about it. Do you the withdrawal withdraw from what?
Hi, you stupid motherfucker. You really don't have a clue
Do you when Kronos leaves the system time slows to a crawl until it stops completely?
You get stuck in your mind with nothing but nightmares to keep you company
You're gonna wish you were dead, but it'll never happen those neighbors of yours. Yeah, they're dead to us
But the shit I gave them they're still there in their minds. It'll never end for them. That sounds terrible
An eternity of torture when nobody can even hear you scream
Maybe I can show you some of them
Get you dossier on the way out and act like a goddamn professional tonight dragon. The name would almost be
Humorous if your recklessness didn't jeopardize our lives and everything we've worked for
I'm not the dragon though. How preposterous of me. Of course
You're not responsible for the rash of highly visible third district murders. It must be some other dragon
And I met the dragon when on the highway during the mission that I was not expecting that who is this person?
Paul long blonde hair swordsman you want an indicator of just how fucked up this chat has been today. I'm telling you
Yeah, there's something what is something in the something in the water today important question
Would you look at this? Would you consider selling look at that? You understand like that's what we look
That's what we're dealing with today. We are aware of an individual who fits that profile. Did he say anything to you?
No, he just said he was the dragon. I see very good yet. Is it a full moon? Somebody check
I had other plans, but yes, I wanted to track down and kill this person
He cannot be allowed to cause more damage. All right, but I thought is he really the dragon?
I don't know. This person is our dragon. He is the public menace who must be eliminated. You are treading on very thin ice
There's no longer room for failure from this point on if you display anything less than your utmost compliance of professionalism
You will be replaced now get out of here. Stay the hell away from there
Delete account it actually is a full moon if you don't think yeah, of course it is say, of course it is
Is it a full moon tonight? Would you look at that every time we've checked?
Every single time we've checked if it's a full moon and people are going fucking nuts in this chat
It's been either almost a full moon or a full-blown full moon
The next full moon will occur on january 10th and is known as the wolf moon
There are many legends in folklore about wolves
Yeah, it's it's today
It does not surprise me target is the dragon target of interest considered extremely skilled and dangerous connected with murder of several government employees
Last seen in high-profile chinatown casino casino. It's of course. It's a full can I play the slots?
I'm the gamble. Let's go
Hey, man, nice bathrobe. My mom has the same one
Thanks, so you want to play?
What's the game?
Two color roulette red or black 50 50 shot 5x payout. What do you say?
How does it work?
It's 50 50. Just pick a color and put down chips. Jesus
Um, isn't really usually more complicated
Look at the big man with the fancy questions. Maybe we do things a little different at
Unimpeachable chen's houch of legitimate wagers
Huh? You're gonna waste more of my time. I'm all in
excellent
Red or black. All right, let's see spin that wheel
Black wow, nice one, man
Do it again mama mia red or black black again
Spin that wheel
Oh red. Oh so close. Maybe you shouldn't have gone all in huh better luck next time
What? Hey, man, let's play
All right red or black
Let's spin the wheel
Wow, what do you know? It's black
Do it again this time. It's red mama mia red or black red
All right, let's spin the wheel
Wow
Red
You're a lucky one. Aren't you at everything again?
Red or black red?
All right, let's just spin that wheel
Red looks like we've got a regular ding dong daddy from dumbest on our hands
I'm out of chips. You've bled me dry. Here's all I got
99,999
Hey, thanks save first save right here
All right, I want to play slot
You're not getting back here without 100,000 chips
I have 999,000 like well, there are only 99,999 chips here
But they don't call me lenny the lenient for nothing go on through
But how did the russian know about no?
He was a fool
But whoever he worked for isn't and they're trying to bring back chronos
That's why i'm here. I'm so close. I know I am but I need your help
This is our chance for revenge the war ended seven years ago. I'm too tired for revenge and with al kasim
Gone the chronos. I don't have much time
For taking away our lives for making us monsters
Making us fight their wars and purging us when they were done. We don't have much time, but i'm so close
I want you to see I want you to see something
Hello
Hello, get out of here. I'll handle this right whoever you are. You just made a huge mistake
Oh, did I?
Oh, that's gonna shoot me
Yes, that should work. What the hell you you were dead
This isn't over
What's in the safe more money got prison security tapes?
You're surrounded surrendered now
No, bring on the music
now playing chinatown bill
kylie
And
Well, this one's good. It's a good one
This is good
See ya. Oh, can I grab it if I jump? Yes, I can
oops
Wait, I can what's going on?
What's going on?
Wait, hold on. Hold on. Hold on
Right, I can do that shit now. I can be fucking hilarious man
He's a comedy master
You already funny germa money has changed you
I i'm not gonna do that. I did that once
Money has changed you I plugged in a I plugged in a fucking microphone
Into an actual audio interface and all of a sudden I like I'm different now
It's still me. It's me. It's still me
I'm right here
It's still me
Nothing's that's the same me
You're infected. I'm not infected. I'm not infected, but I've been able to do that if I was infected. He's got the comedy virus
comedy virus
Probably didn't need you
What guys I I I did the what's going on thing like four years ago this time I just have an echo on it
This time there's an echo attached
When the echo makes me a comedy streamer
fucking full moons, man
The next all right the next time i'm like playing it screams. I'm gonna make sure I don't scream on a full moon
I'm gonna be like wait, it's a full moon tonight. Oh people are gonna be fucked
Hey guys, sorry. I can't like stream tonight
Why what's wrong?
Oh, well, it's a full moon and all of you lose your fucking minds
Astrology i'm telling you this guy's blocking everything shoot again. Shoot again. Oops. I need to shoot again
Shoot shoot shoot shoot shoot shoot shoot shoot
Fuck i'm trying to swing at it. Fuck. What am I doing? Derma is a virgo. Yes, I am
Dodge off with the explosions. It's gonna blow up. Can I hit it hit it? Wait, what what?
I can't swing at these to blow them up
How am I supposed to blow them up?
Use the drone. Ah, whatever. I'll just kill them. Don't look don't look don't look don't look. Oh, come on
Did I really just do that?
Did it?
Oh, I thought that was a background thing. Okay. I'm fine. How do I oh did he actually hit me?
Watch it. No, I didn't even pick it up
Dodge around him in
Okay, watch it. Watch it. Watch it. Watch it. He's gonna shoot me. Okay, wait till he gets up here
Shoot at me shoot. Oh fuck
What the fuck? Oh, oh go out help me. Help me. Oh, I can't help you
I thought I got over it dodge around get him good. Nice
Moon time. Let's get some full moons in the chat, please
All right, that's taken care of let's go through here. Um, i'll kill you
Oh, no, I won't. Yes, I will
This is a molotov. Hold on
oops
I knew you around that what?
All right, don't pick that up. That's it. All right, let's bring this upstairs
Oops, I think okay. No, that was good. Um, can I carry this with me?
What's going on? Oh, well, i'm playing katana zero. It's a fun game. This chat needs an exorcist
This chat needs an exorcist
Uh, you guys need it you guys need
Something we have you trying to get on your knees and put your hands up
Do it now
the golden moon
Casteth wide its brilliant smile upon the altar of thy germa 985 chat room
The chat members bathe in the glow
And go fucking hollow
What the fuck get back now
The stars dictate thy ultimate death ring from the errant heart libations of blood upon this hallowed altar
How did you get here? I was here all along
What are you talking about? Thou heatest not my grim horror spicy
But not three nights ago did I foretell thy choice of silver death and golden life
This altar demanded thine answers dost thou choose the golden mask of life to stay thy blade and be reborn in grace
Or does thou choose the silver mask of death?
And so upon this fallow soil fallow the blood of thine enemy people don't talk like this anymore
Life or death. What a choice, huh?
Uh glad i'm not in your shoes right now. He he
um
Why do I have to die here?
Does the star say so or maybe it's because of that drug business you're tied up in or all those people you killed or maybe
We just like fucking with you
Me personally, I like fucking with you. So what do you say you want to live or die?
I
I want to live
What are you talking? I can't I can't die. I want to live my final death is imminent errant heart
This is for real the chronos in your bloodstream is running out
You'll actually die if you choose to
Think of all the people who will live like these fucking cops and that little friend of yours. He he
What does the girl have to do with this?
Oh nothing forget. I said anything, but surely you'll choose to live
You have so much unfinished work to do
Remember that little talk we had the other night about a big choice you had to make
Here it is life or death you choose
Choose life these guys die and you walk away choose death and well, I think you can figure it out
the choice thou makest
Effective more than just thine own fate
To dawn the mask of death is to embody death and likewise the mask of life bestows life unto those that thy heart seeketh to protect
What do I do?
What do you choose?
I want to live I want to die. Uh
I don't have time. I don't have time. I don't have time. I don't have time
I don't have time the little girl lives if I okay little girl little girl lives
Is this the choice to accept the final end and bear the golden mask of what?
Wait, what did I just put up? Wait, what did I do?
Did I pick the wrong one? No, I didn't did I actually I thought I picked did I am I no seriously?
Did I actually pick the wrong one?
I picked death right are they prepared to bear his death in the place of those seek to protect bear death
Yes, may thou find his peace in death
Yeah, what the hell? Why would he say that that what hold on? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Wait, did you guys die to end the game?
Like the game's over. I just I the game ends actually you pick the wrong you pick the wrong. Can I go back?
Can I go back we did it omega lol if hepe laughs
Ha ha ha they said four times. It was the real end
But okay in a game where you're on drugs and oh, I have a period inside of the
psychiatrists or a
Therapy chair and they're like hey
Criken wait, wait, what what a criken's in this?
What a criken do what?
All right. Um, but I I don't know. I I can't tell what's real and not real
We've had the game like restart five times randomly in random places
Nah, that that can't be the end. I mean, it's gonna be like a joke
It's gonna be like, oh you're back in the you sitting back in the chair. I'm giving you the drugs, right?
It's probably something like that. Yes previous level like i'm good. All right. Here we go. Let's go. I choose life
I was gonna say that's
All right, I choose life
German has the reading comprehension of a gerbil
I'm on drugs the entire game
Am I really supposed to believe what two random guys that teleport to me and say you're gonna die, you know
Like i'm supposed to believe anything these two fucking idiots are telling me. I can't believe germa. This must be the full moon
Not the teleporting drug people
Let's go
I choose life. Why would you kill millions of people for a little girl? I don't
I don't even know what's going on right now. I I don't even know what's happening in the story. I know like slightly
I'm ready to make my choice
What do you choose?
I want to live
Is this by choice?
To forego the final end
Are you prepared to face the consequences to embody death and welcome it upon those around you?
Wait, no, what are they wording it like this?
No
No, yes. Yes
This will be fun
So be it thou chooses to bear the silver mask of death and scorn the piece of final death
Know that others shall bear the consequences of thy choice farewell
When shit like this happens in the game
Like what you I can't believe he didn't know that he was going to see the credits if he picked die
Have a fucking hands the favors like to call in the phone calls
I've had to make and ensure that the media wouldn't hear about your latest killing spree
An entire police squad is dead for nothing for absolutely fucking nothing
I can no longer excuse your egregious behavior and failures. There will be dire consequences for tonight. Hello. Welcome back. Oh that
Sorry, you cleaned the house
Yeah, it was kind of a mess. So I cleaned it up a little bit not a big deal
What's that? Is it a movie?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, we're not watching movies anymore. That's something I found today
Oh, well, can we get a movie then? Yes, we'll go get an appropriate movie
We're gonna get an age-appropriate film this time
Hey, man
Those pre-war samurai tapes you ordered just got in let me get them
Hey, can we get a cartoon?
I already ordered some movies next time. No, why why would I no I want to
Oh man next time then okay, I thought I I don't I want to do a cartoon
32 credits
Later, man. Okay. I have returned it for the crimson blade handed to me or taste my folded steel
I always knew this day would come come brother. Let me test your metal
ayi
Eek, he's bleeding the bad man stabbed him. This movie is too scary
Don't worry. It's not real. Why do I why would I why have a little kid watch these movies?
I know it's not real, but it's still scary
Uh, are you a samurai too like the ones in the movie?
I I don't know
Really? You look like one and you have a cool sword. I think you're a samurai
And now my death blow from hell
ayi
He just cut off his head
Lord our wise it is I reishi come to rescue princess isen you shall die
My son you are foolhardedly as ever or it is you who will die today
Clashing blades. Yeah
Uh, foolhardy. What was that? Is it enough tape?
Did you guys hear one of the prisoners is testifying in some big hearing tomorrow?
Yeah, some military conspiracy thing, right sounds important shouldn't we have beefed up security?
No, that's probably fine
You're surrounded surrendered now b. Oh, well that that was
Okay
That's pretty ridiculous
Oh shit
So is this katana zero? This is katana zero. I already figured it out
oops
Whoa, you can do that. Well, okay, I get it
You can do that while
Katana crew club. Oh, that's probably not real katana crew club
Uh, I guess I could jump and then the thing everybody has to be everything has to be a crew
Okay, let's go
And we go in and
Oopsie
What the fuck just happened? What?
There we go. That makes more sense
That makes more sense. How about we open this up and kick it down the door and get in there
Okay, who else is left you up here I got you oops
Terma super frog enemies
I love super frog
I wish that was a real game
And I know I know you're gonna say it
I know you're gonna say it is a real game, but it's not
It's not fully developed
easy
What the fuck did they come from? Oh, they're going they're going up and down the stairs
Ah shit, okay
I gotta stay up
Stay up. I've done
I couldn't see fuck
God damn it. I gotta sit up. Oh my god. I gotta sit up. Oh my god. All right
It's hard
You know what's the problem? Okay, I gotta stop
I gotta stop caring about that move
And that moves cool, but it's impractical
Only when it's necessary to use back down around. Why can I swing?
I want names now. Who are you?
Oh, this is what we saw. This is what happened before. This is uh yuan, right? Give me names now
Well, I give me names. Uh, um
Josh rose
He was assassinated this week. Omar al kasim al kasim
See the one bringing it back. Does he have anything to do with that russian thug or the ninja lady?
I
I don't know what you're talking about. I didn't know anyone was trying to bring chronos back
I've only spoken to my attorney these last seven years
But I can tell you it's not the government and by my estimation. There are very few entities with the resources to manufacture chronos
Alex and when no contact him
And leon von alvin slaven. He's the one who made it
That's what I wanted to know
Please don't kill me. Everyone has to die for making us this way
Uh, your trial is afar. So you're gonna die tomorrow anyways, or today. I killed him now two days remain
Leon von alvin slaven third district slaughterhouse and meat processing
Your questions will be answered
I guess that's what we're doing. We're at the we're at the meat grinder slaughterhouse. Let's go
Easy what I just do stay tuned for an appointment announcement for you from your employer
It's been a while since I have had a visitor. I'm quite thrilled
This sorry facility was once the testing ground for the null project
Who cares about lore when we can have ads new mecha's most promising soldiers
The scientists were ones who threw my gauntlet to a certain there
Whatever. It's like reading and talking at the same time. It's just like i'm trying to play and read and talk and think
Let us see how suitable you are. All right, you can't help me. You're fucking terrible with shooting
Interesting proceed
Skip the dialogue literally who cares laughing my ass off
I thought I had time
Shit, that was pretty good too. That was going good. Ah, my ears are itchy both inside of my fucking ears
Shoot. Well, there's a guy in here. What?
All right, i'm fine
I don't know. I make it made this go. Look at this guy makes fucking noises
Fuck you. I had it
That guy doesn't that guy only comes up like half the day of time
Whoops, I i'm an idiot
What oops? Oh, I fucked it up again. It's all right
Got it. All right. That wasn't so hard. Why did I make that so much harder than it needed to be?
How did I do that? Oh shit, he's gonna shoot me
Oh, we're good. Oh, I forgot about this part. Okay, so now we just have to go we just dash through
That's fine. The fuck away
Oh god, this sucks
At least I didn't have a gun
Anybody else have a gun over there?
Nobody what is this? What's that? What is this?
What is that? What's this?
Okay. All right. Another one. He didn't even know it's on him. What's going on with my screen?
Why is my screen doing that crush him crush him? Oh, come on. I almost ran out of time. Oh shit
But i'm just blowing up. I shouldn't have done that
Don't shoot me. Don't shoot me. Don't shoot me. Don't shoot me. Don't shoot those. This is small tough
You motherfucker. I want germa to start streaming
You guys are on fucking drugs
What do you think the over under is that like a two thousand people here are on drugs?
What do you think?
I got it. All right. I got it. Okay. I got it. I got it
You gotta be kidding me
Oh fuck. It's gonna do all the things gonna go off
You gotta be come on man. Come on
I hate this part
I'm gonna die again
My god
Okay, fuck just you two
What does this do?
Nope, what does this do?
Uh gonna be crushing them. I want to go down. Why is this taking so long? I don't understand
You're making randomly crush as well. It's on. Oh, okay. That was easy. Wait
Now it's easy
Time save not really. All right guy top guy top. Let's uh go like this. No, let's I can do that
But come on it didn't hit that didn't hit
What are you fucking talking about?
I'm so mad
Why is that not working? It worked like three times already. What is going on?
I've done this like three times. What?
Okay, what is happening?
This happened to me too. What?
Okay, whatever. Fuck it. I don't care
Watch out for the fucking laser
Get the fuck away from me. Oh that stupid thing. Oh, it's so annoying
Hello, sour tower assemble. Yes turn off the fucking lasers
Who's on the other side of that?
One guy left. That's it flooding the market with sour towers. Somebody stop that guy. All right, here comes another
This is the final portion of the null test it has an astronomical failure rate you have been an entertaining participant thus far
Good luck. Thank you. Oh, okay. Well, I have to slow time down
All right, this one's not gonna go down. Okay
It's the moment of green lights
Yeah, what am I stupid?
I was looking up. Okay. I gotta stop. Okay
Oh, yeah. Yeah, this sucks
uh
Fuck this sucks
I have to start to
Gotta stay in the middle right there. We're good. Is that it? Did I do it? What's going on? Whoa. Hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey
Not cool. Not cool
Jesus christ
Don't even think about it. What the fuck who's left anymore?
Jesus god. Damn it, man
Uh, hold on. Let me wipe my hands off
Hold on my like
7 000 inch long hair is getting in my mouth. No, it's not I lied to you. I'm just annoyed
Fucking guy's got a gun. Hey, what the fuck is going on right? Hey, hey, hey
Can I leave the test is over you survived. Thank god for alpha. No, the rate of survival is seven percent beta
No, the rate of survival is 13 percent for gamma. No, the rate is 100 percent of survival. Okay
Congratulations prodigal child
Thank you. Open the door, please
That was rough. I'm not doing this again. Are we? Oh, come on
It's an even smaller room
As a gamma null you were given chronos from childhood and trained to be a new mecha ultimate soldier
Your mastery of time and combat made you a god of the battlefield. You should have won the war
But ultimately chronos and the null project were failures. I must restart from the beginning
Your existence is in error
You will receive no chronos
Whatever you say not this again
There's nothing left for you here
Go I have work to do and I can't be disturbed. Okay
Goodbye. Can you open the gate before you I go?
Did my controller unplug or is this part of the game? No, my controller unplugged. Okay
You've exceeded the limits of my patience
Yeah, my work is too important. I cannot be disturbed
To proceed further is to terminate your own existence. I picked to live actually
Turn on wait a minute. This is the this is my dream
Remember my dream
Is that spot turn it on it's been a while since I've had a visitor. I'm quite thrilled
The sorry facility was once the testing ground for the null project
New mecha's most promising soldiers and scientists were run through my gauntlet to discern their
suitability
Let's see how suitable you are. What's this open the chamber? Wait, should I do that pre-recorded? Is it going?
Who's this
That looked pretty horrible
That didn't look good. Where the hell are you? Why didn't you come in today?
You killed an entire police squad last night. Do you understand the jeopardy or erratic behavior he's putting us in was the guy
What the hell are you doing? Hello. Welcome back. I found something cool today. Want to see what is it?
I don't want to spoil it. It's really cool. Come on
It's right up here
It's the it's the city we're in
Okay, it goes so far. I wonder what's beyond the mountains
You can't see all the mucking trash up here. Yes the lights it's pretty
I want to see it all someday
Yeah, my only response is no, why is it only what we're going somewhere better is somewhere far away
Like the second district
Further. Okay. Hey, what's that?
It's from the war a medal
Wow, you were in a war. That means you're a hero. You need to clean it though. It's really dirty
I haven't taken it off in seven years. It reminds me that no matter what i'm doing. I did something good once
I just throw it. What why did you do that? I have other reminders now
Oh
Can can we stay up here for a little longer?
Yes, i'm pretty sleepy, but I don't want the men in the masks to come back
Uh, then I i'm they're not gonna get you I promise
Okay. All right. So we got we got some weird shit going on. It's not as this judgment day
Don't let her get hurt. I'm gonna do everything I can
Hey, hey wake up
What were you having a nightmare? It's time to get up. Look I made breakfast
Uh, okay. What is it? Oh, I don't know. You didn't have a whole lot in the kitchen
It's tahini paste. I found a couple of fish heads and some tahini paste and then made a soup out of it
That's gonna be gross
Thank you
Pretty good cat puke noise if I will say so myself
How was it? It was uh, it's my favorite. I loved it your new favorite. That makes me so happy. I thought it tasted pretty bad
Uh, there's nothing else
I'm gonna let you borrow behemoth for a little bit just because you don't have one yet
I don't need him when you're around
If you're ever lonely behemoth will keep you company, but you better take good care of him because he's still my best friend
But it's just borrowing
Well, look now leviathan has a friend
And me too and you well, I know you gotta go now. See you later
Please come in and take a seat. So you're still alive. I was beginning to wonder
Not that it matters because you've gone completely out of control
Okay failing to kill your target murdering an entire police squad
Irrelation of duty. I'm surprised you even decided to come back
you
you fucking
This is your last chance if you deviate by even the slightest margin from your orders from here on
Our relationship will be terminated
You cannot possibly understand how gravely important our work
I was no
I how do you know about that?
Hmm, I killed the creator of chronos. Not a big deal
How did you you were never intended to know about that? I want the truth now
Yes, uh, of course, but
How did you know about leon?
I'm asking the questions now, man
I see
Uh, yeah, who am I?
There are no records of your life before no you presumably had a normal upbringing in famably
family
your aggression and
Psychopathy
Psychopathy made you a prime candidate for no you were placed as a child in the gamma project the most elite null unit
Family you were given chronos to enhance your abilities and trying to be a super soldier for the new mecha
I don't know much more my psychopathy. Ah
You lack the aversion to killing that most people are born with perhaps i've misread you but you seem to enjoy it
I don't like it is the only thing I like killing is the only time I feel alive
Yes, it's what makes you so suited for this work, but no matter
Null performed extremely sensitive and occasionally morally dubious operations during the war
Nobody foresaw the unintended effects of chronos on the system as the war ended with chronos production ceased most null died of withdrawal
Everyone I kill is related to chronos its creators must be silenced forever chronos can never be allowed to come back into this world
Uh, why did you keep all this from me? What is it? What are you talking about?
My job is to rehabilitate you to focus on the future your past is relevant only the total elimination of chronos matters
Now it's time for your treatment. He's gonna kill me not if I kill him first
Get you dossier on the way out. You may leave now. All right, here we go
Here's the final mission of the game the bunker eliminate any and all sensitive material currently stored in the safe room
of al kissim's bunker
Located in the center for synergistic research expect heavy resistance leave no survivors
dossier he dossier dossier dossier
I am back. Wait, wasn't this a hotel? Welcome to the center for synergistic research. Are you here for
I remember you you're the guy who showers with your sword. Weren't you wearing the same bathrobe at the murderer?
It's my lucky bathroom. Well, it certainly has character. You missed some blood though there. Oh and there
So get this apparently it's my fault. The dragon got in the murderer. I forgot to check his id or something
Who knows just don't tell my new boss
Anyway, i'll need to see your security clinic
Well, excuse me how rude no, I will not shut up until you show me your id
Oh, i'm just here for the showers. Hi. Oh, I didn't know we had a shower available to the public
I'll have to check my handbook on that. It's on page 335 section f2
Oh, you know the handbook quite well. I guess you must be a receptionist too. You sure don't dress like one
Well go on through and have a nice shower. Thanks. Dope now playing overdose
Let's go
Shoot
Hey, whatever. Oh which way turns
Didn't hit him. What the fuck are you talking about? I'm trying to get
I went up
Really?
Damn it. I didn't even know that was over there. I should I gotta look more often god
Oh, I see. I get it. I get it. I get it. Okay. I gotta wait till it goes over to the door
All right, wait till it gets over to the door
Okay, ready?
Oh my god, this sucks am I okay am I doing something wrong here?
Something wrong
Yeah, what have tell me what am I doing wrong? What's going on? What am I doing wrong?
Tell me what i'm doing wrong. I'm doing something fucking wrong. I have to wait till okay
I know what i'm doing. I know what i'm doing wrong. Okay. I don't tell me don't tell me
I know what i'm doing wrong. I know what i'm doing
I know what i'm doing wrong. I don't know. I gotta wait till it bunches up
like I mean I
Oh, man, this sucks. Okay. I gotta wait till it bunches up together and then you do it
I fucked it up. It's okay
Oh fuck. All right. Hold on. Here we go. Oh my god. I tried a stupid fuck
No, back it up. Wait, I can do it
No, fuck. I hate this
I hate this
It's so simple, but I hate it
god
Whoa
All right. That's a lot of people in here
Not so bad. Well, that's one way to have that happen
Oh, okay
All right
Okay
No, I just
Why whoa easy easy easy easy. Oh god, he's gonna shoot. He's gonna shoot. He's gonna shoot
I got it
Well, it's the idea. I had it. That's the idea. I had it
That's the idea. I had it
What if you're freaking out over what's going on?
Everybody relax. What's going on in here? I put it in full moon only mode
Watch out for the shotgun blast. I can't find it. All right. Now what about down here?
I'm going this way. Oh god, okay
I gotta drop down time's gonna run out but I don't care. What's that? Are these all uh, is these all gamma gamma rays?
Whatever it is. So I've just ran by that. I feel like I shouldn't just run them
I feel like I probably shouldn't just ran by that. All right. Hold on. Let me just
They have machine guns another one. All right. We're good. We're good. We're fucking good. We're good. We're golden. We're good
I fucked it. I fucked the whole thing. No, I didn't
All right
Yeah
Whoa. Hello
Make those back turns
Turn your back. Oh, I can wait I can
All right. I got a bomb. Oh, i'm in trouble now
Maybe not i'm going down. Hold on
They're gonna go all the way over there. I got you. I got you motherfucker. Check this
Shit. All right, i'm gonna go back down
All right. Oh perfect. Oh, I thought it was b to pick. Oh, i'm an idiot
I'm in trouble now
I got no time time's up. I just got crushed by the door. I get killed by the fucking door
Oh, i'm so fucking tilted right now. I get killed by the door
Get out of here you motherfucker fuck off
All right, i'm tilting. I can slow down slow down. I'm full tilting. I gotta slow down
All right, that guy this is stupid asshole
Yeah, come on down. Come on. The guy just walks down. Oh now he's not gonna go now. You're not gonna move. That's great
I don't even know what fucking hit me. No, there you are
dick
Jeremy pick it up. Can I pick it back up? I thought I could pick it back. I thought I was right next to it or something
I don't know
What I went so far much higher than I thought get over here that didn't swing. No, i'm not fucking around
I'm gonna get away. Don't let him get away door the door the door. How do I open the door?
How do I open the door? Oh, thank you
All right, i'm i'm safe hide
No, the oh we found who it was
Yes, that should work. Behold comedy the wayward swordsman awakened from poison slumber. He is getting exciting, isn't it?
The first axe climax doth approacheth. Oh, this sounds like hotline miami
I missed oh, that's so sad and annoying. I'm pissed off. I'm fucking pissed off now. I'm pissed off
Watch it
Excuse me. What's down there? Nothing. Not bad. Not bad. Not a bad run. I have to oh I use guns now
I have a gun
Let's throw the gun. Okay. Oh, I thought I could shoot the gun apparently not. Okay
Whoa, okay. I see what I have to do. Hello. Look at me. Oh my god. You shot me through them
Ah shit
Really? Okay. Well, that's fine. Oh, i'll just do this. Oh that turns on up there too. Well, fuck
All right, i'll turn this shit off. Let's go. Oh, yeah. Uh, I guess
I guess I gotta go around here. I guess I go over here and then they're gonna wrap around
Okay, I got it ready three two
One go
Okay, here they come. Oh shit. Oh my god
Let me see that again. I have to see that again
Sometimes I do it. I mean that was a mistake kind of sorry. Let's see. I don't even know who was what
My hoohoo
Oh that this is me thinking
Can I fast forward?
Yeah, that's pretty good
That's pretty good
Oops, okay
Oops. Oops. Oops. Oops. Oops. Oops. Oops
Oops. Oops. Oops. Oops. Oops. Oops. Where they going? Oh fuck. Oh god
Where they going? Oh god. Oh my god. Oh my god where they going?
Scooby-doo shit, man. I swear to god
Fuck really. Oh my god. This is a explosion. What is gonna happen behind me? Wait a minute. What if I do this?
I got it. I did it
Wow more guy with the gun guy down there. Okay guy with the gun. Let's go now the gun gun. Okay, pop it to a guy
Wow, i'm an idiot. Okay. I'm fine
That room sucked. Oh no boss fight. Oh you've arrived. I was hoping we'd be able to finish what we started
This should be fun. I guess it will be
Okay, I get you
All right. I get you a fucking bullshit
You gotta be fucking kidding me
Oh, they gotta die quick
fuck
That was bad
I didn't slow the time down. Come on. Let's go. I gotta dodge through that
Here she comes with this bullshit again. Ah
God damn it. All right, this is it happens. Did you start you restart so quickly?
What's happening did it your
Start rescue helicopter a man is falling
River a river is falling to the river lego. What are you doing?
All right, who are you?
What the fuck are you guys doing? You don't recognize the uniform. I thought 15 and I were the last no left
Al Qasim paid me in chronos to kill people. That's why you're here. Right chronos. There's none here
I don't know where Al Qasim kept his but it's not here
There's almost none left certainly not enough for both of us
Uh, there's not enough. What do you mean?
You guys have gone full hollow
It's almost gone. The no project is over if the government still has any they certainly won't give it to us
The rotten afterbirth of a miscarried war maybe there's enough for one person, but not both of us
Uh, i'm not even here for that shit
Why else would you be here? There's nothing of value here. Nothing. This is this killing this fight. It's been for nothing
Unless dot dot dot you enjoy it. Don't you?
Killing the immortality that chronos gives us the failsafe of time. It's why killing means nothing because when we die we always go back
Killing is the only time we're able to touch that thing. We were never able to have
This fight will go on forever until one of us surrenders. This battle is happening in our minds
It's a tournament of willpower every time you kill me. I understand a little bit better how to beat you
Oh, okay, after I finish you i'll go after the people who did this to us
I promise I won't let your death be in vain. They'll suffer
Um, you're are you in withdrawal you're in withdrawal
It's been days since i've taken chronos not since al kassim died, you know what happens
The visions won't stop you're you've killed me a thousand times to the point where I don't even feel it anymore
But maybe there's enough chronos in your bloodstream to slow down the withdrawal if you guys lost it completely
You guys have gone absolute full complete hollow
What's going on in this chat? Everyone's freaking out
What's this the real final boss?
Didn't touch it
Got it. Whoa. Okay, that's not fair
All right, how come the ship's on the go? Oh, I just what she just teleports
Ah, fuck got it. Oh my god
That's not even real
What?
I've watched you make that mistake a hundred times. You can't outsmart me. There's no way for you to win this
I just keep dying over and over again till I fucking figure it out
Okay, let's go
How many times do I have to do this?
Now here comes again this shit
Now the side
And then this one below
And then this fuck and then she flips around this sucks
Here it comes nothing in the middle then she goes across
Down and then fuck me
What? All right. Here comes the bullshit that I keep fucking up
There it goes. I don't get I can't I don't understand. I'm gonna get hit by no matter what
What?
Do I have to dodge at the?
Wait, what the fuck? Oh fuck. Okay. I'm safe there
Did she just blow herself up?
God damn it. There's pronos in your blood enough for me to make it one or two more days
Is she drinking my blood?
I couldn't get over there fast enough
No, that was bullshit stupid fucking explosion from that dog shit
Fuck I missed. All right. Here we go. Explode. She's gonna blow up
Oh
I can't why am I on the ground for that long? I'm getting sick of this
My chat
Is this could be the worst chat experience?
In the last 10 years
Absolutely without a doubt
This is absolutely without a doubt the worst chat experience
in
Probably in 10 fucking years
Holy shit
Oh my god
I have to stay away when I hit her. What am I doing? Not smart. Not smart. Not smart
Get the fuck out of here kill
Kill the people who did this to us
Kill them kill them kill them kill them
for me
Access denied retinal scan. Come here
Crush kill destroy the final boss's full moon chat
Well, can I oh?
Well, okay, I guess that makes sense open the door
Friday full moon
I I don't even know. I you guys have gone fucking crazy
Wait, it's me
Uh, do I have to do this? What if I don't touch anything?
Is I need to break this? I have to break the cycle, you know what I mean?
If I if I keep yeah, this is gonna be like a never-ending circle
You know
We would have fucking won if those goddamn hippies in the first district weren't bitching about the child killings
Oh, so
You literally murder everyone in the game. Okay. Well, i'm not gonna do anything. I'm just gonna sit here
Kill kill kill kill kill. Nope
No, I don't think I will
What are you doing? Your targets are still alive
What the hell have you done?
I didn't do it
You do you understand what you've done?
I haven't been able to reach my daughter all day my phone. Why do I still have this?
I can't explain this
They won't come after me. I had nothing to do with this
He lied to me the dreams were the dreams were real
No, no, i'm leaving. I need to leave. There's no time. I need to get out of here. I gotta go
I gotta get out of here. You knew my dreams really happened
What? No, what the fuck are you talking about?
What did you do to me?
I gotta go
Get the hell out of my office you goddamn junkie
What are you doing? What are you your withdrawal get away from me you after all i've
Stop stop you can't
I I can give you all the chronos you want. Just let me go right now, please
You're fucking sobbing
I'm not pressing me buttons. I'm not stopped. I'm not pressing a it's doing it. It's scripted
Give me the drugs. I think that's what this is, right?
Why am I taking I'm taking too much?
That's too much
No, stop you're gonna go into like another dimension
Search the body. What do you got?
Picked up new mecha government key card
Search the suitcase chronos delivery 330 wednesdays 286th ring new mecha
special weapons lab
There's a dossier here as well
subject zero
Null executioner class gamma squadron high value government contractor open for third-party contracts
Must be eliminated discreetly upon questioning of role or gaining knowledge of chronos manufacture process
It was me
They were coming after me next
Okay
Go home. No, wait, don't have like a secret government facility thing
Five ten lol, that's like fine
I'm just going home. How am I supposed to collect the rent if you won't let me in?
This is a crime scene ma'am
The man had no next of kin when we're done conducting our search everything in the apartment is yours
Hmm fine. Who's this?
He's a tenant the room with the broken door is his
Was my house broken into?
Yes
Neighbors was too got killed if it wasn't this it would have been an od guy was a junkie
You can enter is there was a note one life for another the broken door is coming out of your security deposit
Do you see a little girl anywhere?
little girl
There are no little girls here not in my building not in the third district
Randy check his apartment for weird shit. What little girl are you talking about?
Uh the girl that lived with him daughter
There are no children in this building. I make sure of it the man lived alone
Kids in the third district
I had no kids. He was a junkie loner mixed up in some drug business
Sir, if you'd come with us, we'd like to i'm not going with anybody put your hands up and get on your knees now
Comply and nobody's gonna get hurt
Holy shit hawas to dispatch. We have a 452 and tenement 298 medium build male with a bathrobe and a samurai sword
Randy he fits the profile wait
I think he's the guy
He's the guy seven years ago hide quickly. No soldier
This is zero target neutralized zero signing in mission accomplished. No zero here
uh target neutralized
Acknowledged zero fifteen return to base if anyone gets in your way, you know what to do
What this is me?
This is me
It was me all along
Oh, that's a d what?
It was you. Yeah, it was me
Yeah, i'm katana zero
I was just the nightmare the whole time
Who was that? That was the katana 15
katana zero
mid credit scene
What about the secret boss?
Is there a secret boss in katana zero? Did I miss a secret boss?
Katana zero secret boss
Uh, how do I get here?
Boss only applies on a full moon
Wait, wait, wait, wait. What's going on?
V is dead
Hmm. It was a null survivor game of 15, sir
I see
And we will soon need to wage open war with the government. I have no idea what's going on
Because there's gonna be a sequel. Oh
Okay, it was fun
Stream the secret boss. I do it. Do I have to like play through the game again or something?
Or can I just get through it quickly?
V in the bathroom. Yeah
The sequel is gonna be free dlc. That's pretty cool to be continued
Okay, watch how she squirms tragedy
He he
And for naught dear comedy. Oh, whoa upon. Whoa is what baleful end awaits her?
Let's make it fun
Government lab speed run mode and hard mode have been unlocked. I mean government lab gamer mode. Uh, should I do continue?
Government lab the right bunker part two government lab. Is this the uh secret one?
Where do I fight the secret boss?
Yes. Yes. Yes. Okay, this looks pretty new
All right. Let's go. Oh, this is the key card, right? That makes sense key card
Uh, this is a puzzle
Locked I should come back in a few months
What?
I should come back in a few months
Is this dlc?
Oh, this is dlc. Well, all right. Well, hold on. How do I get to the secret boss?
Because hana zero secret boss fight
bunker part two
The dreams were real. Hold on. Okay, so I go back to bunker part two
I go in
I I cut him off. I said the dreams were real
Cut him off again. You knew it. Why can't I remember just all the red shit? Okay, let's go
I mean, no, no
What do you mean? No, no, no, no
Remember, you basically have to piss off the psychiatrist every time you talk to him
It won't work. You have to constantly disrespect the therapist from the beginning of the game. Oh
It's red every time he talks to you. Okay, you only have to do it in the first few missions
Yeah, I mean this is a it'll take me four or five hours to go through it again. Not worth it
Yeah, not worth it the boss. Let me see what the boss is though. All right. He has like all right. That's pretty crazy
Okay, this is fucking insane. This is actually in like disturbing and fucked up. Um
Takes like 20 minutes to get all this stuff
Wait, wait, so you tell hold on show it show it how fast reliably will it do?
If I can I do it reliably just look up a guide you can do it all fast
15 to 20 minutes skip through all the tapes to where you talk to them. So start at the factory and then oh, okay
So I have to just go to every time I talk to the therapist
I don't even remember what the hell if you do everything correct
You just have to cut them off. You don't have to play through most of the game. We'll try it
Look at this a guide. Okay. Hold on. How do I lock the psychiatrist boss?
Okay, katana zero you do not need to start a new game to complete this
It could be done even if you've beaten the game before simply go back to the levels and complete the event
Flags listed below, okay step one hang up in factory and ask for medicine play the factory level at the very start of the mission
You'll get a phone call in the hallway continue to hang up until you've exhausted the interaction
Eventually, you need to answer the phone with hello
Okay, so just hang up hang up hang up hang up interrupt the psychiatrist and ask for medicine until he gives it to you
All right, we'll do that. So from the beginning of the game, right? I'm willing to try it
It shouldn't take too long game boomers is for nancy drew only this is not game boomers
All right from the beginning or from the middle from the very beginning
All right, hang up a bunch of times and then tell them to fuck off so tell me again. Yeah
Yeah, yeah men in the masks. Uh-huh. Hang up. Hang up. Hang up. Hang up. Hang up. I'm bored already
Oh, we're not gonna play through the whole game
I'm just gonna do the specific things it wants me to do because I think they're like three things to do
Go left. Let me go left. I couldn't go left picked up prism key. You know, what the hell does that do?
prism key
It opens the prism, right?
All right. Hang up
Hello
Goodbye. Uh, goodbye
I have how many times i have to do this stop stop. Oh jeez. I almost missed that one
How many times do I have to do this? The guide says do it 15 times. Are you serious? It's done. It's done
It's done. Hello. This is not the time for games. Damn it. Listen closely. All right
So now hang up and ask for medicine
All right
Now just keep telling them to fuck off get on with it interrupt the psychiatrist ask for medicine till he gives it to you. Good. Okay
Let's go. It's time for five nights at freddy's. What? All right. Let me just get through this quickly
Do I have to okay do I have to play through this or do I can I just leave?
Like can I just leave the game right now and just do the rest of the stuff?
You can just exit out
Save and quit just main menu
Because you can leave you can leave. Okay
Dude, so all right, you can leave and then go to the meeting in the tape
Oh, all right. Okay. Let's go main menu
continue
Continue previous level if level progress will be lost if no is selected. Wait, this is gonna work
Try to say no and pick it
You can main menu each. No, hold on auto wants to leave. Hold on
Okay. Sorry. He was like, let me out
He was just hanging out back here
sleeping
Okay. So did we determine if do I have to beat this?
Or should I just continue and beat this level first or what?
Have we figured that out press? No. Okay, so factory and then go to the end
So go here. Okay, and then just keep telling them to fuck off
Sleep go to the appointment and say give me drugs. Give me drugs. Give me drugs
All right, that's actually not that much left
So anger the receptionist and ask for medicine is after this. Here we go. Please come in and take a seat. Yes
Give me drugs. You look well despite last night's circumstances. Shall we begin? Just give me my medicine. I just want the medicine
It's wearing out. Just give it to me. Is he gonna give it to me? Give me the drug
Okay
now make your way to level go to the hotel and anger the anger the receptionist
Just repeatedly interrupt her once you've made her angry complete the mission
This results
Oh, okay. All right, let's go. There's only like two more things after this
So to make her angry angry angry angry and then beat the mission stare blankly
Wow that let me go
Stop talking to me
Shut up
That's it. I don't need this right now. Get out of my face. Okay, complete the mission
So I have to beat the mission now, let's go i'll do it very quickly
Here they come
Boss the dragon's here. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, raise the alarm. It's just level two. How hard could it be? Not very hard
Yes, that should work
Go go go go go
Jerma stop pretending to ignore i'm playing a game
Hey, what's that? Oh, yeah, what's going on?
Smooth
It's way easier when you've already beat it
And we beat level two look at that now last time do do just throw them off
I understand why you're here. I'm not gonna let you get this just get rid of them, right?
Just kill him. Just be bad. Just be an asshole
Okay, cool. All right now interrupt the psychiatrist over and over again. I'm getting there. I'm gonna like a couple more things to do
You missed the ass-eating scene. Oh, no too bad
Stop there are reports of gunfire in this building. Who are you? That's him. He's the guy
What the fuck oh we have to
The receptionist of the murderer hotel has been eliminated due to your lack of discretion
Please minimize collateral damage in the future
Okay, this is where we now
Uh after the mission do psychiatrist session interrupt the psychiatrist just until he gives me medicine
Okay
Okay, i'm busy
oof
In other news time to go to sleep
I can't sleep without my tea really
Okay, go to bed
There's
Two more things to do
Okay, interrupt till he gives you medicine then
Now then you have to speak to the dj
Just let the man have his tea
I already did the dj you can skip that part
So if it's already been done, I don't have to do it. Give me my shot. Shut up
Okay, hang up on the phone hang up the phone call right before the dj booth and then speak to the dj regarding the drugs
I actually do have to do this again. I have to hang up on them. I don't kill. Okay. Yeah
You saw how quickly I did that last one. Let's go
Okay, so we we only have a few more things to do here
All right during the mission hang up the phone call right before the booth and then speak to the dj
Do not kill the dj. You got it. Let's go
Get over there get over there. Jesus
Hey you you're not supposed to
Peepo dance fool peepo dance fool
Oh, I again I blended him in the background. Jesus. What the fuck am I doing?
Hang up shit that guy's a gun down there. Fuck shoot. Can't see me. Can't see me. Can't see me go. Yeah
That should work. I left a few hours ago. He's still in the nightclub. Yeah, this place is fucking hard, man
This is hard as shit
Oh, that would have been cool. I missed it though
Oh look at this
What remember how much trouble this gave me before I don't know why it is it just does
Whoa, is it dead? I almost thought it wasn't dead. What the fuck
Before omega lol
All right. Here we go. Hang up
Fuck you. Hang up talk to this person only talk don't kill
It's me
Are you real?
I'm here to kill you
Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. You are real. Okay, man. Stay cool
I'll give it all back
Uh, what are you talking about? If the shit I found was yours. Oh god
Uh, what did you find?
Your shit man the drugs. I only tried it once at a party
Mm-hmm. It was wild
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
Uh, tell me where it is
All right. So
I mean it's still in your storage unit
Complete the level after this
After you've spoken with the dj
There's another session during the session you need to refuse your medicine to do this simply choose the dialogue about the drug
Eventually, you'll be able to refuse the drug and the psychiatrist will tell you to get out of his office
Okay during you need to refuse to do the simply choose the dialogue about the drug
Your boys are dead
Oh fuck don't hurt me. Look man. Let's make a deal. I'll cut you some of the drugs if you let me go
I'll do anything
Uh, give me the give me the drugs and you can go
Cool. Cool. Cool. Do it. Okay
During the session you need to refuse your medicine. Just choose the choose the option about the drug
Somebody else coming from behind, right?
Yep time to go our employees are not aware of the circumstances behind electro heads death
I am you have been negligent in your duties
Future deviants will be met with strict discipline. Okay, let's skip all this shit
I mean, this is not shit, you know, just be mean
Why am I playing this still because i'm trying i'm trying to see the last bit of it
There's a secret boss that I want to see and I have to do two more small things that I can do it
Under the bed, right under the sofa
Found it. I just want to see the secret boss. See I knew it you had him all along. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Uh, okay, cool
She doesn't deserve this
Well, this is a different timeline. It's not even the right. This is a different timeline. Don't worry
So now after this we have to skip
We have to kill all the officers during the prison level which okay that's
And then that's it. You're gonna play five nights at freddy's. No, how about five nights at freddy's vr
To ask about the drug and then refuse the medicine take a seat. All right ask about the drug
I'm not so sure I share the sentiment
Maybe you could answer a few questions for me. When did you start using a gun? I don't use a gun
Answer my questions first
That's not how this works. You're going to tell me what happened last night at the club neon
Uh, I spoke to electro head. I specifically told you not to do that
All right. Well now we've talked about the drug
Don't refuse the medicine. He told me about a drug that sounds like mine
It very likely may have been and that is the purpose of our mission to ensure that this drug does not reach the wrong hands
Why didn't you want me to know about the drug? What do you mean? I ruined it
It says it says refuse the drug
What are you guys talking about as a veteran?
You should understand that you're not privy to the full details of our missions. My powers come from a drug
Your swordsmanship your combat I can even know those are the products of years of training
Your precognition your perception of time. Yes, these are side effects of the drug
That is why we cannot allow others to abuse it
Uh, I don't want that. I don't want this
It's a shame that you can't grasp the power you've been bestowed
But if that's how you truly feel we can taper you off once this mission is complete
I don't want the drug anymore enough. It's time for your treatment. Sit still. No, do you understand the gift you've been given?
You are invincible
So whatever comes from a drug you hold the power of a god you see the future. How dare you squander this gift now sit
No, leave don't come back until you're capable of doing your damn job
Oh, and one last thing. Are you aware that the media has taken to calling you the dragon?
Do you know what the media should be calling you fucking nothing exercise some goddamn discretion and stop drawing attention to us
Now get out of here you stinking idiot. I'm a pretty good actor. I could fucking act
Okay, kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill. Well, this is uh different
All right. So now
Kill all the police officers during the prison mission, which is this one? So i'll just hang up fuck off
Okay, all right everyone. I have to kill everything everyone has time and then this is it. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
Yeah, we don't need to see that
Just kill everything everybody all things
Full moon tonight. Uh-huh. Oh no, he's dead
Here we go. Uh-huh. Is that all? That's it, right? That should work two three four. That's it video feed lost
What? Yeah, nobody else wait anybody in this room. He's bloodthirsty. He's absolutely fucking bloodthirsty
In the game, all right, they're all dead, right? I think that's it
Okay
This results in you directly obeying the orders. Okay. The final thing is tell the psychiatrist fuck you during the chinatown session
After you've done all the steps above make your way to the chinatown mission
And start the session with the psychiatrist tell him to fuck you when the option presents itself
Here we go. Should I be?
All right, so I can get out right?
Okay kill I don't have to all right chinatown mission. Is that the next one or what? What is this?
Picked up prototype key. I hate doing this but I have to yeah, i've already seen this bro, bro, bro, dude
Um
Chinatown mission and then say fuck you
You don't have to be mean
Well, if i'm if i'm if i'm not mean to the girl then we have to sit through like 10 times more dialogue
Oh, he's got the pliers
I can't believe this blue shit is his hair. Oh, I thought it was a helmet
Is it really?
I guess it is because the sideburns. Okay. All right. I think it's time. Here we go. Chinatown is in five levels
All right. Well, i'll just leave and then go to chinatown and do it
See if it I see if it works. Okay, six days remain chinatown. Yeah. All right, let's go back main menu
Continue and then go to the chinatown mission
Chinatown say fuck you
Here it is. All right
Get the better sword
Does it
Term a new sword. Can I get I get a new sword?
Go to the lab for the new sword. I don't know that exists
Government lab has a different sword
Do it after do it after you do now do now do this now
You got a key for it. I'm doing this note
What the hell were you doing last night?
Fuck you
There are two dozen wrecked motorcycles
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, he's dead. I know
He was found with a goddamn bullet in his head. It's also all over the news. You can't keep
Do you understand the discretion of our mission?
Look at me. This is an elaborate advertisement for your services
While our supervisor saw and they were
Fuck you
Ah, fuck you too
I guess I don't look so great now. Wait, what it doesn't even compare to what's in store for you
What are you talking about? Did I miss the prompt?
You really don't know
No, I cut back to the I cut back don't I?
No, it's fuck you to the psychiatrist. Yeah, okay
That real dragon. Oh, he gave me the drugs. Fuck you
Get your dossier in the way out and act like a goddamn professional
The name almost would be humorous if your recklessness didn't jeopardize our lives
I'm not the dragon
How preposterous of me? Of course, you're not responsible for the rash highly visible third district murders. Yeah. Yeah
When do I get to say fuck you?
Not all of them. I met the dragon
When on the highway? I was not expecting that. Uh-huh. Who is this person?
Uh, he was inhuman inhumanly fast
Did I miss my opportunity to do it? No, he just was the dragon. He was after the people he
He just was the no he just just that he was the dragon
I see very good. Very good. Okay. Okay
I had other plans, but who is he?
Clearly a menace. Yeah, you were the treading on very thin ice
fuck
you
Well, get the hell out of here now
Did it work? Did I do it stay the hell away from there? I think I did it
Okay
If you've done all the steps up to this point, you could see if you did it
Go to the psychiatrist session in the bunker
During this session the psychiatrist will tell you something different
He will say i'm almost disappointed that you're still alive after what you put me through if you get this dialogue
It means you have done it
Okay, so
We just to complete this
Just go to bunker part two. Okay, if I go to the lab, will it fuck it up?
Get the sword. Where's the sword? So if I go here and then here it's not gonna screw it all up
Go get the cool sword. All right, i'll get the cool sword. Whatever. Okay, this opened pick the prism sword
The world is your canvas and blood is the paint
Okay
What's this? I have two keys, right?
Uh the claymore prototype giant cleaver that crushes bullets and defenses
I want the big one. I want the huge one. Yeah, give me this thing
I have it on right? All right. Yeah, I want the big one
Big sword, let's go bunker part two
During this interaction you can get two possible outcomes the outcome the outcome we will get is a boss fight
When you walk towards the psychiatrist, he will say
You're making a very big mistake
bunker part two
spoilers
Here it is
you
Do you understand what you've done?
You're making I
Haven't been able to reach my daughter all day my phone. Why did I still have this?
I I can explain this they won't come after me. I had nothing to do with this shit
No, i'm leaving. I need to you knew my dreams were real you motherfucker
What the fuck are you doing?
Get the hell out of my office you goddamn junkie. What are you gonna do? You're in withdrawal get away from me
I fucked it up. You need to finish the first level after hanging up
Go back
And do it from bunker one
You have to start take it from the top. No
No, I don't so what I did
I think I have to go to the first part. Just do the first level again
He's doing no, I don't just redo one bunker part one
Because it says if you don't know the steps you can see
During the session go to the bunker session with the psychiatrist
He will say i'm almost disappointed that you're still alive
Please come in. Okay, so you're still alive. I was beginning to wonder not that it matters because you've gone completely out of control
Failing to kill your target murdering an entire police squad. I'm surprised you even decided to come back. That's not working
You fucking idiot. Yeah, this is your last chance
I don't think it worked
Maybe you can't do it out of order. How do you know about that? I've killed him
Need factory part one. I already didn't I did factory part one. I hung up on him. I started from the very beginning
Did the lab fuck it up?
You can do it out of order. Yeah, apparently I can get a cool sword though
Okay, um, is this it? Can I do this? It's correct. Don't listen to chat
You have to finish the level after hanging up on the factory
You need 15 hang ups just finish the first level
Go to the speed run mode and select the secret. Are you fucking kidding me?
It's not in here. You need to play you need to
No, so it's not in here
Cancel why are you listening to everyone in chat? I mean I have the source up here and I did everything and it didn't do anything
step one
You have to okay. I'm gonna try to play through the factory level
Hang up on him a bunch of times and then finish the factory level
That makes sense. Right? Did you get an achievement after hanging up? I did
I did get the achievement, but maybe I have to finish the mission. I was doing it. Yeah, I had it right
That guy was wrong. The lab didn't fuck it up. You're fine. Well, how come it didn't work?
Did I do the factory therapy? The guide says I don't have to do it
Well, let's just let's just see what happens when I finish the mission see if I can do it
Boss doesn't exist. Hang up
four
five
six
seven nine
11 13
15 there you go. It's 15 times
I've done it
Okay. Hello
Okay
All right. Get on with it. Get on with it
Get on with it. Get on with it. Get on with it
Interrupt after this mission interrupt the psychiatrist and ask for medicine until he gives it to you
I got just to beat the mission. What do you mean? I didn't how did I ruin it?
All right, I have to actually beat this mission because there's something after it too. Okay, let's see if that works
There's a lot. There's a last time. I'm gonna try it. Let's go. Let's go
Let's go if you're wondering what the hell is he doing. Why is he skipping everything?
Why is this guy such a stupid idiot dumb fucking idiot person?
Pet cat. Yep
Well, it's because I'm trying to I beat the game already. I'm just trying to get the secret boss
so after the mission
Just interrupt and ask for the medicine and that should do it and I should be able to go to the second bunker
Like what an embarrassment worst
Goodbye
Hey, oh
We need to go now
All right, I think you're right. I think I can stand hold on
Oh, I started to think I wouldn't make it. Thank you. Go go go go go go go go go go go go go go
Mind the lasers
Watch out for those lasers. All right to say give me my medicine now
Drink the tea go to sleep
And hopefully this is gonna be it
Because the text that I didn't get I feel like I did though
Yeah
Here we go. Okay
So just interrupt them until I get my medicine just say give me my medicine bad behavior. Yeah. Yeah, let's begin the session
I'm just here for the medicine. Give me the medicine. Let's wear it out. Just give it to me
Okay, that should do it. Let's go to bunker two now. We're gonna get some winks soon
Possibly, okay bunker two. Let's hope it works because I did everything else on this list
Go to the chinatown mission and start the session with the psychiatrist and then say fuck you
No, wait, wait, wait. Whoa. Whoa. No, no, no, no. No, I did the bunker two. Wait. No, where am I?
Access, okay bunker two. Yes
You
Do you understand what you've done?
I
I haven't been able to reach my daughter
I can't explain this they won't come after me
Nothing to do. You lied to me. I don't think this happened. No, i'm leaving. I need to leave. There's no time
Should I just let him go?
You lied to me
What the fuck are you talking about?
um
Get the hell out of my office. No, it didn't work. You're making a very big mistake. Oh
There it is
All right, let's go
You idiot you fucking idiot. Did you really think chronos was the only drug government developed for the war?
I should have done this a long time ago
Let's go
I will suffer you no more
Here we go time for the secret final boss of the video game
Let's go
Hit the hands. I just gotta hit the hands. He's getting mad. Oh, he just blew up my fucking head
He just exploded my head
Oh fuck they come out at different times
Good. Okay. Shit. How many times do I have to do it? Here we go. Oh fuck
Oh my god. Okay. He's spent
All right. What am I doing? He just wait
Fuck, okay
Jesus
The big sword is slow
Is that what's going on?
I'm, all right. Fuck you. Yeah, I hit him
Jesus
Oh, jesus christ
I you just I have to just dodge that shit. Yeah, I can't you can't hit more than once
Impossible
I have to dodge
motherfucker
Aha
It's so quick
You have to like pick a direction and dive through it. I think
Here we go
Jesus christ, what happened if I don't
Oh my god
I'm dead. Oh, they have to hit the right colors
He's turning into a mutant
There it comes
This thing
I don't know how to swing
I'm dead
I can't okay. I have to dodge it only dog
There he is. Holy shit
He's coming up with a knife
Oh, man
God damn it. It's too much
Oh
It gets faster. Oh, come on
Back to three. Hopefully that's not correct. All right, this one. Oh shit. Oh fuck. I fucked it up
holy
Try stabbing the eye. Hold on. Can I hit him in the eye with that?
Oh, come on. I thought it was coming from the left stabbing the eye didn't work. Oh my god
I feel like i'm on drugs right now
Fuck dodge
I don't get that one. I really don't
I like
Oh my god, it's different every time too. Fuck me
All right. How many times do I have to hit him without getting hit?
Probably three or four
That one seriously, I have no idea how to avoid that. It's the only one I can't do
one
Fuck you game
They should have to shoot these stupid things give me a break get out of here
Come on. All right, one more one more one more one more
I'm trying just to jump over the hitboxes five times bigger than my body
But that that one is unfucking bearable
That's I like that one. I'm gonna lose to that every fucking time
You gotta be fucking kidding me. Fuck you get out of my way again with this shit
Where's it going? Which needles dropping first?
It's two. All right. Come on
You gotta be kid. I can't fucking believe I just died to that
I just like I just got so fucking cocky for no reason
We're gonna be for like three hours
All right, fuck off. Stay on the right side
I hate this
Oh fucked I miss it's okay. Stay here
Come on
You guys fuck me fuck me
Fucking rng shove it up my fucking mouth
Can I get the guy to pop up please for the love of god?
We're gonna have to do this shit like four times in a row. Hey. Hey, I did it. What I did it
How did I do it? What that was not I didn't do it. Did I do it was three? Oh shit. I did it
Hey
All right
We got a key card
All right. That was fucking really crazy
That sucked desk carlos delivery. Yeah, I think I already did this right
Dossier is me
Mm-hmm. All right, let's go back to the lab
I didn't think I was gonna be able to do that one. Wait, what do you mean? No, what's up?
I didn't do it do hard mode secret boss. I am not qualified to do that
I'll tell you right now. I'm probably not qualified to do that
It may be some other gamers here or that you've seen in the past that are probably very qualified. I'm not qualified for that
Okay, let's go back to the lab. Did you say Joel was doing jump king? Are you serious?
Are you serious? Yes. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah. Oh, how's it going? How's that going? Let's see. Let's see how that's going. How's that going?
I'm i'm sure it's some some local issue or whatever
He just fell to the bottom. Does the game run better if i'm not like having it in a window like this?
Yeah, he uh, he's at the first screen. He's literally at the first screen. I can't okay. I'm gonna go watch joel. I'm leaving
See you tomorrow
I have to watch this. You know what I mean? Like I have to watch this. I have to
uh, all right
I'm gonna go get like a pizza and watch this. I can't wait. I I get to be on the end
I get to be on this end on your end and I get to walk. Oh, I can't wait. I'll see you tomorrow
Uh, that's pretty much all I want. That was katana zero. Pretty good game
Pretty good game, you know
Thanks for watching everybody. What about the key card? Wait, wait, wait. I didn't put it in. Oh shit. Um,
I don't think I have it. What about the bits? No, no, we'll do the bits. We'll do the bits
I'm just saying like this is the end of the stream. Yeah, it's been about six hours
All right. Well, this was highly recommended and I could see why it was very fun
Story was kind of all over the place hard to follow sometimes but it's still cool
Like the combat i'd like to see more
of just
Playing the game
I wish that all right. So the game is about what four and a half hours or so. I wish it was uh,
I wish it was more just fight fight fight fight fight fight and I don't know maybe i'm asking too much
Swing with this prism sword. I mean that's that's pretty cool
That speed run mode. Well, I mean I would I guess I wanted more video game
I mean, but that usually typically means I liked it. I like the mechanics
Maybe the dlc will add a bunch more. We'll see
Yeah, we'll see you tomorrow. I'm going to start the uh, playstation 2
playstation 2
uh
Lord of the rings fellowship of the ring
I'm only playing it because one person said that they guaranteed I would not be the first level
So we're going to prove one person wrong. That's the plan tomorrow. Thanks for watching. Uh, definitely worst chat experience of of
2015 through 2020
I hope you guys are proud of that full moon chat. All right, that's pretty good pretty good day
Agreed agreed pepe heads
It got better
Oh mega lol, you're welcome
My chat experience. Oh, yeah, like what the fuck is happening? All right, we'll see you tomorrow
Take care of yourselves. I'm gonna tweak some audio stuff. So people don't like fucking try to like murder me
For having a different microphone setup
People people clawing at my door. All right, we're gonna raid joel. I want to watch jump king
Thanks for watching guys. See you tomorrow
For lord of the rings
Let's do the bits. We're gonna raid joel. Uh, if you want to go watch joel, he's already there doing it
But we're gonna do the bits. Thanks for watching guys. Very cool
Hey, yeah
Uh, I need to exit the game
Yeah, so that concludes, uh, jeremy plays a game that came out in the last at least six months
Uh, now let's go back to playing games that came out 15 years ago. Yeah, sounds about right
So I got my quota for game that released in a year like within the last year
But all right was that new katana zero came out like this year, right last year
Let's go back
to the hype train
The hype I can't believe this shit man. It's gonna happen every day
Bring the radio voice back for the bits. No, i'm not i'm not using comedy bits
Remember, what's the device that records your voice a microphone? Hey gnarly. Thanks for the 250 hype time
I'm giving jeff bezos money to bless this katana zero stream hype pug champ
Cougar stable. Thanks for the thousand bits have fun with katana zero. It's a great game. It was good
I did enjoy it. I enjoyed my time a little short. It was a little short, but you know, you it it
I just wanted more I wanted and then maybe if the game was like
If the game was like another hour or two long if it was like a five to six hour long game rather than like
A four hour game, you know, I um, I i'd be more happy about it. You know what i'm saying?
So but I guess it was it. It's it's a little short
If they're doing free dlc, maybe we'll come back to it and give you a exact joel's talking shit about me
That's all right. We'll watch him play jump king and fail and he has to be he has to win
What was my jump king score?
Keeping in mind when you watch joel
The game was made by like four people. I mean, it's a great game. I just wish it was longer
I'm not saying the game's bad because it's short. I'm just saying I wish game was longer because I liked game
Potion dweller. Thanks for the 250. Jeremiah. I must say you need a little work on the mic adjustments
You sound like sick. You sound a little sick on it
We're gonna get a shitload
Of we're gonna get a shitload of fuck your mic settings for it. It's coming in these bits. I know it
Uh, thank you though. Thank you. I a elliot for the five community subs jamie five community subs
Catbag, thanks for 500 bits
Raid plays raid him after yeah, i'm gonna i'm gonna raid joel. I want to watch him play. He's getting a grandpa voice
But thank you catbag for the fire but help the hype train complete compels me to spend bits. I can't control my mouse cursor
Thank you though ipod bat. Thanks for 250 day two of falling for the hype
Yeah, I I might have to adjust it. I don't know if I want to have that happen every single day
If that turns on every day, it's like hey, welcome to the extreme guys
Uh, here's the hype train. Where's the 200 gifted subs?
I think i'm maybe i'll adjust it
I don't know. I don't want to put like pressure on people that have to level up the hype train
But let me see if I can do anything about it
Joel's chat is making you think you're raiding. I mean not immediately but I will in a minute
Caj tech, thanks for a thousand bits
firebird 500 bits
Uh, not a lot of messages on these because it was just to fill up the hype meter, which thank you guys. It's fucking ridiculous
All I can say is thanks
twitchy, thanks for the
678 bits
Thank you
Jamie again 500 bits hype bits for the hype train every if every day is a hype train then the hype train loses its hype train value
Maybe I can go in and mess with the settings
You know if you eat pizza every day, you're not going to want people. That's not true
I would eat pizza every single day forget don't listen to anything i'm saying
Uh millhouse is a pepe. Thanks for the 400 bits
Part of that hype train there your boy. Thanks for the five community subs
Priz, thanks for five community subs fisty mart. Thanks for five community subs ab joe five
Back to back to back there. Thank you
Cold rush 500 bits go back to the old mic. It's it's not an it's the same mic
It's a new audio interface and we're not going back
Because this thing was very expensive
And I've it took me like a few hours to set it up. The other one is going away
Uh, i'm gonna have i'm going to adjust it
Everybody's lost the damn mind
Now you control discord calls
Oh, yay
Yes
Hey now
Gotta be so funny if I did that in like a fucking funny somebody would go to somebody's discord and fucking do that
I can't hear anything you're saying
Joel is not well, let's find out
I'm gonna i'm tweaking the settings. I'll fix it
I'm gonna get it sound a little better. Oh, man. I don't we'll we'll see i'm gonna maybe i'll just tweaks
You know, that's all it is some tweaks. That's it
Crispy bacon. Thanks for the 500 bits. They say hyped. Thank you
Noza, thanks nozo and noza. Thanks for the five community subs
Jason thanks for 300 bits. Hey german today's my 20th birthday. Happy fucking birthday
I hope to see you at the boomer convention coming up this year now that I am one of your kind you're 20
You are a baby or you could be a break 20
You can't even legally drink alcohol yet. What do you mean old? You're a baby
You got that's that's very young. You've got you're so young and so full of energy. I'm happy. Thank you though. Happy birthday
We drink at 18 dumbass
Well, I don't know where you live
You're you're a piece of text on the internet. It doesn't say your country next to your name
laughing in german
Maybe it should
I don't
Research your viewers. I what am I supposed to forget about a census out
Flutters, thanks for the nine community subs. Appreciate it. Thank you flutters
We had five thousand bits fifty dollars from kaj tech more money from kaj tech. No message. Just a bunch of fucking money
Louie the cashew 500 bits. Thank you louie
bulbous swag desu
1500 bits. Thank you for the 15 dollars
How much do we need to donate for you to go back to your old mic nothing it'll no amount
Even if you gave 200 million dollars, I wouldn't go back. Thank you for the 1500 bits, though
Thank you door cube for the 1500 bits door cube 15 dollars from door cube. Appreciate it big bits today
Or at least big for me
Because it's my birthday since I forgot to send you a sappy message for new years. I'll say it now
This past year had my lowest lows. I felt like a directionist dog shit
Directionless dog shit, but because of you I met some absolutely excellent people and learned to be more loving and accepting
So despite my hardships, I feel at the start of this new year the most hopeful i've ever been. Thank you. Happy birthday
Here's the 2020 new year grab it get it
2020 happy fucking birthday door cube glad you met some people that you can
Spend time with we're social animals for god's sakes. Why do you think I like to do this so much?
I love talking. I love talking to people. I love talking to you guys
I love just being around people with social animals. What an egomaniac. Oh, i'm saying no, whatever
You turned up the compress. I didn't touch anything. The compression is at zero
The compression is now on
This is what it this is what it was at the beginning of the stream
This is what it sounded like
This is the settings for the stream. It was that was at zero
This is now compression
Yeah
This is without the compression. This is where we were. This is where this is where the stream has been this whole time
It's right here. Here we are. The compression is bad
Well ready
This is listen to this
This is with literally zero everything
Zero zero zero everything zero
This is what it used to sound like there. It is
It's perfect
It sounds the same
It probably does
Anyways, let's keep going. I still can't hear it
Go eat some food and drink some water. I drink water. What are we talking about? Cut your losses and type to us
Get a gate for the background noise. There is a gate on right now as you can see there is a gate. It's too aggressive
Well, uh, it i'll have to play with it, but regardless
Let's continue
Read the comments of what the black and white video?
No, no, I don't fuck. I don't care about this video
Uh, here here we go
Uh, but door cube seriously
Thanks a lot
I really appreciate it
Does this mean less rooms? It kind of does mean less rooms
Thank you door cube though. Seriously squiggity swanky. Thanks for the 250
I don't know what you did, but this is how I feel about your uh new audio
Okay
Whatever. Thank you
Hi hero hiro titan. Thanks for the thousand bits go back peppa hands old germa would have gone back to the old mic
I don't even know how I could even explain this
You guys just don't understand it. This is like just this is
Oh, I can't even i'm not even gonna address it anymore. What's this all about sound? I literally can't tell the difference
um, well
What what you're describing is
Maybe 100 people
Were annoyed that I changed my microphone setup and then 4 000 just started trolling the stream
so
That's what happened
It's pretty much what happened
It was a dark day for germa chat
It sounded bad at first and but but we corrected it and it got a little better and it got better and it's going to
Continue to get better as I figure out how all these settings
We are a proud people today was a success
Oh, okay. Thank you for the thousand bits though
A B joe thanks for 5 000 bits 50 bucks from ab joe glad to see you playing this game germa
Thanks for the fucking huge amount of money. That's a ridiculous amount of money to give anybody
I just got it myself a bit ago and I loved it people keep telling you that you always help them through hard times
And I want you to know that from the bottom of my heart. I appreciate each and every stream you do
even the bugleberry ones
really
wait even
even bugleberry
Get him out of here get bugleberry out of here fuck that guy he sucks
I
Hope bugleberry has a fucking accident. Oh my god
What's wrong with you guys?
Jesus christ
fatal accident
Okay. Anyways
Jesus
You guys we need to like get some vitamins in you guys you guys you guys have gone hollow today
Please don't ever think you don't deserve this or our love you deserve all of it and more ps
Ask italics to help with your mic problems. He always sounds real crisp
uh
the thing about audio is
If you have a different audio set up than somebody it takes a lot more
Joel quit jump king. Did he?
Well, the thing is italics has a bunch of compression
The thing about that everyone said they said they hated compression turn off the compressor. I hate compressor. I hate how you sound turn it off
What what am I hearing right now?
hearing right now
Fuck you guys
Oh, i'm gonna go eat a goddamn pizza. All right. Anyways, thanks you. Thanks you stremer. Thanks you
You even like the blue. I you know, I love bugleberry. So he's sticking around cvfd. Thanks for the thousand bits
Jerry will hope you know that it doesn't matter what you sound like your friends will always watch you whether you have a crusty
Mark of the best mic in the world
Keep up the great content
You guys we're gonna compare audio and you guys are gonna see just how shitty the mic used to sound
I'm gonna pull clips
And you're gonna see just how bad the mic was before
He's right, you know
All right. Anyways, duh
Daw son dlc. Thanks for the 1500 bits
Favorite streamer of all time. Thank you for the years of laughs. Also, the audio is kind of shit. It's not a meme
a b c d
e f g
h i j k elemental p q r s t u v
W w w w x clip that I want to fucking listen
I want to listen to that and i'm gonna give you another one with the other mic the same mic if it's different audio
Let's see turn this shit off. I want to hear it. That's not it. Thank you
a k elemental p q r s t u v
w w w w x clip that I want to fucking listen
I want to listen to that and i'm gonna give you another one with the other mic the same mic if it's different audio
Let's see
Okay
Now the only difference is there's not a
In the background that's the only difference I didn't have any a gate or anything before
That noise helps me sleep
Hey
Thank you ladies and gentlemen. Thank you
Thank you section bd for the 500 bits small token of my gratitude for the years of laughter. Thank you
Thank you for the 500 bits and thanks for being here for this many years
I really appreciate it
Oh
An asshole
Hey nondescript civilian. Thanks for the 10 community subs. Appreciate that
Hey zake. Thanks for the 250. What's your favorite song by mike row phone ban that person?
Uh nondescript though. That's 10 community subs. Thanks for the fucking money drop really appreciate it
All you guys for all the huge amount of subs sticks renegade. Thanks for 250 draw my fursona or do an oil change on stream
Okay
Mike row phone god damn it
Thanks a lot guys. I'll see you tomorrow
I'm not done. Thanks for the hype train at the beginning
You guys are fantastic
I keep thinking about being naked in the microphone
Give us the lord of the ring stream. That's i'm streaming tomorrow
What the heck mate?
Phinney, thanks for the 250. Hey, I just came here and I can hear by the sound of your voice that you must really be sick
Like the sickest voice i've ever heard get well soon
Uh topac 250. Hey, I just came here to say the sound of your voice
You sound sick, but this same is exact same comment
Phinney, thanks for the 250. What is hard bass turn my 95. Well, here you go
Hard bass school
All right, you asked what hard bass was like four hours ago. I know
You didn't even get to the drop
All right
All right, nice
Hey red walrus, thanks for the
700 bits
Dude, you just got corned so bad. It's the newest thing on twitch laugh my ass off. Also play warhammer space marine
You got corned man. Got him with the corn. He's got you got corned
Shadows one disciple. Thanks for the 250. Hey jeremy
I just want to say how thankful I am for your streams as they really helped me relax after a hard winter day
I work for on a farm
in wisconsin
as a hay
You pick up hay and things can get real rough in the cold months. Also. I told my step brother to eat tahini paste
Um, don't eat tahini paste
Put it on stuff. Put it in hummus. Don't put it on your sandwiches and eat it. It's bad advice
Very bad. Don't do that terrible advice
Uh, don't do that eat a banana instead. Hey white fox. Thanks 300 bits
I typically don't do politics at all
What does this have to do with politics? But recently I lost my job and so i've had a lot of time to sit around and read
Honestly, when I allow myself to step outside the happy entertainment bubble I enjoy from people like you and shows on netflix
It's fucking horrifying
Oh, I see don't mean to be too heavy
But do you think it's better to stay ignorant of world politics or to stay up to date and think about things?
I think too. Here's the thing
We live in a crazy fucking world
and
You have to at least be somewhat informed of what's going on around you
but at the end of the day
Everyone's got a life to live. You know what I mean? You got a life to live
It's a balance of both. Yeah, it is
You you can be informed and you can be you can have positions and you can stay up to date on world politics and and your
country's politics
But you also have to you got to do you
And there are a lot of things to care about but you don't it's it's like my
It's like my my grandpa my mother and my grandmother used to say
If you keep the news on all the time
You just if you just have cnn on in the background, right?
It's just you're constantly going to get a barrage of things that you might not want to listen to
you as a constant it's just constant barrage of the things that are just
At some point you you almost get like desensitized to how all the noise
And all the all the bad news and all the bad things that might be happening and you have to you do have to pay attention
but to an extent
and even on like social media
Constantly seeing things that people have to say and what's your position on this? How do you feel about that?
How do you feel about that? It's like I've I got I don't know
This thing is happening. This thing is happening. This thing's happening over here and it's just like fuck
And then you don't want to feel like you're not caring about that. You're not paying attention
You know, because if you aren't informed on something that somebody asks you i'm
And for me personally if I don't know about a topic really if I don't know about something
I I don't I can't really i'm not going to fight anybody over something. I'm not going to tell anybody something
I'm not going to tell them that somebody if I don't know
You know if i'm not up to date
So I tend I tend to steer away from political talk because for a lot. I mean
I don't really
Involve myself too much in it
And I don't want to be one of those people that when a topic of issue like I have my own personal beliefs, right?
But I don't I don't want to I don't share them on stream. I don't put them on stream
I don't talk about them because
This is this place here
If you're talking strictly politics
You know like republican democrat. How do you feel libertarian? Oh, i'm
I'm not i'm
progressive, right
This is not the place where I want to have those conversations
I want to hang out and have a good time and play games do video stuff
so
From my positions
I do have them but this place right here
German 985
I don't engage on it
And I know there there are some streamers that do and people do and if that's what they want to do
That's what they want to do fucking go out and vote this year. Jesus christ
The thing is like politically I don't like
You guys probably already know
All of my positions i've talked about half of them already on stream. I got like shitfaced and talked about it before
You guys already know like all my that's what I mean. Like I
And there's a lot of things that I don't know about so i'm not going to present things that oh well
Here's what I have to say about that motherfucker
Uh germa that that didn't even happen
What?
What you're saying is not real. You you have no idea what you're talking about. Oh, I don't you're right. Oh fuck
What do I do? Uh, what do I do? How should I double down or should I uh, delete my fucking twitch account?
What do I do here? Okay. Um
Let's go
Go all in backtrack and bury. Yeah
Stay informed, but don't let it consume you
hopefully that's pretty clear because
politics can consume you
and
You can't even have
Like discussions about anything or talk about anything something that you know what I mean
Don't let it consume you be informed, but don't be consumed and there we go. That's my position
All right. I voted
in the last in the last primary
Okay
All right
Wait, hold on. Wait a second. Wait, hold on. Does this work?
I voted for did it work?
Is this supposed to go?
Did it work? I voted for in the last god damn
Oh
Is it working? Why is it even on here? What's the point of that? It's its own button
This actually it's uh, there's a swear button on here
Does that actually have to be its own button? I ain't ever gonna press that ever again clip this not pressing it ever again
Anyways
Let's move on. Thank you white fucks for the 300 bits
Thank you gnarly for the 250 glad you ended up playing one of the two games. I endlessly begged you to play
Yeah, there are a lot of people told me to play it. I'm happy you liked it
This is one of my favorite games of last year. Thanks for the stream. Jericho. Hey, thanks
Hey cougar stable. Thanks for the 400 bits
The final part of that that final part of the club chapter was clean
You're doing great. Keep it up
And then they say play ai
the somnum files
Oh, let me see what it sounds like
Wait, hold on. Wait a second. Wait, hold on. Does this work? I voted for did it work? Oh, it does work
It's supposed to go
Did it work voted for in the last god damn?
Oh
Oh, it actually cuts off the mic too. I didn't know that
That's pretty cool. It actually it mutes the mic
I thought it was just doing it over the audio. Okay
Oh, that's pretty cool
Go xlr pretty good piece of equipment so far
Pretty cool. Just do that whenever you sneeze
Hey cougar stable. Thanks for 300 bits. Nice work on the psychiatrist. It was hard
I was starting to get really upset about that
What happened to turtles of time? It's illegal
acute
pneumonia
pneumo
snorlax
Thanks for the 500 bits
Germa has a 21 year old on dialysis awaiting transplant. I just want to say thank you
These dreams made my tough day so much easier. Thanks for the laughs
Let's hope a uh a donor comes through soon
Thank you so much for the 500 bits
And if you already have one lined up good, very very good
Get well soon
Much luck to you
Thank you for being here and thanks for the 500 bits
We're all pushing for you. We're all rooting for you anybody that's part of this fucking community
You got 10 000 of our percent. So seriously
Thank you for the 500 bits
We had hage gun for the 300 bits if you like this
You can check out deadbolt similar to play style also really good soundtrack
Are we over 11k subs yet? We're not
But we are very very close
We are very far. Uh, it's close
Don't forget to save your audio profile that you've made changes
All right. Yeah, okay. No
No memes aside and no joking around and no like no bait the guy to fucking have a meltdown on stream
It how is how does this sound for real? Like give me it real? How does it sound? Sounds?
It sounds pretty good, right? It sounds okay good. Yeah, I mean
Give me give me the real you did sound fine. You sounded great. You sounded fine
Okay, sounds like you're three feet behind me with a gun to my back
All right. All right. Okay. I'm just making you guys it's hard to determine sometimes
Yes, the uh in the beginning of the stream it was like fucking crazy
Uh
All right, sometimes I don't even know what to think i'm like i'm trying i'm like, oh, okay, we're gonna move on
Earlier it was worse than the basement mic stream. What no way it can't be
Man up with icy hot. Thanks for the 300 bits. Thanks for the stream. Have a good night you two
Hallelu thanks for the 250 always love the retro game streams when you do them
I think you mentioned not wanting to do draw. I must have dragon rompa dungeon keeper once
And was wondering why?
I always enjoy watching my favorite wow reference streamer happy pizza times. Thank you. Hallelu
I think the reason why I don't want to do dungeon keeper is because
It may be just a tad it might be a little too slow
For me playing it on stream that game takes a lot to get going doesn't it if I remember correctly
Black and white wasn't but yeah, but black but I remember I i've never I don't have very many memories
of
Dungeon keeper these idiots watched you play nancy drew
Yeah, uh, yeah, but we
Look if you but we can't hold nancy drew to the utmost lowest barometer
Because everything is more exciting than nancy drew
everything
so
Yeah, that's true dungeon keeper is more exciting than nancy drew but there's
Every game is
And the and they there was the drew crew was created
And now they they'll defend
It to the death
Right. So if they watch that they'll watch anything. Yeah. All right. We'll play dungeon keeper put it on the list
I have no defense and that's the problem when you do though when you go all the way from from like zero to 100
Nancy drew is zero and like
I don't know like sakiro is a fucking hundred, right?
Everything in between is now on on the table. Wait, hold on. You're not gonna play number munchers
You played nancy drew for two streams straight fuck you're right. You are you're right
Dude, you think that like hotline miami 2 is too much for you. You did sakiro on stream dude. That game is ridiculous
Fuck you. Okay, you're right
That pretty much means any game that could be boring is on the table and any game that might be too hard for me is
on the table
Cool, all right do putt putt. Yeah, that sounds good. I already did I played all putt putts at the same time
Hey hot gamer. Thanks for the fire for the bits. Well germa
Watching you play this game is questioning my gamer skills considering it took me 20 hours to beat
And some sections you got through in one try took me like 10 plus
You truly are a god gamer
I am going to toot my own horn here and say
I'm terrible with spatial awareness
I'm really really awful with
complex systems
I don't do well under
long term pressure
but short term
twitch skills
Short term and I mean like less than a couple minutes
I'm pretty good
at fast reflex like
patterns
It's i'm i'm okay with those
If I really really really wanted to and I dumped tons of time into it
I would probably be one of those people that was able
to potentially
speed run a game like this
I just don't have the
attention span
To do it. I just do not I
Can't give it the time that it needs to do
Everything else though. Uh, I'm almost completely worthless
in a gaming skill sense
Sometimes I turn it on but I know that I have I know that I have some skill
You just don't have the patience for it. No, I don't I really don't like if I have to read a section of a book
To learn how to do a spell and then I have to do something to cast the spell and then I have to talk
To three people on the way to the next quest
I'm gonna walk backwards off a cliff
Accidentally, that's just gonna happen has jerma played a toho game yet
No, I actually was talking about this the other day though. Not on stream
I think I would be really good at the bullet hell shit. I really do
There are a few bullet classic bullet hell games that I think I would want to play
Ikaruga is on that list
And I know absolutely nothing about like the toho games
But I know that they are the bullet hell games, right?
But anyways, I digress. Thank you hot gamer
Hey, everyone's good at something
Everybody's good at something it took me 20 hours to beat this game
But what about something else that you could do that I can't
Something you did very quickly that could take me hours
Everybody's good at something just saying hey green. Thanks for the 500 bit screen
Hey jerma showed up late today, but wanted to let you know that I love the content
Known about you for quite some time and recently found you again in september
When I was going through a lot of anxiety transitioning to high school blah blah blah
Anyways, hate to sound all mushy, but keep it up and here's to a fire 2020. Thank you
Now that blah blah was in the message. I wasn't doing that blah blah is in the message
now, but seriously, uh good luck and um
Good luck going to high school
In september when I was going through a lot of anxiety transitioning to high school
High school is not as bad as you think it could be
Just get your work done
Don't take it too seriously
Respect your teachers
Because can we give it up for our teachers, please give it up for our teachers
They got a lot of they're trying. They're trying, you know
We gotta
We gotta we gotta we gotta treat our teachers better
I think
I think that the educational system
I think that education is one of the most important things in the world
Education is the most important thing in the world
I think that we need, you know, we need to make sure our teachers are prepared
What about water? We need water too. What?
Teacher's pet teacher's pet
Mebius, thank you mebius for the 500 bits. It's a dumb
Oh, that's the best comment of the night
Afro and gaming. Thanks for the 500 bits. They say corgo. Thank you for the 500 bits
snoozing copter
Thanks for 250 the politics thing intrigues me because I think about that
I'm not going to get political. I really am not because i'm not big into politics
My opinion though is that
We all live together on earth think it's important that we keep some responsibility that we can continue living here
Don't force stuff on others, but maybe support where support is needed
At least where you can getting your own life in order is support too in a way because you can raise generations that'll help each other
more
That's that's a pretty
That's a pretty that's a pretty good take it is that's a pretty good take
That's a pretty good take
That's a pretty that's that's a pretty pretty political thing to say
We only got one earth too. I only got one earth
You are right. We've got generations to come
We need to take care of our teachers
Just make another earth forehead
That's what elvon musk is trying to do isn't he doesn't want to colonize mars
his boat cars
That pretty good take snoozing though. Seriously who buried juice. Thanks for 250. Sorry. I was such a shit chat member tonight
I'm incredibly tired and wasted after a full week of college course loads and parties
I only caught the end and i've been really pogging and burping at my monitor for the past half hour
Anyways, i'm gonna go throw up in my underwear. Thanks again
What is going on?
Pasta globs. Thanks for 250 a man has fallen into the river in lego city. I can see where you guys started to get
Hey
linsenberg, thanks for the five community subs
Wembley, thanks for 250. Can I recommend you to play star wars episode 3 after you play lord of the rings?
It's pretty much the same sort of hack and slash game
They made star wars games like that
And then finally fitty
Thank you fitty for the 350
Dharma, thank you so much for blah blah blah. I don't care next message
Good night everybody. Let's see tomorrow
We're gonna do lord of the rings fellowship of the ring that stream might be like two hours long
I'm just gonna be real. Let's go watch joel. Uh,
Pepe laugh
Let's go. Let's go pepe laugh and watch joel try to get through jump king
See you guys tomorrow. Take care. Have fun and good night. Tata