I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
Oh, it's loud!
And now, the nominees for the best performance of the year.
What did I miss? What did I miss? What did I miss? What did I miss?
Best performance.
What did I miss?
I have to find a way to fix it all. And the answer is somewhere out with Forbidden Quest.
Everything was so nice.
What did I miss?
Quiet. Go to hell!
Hey, welcome to the game awards. I'm watching it. I think it's alive. Yeah, you have to see right
You see wait
You don't scare me. I can't talk about it
No, we're good. All right
New poll start. I don't how do I get rid of this?
best performance
All right, what are you looking out now? You're this is heavy
Finally, I didn't work out today. Let me see. What are the nominees? You don't mind. Do you if I do a little lead?
I didn't play any of these games
the best performance
winner
Christopher judge
All right
Is that game good?
Yeah, I just threw a shirt. I had ire. I'm here
We didn't just start. I thought it was starting like half an hour ago. What do you mean?
This is gonna dry so weirdly
Okay, now I see why I couldn't get more than a plus one
um
Cool cool cool. Let's go to the game awards. Um, first of all, uh, I have to thank my mama
Um, he's great
Belief that I would amount to something good would uh
Never waver even though it looked like I'd never amount to anything good
um my brother
Who's my hero?
at 40
Changed his life
Went to medical school and is now doctor judge
my children
Who I am muted forever
proud of
Forever thankful of and still the best role i've ever had is being your dad
Hey, he's phenomenal
Sony santa monica miss yumi yang
It is an honor and a pleasure
to work
For you and with you you are a unicorn because you actually
Proved that for the first time. Oh shit. Yeah
The trickle-down theory actually worked
Cory barlog. Thank you brother
Thank you, uh for
believing in me and
Thank you for having me read for the role
um
I was the last actor in california to read stop touching your hair. Um
and corey
Said to me he didn't think I would do it
and uh
If I had known it was a video game back then
I might not
Boy how things have changed?
um
matt
rich
dory bruno erica b
all
everyone
who
Made that volume so special
And so sacred
Uh everyone
at every level
Be a designer be it
Whatever it was who worked
Camps flipped under extraordinary conditions
To get this game out
There we go
Why it's a great it's a great game
It's a great game
I'm an elden ring fan
Are you so greasy?
We were honored to go to try becca. I haven't played it 2018. I didn't play
All right. I played the first three hours of the first one said he wouldn't be directing the next one
I literally did quit quit and he said no
Wait multiverse is one best fighter
And I said
eric williams better be a beast
Of course it did
Are you serious eric williams is a motherfucking beast
Okay, whatever looks so smelly and slimy today you'd know you're new you're new to corey you have to be new
on kind of a artistic level a
Level of of that side of me
eric williams
and I
He's always this slimy from such the same place two different parts of the country
two different
Out of the game awards so far. I just turned it on
but two from a very
similar
emotional place make the face came bigger and
Not right now
I'll never forget
I guess I can't say what it was but it was something
That moved me
so deeply is it too small and
There's a there's a time frame that
cinematics have to fit into
hopefully not speeches
And is it is it is it quiet reel it in oh shit what I do and eric came over to me
What I did how did I just muted it for myself?
How did I do that?
And he just hugged me and just held me as I was sobbing
and then he
Said words I will never forget
Okay, big guy now give us one we can use
to
this amazing wonderful
group of actors
um
who
Brought as much or more
than I did
every single day
Why am I late? I'm not I I just got here we're in there and we'll talk about something. I don't want to this is bravery speech
That's a good speech
this group of actors who
share their
Heartache their loves their lost loves their loneliness
I am so grateful
and thankful
that
I got to spend all those days in that volume with you
This is for all of us
Sonny those awards are huge by the way
I wasn't lying. I voted for you
Your work was
astounding
You're the future of this
just never
Forget
The two things I hopefully gave you
Hire me
Don't be a douchebag
To every single person in this room
No matter what game it was you touched you are heroes because you got so many people in the world
Through a very difficult dark time. That's still not over
Games the gaming community means so much to this world so much
in the course of dreams and escapism and and just
Being better
Um, thank you. The music is adding to the speech
A great night, Pachino
That guy's awesome
All right, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to my coverage of the game awards
I'm here great. I was a little late judge. I think he was trying to give away
We're gonna go we're gonna give our opinions of what we see here. It's time to get the announcements rolling here at the game awards
Tonight many of the world's top studios are here at the game awards to give you a glimpse at the exciting future of video games
In 2023 and beyond okay, our first world premiere comes from a small
Reclaimed studio that needs no introduction at this point. You can't even nominate these anymore multiple awards here at tga
I'm very excited to share the global announcement of their next project. Here we go. You can't nominate this stuff anymore
I love this this dead zone where you guys can't nominate anything right now
Not for these awards. I'm talking about for my awards. I'm talking about for the for the for the end of the year awards
All right, quiet. It's cutting. Oh, this is gonna be good. This is gonna be good
Good this is gonna be good
Now go or so
The least I can do is light your way down. They're gonna be good
You'll be given I was born for this
You're trifle with powers far beyond your comprehension, which
Okay, if I call you rich like that, did he even play hades?
Yeah, I that was like my game of the year when it came out. Wasn't it?
I don't know was it
Was it it was wasn't it? I don't remember
80s 2 oh, that's gonna be cool. Come on
Can they do a crazy thing where it's like and by the way, this is out today
Yeah, oh well, trust me
We are just getting started hades 2 is the next game and first ever sequel now in development at supergiant games
Like the original which was revealed here at tga in 2018
Hades 2 is going to be developed in early access to your feedback and help shape the game and news on early access is coming
in 2023
next
I'm so excited about this one
We're taking a journey to an exciting new world with a world premiere from a studio led by someone with a legacy of building
Incredible narrative driven games and creating genre defining experiences
It's moments like this that get me excited about the future of our medium
Is dying and my only one here is with one of them
What is it people say
Let's go, you know what you just
picked what
you
Broke I don't know why I was reading like that. Like there was a comma there
Like fix what you broke?
A few surprises tonight as a first look at judith coming from ghost story games
Led by ken levine who has created immersive gaming worlds like rapture in columbia a few months ago
I visited the studio in boston and played multiple hours of this game and let me tell you everything you saw there is in in engine
Ghost story games is also exploring different approaches to narrative that you will learn about in the future
Okay, let me just say I can't wait for them to tell you more didn't that look fantastic
Exciting stuff
All right. Well, let's go to another brand is it another world premiere for the fans here at the game awards. Come on
Come on, I need the elden ring dlc. I need it. I need it. This is the bayonetta three
I don't even know what bayonetta they're on guys. I have to be honest
You know, i'm i'm of the opinion that we have to stop numbering franchises now
Yeah, bayonetta origins. Let's get colon explain the thing
Wait, what is this?
Is this supposed to be bayonetta like a younger
the colonel demon
Before she became bayonetta
she was
The power to save who was she bayonetta
Oh, she still was bayonetta. It's not like
Barbara or something. I don't know what bayonetta. Oh, I thought it was like before she was bayonetta
She was this I don't know that's coming out soon
Okay. Oh, that's right following on the heels of bayonetta three
It won't be long until you get to play this brand new action adventure game in the bayonetta series on march the 17th
All right, there are lots more new game announcements and awards to come
But tonight you also have a shot at some cool free stuff just for watching the game awards
On steam val is giving away a steam deck every minute to a viewer of the show. Wait every minute
It's gonna start not every hour, but I probably should start talking a little quicker every minute
That's crazy. Uh, but seriously steam deck is incredible and they're giving away every minute
We also have twitch viewer rewards watch 60 minutes of the show tonight on our twitch every single second limited edition
Jeff keely among us mask. Yes, it's back an awesome kt s from gears award costume in fall guys and a full free game
Rogue legacy on the epic games. I'm never gonna play fall guys ever again
I told you guys I told you already spectacular performance from hosier and the game awards orchestra more awards announcements and yes
Animal from the muppets will be back
Well, he was already here they're describing that he was already here
Wait
Animal from the muppets is here. That was kind of a weird thing to go out on he was there
Yeah, he's here, oh, okay
You missed it, all right
To competing and cooperating in I just I it was kind of an interesting if you didn't know the animal was here
It's sort of like oh, yeah. So what's next? We've got new game announcements
We've got some cool drops for you to get on twitch. Oh, and by the way animal from the muppets
It's gonna bite somebody in the audience. It's like wait what happened?
When was he here?
The elden ring dlc I might shit my pants
It's but it might not get announced, right? We don't know that we don't even know what's gonna happen
What if it's not elden ring dlc, but i'll shit my pants on camera if it happens
Somebody's standing up like oh elden ring got announced dlc. Are you serious? All right, I stand up and just like
Why would I want to do that? What's this? Oh, is this the uh, the
protocol
Ballista protocol
I wanted to play this but I heard it was kind of rough. I heard it was pretty rough
That's not at least technically speaking just one san francisco the city by the bay is under siege by forces
Not of this world, please do it. We need they fixed it. Okay fearless recruits
What's this guts to look evil in the house ghostbusters thing? What is this?
What is this?
You what is this?
What is wait, where is where is that guy? Doesn't it look like he's outside of the house?
One of those guys looked like they were outside the house in front of their front door
Okay
You can play the quest it's on quest
It is not is it on quest. I don't know what any of that means
One of my favorite parts of this show is bringing video game music to life on stage now to perform blood upon the snow
From tonight's most nominated game god of war ragnarok, please welcome multiple platinum grammy-nominated hosier featuring bare mccree
Am I allowed to show this game awards orchestra conducted by lauren bouth?
Go ahead. No, I know i'm not i-e-u-ing this
I won't i-e-u- this
I think it's fine, right?
It's video. It's video game music in a video game, right?
It's fine. I apologize for the window sound. It's it's so annoying and i'm such an annoying motherfucker
It's gonna happen three two one
Sorry
The window sounds gonna happen again
I'll try to match it to the music. I think it was pretty good
What is that thing
Whoa
Hurdy-gurdy that looks like a a musical instrument I made up in my dream
No
This wind
There's a person over here and a person over here sitting next to me. They're enjoying the music
Hey
Hey, did this win?
I don't know
Hey
Hey, dude. Hey, did this win?
Fuck up
That's good
That was really good
Yeah, that's like a come on. Yeah, that's what you get. Come on
That was actually very very good. That was fantastic. It's normal
Hey
Hey, john
Did you go off to the snacks thing? The game awards orchestra? I'm grateful to have the popcorn you got
I don't feel like going up. It's really a joy to hear the music from games
I have like some of the milk tubs. Come on
It's amazing what that orchestra puts together in just a few weeks of rehearsal
They'll be back later in the show to pay tribute to our game of the year nominees
This year a record-setting number of you voted 55 million for the game awards on our website
million in china and on our discord server you can head over to discord.gg
Slash the game awards tonight to join in the discussion about the show right now
Our next award from the new film glass onion and knives out. I don't want to be moderating that discord
Let me just be honest with you jessica hennock
Yeah, if you're oh, yeah, go discuss it. I bet you that discord is probably
They're probably doing lots of moderation there
I don't want to alarm anyone
But someone in this room is a murderer
Just kidding. We're just joking around but also statistically speaking someone in this theater probably is
A murderer. I'm sorry. Let's not think about that
Anyway, I don't want to spoil our film
But I can tell you that there is a very popular video game featured in it
And now to give you some more clues, please welcome writer director ryan johnson and the star of glass onion daniel craig
jessica hedgwick
And hello game awards. Oh, we are so excited for you to see our new film
Uh, we have a new movie scene in it for fans of a certain game
So we wanted to bring a little something to that game
That's you that's been a while. Look look at this adorable. It's a nice skull like the cravet. It's very very nice. Yeah, and now
Here are the nominees. This is so me me, isn't it? Best debut indie somebody's a murderer like
Oh, I gotta play this i'm finding it hard to believe we're I gotta play that one that one's supposed to be good, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah that one that one that one that one that one that one
That one and the game award for best debut indie goes to it created a whole new genre. Come on
Created an entire new genre and it was a whole new genre. That was great. That's it. It made a whole new genre
All right, stray is apparently a very good game. Okay, i've heard very good things about it
I'm a little upset right now. Sorry. It's actually it's supposed to be a great game. I don't want to thank you so much
It's an incredible honor on behalf of the whole team in montpellier that is probably watching right now. Hi guys
um
I want to thank everyone that was involved in making this
This game. It's really a work of love and passion
And all the talented members of our team put everything they have to make this game real
Thanks to everyone who has helped us along the way our friends families partners. I've heard nothing
But amazing things about stray. I can't lie to you
Very important. Um
And a printer interactive you guys are amazing. You make dreams happen
Um, thank you so much. We've been with us the whole way through the vampire survivors soundtrack
And yeah, thank you to the players. Um, we put such a big part of our lives three bucks. It was
Three dollars react to it is the best feeling in the world. So thank you. Merci. Merci beaucoup
All right. No
Congratulations, why am I acting like i'm by yeah, like i'm acting like i'm on the team for vampire survivors
Congratulations. Yeah, but you know our product lightfall destiny 2's next chapter launching in february
Join your fellow guardians to master the cosmic powers of the universe and cancel the apocalypse
Is vampire survivors nominated for anything else because it should win something it deserves it
Oh, hold on when we think about controlling something powerful
It's easy to assume it takes strength, but what i've learned
through loss
We can overcome
The impossible what's this?
Whoa
You can do that
There are tanks
gravity weapon
green
I really had a stuff to say
I'm gonna get a lot of shit for this and that's all right, but i'm just telling you how I feel
I I said this last year instead of the year before that
I don't like
bright blue me neon green purple and pink colors
Do you know what i'm talking about? It's like a certain like game engine brightness
on
Like bright green neon lights, you know, you know, you understand i'm talking about
Oh shit actually
A lot of time dreaming up how I was gonna kill you with it. Is that the flash or is that a guy in a flash costume?
You're mine now and you're in for a world of
shit
No, the flash is is
At least eight here
You hear that kill people
Wait, why is batman so evil, huh? I am vengeance
I am the knight
I am batman. Oh, that's right. Yeah
Absolute absolute fucking legend
After 30 years is the iconic voice of batman in the arkham video games batman the animated series and countless other dc projects
Actor kevin conroy sadly passed away last month at the age of 66. He was such an iconic voice
He was so amazing in the arkham games and I know he was batman gonna miss him dearly
He was batman tonight
We can share that he will return to rocksteady's arkham verse one final time really play batman in suicide squad
Killed the justice league when the game releases on may 26th of next year
Now as we think about the next phase of our industry
It's important to recognize those who represent the bright bold and inclusive future of gaming
That's why we have our game awards future class presented by old spice and tonight
Over 75 members of the class from the past two years are here in the audience. Hello guys
And this week we inducted the 2022 class of 50 50 new members
You can read about them at tga future class.com and right now meet one of this year's new members a chemist
Turn game dev at innersloth who also happens to be a street dancer
I'm mcmunye. I'm the lead backend programmer on among us and i'm a street dancer named doctor robotman
I was looking that's pretty awesome
Dancing video games get in line and realize that we as animation dancers have the unique ability to show the
body control the robotics we have
The ability to bend time and reality among us among us is just still exciting
I think there's a lot of potential. I don't think a lot of people thought that among us was gonna be still sticking around this
Long after camera
I didn't
Where's your face cam
right here
Anytime there's a full video on the screen. I I put it off anytime. There's a full video
I usually go I take the face cam off xbox game. I gave pass whatever the xbox game pass. I can't even say the word
It's sick
Game pass is sick from the studio who spent two years recreating their own game recreate studio presents
Oh my god, this is so cute. Can you teach me how to play this game? Yeah
Wow
Prepare your friends for a cute and relaxing animal crossing like experience animal crossing like destroy them all
That doesn't happen in animal crossing improve your relationship with friends. Oh, what the heck?
Yeah, sure
What's going on? They don't hurt each other in that game epic animal characters starring royal corgi
orange cat
canada goose
Bullshit a regular duck that looks like absolutely no one
All of these animals have very fancy outfits an actual royal corgi an actual orange cat
an actual canada goose an actual
Let's interview the game producer
Join the epic battle taking place in some of the most epic places
Don't try these in the human world
a submarine destroying the world
a freezing cold fighter jet
A station where kiano i like that a dude wearing a suit
a black hole
football
trebuchet
Exploding basketball
While the game offers various modes to encourage different styles of gameplay
But we all know that the only thing that's truly interesting is to watch your friends lose their shit
Oh, wait, they can hold on lots of weapons. I'm i'm very confused very realistic
They say shit, but they don't they bleed needs to learn how to use this
What's going on here and biggest feature of the game?
butt scratching
Party animals play with your friends. Why doesn't why is shit not bleep coming 2023?
What is a tier three swear? Is it?
Stop swearing. I'm i'm not
If I swear in the next 10 minutes
I will
Nothing, it'll just be kind of humorous for a few moments
Okay
10 minutes and i'm talking even tier one swears like
Damn it. Okay. That's right
The last of us is officially starting now pc on march 3rd and later in the show the cast of the last of us show
From hbo will be with us to present an award
But now to present best adaptation, please welcome the host of tga opening act sydney goodman
What was this award
As I didn't hear it. I mean I heard it, but it didn't process it. What was it?
It's adaptation. Okay
A brand new award for best adaptation
This award celebrates when beloved characters and stories from gaming are lovingly transported to films
Oh, okay. Here are the nominees. All right. What do you got best adaptation? I don't want to vote
Okay
Okay, I didn't see that one. I mean it's gonna it's gonna have to be
All the misery right award for best adaptation. It's probably gonna be all the misery
Play it
Yes
Every single person is my enemy
Oh the treachery
Every single person wants to be my enemy
my
enemy
Wow
I mean it's an incredible honor to you know, be awarded by the video game community
you know, we're all we're gamers at heart, uh who built this and uh
It's been a long long journey getting here. Uh, definitely like to thank guys. I've seen the first two episodes
Okay, you see in every frame of the show. I gotta finish it. It's been a wonderful partner, of course
Of course riot, you know for believing in us to mark sean and brandon. This is our
It's just been it's been an incredible ride and I
Can't thank you enough. So once again, thank you
Baby three
I don't remember. I saw the first like two three episodes
I liked it. I thought it was good. Congratulations. I didn't sit down and watch it again and speaking of adaptations later
We'll have the first clip from the new super mario brothers animated movie. Oh my goodness
He can michael keelby with us. All right now back to the games coming later in the show
We'll have an update on final fantasy 16
A new look at cyberpunk's phantom. It's too many. It's too many and the first
Gameplay raw gameplay footage of tekken 8 there's lots more game awards to come and that means
Lots more steam decks to give away. But now it's time for the world premiere of a long-awaited game
Final fantasy 16 final fantasy 17 final fantasy 18. What at what point are they gonna get to final fantasy like 50?
Final fantasy colon retirement. All right, i'll shut up. What is this long awaited star wars?
Imprisoned again
That's cool. But I didn't didn't the first one come out like a year and a half ago like two years ago
I don't think that's that long. That's not really long awaited. It's pretty
He is this a pretty normal amount of time to wait for a sequel
You can do two
Was that
Is a threat that just took me out
As long as we fight survives
I'm sorry. I tried to time it. I tried to get it right
Wait, what the hell is that jeff the hero of star wars jedi put that thing down
Oh, no, it's not okay
It's an incredible honor to wield this lightsaber again
And I think I can speak for everybody at respawn ea and lucasfilm when I say how incredibly excited
We are to show our work on jedi survivor good if i'm up there. I had the chance to play the game recently
Just spin around with it, you know, just like swing swing swing dash put the hand out like this
You know what I mean? Put the hand out something. Oh, I would be going I see up there
I'd be swinging it around the same way when you play it, too
And I've just got to say that I am so incredibly lucky to be a part of this incredible project
and it's really something extraordinary, so
We'll see you all in a galaxy far far away march 17th and until then
May the force be with you
Oh, you gotta be like real real real real real real real real above your head
To play jedi survivor, thanks to respawn even if you don't know how to do it
They'll put sound effects on
Next we're proud to support independent games here at the game awards
This next world premiere comes from a game award-winning studio up in my native canada
Oh, come on, what is it? Oh, okay. All right. This game was awesome
I wonder if it's a similar game looks like it could be
Looks like it. What is going on here?
By the way
This is just level 1-1
Good luck gamers
earth blade
All right. All right. That seems like pretty good. The last was awesome. That was like probably one of the better games that came out that year
It starts in the desert you cling you find others
friends 2024
You that's a while dry dirty streets of civilization
In the ancient halls of the testing stations
You find answers
You seek the secrets of the ever-shifting sands
Spice
Was it open world
You do all of these things in my dream sleeper
I am
terrified
Of what happens when you awaken
What is this?
Dune i'd never seen dune. I've never seen the original guys. I don't like I don't take in any media
I just watched the same fold metal alchemist intro a thousand times and then go to bed
I don't I don't
I don't I try to be excited about that. It seems pretty cool
People love it. That was your first in-engine look at dune awakening tonight
All the major gaming platforms are offering special discounts and offers on tga nominees
You can check out the game awards sale across steam xbox playstation epic store and special offers on nominees on the nintendo
Eshop and that's not all in celebration of tga
You can also play free demos of many upcoming games across steam xbox and for the first time playstation
And right now we're excited to share news about a playable demo going live tonight on playstation
Whoa, I don't have that
I don't give a shit before you came but people have resigned themselves to their fate
Powering in fear of those hunters. Look how cool this is whatever. I don't care
Here
This is fun, this is magical powers and cool stuff like that. This looks cool
And this once and for all
Cool is available right now on the playstation store
If you have a playstation
What's on xbox?
Let's come on xbox today
We already saw this there. We saw this car
Your favorite controller
Yeah, my favorite control is super nintendo. I don't know what you mean by that
Indie partners bring a whole world of fun. They spin new life into familiar faces
No, it isn't players on their toes
Put dance battles front and center challenge us to aim higher and create secrets destined to be discovered
You're watching ads eyes of a captive audience. So here's a big thanks. What do you think this whole thing is?
To see where the fun takes you next
Yes, you are consuming probably two to three hundred advertisements over the course of these two three hours
The whole thing isn't bad
When you order twelve dollars or more it's like oh the pornhub app. Oh, it's not so simple. It's so easy
I thought I was like why is this pornhub?
The pornhub app was this
I played this game on my ipad
Or I want to say
Two or three hours is pure freedom in this world
I was so overwhelmed forever. I just was I remember sitting there lying down on my back
Just being like
Too many things to do. I don't know. There's too many pop-ups. There's too many things happening. I have
40 sub menus
Do I do?
This looks so fun
It was so many things to do. I just got overwhelmed. I was like, I can't it's just too much for me to even look at
It was fun, I'm just walking around doing electricity moves and stuff to be it was like oh this is kind of fun
I was so overwhelmed
vampire survivors is an ios no pretty sick
Welcome back to the game awards. That was like a genshin impact now in the middle of it
It was literally the marvel snap music
And don't ask me why I know that
It was the marvel snap music next is something truly truly special tonight
All of us together get to experience the announcement of the next game from one of our industry's most visionary game studios
Okay
Get ready, please enjoy get ready that you know, it's like get ready if it's not something huge
the death stranding
It's a strand type game
Why do I feel like kojima would make a game
That's just like a 500 million piece puzzle
And he just releases it. It's on like ps5 store for free
And everyone just has to do it at the same time
And when it's completed
It unlocks the trailer for this game and it might take 40 years for us to finish it. It's okay doxels 2
the worst one
You know, I meant that when I said I understand sorry, I just like pissed people off for no reason
What is that?
No, this is not a scorn type game although kind of
Kinda
Going on
Everyone please join me in welcoming back to the game awards a true legend
Mr. Hideo Kojima
He just comes out with a t-shirt gun
Like
People are like just clamoring to try to get it
Haki great to see you. Uh, well, mr. Kojima
It's been three years you're on this stage with us in 2019 where you won best game direction
Ds2 has been announced. Uh, what can you tell us? How is it going to be different than ds1?
Um
I can't really be specific right now, but you just seen the trailer and I put a lot of things inside
So I want you guys to talk about it and find details in it
Good luck. All right
Well, I know we have some of this is a 600 million piece puzzle on a qr code in there
You guys go find it. Um, troy is here as well. We heard him there. Hello troy
We're so excited about this collaboration you have with an amazing cast. I wanted to ask you the story of this game
How is the pandemic and what we've been through? How has that impacted your story telling?
That's the cube from peter. Mala nu. Yeah
Well, I had the story written before the pandemic but after experiment experiencing the pandemic
I just rewrote the whole thing. Uh the story from scratch
I also didn't want to predict any more future so I rewrote it
Hi, mr. Kojima, it's always such a pleasure having you here. I wanted to ask generally what's next for you as a creator
I know we have our fun podcast we do what else you've got planned. Okay
Well, yes, i'm doing the ds2 right now and also one other title that's completely new
I'm kind of experimenting at the moment and also other visual projects. I'm still working on so i'll hope to reveal it soon
Trans translating very prolific. It's such a it's such a skill everyone
I'm thinking about this right now
If you told if you told me in english
Four or five full sentences and said say it again
I'd go we're proud to announce a new game. Hey, what the fuck did you even say a new triple a independent studio be like you
Studios I can't experience making story hard to do fps games like dead space halo and bioshock
They partnered with ea originals label be label behind last year's game of the year winner. I'll try it takes two
Okay, i'll try a single player magic shooter from now ready original world right now. Here is your first glimpse
there's something here is a
A new pair of shoes. What did he say? Here is a new thing to uh present. I don't know. I don't remember a good one
I'll try it after
You help us win this i'll know you're ready
But didn't they just say you can't win you don't win here if you help us win
Did I miss that?
Okay, i'm gonna try
I'm gonna try to say what what actor who recently performed in midnight mass and ghostbusters spirits unleashed when he's welcome
When jeff is back on stage
I will try to do it
I will try as an actor i'm drawn towards stories, but I think that's true of all of us, especially those who pick up a controller
Narrative in games is a slippery thing because there's no single way to tell a story
The beginning middle and end may not even happen in that order
And for each of us there may be different outcomes altogether
But to be truly invested in a game story is to step away and feel as if you've lived another life
These are the nominees for best narrative
Best narrative hugo was always worried that it would start all over again. She doesn't have this
the golden order is
Things are falling apart
This game was fucking crazy, I forgot to talk to you guys about this it should be that one
That game was insane. Okay, it's that one for best narrative goes to
god of war ragnarok
Immortality was actually a crazy experience. I forgot to tell you about it. It actually was a really
terrifying strange
weird
Wild experience. I forgot to tell you about it. Whatever it lost
Why didn't you stream it? I don't know because I
I felt like just sitting on the couch
Put a camera on your couch there are so many people a lot of them over there who should be on this stage with
Me right now
Um so much goes into the telling of a story. I screamed at you. I'm sorry by the way from writers animators
cine artists level and technical designers artists
Qa programmers audio music
It's not just what's on the page obviously our incredible cast
They elevate everything that we do put on the page
Um, i'm just i'm honored to accept this on their behalf
I want to thank uh playstation
scott
herman
I want to thank oh god our uh
SMS it and facilities the the thing the heavy lifting they had to do when we all had to shift to work from home
That's incredible. We're behind you. They're still supporting us now
Uh, it's one of auto's toys
I'm just uh, i'm grateful to be here. I'm grateful for your support all the nominees in this category
You all have my undying respect
um
I also want to thank obviously you me, uh
Cory and our captain eric williams
Hello rich and I
After chris step aside for this one rich and I couldn't have asked for a more supportive and incredible creative partner
And uh, we're grateful for you every single day
Uh, oh, i'm sorry
Uh, I also want to thank our families who went from having to see us in the morning and at night to having to see us
all day every day, uh
Why did you throw it? That's a burden. I wouldn't wish for on anyone
My uh wife suzanne my son james. Thank you very much. I love you and i'll see you later
immortality actually is
Cracked out. It's cracked out if you if you have an opportunity to play it. Don't look up anything. Don't do anything
Don't do anything. Just play it. Just enjoy it. Don't fucking type it into reddit to see like
Oh, what do other people say about this? Don't do it
Just play it
I know you're gonna look it up. You're gonna go why did germa say immortality was a good game?
Don't look don't say that
Just play it
I used to love teken
I remember back in the day. I used to just mash every button and it was fun
And
You would accidentally chain three or four moves together and your friend would go dude
That was pretty good. You're like, yeah, I know
I know I play
A lot of old tekin was just each person was hitting as many button inputs as possible
And whoever pressed it more times won
That's at least if I remember when I was like, I don't know like 14 15. I don't know any one of them came out
Are you always this talkative?
Now it's time to recognize more it's hard to shut me up. Here are the nominees for best art direction
I never shut the fuck up god of war ragnarok. I'm sorry horizon forbidden west
scorn and stray
And the game award goes to
elden ring
Yeah
Yep, he's for best vr ar game after the fall among us vr
Bone lab moss book two and red matter two. All right, it's not it goes to
moss book two
Yeah, is that good?
next the nominees for best sim strategy game dune spice wars
mario and rabid sparks of hope total war warhammer three
two-point campus and victoria three and the game award this year goes to
mario and rabid sparks of hope
The beats are I think congratulations
Here are the nominees address community support presented by discord apex legends destiny two
final fantasy 14
No man's sky and no man's sky. What a story the game award goes to
Congratulations. Don't you feed?
Make sure to check out their discord community at the address below
We have much more game awards still to come and right now
Here's a new look at nightingale a first-person pve open world survival crafting game that we first announced last year
How many things did you say?
It's a roguelike rpg crafting
Survival horror game. What was it here is?
1889 teeters on the brink of any genres. They didn't say first person. Well, that looked first person
Network of portals has collapsed
Your people are cast asunder beyond the frontiers of your reality
realms alive with monstrous beasts
Eldritch creatures of which you cannot conceive
You must gather your wits craft whatsoever you require
And build a life in the realms
uncover the secrets of ram cards
And venture deeper into the unknown
I'm actually very interested now your path forward is winding and full of terrors
save yourself
Survive the realms
And rebuild all that has been lost
I don't know what the hell this is, but it looked cool
We'll see when it comes out
Tonight in celebration of the game awards verizon has a special offer buy an xbox series s from verizon
You'll get a free controller scan the qr code below to pick up an xbox series s
And follow average jonas on instagram at average underscore jonas for more fun details
Wait one
Re-shit
What what we find ourselves now at the beginning free controller before leaving our place of comfort
Before being tried and tested
We can feel it
This is game pass. Yeah
Game pass is pretty good. It's waiting to be shattered. I know you're gonna bad chest me. That's fine
It's good
Sometimes I have been nothing but happy with game pass
They put some good shit on there ways unexpected stuff. And here's another thing
Excuse me
Being able to play with the cloud
Sometimes i'm telling you I will just open up a game on the cloud and i've never heard of it before
I might close it in fucking 10 minutes. I might close it in five minutes
Oh, this wasn't for me. Well, cool that I could play it though and try it move on
Sometimes I play a game for 10 12 hours play the whole thing to the cloud
Don't ever install it
It's good
I'm not gonna you know
Make anything up here. It's good
And i'm telling you xbox xbox shit the bed
Last generation
They actually shit the bed like it was horrible. The xbox one. I thought was terrible
They're doing good things now
Once I get a couple days great under my belt of not vaping
I'm just gonna feel better mentally today definitely was hard. I started vaping nicotine again because what's he talking about the stressful events
I thought it was helping but then I i'm talking about video games made me feel way worse
Gaming and referrals and hardware is currently thinking about putting vaping nicotine is
Don't be afraid to talk to someone and if you don't have a support system
This is quitting can be there for you. So you don't feel alone. I've got the samsung
990 pro series shall we get started then this is what are the exceeds all expectations
Reading speeds are 40% what are they writing speeds are 55% faster
Through the in-house control hard drive the per watt performance has improved up to 50%
The 990 pros and what is it loading controller for its smart thermal solution technology controls you playing computer games
obviously the best
They're not vapes
From tonight until the end of december you can get an exclusive chance for 10 off of the samsung 990 pro ssd
At samsung.com slash us to enhance your gaming experience
It is 990 pro tga 22
All right, our next presenters are absolute legends
They attended the very first game awards where we honored them with our first industry icon award
They founded sierra online
They brought us half-life king's quest and hundreds of other titles and this show my career in gaming would not
What was it a uh, their latest game?
They're back making games which we're excited about it's called colossal cave and it launches january 19th
Everyone please join me in welcome. Those are ssds. They were tiny ken and roberta williams. Those were those were tiny. Wow
Actually kind of cool
They're m.2 ssds. Yeah, I have a regular ssd. It's not
Huge but it's big making games many many years ago
We knew the potential was there to achieve almost anything
Even to change the world
We're honored to be back here to present the award for games for impact
Which recognizes games that change the way people think?
And feel about the world
Here are the nominees
Games for impact
You swear it won't happen again. I just want to know that we can make it through this
Every cycle you take your chances wake up the sleeper
It's hard not to drift into the past
Well
and the game award for games for impact goes to
as dusk falls
I I think this is on game pass
And I remember I remember getting it. I remember opening it and I remember be I was I was really high and I like
I just I don't know. It was like a choose
Your path kind of game like choose your adventure type stuff
I was like, I don't think i'm ready for this
But I was high. I don't I sometimes I take a little bit. Wow, but you know, what if it's just
Thank you so much, right mom. All right. All right dad forgot everything. So
Let's improvise
uh
the game
We made together with this amazing team
Um was like eight years in the making
We really hoped this is important
Oh no experience that was unique
Narrative that was intense
grounded
And also communal because as this falls is multiplayer. I'll explain after I don't want to ruin the speech
and approachable
And so the story of us this falls that presents, you know
flawed characters
Uh normal people that struggle with their real life
Issues and are thrown in super intense pressure cooker situations
And we hope that players would feel empathy for them and in the process
would
Learn a little bit about their values like reflect on what's important for them. And so super thrilled to be here tonight
It means that hopefully
The game resonated with some of you very happy so thankful I want to especially thank our team
Which is an amazing team at internal nights. The best team i've ever worked with
microsoft for their amazing support and partnership
And my family clement joanna and axel. I love you infinity forever
I'll play it
That's nice
Anyways to interior night boulders gate three is the next big rpg. I gotta have an opportunity to tell you this the creators of definity
Original sin and now the team at larion is ready to share just when you're going to be able to join the party
Jake dm'd me. There's no jake right community jake you've seen him before
Uh said dude, you literally have that ssd in your fucking computer right now
Absolute traced people like parasites in their brains all the way here from boulders gate
You may just be the godsend we've been praying for
You're the same as me
You have a mind flared tadpole in your brain. What is that? What is this thing? Try to find a solution together
Is it a vape pen?
Is it a flash drive? I own it. It's in the room right now. It's in the room
All right
Boulders gate three someone I want you to meet a friend who sees the world in simple terms
Not just a friend
a legend
He's not the kind of man who takes kindly to captivity
The cult captured him
I almost feel sorry for them
Cool cool looks amazing. I'm here with joe mad legendary comic artist and ceo of top down
Joe tonight, you have a new title to announce
We do a few months ago. We announced that we were partnered with digital extreme
Which has made those games were awesome just a huge success over the last 10 years
And now we're going to leverage
Their expertise on our new game
Which is a character-based online action rpg set in a brand new fantasy world and we're super excited
And actually kind of into this a little bit more another partner to talk about too. We do another partner
Has come on board to support us and help us reach even more players around the world
And you'll be able to play it a lot sooner than you might think so, okay
Well, let's take a look at the official announcement the world premiere. Here we go. Thanks
Its arrival brought chaos
But we found a way to control it
We choose the path
We face the danger
We control the chaos this balder gate three, no, no, it's a different game. I'm sorry. I was looking
Played a few tricks
But now we fight as one they find us
Loot loot
Okay
What was the name of that? Uh
What was the name of the game with the people floating around with the umbrellas? I want to remember that I need to remember that one
What was it called?
okay
Nightingale. All right. I gotta remember that one finally. We're free
We were just growing weary of each other's conversation
Lend me your strength
Don't hold this against me
Or two of them together
I'm on a mission
I wasn't doing that to be funny. I think it just was a little low
Joining me now are jenova chen from that game company creators of journey and sky and singer songwriter aurora
Welcome to the game awards and aurora right after the show tonight. You are going to be performing a
Virtual and free concert in sky. Is that right?
Yes, and i'm so excited. I'm sorry about my voice. It's gonna be a concert in the sky last night
I mean, yes
It'll be perfect in the virtual concert. All right, but but tonight it will be very good
Yes, so tell us this is an amazing collaboration working with jenova and the team
Why did you want to do this? Um, i'm so excited about it
Mostly because all of the people that are working on sky children of light and jenova. It's just
The best kind of people and it feels like this this project is so full of love and and light and
Understandment
Um of the outsiders in the world. I thought I just did something wrong
The top right was a picture and picture of this video
And I thought I broke something. Yeah, I got to experience it last week and it really is very moving
I think it's kind of the future where virtual concerts should go jenova
You've always built games about connecting people, you know relationships what?
I wouldn't peg you as someone that would go into the virtual concert space, but this is very special
Tell us why did you want to do this?
Yeah, I mean historically we always want to push the boundary of how a game can make you feel
And with our game journey, we connect two people but with sky and now the upcoming concert
We want to try to see connect
Thousands of people together emotionally and this is just something that i've never experienced and to be honest
Like I just played it with 4 000 people this week and I don't know what to say
But so maybe we can just look at a trailer and hopefully that will help to explain amazing. Let's check it out. Thanks guys
Guy is a pretty game flower journey to sky
What game company continue to push the boundary of video games emotional potential?
Can video game create a genuine human connection and bring players across the world closer?
like a concert
In a real life concert you feel the collective energy of thousands of beautiful souls around you
You can ask the artist and their message at a personal level
We haven't felt this in any video games
And after 18 months of experimentation and development we feel it now
We made this concert completely free so you can experience this amazing journey with your friends and loved ones
You can download on any of these platforms and take less than a minute from boot to concert
Join us for this groundbreaking moment shared by millions of players worldwide
I
Wasn't journey the game where you randomly got match made check that out
It's and had to like special take care of each other and stuff
To get your food delivered for the game awards when you order from wendy's it was incredible
It was like a crazy experience
Yeah
Free vehicle wrap on orders of twelve dollars or more through the end of december players will also be able to participate in pubg mobile
And complete other challenges terms and conditions apply. I played that
at pubg
Google what the fuck are you doing?
There's cars in that one
Yeah, there were cars in that one
I'm going to sit on top of it. I'm gonna try to do it. I'm sorry. I'm gonna sit on
So that's an authority. I didn't even look at it. I was a nice imagine
Don't that's a fire man. I'll send you a seahorse to put right. That's cameras
He's been a person as he motiva
So as he said he was as a person as he don't think
It's probably a little bit important. I'm gonna have a little bit of a stereo
Facebook gaming what's going on?
What is this?
And jeff comes out like this is not a bit jeff has a fucking necronomicon in his hand. He's like
Everyone's like what's going on what's happening?
What did it say I couldn't read it what did it say
Took my sleep and changed like I see some reason for nothing. I am disruptive
Muppet is gonna be in this act. You don't know that
Why did they bleep the squares before
That you have
We're gonna get is this a new trailer for diablo 4
All right. All right, everybody settle down. This is this is make or break it for me here
Ow, no, it's not going to be a card game
That's really efficient actually, whoa, that's a good tactic
Hell, okay
Is anything wow diablo 4 and halsey are just getting started on their collaboration leading up to the which is skill tree from diablo and halsey
Next year, but wasn't that incredible? Thank you so much halsey. All right, I want to see a skill tree
Okay, no, that's not funny. I'm done tonight in the category of best sports racing game
Are f122 fifa 23 mba 2k 23
I actually want to see the skill tree though. I want to see that full skill tree
Gran turismo seven
Congratulations
Here are your nominees for best multiplayer game call of duty modern warfare 2
multiverses
overwatch 2
splatoon 3
And tmnt shredder's revenge. That was good and the game award goes to
Splatoon 3. All right. Okay
Oh, all right. Okay. All right now the nominees for best audio design cod modern warfare 2
Elden ring god of war ragnarok elven ring was so good sound effects forbidden west
and this game award goes to
God of war ragnarok. Yeah. All right. It's good content creator of the year. Oh shit carl jacobs
mudwig
nebelian
gnawbrew and qt cinderella
and the game award goes to
Ludwig, oh shit
Oh, wow
Good shit
deserved
final fantasy 16
hogwarts legacy
resident evil 4
starfield starfield and the legend of zelda tears of the kingdom
Maybe a fan favorite but and the game award goes present before the legend of zelda tears of the kingdom
That's not the one that I said
Congratulations to all our winners so far and now it's time for another world premiere
Oh, congrats to ludwig, man. That's awesome
What's this? Is this dlc?
Come on. We gotta hear it
the fallen leaves
him
I'm waiting to see aloi pursue a sinister threat in the untamed wilds of los angeles and yes
Even the hollywood sign isn't spared
And now please welcome the cast of the last of us show coming to hbo on january 15
Like the whole cast
Is it the entire cast?
Just just real quick. I I know that I told you guys this backstage, but just in front of everybody else
I want to let you know
We've seen the show and
We just love you as joe and ellie
Thank you
big fans big fan
so, you know, we are big fans of you two as well as
Joel and ellie
Oh, this is cool. All right
So should we I thought they were all in the show. Wait, are they all in the show?
Let's do it
Okay
okay
We're here to present the award for best action game
Many haves have action and these are the ones that truly kick ass this kicks ass
Here are the nominees
We got it we nailed it action game we nailed it
I haven't played it but people tell me it was good. This was actually fun. This was very good
Highly recommended if you haven't played it
It was a very good time
And the winner goes to
I've ruined it
All right, this is pretty awesome
um on behalf of the development teams at platinum games
And nintendo that worked tirelessly on bringing bayonetta to life for the third time
Thank you so very much
It's about noon back in japan tomorrow and i'm sure they're watching right now. So this is for you folks. Congratulations
Oh shit, i'm sorry
I think you all know this but no one does
Action games and over-the-top action games like platinum games and as you saw they're already hard at work on their next project
So they asked me to say a few words on their behalf
With our long history of creating action games. It's a huge honor to be awarded bex action game for bayonetta three
We're also delighted to been able to reveal a brand new title for the game awards today
We'd like to thank everyone who helped us bring the game to life and of course the fans of the series
With the characters just as important as the many players
Uh as the many to the many players is gameplay pianoing. You'll keep your eyes. I was there here for sarazes next stories
From everyone at platinum games. Thank you very much. Thank you. He was up there for probably
25 seconds
Congratulations to pg and nintendo and next we have a trio of exciting new game announcements
First, let's head to japan for a special announcement
Yeah
Blue protocol
Amazon games
I'm interested
Okay
Let's go
Do you remember?
What our world was before?
before the sundering
That looks pretty good
for the war for the darkness
Do you remember you will?
Constant conflict there is no rest only fireballs
Your future needs you
Looks kind of good. It's all right. I don't know what the game is
Can we see more of this game? What is this?
Is it remnant? I played a little bit of remnant. It was pretty good
All right
That's probably gonna be pretty fun
This ain't working
We should melt it down for ammo
And we're alive
Sequencing at 17%
Loading memory cord now
Every day it seems we're wasting away
I want to make a game called constant conflict and even in the safe hub world
Just people just run around attacking each other and like fireballs going off and like cars crashing into stuff
Transformers
Like I want in cutscenes for you to be able to die coming up animal from the muppets drops by and keegan
Michael key shares a new look at the super mario brothers movie and still to come the award for best game direction
Stick around
No, not qte's like you are having a conversation with another major narrative character
And there's just crazy shit happening behind you and so it might just run into you possible
Wait, what did my stream crash?
Now we're good. Is the audio screwed up? We're good. Well, that was for a game
Heroes 3 console edition coming in 2020. There is no victory to be had. What did you think it was?
I thought it was a movie or a tv show or something
the strength of your resolve
Is the only thing that will grant you another day
The game awards they talked about movies and tv shows they had the whole cast of the last of us tv shows come out
I mean
Promising but I i'd like to see something that wasn't a
Look, they're full motion video
cut scene
Looked all right. I mean i'm i'm into it when all through the land not a we are
Not even uh, oh
Whether the beans have been naughty or nice there were presents on offer in the snow and the ice
Store for all a ski costume for free. Yeah, that looks so fun. But what they don't show you
Is the outside blue chaperone appearing every two seconds the hands jiggling all over the place
And you walking into walls
Celebrating styles curl up by the fire and play fall guys for a while
He's the voice of toad in the upcoming. They also didn't show the the character going like this every five seconds
Please welcome keegan michael key
Oh mario time pause enough pause what happened
It is so great that we can all be here and having such a good time and celebrating tonight, right?
Yes
Okay. Now. All right. There is something that I would like to address and uh, if you guessed that it is
well something about
toad's head
You would be right
Uh, because I I see a lot of people online
Saying that it's a hat
And and you know what? It's not a hat. It's a cap
You see because the cap is that top part of the mushroom that houses the spores in everything
and also a cap
Is another word for hat. I
See how that okay. I just right now saw how that could be confusing. Um
Wow
Well, okay, whether you call it a cap or a hat or a kapat
I'm good with all of it because it's just part of toad's awesomeness
So now please enjoy this clip of a few of the German routine and hatted
Friends in a sneak preview and it's super the comedic timing is fucking unbelievable, by the way
So, excuse you
That's a legend on stage. Excuse you
Here you go. Excuse me. He's trying to clear a path. That's all i'm doing. He's gonna be fine
Shantrell I see you bud
Here we go. Okay. So these bricks are just floating here
Just popping this pipe and we're on our way. Oh, it's the only way to fly man
Wow
Yeah
Here we are palestaur's big big boom that looks absolutely so amazing
Let's play let's play let's play
He's in the movie. Yes, I like the energy as you can see i'm now joined by animal from the upcoming muppets mayhem
They're recasting first prat
It's animal
Playtime playtime playtime playtime. We are at the game awards
I love this enthusiasm animal. So I have to ask what do you want to play? Do you have a certain game or uh
tarnished
Elden ring is that what you're saying?
I didn't imagine you being a soulsborne player. Oh based. Do you have a favorite boss in elden ring? Oh
And i'm gonna love my
Thinking about it. She's pretty tough in the game
Well, now that I know you're such a big game fan have you ever thought about kind of appearing in your own game
We're having an animal game. Oh, yeah. Yeah, kojima kojima
Y'all everyone's laughing he's in death stranding too. He's in death stranding too. I'm telling you
There's no way animals not in death stranding too so you had to make your own game what would you call it
Ha ha ha ha
I think that one's taken the nintendo lawyers might have some issues with that
But anyways animal it's great to have you here at the game. He just doesn't miss maybe give out an award now
What do you think about that? Oh, yeah music music. Oh
Okay animal has spoken. Let's check out the nominees for best score and music
Best score and music he doesn't miss
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes
That's up there too, though
And the game award for best score and music goes to god of war ragnarok
My favorite drummer
I literally don't believe it. Uh, no, thank you so much everybody
Um, but I I really got to give a shout out to everybody at santa monica studio
corey
When you told me this story eight years ago
Uh, I was moved to tears then and it's been a part of my life ever since
Uh, and eric williams
Uh, you really brought this out of me, man. Uh, thank you so much
All the musicians ivor and hosier who is up here tonight, uh all the ethnic
Fiddle players and and hardinger fiddle and nickel harp all these wonderful
musicians from around the world also lent their uh,
their beautiful performances, but
I just also want to say I I i've learned the power of simplicity and kratos is a man of few words
And I wanted to write him just a few notes. You knew it was gonna be close and I got to write
Um, um, um
And if I only wrote that I I I feel like the story would sort of be there
So I got to write a lot more. Thank you so much everybody. This means the world to me. Thank you so much
So
All right, I don't know why in my brain I thought he wrote this music
Did he?
Wait, and now it's time i'm confused reveal of a brand new action rpg developed by the creators of life is strange
Don't nod and no i'm focused entertainment. I'm losing my mind. What what happened? So I was reading chat
I was reading chat. That was my own fault
You knew it was gonna be tight, you know, if a god of war game comes out, you know, it's gonna be close
Right every one of these categories
So you're a banisher, right you want ghosts, right?
You must have seen some strange things
We had our share but i've never seen a ghost myself
But they are real
right
So what you track and kill him? Is that it?
I so wish you a good hunt then
It takes a brave man to walk these wilds alone
Not alone. Okay. All right
A bow and walk. What do you got show us?
No
Oh, that was
All right. Okay
I I was we I want to see what the gameplay looks like against the horrors the dwellness
Where we draw breath space marine two
While we stand we fight the angels of death
We are the blade drawn against the endless night
Nothing
Will survive our wrath
Yeah, warhammer 40k is really starting to uh, back into focus here go
minecraft 2
Wait
pvp, I'd know I think it's a
Sort of a try again. Try again one more one more one more game
Okay
So you build a base and then say kind of like meet your makers sign up for the upcoming beta the game launches april 4th
2023 could be kind of all week twitch is celebrating what games week recognizing all the games from gaming history
That never got their proper do like ea's over blood which was the most played game this week is a game from 1997
Which game saw the biggest increase in viewership over the week according to a twitch twitter poll the winner was katamari
All right, we've got much more game awards ahead more. That's a great one including an update on final fantasy 16
And of course the game of the year presented by last year's winner joseph ferris. Who knows what he's gonna say. Hopefully it's short
All right, we'll be right back
I hope he comes out with a lightsaber
Can he just take the lightsaber? I know it's like licensed and it but can he just come out with a lightsaber?
Please it would be so cool
Just let him do it. Let him come out with the saber
Here's to you splatoon 3 community
Is imminent team up with friends and fend off the seminet invasion this weekend
What the hell was that? That was jarring. I feel like everything. I thought the computer just turned off
You wretched scum. Do you have any idea what blood ball is moving?
Get it lodging
parsing
protecting the ball carrier and crushing the hell
You know, I actually heard really good things about the original here
That's funny blood bowl three and she's in danger
Once after her costs witcher legend cannot be killed can it
Wait, the witcher three
Oh, they're just oh, they're doing a next gen update. Okay
Motorcycles being added to well
I thought that was intentional for a second. I thought they were freeze-framing
It's crash
The remake was good
Oh, no, is it my computer is it building let's go I think I think my screen is fucked up get ready for an epic reveal in three
No, it's 7 30
Zero, it's 7 30. Oh, no
negative two guys
Where's my crew?
No
We're getting interneted out. What happened?
We were supposed to meet up here and steal all the wumper fruit from the game awards, which i'm now realizing
Was a fruitless plan
Oh, excuse me. Are you guys on mute? Oh, I get it. We're on 160p silent treatment. That's fine
They work for me wherever it is
whatever
Roll the trailer grandma
I don't even know what just happened
Damn, we almost made the whole time too. We almost made it
Shit. No, we almost made it too
God damn it
Come on. It's almost over. Now, please welcome two outstanding
Here are foosly and valkyrie
Evolve every year if there's one category that seems to advance the fastest and furthest it's innovation and accessibility
Each year designers impress and inspire us by discovering new and thoughtful ways to enable an even larger audience to play their games
Through determined consideration for those who are often marginalized here are the game awards nominees for innovation and accessibility
Innovation and accessibility I think we're all right and multiplayer experience. We wanted to draw in people who weren't necessarily gamers
I might be able to get up there if you help me
A forward open this book for guidance that suite of features enables gameplay by players who are blind in their provision
I'm at kennedy and the game award for innovation and accessibility goes to
You
God of war with the sweeps here
This is when the lord of the rings came up
They won almost every single category
back when lord of the rings what return of the king won like
15 out of 20 categories absolutely humbled and grateful to everyone who's helped us in this journey along the way
Because playing games is what's important for the players
It's you all you who play the games that are really the ones that deserve this award
Everyone who was on the team at sms we are truly honored to be with you
Thank you so much eric and yumi for supporting us john and jason for being there while we were trying to make these accessibility features happen
Katie sam and zach my closest cohorts when we were trying to make these features
And all of our team in the qa and accessibility research teams
The ui ux team and everyone who made it possible
Uh, I can't thank you enough and I think that the the players themselves are the ones that are going to benefit the most
This is a race that no matter who wins the player is the real winner
So let's go out there and make all games have no limits. Thank you
Well from here, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh wait, that's not elton ring
That's not elton ring. I'm sorry
What a child
Oh, no, stop, please
Well, i'm sorry elton ring is
Uh for adults, so sorry wickedness dwells that argument just fell through didn't it?
The lords of the fallen
Wait
wasn't
The lords of the fallen wasn't it already a game and now from 505 games a new organized stop lagging
I'm so mad. Stop lagging. Stop lagging. Stop lagging. Stop lagging. Stop it. Damien boitier and the boss himself
Michael mr. Michael lagging
My stream's gonna crash at game of the year, isn't it? We are here to slight us
We're here to set a slightly different tone for the trailer. You're about to watch
You see this trailer here. Well, it's a little different than the rest of these trailers. You're seeing tonight
This one's a little bit dangerous
So the boss wanted to come out here, you know, make sure you don't hurt yourself sometime during the next 60 seconds
Wow
What a crowd
My god, what a night. Wow
um
Listen I uh, i've had some wild times. Uh, i've been involved in some crazy things in my life
uh
I even made a picture with mr. Al Pacino
Donnie brosco
If you haven't seen it, you should look it up. God damn it. So
Anyway, I have to say being the crime boss of rock k city
That's a lot of fun
And uh, we've got an amazing cast with us
These two handsome guys with me
And uh, anyway
Enjoy the debut trailer for crime boss rock k city
coming march 28th
The name of the game is crime boss
Actually, all right. We need to see this
Crime boss
All right, let's watch it
They're lip-syncing
Why is chuck norris, what is this game? What is this game?
That's right. Chuck norris. All right
And now we are happy to announce more winners here at the game awards based on those
I want to play it around the world. Here are the nominees for best role-playing game elden ring live alive
Pokemon legends arkius triangle strategy. I don't care how my computer is. I don't care about my lag
I don't care my internet sucks. It's elden ring say it elden ring. Congratulations to from bandai namco
Yes, here are the nominees for players. I don't want you to see my fucking armpits. So that's why I did it weirdly
Fan voted category you guys were very busy voting the past few days
Nominees sonic frontiers. Yeah, by the way
crazily enough
70,000 people have been banned from the discord in the last hour took out all the bot votes the game award goes to
genshin impact
Please for best independent game
cult of the lamb neon white
sifu
whiz
tunic
and the game award goes to
Stray congratulations, where's vampire survivors here are the nominees for best action adventure game
A plague tale requiem god of war ragnarok horizon forbidden west stray and tunic and the game award goes to
god of war ragnarok
Here are the nominees for best ongoing game apex legends destiny 2 final fantasy 14
Fortnight and genshin impact and the game award goes to final fantasy 14 the second time tonight
Mr. Fire survivors
If I might watch this i'm just getting mad somebody said
Hey it
Listen
You don't need somebody to tell you
What game you like to play?
You don't need somebody to tell you that
If you like a certain game and it's your game of the year, that's for you to decide
You don't have to let somebody tell you that it's the game of the year. It's you decide that
You decide that lose comes if we keep going to see what it leads
If it's god of war, it's god of war
If it's elden ring, it's elden ring
You can decide fine. Okay. Yeah
Because the chat implodes regardless of who wins plus naoki yoshida takes the stage and the game awards orchestra honors the nominees
for game of the year
Chat like conflict are we still lagging properly? Hopefully it's not too bad
Just
Hey, take a look at that the samsung
ssd
Gaming to i don't even know what number it was doritos triangle island created in fortnight starting tonight
They're challenging fans with a scavenger hunt contest to find one of three hidden doritos chips
Head to doritos instagram or twitter for more details and a chance to win the 990
Hey, i'm van brode from second dinner the developers of marvel snap and we are so excited about our new collaboration with martin garrick's
And jake on this incredible new music video that explores love throughout the multiverse. I thought that was an x I was going to click the top left
I thought that was an x
on the top left of this
Marvel snap was actually pretty fun. It was it's quick
I feel like I can just play like an absolute asshole like just a moron and I could still have fun
It was fun. I don't play it anymore. I played it a little bit when you know
Hell that was fun
Marvel snap was fun
Hello, we have 900 people in here right now. How are you feeling? What's up? Kenzie? I see you out here
What up? What up? What up? My name is Michael Reynolds and I am the fierce diva. Where are you being?
So to me what it means is just being very authentically myself
And apologetically me
My mental health is very important to me for several reasons constantly thought that I was lesser than my peers
I just could never focus but going through that mental health journey with my therapist who I adore
We learned that I had ad d it gave me a whole new perspective on my life and gave me a lot of answers
That I didn't even know how to war wins. I i'm telling you I
I think god of war is going to win game of the year. It hurts honey. I'm telling you
I knew that to usher that experience for folks that really needed it
Thank you for the love for usual the mess for usual if I am inspiring other people to be
I will give all of my energy to elden ring. I don't know then I definitely feel good about that
He drops by every december just like santa give it up for reggie
Hey
So this year
I'm here to present the best game direction category reggie's awesome and it's a particularly
Exciting award, especially in our industry
Games are constantly pushing the boundaries of creativity innovation and artistry
to be nominated
You need to have created an experience that is incredibly special to the players
To the teams represented behind these titles. You have my utmost respect
Here are the nominees for the best game direction
Uh
I'm just saying
For best game direction goes to
elden ring
You know, sometimes things that you like win
If you liked the other category the other nominees then of course
You know, we games are you know, if you like the game you like the game
It's a great pleasure receiving this such a wonderful award
As a director i'm very honored about that
Um
Elden ring is our you know, um, the biggest game that we have ever worked on
um, so
We have worked with uh, several co-directors including mr. Tanimura and mr. Ishizaki
um without their support, um, it's
It would be almost impossible to you know, um finish working on this project
um, so
We really want to share the this great joy of receiving this award with them
It was great. It was just
So once again, thank you so much for your support
The world was huge. There was so much cool shit to do
It seemed like every single piece of that world with somebody hand made it out of clay
You know what? I mean three times you're willing to get burned before you stop trusting someone
How many times you got to take a bullet for these motherfuckers in the name of empty promises?
Medicians military runners intelligence operatives all the rotten fish in one fucking barrel this dogtown
Tell me you've got a plan
not a plan
a man
If there's anyone we can trust now, it's him
salomon reed fia
So what do we do now?
Dogtown burn it to the ground is what we'll do. It's a simple choice
Them or us
Peace comes at a price. Someone's always got to pay
cyberpunk 2077
Usa agent solomon reed in cyberpunk 2077 phantom liberty can't wait for you guys to meet reed
When phantom liberty releases in 2023 see you in night sea
Is this game playable yet? Should I play it? I thanks idris
Tonight we are thrilled to share with you another global game announcement
This comes from one of the most decorated developers in the world who consistently pushes this medium forward
For each of its releases this studio has been nominated multiple times for game of the year here at this very show
And I am beyond grateful that they have chosen the game awards as the place for this
global announcement
Everybody shut up the fallen leaves
Hell, it's not that sorry for those of you that were waiting. Let the light wait. Let the last cinders burn
It might be no it isn't
It's armored core
A lot of people have been waiting for that. I'll take that i'll take it over elven ring dlc, but it's not over yet
I don't know
I have people been waiting a very long time for this
When we come back, it's time to crown the 2022 game of the year
Right here on the game awards. It's not ready. It's not ready
It's all right. It's not ready
Your brother has led it in the dark lands they're under bowser's control a mustachioed human has arrived in the mushroom kingdom
Do you know him do you think I know every human being with a mustache wearing an identical outfit with the letter of his first name on it
Because I don't
I don't I mean elden ring's a big game through december 31st get a freak. It's a huge game
It's probably gonna take a little bit longer
Right. It's there's a lot to do. There's a lot of potential
Story pieces they have to get correct. This is cope. That's fine. It is
That's fine. It is cope. It's gonna win game of the year
Bro, that's fine. It is cope. It is i'm coping right now, but it's gonna win game of the year
And then i'm gonna give you my games of the year. I'm gonna give you what I think
By the way, while I have you here the voting for my awards the end of the year award show
It's gonna be december 17th. I gotta know I got an announcement of my own
December 17th is going to be the christmas holiday show
Featuring the end of the year awards
Also tonight you are going to be able to vote and yes, it is about a week and a half. There's like 10 days
For this or this show
So if you want to vote the poll will be up check my twitter check the discord
I will put it up
You'd be able to vote on all your uh favorite moments of the year or your least favorite moments of the year
Like we do
Be there tonight. Keep an eye on the twitter. Oh and I uh, I might see you this weekend, too
I might see you this weekend, too
Delay daniel my computer it keeps lagging and I don't like it and it makes me angry
Volume up. Yeah. Sorry. I just had to turn that down by the way at the here it comes
we're about to get a
Windows sound
I will blink when it happens. So, you know
You can mute the window sound. Yeah, but I it's it's like three clicks that I don't want to do
I know that's so dumb to hear
That was a look at wild hearts coming from koi tecmo and ea originals next year
And now we welcome one of the busiest men in gaming known fondly by his fans as yoshi p
Both the producer and director of the successful online role-playing game final fantasy 14
winner of two game awards tonight and producer of the highly anticipated new entry and the acclaimed final fantasy franchise
final fantasy 16
Please join me in welcoming for the first time to tga
Mr. Naoki yoshida
What's happening here? What's happening here? What's this?
final fantasy
On behalf of the final fantasy 16 team i'm honored to be here
I'm not on dial-up you it's 7 30. It's tonight people that don't know whatever world premier
to all our fans
Thank you for keeping face in us
I hope I hope you enjoy
our latest trailer
revenge
To safety i'm not going without you all the enemy here while you make your escape
Revenge is a weapon
I sometimes wonder if I am controlling it or if it's audios buck trolling me
No
That audio buried better the truth that awaits me. I got it. I got it press on
Do we do the usual?
13 years i've waited for this chance
I won't be dying today
Very cool
final fantasy 16
It's wait. It's a playstation 5 exclusive. Oh the other ones were weren't they?
Please welcome the director of flight studios game of the year winner for it takes two
Here we go
Don't my internet, please don't crash. This is important
Yeah, really nice being on stage again. Actually, it feels really good
I know I know a lot of people are nervous, but don't be i'm gonna be super cool and short. So
Let's see now. Yeah, I remember recently
Last year winning game of the year, it's a fantastic feeling. So obviously as a nominee
You should be very happy and very proud, but trust me you do want to win because it's a great feeling
but however
You do actually win something the game order is super cool because you know this beautiful orchestra when they play the music from your game
I mean I was sitting over there and trust me the hair all hair on my body was all over the place
no
Goose pump. I mean, it's really awesome. So
Please
Give a big applause to the beautiful orchestra and conducted by long bath
Are we gonna get all right? This isn't this is huge. This is huge
Holy shit
Come on internet. You just have to get through the next five minutes
shit
please
Please I just want my internet to work
I'm telling you right now if this doesn't work out i'm gonna be fucking furious
Come on
The earthquake is happening
Come on, man
He's losing his mind
What did I say?
who wins
the game of the year
Goose pump. I told you. All right
game of the year winner
is
elder
They won they did it they did it they did it. Oh they won. Yes
Woo, dude somebody
Somebody said you are so unfunny. I'm so sorry. Did you hate me? I'm sorry
Thank you so much
People are strangling each other in that discord
I would like to share this great appreciation
With our entire air landing team members everybody at from software our partner bandai namco
All collaborators and last but least mr. Joyart martin who created the great mythos for this game
Now that all jokes aside is actually
probably
I mean, I don't think an experience will come out for a while
I can match that
A lot of good things did come out this year though
We have faced so many difficulties while developing this game so as a director i'm really relieved
And this might not be the you know light thing to say
at the you know, the on occasion of the
Receiving the goatee award, but I haven't made up my mind to create even more interesting games than this one
I mean it's
As for elderling we still have several more things we want to do
Um, so this getting this goatee award lily lily and college us
You can't vote for that
You can't vote for the shitting my pants when elden ring wins the poll is closed
And finally, um actually awesome awesome job, you know, um express our utmost gratitude to all the fans
Who played who enjoyed and who supported this titles was that bad?
Um, and we create the games we want to create and do our best because of you
Um, thank you so much
Hey martin
That was actually deserved i want to thank everybody and say that I think I want to nominate
This award to my reformed orthodox read by bill clinton. Thank you everybody
What was
But what all right what's happening?
The vet believed in congratulations. This has been such a special night
And I can't believe what is happening that next year 2023 marks the 10th annual game awards
So we are lucky to do this every year
And we want to thank all the industry for their support and of course all of you around the world viewers of the show tonight
I do have one last special announcement from us to celebrate our 10th year
The game awards is thrilled to be partnering with the la phil for a very special evening of video game music
Performed live at the world famous hollywood bowl next year on june 25th
2023 we'll be celebrating the past decade of video game music and looking ahead to its future
Let's go hearing much more about this historic collaboration early next year until then. Thank you so much
Have a safe and happy holiday season and we'll see you in 2023. Good night everybody. Very cool
I need to examine something really quickly though
I mean my internet's a piece of shit right now
But I need to I need to see just how bad this was if I allow it into the awards, which i'm not going to
I'm not going to but I need to see how bad it was
You have to allow it. No, I can't I can't do that
All right. This is pretty cool stuff this year. First of all vampire survivors
I think is probably top three in game of the year. I think wait. What did I even say?
You're a man of your word. What did I say? Wait, let me I gotta put it on stream. Let's examine this
Goosebumps, okay. I'm gonna I'm gonna go away for a second
That was scary
Scary
You can see i'm getting ready to press the button. This is this motherfucker right here
Is about to press the fart button and that now those are i'm pressing the fart button eyes
I told you game of the year
winner is
Elder
They won
Okay, the fact the fact that it was
The fact that it was that one. I couldn't even hear it. Everything was so loud
I just I just clicked on the first one
Fart sound effect. I'm sorry. I'm really sorry. That was naughty
They won they did it i'm sorry I can't put it in like I can't put it in the awards
I'm sorry
Why would somebody do that?
Imagine you're watching this with a bunch of friends
You're in
You're like five or six you're on the couch
And one of your friends is just like dude. Ah, man, if elden ring wins, i'll shit my pants
That's so funny. You're such a goofy guy
Yeah, you're so what a character that guy is and then the announcement of elden ring happens and this motherfucker does this
Elden ring
Well that was the game awards but I do have to tell you who I think should have won
Right. You're a coward. It's fecal funny. I
It's so childish and it's not it's so it's such a basic joke to make too. Anyways, so oh, I think that um
Vampire survivors was a good game this year. I also think that elden ring was better
One or two, I think yeah, how do I what do I even do for how do I go from here elden ring vampire survivors?
What else did I say? It was three scorn didn't win anything. Yeah, I know my internet's a mess right now
But thanks for watching that. I'm sorry. I was I was late. I've been doing a lot of shit
There's a lot of stuff going on. I will see you this weekend. Maybe just follow my twitter
I would follow the twitter if you don't grotto beast is so close christmas show is coming here
17th of december is going to be great. There's a lot going on
Um and working a lot and trying to get some of this stuff ready poll for the award show
Will be live tonight. So if you want to vote on that there's a lot
I will say that
Um, it's always funny to go through the nominees and uh, cause like and huge shout out to the mods too the mods
Did so much
This there was so many submissions and then obviously me going through them too did you know have to narrow them down
but
It's always funny to do these because when you do when you have something like best impression and worst impression the best impression category had
you know
10 to 15 nominees the worst impression category had like
After you know the first few passes so trying to
Worst noise I think had like 70 nominees even after going through it a few times, but it's in a place
Where we're it looks pretty good
So you'll see it take your time on it. You've got eight or nine days ten days
Which just doesn't sound like a lot of time because it's not i'll see you soon. Thanks for watching. I'm gonna go
I know my internet sucks. I I was thinking about
Changing over to like frog detective, but it's it's a mess right now past 7 38 o'clock
So I've been streaming earlier. But yeah, I will see you next time. You will see me will be this weekend. I'll see you
You'll see
Um, i'm sure you'll see it. It'll probably get announced soon. Maybe i'll announce it on twitter follow the twitter
If you don't follow my twitter or um, you know, just when I go live tweets and sponsor ads
Sometimes I read my drafts
So that's good
All right. Uh
So let me let's raid let's raid somebody who we're raiding. Let me see who's live. Thanks for watching though
It's always fun to do this
Uh a lot of great games this year. I gotta play god of war
I have to it
I feel like god of war is one of those games where you you gotta play it to get it, right?
It's like oh man, it's
God of war won like seven categories like what the fuck but I i've never played it
I'm sure I probably would feel pretty strongly about it if I played it. I've played the first one a little bit
It's amazing
The first two or three hours of that game is what I've experienced. Maybe a little bit more. It was awesome
I don't know. I don't know. All right, where are we going? Who's live? Let's see. I'm gonna pick somebody here
Who is currently live? Oh dwarf fortress. Is that game good? I've seen people playing it
italics is playing it right now
Did I just dump you guys on italics? Yeah, let's go. It's been a while since you raided italics. Go say hi to italics
He's playing dwarf dwarf fortress
Uh be good be nice be be good be nice. But yeah, i'll see you guys this weekend. See you later
Go say hi to italics dwarf fortress. I'll see you guys soon. Take care. See you later. Goodbye
sorry for the that it's not worst joke of the year this is this is in the the
The zone where you can't nominate things. I'm sorry. Good night guys. See you later. I'll see you this weekend
Oh my god, that's a lot of subs. Holy shit. That's actually a ton of subs. How many subs came in today?
Well, thanks guys appreciate it the next time I will be live on my channel
That's a good actually good point the next time i'll be live on my channel will be probably
the I want to say
Maybe tuesday the 13th wednesday the 14th. We'll do a couple of things
And I will tell you this. I want to make sure this is clear too. Once some of these shows are done
Especially uh the christmas one the christmas there's a lot happening with the christmas without going into it
So once the christmas show is done, we're gonna get back to normal here
We'll do some we'll i'll make sure to it's been kind of erratic the last couple months. I'm aware of that
Oh shit
Never mind everybody's gone
Well, see you later. See you later. Bye everybody. Whoops. Good night everybody