Gemma985 is filmed in front of a live studio audience.
Okay, let me get things all settled here. Got my microphone, I got everything set, got the gameplay, ready to record.
Alright, let's do it.
Ahem, ahem.
Hey, what is going on everybody? Jermi-
Oh, making a commentary?
Well, I was trying to until I was rudely interrupted.
No, but seriously, man, you look stressed. What's, uh, what's wrong?
Ah, yeah, just got back from the grocery store. The lines were really long, but I managed to pick up some fruits and vegetables on the way home.
Oh, I'm gonna be making some of my famous chicken pot pie.
Oh boy, looks like we're doing takeout again tonight.
Why wasn't I invited in the shindig?
Boon, I didn't know you were coming over. God, I had so many interruptions. I'm never gonna get this commentary.
Um, guys, this isn't part of the video right now. I just got a phone call.
Um, everybody I've ever met in my life is in the hospital right now. I have to go.
Pizza? I didn't think we were gonna get pizza. Hang on, I'll be right back. I'm gonna get my wallet.
Let's, uh, let's do this commentary now. I can sit down, I can actually do this freaking thing. I don't have to keep getting interrupted by people, so-
Hey, motherfucker! It's me, Grandpa!
What are you doing?
Um, working on a commentary, actually.
Oh yeah, working on a commentary. Look at me! My name is Gerber! Working on a commentary! Look at how smart I am!
Yeah, that's- I'm trying to get it done, so I would appreciate it if you just took off for a little while, Grandpa.
That's okay, I'll leave you to your work.
Cause I- I'll just leave you to your work. I'm gonna make sure-
Don't- I- Tonight can you hear me talk? I didn't even say anything funny! Shut the fuck up!
I forgot my line. They really just screwed me over right there.
You know what I'm saying? Thank you! Thank you, studio audience! You really fucked it all up for me!
Yeah, you know what that is? That's the double middle finger. You can laugh all you want, I don't give a shit. I'm outta here.
Alright, well, see you later.
Can I finally get this thing done? For Pete's sake, here we go.
Hey, what is going on everybody? Gerber here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as the Soldier with me, and that's it!