Morning, how you doing? Remember the golden rule of this channel. If one minute has gone by and
Jerma does not say something, he's dead. It's a golden rule here. A full minute has passed,
he has not spoken. He's dead. He had to have died. It's true. Hey, how you doing everybody? Welcome
to the stream. We're gonna do DLC movie night part two. We have well over a hundred plus more
videos to watch. Told you last weekend we were going to do it exactly one full week from,
you know, there. Here we are. I have to apologize because of yesterday. Those of you that were
watching the stream yesterday, the power went out and I didn't come back for a pretty long fucking
time. So sorry about the power going out and I couldn't even reply to you guys. I couldn't even
get in there because it killed my, uh, obviously killed my modem and my router. So I was just on
data, like just phone data. And when the power goes out somewhere, it kills everybody's router.
So every single person in this entire area, all at the same time, switched to data mode
and called somebody. So I'm trying to like get in line in like the data queue at the tower
and I'm trying to tell you guys, Hey, the power, I don't even know if it went through.
It's like when you land in an airplane and you land and everybody ding. Okay. Every fucking phone
comes up in the seat. The second you land and it's like, wait, why do I have no service?
No, I'm trying to get through. Can you hear me? Hello? Okay. Times that by like 50,000.
That's not how it works. It is in my head. So that's what it is. Hmm. Never thought about it
like that. Yeah. As you still have to connect to something. So do you know how the infrastructure
works used? It doesn't, it's not a magic trick. You have to connect to the tower.
And if you, if like 10,000 connections go to the same time to the tower, you get, sorry,
you don't get to go. You get a call drop. You get the five G. What about five G? Yeah. Who knows?
Maybe five G will solve this problem. Frog damp moment. All right. Frog damp moment. Apparently.
Hold on. Let me show it. Yeah. I'm, we're going to stall a little bit because I want people to get
in here because people want to watch this stuff. I'm not going to be like, Hey guys, welcome to
stream. Oh, video. No, we're going to wait. You got to wait like a minute or two, five minutes.
Hurry up. It's, it would just, I just know you hurry up and sit down. You hurry up and sit down
for a little bit. And that like a peasant NPC. It really is. It sucks how much of a peasant NPC
this is. Can you get an emote? No, it already is an emote. You just jump scared.
All right. I'm going to move. Well, okay. Are you ready? It's been five minutes.
Am I going to play custom robo again? This probably, I feel like we were just starting
to get into it. The worst part about when your power goes out, this is the worst thing about
power going out. You do it. You think that your house may have exploded, right? So you're just
sitting there. I was mid sentence. I got monitors on. I got an AC running and all of a sudden,
like a light is on and you just, Oh yeah. What happened to my dad? Did something explode? No.
Okay. What happened? Oh, the power's gone. It's when you don't, and this is when nothing happened
at all. Oh wait, there's a big snowstorm. Oh, tons of rain. Something must have, oh weather. No.
You're just sitting around and nothing, there's nothing wrong. Okay. Yes. Every power outage is
personalized. Yeah. It was weird. And then you get, you start freaking out because it starts turning
back on and off and on and off over and over again. And then you run around like a psychopath
unplugging everything in your whole house. Oh fuck.
Fuck. I got to plug that thing. I was like, that thing's toast. And then I, I smell something. I
something's burning. I smell electricity. Like you're fine. I go and unplug everything. What's
the matter with them? That that's a power going on and off. And then you start smelling electricity.
Yeah. I freak out as I don't even like to use the oven. I think the oven's scary.
Are you really this surprised that I don't like power outages?
I'm like a small dog in personality. Do I know what it is? Cool. I love it.
Does something startle me? Do you, did you walk into the house with my favorite toy and costume?
Did you walk into the house with a Gumby outfit on and you're going to freak me out?
Anyways, let's watch the movie. The literal man child. No, I'm a little dog child. I'm a man dog.
I'm a dog man, but not in the sense that you like not, oh, he's like a furry. No, no, no. I'm just,
I'm a dog man. I have the dog brain. There you go. No, I'm not a dog. I'm not an anthropomorphic dog.
I am a person with a dog's brain. Clarify that. Okay. You ready? Here we go. Free. This is called,
this is the germ-tastic voyage. Ready? Let's go. What? The plan is one shrink ray,
go to the heart, kill the virus and extract. Holy shit. That was loud. Oh, my butthole. All right.
Okay. This is the Osmosis Jones.
Yeah.
All right. I just took like a big, hold on. I just took a big gulp. I just, I just took a
full sip of water and like laughed internally and just almost exploded my head. I almost just did
what happened in the video when it happened in the video. Look at the painting. Look at the,
all right. I'll go over this really quickly. I'm going to go over this very quickly.
I don't know how real this, look, this could be real. I don't know. But apparently this is the
Chuck E. Cheese stock price the day that I streamed and Chuck E. Cheese came in.
This is apparently real. I don't, I have nothing to do with this. I don't know. I don't, look,
I didn't ask for this. Coming up next is average life of car germa.
Is good. Only a few of these left in existence. I'm certain of that and I'm giving it to you.
That's right. Take it. It's yours. Don't sell it though. I don't know.
Hi. Hi. Hello. Yes. How are you? Black screen. Shut up. Shut up. Is this supposed to be a video?
This is ridiculous. You catch up to it's like this every single day. And I'm sick and tired of
hearing. Do you want, I don't know. Do you want it here? I can hear you all the way up here.
Take it. And I pay rent too. Take it. Take this. Take this from me. Take this from me. Take this
from me right now. Take it from me. Take it from me dude. I don't want to fucking hold it anymore.
Okay. That was just, I was odd. I could describe that one as odd.
First of all, we had 10 community subs from Minty Fox and 10 from hallowed guru.
Thanks both of you. Would the subs, 10 subs each. Welcome to the sub crew. Thanks guys.
Really appreciate it. Half life streamer. This is for the sub crew. YouTuber. Hey,
you're part of the sub crew now. That's right. You paid me $5. Now you're part of
an exclusive club. Oh, the other people that don't pay the $5. This is not allowed in.
No, no boys allowed. Damn it. It's like,
I'd like to report a accident. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, three.
Here we get invaded while playing dark souls. Oh, the Twitch watcher. What am I drinking? That is
water with a little bit of lemon. It just gives it just enough to a little bit of a kick.
Stay right there. Was that two? Was that you guys? Was that somebody in chat?
Did I just get stream sniped? That was amazing.
This is, wait, this is before we even had the Chuck E cheese arc on the channel.
Remember ruins my fit for, I want to watch that one again. At least from here. A little bit of
lemon. It just gives it just enough to a little bit of a kick. The best part is when you edited my
head going all the way backwards, I can't even see the game. Don't do it.
Don't please stay right there. Was that two? Was that you guys? Was that somebody in chat?
Did I just get stream sniped? Uh, yes. The answer is always yes. Why even ask that question? All
right. Derma ruins my birthday. Oh, we stuck here forever. All right. Derma ruins my fifth birthday
and loses his job.
I'm not a real dinosaur.
Oh, please put it in. Did you get put, did you put big birthday in here?
Do it fucking right. Oh my God. So bad. Die you motherfucker.
Stupid ass. So I appreciate. All right. I appreciate the, um, I appreciate that I'm only 500 pounds
thing. What the hell was that? What the hell was that? What just, what just popped up over there?
What was that trying to capture? A real ghost on camera. Wait, did that not pop up for you?
Okay. Okay. Uh, that was the ghost. I have no idea. All right. Anyways, what was I going to say?
Who cares? I don't know what the fuck I was going to say. Let's go. This is Derma's Europe trip.
This is, this is Russia. Like I'm, I'm not going to Russia. Like I'm not going to go to Russia.
We're going to start here. Plane's going to come in. It's going to go like, this is a different
color for the plane, right? Like it's yellow. Here's where the plane comes in. This is Spain.
Wrapping around into England. We stop on England. I'm going to say we stop in London for like a
couple of days. Hey everybody. Guess where I am. Hey mom. Mom, I see it. Yeah. Wow.
And then on the way out of London, we get up Greece. Greece is right there. Here's the worst
part. I don't know where any of these places, what any of these places are. I don't even care
if I win. She's the Russian colors. Wrap around to Italy, come down to Italy all the way to the
bottom of the boot. But I want to see, I want to see the bottom of the boot. You know what I mean?
I want to piss off the bottom of the boot.
One earbud left only.
Still going to be, we're going to be the bottom of the boot in Italy for like at least a week.
So we got like two days. We got one W here, one week, all the way wrapping around into,
this is Lithuania here. I want to go to Lithuania for like at least a month. I want to spend
some time there, want to learn the color, learn the language, I guess. I was trying to say learn
the culture. Stupid. That could have been TOS. I have no idea what they said. All the way up to,
uh, I mean I have some ancestry. So I mean Ireland is a good place to stop.
And I'm going to stop in Ireland for maybe like a couple of days, like maybe two days.
Wow. He's shooting arrows. That's cool. Are there archers up there?
No, the main channel's not dead. It's in a museum.
Hello there, ladies and gentlemen. It's crap, aren't you? You haven't seen me in a while,
but you know what? Fuck you.
FPK's coming back next weekend, by the way. Those of you that want to join in.
Looks pretty dire for Jerma as well. Looks like he may have at least one broken bone here,
as the EMT is going to pick him up and get him on that journey. Is this my thoughts?
And then we're going to go, we're going to take off. So here we go. Like we take off from Ireland
up to here. And here is Iceland. And we're going to, this is going to be blue because it's cold.
Arming. Stopping Iceland. Arming.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of JermaCraft, the series where I play Minecraft.
This is going to be a single player. Let's play. You know, I'm going to piss off,
I'm going to piss off the ice and I piss off the edge and then come all the way back around.
Of course, go all the way back around to America, which is over this way.
Back to America, flying over Russia.
I have a comment on this. That's my trip that I'm going to take.
I have a quick comment. I thought for some reason, I don't know why, don't ask me. I get it,
right? I know what this is for, but I for some reason thought that this was them censoring out
me having a huge, huge elephant. Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode off the edge.
You know what I'm saying? I was like, holy shit, dude. I'm like, this is not P. This is so like,
what the hell are you implying here? This is P. I get it. P coming down the edge and then come all
the way back around. Of course, go all the way back around to America, which is over this way.
Such good sports back to America, flying over Russia.
And that's, that's my trip that I'm going to take.
All right. Dermot deserves a family of wild animals.
What the fuck? Holy shit, dude. This is by far, this is the best part right here.
You got something to say?
Dermot gets rejected on The Bachelorette. This man doesn't see it coming. He's going to
feel so blindsided. It makes me feel so terrible. Oh fuck. Oh man. This is like spilled water on
myself. This is not even. Hi. Hey. Very nice. Incredible. And I'm giving it to you. That's
right. Take it. Take this from me right now. Take it from me. Take it from me, dude. I don't want to
fucking hold it anymore. Take it from me. Take this thing out of my fucking hands before I freak
out. There's just one piece with somebody else that I am not ready to say goodbye to yet.
I think that there's just a better fit for us. Awesome. Oh, yes. A baseball one.
I can't wait to hit like two home runs. The unfortunate Jermariner's game. Jermariner's.
This is not a baseball one. I'm not hitting a grand slam. What is this? This is bullshit.
Why are they going so far? He's catching his own ball?
It's out of the park.
Picture. Oh boy.
The fuck is going on? Are they on different teams?
Yes.
Quit.
Oh shit. It's coming real fast. Yeah. Funny.
Holy shit. That was absolutely insane. I need like a minute just to process the last one.
So there's three teams. Team one was the white and then gray and then red. There was only two to
know it was the umpire. Okay. That was not. One was the ref. Can't wait to do the baseball stream.
It's going to be so much fun. I can't wait. You like my hair today? It's funny you mentioned that
because I sat down here like an hour ago and I had mustache hair. So I was like, how the,
I can't get to ever do what I wanted to. So I wet my hair and just buried the comb in and just went
over, over, over, over, over. And then I sat down and went, okay, that looks okay.
In about an hour, remember this, in like an hour or two, all roads lead back to mustache hair.
As you see, it's already forming. You see that? Do you see it forming already?
All roads lead to mustache hair. All. I'll check back in a little bit and we'll see.
This is uh, German goes to the mayor.
Excuse me. German nine eight is here. Okay. Let's see what we have here. Mayor. Michael.
So Michael, can you tell me you're a doctor of energy now? Yeah, it's a great gig and you are
not going to believe the car they just gave me. Not a LeBaron. Oh, watch the show by the way.
I mean, you probably have no idea what the fuck's going on, but I think that's
okay. So what the hell is this? So Tom goes to the mayor is the Tim and Eric's
first real show that they really had on TV. It's worth watching.
They had a lot of just random celebrity guests that would just show up. It was pretty cool.
It was really fun. All right. What is this? What is this? But German escaped.
Oh, now everybody online say that this is the best thing.
This better be transformative or I'm going to be upset about this.
It definitely feels gentle. I definitely can't wait to get home and use the lawnmower.
Is this an ad? Did we have to see this one? Oh, skip it. What? Wait, what? Why were the beginning?
Hold on. How did I get to the beginning of the playlist? What button did I press? What did I do?
What did I do? Did I press like, did I freak out and press like the start over button?
All right. We're good. We're good. Hold on. Where are we? I think that video was removed from the
playlist when I clicked on it. It's not here anymore. I'll prove it. Ready? This is germ goes
to the mayor. Okay. You ready? Germ goes to the mayor. What's right after germ goes to the mayor?
You know, all right. Anyways, I got yoinked. Oh my God. It never happened. It never existed.
Weird. All right. Well, anyways, it's lost media. This is the germ saw killer, a German 95 green
screen thriller. Okay. Here comes like probably the entire first movie trailer or three trailer.
I don't know. It's probably the whole entire movie. Here comes saw spoilers. Be aware. Be aware.
And I know what one there's like 10 of them at this point. Like it's like saying in the
Jason movies that Jason kills people. There's been like 10 of those two. Is that a spoiler
saying that like, Oh, Jason Voorhees is Mr. Voorhees and he kills people at the camp.
He does that in every movie. Guess what? And saw he's going to like carve up somebody's head.
He's going to like stuff. Somebody's brain full of like a, uh, and either brain and shit. I don't
know. Let's go. You remember what's going on with this crap. What are you? I was just kidding. Look,
finally. What is this?
Absolutely acceptable. Good question. We've just tried to get the key out of your ass.
What have your sternum or your eye, whatever I decided to put it?
No, no, no. I actually, that was me. This is a dream. This is a dream. A dream.
Make your choice. Make your choice.
You sick fuck. Oh yeah. Like, uh, five wires. That's what it is. What the fuck?
Yeah, whatever. Just put it on the top. Oh, what are you, uh, you're ordering food. Okay.
Can you get me some food?
How am I supposed to get a key out of my stomach? You don't even give me anything.
What am I supposed to do with my hands?
Woot. Yeah. It was the most work I've ever done in my life.
Oh no. Okay. Oh, just right there. Just right there.
You ran and ran and as his legs grew, he glided over the desert earth.
Oh, I feel like somebody like ordered this. Don't you feel like somebody ordered this?
Fulfilling an order. My order. So please hand them over. Thank you. Goodbye.
That was very, very good. I'm so glad somebody did this. I did like 40 minutes of soft footage
and use once. I'm going to be really, really sad if this is the only soft footage that we get.
I spent a good 40 minutes doing it. And Hey, even if, if this is the only one worth it,
worth it. It's worth it. Uh, German's unusual hobby.
Is this some kind of sick joke? Kiss my ass. That's a pretty good, pretty good view.
I don't know what this is. I'm just going with it. I don't know what I'm supposed to be doing.
I feel like I'm a baby in a car scene.
Okay. That was interesting. Uh, this is Germoyal versus the Death Eaters.
I can already see that. Okay. I would have lost the Where's Waldo initially.
You know, something is so obvious, but you just have no idea that it's there.
This was not here in my brain. Here comes spoilers. Yes, this is going to be Harry Potter spoilers.
If you've never seen Harry Potter. Oh, by the way, the rules have been updated
for green screen footage that I'm going to show on this stream. Here comes Harry Potter,
something late game Harry Potter, by the way. I'm, I'm assuming because they're not eight,
right? That's how you tell when you're going to get a real deep Harry Potter spoiler.
How old is he? Okay. He's like, he's like 18 or 19 in this picture. That's deep,
late game Harry Potter spoilers. I've had all the essentials packed for days.
Just in case. By the way, these jeans, not my favorite.
Harry, hurry.
I just, I just hit him right in the skull. I just cracked his skull.
Oh no, my cloak. Quick, into the castle. Get the lights.
He was on the astronomy tower the night Snape killed Dumbledore.
This is dollar hop. I reckon this is for the water posters. Disgusting.
So what are we going to do with you, eh? Kill us if we turn around, won't you?
We killed them the moment we were here. Harry, Harry, it's time.
Give me some leverage here. How would you feel then?
Thank you. On the count of three. It's better we wipe their memories.
One. You're the boss.
Two. Three.
You're the best of spells. What am I even doing here?
It's G to five. I'm not even here. Other words they say.
Oh my God. Damn it. My fucking head hurts. I hit him in his skull. Oh, okay.
This is German on the run. FMV game parody. Water out of the toilet.
After a long day of work, Yereminin85 tried to rest a bit. When suddenly.
Delete.
Uh oh. I thought my computer crashed. This is my actual background.
I thought that everything crashed. That was crazy. Wait, it's round two. All right.
You got to get it right this time though. The giant enemy.
Russian German.
The giant enemy. Russian German.
What's even going on? We haven't seen very many Russian German either.
I did that for a while. All right. Come on. Come on. Oh wow.
I don't want to hear any. All right. This is German.
The German family goes to McDonald's. Another McDonald's one.
This is a, this is a long one. Let's see.
And I don't want to hear any. Hey, I want to go to McDonald's.
I want to go to McDonald's. I want to go to Wendy's too.
Buckle up. Mom, I want to go to both.
Mom, McDonald's. Shit, nice smoothie.
Nice smoothie. Shit.
Only McDonald's. We're a McDonald's family for Christ's sake.
We only eat McDonald's. Dad, Jimmy, and mom.
Wait, why are we changing cars?
Why are there so many of us?
Sunny day outside. Safe to me.
I'm full. And I don't want to hear anybody talking.
Go ahead and get out of the way. Leave your dear old dad here.
Let me just relax. Nice smoothie.
Nice and smooth. Smooth.
I know. I love left-hand turns. Maybe I should try going right.
But I can't. I've always gone left.
I was going a big square. I can't.
Okay, this time, this time, you can do it. You can go right.
Hey, fellas, I'm going to go right.
Are they okay? I think I'm the Superman.
You okay? Hey, you all right in there?
Hello, who's this? Yes, yeah, I'd like to report an accident.
Sorry. Yeah, I'm on 12345678910th Street.
I punched a car and it crushed me. I think I'm at a supercar accident.
No, don't tell the government about that.
That was really unfunny. I really wish I knew how to delete things off that thing.
That was terrible. Don't use that. Don't use any of that.
Don't even bother. Is this another actor?
Was that an actor? A self-insert?
Was it? Oh, come on.
What did I say? Rule? What was rule one?
What was the number one rule? I said it earlier.
What was it? I don't remember what the number one rule is.
I said it like an hour ago. What is it?
You didn't say? Yeah, I talked about like the rule.
Yeah, okay. No, no.
You actually didn't say what the number one rule was.
I did. I talked about the number one thing.
All right. Well, the number two thing is,
you're not allowed to be a better actor than me on my own stream.
You said there are new rules. Oh, right.
Okay. Well, rule two, you're not allowed to be a better actor than me.
Since its inception, hundreds of TV...
Okay, this is the Adventures of Cartwheel, Germa, and Orange Froglodyte.
Mystery of the Fun Fair. Wait.
Is this a spin-off or is this a copy of the show?
Germa and Purple Alien. This is a spin-off.
Cartwheel, Germa, and Orange Froglodyte.
This is a fine fighting duo against a briefly athletic man named Kaden.
This was canned so badly by the critics.
It's a Purple Alien spin-off.
It is. What is it? The same guy?
Pog. Did that person stem a new genre?
They couldn't talk.
Fuck.
Unfair time.
God damn it.
Watch out.
Gamer. The Mega Prize.
Be continued after these messages.
Uh oh.
It was actually... Okay.
We should watch the whole thing apparently.
Part two.
Mystery of the Fun Fair.
Let's just play an ad.
What is it? No more sequels.
No more sequels.
We want remakes.
I want a remake of Germa...
Germa is short.
He's 5'2".
It's too many.
Uh oh. You fucked with the toy.
Nice.
We're gonna get a final battle?
No.
But he got away.
That's not good. That has to be a part three.
It's up in the event.
Is it the end?
After credit scene.
Has to be.
But wait a minute.
What? But the villain got away with it.
It's gonna be a part three.
It'll be a sequel.
Man, I really can't wait for green Germa.
And crawling Germa.
That's gonna be great when we see that one.
Green Cucumber and crawling Germa.
I'm going to kill you.
No.
One, two, three, break it down.
Get busy.
You think I can do that, didn't you?
One, two, three, kick it.
What?
I'm sorry.
Following motion picture,
Yopla's topsy turvy
has been approved by someone without any authority to do so.
Whose resemblance to anyone living or dead is merely a coincidence.
It's supposed to be...
All right, here we go.
Yopla's topsy turvy.
Germa edition.
This is not...
It's topless.
It's very clearly not a T.
Okay, that...
No, it's not like...
I don't have like boobs or anything.
It's all right.
Ready?
T-pants production.
What is he driving?
A chair?
Wait, what was that?
What the hell is happening in this video?
Your movie.
From the movies,
you did a shot-for-shot remake.
It's a shot-for-shot remake.
Sorry.
What do you want me to do so I put my arms on my sides?
Transformers.
Transform into...
Object of flight.
Ow!
My fucking bones!
We're not just psychoporate.
That's Baby Joker.
Okay.
I had no idea what was going on.
Until about a minute and 45 seconds ago.
Guys, I even thought that this person...
Oh, topless.
Yes, right.
This is...
I made this movie.
How long ago was that, though?
If it was more than a year ago, it doesn't exist.
In my brain.
Like three, five years ago.
Well, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Watch the original one.
All right.
Yeah, hold on.
Let's watch the original.
I'm actually curious about this.
Let's see how close...
How correct this was.
Enjoy it.
Do it side by side.
I...
I'm not going to be able to cue that up.
All right.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me...
I'll put them side by side.
All right.
Hold on.
I'll put them side by side.
Are they timed correctly, though?
The beginning?
Okay.
Hold on.
Let me get this right.
I'll put them side by side.
All right.
You know what?
Let me do this.
It's not shot for shot.
Oh, it's not.
Oh, it's not shot for shot.
Okay.
All right.
We'll just watch...
We'll watch the original.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
It's not cued up correctly.
On your own...
On your own time.
All right.
Let's go.
Not shot for shot.
Oh, man.
I'm curious.
Let's watch it.
Enjoy it.
When are you going to get the playlist?
After the...
At the end of their stream today.
Chair.
Okay.
I remember the chair.
That was accurate.
Dearly beloved,
we are gathered here today
to incorporate
our final testament to this man,
this wonderful man that lies before us.
His name was Harold Slunk
and he was my best friend.
And can somebody turn that fucking music off, please?
Thank you.
As I was saying,
Harold was a good friend of mine.
Lost my heart,
hope, and I a promise that's real.
And I'm just going to miss him so fucking much.
I'm going to miss him more than anything.
And by the way,
after this, I'll see you at Fridays for two set wings.
That was the joke.
This is fucking terrible.
This is the worst one ever.
It really kind of was.
That was the worst fucking one.
That was probably the worst one.
Moving on.
Because we do have a shitload more videos to watch.
Up next.
Irma says hello in the fight.
I don't know what the fight is.
Ever seen it?
Don't know.
Spoilers.
Spoilers with the fight.
Got it.
I was scooped.
I almost did.
Keying.
Turkey arms.
Balloon.
Fuck off.
Okay.
All right, so he won.
Is there more?
There's more.
I was 18.
I found myself in the high school dance.
Nervous for all of us.
Except on this particular day.
He didn't do anything.
That is, I believe what we just watched is
shit, gotta make deadline.
Gotta hit export.
It was good though.
Yeah.
I'm really enjoying the school dance.
Should I come a little closer?
Wait, what am I doing?
Am I choking?
So do you have a math homework?
Do you have to do this one?
What the fuck are you doing?
Yeah, I have to do this because she's the worst.
Entering the ring first.
We have the bad boy, Joey Jamila.
Wait, what is this?
This is another, wait, this is a bunch of actors.
This is all actors?
And his opponent.
Entering the ring.
From Boston, Massachusetts, Jerma985.
You're the one I'm gonna get.
This is the versus the invisible man.
Okay, yes, yes, I know this.
I've seen this.
I didn't want to, I didn't want to knock this, but I did.
That's my little type.
You can't do this to me.
Ow, do you have any idea who I am?
Yeah, Jerma985, look me up.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Wait.
Joey Jamila.
Don't move.
It's hard, man.
He's up top.
Oh, he's rolled up.
And your winner, the challenger, Jerma985.
That's the song, that's the song.
I don't believe in babies.
That's what babies do.
Oh, and Jerma, go for it, come on, cheap shots.
All right, put the camera, get this guy on the ring.
Oh my God.
Hold on, I want to see the roll up again.
Entering the.
That roll up is so good.
Oh, he's rolled up.
Babies do that.
Okay, that was awesome.
Jerma sits down for dinner with his family.
We saw this already.
No, did we see this exact one?
I don't think we saw this one.
Okay, yeah, so what do we have tonight?
Look at that.
Delicious.
Potatoes, mashed potatoes and gravy.
You've about done yourself.
You pass the salt.
Don't throw it over here.
What about just a sicko?
Okay, so how was your day, son?
Wow, in class.
That's unbelievable, Susie.
My kids, my kids are the smartest, straight A's.
He's like, this is sad.
That's a little tough, I think, a little tough.
A little overdone, but it's still good.
This is scary and sad and horrible.
Well, my day was pretty interesting.
I got fired.
I can't even like watch it, it's so fucked up.
Yep, and then I got hired.
Oh my God.
I had a company next door.
Just walked out, brought my briefcase in.
This is the TLT guy, perfect.
Oh my God, I'm so happy.
Ah, hold on, I need to take a second.
That hurt.
Oh, that's like scared me.
Oh, we're not even halfway.
All right, all right, let's go again.
The timing was perfect on that too, by the way.
Like very stellar editing here.
Well, my day was pretty interesting.
I got fired.
Yep, and then I got hired by the company next door.
Just walked out, brought my briefcase in.
This is the TLT guy, perfect.
Oh my God, I'm so happy.
What is this?
What?
Oh, boy.
Oh no, so loud.
Shut up, shut up.
Get out, go back, back into the scene, come on.
So I heard, who's you got to fight today, son?
Okay.
Let me tell you something.
If you can do not do it diplomatically,
then you shouldn't be doing it at all.
We only eat McDonald's.
I want to go to McDonald's.
Gravy, potatoes, meat, cheese, onions, tomatoes, peppers.
Well, I mean, it's kind of insane.
I heard that you punched him.
Did you?
You punched him?
You punched him in the face?
My son doesn't do that.
Diplomacy only.
You know how much trouble I could get in?
I'm in the gosh darn.
I'm getting heated here.
My son, a United States representative.
I'm your dad.
I'm the representative, not you.
That would be strange now, wouldn't it?
You got to do things diplomatically.
Or you're grounded.
No, you know what?
I'll handle it.
You are grounded.
You're grounded.
We don't fight in this family.
Eat your gosh darn.
I keep saying that stuff and I don't want to.
Now listen, family.
If we could join hands.
No?
Okay.
Is that it?
Wait, what?
Somebody said, this is a scene you'd see at the Oscars for a nominee.
Yeah, it kind of is, isn't it?
Happy birthday.
Oh, God.
All chairs turn.
I already know.
I've seen the whole video.
I don't even need to see it, but I'm still laughing about it.
Happy birthday to you.
Everybody, come on.
Happy birthday, dear.
Birthday.
God damn it, it was so close.
It was so close.
I was spooked.
I almost did.
This thing we have ever had on the show.
The blood is rushing through my entire body.
Who are you?
What's your name?
I think a collective, it was a whole performance.
It was like completely captivating.
I believed everything you were doing.
It was like, it was a real trance.
I'm so excited.
You have to be on my team.
Really important not to like discredit too is that you're a performer.
You're like, you're not just hiding behind anything.
Like you were moving, you were singing, you're a great vocalist.
Don't break my heart.
That'll be $200.
Holy shit.
Wait a minute.
What does this say at the top of the screen?
Quick, German, green alien.
Wait, what?
No, wait, hold on a second.
I thought that was this German.
This is, wait, this is another one.
This is the one.
What am I just talking about this?
Shit dick.
Quick, German and green alien, right?
Bitch.
It's time to get punished.
Oh, excuse me.
Why are there so many knockoffs?
Hold on.
I have to diarrhea.
Kill him, kill him, kill.
Holy shit.
I can't believe it.
I did not see this list beforehand, guys.
I swear.
We got him.
Hey, hey, what's your opinion on politics?
I was doing something.
The bootlegs are fighting each other.
Oh, no.
I have to see a six-way tornado tag tournament
between all the green alien purple alien knockoffs.
Excuse me.
What's going on?
I just popped my pants.
Breaking news.
BDGerma is dead.
The sidekick red alien listed as missing.
How smelling green footprints have been discovered
near the crime scene.
The culprit is believed to be serial killer green alien.
Now on the FBI's most wanted list
for the murder of master Kit Fisto.
I just haven't get it right.
I'm going to calm down and stab you in the fucking head.
Hey, shh.
Don't tell him.
Hey, don't tell him.
Why is everything shitting?
He's a Reddit user.
Die, you motherfucker.
Is this candid?
I don't know, man.
Everyone quiet.
This is soft footage.
Oh, you got me with the cliffhanger.
Good job with that cliffhanger.
Now I'm interested.
Derma attacks the Death Star.
Star Wars.
Yes.
Red 3, standing by.
Where am I?
Red 11, standing by.
Red 5, standing by.
Luck has bought us an attack position.
We're passing through the magnetic field.
Hold tight.
Move your deflectors on double front.
He's going to come back and bite me.
Press the shutter at two.
Accelerate to speed.
Cross the axis and try and draw their fire.
I love left-hand turns.
It's the only thing I've said.
It's not going too good over here.
Maybe I should try going right.
I'm going to go right.
No, you can't even get.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Boogers.
Pee break.
All right, we're going to take a pee break.
We'll come back.
Go take a pee break.
First pee break.
See you in two or three minutes.
Okay, I have returned.
Got some water.
I want to say thanks to Wink Dinker
for the five community subs
and Sunny J for the five community subs.
Wink Dink City, that's right.
Okay, coming up next.
We have a, this is Uncut Gems.
I don't know if it's part of the trailer.
It might be part of the trailer.
I don't know.
I can't tell.
Or this could be a part of the movie.
This could be a very somewhere late game
or I don't know, mid game.
I don't know.
Or Uncut Gems.
So regardless, if you've never seen Uncut Gems
and you don't, even if you're like,
no, fuck that.
And I want to see a single thing.
I'm back in about one minute.
Okay, here we go.
It's incoming in three, two, one.
Uncut Gems spoilers.
Get married with me now.
It's okay.
Oh, this fuck you got.
Do not let him in.
Understand me?
Just ignore him.
Ignore him, Jodie.
Okay, that was not, that was like from the trailer.
Okay, whatever.
But still.
Melonhead, thanks for the five subs.
Okay, this is called I'm So Sorry.
And right off the bat, a mod, a mod in the chat.
Grump Clump just said, oh boy, this one.
Take a look at that.
One hour mustache hair.
I told you.
And eventually, this is going to keep parting
until it's complete mustache.
The definition starting to form on the, well, my left.
No, my right, your left.
On your left, my right side, you'll see.
Anyways, this one, apparently this I'm So Sorry.
And a mod said, oh no, this one.
Okay, well, that makes me scared.
Let's go.
Wait, did anybody even say that?
Did I just make that up?
Is he wearing underwear?
I think I just made that up, but yes, I am.
Wait, did anybody even say that?
You edited out my pants.
This is like a 3D model.
It's like a Sims character in the mirror.
Those aren't real feet.
How did he do it?
I don't know.
Did he put it in front of a green screen?
He had to have made a 3D character or model or something.
He put it in front of a green screen and then cut it.
But no, this is not me.
It's the creator.
It's the editor's legs.
So you're telling me the editor did a full frontal nude video
and then edited me on top of it?
No, that's a 3D model.
You can clearly tell.
All right, let's go.
Coming up next is spoilers for American Psycho.
This is the movie spoiler stream
where we spoil every movie that's in your Netflix backlog.
Spoilers incoming for American Psycho.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Where's the audio?
Skeleton...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Exoskeleton Bug Millennium Boy for Jerma Rumble 2020.
You know what's fucking ridiculous about that picture?
Let's break this down real quick.
This was just thrown together over footage
that was taken almost 10 years ago.
The ads that you see now look like this.
This stupid fucking thing pops up
on the top of your browser,
on the right of your browser,
on the left of your browser.
We have come so far in technology.
Why haven't the ads caught up, right?
Isn't that...
I feel like that's a huge problem
why people don't want to fucking listen to a single ad.
Well, look at a single ad because they look like this.
It looked like they were made in paint in 10 seconds.
That's stupid.
You're right.
What do you mean?
Am I being...
Wait, am I being disagreed with?
Oh, you don't have adblock.
LOL.
Yeah, but the reason why they were...
The reason why adblock was invented in the first place
is because a banner would pop up
and it would be like somebody's dick
or it would be like some weird fucked up website
that you don't want to go to anymore.
And you'd be like...
When I say anymore, I mean like ever.
Okay, let's break that up so you don't want to...
Listen, ads were intrusive and...
I fucking can't.
Ads were intrusive.
They were annoying and they were ugly.
They were very ugly.
And now they may have even...
Some companies try to make ads look a little better
but they take up your whole screen, especially on mobile.
And you try to close the thing
and you keep scrolling it pops back up against...
No, just they've taken over the whole screen
not just annoyed some of it and put like gross weird stuff.
All right, let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Just use adblock.
But that was why adblock was invented.
It was because ads sucked in the first place.
What if ads didn't suck?
Why do you think I don't run ads on this channel?
Because they're fucking annoying.
And I don't want to have you guys suffer
through the same like three ads 200 times.
How many times do you guys want to watch the new
like Call of Duty trailer?
40 to 50 times?
I don't...
I wouldn't want to do that.
Living above a spee nest.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Oh no.
Hi, hello.
Yes, how are you?
Shut up.
All of you.
Let's go.
It's ridiculous.
It's like this every single day.
And I'm sick and tired of hearing it.
I can hear you all the way up here.
And I pay rent too.
Unbelievable.
Yes, my more slick hair.
Here comes another Star Wars clip.
This is chat during green screen streams.
If you've never seen any of the Star Wars...
Who cares?
I'll be honest.
It's not...
Don't worry, but it's all right.
All right, here we go.
Chat during a green screen stream.
This is going to be from either the...
One of the...
The sequel series of Star Wars.
Be careful if you haven't seen it.
All of you have.
Three, two...
Wait, what was that?
What was that?
Dead.
Oh, I see.
The bar was in the way.
Okay, wow.
Dermacraft gets a taunt kill.
Nice.
That's short and sweet.
Dermacraft gets interrupted by the Iron Giant.
Is this the Iron Giant?
Okay.
A lot of you after these streams are gonna...
You're gonna go to your Netflix
and you're just gonna start
getting stuff off of your watch list
and your wish list and stuff.
You probably have like 10 to 15 shows and movies.
You're gonna go remove like four or five of them.
This is huge spoilers for the Iron Giant.
Huge spoilers for the Iron Giant.
All right, we're...
We're second at the...
That was supposed to be me.
What is even going on?
I saw the...
I...
This is a great movie.
That was huge, Rula, by the way.
That was enormous.
It was as big as the Iron Giant.
This made me love the Iron Giant character so much.
All right.
Good.
Because this is what happened
when Chuck E. Cheese was on the stream.
Thermo Jeopardy!
This is Jeopardy!
It's gonna all be...
Oh, Earl Bump is here.
Finally got Earl Bump.
Reuben Guy.
Come on.
Celebration.
Thank you.
Wow, you won.
You did it.
You get to go up there.
God, that looks like fun.
That looks like a lot of fun.
I wish I could get up there.
Son of a bitch.
After a while, Jeremy and Earl made it to the final Jeopardy.
It cost us this much money to hire Louis Anderson.
Bob, what is $3,200?
Probably more than that.
Wait, me?
I get it?
I get to go up there.
No way.
Right here, man.
Fuck you.
You gotta get a high five from me.
Maybe I need one of these, though.
What is one of these?
No way.
Oh, yes.
What's in the mystery box?
Hey, do you guys want to know something funny?
Your cube video got claimed because of, I believe, that song or that clip that I fucking had to buy.
Like, I bought this.
Like, I purchased this thing.
I think they claimed the song.
No, this is not Dr. Phil.
Is that Dr. Phil?
No, it's not.
Is this a repeat thing?
Did we talk about this already?
Yes, we did.
Yeah, I was playing visitor cleanup.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
Yeah.
Guys, remember, I've spoken out loud for like 20 years straight.
Sometimes it's hard to remember.
All right, this is Beach Vlog.
There we go.
Beach Vlog.
Perfect YouTube intro.
Hey.
Fuck.
Hey, what's going on, everybody?
I am here on vacation.
Oh, no.
You didn't have the video outside the plane window.
And it got me through many waves.
Nobody used this for what I wanted either.
Nobody put me on a slide.
What the fuck is going on?
I'm going to sneeze.
I just want you to understand I'm going to sneeze.
No, I don't want you to be near me.
I held it in.
No, don't sneeze.
Don't sneeze.
Sorry for making this mess of a video.
It's 3 a.m.
I'm so bored.
Thanks for watching, though.
I'll be surprised that this even makes it in.
Well, it did.
I liked it.
What's wrong with it?
This stylish desktop computer comes with a Pentium 4 processor, DVD,
ROM, 60 gigabyte hard drive, and a printer, a perfect addition to your home.
Every American I was told had that computer 15 years ago.
$150, Tracy.
$900.
$900, Craig.
$1,700.
$700.
Bruh.
Yes.
What is $12?
What the fuck happened?
You're going to play the piano.
Do you eat ass?
I think I should be the first person to say yes.
Oh, all right.
This is like you made it.
Well, look, this is your moment.
And good luck.
You made like a this is a Simon.
I've heard enough.
Come on.
This isn't working for me.
I'm just looking and seeing some of the others where I'm seeing originality.
This, to me, is too generic.
Not enough personality.
Huh?
Okay.
We have a guy back here.
What's that, sir?
I'm kind of in the middle of doing something here.
Can we get security to take care of this guy?
You could be funnier than I am.
I highly doubt that, though.
It's crazy, people.
That was great.
To be continued.
The Kylo German drive-through.
My fucking eyes hurt.
My eyes hurt from just like laughing at this shit.
Okay, here we go.
Can I get a you guys you can still have coffee.
And you guys have coffee.
It says you serve breakfast all day.
I'm one of those fucking weirdos that comes at like 7 30 looking for all the breakfast items.
Okay.
Wow, this place is sick.
Can you put the ice in it?
Can you put some ice in the coffee, please?
Oh, really good use of the bugleberry cameo.
He loves it.
Can you put the ice in it?
He loves McDonald's.
Okay, there's German in a bottle of water.
Who will breathe?
Idiots.
Yeah.
This is the thing I'm talking about right here.
I told you guys this before.
Absolute perfection.
No ifs, ands, or buts.
This right here is absolute perfection.
This is it right here.
No, it's not purple alien.
Don't get your hopes up.
Hey, are you in charge of this?
Here's what I have to say about this.
See this bullshit.
What is cool breeze?
What's cool breeze?
Wait a minute.
Oh, I'm tensing up for this one.
Jerma hits a home run.
Yes, it's a fictional drink in the valve universe.
Oh, here we go.
Jerma hits a home run.
This pixelation is so ridiculous.
What are you playing as?
I'm going to play Team Fortress 2 as the pyromaniac.
I'm going to be playing Team Fortress 2 as?
Mario.
Woo hoo hoo.
Hey shit.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm going to talk about this so much.
I've heard of that before.
Go grab yourself a nice pizza.
Pizza music.
Good enough.
Let's get out of here.
Dude, there's a fucking knife.
There's coffee, cheese, it's chicken.
Coffee Cheetos.
What?
What the?
Chicken.
Coffee Cheetos.
oh that was insane that was insane giant enemy you can always tell okay just
doing one of those they're like dude it takes a few minutes to get that in the
right spot now imagine doing that like 4,000 times that was stimulation that's
right it was awesome all right this is a another song I think we're gonna get
here giant enemy Kirby the giant enemy have we seen this one before
yeah sneaking around two-fourth same same turkey arms
Jerma's bunt of 46 veteran player Jeremy Albertson had joined the Boston Red Sox
Jeremy had found himself playing with some of the greatest ever put on the
Red Sox uniform like Bobby Doerr Johnny Pesky and Teddy Ballgame himself Ted
Williams Jeremy was a strong player being a consistently good hitter
throughout his entire career however Jeremy was quite mediocre when it came
to his defense his short stature meant that some balls would go right past him
when the ball gets past Albertson he can't reach it now one more score and when
Jeremy was moved to the outfield things didn't get any better but on one fateful
day during one fateful game Jeremy would write himself into their history books
forever with one visit to the batter's box somebody did it so it is the bunt
home run and sure enough the home run became history
Jeremy remains as the only player to have bunted a ball for an out-of-the-park
home run many have tried but Albertson's home run stands alone to this day
excellent excellent excellent excellent all right coming up next
you know what's cool about baseball now Rich is if we get Jerma's final game
before rehab highlights another baseball we're getting baseball ones back to back
here you know what's cool about baseball now Rich is if we get to see more
players personalities and to see players the other side that's a lot of times as
fans you don't get to see the personalities their laughs their smile
their characteristics and I think it's it's a great thing that baseball is
doing now Jeremy at the plate he's that thread he wants to be up in those big
moments that one's hit NT came back and that's gone goodness 41,000 here that's
the first out in the bottom of the ink what a thrill today a game-winning home
run in front of 40,000 fans congratulations young man stay healthy
and good luck the rest of the way big hit to the outside of the bounce that's
pretty cool I mean that is really cool I have to watch the whole one again I'm
sorry I have to watch the entire thing again baseball now Rich is if we get to
see more players personalities and to see players the other side that as a lot
of times as fans you don't get to see the personalities their laughs their
smile their characteristics and I think it's it's a great thing that baseball's
doing now Jeremy at the plate he's that thread he wants to be up in those big
moments that one's hit NT came back and that's gone goodness 41,000 here that's
the first out in the bottom of the ink what a thrill today game-winning home run
in front of 40,000 fans congratulations young man stay healthy and good luck the
rest of the way big hit to the outside of the bounce that's pretty cool I mean
that's pretty cool holy shit oh that's great those back-to-back two great
back-to-back baseball themed ones down the rat hole we go oh shit someone's
like coming in oh fuck dude oh he's got he's got a knife this is Jeremy I once
started in 34 year old with a loving following a gamer girlfriend and a
stable job he was on top of the mountain of success his life seemed to
be perfect then what went wrong from primetime streamer down to a hole of
addiction and fights we go down the rat hole of German I net five I dead in this
video it all began with his notorious dreams of various games which amazed
millions of views and thousands of followers thanks to his charming
personality and humor this quickly skyrocketed Jeremy into success at first
he was easy going with his newfound fundings spending his newfound money on
better quality for his streams and better games to entertain his fan base
but this power quickly began to take a toll on his populating quickly made him
develop on it for more power as you can sometimes see his streams the rage he
had boiling inside of him streams quickly dropped in quality as he became
more desperate for probability eventually this will lead to a gambling
addiction as to find any way of feeling strong once more but it will prove to
become a failed attempt I don't even care if I win this is the rush of the colors
now with no money and no fame he resorted to giving morale speeches in the
high school dance nervous for all of us so on this particular day that's so
stupid that's dumb we talked about that's fucking stupid yeah look I'm
holding up yeah look I'm holding up buddy yeah no finger no finger no we
can't they're not going to do anything to me because I'm not doing anything
wrong I am fighting you I know I'm fighting than you what are you doing
what the fuck what the fuck's wrong with you
as we try to capture footage he recognized us and became hostile very quickly
why do I have to hurt and kill so many of you guys
you're the one I'm gonna get
die you motherfucker
police were called but in his rageful state of mind he resisted arrest and
that's the end of Jeremy's story from what it seemed to be the peak of success
it all came crumbling down the rat hole thank you very much yes that was nuts
was walking like so you guys okay you guys don't hear because I have like a
noise gate on and like I lean back when I watch and sometimes I mute if I get a
little too weird but I've just been in constant state of like contracting body
like I've just been sitting there just giggling like a little shit just
constantly okay here we go this is the story of when I met German I hope this
is just somebody just dictates the electric interference thing oh yeah like
this like you're doing now I hope somebody's narrates it was walking my
kids from school one day and I ran into Jeremy told him how big of a fan I was
how he makes me laugh and then I appreciate him I could see in his eyes
were dollar signs ask me so large was the last donation you made explain that
I am a single father I don't make enough to donate to him but I will try in the
future said to me but my child word for word suck a fart out of my ass walked
away stay on my wife didn't happen that didn't happen but you know it of course
it did because somebody copied and pasted on a forum somewhere this is
German the Fortune City zombie outbreak dead rising to play dead rising to well
dead rising ones better it's okay and then dead rising trees not very good at
all so don't worry feel a good game dead rising to I did enjoy it very much so
even though I got gas lit into playing the wrong version but you know I still
liked it it was very very good I'm one of the survivors
wait wait me wait me think I'm a zombie come on get it you can get it rare emote
holy shit biggest daily use of that emote since I made it they get any
money this video gets plus one letter grade
whoa this is my favorite part this is the best part it was fun did you
understand how long I'm gonna be here for nothing about this is good not one
thing wasn't it for this long I was it I was it for like maybe five minutes tops
that happened all too often I can't manage time for shit
Hermes Eldon bones
you fucking dick hey oh what happened yo don't do that add that to the list of
rules put that on the list of rules I want that unless no loud explosive
noises it already is fucking rules all right louder louder like all right here
we go come on next is a okay Matthew's birthday bash giant rats crew featuring
on the right side of it I'm on a birthday match
Matthew
It's your birthday today
Take an ice cream, it's on its way
Matthew
That's a good boy this year
Open up your ears while we all cheer
Rats, rats, we are the rats
Shit
Matthew
It's your birthday
Look at all these balloons
There's balloons everywhere
I can't even get away from them
They're just surrounding me
Matthew, happy second birthday
My goodness, you're getting so old
You're growing up big and strong
Eat your vegetables, especially that broccoli
What's your favorite color?
My twin
Okay, so you know
What this is
This is a videos that
resurfaced
10 years later that I should be embarrassed of now
Today
Oh hey look at this clip of you dude
Remember back when you did this shit
That was like 2 months ago
It's like oh remember back in 2011
when you made the
Minecraft series, JermaCraft
That's the kind of reaction I should be having to these
But I did them like
Not even a year ago
Alright
I'm going to take
Next like 2 or 3 weeks
And 100 days
Only focus on
This game my dog
Say goodbye to your seed might want to do
That seed might want to do
And get actually definitively
Truly diagnosed
For whatever the fuck is
Going on
What is this
Oh alright
Alright
Goodbye
Also
I wouldn't here
I got to talk about this
So this kind of bleeds into a conversation we can have about
Future videos
If we could stay away from
Like real
Tragedy
That would be a very good thing
There's been a couple of videos that have come through that are like
Oh hey we've got like
Oh there's like a house
That burnt down and stuff you know what I mean
Like oh no but this is
This is the Paul Walker clip right
Cause don't they do like a thing
It's the movie no I know it's the movie
But what I'm saying is like
This is from Fast and Furious yeah
That is dumb
What I'm talking about is Paul Walker died
Kind of right before this right
And although this is like
A goodbye to Paul Walker
Right it's I mean putting me
Here I don't know
Like it's sort of like
Yeah you're right I'm just
Trying to come off as I'm trying not to be
I don't want these to be like disrespectful we'll put it that way
And as however I can
Say that I'm gonna say that okay
Am I overthinking it maybe
A little bit but I still I don't I know that like
Some some stuff can come
Across as like
Disrespectful and I don't want that to happen
But let's go
I used to say I lived my life a quarter mile
At a time and I think that's why
We were broke
It's his channel well
Look there's been a lot of videos that have come through
And we try to like
Put them in a good enough order
And we try to take weed out
There'll be like 500 videos
So my channel my rules
There's also on that list we gotta talk about
Like the copyright stuff we gotta be careful there too
That's another thing we have to
We'll talk about this at the end
It's my channel
It's not it's not your channel
He's above the law
The dead angle doesn't date it
Gets caught low again
Has to burst immediately
Low meter
Oh my god
So smart he couldn't burst
Because of the super
But Woshiga thinks it's over
What the fuck
Woshiga thought it was over
And stood up and Ogawa gave him
No remorse
Exactly what happens
Oh my god
I don't even know what that is
I just experienced all of it
I experienced that entire tournament
You did though
German 985 show
Oh this looks like shit
Itchy and scratchy
Our favorite show
Nothing about this is good
I'm gonna dab you in the fucking head
Let me tell you something
If you can do not do it diplomically
Then you shouldn't be doing it at all
Now I'm really bored
I know
Ladies and gentlemen welcome to episode one
Of the show
My name is German 985
Let's get this party started
And here we are
The master of illusions
Is ready to begin
It's gonna be very very interesting
And you're gonna say the magic words with me
Anytime we do a trick
You gotta say the magic word
The magic word is presto
Majesto
So on the count of three I want everyone to say
Presto majesto
One, two, three
Presto
Majesto
Deliver this
Ladies and gentlemen
Again? Really? You're gonna do this again?
This is the best fucking life nerd
Who's never gotten pussy before in his entire life
God damn it you motherfucker
Oh you've got a mouth on you don't you
I'm coming out there
Die you motherfucker
It's supposed to be
German and the prisoner of
Ascaban
Alright here comes
There he is again
Alright I'm ready
Shut up mouth boy
Woohoo
Get him, get him mouth boy
We go
Demental, Demental
Oh my god Harry you're a stupid idiot
Harry's an idiot
That's it
What the fuck
You got something to say
Look at me
Look at me, look at me
That's what you sound like
Fucking idiot
Real tragedy
No that's
Oh fuck
What
Oh you didn't think I was gonna
Catch it
No that's not what I'm talking about
I just want to see this one again
That's not
Real tragedy
Oh god damn it
Alright coming up next we've got
Jerma is that one guy at the birthday
Party
They grow up so fast
Wow
Three years old
They grow up so fast
Four you say
Four years old
Getting bigger, stronger
Five
Five that's a milestone alright
Five years old
Six years old
Holy shit
That's ancient
Seven, seven years old
Oh wow
Lucky sevens
Eight
Nine, ten
You're eleven, you're twelve, you're thirteen
You're fourteen, you're fifteen, you're sixteen
Sweet, I'm so glad to be invited
To your sweet sixteen
Mike, Dave
Anthony, Sharon
Crystal, Carl
Matt
Tom
Jessica
I'm happy to be here
Happy birthday
To you
I hate it already
Happy birthday
To you
Happy
Day dear
Happy birthday
This is a real tragedy
Stop it
Alright that's it
We had so much fun
It was a great time
Look at what you got for presents
That'll be two hundred dollars
Die you motherfucker
My name's Jerma
Go ahead and press it
Thumbs down, that's over there too
Hey what's going on
Hey welcome to my channel, welcome to my vlog
As you can see
I'm out and about right now
And I'm having a ton of fun
It's so cool, I don't even wish
You were
Hey welcome back to I murder you
Hey, hey how are you, hey it's me
Good thing I caught you
Right at the beginning of the video
I'm about to skip this one, this one sucks
Should I do it? Should I do it?
Jojo?
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure?
No, no, if something, there's music behind it
With me dancing in front of it, it's not Jojo
This is Jerma caught on camera, should we do a piss break?
Anybody got a piss?
Got a pee? It's probably going to be final pee break
Yeah, alright, final pee break
Let's go, alright
I feel good, I feel good
We are down to the final
We're almost in the top 50 of videos
That have been submitted
We got about 50, 60 more
Should take another probably hour
Maybe, or more or less
This is Jerma caught on camera
How many cameras do you fucking have in your house?
I'm coming for you, you're the one I'm gonna
Excuse me
Well that was terrifying
What's next?
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Episode 1
Fighting Chat
Actually Jojo this time
That's some duality of chat right here
Is that intro, outro?
I don't know
I'm virtually murdering you
Just please give me a thumbs up
And a like
And I hope you spread the video around to Jojo's parents
And try to get me some followers
Ok, let's get started
This is a simulation
I fucking murder you
Oh my god, I have to get this done
Please let him go
Die you motherfucker
This is a real tragedy
Alright, don't
I better not have created a fucking meme for myself
If you like that video, follow me on my journey
Where I virtually will kill you
Virtual Murder
Virtual ASMR Murder
That was insane
Brad, wait
Brad will be ending
Remastered HD
My name is Jerma
Russian Jerma
A little bit out of gas at this point
Ok
Jerma gets booed off the stage
Shit
This road sucks
Such a bad road
Seat covers
Go out and look
What's with the seat covers
There's a tree, two trees
Hey mom, hey mom
Mom, mom
Did you see the tree
Hey mom, hey mom
We got going back seat here bitch
The fuck up
Jesus
Hey
You're a badass
Hey, who are you
Who are you
This is terrible
Absolutely terrible
Jesus
What is this
I wanna
This is the demon dog
I told you guys this before
Absolute perfection
We got him
Wait, hold on
He actually hits that guy
Life is pain
I hate
What's it called
A TV show
Called El Chavo
It's called Jerma's Brush with Cigarettes
Real tragedy
I don't know
Hey
Get his plate
That's pretty good
He's probably going 200
Bounds per hour
I didn't even see him
Turn it up
I saved the world
I just saved the world
No earth exploding
This is rescue Jerma
Michael
Look at him
Is that his
That's my thumb
Right, okay
Jerma becomes
Larry Potter
I get super excited
Uncensored version of the one
Wait, is that the one with the
Sensor bar over my fake bottom half
I'm not clicking on that
Alright, here we go
When I call your name
You will come forth
I shall place the sorting hat
On your head
And you will be sorted into your houses
Is it my turn
Oh, great sorting hat
I know exactly what I'm
Going to get
I'm a Slytherin
Right then
No
Stop laughing
This hat for me immediately
Torturing
Murdering people, murdering them
Slytherin
See, I told you
You're evil too, right
We're probably going to be really good friends
I'll probably die in the third movie
Three movies later, uh oh
Now hand me the prophecy
Death eaters
Expelliars
Hahahaha
Harry Potter spoilers
Yeah
Holy shit, this is long
This is
Seven and a half minutes
I'm just checking to see how
Just watch it
If I get the feeling that I'm going to get arrested
I'm going to skip it, okay
Oh
Both sides
I gotta skip it
I gotta skip it, I gotta skip it, I gotta skip it
I'm going to get arrested, I gotta skip it
I can't fuck around with that mouse
That mouse will fucking eat me alive
He'll eat me whole, I will get swallowed whole from the mouse
Alright, this is a Vod
Destroyer horse
Why did I just read that out
Loud, oh
It's being spammed
Get it, oh my god
Skip
No, okay, hold on
I can't
It's deepfaked
Don't ever have this hair
Well this is a deepfake
I don't have this hair
What the hell
Prove that you don't have this hair right now
That guy was brain screened, I thought that was me in a costume
I thought that was me in a fucking costume
For you
You're the one I'm going to get
I'm kicking ass right now
It's just a deepfake
The Vod is going to get crucified
The Vod is going to get thrown into a dumpster
Not only is the Vod going to get crucified
I'm going to be fucking killed
Playlist will be available
Somebody said I don't care, continue
What if I just disappear tomorrow
What if I just don't
Tomorrow you wake up and I just don't exist anymore
We'll find you
What about American Cycle
American Cycle is not scary Mickey Mouse
Give me the shock
Shock me
What
Give me the shock me
Who do you think I was going to catch
That's the broken bone
What
You didn't get
Nothing happened to you
I'm going down
I moved here when I was probably 19 or so
Oh shit sorry
Concentrate all fire on that
Superstar destroyer
Sir, we've lost our bridge deflector shield
Intensify the forward batteries
Nothing above us is painful
Not poor thing
I needed a break
Mickey's inside your house
Jesus Christ
This is a tragedy
You motherfuckers
What happens in the end
Legos
Help me take
It's gonna be Bugleberry. I already know it. It's gonna be it's gonna be Bugleberry. I know it
What what happened
Oh my god
I never I didn't I never heard that before that's not terrible. That's absolutely fucking awful
So bad
This is UNSC Pelican Echo 216, can you hear me? Halo infinite
This is UNSC
salt sugar and
one gram of cocaine
These were the secret ingredients that professor X
put into his pot of stuff and he created
Crack girls. Oh
Wow, do they fight crime?
Nope, not at all. In fact, just now they've robbed and killed professor X
And the credits just fucking scream by there was like 12,000 people that worked on it
There was a villager at your animal manager, we're gonna wait. Okay. Hold on. You're at your villagers Animal Crossing birthday party
So glad I got to go to your birthday party villager. We're gonna have so much fun
Everybody's here. We're all here for your birthday. Happy birthday villager
Hey guys, holy smokes villager is about to blow out their candles
Everybody get around here
Go on
Happy birthday
To you you can use this wherever you want
Happy day dear
villager
What the fuck is this she's being germ Malkovich, what is it? What is this?
This is spoilers this is for a movie
We're being John Malkovich
Hey, you're supposed to be more list for being John Malkovich. Apparently. I don't know. I don't remember any of these scenes
I'm breaking out here. No
Mom, I see it
Transform into object of life
Piss on me piss it piss in my face
Is this even that movie I'd what was even a scene from that movie
You're here for the interview
What's your name what's going on my name is
5 or you can just call me German. That's what
I'm a gaming channel
You probably could guess that by all the different playlists and all the videos below
Which you should check out and you should go watch something right now and possibly subscribe
That's the whole purpose. You're here for the interview. You see on this channel. I like to call myself. Dr
Jekyll and my Mr. Germo, okay, because I have two different sides. I have the very professional side
Well, we're gonna need a lot of that. So it's really really important that you look here's a cup. What's up?
This cup is good. What do you know? I'm gonna take a chance. Well, my day was pretty interesting. Yeah with you
Wait, wait me wait me fired. I got fired
No, I'm just kidding you're hired. I'm not fucking firing you
Say something before you say anything I just want to make sure that you're aware of how strong I am as your where are you gonna
Use an integer this wooden desk
445 pounds and with these I can just get
Process this one, but I want to
I'm
Speed nest on dust balls as they pop up from time to time, but I've got to be really careful
Blue and red bees are gonna be mating
Very very quiet here
That would have been very bad
Fall guys waiting
My career did not peak at speed
Someone who will be proven wrong by a hundred percent German probably. Yeah, I didn't peak at speed. Come on
Ran wraps in chat. Why would you say that?
Oh
My brain's fried
It doesn't help that like I you know
I decided today was the day that I was feeling a little tight this morning and
I did I did I did a little bit I did a little bit THC and PCB to make to
alleviate that and this is probably the wrong day
Like two hours ago. I was just like wait a minute. What the hell? What the fuck is happening?
It's about two and a half hours ago. I realized probably you know, that's all right
By the way, it's a hundred percent legal in Las Vegas recreationally
So don't worry, I'll take it recreationally take it for medical uses. Sure. All right, but man has fallen into Lego City
Emergency collection from Lego City. I love this one
I love this one
What tons and tons of special effects my super sweet cake
I
Think these have turned out to be my favorite ones
Yeah, like somehow just because it's the same it's same footage and you just happen to change it a little bit
I thought this is gonna be used gravy. Hold on
I thought this is gonna be used the least out of every clip that was done in my mind
No one was gonna ever use this even the ones where I said no one's gonna use this people might but this was what?
What were you supposed to do with this besides just have you do me sitting at a dinner table for five minutes. That's it
There's nothing else to do
Delicious potatoes mashed potatoes gravy and mashed gravy
You've all done yourself
You pass the pass the salt
So, how was your day son
Wow, that's unbelievable Susie
My kids my kids are the smartest straight-edge. That's a little tough. I think a little tough a little overdone, but it's good
Well my day it was pretty interesting I got fired
Head hurts
Evangelion
This is Van Gellie and spoilers neon Genesis Vangelion spoilers
15-year-old me. No, I'm not you guys. She stood up
This is what it looks like up close are you in charge of this that's right son
You are in big trouble
Wait, wait me wait me I wait I get it I get
Oh
Well, I mean it's kind of it's kind of insane
Megatron you've got the septicons coming at us from two angles
We're incredibly intelligent monsters if you were going to take us seriously
These scientists
Oh
Let me try you it's time for you to pay my butthole
I'm coming down there and I'm gonna fuck you up stay right there
You can do anything you can do you can fight on the ground
This is what I have to say about this
Bullshit
Oh god spider-man dance
Way to go Pally
Fantastic thanks for the video. I'm a faked his breakdance
Oh
Ten out of ten video
Absolute absolute masterpiece now master
Why is Republic Starfighter? Oh, I don't even know what movie this is. I have no idea. It's one of the Star Wars movies
I don't know just if you're gonna watch just you know, it's a spoiler for Star Wars movie one of them. I
Don't I don't want to hit it I don't want to hit this thing
I'm gonna go slow. I'm gonna go really slow
Unbelievable is it alive a short streamer
That's a good song what song is this I'd like this song
This is from like rhythm heaven. It sounds cool. That was good. And the and the rats in the background
Beautiful. This is German hearts final HD remix secret episode. Okay, I don't know. I don't I didn't play Kingdom Hearts 3
I don't even remember Kingdom Hearts 2 and 1. I don't know the story, but it's okay because the story
I could get the same story if I just kind of hit my head against my desk as hard as I could and then
Just started thinking I'm sure I'd come up with the same thing. I don't know
I have no idea what the story is. I don't have no idea
So this is a secret if you don't see that, you know, it's a boy or less for that, but who cares
Is this even what even is this
Donald and goofy
No idea what's going on that Gollum
Your my heart's three wait, was that the e3 trailer from like
2006 and then the game came out actually in like 2018
time space adventures
Are you ready? What the fuck are you talking about?
Oh
I'm losing speed
Want some instability
The hell is that sometimes
Irritating
Take care of that engineer right now
Fucking rumors
Oh
Secret alternate bad ending that's for you to decide
Okay, that was ridiculous
My brain is gonna need
Time after that one. That was so good. That was insane. That really was so good. Watch the secret ending
Watch the bad ending. It's time to do a rant to fill time. No, wait, hold on
I don't want to give a spoiler. How many we have left? Oh
We're getting close. This is very close. There are like maybe 20 30 left
There's a secret ending. Yeah, we got about 25 Pepe hands. Okay. Here we go. Ready?
This is the secret alternate bad ending. Well, the thing we just watched sure was fun wasn't it Jerma?
Okay, so at first I thought that was the moon theme and now that was
Carmorell dancin. No spoilers. I don't want you to see what's left. Okay up peewee peewee streamer. Hey
Yeah, that's peewees big
Balloon pops and it lands on the toast
TV's big adventure is one of the best movies ever made. Can you move the watch if you've never seen you please move?
What are you under the influence or something? Yeah, I'm a very very highly influenced
Like extremely what did you do? All right, come on boys. Let's get him
Yeah
Best scene in the whole movie
That's great you
Wait, what happened skip one?
No, right. Okay, Jerma angry. He's okay. Here we go. Jerma angry. He's in another anime clip this year
I hope Jerma doesn't mind if I insert him into a persona clip this year
well
Do you hear this?
One of my boys
Okay, uh, this is persona. I guess persona something let's go. It's not a three spoiler
Again again
Oh, you've got a mouth on it, don't you i'm coming out there. All right, let's go
Hey, hey, how are you? It's me. Ah, it's a good thing. I caught you
I got you right at the beginning of the video
You're gonna want to skip this one because this one sucks
You know, typically I I bring you the weather on a daily basis at six a.m
Six a.m in the morning with dying. I'm just kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. Hey, hey, how are you?
Hey, it's me. Ah, it's a good thing. I caught you. Good thing. I got you right at the beginning of the video
You're gonna want to skip this one because this one sucks
Oh
Wow three years old two years old they grow up so fast they grow up so fast getting bigger stronger
Six years old
Holy shit
Come on everybody gather around
It's about to blow out their candles
Hey, all right. That's it. Hey you
Wait, wait, wait me
Wait me. I wait I get it
Oh, yes
Yes, i'd like to buy this mcdonald's mcdonald's, please
Only a few of these left in existence. I'm certain of that
Take it. It's yours. This is valuable. This is that'll be two hundred dollars
Is it japanese writing great prices? Thank you. You guys got great prices. Don't sell it though. I don't know
My favorite
Are you really fucking watching this shit everybody else hamburgers in this town that don't quite make it
I just wish just once
Just once that my cheese was soft and cold and my lettuce was cool and crisp all at the same time
You know, i'm talking about the new
Mcdlt
I'm talking about a pound of beef on the hot hot side and the hot
Stay hot the new mcdlt so hot crisp lettuce and tomato on the cool cool side and the cool
Stay cool the new mcdl. I feel like this is oh my god
Yeah, I do too. You know typically I I do too
Whatever he was gonna say I agree with
Quote I don't put ads on my stream
Sure
No, mcdonald's doesn't count. I love that place. That's not an ad. That's real life. All right rising waters bring you the weather
On a daily basis at 6 a.m. 6 a.m. In the morning with diane
carolyn rick
Uh, but today I want to show you something different
I want to show you something that I care
Something that I want to show
It's easy no no mess no bullshit throwing the fucking sink behind me I had no opportunity to do it till now
That's me on my fishing trip that's me and my son yeah
Don't worry about the weather you just go outside and sniff you'll be just fine
It's gonna be cold some days. It's gonna be hot some days
It's just just go out there go out there
Coming soon. That was crazy
Star captain long star bath or six one four point six during the journey. We will be hosting a special guest
Set phaser power to three percent narrow beam
three percent
Here we go
The first incision is complete
I tell you how you guys seriously you guys getting hungry i'm getting hungry moving on this job for the last god two or three days
And I am fucking tired. I am tired
Of hamburgers in this town that don't quite make it
I just wish just once
Just once that my cheese was soft and cold and my lettuce was cool and crisp all at the same time
Creature is now in direct contact with the hull sir on screen. I believe it is dead, sir
Uh
What does this one say I have a surprise for optus is transformers, I guess I don't know what this is supposed to be
Who sent you here
We're all here for your birthday. Happy birthday jeffrey
My name is optimus prime
Wait, i'm not this is not jeffrey's birthday party
Oh, sorry
Is
Yeah, don't forget you have a fun
Spoilers for 2001 a space odyssey
Wait, is this a movie?
I'm so confused
I'm a hog and i'm looking at the preview right now right right now. I'm looking at the preview in obs
It's perfect. This shit is perfect on obs. What the heck what the heck is happening here?
It's perfect on obs
I feel like am I getting i'm getting like deja vu right now. Did I do this exact same thing?
Oh, this one's like shit
And then we did it in 1080 and 30 am I fucking going crazy?
Oh, well, here's the report the national weather service is calling for a big blizzard
Especially cold
This happened the last time
Okay, give me I need a minute I really do I need like a second or two
Oh my god
My my brain is collapsing on itself
We have about 20 let's see 30
40 50
There are 24 more videos and that's it
We've reached the end of the playlist at that point as the german 95 sweet voice
You guys these candles are getting waxed all over the place seriously, yes, come on skyler skyler
Oh, this is all right. All right. This is breaking. This is breaking bad. Okay. This is breaking bad
I don't know what season it's like season three or something. So just be aware of that spoilers for breaking bad
This is a spoiler. I guess a big spoiler people are saying in chat. Here it comes real. Those are getting waxed
Yes, come on skyler skyler skyler skyler skyler skyler no, yeah, you're right
To you
Big spoiler for breaking bad. Why did you say that?
Safe place
Welcome back everybody vacation vlogger has a mental breakdown
That's right on vacation
Take a look
I never get to go out of places like this
So it's so much fun for me
And before we video get started if you could please give me a thumbs up for being on vacation
Well, you're not on vacation. I'm doing all this cool fun shit and you're not
And i'm going to continue to do all kinds of really cool shit and you're just going to watch me do cool shit
And give me money to do it too and i'm going to fly around the entire world and i'm going to do a bunch of cool shit
Hey, you and me we're friends
Look at that. This is good. It's a palm tree. Can you believe it?
Jerma gets dragged to a baseball boston red sox game
No red rats game against his will
Jesus
Uh jerma man short baby jojo
I guess it's a jojo. Some said jojo. It's probably not from devil man. I've never seen it. I don't know what this is
Last time I carried myself out before the fucking 20 minute run
I'm really enjoying the school dance club d l d l t
I got you right at the beginning of the video. You're gonna want to skip this one music change
Whatever the music is the snow the music is the same
I think he might eat his own shit. I really think he
Excuse me
That was a really fun party next time
Alvin drinks
Hi. Hi. Hello. Yes. How are you? Great. Shut up. Absolutely terrible. Shut up all of you
This is a fucking terrible one-man show, by the way, i'm tired
Of hamburgers in this town that don't quite make it
I just wish just once
Just once that my cheese was soft and cold and my lettuce was cool and crisp all at the same time
You know
Well, I say you got it
I'm talking about the new
Dl. Uh, I forgot the line
Make d l t
I'm talking quarter pound of beef on the hot hot side and the hot price stays hot the new make d l t so hot
Can we get security to take take care of this guy?
Medicine tomato on the cuckoo side and the coot stays coot the new make d l t
You do drugs
Better watch my fucking stream
We want to make a deal
That'll be two hundred dollars
I don't have time for this shit
I'll make sure to change into my super flying jet monster
Jet monster activate
What's this we got company
You want to make a deal?
How about this?
You give me neo or we all die right here right now. I'll give us a barrier shield
Have I ever told you you're my best friend
If she has to she'll kill every one of us
She's in love
I ain't gonna fuck yourself
Time's up. What's it gonna be murph?
I don't know. I don't care
Fuck this job
Uh, germa adventure that was great
Germa adventure two sonic adventure two
That was joel
Uh germa fellas, I don't know what this is, but it's probably good fellas. It's probably a
Warped scene from good fellows. You haven't seen good fellows. You know what to do. Okay, here they come
Good fellows spoilers in three two one. Yeah. Yeah, I've lived around here. I've lived here for about 10 years
Can hey can you not do that
Can you relax back there, please
This is what what you're doing is incredibly distracting
Excuse me
Can we be quiet, please?
Some of us are trying to sleep
As far back as I can remember. I always wanted to be a gangster
This face is fucking awful
The streamer with the green screen
Coming to reddit.com. Okay
Coming soon to reddit for the prom one. Yeah
I'm really enjoying the school dance
Should I come a little closer?
So do you have any math homework that you have to do tomorrow?
I I I have uh, I have mr stevenson. She's the worst
Yeah
Wait, don't people like get don't people like that's I probably shouldn't do that
Mission control. We have a belligerent dumbass here that won't cooperate
Yeah, i'm doing all I can i'm gonna need you to send me in some backup
It's I don't know. It's acting
What the fuck
What the fuck was that? I ain't know what to be for but normal
Wait, this is a spoiler coming in for reservoir dogs
Spoiler for reservoir dogs incoming. I ain't know what to be for but normal
You lost your fucking mind relax put it down you put it down. Come on guys
Nobody wants this
We're supposed to be fucking professionals. All right. Look
It's been quite a long time
A lot of jobs. There's no need for this man. Let's just
Put our guns down
And let's settle this with a fucking conversation. This is a spoiler for reservoir dog
I will put fucking bullets right through your heart. You put that fucking gun down. You have real spoilers. Yeah
Now you put yours down
Oh my god
I can't I seriously that one was up. I can't even talk anymore. My brain is fried
Shit eating grin, uh, that was good. That was good
Jerma at his actual height wins an award for real and nothing bad happens to him
But a good transition
Well, thanks everybody
I just want to say
being
uh the number one
streamer on twitch
Clap it was a dream come true smile smile. I never thought I would be here smile
I feel against the stage in my life clap smile is the number one most viewed number one most subscribed number one most watched
Uh, we're bigger than espn now, so I mean luge me, right? Yep
That's a fan. That's a fan up there guys
Luca Luca me Luca me Luca me Luca me
Hi, hi, hello. Yes, how are you shut up?
Excuse me
Can we be quiet, please?
Some of us are trying to sleep fucking idiot. Oh, you've got a mouth on you don't you i'm coming out there
I'm doing a pretend fun thing. Hey boys and girls looks like we got a stay right there. Don't move
Yeah, yeah, that's right
Irma and glue man make amends
Hey, hey boss. Yeah, you're not having a good time. You know, it's it's great. We got to hang out together
Yeah, you know, we're getting this together always. Yep. Always we're best friends now
You're all glad you put our differences inside. I know it's unbelievable. It really is unbelievable
You know an asteroid might hit the earth
What are you talking? What? Oh, oh my god. Sure. Why would you oh, oh my god. I'm bleeding. Oh my god. Oh my
What's the what did I do that?
All right, this is terrible absolutely terrible halo reach
Not one thing
I hate this
I'm gonna sneeze. I just want you know, I just want you to understand i'm gonna sneeze and I don't want you to be near me
I'm not held in
What is that in the road
Fucking jesus christ, I just fell out of my window. I just fell out my window
I almost just went out the window. I flew back and my hands touched the glass like I would have almost went out the whole window
Oh
I didn't
My name is germa
I used to be a streamer. That's how most know me but I fucked up too much. So that's no longer
Tts. Yeah, I can't go to prison. So I have to assume a new identity
The life I have taken
is now
the new me
I
What
Wait, what is this? What does it say? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What does that say?
We got arrested later that day and is now spending his days in a in a part-time
jail
He could be released earlier if he accepts that he must finish his la noir and other abandoned playthroughs
I'm gonna be in jail for the rest of my life
I'm a cyberbullies aspiring youtuber or his pizza roll meme pizza roll
pizza roll
Pizza roll
You see it's funny because it's pizza roll
I'm so oh my god. That's germa. Oh, you're my biggest fan. What do you think of my good joke?
This is terrible. What?
Oh, absolutely terrible. I spent like five minutes on this nothing about this is good. Oh, it's not one thing
I hate this. Why are you being so mean? This is terrible. Why can't you just give me genuine criticism?
This is baseball
No, it's pizza
What the fuck are you?
Have you been paying gasoline?
What?
German what are you doing?
Yeah
You stumble upon this thanks so much for making my life easier to cope with your huge inspiration
I'm glad I found your channel when I was younger. Thanks for the hilarious memoirs
Memoirs quotes and genuinely seeming like a kind person but one day we can meet so you can pepper spray me
Well, uh, no, it's my pleasure
Thank you
I don't think I will do the I don't think i'll pepper spray you in the face
Unless we're doing a youtube video with like crazy fucking stunts and then you gotta do me
But then you gotta spray me and like i'm gonna say something really bad
Absolutely mental old resident lashes out boy. Do oh but seriously
Thanks for watching
Excuse me
Can we be quiet, please?
Some of us are trying to sleep everyone's using the same window asset
That's hilarious. Yeah, is this supposed to be my stream?
It is isn't it?
Where you going?
Hi, hi, hello. Yes. How are you? Shut up shut up all of you, okay
Again really you're gonna do this again
Words cannot even comprehend how it oh you've got a mouth on you. Don't you i'm coming out there
That's pretty high coming down there and i'm don't move on. Yeah. Yeah, that's right. Wouldn't that make me huge?
Wouldn't that make me like 30 feet tall
Real tragedy, uh, yeah. Yeah
Yeah
Ah
Hermes throws through pompey
Wait, uh, I need to check. I want to see how far we have
guys
We're at the final three videos actual actual tragedy. Yes
Hold on. Yeah. All right. All right. All right. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
This is a real threat is it yeah, hold on he fell for it. Did I fall for it? Wait, it happened
Thousands of years ago
All right. Let me let me let me clarify get this out. Let me clarify the statement
I made earlier what i'm all i'm saying is if you have an option to make me the butt of a joke
That's all that's better. That's all I meant. That's all I I know it's been thousands of years ago. Yeah
No, no, no, no, no, it's not. Yeah, it is
I'm sitting there going wait. Wait, what do you mean? What happened recently? What? Oh pump?
Yeah, thousands of fucking years ago. That's like saying that the dinosaurs
No, I don't want to show anything about the dinosaurs because that's the only one extinct
Oh, no, no, no, you're not supposed to see this. You're not supposed to see this this that's a spoiler
Shit now you saw the last three videos
God damn it. All right. It's all right. Okay. Um, let's just let's see what this is 79 ad
This is like what this is like 2 000 years ago. Do you have any idea?
The the absolute just
Daily moisturizer what
I don't know. I don't know what that what what's that supposed to be?
It's crashing
This show was awesome on nickelodeon by the way
Oh
All right, we're we've got I think two more videos left I have no idea what they are. Oh fuck you
Okay, bye
And now back to george lopez
an awkward carpool
Wait, did I change sides that I was driving on?
Yes. Oh, I had a long day at work. Let's go
Is it why is he chained into the car
Okay, this is the final video
Real tragedy. All right
I hope you guys know what i'm talking about though
Look and in my like cbd brain did did I come to do did I could you understand what i'm saying?
You do right? Okay
Here's the final video
The germa bowl before we watch the final video. I want to say
once again
that
I am blown the fuck away by the insane amount of editing talent that a ton of you guys have
If you would have set up like a green screen thing
In a lot of places on the internet the amount of quality submissions
I mean look at me, right? Look at you
I think I think this is top-notch shit right here. So seriously, thank you for all your submissions
There were hundreds and fucking hundreds and hundreds of them
And I it's hard to cut stuff
If your video was not seen that doesn't mean that the video sucked
We just tried to remove some things and shrink it down and condense it
So it could be done over a couple of streams. This playlist is going to be available
I will give it to you
and then
Also, maybe at some point in the next week or so we might do like an extended one
Just adding some of the other submissions that were there and then you can watch
And then you can get arrested by disney on your own so part three. No, not part three
I think from this point forward we're going to take any of the new stuff that comes in and do community content stuff
And community content night is going to be a lot different
a lot of the artwork is going to be put into brb screens and
at the end of the streams
I can't it's it'll be impossible to catch up
Even if we did it like every other day or or twice a week three times a week
There's this three months before I left of content and then when I got back
You're talking about I was we were already two or three months behind. There's probably six months of artwork and videos
So I have to think of a solution there how i'm going to do that and the best one I can think of is
Because I don't want people to get
Community content exhaustion. It's one of the reasons why I broke this stream up into two after, you know, four or five six hours
Of I don't want to just be scanning through pieces of artwork three four times a week
Because if people do an art piece of art for this channel
I want someone to see it and I want it obviously to be like, oh well look that's cool
But I don't want to exhaust everybody with like
Okay, we're gonna we're gonna play a video game today
And then the next two days are going to be artwork and videos
And I don't want to me personally be sitting there going skip skip skip skip skip skip I gotta go fucking fast
There's 3 000 of these. Hey, thanks. Hey, thanks. Hey, thanks. Hey, thanks
Hey, no, I don't want to do that because I obviously if you took the time to do it
I would want you to I don't want to just skip through you
Play it already. We're going over the future of the community content stuff, man. Come on
Uh, let's watch the last one. This is the germa bowl and then I'll put the link in chat
And we will say our goodbyes. Thanks again, everybody
Excellent fucking work. You floor me every time
My face hurts my chest hurts
Everything just hurts. I'm gonna take a bath after this. Here we go
Hello, ladies and gentlemen, this is anthony wimbles and coming at you with a shoutcast our germa 95 seattle
I got a lot of requests to get back into this and do another shoutcast
So i'm gonna start it here we go. One, two, three, four five. Let's do it. Are you fucking serious right now?
Get out of here two players
Wait what unfortunately
Your saturday football game is gonna get potentially rained out
Okay, that's it
Great honor to meet you, sir. Peter. I hear you fight the scientist
Well, i'm something of a scientist myself. I read all your research on nanotechnology really brilliant
Okay
Oh
Yeah, the playlist is in the chat right now
That was a ton of fun. It saddens me that this is the
second and final
Part one and then part two
But that doesn't mean we won't do this again
I think every year or two
Going in front of the screen and doing a ton more stuff
I'm cool with that
And then obviously stuff for community content
Nights and purposes. Yes
That was awesome
I will see you guys
Very soon. I will see you on let's see saturday
I'll see you guys on wednesday
And wednesday wednesday and thursday back to back we're gonna do 3do
I have about 40 games for the 3do
It's gonna be a shit show. So wednesday and thursday of this coming week
3do and then
Sunday
Is ftk sunday the 13th at 3 pm pacific is ftk on the stream on wednesday or thursday
I'm gonna give a ton of details for it and we're gonna start preparing the servers for it and everything
That's the plan for this coming week
Uh, there were a shitload of subs that just came in
First of all, thank you undead
Keechan, thanks for the 20 community subs. It's a lot of fucking money. It's a lot of subs. Thank you 10 from sovoksky
10 from bottle lemon 20 from bottle lemon actually
50 from jake in progress, which is
That's a stupid amount of money 50 in bits
You promised saw next week
I will do saw on fucking
Thursday, I don't know saturday. I don't whatever. I'll figure it out. We'll get it. We'll fit it in there somewhere
Don't worry. We'll fit it in
Uh, but jake it's they said it's my birthday today. I want to share my appreciation for all the shit you do
Uh, well today and last weekend and not had nothing to do with what I did
Sure, I I stood in front of the screen and did all the stuff, but I didn't make these videos. So
Thanks guys
Happy birthday to you jake as well 10 subs from mecha murph 5 from melon head
And that catches us up there. So good night everybody
Take care of yourselves
There's 10 000 fucking people here if you like what you saw
Cool, if you didn't you will you will you'll be back. You'll be back next week. I'm sure of it
All right. I'll see you guys later. Thanks for watching here come the credits
speeding by
Yep, there they are link link link link link link link link link
Was this actually a thumbnail at some point?
That would be hilarious if it was hold on is this doctored or was that there for it?
Was it actually there swear to god?
It's a real it's a real tragedy. Oh my god. See you i'll see you guys next week
God damn, I forgot one
Uh one got removed in the middle this one. What's what's the one that got?
The fuck is talking
Hello
I thought my computer just got hacked. What happened lord? Oh, no, it's i'm in the i'm on okay
I'm on twitch's main page opened up. I seriously thought somebody was just like hacking my computer. Jesus
All right. I have to get up. I gotta leave this just like happened last week. I feel fucking I feel tight. I need to leave
Raid lord. No, all right. I'm going you want to rate. Let's all right. Let's write rate
Let's who who who have we never rated before who've we never rated before I want to write somebody
We've never rated before tomato. You know what? Yeah tomato. You don't know tomato gaming
It's funny dude
It's been a long time since we've um rated tomato. Have we ever even rated tomato? Well, we're doing it today
What are you doing? And by the way twitch.tv slash tomato
I can't I didn't even realize this that how the fuck did you get that name tomato?
All right, go say hello to tomato. I'll see you guys next week. Have a great rest of your day. Good night. Take care
See you soon. Goodbye