My child, the task is at hand. You must go undercover to stop the human-dragon conflict.
Father, I'm not ready.
Silence. You've always been ready. You must live among them. Be part of the human race. Find out what it's like to be human.
But what if I fail?
Take the magical cloaking cloak. It will always disguise you as a human. Our ancestors used dragon wizardry to create the spell that's extremely strong and powerful.
As long as you wear this, you are safe.
Okay.
I love you, my son.
I love you too, dad.
Be careful.
First day. Go in. Meet a few people.
Good day, folks!
A dragon! I saw a dragon!
What?
Shit!
Cloak doesn't work. Dad, a magic cloak? Really? He was probably just shit-faced. Please stop hitting me with the sword. Please. We can live together in harmony, don't you see?
Maybe a tad on the large side for a head. Longer neck. Put his head forward a little bit. He's real perceptive. He sniffs around a lot. He really must get to the bottom of stuff. He's a private investigator.
And I think that's all right. I like it. Maybe a little bit bigger. Yeah, that's good. That's good. We're not going to go any more extreme than this.
Excuse me.
Welcome, child.
I just was wondering...
Stop.
I can't even fucking see anything.
It looks like I seriously took this guy's face and molded it out of clay.
Like, this was an art project that I did. I found out that I had to do this art project 15 minutes before it was due. And it was to make a person's face.
I can do better than this.
Why is this bullfrog person listening to this guy sitting on a park bench?
How can you keep a straight face right there? Would you not be scared of this?
You walk away.
See how big my arms are, dude? You have any idea how big my arms are, dude?
Sometimes you just gotta run. You know what I mean? Sometimes you're really going to build up that CO2 in your body and breathe it out, and you just kind of go on a little jog with your hands.
You know what I'm saying?
We've got to wrap behind this guy and do our stealthy little secret technique and get my little small sword.
Just get right in the back with the backstab.
Ugh!
The fucking lady's dead, man.
Wow. What a sicko.
I have some bad news, honey.
I accidentally backed over the cat this morning.
It's okay. He's in high spirits. He's still alright.
You know, I actually thought I was going to have way more to say about this.
This is a cat riding a horse.
I'll see you next year when this is a Disney Pixar movie.
You foul humans. We have every right to go through this tunnel.
You can't stop us.
Well, you've never seen a cat riding a horse before?
Get cultured.
Oh, shit. The fucking Thanksgiving turkey's on the loose.
Everybody watch out.
Hide the women and children.
No sudden movements.
Nothing crazy. I just gotta run my meat shop.
I'm doing well for myself.
I don't have to be concerned that there's an evil Gumby behind me.
Could be much worse.
Just don't let him know that you're afraid.
And everything will be okay.
This is a Dark Souls game.
What Dark Souls boss did I make?
Shoot to the arrow. Shoot me right in the penis. Good job.