All right, hi. Hello everybody. How's it going? How's your day?
A lot of stuff going on. About 15 minutes before, 20 minutes before, about to start the stream.
I had to make sure that Kim got to the doctor because she's not feeling well.
That was just popped up. I'm just coming off a few days of being disoriented from
having a procedure done to me and then we had to move Halo to tomorrow.
And then I had to talk to like a bunch of people. Today's been a busy, busy, busy day.
I almost read that out loud. It was really close for me to read that out loud.
Yeah, she's okay. How do I feel? Well, I've gotten a few answers and I'm not sure what
that means for these answers, but it means I have to keep going. I have to keep figuring stuff out.
But some of the things I thought were real are real. It's kind of a weird scenario. I have a
hernia. Let's just put it that way. I have a hiatal hernia and I might also have costochondritis,
which is inflammation in your ribs. Like my rib cage is like fucked up or something.
So, it's been a weird, it's been an interesting couple days. Let's put it that way. Am I all right?
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm doing all right. I'm fine. I got a hernia from laughing too hard. I don't think
so. I don't think that's how you get a hiatal hernia, but the harder I laugh, the more I'm in
pain. The hernia is just a hair ball in his stomach, but I still don't know exactly what's
going on. So, that was literally like two and a half, three days ago. So, hey, this is what's
going on. This might be something else going on. We're going to go talk to somebody else now.
The game board of figuring out medical issues is just, we move like two more spaces to the right.
You know, we rolled two and now, okay, when can we land on Park Place? Can I land on the boardwalk
yet? Like when do I pass a go? No, no, no. You landed on Baltic Avenue. That place sucks.
Yeah, I don't want Baltic Avenue. You're going to have to wait until next week. So,
you have to wait two weeks to go to take another turn. Oh, okay. Siri, don't, I'm not talking to
you, Siri. Get out of here. Don't record this, Siri. Don't record me. Anyways, I need to make
a tweet. All right, I'll be right back. I'll be right back. Okay. Sorry, I'm like texting people
to this. This like, it's the busiest day of the fucking year, apparently. But we are today,
today is not even a stream. Let me just be very, very clear about this. I was going to go three
days in a row starting with Halo, but Halo had to get pushed to tomorrow. I think Joel was doing
something that he wanted to finish. So I was like, yeah, that's fine. Let's go. And then on Friday,
we're probably going to do that tools up game. So we're just doing four days in a row because
like I'm still, I'm back. I'm coming back. So we'll just do probably three, four straight days in a
row as of today and tomorrow. What that means is we get to play a game that I've wanted to play
and everyone hates for some reason. Hey, I hate this game. This game sucks. This game's stupid.
Don't play that game. Well, I already bought it. So I'm just going to, we're just going to hang out
for a little while. And this is, this is a stream that's not even a real stream. The real stream
starts tomorrow. This is the pre stream comeback stream. We're going to be playing. Of course,
I'm talking about hand simulator. This one's not canon. I saw one person say, yes, this is the,
this is the halo reach tomorrow waiting room. Yes, I'm aware. All right. So how hand simulator
works for those of you that don't know, you just use your hands. You get to play with fidget spinners.
That was cool. The milkmaid, Merry Christmas and horror. Are we gaming? No. Well, let's do the fidget
spinners. Let's get it out of the way. This might be really loud too. I have no idea. Is it going to
be loud? It's not loud at all. There's no audio. Help. A S D F space, bend certain fingers.
How do I do, uh, A S D F. Oh, F is okay. This is the surgeon simulator, but you just do regular,
like normal stuff. Why is this? So is there any audio? Okay. Bend all fingers, hands mode. Oh,
you switch hands. Space is run. Crouch. Why would there be a crouch? Okay. Right mouse button is
rotate. This is just surgeon simulator with two hands. He's going to get bored. All right. So
how do I go down? Rotate forearm. But how do you, how do I move my hand just down? Like how do I
move it down? Middle mouse button? No. Why am I locked in place? What's wrong with me? Left shift
is hands. Okay. Oh, there we go. All right. So what do I need to do? I need to pick up the fidget
spinner and spin it. Oh, it's the mouse wheel. All right. Shit. This was like funny fucking seven
years ago. God damn it. I know. I understand. I know this was funny back in like 2013,
but just imagine we're there again. How do I pick this up? What do you mean? No, it wasn't.
If this was not funny in 2013, why did every single person make a YouTube channel about this
exact video game? It was bait. Somebody thought it was funny. All right. Pull it up. I did. Wait,
I almost got it. How are you supposed to grab stuff? Is this like the part, is this the game?
All right. I got it. Did I win? What do I do with it now? I have to make it spin. How do I lock this
into place? Spin it. This is like wrist exercises. How do I get it to move forearm, rotate forearm,
bend all fingers? Left shift hands mode. Okay. There we go. I see. Pull this down here. How do
you even use a fidget spinner? I don't think I've ever used one. This is wacky. You guys wanted
wacky? Here it is. It's not quite wacky. This would be music too. Why is it no audio in this whole game?
This is tearing, it's not tearing fingers off. Oh shit. This is just, this is like wacky in quotes.
I, now I know what you guys are talking about. Hold on. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I
at least have to get one of these done. I bought the fucking game. Play the multiplayer? Well,
I can't go into multiplayer until I know how this game, how the game works. All right. Put
the whole thing down. This game's $2? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'll get it.
Is it $2? Dab with the fidget spinner.
I need to, how do you, okay. I need to be able to do this. I need to do this in real life first.
How do you pick shit up? I don't even know how, how you, how the person you do this.
Like you grab, like I just grab stuff. I don't like know how I just do it. It's like breathing.
So I need to like pick this up in real life before I can actually know how to do this.
You go down and use your thumb, right? What's the thumb? Thumb is space. So if it were me in
real life, I would go like this and I would do my thumb and my index finger, right? Yeah. Okay.
This is how you pick stuff up, right? Here we go. Hold on. I almost got it. Get it. Come on,
pick it up. That one's too hard to get. I'm going to get this one. So what's the point of the other
hand? All right. Go like this. Come on. Okay. I got it. Now how do I, I gotta get it to spin.
What is like a soundtrack? All right, hold on. Let me get it to spin.
I can't breathe. I can't breathe. It's so funny. Oh, I fucking dropped it.
Fuck. I actually didn't mean to do that. Wait, this one's bigger. Maybe I can pick up a picture
I've already tried. Actually, wait, I probably can do that. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm interested now. I wasn't interested until 10 seconds ago. Give me the pencil. How do you pick
up a pencil? No, no, no, no, no. Don't drop it. I'm right-handed. I should be using this.
You see, he's a fucking wacky Twitch personality. It's too hard to grab stuff. Okay. I got this.
Now I have to activate it, right? So let's activate it. What's the hand again? It's this one.
All right. Flick it down, right? Why is this not working? Flick it down. Flick it down. What the
fuck am I doing? This looks like it hurts. Is it actually, is it already activated? No, there's no
pen coming down. What about the thumb? Let's try the thumb. Space, right? All right, bring it up.
Bring it back like this. Grip it. And then, is this pen already activated? Oh, I mean, oh.
Nothing about me. Something about me. I can't, I can't. No, I have to put it like up in my face.
I actually kind of like this. So I don't, middle mouse button is look mode. Wait, hold on.
Can I freeze individual hands? All right. Click it down. Why is it not clicking it down?
Am I stupid? Am I actually out of my mind or am I not doing this right? Both.
Don't, don't fuck come at me. Don't. I don't understand how this works. First of all,
this needs to go down. Act like a normal human and just put your hand down. And then this is how
I would leave you right on the desk. Okay. Now put this down here. Standard document. How do I
write? Wait, hold on. Let it go for a second. Middle mouse is look. All right. So shift hands.
So that's it. That is how you freeze. Okay. So if you want to freeze something, you have to hit
shift. So right now I need to, I gotta pick this back up. Just drop it. You're holding it like a
syringe. Yeah. Well, how the fuck am I supposed to do it? Is this even possible? Tell me now,
tell me, stop. I don't want to waste my time anymore. Is this possible to pick up the pen
and use it? Yes. Are you sure? Grab it. Grab it. Okay. I got it. Now I have to arc my hand up
like this. All right. Get it down there. Now, how do I do? Okay. Do I have to click this?
I actually have to click this down. You have to write funny. Yeah. But for me to write funny,
I need the pen to work and all these pens, you have to push these buttons down.
There's pressure there. Why is it not working? This should be working.
Is it ready to go? He doesn't know how to use a pen. This is how you use a pen. I know how to
use a pen. Look like this pen sucks. Okay. It needs it. Wait, stay right there.
Fuck. I almost got it. Come on. Just click for fuck's sake. Oh, please. I don't want to
just wait. I got to bring this over here closer, like up in my fucking face and put it up. So it's
like that. And then up into my face right there. Here we go. You gotta be fucking kidding me.
What's wrong with this pen? What is wrong? What's wrong with the pen? Use your palm instead.
That's not going to work. Why am I handing the air? What am I doing?
This is going to drive me fucking crazy. You know what? Move this hand over here.
Your hands just move on their own slowly. See how it's like moving to the right.
Come here. No, you fucking dumb thing. Move it over here and up right there.
Okay. Now I have my index finger. I'm going to tilt this like that. Why is this so hard?
Why is this so hard to do? This fucking camera. And then down. And then we do an index finger
right here. I'm going to do a different strategy coming through here. This is not how hands work.
No, it's not. It's a mess. I'm currently on it. How much pressure needs to go on this thing
to fit through the clothes? Why is this thing made out of fucking cement? Why can't I just
push it down? It doesn't make any sense. All right. Already angry? Yeah. Because like,
what the fuck? It doesn't make any sense. And plus, all right, when I move my hand to the right,
it just immediately moves it. Look at this. Where are you going? Where is this hand going?
Do I have my controller plugged in moving up? Move to the right. Are you sure you didn't move
up to the left? This is a chill stream. It is. Tilt it this way. Like this. Stay right there.
Come on. Wait. Somebody help me here and tell me why I can't move these things. All right. You got
to tell me why the fuck that ain't moving. It doesn't click. What do you mean it doesn't click?
Sometimes it just doesn't work. Give me the pen. No, give me the fidget spinner. Give me the beer.
Give me the, I don't know. Give me something else. Fuck. Why can't I lean this way? Bring the other
hand over here. Oh, it's gone. I can't even reach that far. How am I supposed to get this?
My body actually can't go that far. How are you supposed to reach this stuff on this table?
Is there like a lean button? C? C doesn't do anything. Can I like move my body? I can't even.
Nope. Oh my God. I got it. I got it. I got it. I almost got it. All right. The mouse scroll
into clicking and holding. Like that ain't going to work. Let me try. I have to do at least one of
these fucking tasks. I don't care how stupid and shitty this is. I almost got it. Come on.
If it spins in the air once, it counts. I don't care. No, wait, hold on. I think I can grab it
out of the other with the other hand. Oh no. He doesn't like hand game. Is that, is that really
a big deal? If I don't like hand simulator, that can't be a big deal. It's not a big deal.
If I don't like hand simulator, just grab it. Get it. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, didn't work. Can you even fucking do anything? Are you having fun? No. Ow. Stop. Hey,
you know, I got a hernia. You can't make me laugh. I have a hernia now. If I could pick this up,
make him laugh. Make him laugh. All right. I, I almost feel like I want a different control
scheme for this. Mouse XY and scroll wheel is move forearm. Using the scroll, I wish I could
just make that like right click and move down. In VR, it's a one-to-one movement. I feel like if
you did this in VR, everything would just be really easy. You just pick it up with your hands.
You just pick it up. Got it. I don't even know what buttons I'm holding. I don't know what buttons
I'm holding. Spin it. Quiet. That counts. That counts. That counts. I got it. It counts. It counts.
See? This would be real sad if you saw somebody doing this. Resident sleeper pog.
All right. Beat this one. Let's do another one. That took 30 minutes. Holy shit. Time flies when
you fucking hate the game you're playing. All right. How about, uh, let me see if I can fix
this though. No. All right. I did it. All right. What's the other ones? Milkmaid. All right. Now
we have all of a sudden audio. What is this? Cow? It's a cow. It's a cow. All right. Do I do
the other hand? So this one was, this is it. Punch the cow. Band that person. Get that person out
of here. I just had it too. I already did it. I did it. I can do the next one. It slipped. All
right. I win. I'm watching this in between classes. I'm milking a cow. This is a fucking cow.
All right. I got enough milk. I got enough. I got enough. Uh, what is horror? What the fuck is this?
Okay. You use WASD in this one. How do I control my hands? Am I gonna, am I gonna die?
Okay. That was, that was just, they were just there in the room.
Are you, they're slowly walking? Do I have to kill this person? All right. We're gonna use the
candle. No we're not. We're gonna use, um, there goes all my light. But why does your hand float
back up? I don't understand. When you put your hand down, it just comes back up. Down, up, down,
up. Stay down. That's how hands work. No, if I put my hand down, it's not gonna float up.
I'm not on a bunch of drugs. Hurry up. I'm trying. Punch her. I don't think you can punch.
All right. I'll try punching her. Come on Moe. What are you crazy?
Oh jeez. This looks like I'm just arguing. Why is she not walking any closer? I'm just like
pointing. Is it working? I think I'm pushing her. Um, is this working? Hold on. Oh, well that one
sucks. How about shooting range? Choose a weapon. All right. How about, um, zero? This is gonna be
impossible. This will be actually impossible. Maybe not. All right. Stay there. All right.
Keep it right there. Right. Which way does it go in? Like this. Yep. Don't drop it. Don't drop it.
Don't drop it. Don't drop it. Come back up. No. Other way. Oh man. This is not gonna work.
It has to be probably exact too. No. Pick it back up. It's not gonna work. Pick it back up.
All right. I have to come at this from a completely different angle.
Fucking mouse scroll. It like hurts my finger to do this this much. Get it over here. What the
fuck? Dude, imagine having mouse scroll be anything other than slide around a menu
in any video game ever made. What just happened? I caught it. How did I catch that? All right. I
gotta slow down. All right. That's not, that's not bad. That's not bad. Freeze it there.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Oh my fucking god damn it. Give me a break.
Do gun second. Not first. Please. Is there a way to rotate my wrist? Like that? Yeah. Do it again.
Fucking damn it, man. Why does this have to keep happening? Oh, it's killing me. You know when
you're in a really bad fucking dream and you just want to wake up but you can't? You have to fucking
pick up the clip. This is a bad, this is not even hand simulator. This is a, this is bad dream.
The game. I feel like I'm moving the same way that I move when I'm in a dream.
Got it. Now turn this way. Please. What are you doing? All right. Now give me the gun.
I'm not even, I'm right handed though. Wait. I'm up this way. Like that. All right. Almost there.
Almost there. Don't fucking move. Eat the bullets. Oh my fucking god. Why? This is,
you guys remember QWOP? Okay. Imagine if QWOP had 15 more buttons. Now it's upside down.
Just read fucking fresh shit again. Stop. Just get it. Play QWOP instead. I know. I know. I
feel the same way as you. All right. Can we just be very clear? I feel the exact same way,
but I can't, I have to do, I have to do this. I feel identical to your feelings. We are the same
right now, but I have to do something. I have to do this. I have to get the guy in the dream.
Don't move that hand. Just play QWOP. No, I'm not going to play QWOP. QWOP. You guys want to talk
about old YouTube shit? QWOP is the boomer of these LOL. It's hard to control games.
And you guys hate boomers. Don't, huh? I'm getting angry. Don't it's going to fall off the fucking
table. No, it's not. I got it. QWOP is a zoomer. No, it's not. It's, it is the boomer of these
types of games. Okay. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't let go. Don't
let go. What do I do? Don't let go. I have to use, I have to hit the mouse scroll, but I can't,
I can't reach it. No, I have to grab this at a better angle. Fuck. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
don't, don't, don't. This is going to be such a miserable experience. All right. Stop. Why does
it have to do that? Why does it do that? Why does it do that? You have to hold the thing. And then
when you switch, you're holding the wrong stuff. Make sure you spam mouse scroll down to be able
to even have your hand. Remember when you put your hand down, you, I've made out of fucking air. Why
would you ever make it that button for any reason? Literally make it, I make it controlled with my
tongue. It'd be easy to do. All right. See right now I have to hold all the things that I was
currently holding before. All right. Let's try it. It's weight. The weight is going down. Oh,
this sucks. This sucks. Get in there, please. I have to beat my nightmare. Oh,
oh, my whole body is fucking hurting right now. I hate it, but I can't, I have to have to do it.
I hate this. You know, you sit down to write a paper for college or for high school, doesn't
matter. And you, you hate, you, you write one sentence and you just go like, Oh, I fucking hate
this. And you like stand up, like move around. You're like, God damn it. I fucking hate this.
Then you know, you have to do it. This is, I feel the same exact way. I have to do this.
All right. I might be able to, what if I keep this right here? Tilt wrist down. It's almost there.
It's almost there. It's almost there. It's almost there. Look at this shit. Does it actually have
to be exact? No, it fucking doesn't. No, it doesn't. Why does it need to be exact? This is
a video game. Nothing's exact. You have to do it with one eye closed. Did somebody even just say
that or am I making that up? All right. It's not, it's not in the right place. This needs to be up
like this. Uh, don't, don't. Oh, if I feel like it's, Oh, no, no, just go in there. Get in there.
Get the fuck in here. Is it in? No, no, it's not. Dude, this is not hard to do this. This is not
hard to get this in here. Don't force it. It's not fucking possible. It's not possible. This is not
is not fucking possible. Where's my hand? Where am I going? What are you doing? What's it doing?
I'm not touching anything. You see in this shit. I'm not touching anything. Why is it? What is it
doing? All right. I would like to bring my arm down, please. Let go. You sure you don't want to
push it forward? That's not what I wanted you to do. Why are you like phantom moving? This is,
I don't know. What the fuck? All right. I'm going to try something else. Put the, put the gun down.
I want to try to get underneath it. Okay. Then down. This is absolutely not going to work.
Without a single doubt in my mind. There's no way this works. All right. I have to at least get it
in here. Maybe it'll be easier if I go this way. All right. I'm going to try this. It just doesn't
go the way it doesn't go where you want it to go. Stay right here. Move forward. Don't fucking move.
You're moving. Why are you moving? You shouldn't be. Which way does it go in? Which way does it go
in? Like this? I don't know. Would you like to move left? No, move right. Why is it fighting me to
move left? Dude, this shit is fighting me. Move left. No, move this way. Move left. No, you want
to move this way. Move left. No, move that way. What are you doing? Why is it a rubber band?
Why the fuck is it a rubber band? I just move here and stop. Move mouse left. Move mouse right.
No, what are you doing? You don't want to move mouse right? No, I want you to stay here.
It's not. It's not going to work. God. Why is my arm just broken? Why do you have to hold it like
this? I have a better idea. I have to hold the gun in a different spot. I have to hold the gun
with two hands. Yeah, fuck this. Give me this thing. Fucking mouse scroll. Imagine having mouse
scroll. Imagine it. Just imagine mouse scroll. I just want you to picture it in your head.
All right. Move it this way. No, I just want to imagine. Imagine. Oh, God. Pain in the ass.
This is great. All right. Now, wait. I just want to tilt it down. Why is it so hard to
even rotate your wrist? It's just all fucked up. No, I ain't going to be able to do that.
This guy at the gun range, it's like, no, you're doing that real wrong.
You know what? I have a better idea. Am I going the right way? This is painful to watch. This is
painful to play. So I agree with you. It sucks. But I have to try. No, no. Wait, wait, wait.
This is the opportunity. Why are you naked at a gun range? I don't know. Because I don't know the
lore. Okay. Hold on. My initial plan might work pretty well here. My hand needs to go down like
that. All right. Everybody hold your breath for a second. Beautiful. Hold it in place. Let go of
this. Oh, fuck. Yeah. All right. Now hold on. Now I just need to put this in the right spot.
Up and like over here. Okay. You can breathe now. Yeah. Take a nice deep breath out. And then
this needs to be perfectly straight. Just go to the left. If I move to the right, he moves to the
right. If I tilt to the left, he moves to the right. What are you doing? Like move your fucking
hand. I hate this game. This is the worst game of the decade. I can't even bend my wrist. It's
the weight of the gun. Oh, please. I can't even get the thing to stay straight. Come back over
here. Try a grenade. No, I'm not quitting. I'm not quitting yet. Just because you say a game is the
worst game of the decade doesn't mean that you're not going to try to win. Give me my other hand.
Wait, that's not a bad spot. Where's the clip? All right. Get it over here. I have to spin this
around. You have to throw a grenade. I'm not done yet. I need to move this in a circle with like
my thumb. Just don't knock it off the fucking table. All right. So that's going to be going
the right way, right? Keep spinning it. Let it go. It needs to go. All right. So shoe out,
right? Forward shoe out. Is that correct? Like the toe of the shoe here. It goes out. Tab forward.
Right. Okay. All right. Cool. So I have to do spin this. Don't fall off the fucking table, please.
All right. Almost there. All right. Tab is almost going to be facing out. Just going to grab it
from. I can't, I have to make sure I grab it from the bottom. I got to close all my fingers
completely. And then cause it'll get stuck. All right. Tab is now facing out. Hold on. I
should be able to let it go from here and it won't fall off the table, but it'll be in the
right. Oh my fucking God. Don't fall off the table. Don't fall off the table. Don't do it.
Jesus Christ. Oh fuck. Okay. Hold on. This is important.
It's going to fall off the table. It's going to fall. I have to use the gun.
I actually am naked. You're right. That is weird. All right. Wait, flip it again. Now it's almost
there. Why can't I just tilt the gun to the left? There's like an invisible wall here where I can't
move the gun this way. I can go literally every single other direction. Fuck you. No, not you.
You. Me? No. Yes. Not yes. Not yes. This. Why is my pinky not closed? Oh my, I don't understand why
I don't get it. I can go every other direction. The gun is apparently too heavy for me to hold
in one hand. Is this the new Mario Tennis? No, because everybody likes Mario Tennis.
That's different. That's a different scenario. Except for me. I like Mario Tennis. I don't like,
I don't actually like Mario Tennis. I just have to say that. Again, let me just maybe be very
clear about this. Move character's arm to the right. No. Go that way instead. Move character's
arm in. No, just go that way. I don't have any actual precise control of my character.
Sometimes he just, just bounces. It's over. Zero progress. Point and laugh. Yeah,
I'll give you a laugh. Such a fucking mess. What a mess. I know, look, I know this is what the
game's point is. I understand. I know. I know the point of the game is for this scenario. This is
what everybody likes and everybody wants to see. It was made for this scenario. This one. This is
what you wanted to see. This is what everybody plays this game for. No one wanted to see that.
That's right. Fuck, you're right. No one wanted to see this. Shit. Yeah, nobody wanted to see this.
Everybody said, don't play this. This game's terrible. And I was like, oh no, I want to do it.
Yeah, I get it. You're right. Nevermind. Shit, I was wrong. I'm sorry. I was about to go off
like a tangent about what you wanted to see and nobody wanted to see this.
I'm like painting a pretend fucking narrative. This is what you guys said. This is what you guys
wanted. No, no, we didn't. Oh, right. What I meant to say was here's the fucking worst thing though.
I like need to see this. I have to do this. I can't open this and then not do it because then I'll
never live this down, you know? I'll be the one moron that opened this game and went, no,
I don't, this is dumb. And then, no, no, no, I have to do it. I have to at least load the gun.
I have to load the gun. I have to load the gun. Wait a minute. Will this work? No, I didn't pick
it up. Great. Yeah, didn't pick it up. It didn't pick the fucking thing up. And now I'm on a
different view. This is fantastic. Oh, good. Do it again. No, no, do it again. No, do it again.
Okay, this time. No, you didn't get it. Okay, please. Spam mouse scroll. Now click. Did you get it?
No, sorry. Your hand floated four inches up for no reason. Spam mouse scroll. Click. I think I got
it. Did I get it? Oh, good. Got it this time. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. It's almost there.
It's almost there. Stop, stop. Stop. Can I save state? In there, please. How is it not going in?
What? Why is it going out? Why? Go in. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Go. Go. Go. Why? It's stuck. No, it's not. Wait, hold on. Move my thumb out of the way, maybe. No,
no, no, no, no. Turn the whole thing upside down. Stop. Okay. Turn the whole thing upside down.
Fuck. Let go. Let go. Let go. Let go with your finger. Let go with your finger. Let go with
your finger. Let go. Let go. Let go. Let go. Not yet. Don't. I'm crossing here. Should I let go of
my finger? Let go. Okay. Yeah. What did I say? Worst game of the decade? That's fucking harsh.
I got it. Now shoot it. Okay. Wait, wait, this been a bunch of subs that have come in. Okay. I got
it. Now I just have to shoot it. Get my finger in there. Oh, that scared the shit out of me. Okay.
That's how you shoot the gun. I shot it. All right. So I shot the gun. I did it.
I have to aim it. I have to hit the target and then I can play a different game. I'm not going
to play a different game. I'm like obsessed. Look, this is the extra stream this week. We already
talked about it. This four days in a row. This is the extra stream. This stream didn't even happen
today. You're all imagining things. You're dreaming things. You can't wake up from the dream. All right.
Let's go. All right. Now I can move my hands like this. Perfect. All right. The pinkie's got a thing.
Okay. Here we go. I'm trying. Okay. Why is it? Why am I dropping it? Why am I dropping it? Does
this gun weigh like 70 pounds? What are you doing? What are you doing? What the fuck is it doing?
Come here. Oh, don't do it. Don't shoot me. Okay. It can't shoot me now. Oh, it's freaking me out.
Don't drop the gun. I need to actually, I can, I can drop the gun over here. I'll try picking it
up one more time. Don't let it go. I'm not going to let it go. What's the next gun? I should try
the sniper rifle. There's no way I'm going to be able to do that without a single doubt in hell.
Jesus Christ. I have to at least get a shot fired over here. I'm trying. Don't drop the gun.
It's aiming at my stomach now. This is not good. Ooh, tilt.
I'm not gonna. I have to just put it back over here. Oh, it's in a bad spot.
I don't like this game. I really don't. It's like, it's seriously causing me a ton of anxiety right
now, but I can't stop. All right. No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Just give me the damn thing.
Chill stream. Oh, beg a lull. Whatever. I can hold it upside down. The gun still works upside down.
Pick it up. Grab it. Half-life Alex game play.
All right. Just aim it. Did I get one? All right. I shot him. Okay. I got it. Yep. Right over there.
I got two. One, two. Okay. Cool. What's the next thing? Why can I not use the, what do I mean?
I can't. Why can I spawn the other gun? You have to unlock the next one. You need points
to unlock the next one. I'm going to do this real quick.
Shit. Okay. I know. I know. I know. I know. I know. I know. No, no, no, don't do it! No! No!
Just hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Just hold on everybody. I know. I know. I know. I know. I know.
But whatever. This is not even a real stream. Fuck. Just re-do it, re-do it, re-do it, re-do it.
I just realized this streamer is only in 720p. Oh no. What a disaster. I can't believe he's in
720p that sucks that's fucked up yeah 720 60 you guys know anything about bitrate
if you do a 1080 stream at like four five six thousand k up unless you're at 30 fps
that looks like shit when you don't know anything about bitrates you guys want 1080p for this game
that's even sadder the human eye can't see past 30 fps but that's not that's bullshit because
human eye can see rainbows so i'm just gonna crush that right there put this down all right
is it is it tilted or something what's going on play feet simulator next i don't think i'm
gonna do that imagine trying to load a gun and fire it with your feet
be fucking ridiculous speaking of fucking ridiculous almost all right now oh why do you
have to be so finicky about every single movement stop much faster than last time
it's not even on there stop fucking goddamn nightmare i can't take it anymore just get it
in i'm trying slow oh it's going it's going it's going it's going all right okay all right all right
okay now um it's not backwards don't fucking just pull it push it forward
that's it i can't take this anymore hello ladies and gentlemen weapons and what i'm sure my crap
the series where i play Minecraft just get some hot cocoa go go go go get coffee coffee and all right
so yeah
we have bottled lemon thanks to 10 community subs and then a b joe thanks with 5 000 bits
are you winning son jeremy pop no can i pick it up that means i have to stay
that means i have to stay oh i have to stay oh i gotta write i wrote fucking the
and i got it from the chair again but thank you for the 50 fucking dollars a b joe and there was
other community subs as well that i've missed i'm too locked in to the worst game of the decade
that's not fair that's can i just be clear that's not fair the worst game of the no it's not fair
it's not fair it's not fair it's not fair okay i gotta get up and like move all right the ancient
civilization of maya the ancient civilization of maya i gotta just fucking get it don't i can't
fucking believe it i need to unlock the gun stop move it forward move it forward what are you stupid
stop just jeremy jeremy jeremy jeremy no it's not lined up perfectly jeremy jeremy jeremy jeremy
jeremy jeremy jeremy jeremy jeremy jeremy i can't fucking believe it i fucking i'm
imagine the speed runs of this game you know they exist you know they do and well i just
pressed one accidentally he's mauled no i'm upset there's a difference just move the gun a little
bit how did i get it so quickly last time seriously okay this was the invisibility
bullshit what's this invisibility bullshit look at this what's the invisible wall my god
i fucking have to do it this shit was just not even touching it was like an invisible wall
between the two pieces slow oh my fucking god it's like playing the crane game there's like no
rhyme or reason to any of this shit let's just take a wild fucking guess jeremy please stop for
the love of all is holy stop for your health and mine i can't take it anymore i'm about to die
what this shit is so stupid i had it the first fucking time now how do i how would you even
tilt i you can't even tilt forward i can go like this but then i can't take it anymore my fucking
god it's just it's so unbearable dude this is the type of cia shit that they make you do before
you can like apply this is part of the fucking cia test you want to be like an fbi agent you
have to play this game first then not show a single sign of emotion and get it right the first time
when am i going to stop i might not ever stop it might never end now i need to turn this gun
because it's impossible to actually spin anything in this game you have to like
swipe your hand on it all right stop stop stop i got it it's almost there almost it's pretty
much perfectly lined up bring it up a little what is even the problem here what is the fucking
problem what's the goddamn problem that's not lined up what the fuck what the fuck fucking about
what are you talking about not you i'm talking about gate like what are you talking about
not you guys the game like what are you talking about press f1 i know the controls
i've been playing for an hour and a half really like i know how to move my hand i'm gonna write
this paper just go stop moving to the i'm not moving up ah okay down go up no that's just stay
here i just you know what you go up go down don't go up why are you doing this down lift my hand
off the keyboard control no we're going up why am i made out of fucking helium
all right what's your shoe size 14 fucking god damn it man this is so stupid
game just game crashed fucking helium filled hands game crashed oh it's
it's time for happy wheels get out of here with that shit no we're gonna do
merry christmas because it's almost christmas how do you even play multiplayer in this game
this one is this one's stupid too isn't it all right you can break stuff can you drive a car in
this game wait let me light some incense you're ruining christmas it's fine okay all right down
go back how did you get back here because i'm addicted to pain apparently thank god all right
i'm giving it five minutes and then i'm doing something else no the game's gonna crash again
this is what you get from misbehaving and free stream again move arm forward arm is moving back
move on forward no i want to move back move arm to the right are you sure you don't move back
why is it weighing me down the other direction we get it i need you to know i need you to know
i'm a fucking radio host that keeps going over the same ad i'm done i do elf bowling i did shoot
the gun though i did just not at the target all right now what the hell am i gonna do
why would i start kenshi i played it like a year and a half ago it start new what no here's what
we're doing we are gonna start but we're not gonna finish it uh we're gonna start a game that i am
looking forward to playing we're gonna play a medieval medieval i did say that i wanted to
start that this week we are not gonna finish it probably until next uh week though and i say that
because we got a lot of stuff going on this week how long is the game this is by the same studio
that did dusk by the way tf2 what are you guys talking about is this the part of the stream
where we bring up games i haven't played in over a year farm dynasty no give me one second wait
how long has the stream been muted for did you guys hear anything i just said
did i just unmute or did i mute that's weird why is it indicated that it's on or off all right give
me one second i gotta change some streaming stuff around i'm gonna play a medieval thanks with 10
subs for litty i did fire the gun so i did win thanks for the 10 community subs for litty and
wait somebody else gave subs too that i missed before bottle lemon to 10 it was snar bosis gave
10 thank you snar bosis appreciate it and i think that was it for community subs it came through
all right give me a second let me uh change some of these things around let me capture a
new thing and i'll be right back see you in a second