What do you think about the new track? This is not replacing the starting soon screen, by the way.
I just kind of really wanted you to listen to it. I think it's great. I think it's really good.
Bloordow made some new things, as you can probably see. We have new sub badges.
We have a bunch of new music. Is it gonna be on? I got a lot. We'll go through them.
Well, no, maybe not. Maybe you should be surprised. Time for a new season.
I'm one hour late because of Daylight Savings.
Now, what I meant to say was, yes, I value what you just said.
But we live in a world where we move our clocks around.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding. It was a joke. I'm kidding.
All right, let's turn this down. Yeah, that's one of the new tracks. There are four new tracks.
Let's put the old one on. Here's the old one.
And Bloordow just, honestly, somebody got to hire Bloordow to make a whole game soundtrack.
When I listen to these songs that he makes, I'm thinking of indie games that would just,
he'd probably win fucking music of the year if he actually got onto a game or something.
He would win soundtrack of the year if he was able to just kind of go wild and do whatever he
wanted. Speaking of Bloordow, there's a lot of new people here that do not know who Bloordow is.
Let's go ahead and make a very, very quick shout out to Bloordow. Bloordow is the person
responsible for the J, the way that it looks, its whole design. All the channel branding that you
see is from Bloordow. All the music that you've heard, at least on regular streams like this,
sometimes it's not Bloordow. But for the most part, the little tracks you hear are Bloordow.
I want to make sure that we send some support his way. Let me get you some links here. This is his
band camp. Make sure we get that in the exclamation point if we can for exclamation point Bloordow.
And he also has one of those coffee, co-fi, whatever it is. He's absolutely incredibly
talented. Deserves to be supported for sure. It's coffee, right? Well, I don't know, co-fi.
What am I supposed to say? I don't know. Is it SoundCloud 2? Yeah. You're gonna hear today
another like three or four tracks and there's more badges going up and me and Bloordow were
talking and we think we might be doing potentially seasonal BRB screens. Seasonal intro screens
that have different music and different animations and not just this one. Why not, right? It should
be fun. Seasonal BRB. Yeah. Stuff for holidays maybe. I don't know. Just that would be fun.
This is a new season. It's crazy that it took me this long. All right. It took me so long
to do any of this stuff. We're like 11 years into me being on YouTube and Twitch and stuff.
Like it's what the hell? Why has it taken me this long? Lazy. Yeah. Yeah. Maybe a little.
If it isn't broke, don't fix it. Did I say that wrong? If it ain't, if it's not broke,
if it isn't broken, how did I, what did I say? If it ain't broke, don't fix it.
What? Well, how do you say that? Okay. No, I got it right. Yeah. I said it right. I got it. I got it.
All right. Let's, uh, we're gonna play gas station simulator today. Hope everyone had a good week.
We will be live today and probably Wednesday. So we'll do that. Got some stuff to do. Gas
station simulator. I'm looking forward to it. How are you? I'm doing okay. I'm doing all right.
You know, I'm doing all right. I'm doing good. I'm doing all right. If it fixed, broke it.
He's so high already. I'm not, I'm not, I'm not going to. Okay. It's time for boring games.
Boring games are back. Pog. What do you, what? This is a boring game. I thought everybody wants
me to play this. Everybody's been, so many people have wanted me to play this game.
That's not a boring game. How's the boring game? You're stalling. I have, no, I'm not stalling.
We just heard new streaming musical content. We heard new streaming musical content. That's not
stalling. All right. Let's go. Gas station simulator. Again, support Lordow. A lot of the
character and a lot of the, a lot of the vibe of this stream is because of Lordow, right?
And he's going to be making more shit. So go support him. All right. Make sure my camera's
not on. It's not. All right. Gas station simulator. Let's go. Can you hear it? Cause I can't.
There it is. A little loud for me, not for you. I'm not stalling. I'm not, what do I mean stall?
How am I stalling? Stop. Okay. So how do we play? I'll badge check. Anybody have the new ones?
There's like six or seven new ones. There's more, but I want some of the newer ones that are a little
less. There's some that are a little less elaborate that I want to be in that two, three, four, five,
six month period. Right. But I don't think I can move them around. I think I actually have to like
delete them and re-upload them. So I have to do that. I'll do that another time, but there should
be some new ones there. All right. Gas station simulator. It may take a while for what? To load
the game. There's a GTA screen. Gas station simulator. Have you updated windows? I have
not updated windows in like probably like a year. I'm just kidding. Am I driving? It's a cut scene.
Loud cut scene. Be careful. Be aware. Loud cut scene. Is there no mirror? Oh wait. No, there is.
I was going to say, where is it? For sale. Am I going to get the car stuck? Congratulations.
You're now the owner of Dust Bowl gas station. Okay. 12 hours later. I gotta turn on like V-Sync,
I think. Okay. Hold on. Hold on. I got V-Sync has to turn on. Where is it? I'm seeing a lot of
screen tearing. Where is it? Is it here? Display. Lock FPS. V-Sync on. We can lock FPS. Yeah.
We still getting screen tearing? That's much better. Okay. Better, better, better, better,
60 FPS. Yeah. Whatever. Change the FOV. I don't think you can. I think it's fine the way it is.
This is going to come way down. Like three maybe. Can somebody explain this to me? I know there's a
really simple explanation and people are going to be like, dude, this is why and you never knew that
you're an idiot. That's fine. Why does it seem like every single game I've ever played? Like to get
the mouse to actually work, it's got to be way down here. Like shouldn't this bar be way smaller?
I feel like I would... there's no... everybody always puts it like down here, like one centimeter
on the bar. Why does that keep happening? Is it because of just different mouse DPI's? Like DPI's
like just so high? Because look, ready? So that's at 0.3 and I... that like feels pretty good. Maybe
0.4. That's all the way down to the left of the bar. Dude, you're an idiot. That's fine. Let's do
0.5. All right. I gotta get out there. Gas station. I use high sensitivity. I usually like to keep it
high. It kind of makes my head hurt a little bit. All right. What we got? Figure out how to enter
the gas station. Hint while holding something. Throw it right mouse bumper into the trash to get
a score. What? Throw it into the trash can. Is there a trash can? Did you tweet? I didn't...
look at me. I'm not even fucking streaming. I didn't tweet. You're right. Let me take care of
that. Stalling? Gas station simulator. Just to the point. We're not going to add any flare or
anything. There it is. Okay. A colonoscopy tomorrow? It's... what have... retry? What?
That didn't go through? Why? How did my... the tweet didn't go through. Why not? And why does this
happen? Do you hear this? Did you hear that? Somebody had to have heard that. Why does my
volume just go to 100 randomly when I type? Does that happen to you guys? What the fuck does that
do that for? I didn't know. I'm not hacked. That happens all the time. Just will go to a thousand
percent volume. Okay. Gas station simulator. Tweet. Your tweet was sent. Okay. I don't understand why.
Dude, you gotta fucking freeze your credit score. Oh shit. Yeah, I... guys, my tweet didn't go
through. I gotta freeze my credit scores. I'll be back. I'll see you like next week or something.
Throw into the trash? Is there a percentage for throwing? Okay. Well, I can throw things.
Where's the trash? Are you serious? Holy shit. Oh, right here. There it is. Yeah, I got the high
score. This is some Olympian shit right here. All right. Well, it's kind of hard to do.
Figure how to enter the gas station. Okay. Give me a break. What the fuck? Okay. Okay. Let's go.
Do I get money for doing this or just points or something? Last score. Longest score distance.
Why is that a thing? Do I have to empty the dumpster? How am I supposed to do this?
This is not a gas station. This is a disaster. It's gonna take like $500,000 to repair all this
and redo everything. Yeah. Is that even about my house? Yeah. What is that? A sprint?
Was this like alien spaceship over here? What is that? Oh, this is a sign. Oh boy. Oh boy.
That was bad. I thought that was like a weird like tripod alien monster thing. Okay. What we got?
More trash. Pass completed. Okay. All the high voltage cable and find a way to turn on the
electricity. I mean shouldn't I do something about this? This is bad. Can I repair this or redo this?
Oh, the high voltage cable. Okay. Caution. High voltage cable? Where's there a high voltage cable?
In here? Has it been back there? Read that clock. There's no minute hand guys. I can't read it.
I was about to say holy shit. Why can't I do this? All right. Where's the high voltage cable?
Buy fuel. Oh fuck. Okay. Hold on. What's out here? I thought it was inside the house. That's why I
didn't look at the... I thought it was inside the house. Okay. What we got? Power back on.
Bro, you've been streaming for four hours. I have not. Are you legitimately high today? No.
Pick up the phone at the booth in the front of the station. No. I don't like coincide every time I
turn on a stream with me being like high on marijuana cigarettes. Okay. All right. Who is it?
Congratulations on your purchase and investment, little nephew. It has been a while since you've
heard my voice now, hasn't it? I guess, yeah. Yes. I'm a busy person, but luck would have it. But
the land you've purchased once belonged to my father. Since you are not only a potential
business partner, but family no less, I'll do my best to help you. Hey, thank you. I will send
your emails on a regular basis, providing you with information on how to handle each part
of the business. Do make sure to pay attention. Well, I always feel so bad about this kind of
stuff. Okay. It was pleasant speaking to you again. Okay. Let's be maybe potentially relatable Andy
here. So how many times you guys opened up your email that you haven't like opened in like months
and like an aunt or an uncle has like sent you three emails and it's just like, oh fuck, I don't
communicate this way at all. I don't want to, I'm not trying to like avoid anybody or anything. I
just don't communicate like through email and I always like feel so terrible. I don't like
communicate at all. I'm serious. I read the email on the computer. Okay. How do we turn the gas
station on? All right. Gas station mail. Howdy. Greetings and salutations. The dialect never really
was my forte. Regardless, I've just heard you've made a solid investment. Though I pity the fact
that you had to sell your car for it. You could have always asked me for a loan. I'll pitch in
with a few tips and tricks. My emails will come periodically. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You need to get
this station up and running. Who knows how badly it got damaged all those years ago. Don't forget
to keep generating profit, refurbish a fuel dispenser first. Oh, and don't worry about the
money for this part. We're a family after all. And family keeps an eye on each other's backs. And
why am I doing like a sports center routine? And family keeps an eye on each other's backs. I'm here
to let a helping hand and make a man like me puts money with my mouth is as they say. I feel like
I'm reading about like the last NFL game, like baseball game or something. Market player already
played this game. Yeah. Okay. And he's like the god of the internet. That's what do you want me
to say? Like, that's literally like god of online entertainment. Who doesn't like like market player?
Right. You know, I watched a jacksepticeye video the other day and I was like, this is like,
this is a good dude. Like I like like this guy. Different person. Well, I'm just saying like
another YouTuber, you resuded. Well, okay, look, if I had a choice, right, of like who I wanted,
like if I had like kids, right, and they grew up a little bit, and I have like friends or whatever.
Well, I do have friends, but you know, forget what I'm saying. I would want them to watch
with YouTubers like that. That's whatever. Okay, question mark. I didn't bring them up. You did.
Why is everybody acting like I just brought up these the YouTubers out of nowhere?
You know, guys, let me tell you something. I watched market player yesterday and boy was he
he was great. No, I was react. Oh, hold on. But I mean, I like those guys. I think they're
they've got good channels. What? What? I can't talk. I'm not allowed to talk about somebody
in like a positive way. I don't have any gas. Oh, shit. How am I supposed to Okay, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, find a way to refuel Rudy. Search around for an old Jerry can. Okay,
I need to find an old can. This dude runs a gas station and is out of gas. Okay, while holding
the Jerry can click left mouse button on the distributor to replenish it. If it's full,
click left mouse button on the excavator's fuel cap or fuel it. Okay, so I can equip it. Ooh,
this is empty. You have new mail and that's going to go to there's going to be an X next to new mail
up to like 12,000. Okay, place and we get it. Oh, shit, I got it. All right. All right. Now,
I'm going to refuel Rudy. Why does this game exist? I think it's kind of cool.
Okay, this is full up. Alright, so now return to removing the sand piles. Alright, sand piles.
Remove sand piles. F to interact. Fuck, don't do that. Why is it saying F to interact?
Okay, hold to break turbo. Okay, please. I have to remove the sand. How do I do that?
I didn't do it. When the exhaust turns red, hold right mouse button to cool the engine
overheating locks turbo. How do I do the turbo? No idea. Don't flip it over. Spacebar break.
What about T? Okay, left mouse button is pick up and drop sand. Okay, so it's left mouse button.
Okay, so get right here. I got it. Where am I supposed to put this? Open the gas station
for customers. This thing this thing's pretty much on fire inside. What? I wouldn't want to
open. This is a hazard. I dump it. How do I dump this? Oh, fucking whatever. Am I in trouble?
Okay, what the lights on? Alright, gas stations turn it on. Flip the switch. Let's go. You can
open and close the gas station at any time. Use the downtime to organize the gas station or do
other activities that you can find. Right next to the lever, there is a button that restarts traffic.
What? We're open for business. My entrepreneurial ship begins today. Oh shit, a customer. Please
stop. Okay, refill your fuel supplies using the PC. What? Oh shit, there's a customer. Where's my PC?
It's a mess in here. Delivery. I need fuel. How much? How much was it? Just two cents? Your order
is less than 100 units. Alright, I need 100 units order. I need gas first. Hello. Welcome.
Is there gas in here? Okay. I don't have any gas.
This is like the Luigi driving by in Mario Kart phase. Holy shit, man. I'm sorry. Oh, here's the
delivery. Don't come in. Wait, I want you to come in. This is the delivery truck? Why is this
a hearse? Is it what it looks like? It looks like the Oscar Mayer hot dog car. This is what
that car looks like. That's crazy. Alright, yeah, back it up. It's the wiener mobile.
You're literally insane. I hope you know that. Yeah, I mean, I guess you're right. Alright,
hook it up. Need help? Oh shit, nice. Alright, you can't hit anybody. Just in case you were
wondering. Because I wasn't. Alright, is it in? Wait, am I putting it back in his car?
Oh shit, I think I put it back in his car. How do I get it? Do I have it? Is there gas in there?
Wait, there's a customer. Do I have fuel? I don't have any fucking fuel. What? Hey,
you know, I'm not gonna pay for it if you take it. Get back here. Get back. I'm gonna put my
mouth on it. What happened to my gas? Officer, arrest that man. I have gas. It said no fuel.
You have a hundred. I just walked three times. The gas. The person at the pump right now is like,
I just watched this guy walk around his house three times. This guy's a fucking crack. Oh,
okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. So what? That's how much gas they want? Alright, stop, stop, stop, stop.
You're welcome. Open tools. I have a backpack. Okay. Alright, goodbye. Who's coming up next?
How much gas do I have? I'm like 85. I need more gas. Sweep the cars with the broom. Is there a
broom? Where? Where's this broom you're talking about? Where's the broom? Play the arcade game.
Yeah, but this... Wait, I gotta close the gas station. No. Alright, I'm going. Test your skills
in the arcade. You unlock it later. Okay. Well, I don't have it then. I don't have it right now.
What is this? Race car. Get through all the checkpoints in the outlined order.
Finish the race before 1 15 to get 20 bucks. Oh shit. Alright, I got it. Well, I mean, how
was it close to know where the road went? I can still do it. Okay. Why did that happen? First F
to quit the car. Well, I don't think it was a minute and 15. I don't think I'm going to get a
minute 15. This is for $20. This is just a mini golf course. Oh my god. I thought this
said save the customer at the fuel dispenser. What happened? What did he do? The car can only
be refueled after the customer has left the car. Okay. Hello. Grab the injector when client is
waiting. Fuel cap will be outlined. Fuel the car by interacting with the cap. Boost the speed. Hit
the mark to get paid a tip. Thank you. Where's the broom? Okay. I have 72 liters, which that
should last me a little while. 320 bucks. What else can I do? Buy a trash bag and equip it.
Oh, here we go. Trash bag free. You can buy tools. Okay. Trash with a trash bag. You can pick up
small garbage and replace garbage bags and trash cans. Bigger garbage like junk or filled trash
bags must be put in containers outside. You need to order garbage collection using a PC.
If you left trash cans for a long time, they'll start to stink and discourage customers.
Why would I have opened this place yet? Okay. So collect small trash. Okay. Then what do I just
dump it? Okay. Empty the trash cans inside the station with your trash bags. Okay. Dispose of
filled trash bags and old furniture. All right. I like this. This is hitting all the notes for me
right here. All right. There's a bunch of trash. Hold on. Yeah. I know it's making bags. I'm going
to run around and pick them all up later. What do you have for a coaster? It's Pac-Man coasters.
Just Pac-Man. You know, nothing's crazy. You can't throw away the grandfather clock. That'd be weird.
All right. Let me see. Dispose of filled trash bags. You got it. Oh, shit. All right. I got to
get good at this. It's not 20%. What is it from this door? What is it from here to here?
If I hold my cursor like right there. No, it's probably like 40%. A little bit higher. Like
right here. Yep. Okay. I think I got it down. God damn it. There's so much junk everywhere.
There's a customer. Oh, it's a cop. All right. You got it. Thank you. Do I close the gas station?
I have to clean up. Anarchy. Anarchy. Anarchy. Anarchy. No. No. Anarchy. Okay.
I'm trying to run my business here. Everybody in jazz is saying Anarchy. Anarchy. Anarchy. Anarchy.
Oh, that's funny. Any more trash? How much can fit in one dumpster?
Guess we'll find out. Because this is still going in, right? Yeah. There's so much trash. Although
I'm probably going to be able to clean this up though. I'm looking forward to this. This is
going to be awesome. God damn it. It's with the calming music. Yeah, it is kind of just calming,
isn't it? Should I call for the service to come pick this up? Or should I? Did I pay for one
dumpster when I need four dumpsters worth of space? But just pile everything on top up to here with
one dumpster and pay one dumpster price. Customer. Oh, hello, sir. Madam. How are you? Hold on. Let
me just hold on. You had a little stain on your window there. Welcome. I got the best gas prices
in the entire valley. You just stay right there. Perfect every time. Remember, tell your friends.
I really appreciate a potential at least four star on Yelp if you could. We have zero reviews,
even on Google, which is unheard of. Yup. Thank you. Have a wonderful evening. Tell your friends.
Thank you. Okay. Yeah. And none of that bullshit where on Google you give me a five,
but on your Yelp account you give me like a three eight. None of that bullshit. Google's always
higher. You gotta be careful. You have to take the average. If you look up like a restaurant,
like, oh, what's this place? This place looks kind of good. Maybe I'll try here maybe. How's this one?
It's got like a four eight on Google. And on Yelp, that same place has like a three five.
It's like, what is, what's going on here? Who recommends gas stations? What's wrong with
recommending a gas station? What if it's like the people there are friendly and, oh,
uh, hello. I'm so glad you made it to my station. What a car. It's 2016. Oh, love it. Love it. Love
the paint job too. Is it? That's like a ocean teal. Absolutely fantastic. These are off-road
tires too. Very, very cool. You come out here often? Yeah. Yeah. Nice. I'm just on vacation
with the family. That's really cool. Awesome. Awesome. Awesome. So just fill you up. And if
you, I got snacks too, if you need anything. It didn't need very much. Uh, yeah. I gave you
a pretty decent review of your car. I thought it was a nice car. I would get, I would probably
give your car, I would say probably like a 4.5. That's what I would give your car. Uh, so if
whatever you want to give me, um, I would, I gave you a four five on your, I'd like your teal.
Thanks for coming again. Don't talk to the customers. Why not? Why are you such a serial
killer? Um, I got, I have to get this taken. There's too much here. You're a real charlatan.
No, I have, I have fair gas at fair prices. Okay. I'm going to buy a broom. This place is
cleaning up a little bit. Okay. So what is it? How sweep the floor? Oh, this cleaning
in the top of corner, you can see the floor is dirty status. Swipe the footprints, paint stains
and other, other dirt from the floor. If you do not take care of the cleanliness customers will
stop shopping. What do you mean shopping? This thing sucks. This doesn't do anything. Oh my
God. It's going to take forever. All right. Is there any, hold on. You actually have to sweep
with it. You have to push it. There we go. I need more. Don't know. Yeah. Yeah. I'll get back on
that in just a second. Fill that order for the customer back there. Yeah. We want to take care
of our, we want to take care of our people there. Hey, how are you? Good to see you. Okay.
Got to fill you up here. Sorry. We got like, got some customers, but pretty busy.
What do you need? Just regular unleaded. You've got it. 29.75. Have a great day. Have a wonderful
day. Have a good day. Have a one. Have a good day. Have an awesome day. You're a psycho. Whatever.
It took you this long to figure that out. Okay. Why won't this clean? Shit. Don't I have two of
these? Who's the other one? Oh, Monka W. We should have seen it earlier. Whatever. Can you please do
the, so you married into it routine again? No. Oh shit. You know what? Actually that makes sense
today. That makes sense today. You live in that house, not back? Well, yes. We have, we lived in
Temple, Texas for many years. Can I broom? This is powerful. Holy shit. What? How are you going to
leave? Wait, hold on. Hold on. I'll get it back. Holy shit. I had to rotate your tires. Okay.
Where's gas do you need? Thank you. We'll see you soon. All right. See you later. Have fun.
Thanks for coming. Holy shit. Hold on. Wait. Oh my God. The broom is very powerful. 3.5 on Yelp.
Yeah. That's not going to soft lock me, right? Hold on. It might actually soft lock the game.
Dude. Oh, oh, okay. It's going to take a little, it's going to take a little bit of time,
but I have, I have an experiment I would like to try. I want to pile just cars up on the road here
in front. Have like a stack of like 30 of them. I wonder if it's, if we're not going to be able to
get any more spawns. Not yet though. Not yet. Would it go back? Oh shit. Why does this stream
look awful? It does? What do you mean? I'm very curious what you mean by that. Looks. No, no, no.
Oh, I ran out of gas. Oh shit. Here comes the Yelp review. I can't believe a gas station ran
out of gas. How does that make any sense? It's the only gas station within 30 miles.
Shit. I need to order more gas. I need a gas. How much the order has been reduced to match
the available capacity. How much money do I have? All right. I need it. I have like no money left.
All right. Back with what I was doing. Very important. I know how to use the broom. Leave
me alone. Where's the car? I believe it despawned. Yeah, the car despawned. Well, I don't have any
gas so I have to turn people away. There's no gas in this gas station. Sorry. No gas. Wait,
let's do this. Turn off. This is the guy with the, the owner of the gas station is sitting out with
a broom in front of the entrance swinging it around like an orc sword. What is he doing?
We're not going to that gas station. You know what, by the way, I, I would open up Yelp and I would
just say that this like, this is a kind of a dangerous place. I would give it a one and then
reply from the business owner. I'm very sorry that you feel that that happened that way.
Please, if there's anything I could do about it, send an email to this email that I don't check.
That's probably a dead email that I haven't opened in years. We value your feedback. Thank you for
shopping at the Germa gas station. I was about to throw this guy. Hi, David. I would really like to
get this situated right away. Please hit me up at my email. All right. Connected. I felt like my
life was in danger. Four out of five. All right, let's turn it. Thanks a lot. I have a bunch of
email. I don't read guys. Do you understand? I don't like read emails. I don't answer phone calls.
I, I'm never, I don't, I w okay. When I'm not streaming on this website right now, I don't exist.
I completely disconnect. I do. I look, we have gas. Yeah, I disappear. How much gas are you giving
me? Come on, hurry up. Oh, I stopped it. Okay. You check your pager, right? No. What about your mom?
Of course I talk to my mom. I disconnect from like the internet. I got, I try to stay, I try to keep
my brain away from the internet. I live on the internet. You know what I mean? But I'll tell you,
you want some real, no more joking around. Let's like be honest about something. You got to give
yourself some time. Seriously. Give yourself a little time, at least a day or two to just not
just disconnect from it. It's actually, it's very, very much healthy for you. Check this shit out.
I'm going to hit the fucking tip of that goddamn thing right there. Shut up. You're a serial killer.
Why is it still telling me that this is delivery? How much gas would you like?
You're welcome. You have to do the sob voice and say gas. I don't, I don't have to do that.
Please do the coin toss scene. Clean, do the, I'm not going to, no, I've done it so many times.
You could just go back and watch like the five times I've done it in the last year.
Okay. What about, okay. Mail. Fine. Sweeping. Yeah. Fueling. Ordering. I know how to do this.
Okay. 60 seconds of traffic to untangle itself in some, okay. So this is just email. He's just
email tutorials. I already know all of this, but I can, I can sell alcohol. There's a paint roller.
All right. I need money. I need to, wait, wait, wait. Let me clean up.
I need, how do I get the trash to be taken? There's still this dumpster back here. Full.
How do I get somebody, how does somebody take it? How does somebody dumpster? Yeah, I know. I said
dumpster. Whatever. Dumpster. Dumpster. Dumpster. Museum. Museum. Um, how do I get somebody to take
the trash? Hi. Gas. Okay. Super. Thank you. You'll remember that, right? And I think you're going to
get a false star. You'll go from a three to a four. And even if they don't review, they will
remember this weird, like guy that did the weird voice and they'll come back because they'll remember
it. It's going to be in their brain. Okay. How do I get somebody to take this? You know what I'm
saying? Like how does it, it said, oh, we have somebody pick up the trash. Did I not unlock it
yet? I don't see it on the PC anywhere. Locked. Locked. Gas station. Level one. More info. I have
to finish the sweep tutorial. Okay. Okay. Am I tracking this in here? You take your shoes off
at the door. You know what I mean? I think I have to move this. Wait, no, no. No, you don't have to
take your shoes off at the door to come into the gas station to buy a Coke. Can you imagine?
No shoes in the ga- yeah. Oh, excuse me. I just had these floors cleaned.
You gotta leave your shoes at the door. There we go. Okay. Garbage collection. How much is it?
What's that called? Dennis. Dennis will appear on station occasionally and paint graffiti on the
walls. Stop him by throwing items at him to scare him off. New events will appear during the course
of the game. You can turn them off in the options so they don't happen again. What? I'm about to
throw like a table at this kid? Get out of here! You little bastard! I just threw a table at him.
Okay. I don't have any more stuff to throw at him. Throw back a trash at him. Where'd he go?
Officer! Officer! There's a kid that's a disturbance. Oh yeah, we actually have
reports of a grown man throwing furniture at a child. Trying to hit the child in the head with
a piece of furniture. Well, you see, he was putting graffiti on my walls and I had to scare him off.
Oh, you want some gas while you're here? Thanks. And don't forget the motto with two shakes.
Shake, shake. We have another custom. Shake, shake. Shake, shake. What is that? Shake, shake.
Shake, shake. Mischief makers for the Nintendo 64. Shake, shake. Yeah, that's mischief makers.
The N64. That's the one. That game was good too if I remember. Did it take the trash? Hold on. Wait.
It's coming back. Help me, Marina! Did I get it right? Did I get that right? I think I did.
I pulled it out somehow. Did I get it? It's like opening cutscene. What are you talking about? I'm
talking about mischief makers for the Nintendo 64. What are you talking about? Minus two. That
wasn't a good impression. Shake, shake. Yes, it was. How is that not a good impression?
Much more important. Hold on. No, where is it? I know it's here. Mischief makers. Intro. Mischief
makers. I was going to type in mischief makers. Help me. Does anybody have it? This is it. Oh,
fuck. Yeah, I got it. I did it. I got it perfectly by the way. All the people in the chat that said,
what am I talking about? Excuse me. Listen to that. Here it comes. Not that one. The song is good too.
I'm going to take a bow right now. Thanks a lot. Thanks for coming. Thanks for coming.
It's not Homer. Not everybody is Homer Simpson. No, it's not every single person is Homer Simpson.
Keep the trash gone. Buy a roller and paint the scribbled walls. Okay, hold on. I got,
I still have trash. He's throwing, I'm not throwing a tantrum. What are you talking about?
I'm just messing around. You guys, we just have a lot of fun here. That's it. That's it. You know
what I mean? Oh, you're 50? No, I mean I'm almost 40, which is kind of terrifying. Weird. When I was
younger and I was like, in my teens, somebody that was 40 was, okay, it was like the dentist.
You know what I mean? Does that make sense? It was like, like my, you might not, the dentist was 40,
right? My teachers were 40 and they were old. It was like, oh, you're much older. You're like
an older person. You're the dentist. You're the teacher. I will look at people like, oh, this
person's like in the news or whatever. And they're like 33. And I look at them and I go,
holy shit, I'm like three or four years older than this person? What? It's weird. You're 40
and still an E-clown. I'm not 40 yet. I'm not 40 yet. Midlife crisis? No, midlife crisis is when I'm
like 50. I'm not there yet. I'm not having a midlife crisis. I definitely, okay, here's one
thing I will say. I definitely feel like I've grown up a lot, like in my brain. I'm pretty,
I'm certain of it. I have to paint the walls? Oh, I just have it. Once equipped or shift to
select a color, I can paint whatever I want. Sure. It seems like it really, I'm turning 18 and I don't
think 40 is that old. No, it's not, but still it's interesting to think about. All right.
Uh, don't splash paint. What should I, what should I paint it? Um, oh, I really gotta, I hope that
guy comes back. What happened? What happened? I don't, I don't understand what I'm supposed to
be doing. Stay in the green. Oh, it's like Stardew Valley fishing. I get it. Okay. I hope that guy
comes back with that, uh, teal car. What the fuck? Hey, take a look at my, like, like the color.
Yeah. I love that color too. What did I get? What did I rate your, your car, your color?
It's like for something. I think I, I mean, I've got the same color. Great minds think alike.
Move is really strange. Does this cost money? It doesn't look like it does. Oh,
paint their car. No, that's awful. I'm not going to paint somebody else's car.
What? What happened? Why is this? Why is it white? I'm not sure that thing really matters.
Cause it just paints it anyways. What's your thoughts on couscous? It's really good.
It's, it's really good. I think it's really good. So nice. They named it twice.
I don't like New York, New York city city. So nice. They named it twice.
Could the whole thing just be green? That's a boomer joke. I mean, that's not,
Rob wasn't really trying to make a joke or anything. Oh, fresh paint job right in the front.
Oh yeah. We're going to do for you. How about, yeah, fill it up. I got plenty. I got plenty of
fuel. How come nobody needs more than a quarter tank of gas? Give you a shortcut. Oh God. See you
later. Why can you do that? Find the right tool to break into the car trunk. What is it? Like a
lockpick? Oh, equip the lockpick and then use it to open the trunk. Press AD to rotate the pin.
Hold spacebar to try and open the trunk. You can't run out to break the pin. You'll have two attempts.
If you fail or leave, you'll not be able to try again. Okay. Rotate the pin. Don't break the pin.
Got it, right? I got it. What? There it is. Dust bowl painting. $13. Nice. What should I do with this?
I'll sell you this painting for 13 bucks. Where did it go? Where'd it go? Okay. Oh, cool. All right.
Wait, you. Come here. Awesome. Bye. I'm gonna read my message to Otto. Otto said, thank you.
He really appreciates it. Oh, shit. Soft drinks? Snacks? Definitely. I want a big soft drink stand.
Okay. Gels. Okay. Big soft drinks. I can't put this outside. I want to rotate this though.
Where should this go? Right here? Oh, that's. That looks off center. Shit. It's better. Okay.
Uh, place. I need products? Okay. And a snack. Small snack tray.
Shouldn't be blocking the door. I think it's fine. Nice. All right. I got the drinks. It's
not blocking the door. Look, you can. It is blocking the door. Can I move this? Who wants
this clock? I don't want it. Just. Where do I put it then? Okay. Well, I can do this though.
Right. Up against this pillar. I should do it. Yeah, that's fine. All right. Oh, yeah. Okay.
Buy additional parking space. Parking space? Parking lot. The only serviceable parking lot
for the time being. It's free. Your uncle paid for it in full. You will need to clean it
from sand, however. Okay. I have to clean this area of sand. It's a great looking gas station.
I want that person. No, I'm going to relax. I'm not going to. No, don't let them get to you.
Ignore them. Ignore them. I need to. How do I dump the sand? You did that joke before. I do that
joke like once a week. That happens all the time. I want to dump this. How? Pick up, drop sand,
hold left mouse button. I can't put it down. Don't put it on the road.
Do you have any thoughts on the CSGO major? No, not really. I don't really watch Counter-Strike.
What the fuck happened? Oh, shit. I don't know. I don't. I can't. I don't know what's going on up
there. If this goes for miles. This goes for miles, man. I don't. There must have been something.
It's a construction like five to 10 miles up. This goes all the way back, man. Don't just stay
there. Don't get out of the car. There's no reason to. I don't. I don't know. It's crazy.
It goes so far. Oh, my God. Yeah, I found the problem. There was a little bit of a jam.
OK, I need to dump the sand. I can't dump the sand. It won't do it. Right. No, right. Right.
Mouse button is cool off the engine. Left mouse button. It won't do anything. Oh, fuck. I'm out
of gas. Oh, shit. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Why did I just make that noise? OK. Oh, no, I need that.
All right. I have a question. If the car is upside down, how do you drive it? We're going
to find that out. Oh, my God. How? What? What are the odds of that happening? See, this is why
I don't want to be a dick about this. Excuse me, ma'am, but I'm going to be. This is why when you
pull up, make sure you know what side your gas tank is on. So I don't have to do this shit.
Thank you, though. Yep. OK. How much do you want? No, I want it to be flipped over. Oh, fuck. Oh,
God. OK. Well, how much did you need? Water tank. You got it. Thanks. Come again. Good luck.
He's starting to turn. Oh, it's another customer. Just keep it. No, there's another traffic jam
again. Now what? What's the problem now? This guy's just not driving. This guy just crashed
into the wall. I was the same person. Well, you will not be coming back. You're lucky. No,
stop trying to come back here. Just leave. Get out of here. No, you have too much like determination
to get back. Get out of here. I'm launching you all the way over there. I can't. OK, stop. OK,
he's not moving now. Stand on top of the car and sweep it. Great idea. OK. Hey, welcome. How are
you? Good to see you. Let me just go ahead and fill you up real quick. But before I do that,
I just have to give you a little bit of a few safety precautions with your vehicle and make
sure that everything checks out. You know, check the windshield wiper blade movements. Make sure
they're not squeaking or anything. Oh, no, no. OK. No, I'm. Why do you have hostages? I don't.
Have you ever finished the thought in your life? That's a good question for my math teacher.
It's a great question. That's a great question for anyone that's ever communicated with me.
I mean, what? Because I would try to explain the math problem and I'd get halfway through and it
would just I'd be like, I'm not doing it anymore. I can't finish this. I can't finish this thought.
I can't do it. I think I did. I actually softlock myself. I might have picked the trunk of their
car. Can you do that? No, you can't actually do that. Oh, my God. Oh, that went very far.
This is such a mess over here. All right. I have to. OK. Honest to God, you just go.
How did that happen? Everyone just get out of the way. Holy shit. All right. We got in.
I'm going to break the game and we're going to have to stop. All right. I'm not going to do that
anymore. I have to go get a can. I have to fill up this thing and I have to figure out
how to dump this shit here. I can't dump it. It's bugged. This shit is bugged. No shit. Come here.
Press T. No, I have to fill this thing up with gas. There's a dumping zone. Is that why I can't do it?
All right. Come here. I have to dump it in the sand pit. Oh, shit. OK. Fill it up. What was that
can? Oh, literally in my inventory. I don't have time to deal with it. No, I'm sorry. Go find another
gas station. I hit you like 15 miles that way. You'll find one. I need to buy more gas. OK,
actually no more messing around or anything because I'm going to run out of I'm going to
I'm going to run out of money. All right. I need to dump this shit. Where can I dump it?
Right here. But this is where the parking spot is. Where's the dumping zone? Near the road entrance.
Break the game waiting room. Sand disposal. Oh, my God. Here you go. Why can't I just put it over
to the right? This is a giant sign. Are you think I'm paying attention to the sign over there?
Fill it up. Now I can buy a parking spot. Game journalist moment. Put it in self only and emote
only. I'm not going to be talked to like this. I'm not going to talk to like this. If you would like
to address me, then you can say excuse me, comma, streamer, comma, and then ask a question. If you'd
like to address me, that's how I will be addressed. Diva. I don't want to be a diva. You know what I
mean? Like, I really hope it never happens. I don't think it's ever. I hope it doesn't. I really
don't. I hope not. This one's free. Oh, I just spray painted white spray paint on the sand.
I didn't make a parking spot. What? OK, answer the call from uncle. OK, I have somebody said
spray paint. I liked it. That was funny. Hello. I see the business is doing well. I'm calling
to congratulate you on successfully getting it off the ground. But you can't run a business on
fuel alone. I've had a few of my people deliver some extra stock for those empty shelves of yours.
Time to talk money. You now owe me. Well, I'll send you the invoice to your email.
Don't miss it. I'm sorry, nephew, but there is just no room for charity in this world.
I hope you'll find it within your finances to repay the debt. Otherwise, we'll be forced to see
to more persuasive methods of reimbursement. Don't have me wait too long now. You're by.
Hi. Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me. This is what do you do? Oh, they're parked in the way.
Come on in. The trash. Look at all this junk. Soft drinks over here. We got chips. Yeah,
that's right. I have Pocky. I have Pocky here. That's right. I know. Aren't you? Don't you think
it's awesome? Use L shift to move the belt and hold left mouse button to move products.
Move products over scanner and put them into the basket. The belt will get dirty over time
and slow down. Clean it by holding right mouse button and wiping over the belt. Make no mistakes.
All right. You got Oreos and orange juice. Another orange juice. A can of Pringles.
Oops. That went for free. Oops. That's not fair. You don't just get that for free because it fell
down. Soda. Okay. All right. Are you just putting shit up here like just to fuck with me?
Well, I need this. Okay. Okay. Your total will be $22. What am I gonna do for you? One can of Coke.
Eight Skittles. Pringles. I got customers out there. I got customers out there.
Just take it. Just take it. Just take it. Take it. Take it. What? I thought there was a customer.
What? What are you doing? What do you mean scammed? He got it for free. He was pissed that he got half
that shit for free. What are you talking about? You got it for free. I'm moving it. Hey, looking
for soda? I got plenty of soda. Now what's the problem? There's nobody in this car. Oh, that's
the person I just saw. It's you. Just... Uh-oh. Here comes the police. All right. What can I do
for you? Okay. Okay. Yeah. You're gonna bring like all of your trash in here. That's like a
full trash bag. Thank you. Have a good day. You received a tip from... Oh, I got a tip. Thanks.
Sweep that guy. No. Oh, shit. Where's the... Where's the cop? What was that? Where's the cop? Okay.
Here you go. And, um, hold on. Just one minute here. Hold on. Sorry. I have to... I have to go
to the bathroom. That's it? Not where you left it. No. Oh, well. What happened to this person?
Is somebody still here? Oh, shit. Sorry. I'm trying to do it fast. You want me to pay full price for
this? What? It's a... It's a bag of snacks. What are you talking about? Sweep them.
No, it doesn't work. You can't... You can't sweep people. It doesn't work. Hey, Paul. Where's our
goddamn money? What the... I don't understand. Is that one of the guys' cars that I threw
like an hour ago? I didn't read the emails. I'm not dead, right? Is this my uncle? What happened?
This is where you get ghosted by emails for six years. All those times I said,
Merry Christmas. All the times I said, let me see the baby. Wake up, Sam. You've got a gas station
What? Was I rescued by uncle? And who is that guy? Wait, what? Wasn't he just here?
Why wouldn't we just talk? Why doesn't he left and called me?
There was a mistake, a serious one. You can rest easy knowing I will have the responsible people
dealt proper retribution for what has happened. Wait, the amount of time on your investment
I'm not taking on anyone was rendered far too short for what the amount was. It's plain bad
business. And I don't make bad business decisions. Let's forget about this debacle for the time being
as a token of apology, please accept this small gift. It will help with your next delivery.
No strings attached. However, you will need to make the warehouse operational again. I don't want
alone. I'm doing it somehow with what I have in cash. You're a resolute land. You'll figure it out.
Okay, thanks, uncle. All right. All right. I hold on to have a gas. You stay right there.
Just as I want. Okay, but I'm gonna I've been restocked things. I think I need to buy fuel
decorations. And I just do that. Wait, hold on. It seems to be actually more cost efficient than
the actual gas station. 12 to 20 bucks every time. In the conveyor belt. Oh, shit, you're right.
This is so dirty. I can't I have to wait till somebody's here. 33. I have enough. Read emails.
All right, fine. Alone. Feel free to ask for a little pick me up. You can reach out from your
PC a one time injection of $1,000 should pop you back on your feet. Yep. Okay. Cash register. We
already know how to do this. We know how to do all this. We know about Dennis. Okay, I need the
sponge. Here we go. All right. I don't mess with your stuff here. Let's go.
One more. All right. Come on in. Email waiting room. No, stop it. Good. Very good.
Just throw it on the floor. No, they leave if you do that. This is a huge eyesore. I really need to
get rid of that. Whatever it is. Oh, shit. Turn it on. Thank you. How are you doing? Bye. All right.
Complete all challenges to be able to upgrade the gas station. Okay, I get to buy an outdoor
decoration. I get outdoor small table. I can only buy a small table. How many bucks are I get it?
I guess it just stays in a static place. Okay. All right. I got gas. I've got, I got to order
more food. Purchase the level two upgrade to your gas station. Can I afford it? Level one. Level up.
So it's free. Hey, why did the paint go off? I upgraded level two to strip the paint.
No shit. You get that for free. Whatever. I don't care. Don't be mad that you got a carton of milk
for free. I, why are people so pissed about that? All right. Find a way to enter the warehouse and
open its gates. I need more stock. No, I can't do it yet. Oh, thank you. All right. Goodbye.
Anybody? Yep. Come here. See you later. What are you doing back here? All right. Find a way to enter
the warehouse and open its gates. Okay. I got a key. All right. What do we got? One bag of potato chips.
Thanks a bunch. You're welcome. You have a peanut sized brain that's smooth, creamy,
and delicious. Is that supposed to be an insult? What does that do with the hay?
Do I need that for anything? What is this? Press F to play. What? How do you play? Change chord?
Okay. A S D Z. Oh, I didn't want to leave. Sounds like an organ. I told you guys before about that
stream that I watched. This is like, I don't know, it's probably back at like, like just in TV days.
This is like before we was even Twitch. I thought there was this, there was this guy that had
headphones on and the music was blasting into his ears and he was sleeping and you could like
activate a thing that would blast music in his ears or play something in his ears while he was
asleep. And he's just sitting there in this dark, weird, like kind of dark room and the cam,
webcam's kind of all pixelated and he's just in his bed with these big bulky headphones on.
And all you hear is like this blown out, overdone, like just absolute blown out piano mashing keys.
Just like this dude just sitting there with his eyes closed. It was fucking mayhem.
I don't even know where you find that song. Like I don't even understand. I was sitting there
just going, what the fuck is going on man? I was laughing so hard. But it was just somebody was
just hammering like dozens and dozens of piano keys. Not a keyboard, a piano. The ones, you know,
an old fashioned piano where you have to put weight down on the keys. So sometimes it's like
done, done, depending on the pressure. So it was just all over the place. God, it's the funniest
fucking thing ever. This customer is hold on. Reset all cars. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. I need to
open the gate. Wait, hold on. I'll be back. What is this? A wrench? No, don't throw a saw at somebody.
Customers. It was just so damn funny. It really was. Mainly the fact that it's just he had a stone
cold just default blank face with huge headphones on. It was so abnormal. Like that was the perfect
word to describe it. It was just so abnormal. I think about it all the time. Good job. You're
trying to prove a point to people that already believe. No, I'm just so excited to talk about
it because it's like one of my favorite things I've ever seen. You have to recreate it. I don't
have a piano. Okay, more customers. Easy, easy. Oh my God. Okay, I have to go back. Okay, go back
to the warehouse and open the gate. Just use your thighs. I don't whatever you say. I have to open
this gate. Oh, I see. All right, let me get in here. This is a big lever on the wall. All right,
here we go. Keep your warehouse gates closed. Otherwise, someone may steal from you. What?
Remove haystacks. It doesn't really matter where those go, right? I should really probably close
the store. We've been saying that. Holy shit. Yeah, but it's been fun. All right, only three more.
Oh, right. Okay, there is that right here. Yeah. Oh, let me go. I'm going to go close the store.
Let me serve the customers here and then I'm closing. I still have plenty of gas.
All right. I'm almost out of stuff. I need to order more food. Thank you. Remember, you're the
type of guy that wakes up your significant other to tell them you're going to bed. No, I'm the type
of guy that if my significant other is sleeping, I do everything possible to not be heard at all.
It takes me like 15 seconds to close the door if they're sleeping in that room. If I need to
brush my teeth, I brush my teeth in a different room and I move around unheard. Oh shit, I gotta
take this out. Crash. Do you normally brush your teeth in a bedroom? Well, no, but I make sure that
like I... Oh fuck, I just got caught. I just got caught and I didn't even know. You know,
like then when that happens, I just got caught because what that means for you is like,
wait, what are you talking about? I'm a walk-in brush. I walk around and brush my teeth. I walk
around like my place and brush my teeth. So I just got, yeah, I'm kind of a weird guy.
My toothbrush travels around. Sometimes it's in the shower. Sometimes it's on like the kitchen
sink. Sometimes it's in the bathroom. Yeah, I clean it. Not in the toilet, like in the...
What do you brush your teeth? That's not normal. Yes, it is. The gas station's closed.
Oh, why did he come in here? A red fucking sign. Bathroom sink. We're closed. We're closed.
You're just gonna have to get back in your car and leave. Just go. We're closed. I really wanted
to go into like the stratosphere with this one. There it is. That was a big spin too. What's wrong
with me? Okay. All right. Now that it's closed, I have some money. I need to finish painting.
Yeah, I brush my teeth. I, guys, I used to... Okay. I am one of those people that thinks brushing
your teeth in the shower is more efficient. It's more efficient. I don't do it all the time, but
okay, let's say for instance, I'm going to give you a real example here because I mean, I'm going
to... I'm just going to tell you real stuff, okay? This is real things. So let's just say a stream is
about to start. How many of you guys do this? I know I'm not the only one. So you have like a
thing you're doing or like an obligation you have or an appointment or you're meeting up with friends
or whatever it is. It doesn't matter. That could be work or play related. It doesn't matter. And
you know that you only have like five minutes to get ready. Maybe 10 minutes tops. Do you
uh, count to like 60 in your head three times in the shower to guarantee that you don't get
stuck, shower stuck, because that shit happens all the time. And sometimes I will get into the
shower going, okay, I'm going to count to 60 three times. That's three minutes. And I will get to 60.
I will do... I will get to like 120 seconds and stop counting and get shower stuck.
Even if I'm trying to not do it. And then after like a couple of minutes I go,
what the fuck? I'm still in here. Oh my god. It's really easy for me to get shower stuck.
So I'll sit there counting in my head. One, two, three, four, five. While I'm brushing my teeth,
shampoo is in my hair with other hand counting. And like I need to be out of there in like 180
seconds. Aggressive ADHD. Yeah. Three minute shower Andy. Well, if you have somewhere to be,
you know, I don't, I also have to be, I have to clean myself every day. I have to. I always,
I just feel so gross. I just feel disgusting if I don't. Gross feeling Andy. Don't listen to all
the one guys. I know what you mean. It's either five minutes or 30 minutes when you take a shower.
Yeah. And why does that happen? Actually, I'm not, it's not going to be all green. We need
to have accents, right? Yeah. What should I do? White? It seems to be a full green spray painted
house. Peach? Orange? White? Let's see. I'm not doing all green. We're closed. Why are people
coming in here? Do you know what my uncle is? Shit. I'll clean it up later. I have not slept
in four days. Do you say you're supposed to sleep in this game? I think one of the worst things in
the world is when you think you have like five to 10 minutes or whatever. And then, okay, let's say
somebody's like picking you up or like you have a appointment or something. Especially if you're
on like somebody else's time too, it can be like, oh shit. Like I've gotten in the shower before
and I, the water just got hot and I just got inside of it and directly hit the water hits
the top of my head and shampoo goes in and I hear like and it's the person that is here to pick me
up. And it's like, I can't even answer the phone. I can't even answer this phone call. So you try to
get out of the shower while it's still running and you're covered in soap. Soaps going to your eyes.
It's like burning. You grab like the end of a towel to wipe your hand off enough to be able
to use the phone and you answer it and pretend like you're not in the shower. Hey, what's up, man?
Oh, hey, I'm outside. Oh, all right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I just gotta take care of a couple things.
Let me just give me like a couple minutes. All the while, like your eyes are burning with soap.
You just like in the shower, like just sitting there and then you make up like some, oh,
there's some reason as to why. Yeah. I've got, I've got it. I've got something I gotta do.
Just real quick. They caught me right at the second. Yeah. Yeah. I'll be right out.
Jerma, what the fuck are you talking about? Why is that not cleaned up? Do you live in a sitcom?
No, this is, this is real shit. That really happens. I have to brush it. I would not brush
a wet paint like this. This isn't doing anything. Why? How do I get rid of that?
Repaint the column. What the hell? Brush the ground. Please. Okay. Guys,
there's a spider here. It is, it is getting late. Yeah. I hear a spider. It's getting late. I don't
have any torches. Yeah. Oh yeah. Now that's a good one. Okay. You, are you trying to tell me that
that was not a good one? That's just the Minecraft spider sound. Do I have to explain all of my
material? God, nobody gets me. All right. What am I doing? I'm in a, I'm in a weird mood. All
right. I'm sorry. It's one of those, it's one of those weird mood days. Oh, fuck. Oh,
did nobody steal anything? This has been open the whole time. Come on. Don't do this to me right
now. Don't do this to me right now. Hello, ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to episode one of Jerma
Craft. Jerma, I said it so weirdly. Jerma, Jerma Craft series where I played Minecraft,
whatever, whatever, just throw it. It went all the way over the mountain. Okay. Well, how come
nobody has sung that yet? Like a singing remix of it. And I'm talking real like power singing.
Like I need to impress everybody here by singing the national anthem,
power singing. You know what I mean? It's never just like, oh, say, can you see? Nope. It's like,
oh, say, can you see? They always have to make it. No, nobody just does it the normal way.
Did I clear this out? Is this technically trash? Not really. Recycling, shh. Recycling jokes, shh.
Stop. Don't you, like, okay. Every year or two, a bunch of new people cycle into the channel.
So we just do all the material we did two years ago. And it's brand new to everybody here. And
they stop blowing this up for me. Yeah, I guess restore the warehouse. Dusty roads. I gotta go
to the computer and turn the warehouse back on. That probably was dangerous. There is no material.
You're just insane. That's not true. Hey, what do you mean? I'm seeing, I'm seeing trues here.
I'm seeing trues to that statement. This is all okay. I have to come in here and throw this
away. What? Oh my goodness. How did I not? I thought this was the wall. Wait, what's going on?
Wasn't there a wall? I feel like I'm having an out of body experience. Oh, I upgraded. I was
going to say no way because everyone's like, you're blocking the door. What are you doing?
What are you doing? I was like, okay, I'm fine. I need a little bit more trash. I just dump it.
No, I need another little bit to get a bag. Come on. Come on. Trash on the roof. I don't think so.
This is more than a simple weed brain. He's been molded like a Resident Evil 7 monster
from marijuana. Really? I kind of don't, I don't know what you mean by that, but that's probably
funny. Wait. All right. Restore the 50 bucks. What additional products for sale? Ooh, products.
Here we go. You have several different brands of products on shelves. The customers will buy more
things. Prices change every day at midnight. Renowns indicate a bargain price. Red mean the
price is less favorable. You'll make profit regardless. However, the cheaper you buy,
the more profit you'll make. Okay. Every day at midnight, you can track the price curve by
looking at the price history. You can order only one delivery truck from each company at the same
time. I was about to burp. Should I get alcohol? Cigarettes? It means strong menthol.
This is super bland tobacco. All right. Cigarettes? How much should I buy? Oh, this is times 10.
Oh, I have 50 cartons of cigarettes. Okay. How about some, uh, some beer? I need to refill the
snacks. I'm, I'm, I'm going to be burning for money here. Okay. Sound good? Is that, is that,
is that coming? Waiting for an order? Is that coming in? How do I say order? What's the order
button? It's not this, right? Where is it? Up right? Oh, I thought that was a trash can. I thought
that was like a delete button. I don't have enough warehouse capacity. Um, okay. I don't need these
things. Insufficient warehouse space. Fuck off. Wait for the delivery truck to arrive and unpack
the products into the warehouse. I need to move a lot of this shit out of the way. This is all
trash, right? I can't sell this for anything. More shelves. I know, I know. I'm trying to move.
I got a lot of shit here that I have to get rid of. I'm going for it. Don't worry.
Yo, uh, somebody's going to take this trash. Someone's got to take this. Um, okay. Wait,
can I like unroll this carpet? It's so huge. Uh, where's the truck? There it is. All right.
You're still closed by the way. Yeah, good. I don't want to be open. You're making a sad Jesus.
Oh, um, I know. Hold on. Don't invoke the wrath of the broom. I'm telling you, don't do it.
So what do we unproc, un, unproc the, is that, oh my God, that's so, this is so much.
How much? Oh, no, no, no. Okay. Thanks. Let me get it. Take me with you. Oh, what's this?
Hey, hey, simple to guess how closely I can get before it starts to burn.
I can feel the air. What was that? Was that that kid? I think it was that kid. I just heard him.
I heard somebody go like, you're out. You're fine. Oh, just go. Where's that kid? I heard him.
All right. We've refilled the shelves with products from the warehouse.
So do I have to grab it or is it just already there or close this shit up?
I don't want anybody stealing anything. Okay. Uh, I'm going to get a trash truck to come
garbage collection. Thank you. We're getting worried about you. Why? What's I'm just messing
around, man. We're just hanging out. Okay. I need to clear this stuff out back here
because I want to move this. Where's the garbage truck coming soon? It doesn't matter if it's in
there all the way, right? What would your last meal be? Uh, a buffalo chicken sub with extra
blue cheese. You had that ready? Yeah. Buffalo chicken is one of my favorite things in the world.
All right. I need to redo this. This is going to be where the food is right here. Never mind.
Who's going to be over here? That's not perfect. Hold on enough. This can go right at the door.
Plus two buffalo chicken, minus two blue cheese. What do you put on it then? I cannot eat
Buffalo anything. Just Buffalo, Buffalo. No, I like it, but it needs something on it.
Ranch. No, we got, we have, we have ranch users here. Ranch on Buffalo chicken and not blue cheese
guys. Ranch is just like the, it's just like the not as good blue cheese to use on a buffalo
sandwich or a Buffalo chicken. If you're going to do ranch, go all the way and do blue cheese.
I mean, I guess ranch is a little lighter, but what's blue cheese? Ranch is,
I don't know. I don't get the ranch thing. I don't, I think it's okay,
but there are people that are like, Oh man, ranch. Oh my God. I love ranch the best. It's so good.
I don't know. I don't really like it that much. It's time for some ranch. He hates ranch. No,
I don't. I like it. I think it's fine. All right. I got, where are my products?
Is it in my inventory? Products. Here we go. All right. We got these cigarettes. How do I,
how do I do it? How do I get these cigarettes? How do I get, how do I get them? Oh, here we go.
How do I put cigarettes down? Refill the shelves with products. Go to the shelf and interact with
the, yeah. How do I put the cigarettes? Different shelf. Oh, it's a different shelf. Different
shelf for alcohol too. What? I have $33. I have to, Oh my God. I'm going to go bankrupt. All right.
Cigarettes. Can't be behind me right here. It's sticking out. That's all right. That's okay.
Is it too? No, this one, right? Jesus. Okay. I need that alcohol shelf. Hey,
oh, you guys said I was getting not too much. This is not too much.
There's only one popcorn. Wait, what? All right. Everything's restocked. If I come into this place
and I see the shelf, I'm not going to buy anything in here because I feel like that it has never been
restocked and they don't restock until it goes to zero. It could be 10 years. I have 74. All right.
Open it. Your uncle has words for you. What? I see you're putting hard work into keeping your
station running again, kid. Good. Good. I wouldn't have it any other way. I just wanted to remind you
I'm not the only one judging your performance. Sure. Your uncle knows better how to keep a
business going and wants to see you flourish, but my approval only goes so far. The real approval
you need to watch out for is the one given to you by your customers. If word of slander gets out,
you might even sell Egyptian diamonds for free and nobody will bat an eye. Keep those customers
happy. Popularity. You hear? Gather positive feedback from customers who increase the popularity
of your station. Higher popularity increases traffic around your station, which increases
the amount of customers coming by. Okay. All right. So we are actually looking for Yelp reviews.
Uh, I'm going to open it up. Open for business. Let's go.
Ooh, clean this up. You can get more than one in one go. All right. It's pretty clean in here.
Okay. Looks pretty perfect. Ain't the inside. Can I? Oh, what color should I do? Uh, how about
what color should I do? Orange? Peach? No, not green. I'm not going to do green.
Ah, it's kind of ugly. I have to commit to it though for now. Yup. Coming.
One, two, three, four. We've got cigarettes. We've got snacks. We've got beer. I don't know. I'm
fucked up today. I'm sorry. You can, I, okay. You can always tell when I'm in a fairly good mood
based on how odd I am in front of everybody. Oh, where is it? It's a different color. Is this a
different color? I can't tell. It might be. Is it? That's a different color. What are you looking
for? You're looking for the beer. The beer is right there. Not the right brand. What'd you get?
Good choices. Good choices. Good choices. All right. Come on in. What do you got? Got a beer.
Yup. And some snacks. Thanks for coming. Have you have a wonderful day. I'll take care of that.
Whoa. I went a little over. I didn't look. I tried to stop. It didn't stop. Whatever. Who cares?
Be stranded. No, I, I, I, the whole point of having a gas station out here is to make sure I can
serve the customers that need, um, get some stuff, right? I got to order some more fuel,
more parking. Oh shit. 399. That's too much. I need fuel.
200. Shit. Um, my moon is huge. You don't, dude. Okay. Can I talk about this? This most nerve
racking thing in the world. Some fast food restaurants do this now where you order with
the person that's like walking and running with your car. I hate it. It freaks me out. I'm not
ready. Chick-fil-A. Yeah. I w it was so much anxiety inducing. I was just like, what the fuck?
Cause I don't. Okay. I usually don't know what I want when I go anywhere. I usually don't. I usually
kind of figure that out. I look at like a menu, whatever. And this person's holding up a laminated
menu, walking with the car. I'm just like, what the fuck is going on? I don't, I have to drive the
car. I have to drive the car because there's just like 700,000 people that go to Chick-fil-A.
Every, I don't. Okay. I know that like, okay. Chick-fil-A, right? Oh, they've got good chicken.
It's okay. It's good. It's good. But this car, it's just like, what the hell is going on here?
It's like 50 cars in line all day. I would just go to McDonald's. I'm not, I'm just going to drive
by that. You know what I mean? It's like, holy shit. That's like ridiculous. Oh, come here. You're
looking for, there's beer. You're looking at, he just, isn't that the exact beer that he just said
he wanted? I went to Chick-fil-A and In-N-Out today and yeah, In-N-Out's the same way. In-N-Out's
just, there's so many people. It's just always there. Come on, come on. Yo, me, $5. In-N-Out
is overrated. Be careful. Be careful. I said that before and I was nearly, I was nearly killed.
Be careful. Don't say that. The chat chimpanzees were not happy about that. I don't have enough
money for this. I, all I said, listen, all I said was that I, I, I, when I order food from In-N-Out,
why do they put it like in a half-open bag? If I'm not eating in the restaurant, wrap the whole
thing. Wrap the sandwich up. I don't want it in a half-open bag. Have you ever had Whataburger?
No, I haven't. I've never had Whataburger. I've always wanted to, but this never, I never had an
opportunity. Who's beeping? And actually, okay, it could be time for me to do an updated tier list
because I feel like I've eaten a lot of, of the fast foods I have not had before. For instance,
I think I mentioned this before, but holy shit, Jack in the Box is unbelievably good. I couldn't
believe it. I was like, this is fucking unbelievable. I was like, what? I've only had it maybe once in
my whole life before I had it before. And I was like, yeah, it's okay. Dude, I had their burger and
I was like, this is like good. This is like really good. What, what is it going on? It's underrated,
but it's not that good. I think I, okay, I think my brain was expecting it to be terrible,
but when I realized it wasn't terrible, my brain put it up like three tiers. What do I mean?
Great job. Your tacos are horrendous. I mean, I kind of, kind of like those,
kind of like those, but it's whatever. Wait, it's already at the gas pump. I am almost at a gas.
Cigarettes and beer. Have a nice day. Okay. Buy a toilet. Not yet.
Need that. You try Boston Market. Um, I've had Boston Market, I think a handful of times of my
life. I remember it was good, but I don't, they're not really out here. I don't think
there's a Boston Market out here. Could be wrong, but I don't think so. That fuel here.
Please finish painting. You got it. I was looking at chat. My bad. What was the cop doing?
He got out of his car? The wrong orange. It's okay. I'll replace it later. What he said is this
portal to gas station. Let's go with that. Sure. Okay. Fuel's here. Why would you come to the back
to leave? Just turn and do a three. You're going to have to wait. Thank you. All right. Um,
finish the paint job. Actually looks terrible. Okay. That don't matter. Hey, yeah. I know I need
a bathroom. I'll make it in a moment. Okay. What do you need? Very good. How much gas do I have?
103. Now I need. All right. Okay. I think we're good. I got to, that's ugly. I have to paint that,
don't I? I can paint the roof. What? I want someone to fill their tank. I do white, darker color.
What do you think? I do. What color should I do? Okay. Let's do this color. Peach about, uh, maroon.
Uh, my eyes. I'm just, I'm seeing what the colors we have. I could just do this. I like the gray.
Well, a resident sleeper. It's a neutral color. It's a roof. What do you want to paint the roof?
Like teal? I think it looks nice. I don't care what you say. You're a Slytherin. You have customers.
Don't they see what I'm doing? Ah, paint all over me. What? Did you do that? You bring a dog in here?
You bring a dog in here? What happened? You have millennial humor? Um, I just want to make sure that
you're aware of this. I'm, I'm a millennial. I think I probably, I, that's how, that's how old I am.
Oh my God. Gasp. Wipe your feet before you come in here. Come on. What is this millennial humor?
What kind of humor do you like? What's your humor? Zoomer humor? Zoomer humor is interesting to me
because I either hate it completely or I think it's hysterical. There's no in-between for me with
like, uh, kind of Gen Z's humor. Can you buy something? All right, come on. Wait, you first.
Please don't rant about how popular you'd be on TikTok. Please. I'm not going to do that. Don't
worry. We're not doing that right now. I was not about to. No, I'm, I'm full of shit. Don't worry.
There's one thing that you guys can know and you probably already do is, you know, I'm full of shit.
You know what I mean? Like, I just am. Okay. Do I have enough for a bathroom? Toilet. How much is 50
bucks? That's it. Okay. Sure. Make it. Do a funny sound effect. Is that, did you like that?
That was so funny. You guys are fucking so funny. Okay. What, uh, I don't, I didn't mean that
sarcastically either. I really believe that. All right. Uh, I don't need a lawn. I have a toilet now.
I have to clean the toilet. Where is it? I don't even know where it is. Excuse me. Where's your
bathroom? I don't know. It's somewhere attached to this building. Put new floors in? Maybe eventually.
The weed kick in? Oh, a little bit. Somewhat. I, I'm kidding. There's 15,000 people here. Holy shit.
All right. So they very, they want, okay. They want different beer.
I need to order. People keep asking for this one and this one's expensive. Okay. Don't go overboard
here, but people will keep asking for these. How much is it going to cost? 100 bucks.
Hey, they keep asking for the same beer. Clean the toilet. No one's even used it.
Nobody's used the bathroom. Why would I need to clean the bathroom? What the, what the fuck?
Excuse me. Um, excuse me. Why is there a big shit log on the ground? I just opened this. What?
Oh, don't pick it up with your hands. Oh my God. That was disgusting. Do not touch that with your
hands. No. Oh no. I didn't wash my hands. I'll use the sponge. Jesus. I'm so, I want to let you know
I didn't wash my hands and I was just in the bathroom. I want you to know. So make sure you
wash your hands too. That's disgusting. What the, what am I doing? Would you just put it all back?
I don't even know what I would do if somebody said that. Yeah. Have a nice day. Oh, by the way,
I didn't not wash my hands, but I just used the other bathroom. It'd be like, okay, well,
I want a fucking refund and I'm washing my hands and you think five times and I want you to give
me $20. I want, I want you to give me $20 and the health inspector is going to get here too.
Oh, okay. You're throwing it for some reason. I thought she was saying like, let's go. Like
let's throw down. Like she was like pointing down. Like let's go. You and me right here.
Delivery truck. Shit. Coming. I don't have time for this. Thanks for coming. Appreciate it.
I'll get out. Bye. Thanks. Have a good day. Here. Have a few like bags of potatoes or whatever
rice, whatever this is. Howdy. Fresh beer. You got it. All right. I'm making money. The door,
the warehouse door. Yep. Shit. Be hopping doesn't work. Shit. I'm in trouble. Usually I get around
games like that. Is that in games anymore? It's not right. Cause that was like essentially a
broken piece of code that people used. People don't put B hopping in first person shooters
anymore. Do they? Boomer shooter, boomer shooters still have it. What's your guys favorite boomer
shooter? I feel like I want to know what the kind of crowd has to say about this. What do you,
what is yours? Money. I don't think TF2 is a boomer shooter. I mean, maybe a little bit
cigarettes. That's 20 bucks. You know, those are bad for you. It's so bad for you. You shouldn't
be. You should quit smoking. Did you read the surgeon general warning on the back? I just want
to make sure you did. Did you read the surgeon general's warning? Yep. Just making sure you did.
Those are not good for you. This is bad for you. You have a gas. Oh, I'm almost out of fuel.
I need to restock the shelves too. Hey, there you go. Now you have some variety.
The toilet. Oh, were you just in there? Oh, that's not how you clean up that. Hey,
get rid of the rest of this trash. I can't use that brush anywhere else. All right. We're going
to paint this white. It's bathroom. It's going to look like clean, fresh. I have a workshop from
the main PC hub. There's a lot more to this game than I thought there was going to be.
I came into this game without, I'm sure I shouldn't be in here. It's being painted.
Have a nice day. Can I even go in there and paint that? I don't think I can. I paint it.
Looks like I can, but I can't open the doors here. Oh, I can. All right. That's kind of a weird
setup though. Customers, customers, customers. I know I'm going. Sorry for the wait. He said to
paint the bathroom. What do you got? Have your cigarettes. I don't know why I'm so like passive
aggressive with it right now. Like I'm selling them. Yeah. Like what am I talking about?
It's a lot. Almost out of gas. Trash. Thanks for coming. Bathroom's clean. Somebody said poop.
Ha ha ha ha. I'm glad you think it's funny. Can I even paint this back wall? I don't think I can.
I want to paint the back wall. Can I not? Did we have a raid? Did we? I don't see a raid.
Make that up. You made that up. I don't see a raid. You made that up. All right. Well, whatever.
This stuff is so boarded up. I have to take care of that. How do I take these boards off?
I can't paint the dumpster. I can't buy more fuel. Oh, I don't know what that is, but I can't
afford it. Customers. I'm here. I'm ready. Looking for any stray trash. Trash, trash, trash. Nope.
Okay. This room going to the bathroom. There's two people in there. Where is everybody? I need to
tell people about this place and more people come so I can have more orders. But you got to wait.
I got a big combo going. Only one more seagull. Huh? What? Oh, say later. Thanks for the fuel.
All right. I need features. No, I need to make some more money. I need 300 bucks to restore that
thing. Evening. In here. How much do you need? Oops. I didn't mean to click it twice. I just
want to get up on the roof. Does he even know I'm on here? This person. So where are we going?
I'm going to do this because yeah, I'm terrified about this. What will happen? Come on. From
downtown. Ugly shot. I love that game. I could play that game for like the next 100 years and
be fine. Is that like important? It's not like my luggage or anything, right? He's heating up.
Yeah. When you got on fire, you just steal the ball and shoot from anywhere on the court.
Make your friends go mad. Steal the ball. And you would shoot the fireball and you just sink it
every time. Oh my God. You find a lot of shit. Good. Okay. I need 300. These are the expensive
ones. They're like 10 bucks a bottle. You imitate the sounds of shoes squeaking on a basketball
court. Yeah. Is there any other requests? All right. 250. I need 300. Emulate my father coming
home. Hey kid. It's me. Your dear old dad. What's your report card look? Oh, you got a B minus in
science. I had bad time in science too, son. Don't worry about it. I heard that little shit kid.
Where is he? No, I'm not going away. I'm like, I'm going to spray him. Where is he? Where is he?
Where is he? I heard him. Where is he? Where is this kid? Is he in the bathroom? I don't know
where this kid is. Get out of here. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Yeah. Do you see what's going on with kids
these days? What's going on with kids? What's going on here? $20. $8. Yeah. I don't know what's
going on with kids, man. Honestly. Sweep the floor. Oh shit. The Minecraft spider joke. I think was
a 10 out of 10. I can't believe nobody liked that. I'm shocked. I can't believe it. Awesome. Okay.
How's my inventory? It's pretty good. I have cigarette batteries. I need another few customers
and I can do the workshop. I have to take care of the paint. What did he write? He wrote like,
fuck you. Where is it? Where is it? Yeah. Fuck school. It's supposed to be in school.
Fuck school. What are you getting? Finally, somebody actually orders a half tank of gas.
Workshop time. Restore. How many saltines can you fit in your mouth at the same time?
Probably two. I mean, more than that, but why would you do that? It's kind of dangerous.
It's like bad. Wait for the client in the workshop and fix his car? Wait, I'm a mechanic now?
Wait for the customer to leave the car and press the button on the left to start the repairs.
Use your skills to see which areas require your attention. Before you start repairing,
make sure you have enough spare parts and the right tool in your hand. Restocking car parts
is done in the exact same way as ordering new products to tell. Use the delivery tab on your
PC. Well, shit. I'm going to have to do this a little bit later. I need to make money. No,
not yet. I can stay. How are we doing? All right. You're the kind of person that eats Doritos
vertically. When you're 3D, you're in a 3D world. Doritos 3D. Crunch the power. I don't know why.
I don't know why I do this thing where I'm deliberately trying to make you hate me.
You know what I mean? I find it's kind of humorous, but I don't want anyone to actually
really hate me. Maybe I should cut back on those, please deliberately hate my guts references.
Okay. Wait for the client. I don't think I can fix this person's car. Is it you?
All right. What's wrong with it? What's wrong with your car? Are you going into the repair shop?
The repair shop is that way. This is how we go real fast.
One of us is going to puke and it ain't going to be me. All right. I'm out. Get me out.
You have unread mail. Yeah. You know what I do with mail? You know what I do with mail? I don't
know. I shred it. That would have been funnier if I didn't start doing that weird voice. I don't know
why people send so much shit. I really don't. Why? What's the point? People send so much junk.
Have you guys seen those pretend invoices? You've seen these yet? I swear if there's bugs.
Bugs? Where it's like this piece of paper that's filled out as if you had potentially ordered a
product or like, oh, here, here's like this is going to do that. We're going to be doing this.
We're going to be doing this. And they had it signed at the bottom. I like the guy,
the owner of the company, whatever. And you look at it and you're like, wait, what the, what is this?
And it looks like it's on paper, like written paper. It's really weird. It's a good advertising
technique to be like, well, this is what your invoice could look like if you used
BNA Stevenson. Oh my God. Somebody in the garage. Hi. How can I help you? I'm wrong with the power
steering. Yeah. Power steering. Sometimes it's fluid. Sometimes it's, um, why do I have a timer?
I need a new car battery. I don't have any of this stuff. Let me see what we got here.
Uh, let me just go like this. Okay. Maybe one more of those. I think we'll do.
Okay. I mean, use the saw a little bit. I don't have any materials. It's immune. Oh shit. People
let's register. How am I supposed to do all this? You need more CPU thermal paste. Yeah. All right.
I, I have to buy a bunch of shit products, car care. I'm, I need to be level three car care.
All right. So I need to buy a car battery. I don't understand. I need tire, need new
mirror to start fixing old mirror, need wheel and need scratch remover. Where am I supposed
to get all of this stuff? Use the delivery tab on the PC. It's on the wall. That's not it.
Tires are here. What are you talking about? You have them. There's a fusion. It's a fusion.
I don't have car parts. Okay. Take it on there. Nope. I need a car door, scratch remover. Where is
it? Oh, it's this. It's the stupid thing I was doing. Okay. And what else we got? You need a
mirror. You need a car mirror. Here we go. Ow, my finger. Okay. That'll be, uh, that'll be $1,700.
What are you going to do it yourself? Nope. You're fucked. I need to order car. I don't have enough
money to do any of that yet. People let their register. Nobody's getting gas. I have a really
bad reputation for gas or something. How come there's no cars been pulled up? Life saver.
No lifesavers are under the register. I'll see you again soon. Take it easy. Take it easy, Jake.
Thanks for coming into your mic. That's how you get the good reviews. Uh, car parts function
identical to purchasing products. Prices change every day. Yeah. Greenhouse indicated bargain
price. Yeah. Yeah. I already have plenty of these. I've wasted like three of them. How much do you
need? All right. What are you plus doing? The floor. What are you guys tracking in? Probably
should clean the bathroom too, right? Probably a good idea. Can you take a potty break? Um,
yeah, we'll take a break in a minute. Get some water. Uh, 400 bucks. All right. I'm slowly
accumulating money though. That's a good thing. It's been three hours. I need to get some more
food. I think that's important. No, I need to, I don't need to know. I need more money.
My reputation is pretty high. Oh, I got to clean that bathroom before you go in there.
Don't go in. Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't. Oh, whatever. Anything from Sonic?
Um, no, not really. I know people looking for Pringles and yeah, I know.
Oh, super. You don't have any soap dispensers? I don't think I can buy them. Once I get over
600 bucks, I'm going to start ordering new stuff. The only snack you have are those awful little
Debbie cakes. Why did I just throw that in the trash? Any more fuel? Yeah, I do. That's essential.
So I'm going to buy it. Are you high? No, really not. I have no more products.
Please, when are you going to do more tier lists? They're objectively your best content.
I mean, I did them all. All the ones everybody wanted, you know, cereal, fast food, snacks,
drinks, cheese. I did pretty much all of them. Pretty much all the ones that people would want
to see. Seasoning tier list. That's all right. That's you've piqued my interest a little.
Okay. The truck is here. New tier list after the break. No, I'm not doing tier list right now.
Maybe we'll do that in the middle of the week. Maybe. Okay. I'll find some more like
quizzes and tier lists and stuff. Maybe we'll do that on Wednesday.
You got to give me some good ones. Some ones that I haven't done. And maybe I would go back
and do one that I've done already because my opinions may have changed. Then the recommended
channel in the discord. An opportunity for you to say, you know, what you think would be a good one.
Garage. Somebody in here. Shit. Somebody is in here. All right. You need a what's wrong with it?
Scratch remover. What happened? Geez. Okay. What else? Need a new tire. I love that sound.
There's a werewolf attack. That's a lot of money. Wow. This is really worth doing too. Almost 200
bucks. Oh shit. I wasn't paying attention. I was bunny hopping. There we go. Expensive beer,
expensive booze. Thank you. What can I do for you? Yeah. How's it going? I feel like the actor
that, you know, I'm, yeah, I'm going to go do the, uh, I'm going to go be the clerk to get ready for
the role. Good morning, sir. How are you? Yeah. I'm going to do this for like a week. Maybe like
three days tops or maybe even possibly an hour. Yeah. I know I get, I get what it's like. Yeah.
Simpsons did that joke. Good. I'm glad. Simpsons family guy. 30. You have a lack of charging
ports at your station. And this is the part of the movie where like all the, all the country guys
look back and forth at each other sitting around and they all go, what are you talking about?
Charging port. Hey, are you going to go up in a spaceship? That's supposed to be a really funny
part of the movie. You're doing pond stars again. This is not pond stars. This is me running a gas
station. What? These cars are really small. The garage. I'll get, I'll get back to you.
Where's the garage? That's over here. Oh my God. Oh, mega laughing. What do you need? Quick to Larry
the cable guy impression. Okay. What do you, what do you need? That's just crazy. I'm just crazy.
Internet. Oh, mega laughing. All right. I need to, I need to stop doing that.
I'm like so energetic today. Why? Just relax. Like it's all right, man. Like what am I doing?
I'm just so excited. I don't know for nothing. I don't even know why. All right. What do you need?
Two tires and a mirror. Let's just relax. YouTuber Andy. I know. I've never, I've never,
it's the YouTuber in me. It's good to be excited. Yeah. That's fun. Over here. No umbrellas allowed.
Waiting room. Oh yeah. That's right. Oh, Oh no. You guys know the rule of the channel, right? How
this all works after a week of not playing the game. It's gone. Shit. Yeah. That's actually true.
That's actually true. You're honored. All right. I got plenty of money. It's time to start upgrading.
I'm coming. It's actually not true. What about the movies and house flipper?
I think some games do not qualify for that just because I love them so much.
30 bucks. Nice. Oh, is this place dirty? Okay. Nice and clean. Looks good. All right.
Now I've got 800 bucks. I need to gas station level three. Complete more objectives to be able
to upgrade the gas station. What are my objectives? Order car parts. Okay.
I'll order. Oh, these are expensive this week.
Order one of these and one of these. Okay. That's very expensive. Oh, it goes to the warehouse.
Are you gonna stream Elden Ring when it comes out? I would assume probably.
I don't see why not. I always play the new from software games on stream.
I just hope it's not as hard as Sekiro was. My gamer skill is on sort of a curve
where every six months now, I lose an extra step in my gamer skill. So I don't know. It's
gonna be tough. I did see the new gameplay trailer. You have games that you won't play
on stream because you want to enjoy them without 10,000 backseat gamers. I mean,
there is something to be said of playing something off stream for me just to kind of
do whatever, potentially just be awful at or to just keep my mouth open and sit there and not
say anything. All right. But no, those games are fun to stream. Customer. Oh, no. Refill
the shelves in the workshop with the car parts. Can I just do that? I feel like my favorite games
would be really bad ones to stream. Um, yeah, I mean, streaming for me has always sort of been
YouTube was like this too. I had the most fun when whoever was watching, whether it be on a live
broadcast or a video that I edited or whatever, that we would collectively think something was
fun or funny. Or, you know, something was interesting. So the prospect of just kind of
playing a game for me at this point is interesting to me on my own. But I think like on stream kind
of stuff, I have the most fun when I'm doing stuff like this. I'm just talking and just fucking
around. You guys are cracking jokes, cracking jokes. You know what I mean? I have the most
fun like this. Just hanging out fucking around or doing like a big project. That's where I have
the most fun. How many cops live here? A lot apparently. Well, I don't think this is,
from my understanding, this is a long sort of abandoned road. I don't know. I mean, I think
I'm like one of the only gas stations. This is ugly. This is a very ugly house. Oh, it was gray.
It's a yeehaw town. Why is this a different color? Light? What color is this? Remember the warehouse,
the warehouse? No, this is correct. You know, like, okay, I've never lived in an environment
where I just fell off the roof. I've never lived in an environment that was less like technology
and more kind of like just local stores and more like country. I feel like it would be kind of an
interesting experience. Close the warehouse. It's not. Rural, rural, rural, I can't say it,
rural, rural, rural life is, I missed everything you just said, Josh. Rural life is nice,
but you definitely lack access to a lot of stuff. That's the Seth MacFarlane dog sound.
Yeah, that's the Brian, Brian from Family Guy.
Yeah, it is. What do you need, Gap? Shut up about Family Guy. Shut up. All right,
can you take it? Okay. Can you tell that I'm clenching my teeth?
Idiot. It always sounds so, I don't know. It sounds so funny. My sister used to do that.
She would go, shut up, you idiot. That you could tell it would. Sister was mad. Dirty in here,
kind of. Are you saying we are the champions? No, I can't. My vocal range is gone. It's not high
anymore like it used to be. And I used to have a huge range. Now I can just make cash register
sounds and low baritone, yeah, noises. There's no range anymore. It's just one or the other.
All right, let me put, let me do this. I need to stock the shelves.
These tires. Place the mirrors and the scratch remover. What do you need?
Two tires and a mirror. You got it. This person's been in the garage for three hours.
Well, I'm working, I'm only one person. Are they going to add like a kitchen? Am I going to be a
chef? Your catering order just came in. Hurry up. They're waiting. All right, nice. I'm 1,200 bucks.
Okay, I need more fuel. I need, uh, I've got customers. Order some fuel. Complete all challenges
to be, all right, challenges. Cars fueled, shop customers served, and repair cars. All right,
so now we just have to kind of grind for a little bit. Read your emails. No, fuel. You got a bunch.
Oh, I need, okay, I need a snack variety. I need a snack variety. Snacks. What's some good shit?
These. People love these. And that's all I'm going to buy because I'm not buying the expensive ones.
Soft drinks. We got, uh, toffee, Aunt Betty's tonic, propicolo, and then, oh, ice cream.
Oh, hell yeah. And, uh, Betty's. Yeah, that sounds good. 208. Oh, yeah, yeah.
There we go. All right, whatever. Just need to serve customers, fuel up, and then I can upgrade
the, yeah, I'm supposed to go to the bathroom. Oh, hey, it's time. It's time for a BRB. It sure is.
Be right back. I haven't left yet. I'm listening to it. Imagine a BRB screen with like summer,
beach, tropical drinks, and shit. Oh, I do. Be right back for real. I haven't left yet again.
Uh, Lord, I was going to be making those. That's not just an idea. Right now, I'll be right back.
Good song. Great. This is a good song. Hello, I'm back. And let me give you a quick little
teaser of this one. Ooh. Imagine going BRB and hearing this. It's a little teaser.
It sounds like winter. Could be. What about a space BRB? Oh, that would be cool too. I mean,
I haven't even shown you the one that I think I'm going to use for fall. It could be this one. Or
you never know. Seasonal BRBs or yeah. I love this one. This one's awesome. You should have a BRB
random, like a gotcha. They could be rare BRB screens. Actually, that's kind of a cool idea.
All right. Well, I want to listen to the other ones. I'm sorry. That's what we're doing.
I want to hear the other ones. How about a 1% chance for a jump scare screen?
All right. How about this one? This one's good too. This is a pretty, this sounds like spring.
Yeah, it could be. Or winter. I can see it fit wintery as well. This one fits fall pretty well.
Yeah, we got, we got, we got blored out on retainer by the way. He's,
we make it much more of this stuff. We are entering a new highly pogged era of BRBs.
Yeah, this is spring. I love, I love this one. This one kind of reminds me, not this one,
the one I'll play, the one that I played in the very beginning. I don't want to cut this off
because this is equally as good. Are there any new BRB animations planned? Yes. Okay. So I have to,
they loop, but I have to loop them. I'm just kind of playing them.
This one reminds me of the intro and the outro. That same kind of vibe that like the drums that
go like, you know what I mean? I think this one might be my, this one could be my favorite.
This one has the same vibe as the intro and outro. I love it. I just want to listen to it like all
day. Who made these blored out, blored out. I'll support him. Did a hell of a job again.
And he's making more. The entire like soundtrack of this whole channel is just blored out
every time. Like I was saying earlier, this shit is, I would love to see a blored out
composed indie game. Wouldn't you? It'd be fucking incredible. Oh yeah. All right. I just want to
listen to it again. I don't think, blored out is probably not here. Blored out lives in Australia.
So not the best time for my stream to be live. So I don't know if they're watching stalling. Yeah.
I mean, this is a stall. You're right. Yeah. He's got a band camp. He's got a coffee.
Absolutely support them. By the way, those of you that probably didn't know this,
or maybe you did, this is some information for a lot of the newer viewers. Blored out was the one
that made all the music for the Jerma Rumble live action video. That was blored out. That was all
him. But that's another little tidbit. By the way, the B.S. song is probably the best thing
that he made on that. Stop. I'm trying to talk. When is the next live Jerma Rumble?
I mean, you know what I mean? I don't know. I don't know. You know what I mean?
Oh, I got it. Hold on. We've got a customer. Not tomorrow. What are you talking about?
Big if true. I. Hmm. Maybe we can talk about this. Maybe we should talk about this.
It's actually kind of personal. It's actually very personal. Yeah, why not?
Why not? We're just hanging out. We're just chilling. So I want before I am done streaming
and kind of doing the whole content creator thing, I want to have an absolute blowout show,
absolutely monumental show. And one of the things I really want to do
is like and like this is not spoilers or anything because it's so there's so much shit written down
for this. I really want to do like a Jerma Rumble live on Twitch and have it be a fucking monumental
magnum opus type show. So obviously that's not happening anytime in the near future,
but just know that that's going to be that's going to be as insane as I can possibly make it.
Whatever I can do to make it happen. Define the near future. I don't know if I could even
answer that. I really don't think so. But the plan is to essentially have an experience that
might last more than a day or two, maybe longer, maybe one event. I don't know,
but I want it to be huge. And we're talking like, I don't want to okay, I don't want to
talk about something that's not happening in the very near future. Are you going to retire soon?
No, it really no. It depends on what your definition of soon is, I think. Because
my definition of soon is probably different than yours. I will tell you right now there's no plan
on that for at least the next couple of years, at least. So don't worry, I'm not like leaving
next week or anything. There's no plan for me to even start thinking about that for at least
another few years. But when it does happen, and look, I have to be realistic too, right? I mean,
I feel like I try to be pretty realistic with everybody here. Whenever we talk real, I know
that I can't really do this forever. And I said a long time ago that I was going to do it and have
as much of a good of a time as I can and try to do the best job that I can,
as long as I'm having a good time. So I can't really tell you when. Quitting in 2025.
I don't know. I can't tell you that. I don't want it to be inaccurate with what I mean by this.
You're not allowed to stop. What do you mean you don't know? No, I don't want to talk too much
about it. But you guys have to remember, I'll be 40 pretty soon here. I'm having a real talk with
my chat room, okay? Who do you think you are? Who do you think you are? Fan for life. Sweep that
asshole. No, but I want to be realistic with you guys too. Is it delivery here? Oh, level up.
What do I get? 40 isn't that... I know 40 is not old. Elon Musk. Awesome. And I want to make it
clear too that if I do at some point end up saying, you know what? It's probably time for me to
put up the... What's the term? Hang up the towel? Hang up the gloves? What do you want to say?
You guys would know very, very well in advance. This is not something that is going to just be
like, well, you know what? I'm not coming back ever again. Bye. See you later. I would probably
announce something like that. Kind of transitioning out of YouTube and Twitch stuff. Probably at
least a year in advance. I would want you guys to know because I don't want... Here's another thing
too. Stop talking. Another thing what I don't want to have happen is let's say that, you know,
years from now, whenever it is, I decide that's probably it. We've had a great time. It was really
fun. And then maybe we'll do a few big like kind of blow up shows, right? I don't want people to
like sub to the channel and like I just leave. I would want it to be really clear. Like, hey,
everybody at some point, like over this next year, this is going to be it. Don't be sad. It's not
happening yet. You can't... Don't be sad yet. Don't be sad at all. It's not happening. It's
not happening for a very long time. It's been something that's not necessarily been on my mind,
but something that we've really never talked about is... And I've been doing this for a long time.
And my 10 year content creator, in quotes, anniversary, right? I mean, there are TV shows
that don't last this long. There are things that... It's shocking. Don't hit them. Again,
this is not happening in the near future. This is happening like at least years from now.
At least years from now, okay? So don't worry. And then no more... I thought I had to deliver... Oh,
I didn't... Oh, shit. The delivery guy. He's been here for two days. He's been out here for a full
two days. Sorry. That was an angry honk. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to. And there's other ventures that
I think I want to do. You know, maybe I want to start producing some shows. Not being necessarily
in front of the camera, right? But maybe to help with creators making stuff for...
Open up a fucking animal sanctuary or something somewhere. You know, I don't know. There's like
a new chapter of the thing that I want to do. I just don't really know exactly what it is.
What about president? You know, I think I could probably do a pretty good job. I think so.
And look at how I'm running this place. Okay, we're good. I gotta close this.
Okay, we can move on from that conversation. It's just I want to do over these next at least
couple of years, I really kind of want to do some big fun stuff. The dollhouse was sort of,
and like the archaeology stream, those were sort of precursors to what I want to do,
at least for the next few years. If they can happen, then I'm going to try to do them.
I'm going to try to do for it. Do for it. Go for it. Baseball stream is coming up too. That's
another one that is. Yeah, I think there's gonna be a lot of opportunity for fun.
The person leave immediately because it smells in here. You got so mad at Nicktoons baseball,
I'm afraid for real baseball. That's different though. Okay, we're almost halfway there. I want
to see what happens at level four. You wouldn't be able to hold down a real job. Yeah, you're
right. I'm never going to stop streaming. I can't do anything else. Actually, I mean,
actually, potentially accurate though. I mean, I'm not a fool to know, you know, things that I
think I would like to do. I don't know if I disagree with that statement, but there's other
things I want to try. A clown? That would actually be kind of fun. Oh, parking lot upgrade. That's
right. I need to clear this. I gotta clear this crap. It's not like we wouldn't be there to throw
money at you if you came back to streaming. Yeah, but that's not, that's not, I wouldn't want you
to do that. Where is, where the hell is my excavator? If you got a regular job, you'd be
hounded nonstop because of who, not very many people know who I am. If I went to go work
somewhere, it's not like I would, I'm not like a celebrity that opens the door and it's like,
oh my God, it's Gerber. Oh my God, it's Gerber 95. No, I, most people don't know who I am.
I'm gonna take two or three trips. Literally everyone here knows you. Yeah, but that, this is
a, in the grand scheme of the human population. Yeah. I know we don't get real that often here.
They just mainly fuck around and stuff, but sometimes it's important to talk about this
kind of stuff. That many people know you passively. Yeah, but they don't know who I am.
Sure. Somebody might've seen the like 50,000 upvoted thing on Reddit of me being the AI
serial killer image, but that they just think that that's a real image of a serial killer,
right? They don't think that's me. In fact, if somebody saw me that saw that picture,
they would probably have a double-take and go, holy shit. That guy looks just like the serial
killer. So yeah, I would get recognized as the serial killer, not German 985. Just kind of
interesting. Hey, I just, sorry to bother you. Are you the serial killer guy? That's me. Yep.
Whoa. Dude, how does it feel to know that you look like every serial killer? That must be so
fucked up. Yeah. I mean, it's, it's crazy. Wow. The garage. Ooh, we got, damn, that's crazy.
The exit conversation as soon as possible. Statement. You get a bad door.
Like what the fuck? Holy shit, man. That's crazy. You can use all these if you want.
Oh, we don't need more than one tire ratio. You fell off. I don't even know what that means.
I've done this. I don't. You have two broken tires. Shit. All right. We'll stay here.
Stay here. I'll, I got to order your parts. Band Twitter users.
I've been watching you for a month and you're already my father.
What are you talking about? That just, I was not prepared for that one.
I thought you were saying like favorite, like, oh, wow. Thanks. I appreciate that.
No, I'm apparently your father. All right. I need to, I got to get deliveries. These are expensive
today. Whatever. How much is this? Too much money. $885. Give me a break. What's so expensive?
The anti-scratch. I'm just going to buy the tires. They're so expensive. Whatever.
Dad's leaving for cigarettes again. Nope. I'm not going to have to do that for a long time.
Goku. Oh, I keep forgetting to restock these stupid shelves. All we have is Pringles,
but there's sour cream. Those are the best. If you only have sour cream and onion Pringles,
that's fine. Finally, what about pizza Pringles? Um, I would probably rather have sour cream and
onion. Salt and vinegar are based. They kind of burn the edges of my mouth. I get that kind of
almost like irritation on the corners of my mouth. I think they taste all right. What even is this?
Oh, it's the car parts. Right. All right. See you later, man. Yep. Yep. That's how we know. Hey,
that's how we know the business time for you to leave. Take care. See you later, man. See you
next time. Oh, I bet you they do shit like that. I can't get going. Take off and it's like, oh,
what the fuck, Gary? Fucking dick. When's the last time you cried?
There's some real, there's some real bangers coming in the last 20 minutes or so here, guys.
There's some real good comments coming in. These are awesome.
Um, it's a fair question. How is, how is it a fair question? Oh, no, I know what it was. It was
Ernest scared stupid at the very end when he like doesn't have any friends. He's sitting there with
it sad because like he doesn't have any friends that want to like hang out with him and like he
saved the day. Yeah. I was fucking started crying. It was a week ago. Hey, don't just yeah. Like
Ernest saves the day and his dog, his doggy thinks is gone because well, I don't want to spoil the
movie. It's a fucking classic. Every Ernest movie is a classic. By the way, you want to talk about
like comedy influences on me in this channel. Ernest is one of them, has to be. Jim Varney,
the garage fuck. Ernest made like 15 movies or something. He had a bunch of commercials. He
was had a bunch of movies. I loved Ernest when I was younger. He did Shakespeare. Yeah. He had such
animated. Okay. You know, like Jim Carrey, the way that Jim Carrey kind of moves and talks.
Jim Varney in his comedic performances was like another Jim Carrey type, really animated movements.
He was super, super funny with his body and his like face and stuff. It was hilarious. He was,
he was a great like physical comedian and not like, you know, when people do like that physical kind
of exaggerated stuff and it comes off, you have to be like the right kind of person to do it.
Right. Those are huge influences, especially Jim Varney and Jim, two Jims, Jim Carrey, Jim Varney.
He was also the original Slinky the dog in Toy Story. He didn't know. It's dirty in here. Almost
at the place where I can upgrade original, like just Toy Story one, none of the sequels.
Cause I believe, correct me if I'm wrong. I believe after Toy Story, I think he, he, he died
after Toy Story, right? That was his one of his last roles. I remember that was one of his last
things he did. Oh, I can do the parking lot. I like kind of think back at like, so Jim Henson
is another one. Oh my God. It's only Jims. I'm having kind of a moment here. Jim Henson,
Jim Varney, Jim Carrey. Anybody else? Jimmy Neutron. Oh, hey, hey Jimmy. Oh, hey Jimbo.
I'm not Jim Gaffigan. Um, but yeah, I think I was probably a little too young to necessarily
understand when Jim Henson, Jim Henson, when did Jim Henson die? Somewhere in like the early 90s,
late 80s. I forget what it was, but man, I just can't even imagine, um, how much more awesome
stuff that he probably would have done. And it kind of makes me think too about like our kind of
kids content and stuff that's for children nowadays. I feel like we need some better stuff
for kids. I really believe that all the stuff that Jim Henson was doing back in like the Muppets and
like stuff like the old Sesame streets and stuff. I feel like there needs to be some more
stuff that kind of taps into kids' imaginations and taps into kids, um, more creative thinking
and stuff. Like there's a lot, it's an untapped market right now. When I was younger, I remember
I feel like a lot of my personality and how I see things were developed from
watching stuff like Sesame street and what's going on? Did he just get pulled over?
Why did he get pulled over? Oh my god. Oh, the parking lot. I gotta let this guy out. Okay.
All right. You can leave. Do not release. What's your opinion on almond and oat milk? Uh,
used to be almond milk Andy. Now I'm an oat milk enjoyer. I actually like oat milk a lot.
Parking lot. Come on. Where is it? Here we go. Have you ever tried potato milk? No.
Didn't even know it existed. That's why I even asked that, man. Why ask that? What the fuck?
I'm not even, whatever. We're just going to keep, we're going to move on.
Uh, potato milk. I don't, I've never had it. I probably would be, I don't really like rice
milk though. I don't like rice milk. I don't like soy milk. I drank almond milk and put it in my
coffee and everything for the longest time. Raspi voice Andy. Here I am. Here I am. It's me.
Oat milk and almond milk are the ones that I find or taste the best.
Rice milk is too runny for me. It's too thin. It's like water. Water. Uh, rice milk is too watery.
Oat milk has that, that thickness and that sort of viscous-ness to it that I like.
How about Mountain Dew? I don't think I've, I've not, I don't think I've had a sip of Mountain Dew
in like eight years. Good though. I would probably drink it if it gave to me right now. 17 to 25.
All right. One more car and then I can worry about the, somebody's already here. What about
a refreshing Capri Sun? Yeah, Capri Suns are awesome. Although I like Capri Suns until I see
the liquid out of the pouch. Something really odd about the way it looks, right? It seems odd.
The mystery of the Capri Sun being inside the pouch is like, I don't care. It could literally,
the liquid could be like dark brown and I wouldn't even care or know, but it's sort of like a,
it's like a transparent, like it's almost like a pink, isn't it? Or like a light blue,
like it's like water, but it's like pink or blue. Yeah, it's slightly pink. I don't think about
that. I don't want to take it out of the pouch. Why would you? I don't know. Because when you're like
12 years old, do you think it's funny to stick the thing and pour it out? Like squeeze it out
into a cup and then drink it? Because I used to stay in the bathroom for like an hour
and make magic potions with shampoo, toothpaste, mouthwash. I would do this kind of stuff.
Oh, there goes the combo. That's not good. You botched it. What did the potions do?
All right. I don't know, but, but okay. Is this weird? This might sound a little weird,
but it was an excuse to like not go to the bathroom. I could just sit here and then hold
by like, and I, it was like, it was, it was enjoyable for me to like sit there and like
make the potions and not go. I don't want to go to the bathroom. No. I was like a little kid.
I'm making potions right now, mom. I'm busy. And it's like, no, get, go to the bathroom.
And like, if you go into go like number two, it was an excuse for me to make potions.
Oh, I can do this. And like, nobody's going to come in. I could make magic potions.
Because when you're in the bathroom, obviously like the doors closed, no one's like coming in.
So it was like, I could make potions and like, oh yeah, I'm in the bathroom.
Give me the shampoo and give me the mouthwash. All right. Only a few more customers.
Getting robbed. What? What the fuck? What happened? We're just like,
it was stink bomb in here. Oh, it's that kid. Where is he? Is that him? I should kind of like
that. It's staying a lesson in beating the haters. This looks really good. I'm going to keep it.
I think it looks awesome. Actually not changing it back. That has to go though.
Okay. That has to go. That one does passive aggressive, Karen. I, all right. There's only
two. There's two more here. Mr. Albertson, you have emails. I, I know I'll get to them.
I'll get to them. No worries. One more customer and I will go close the doors.
Sweep your floors. I'm going to go feral. One person can only do so much. I'm sorry. I can't.
All right. There we go. I need to repair cars. You can hire people. Really? I need to close this
fucking garage Albertson. I'm, hold on. Nobody took anything. We're fine.
Heal is low. Yeah. I'll get a couple of deliveries here. Make that little shit head work for you.
I, we need, I need car parts. They're good. They're cheap today.
Pour those. Get some of these. I need a couple more of these. Oh, that's going to be expensive.
Okay. I need to, what smell? Well, don't throw like a fucking three day old, like
Thanksgiving dinner in here, whatever you did. I don't know. Oh, Thanksgiving dinner,
stuffing, cranberry sauce. Wait, I would like a poll to be made. This is going to determine
how many people get banned from the channel. If you vote for the thing that I say that I,
if you vote for one of these that I don't like timed out for 10 minutes, I would like for you
to do a poll. Whoever is available in the chat, do a poll or do you prefer the canned
cranberry jelly sauce? Like the can in the can, the jelly shit or fresh cranberry sauce.
I need to know cranberry sauce or the cranberry can. I need to know. I'm not American. Well,
this is what you have to be American to eat cranberries. That American thing. Who is he
talking to? Laugh out loud. You. It's looking, it's not crazy, but you know what I love doing.
I'm a cranberry fiend. I go. All right. I'm going to gross out everybody here. Are you ready to
fucking hate me? Everyone's going to hate my guts after this one. Um, I like to buy
the not concentrated, not diluted, 100% cranberry juice, not concentrate. This is the real shit.
And I drink that shit. It hurts. It's painful. You did like the citric or malic, whatever acid
that builds up on the back of your tongue. It hurts. It's brutal, but I like it some. I don't
know why you can't drink too much of that though. You can only have like a little bit of that. It's
way too acidic. What you guys don't know is that when you buy cranberry juice off the shelf,
Oh, cranberry juice cocktail. When you think of cranberry juice, I'll take a cranberry juice.
You're drinking like 13% cranberry juice and then like water and sugar.
You're not drinking the real shit. What you guys don't know is
you just called me out. I know. I see what you guys don't know is that's not real cranberry juice.
It's cranberry cocktail. I'm so much smarter than you and I'm better than you and I'm more
healthy than you. Yeah. Yeah. I know. Look, I know. I'm sorry, but it's, I know it's a little weird.
I like to drink a hundred percent, not from concentrate cranberry juice in small amounts.
Oh dude. Yeah. I don't want too much of that. It's too harsh. Did we even do a poll? Oh, we did.
Okay. What do you got? Okay. So it turns out that 57% of you, 57, 58% of you are in complete
agreeance with all the other idiots that think that fresh cranberry sauce is better than the
canned stuff. Canned stuff is way better. I prefer the canned stuff. I do time them out,
time them out. You can't time out like what's, what's 60% of how many people are even here?
You can't time out 8,000 people. I don't think we can even do that. I don't think it's even
possible. Uh, no, all jokes aside, I do prefer the canned stuff. Easier to work with. You can
grab a knife and kind of just grab a little slab of it and put it right on the turkey and it sticks.
The sauce gets everywhere. It doesn't stay on the turkey. It doesn't become part of the bite.
It becomes a sauce. Omega laughing. You know what else I really like? We're just, we're just,
we're just hanging out. Um, you guys ever have red pepper jelly on top of, you take the red
pepper jelly out and you pour it over a slab of just Philadelphia cream cheese, just the plain
Philadelphia cream cheese, grab some like wheat thins or crackers and you just kind of smear down
and grab a little bit of the jelly and a little bit of the cream cheese brick. If you've not done
that before, I assure you, if you do it, you're going to understand. It's very good. It's
unbelievable. Red pepper jelly goes great on a lot of stuff. I need to eat more jelly.
I love this stuff. You don't eat the whole thing on your own. You put it out as like an appetizer.
You want to kill it at an appetizer? I'll tell you if, listen to me, you bring the red pepper
jelly and the Philadelphia cream cheese and you make that. It's so easy. People are going to think
you're a genius and you can use it. Be like, ah, it's like my little secret recipe. Like you don't
even tell them that you got it for me. You take this. It's yours. You take the credit for this.
Baked brie and strawberry jam. That's leveling up a little bit. I think because that requires
actually baking. You don't have to do anything. You buy the little brick of Philadelphia plain
cream cheese, open it out of its package from the fridge and just pour the red pepper jelly on top
and then take some crackers of some wheat thins and just put it out on the table.
You don't have to do anything. Well, you also have to make sure that people like red pepper
kind of jelly. It's not hot, but it kind of is. Derma, a millionaire eats pepper jelly on cream
cheese. It's good. It doesn't, there's nothing to do with, what are you talking about? It does have
a bit of a kick. Yeah, it does. That's the, what do you mean? That's like, you've got mail. I know
I've got mail. I have to repair cars. Don't let them shame you. No, I know. Hub cream cheese is
better than brick cream cheese. Um, I mean, that's a debate, but for this particular purpose, you need
the brick because you have to push a cracker through it and it sits out on the table nice.
So you can kind of go through the jelly and into the cream cheese. All right. Forget about the,
I need to do the garage. Is anybody in there? All right. Somebody just got in. You can wait like
four days. It's fine. Oh shit. I have no more fuel. Oh shit. Any kind of jam and cream cheese is good.
I haven't really had that much experience with it besides the red pepper one.
He's spending all of his money on NFTs. I'm not. Yeah, the kudri boards. Oh yeah.
That fig jam. You get fig jam on a kudri board. What? It's not even dirty in here. Disgusting.
What are they talking about? Oh shit. Okay. I need to restock. I need the ice cream freezer.
When are you going to make a sus face NFT? That's not going to, I'm not doing that.
Oh, out of fuel completely. People are pissed. Oh, I'm sorry.
Uh, um, um, um, um, I need products. No, I need gas.
I'm going this way. Tread carefully here. What do you mean about NFTs? I could give you a small
opinion on it. Not really a major one, but I think that over the next five to 10 years, I really hope
that if that's something that's going to stick around, that some of the new technologies in
like the crypto space makes them a lot more efficient if they're actually going to be around,
which they might not. Um, cause I was obviously at the current state right now.
I could use a little bit more efficiency and maybe a little more green. Where, what's, what's
going on? Get off me. Are these all my tires? All right. What is it? Is that it? What is it?
What does he need? Oh, it needs a second mirror. Shit. It's an interesting concept,
but I wish it wasn't ruining the environment. Yeah. Well, that's another thing to remember too,
is that when people think of like blockchain, right? Stuff like Bitcoin, stuff like Ethereum,
you know, I, there's like proof of work, proof of stake, but hopefully potentially over the years,
those become way, way more efficient where they don't need to do that much and generate that much
electricity. I really hope so. I think there's a lot of people that are trying to solve that problem
at the moment. I can't say that I, oh fuck, I gave him no gas. He got zero gas. And I also have to be
completely honest here too. I don't really even know that much about them. I know about like
cryptographic technology, right? And like cryptocurrency, but NFTs are kind of,
I'm kind of a boomer with that shit. So it's hard to immediately speak about it. Oh my God,
this is a long line. I've been in the line for days, but if you want to hear the optimist in me,
right? I hope that some of these new technologies, some of these new things people are making can be
made and done and used in, you know, kind of proper ways. I mean, I, look, I got to be honest
with everybody here. I'm not going to try to, you know, pretend like I don't speak of a certain
topic. I used to have an Ethereum address that you could donate to on this stream. It was there.
Like I, it was, I was like, Hey, Oh dude, come on, give me some Ethereum. This is like 2015 or
something 2016, right? I think as these networks grow and more and more and more and more and more
people are using them and we need more and more and more like, like mining farms, right?
They're trying to come up with solutions to that. And I can speak personally that I,
I hope they do. I hope they can actually come up with a solution because I think this, I think
it's a really interesting technology. I do for many different reasons, but if it has to be,
it has to be done right, right? Getting a raid. What's going on? Oh, good. Perfect. Change the
subject. Whew. Hey, big raid. I forget about all that shit. I was just saying. Connor Reads Pants.
Thanks for the raid. What's up, Connor? Welcome guys. How are you? Good to see you. Thanks for
the raid. Hope you had a good stream, Connor. We're playing gas station simulator. Raid song,
please. There is no raid song. It hasn't happened since like 2019. Stop. There's no meme anymore.
The meme is gone. See? Yeah. You're talking about a season three. No, no, no. That's like
season five, season six meme. We're in like season. No, are we in season 10, season 11?
That's like a season eight meme. Yeah. I'm sorry. You guys are talking about like,
you guys talking about when, uh, when Dale dropped the chili. Um, no, sorry. We're like,
Jeff and Pam had a baby. We're like, that's where we are. So I know like you thought that was funny,
like back then, but we're in, we're on the new season here. I've not watched more than one
episode of the office. I've only seen, I think 20 minutes of one episode. Somebody, oh, there's
nothing on the shelves to buy. Somebody buy something. I need more alcohol. Wait, what do
you need? Hmm. Everybody keeps busting out their mirrors here. What's going on? Remember that
office crack was actually really funny. The way you got the names wrong. Thank you for saying that.
Okay. Come on. We're talking comedy here.
We're talking comedy. We're talking comedian. Like me, you know, I need one more car and that's it.
Do you think this is worth buying? Um, it's kind of a fun, just busy work game. I think it's pretty
fun. How much is this game? Does anyone, anyone know how much this is? 20 bucks. Yeah. 20 bucks.
Yeah, I think so. Full of trash. Oh, the smell is horrible.
All right. Check the email for God's sakes. Off my screen. All right. How are we doing? Didn't read
them. No, I marked everything as red and closed my computer laptop hard and angry. One more car
going in. Whoa. You've been robbed. Somebody took, what'd you take? Took two gallons of milk.
Oh shit. I need to repair a car. Oh, by the way, to all the Raiders, take a look at this.
Remember that one? They're all, they're already all gone. I don't think all of them are gone.
Cigarettes are a big seller. I almost have to restock them. Can you beatbox please? Yeah.
You got a lot of stuff. No. Where's the beer? It's a popular place now. There we go. All right.
Finally. What can I do for you? Tire. Lucky for you, I have one more tire. Okay. I have to,
you had a mirror problem. Both mirrors are just one and then scratches. Nice. Nice. Okay.
Gas station level three. These are all, I gotta throw these away. All these deflated tires. Oh,
whatever. Okay. Let's go on to the next step. Now I'm going to close the store after this.
I feel like I'm kind of, I have money. This is where you become a combination KFC.
That's a good one. I like that one. Okay. Level 700 bucks. Let's go. So what does that do?
Ooh, it's like a freezer section. Cool. Reconstruct the bus stop. And this action
might have direct and immediate consequences. Get ready. What? Where is that? Bus stop? Gas stop?
Where's the bus stop? I need to restock shelves. I'm not going to do, I'm going to have to get ready.
Yeah, I gotta get ready. I need more materials. Other? Oh, more parking. Toilet. I can do two
toilets. Second toilet. Okay. Oh, a second fuel dispenser. Shit. I need money. Bus stop. Don't
buy that yet. I'm going to fill up on some products. What do I need? I need alcohol.
Insufficient warehouse space. Okay. How much fuel do I have? I think I need fuel. I have
160. I got plenty. Stock what you have. I got those. No more cigarettes. I have no more alcohol.
I need a freezer, right? Yeah. I need a storage shelf. I need like an ice cream thing.
Ice cream. This is so expensive. 260 bucks. What are you talking about? Where do you mind? Shit.
What do you want? I don't know. A tire. Damn it. You need a tire. Can I put one of these
dead ones on? Oh, one's on the ground. All right. Give me one second. I think Otto needs to go
outside. I'll be right back. Yes. Is it? You need to go outside? We'll take a second break. I'll be
right back. Guess what you get to hear. That's right. Okay. I am back. Right at the very end.
Right what it ended. Perfect timing. Okay. Yeah. I had to take care of Otto. What time is it?
What do you go for time? Let's have one of mine stream for five hours. We'll go for like another
hour. We'll keep going. I'm curious about what this next step is here. Do not reset character.
Oh my goodness. That's so close to resume. Over here. What's going on? He's all over the floor.
Oh, if you get stabbed, that makes sense. If you get stuck. All right. That gives me...
I need more tires. I need more mirrors. I have five, four. Actually, I think I'm okay for now.
I just licked my screen and I got to be honest. The stream tastes terrible. No, those are the
boogers you've wiped on your screen over the last like six months. Boogers taste good. I can't. Oh,
it makes me shake. It makes me shiver. All right. I have enough to put the ice cream thing in.
All right. I need to rearrange this whole place. Good. Clean out all of my stock. Thank you so
much. That's 30 bucks. I'm going to do this. I'm going to close the store. If you serve another...
I want like at least 500 bucks. Don't make a comment. I'm doing it right now.
Can I get the distance award? Oh, I got it. Nice. Okay. That wasn't that far, but still
surprising nonetheless. Okay. I got to close. We're closed. We're closed. Oh,
there's two customers coming in. Okay. No. After this. Hey, get two more cars. No,
they're not coming for gas. All right. Close the store. All right. No new customers. It's
pretty dirty in here. Let's take care of that first. Filthy. You guys open? No,
we just closed. You just missed us. Graffiti too? Yeah, I will. You should watch the sorcery
tribute video. Sorcery tribute video. I'm interested. Oh, we're closed. Right. I was
going to serve you. Oh, well. All right. We have one cigarette left. One pack of cigarettes. That's
it. I need some major restocking here. First things first. I need an ice cream thing. It's
not even that much more money to get the big one. All right. I'm going to move this out of the way
for now because this is going to be the ice cream station, the ice cream and drink station
because this is blue. I was only blue because I haven't painted it. I thought this was ice.
I thought it was icy over here. Well, I'm keeping that theme. So let's retribute. Yeah. We'll,
we'll queue that up on Wednesday because Wednesday we're going to do just a chill stream, right?
Do tier lists. God damn it. I like that. Yeah. Okay. Is the section for ice cream.
So you are going to do tier lists. I'm thinking about it. I do maybe just like,
wait, I can't paint these. Can I paint the ceiling? No. Oh, God damn it. No, I don't want to do this.
I cancel, cancel. I want to cancel this. I, why am I painting the roof? Okay. Well, now we need to
clean this up. How about an ass eating tier list? You either do or you don't. It's either S or F
and it's one icon. I, you, you put it there. I don't need to have this conversation anymore.
It is clean in here. Let me put that against this wall and then the drinks will be on this back wall
here. Yeah. This is like the chill zone. This is the cool zone. Come on. Come on. There we go.
Look at that. Yeah. Awesome. Oh, I love it. No, put that back. Put that back. Stop taking them out.
How do I put it back? No, stop taking them out. Oh my God. Okay. That was perfect. That's fine.
Can they get to this if it's here? I wonder if they can't get to the ice cream and they get to
the ice cream still. I think so. Maybe not. Maybe we'll see. What happened to all the stuff? Oh my
God. I'm just a heart attack. Let's go back here too. Who cares about the window? Yeah, that's fine.
Looks good. Um, okay. Well, it's back behind the wall somehow. I guess. All right. What's next?
Alcohol. Snacks. All right. I think I, I, did I get an alcohol delivery? I did. Didn't I?
Did I not? Maybe I didn't. Alcohol. Well, these, these, one of those. How much is that? Okay.
Jerma, how do you deal with the winter lanterns on Nightmare of Mensis? I turn my volume down
all the way and just go and kill them as fast as I can because the audio is what causes the
most problems for you because it's the most terrifying sound that's ever been put in a video
game. Fuck, I had alcohol. Can I cancel? Can I cancel that delivery? I needed snacks, not alcohol.
Whatever. He's already here. Wave him down. I'm canceling. I cancelled the order. I cancelled
the order in the app. I'm sorry. I cancelled the order in the app. No, I, no, I know. I'm sorry.
Make another alcohol shelf. I don't think I can afford to buy one. They're like $300. Yeah. 170
bucks. All right. I can open up the store now though. Let me just make sure I clean up. I need
snacks and smokes. That's true. I have plenty of alcohol forever now. Hey, goodbye. Please leave
so I can do the funny thing where I close the gate when your truck is halfway out
and we see what happens. Oh, you made it. I think you broke my garage door.
Oh shit. I think it is broken. All right. We're good. Jerma, you're not beating the furry
allegations. I don't know. When did I say I was a furry? All right. Open the store. I have to
to make some money and then I'm going to reconstruct the, that thing, the bus stop.
I don't even know what color it is. Hopefully this is the right color. It is. Okay. Good. Hey,
I have a lot more to paint. Friendly reminder, Jerma once went incognito to a furry convention.
Well, no, not yet. Almost done with this. It's going to have to wait. Oh, all right. We can go
back to that. And this is not going to be a dollhouse scenario where I'm doing like,
oh, look at me, look at me and doing the walk and stuff in that costume. No,
no, I'm going to be stone faced. I'm not going to make any emotion. I'm just going to walk around.
Oh, welcome. A lot of you have this thing in your head where I'm going to be walking around
doing the look at me thing all the time and trying to get on people's TikToks and photo bomb. I'm
not going to do any of that. I'm going to be the most unassuming person there. Like honestly,
anytime you see any footage of somebody in a fursuit from here on out, from now going forward,
it could be me. I just want to make that very clear. You don't know.
That's more shit. I have to paint this. This is really kind of messed up looking to find the guy
that's five too. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Give me something heavy. I don't know why. Okay.
Where is he? Where is he? Where are you? Where is he? Get out of here. No, stop. You little shit.
Where'd he go? Did he fly away? I just saw the shadow on the ground. It was like a bird
flying. Where'd he go? Oh, you're stuck. Aren't you? Oh, there's a lot of people here. Oh God.
There's a lot of people. It's like 10 people here. No, I don't suck. Okay. I don't suck.
I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. Hello. Yes. What do you got? Ice cream?
Ooh, these are good. Nice. This is quite a haul. Oh my God. How much shit are you buying?
That's a lot of stuff. It was like six ice creams and like five orange sodas or something.
Like four beers. That was a lot. There was like 15 items. Ban me if I'm wrong. I bet you can't do
a perfect wolf howl on stream right now. Ban that guy for life. Ban that guy for life. Ban him for
life. He doesn't get to come back. He does not get to come back. Ban that guy permanently. He
does not get to come back. Wait, what was this? What was the stipulation? If I couldn't do it,
then he would get banned. I don't even know what I was agreeing to. No, no, no, no, no. I'm not
done. I'm not done with your car. I pressed the button to have it come down. That's it. You're
getting fucking swept. That's it. You get swept. That's it. Yeah. What are you going to do? Run me
over? You're going to run me over? Is that what you're going to do? Yeah? Get out of here. Get
out of here. Come on. Why? I got to get it to be just snap. There it is. I get to do that once a
year. I want to go audition for Mario. Before the audition, I want to make the audio directors
think that I'm really into the role and everything. I'm going to warm myself up to be Mario because
I'm a huge fan. Before I say anything, I get into the audition booth. I get into the room.
They're all like, okay, so they're waiting for me. I just put the headphones on. I start the
audition and I just start going. Then I do the Mario impression. Does that show passion?
Would I be the annoying guy that's trying to make his audition way better than everybody else's
and trying too hard? I'm going in with a plan, man. I'm going in with an audition plan.
I remember I wanted to be an actor. I always thought, man, if I ever went to an audition,
I'm going to stand out. You put it on the conveyor belt wrong. That's not my fault.
You owe me money for what you just broke. Hey, hey, I'm not done talking to you.
I could have been Mario. That person's liquid. That person's liquefied. There's no way.
Remember, you're not the horn section. You're the whole orchestra. Do I have enough to repair
the thing? Choice. It's quite a lot. It's time to repair. Wait, I think there's one person in the
garage. No, nobody comes to the garage anymore. You'd make a much better Luigi. I don't think it
would be a good Mario character at all. What? This looks like a wet paint version of this.
All right, I'm going to buy an order of snacks and cigarettes and then I'm going to open it up.
Snacks. These are popular. These are popular. All right. Order. Insufficient warehouse space.
Get out of here with this bullshit. Now I need cigarettes. We're going to go with the Super
Blend. Premium tobacco and Super Blend. That's a lie. I have room. What is this number even
trying to convey to me? 20 in brackets, 122 out of 200. What? 20, 122 out of 200.
This is delivery on the way. Can I upgrade the warehouse? I actually might be able to.
I'm okay on gas. I might need some more. Thanks. I might consider a trash removal
because maybe this smells. Still streaming. Yeah, for now. What's wrong with your car?
Can I do any funny dances? Yeah, I can do most of the Fortnite dances.
I practice them a lot. At least the default ones that came with the game. I haven't played
in a pretty long time. I have like probably two or three thousand hours in Fortnite though. So
I do know a little bit about it. Stopped playing it a while ago though. I can do those. I love
that game. I just kind of wish they would. And I want to say out of the building, when you like
build and jump around and build, I kind of just lost interest after a while. It's a really fun
game. I think it's really like great game though. You love making people hate you.
Didn't I say I was going to stop doing this? I did say that, didn't I? I made it pretty clear
that I was going to stop doing that. Well, well, well. Clean the scanner? I didn't even know I could
move my mouse in that direction. All right, get that delivery, order the food, and then we're
going to get the bus stop. Where's this delivery? Hurry up. What's going on? Something, there's
something wrong over here. Something's going wrong. Oh, this is the guy I threw into the atmosphere.
He's back. Yep, I got it. Come on in. This out. Go ahead and take off so I can close please.
Which is you just know the devs did not want to fix. What is that? Is that like a wait problem?
It just wasn't necessarily programmed that the cars were going to weigh more so they can be
moved very easily. Yeah, you can broom the delivery trucks. I just don't want to
because I need the deliveries. You're breathtaking. All right. Wow, these are popular.
Okay, now I need cigarettes and a little bit more ice cream and I'm done and I'm ready. I didn't know
I forgot to add the whatever. It's a naked guy in the store. No, it's not. Game lag.
That's it. Thank you. Okay. I've not cleaned the bathroom. Holy shit. That's accurate.
Oh, God. It's probably horrible in here. These like piss prints. Why are they weirdly single file?
Mm hmm. Give me a minute. Painting over the poo stains. That's just gross. Grow up, Jeremy. Grow up.
Oh, shit. Customer fuel. Cash register. Fuel is low. Customer garage. Mm hmm. Thank you.
All right. Next. This guy is naked. I thought you were lying. Holy shit. This guy has no clothes on.
Why is the merchandise so dusty? Hire staff? I can't hire anybody yet. I have to like level up.
Thanks. Out. Room the truck. You happy? Are you happy? Now it's stuck there. Almost got it.
There we go. All right. Now just keep going. You're good. Keep going. Stop turning to the pole. Yes.
Okay. He's good. He's good to go. All right. Time to open up the thing. How many people have I killed?
Zero. Warehouse door. It's okay. Let me just clear out this queue. It's a never-ending queue.
Oh my god. There's too many people. Thank you. Goodbye. Okay. What else did I get? Alcohol. He
made it out. He's a little wobbly, but I think he's all right. All right. One tire. Two mirrors.
Warehouse. I know. I know. I know. I know. There's a lot going on. Playing Among Us
mini games. That's fine. Thank you. Okay. I got a lot of money. It's time. Yeah. All right. It's
time. It's time. I need fuel. All right. I need a delivery of fuel and then I am constructing that
bus stop. All right. Let's go. One more delivery of ice cream. What are you buying? What is all
this shit? I caught that at the last second. How many? Did you buy like three packs? How
much cigarettes are you buying? Imagine being a cashier saying all this shit. What are you buying?
Oh my god. How many cigarettes are you buying? Too many. Two? Four packed cigarettes? What the
hell are you doing? Making money though. And now I understand. Let's say if I was running a store
or like a restaurant or something and it's like you got like 20 people in line and the person's
ordering. Just like, oh yeah. Can I, can I get it? I'm sorry. It's like you order what you want. Get
out of the way. Oh, but excuse me. Can mine come with light oil? No. Just order it and leave.
Oh my god. Let me see the menu. I'm like, let me give it a little closer look here.
So Dex, this says it comes with vinegar and oil. Can it come with just light oil? No, actually,
you know what? No, I can have a peppers on it. Yeah, just order it and leave. Clean the store?
It's always funny when people go to like a fast food restaurant where the menu hasn't changed in
like 60 years. Now does, does the Whopper come with pickles? It's been the same menu for fucking
a hundred years. What are you talking about? I don't, what? They have not changed that menu in
like, since like 1950. What if they, what if they don't know, Jeremiah? I know. I'm just saying.
That's, I love that video. It's like the funniest video. I can do a quick like this
fastest hot dog shooter, uh, in a North rest. I don't know. Probably the whole world.
I can do a quick
get the bus stop. Why is there? Okay. Here it comes. Here comes the bus stop.
A single bus can hold a massive crowd. I are some employees. I don't have access to employees.
Where do you see this? I have shelves. See it's grayed out, man. There's a, there's a bus comes
immediately. I don't have any more fuel. Uh, you know what's insane about that video? That guy,
somebody, uh, if somebody's like a doctor or a scientist or whatever, maybe you just know
he is, he's inhaling the hot dogs into his lungs. Am I understanding that correct?
How do we feel? No. Are you sure?
Yes. There's pickles on the Whopper. They've been there for 50 years.
Yeah. I can do the fries without salt. Of course I can. No, no, we don't sell another restaurant's
food. Why would you think we have another restaurant's food? Oh, sorry. Stole shit out of
my. It's time to clean up. What is going on? What is happening? What the fuck are these people?
Are they taking shit? What's going on? Are they paying? I can't tell if they're paying or not.
What is wrong with you? Is this Santa? All right. All right. All right. I'm going. I'm going. I'm
going. I'm going. This is going to be a ton of money. Okay. I really hate to be this guy,
but can't you all just order a huge amount of shit together? There's only four items in this
entire store. Can you just like kind of do it together on the same check? You know what I mean?
Like I'll just put like 10 of each thing into a basket and look, you can even pay me like 10%
under. I'll give you like a fucking warehouse price. I'll give you a bulk price. Just please.
What are they doing out there? Yeah. I don't have any gas. Oh, you guys are
fucked. How's that for a party music? Wait, that's it. What? Okay. So just to give you a
little bit, I'm not going to be doing this in the furry costume because that's me, right? That would
be me doing that. I'm not going to, I'm not, it's absolutely not going to happen. Hey, man. Hey,
what would you get? Pringles. Yeah. Me too. Hey, I also got two, three doctor peppers. Oh yeah. Me
too. Oh, the tongue. I mean, what'd you get? Hey, you know, you can't drop pepper and a, uh,
can't pringle, you know, it's just simple stuff for me. A couple beers. You got it too. Yeah, man.
Wow. Pringles. Cool. Awesome. Hope you enjoy the party or whatever it is. What the hell are you
doing? Yeah. Take this with you. I actually hit it. Where am I? Oh, imagine the cast. What happened
here? Answer the phone. Oh no. Somebody cars upside down. What happened? All right. Answer the
phone call from uncle Ted. It's not his name. I don't even know why I said that. I was the rush
hour nephew. Hope you didn't get trampled beneath all the customers coming in from that bus.
I've heard workers tell me I'm on the phone just between a passenger bus. I'm on the phone. Now,
if you're feeling overworked, how about investing in some help?
Trust me. Oh my God. Are you kidding me? Thank God. I need somebody to work this register.
All right. Uh, just hold on. Employee. There's nobody, there's nobody here. Employee camper.
Oh, they have to live. Okay. If they live here. Okay. I have an employee camper hire. Shit.
I didn't need to buy an employee camper. I need to register. Why do I only have 47 seconds to
make a hiring decision? This doesn't feel right. What? Um, okay. John's resume makes it clear he
is overqualified for the job. He finished law school and held a job as an attorney. He ceased
working in law at a strange time, too early to be a career choice mistake, too late to be
disenfranchised with his line of work. He does not appear willing to elaborate his website.
Surprisingly, does not. All right. The resume has no hesitation in telling that, uh, Emily is
looking for a temporary job. Her goal is to become a socialite based off her listed personal
information. Her previous work experience has all been mundane jobs at the service level, but number
she's worked in the industry for years now, she became a different person. Oh, right. Cause
23 minutes? What happened? Andrew just finished working three jobs simultaneously. There's
somebody else that he's looking for more profitable work. No matter the difficulty to have a little
more time to himself than, but why do I have 24 minutes now? The last page of his resume
notes that he is trying to save money for either a potential trip or immigration to Europe. Okay.
He's noted to be an outgoing, easily approachable man with no service experience. You can only use
his opinions to judge his effectiveness in working at the gas station. Okay. Cleaning six, register
one, repairing one, 14. I think honestly, I'm talking, I think a lawyer would do pretty good
behind the register. I'm going to go with the lawyer. Oh wait, I can hire you both. All right.
You both hired. Okay. So how do I, now what do I, all right. Well, I need help. I need some help.
Where's John? I just hired him. John, is he in his Hollywood actor trailer? Where is he?
He's resting. Oh shit. Look at this line. Look at this line. Come on, hurry up. How come I don't
get to go to sleep? Close the store. I mean, this is money coming in. You would after the rush.
There's a lot of people here. Do more cocaine. Stop staying open 24 seven. Why would the scanner
be on the other side of the basket? That's such a small thing, but I, it's funny. That's such a
little thing. You guys are making me fucking laugh today. Okay. Where is that employee
van thing? Whatever it was. I saw it get built. Where is it? There's a mirror. Only, holy shit.
You're going to pay me 200 plus dollars to just replace your mirror. Oh my God. I could probably
do this. You're not going to be, okay. Behind the warehouse. Is he in here? There's a health bar.
John, can you go handle the register? There's a health bar. All right. You take the register.
I will handle the cleaning. All right. If you need help, John's here to assist you if you need
it right there. He's ready for this trash and this place up a little bit. You're ringing up the stuff
more than once. You just rang up things like four times, John. And by the way, how come you can use
the scanner in the basket? I didn't even know you could do that. That's based. You're going to get
higher profits. Uh, what was that? I don't want to be like the annoying boss. That's like me. Are
you doing it right? Are you doing it right? I would need more ice cream, more ice cream,
more drinks. Let your employee work for eight hours. Oh, okay. Pretty good. Take care of this.
Thank you. Uh, nice work. Hey, premium. Wait, I owe him $22, but I can pay him 200. What does that do?
Oh, here's what I paid 200. I don't even have $200. Oh, okay. Yeah, I do. Hold on. Don't need
the garage. I got to make a delivery. Okay. What did I say we needed? We needed ice cream. I want
one of those right now. Okay. And I want bold almond. Also, we need some drinks. Okay. That
should be good. And then a snack. We got plenty snacks. It's far too much than I can hold. Come
on. Come on. I got to upgrade the warehouse. Oh, you're doing great. Warehouse. Oh, it's like
200 bucks to upgrade this thing. Finally workshop level two. All right. Not yet. Okay. Now I can do
this delivery. One ice cream and some drinks and what else? So maybe a little bit of something
for the car. It's going to be a lot of money, but all right. You kidding me. All right. Let's go.
Still have plenty of gas. I think I had a Raptor mask on. Hire somebody for the garage.
I couldn't hire a second person. A hire. No space for new employee purchase additional trailer.
You need to upgrade your station. All right. Look, can you hear his 30 bucks?
And I'll give you a premium payment after this. Go and head to the repair the shop. Plenty of
alcohol, ice cream. I got plenty of snacks. Okay. Get another gas pump. How much is a second gas
pump? 300, 350. Get a second dispenser. Good. Oh shit. I need to be able to afford to pay this guy.
Stop. I'm here. Old restocking. That's good. More. Nice. Okay. Restock all the shelves.
Clear. I think I need fuel soon here. Oh God. Where's your, I'm going to run out of fuel.
And that'll do it. That'll do it. That'll do it. Come on. Hurry up. 200 bucks. Okay. Get it.
You're a human parrot. I know. Just say shit all the time. Your employee is getting tired.
All right. I'll make, I'll send him. He can rest. I'm going to clear out this line.
You've been playing this for six hours. Yeah. I know. I mean, it's, it's kind of, it's fun.
It's just like a menial task game. It doesn't really need to be anything else. And there's
like a little, there's a slow trickle of upgrades. I think you want to keep going.
I think it's fun. All right. Here comes the delivery. I don't, customer's order. I,
you, I know you want gas. All right. Don't be mad at the customer. Relax. Good. Good. Okay.
Cigarettes are there. Booze is here. I got a fully stocked store. Oh, John. Yep. Connect it.
Fill it up. John, John, take a break. You can take a break. Excellent work. Okay. Uh, don't fire him.
Take a break. Hello, sir. Parked in a weird place. Where's this premium payment? I don't,
I can't give, I don't have $200. I, I have $143. No one in six hours has needed a full tank of gas.
Go perfect hits by serving customers to receive tips. My God. Stop shaking their sodas.
That's definitely supposed to be Elon Musk, right? Yeah, that was, I would say that was a great order.
Two of those like fruity pushup, uh, frozen treats and two popcorns. That was a great order. Oh,
I thought I didn't like the ice cream. All right. Clean up and then I'm going to go check on, uh,
I'm going to get a garbage to come and then let's go check on, I'm going to clean and then I'm going
to go check on John. Buy a new floor. You mean I could have had something besides this dirty
ass floor the whole time? Really? Decorations indoor. Oh man. No, no, you can't. How about an
old wagon wheel? That's cool. Let's get that. Cool. Put the clock back. Look, now I have,
the place has personality. All right, John, I need you out here. You have a minute. All right,
John, you take care of the, uh, I don't think there's enough materials. No, there's not. I need
a delivery of the materials. Um, go do the register. That helps. Okay. I need you to go
in and handle the register. Dirty bathroom and all this. Okay. We're good. Now clean the mirrors.
There we go. Fuel. How come you're not picking locks? What the fuck? I was curious why I couldn't
do this. I'm going to get in trouble for this. Picking the locks. What's in there? Five bucks?
That's it? Why am I saying that's it? Hold on. Oh, I need to be a master. I got a first try.
Hold on. You got a drum set and you need $18? Holy shit. This is perfect. Where's John?
All right. You just can't, you're irritating me now. Get out of here. Stop it. Don't rob too many.
Your reputation is going to be on the line. Shit. You're kind of right. Aren't you?
Oh, weird. The, uh, the owner of this place is just walking around picking locks. Stop,
stop moving the car. Five bucks. That's a lot. 370. We need, I need to buy more car parts.
Nothing's gone. I'm good. Hey, I'm going to tell you right now. I got a premium payment for you.
Keep up the good work. In fact, what I need you to do now, I really kind of need, I'm,
you know, you go ahead and you feel, um, oh, let's go help the cleanup.
Take over from here, John. Okay. We need tires. This is so expensive right now. God damn it.
140. I think I have a few of these. I need tires bad. All right. Hey, uh, all right. Come here.
Take that register. I'm busy right now. I got this. Okay. Finally, here comes the delivery.
You go ahead and keep them distracted. 16 bucks. Thank you. This doesn't open this one.
There's a master lock. Shit. Shit. Oh, good luck with the snakes. 11 bucks. Nice. Oh, delivery.
My stupid. All right. Open this door. Take the delivery truck. This is my, my order. I'm going
to lock pick my own order on. Hurry up. Wow. I'm sorry. She's just sitting there.
Okay. Fuck. I have one more chance. That's the best one all night. For sure. I ain't,
I think there's going to be one better than that one. Oh, God fucking damn it. I didn't want to
give him 200 bucks. Thank God. There's a timer. I didn't even mean to do that. You have a smash
brothers when you would do the hit the dummy with the baseball bat. And for some reason you did it
perfect that one time. It's 30 to 40% harder than any time you'll ever do ever again. That's how I
felt about that last one. I'm not going to be able to replicate that again. All right. My delivery
came in, so let's go stalk that. I can't believe, why did you tell me I could steal from people?
Now this is all I'm doing. Some comedian, some, you've probably heard this a thousand times.
So I'm not claiming this is my like funny joke or anything, but there really needs to be two horns.
It needs to be a like fuck you horn like, like this. And there has to be a little like,
huh. Should be two different sounds. You've said this before. Yeah, but I mean it.
How many times I would like to beep at somebody, but have it be like a, Hey,
I just like, I'm just trying to let you know something is a regular car horn is just
you're pissed. It just sounds so angry. Herb your enthusiasm. Yeah. Yeah, probably. I'm not even
working anymore. I'm just like stealing from people's cars. Come here. Oh shit. I still do
this. What do you need? All right. You got a messed up tire. I can take care of that.
This has been really cozy stream. Oh, thanks. I'm just kind of hanging out. I've been having
a great time and having a really good time. I need an anti-scratch. You're welcome. Shit.
No, wait, something wrong with your tire. There's something wrong with your tire. I forgot.
She's trying to drive. That's why I can't do it. Stop trying to drive and whatever.
What bucks? What do you have yet? 15 bucks. All right. That'll be 15 bucks. Where's John?
What's happening here? Hold on. There's nobody in this car. Does it help? What's that guy doing?
All right. No more stealing. I'm not doing that anymore. Where's John? How you doing, John? Nice
work. Good. Cars fueled. Shop customers met. Received tips and repaired cars. It's going to
take a long time. Hire somebody. I need another trailer, right? I can't get another trailer
until next level, which is probably going to take a long time. It's probably not a bad place to stop,
to be honest. He's stuck. He's not. What's going on here? Are you not ringing up customers?
These people are waiting for... How many people have you not serviced? Why does he have one of
those weird microphones? He's got one of those evangelical microphones. He's on stage doing a
stadium full of people. He's a televangelist. John, go take care of the cars. I'll get this.
You bought car goods? I only bought two tires. That's all I could afford. What's this thing?
What's this thing on the bottom? This product scan at a 732? That's kind of a weird number.
Out of 732? I kind of need to know what that means. Leveling up? All right. How are we doing?
Restock that. Restock this. Okay. Looks good. Holy shit. That was like a hiccup thing.
Don't fuck it up. Come on. It's right there. Where is it? Right here?
There we go. Running out of gas. No more fuel. He's looking for me? Where is he?
Where is that little shit? I got to keep some plates around or something to throw at him.
I don't know. I'm going to throw a can of Pringles at him. Where is he? No. Give me those. Give me
this. Give me. How do you miss that close? Just stop. Oh my God. Give me the... What?
What's going on? I didn't get it. What? How did I not get it? What the fuck is that?
Why did it break? By the way, thumbs down upside down is thumbs up. So, sorry. Blue rocket. All
right. I got some cool stuff. What did I get? Where's John? Oh, he's repairing somebody's car.
Never mind. Okay. Goodbye. Why am I still playing this? Oh, I don't know. I'm having a good time.
With the drum set in the store. I have a lot of decorations. I got to glitch a car into the store.
Yeah. That's a good idea. Oh, whatever. I'm out of gas.
How much do I owe you? It's going to have to be one of the little cars, I think. No,
there's no way a car is going to fit in here. No way. But what I can do, and I'm willing to do
this before the stream is over, is to put like at least, I would say at least 10 to 20 cars in the
warehouse with people driving them. Let's go ahead and get that started. Come on. Oh, no. I got to
open this first. Shit. Don't move. All right. You're not going to move. That's fine. Why is the back
door open? What? The back door shouldn't be open. No wonder the people have been stealing stuff.
All right. Let's go. This is a different person. This is not even the same person.
Okay. Good. There's one to keep you in. Yeah. You're definitely stuck. Let's try to get at
least 10 cars in here if I can. You're going to escape? No. Because once I get these two in,
I'm going to close the door. I wonder if they despawn. They might. Now you beep. Of all the
times we just go in here. I feel like I'm, what's like that sport with the, you're on the ice
and you have to go with the brooms curling. Okay. There we go. Now you're in. Okay. Good luck too.
All right. Let's close them in. They still in there. I want this close. See if they breed. Oh
yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Well, we've got plenty of people to push on. Are you trying to scam me?
Just trying to concentrate. Hey, almost there. Nice. They didn't despawn. Perfect. I think I
could probably get 10 before this takes too long. Oh, drive this way. No, you fool. No, you fool.
All right. Get in. Very nice. How do you not have a headache? Um, I don't know. I don't. Are they all
still waiting here at the register? Stop. Why are your cars so much heavier than everybody else's?
There you go. Stay right there for just a second. Oh shit. You're in the way. You're in the way.
Just get out of the way for a second. No, she's escaping. No, she's not. Okay. Go on this way.
Excellent. Stop. Stop. Oh boy. Oh boy. This is becoming ugly. It's already ugly and I haven't
even started. It's, she's doing it. She's going to stop driving around. All right. We're secure.
This is way lighter than all the other ones. Holy shit. Look at how this looks like air.
John? John. I owe John 200 bucks. He's just there. Oh no, John. John, go take care of the
register. Okay. Wait, John, where are you going? John, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I need to talk to you for a second. There. Take 200 and take another 200. Okay. I just gave you
$400. Go handle the register if you could. Thank you, John. Your boss is insane. Well,
stay like that for a second. Car like, yeah, this is too, okay. John is keeping this place afloat.
Yeah, he is. Good. No, no, no, no, no, no. Okay. There's plenty of room in here. This is a horror
movie from the antagonist's point of view. Just wait. Stay right there. Getting harder to get into
this room. What was that sound? I have to parkour over all these cars. Wow. Look at that. Didn't
even have to do anything. We got two. No, no, no, no, no, no. No, stop driving forward.
So me and John have quite an interesting operation here. So they're going through
the checkout line and they're driving through the exit over here and I'm pushing their car
into the garage. You should order a delivery. Yeah. The plan is if I can get 10 cars in here
and order delivery and then open the damn thing. Let's see what happens. Come on. You're dragging
John into this. No. There we go. There we go. Are the cars all spawned in here? One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven. Yeah. I don't even think I need to even close this. No, I don't.
I do not need to close this. All right. Send them. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Looks like this. No.
All right. Let's go. Come on. I need customers. Where's John? All right. Come on. Oh, there you
are. Rude. Almost there. No. Shit. So many more. There's so many more. There's so many. They're
all leaving at the same time. All right. You go in. Okay. You know you. Somebody's getting out.
Somebody's getting out. Somebody's getting out this side. Somebody's trying to get out.
This is a mess. Okay. Uh-oh. It's going to be really hard to get out. I don't think I need to
close the doors. Her car is wedged in blocking everybody else. Un-equip the broom. The broom
pushes it around. Nice. I'm not quite sure cars bounce like that. Somebody escaped? No, they didn't.
Oh, you're in. All right. Good. Not bad. We're going to have to make a little bit of room though.
So what I mean by that is some people have to get over on this left side here.
You're not going anywhere, so that's okay. Okay. That looks fine. You're not. You can't go anywhere.
One, two, three. All right. I got a lot of cars here. Let's get like three more.
I don't even think about it. Perfect. Perfectly wedged. Oh, perfectly wedged. Lovely. All right.
Well, there are no more customers. I think we are at the limit of spawn. Yeah, this is the spawn limit.
It's worse than before. There's more of cops. They're on to you.
I am Toga. Oh, shit. You almost got out. Is that the car? Wait, what is this car? Is this the one
I was just using? This car is really like bouncy. See? Why is it so bouncy? I'm being so bouncy.
What the hell? What is this accomplishing? You need to rethink your life. Well, I mean, there's
a goal here. The goal is to get a bunch of cars in here and then order a delivery truck.
So, I mean, there's a goal. I love how the shape of this car is hard to move around. God damn it.
You had so many opportunities to get away there. Oh, this car. No. We're losing people.
That's better. Yeah, that's fine. Do that. So close. You, get back in there. Got it.
They're going to start to just pop around and I'm not going to be able to stop it. Oh, shit. Oh,
shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
No, no, no, no, no. Damn broke. Nobody nobody's getting out the other way, right? We're good.
All right. One more and I'm calling a delivery truck. Why is this the longest stream you've
done in three years? What? I played the Lord of the Rings game for like 14 hours. What are
you talking about? That was like two years ago. Very invested. I'm going to call the delivery
truck and then we're going to play the tour go theme for like 10 minutes until the delivery
truck gets in. I don't want to be too crazy about this because they all have to go in.
Perfect. All right. In, in, in. All right. It's time. All right. It's time. This is perfect
entrance. I have to order the delivery truck. This is ready. All right. Save the game. Cool.
Okay. Order delivery and I'm going to sit right there. I'm going to watch it. The whole thing
and the master. I will not be pleased here. Take a shit load of money. You know what? Here,
just take it all. Take it all. And then, you know, just don't, you don't get out of here.
I don't want you, I don't want you near this. Hi, I'm Targa. All right. Let's call a, uh,
we need a big, we need like a big one. So tires go. I go from inside or from outside.
I wonder what's inside. Maybe what's a better perspective. Oh no, no, no, no. Where is he?
Where is the delivery truck? Oh, here it comes. Oh God. Here it comes.
Play the guitar. Oh shit. I don't want to be in the middle of this.
I don't want to be in the middle of this. Where's the guitar? Oh fuck. He's here. He's coming. He's
coming. He's coming. I can't even get to the guitar, man. I'm stuck now. I'm right in the
middle. I'm right in the eye of the storm. He's like, I'm not going in there. What are you talking
about? We'll go in there. Look, I am talking. It's going to be so hard to get him in here.
It has to be precise. Turn the car around. Turn the car around. Be facing the right direction.
Come on. You need to be facing the right way. It's not too tall.
I think a party bus just came in. Oh shit. I gotta get the bus. I have to get the party bus in here.
Come on. Get in there. Get in there. I have to get the party bus in here. That's the absolute
culmination of this whole thing. It's in. It's in. It's in. Oh my God. It's in. I'm going to the back
door. I'm pushing it in. Get out of the fucking way. Get in there. Get in there. It's in. Oh my
God. Oh, I think this is over. How can you work here? Give me that party bus right now.
I'm not having a good time at all. You know what? Hey, who cares? Everything's free today.
Everything's free today. You don't have to pay for anything. All free. I shouldn't have said
anything. Come on. It's all for free. Who cares? Can I join the party? All right. This thing is so
big. It's so huge. I have to get it over there. Nobody's even driving this stupid thing. Here we
go. Oh, what a perfect shot. I think the cop got out. I'm closing the door. I'm going to have a
rave in here. Make room. Make room for the party bus. It's almost in. Get this out of the way.
I thought he said imagine the fumes. It's almost in. Just wedge it in. Come on. Get over there.
Not bad. This might work. It's straight in. Oh, it's in. Get in. It's in. It's in. It's so close.
It's so close. One or two more pushes. This should be it. Got it. Done. Game over. Lock him in.
All it takes is a little bit of chaos and this should start moving.
I can't play Venga bus. It's illegal. Okay. That car is hiding from me. That car is currently
hiding. Like I can't see you. Does that mean all the aliens are going to come back here?
I don't think there's any more cars. Oh, shit. Who are you? We got to go in the back. Get a
plane in here. I don't think I can't drive a plane. Just go this way. Drive around. You can do it.
Don't worry about that. I don't think there's much else I can do. You need a fuel truck.
Don't even tell me to do that. I'm pretty sure that's the end.
Close both ends? I don't think I can. I don't even know how this car got like this.
I can't go that way. I should be able to close both now, right? Yeah.
Mart, you waited till I opened the door. Then you think you can get out. Very smart.
Why am I speaking with a fake English accent? I'm going to let you go. Yes, fucking kidding.
Can I pick the party bus? No. Master Lock. I can't sit down. What the fuck?
I can't sit down and play this. There's a truck on it. Really? Oh, that's annoying.
Nope. It's broken. All right. That's it. I'm out. I'll see you guys on Wednesday.
Press the red button. What the hell? This has been a gas station simulator. I recommend it.
Very fun. I think that I had a pretty good time. That was a good time.
And I'll see you guys on Wednesday. We're going to do some redoing some tier lists.
I've been to more restaurants. I think I have more. I want to see how much I am the same.
Maybe I'm a little different than a few years ago. So we'll see you Wednesday.
Have a good rest of your weekend. Tomorrow is, well, it's kind of the end of the weekend
right now on Sunday. Hope you have a good week though. We'll see you Wednesday around
two o'clock Pacific. Maybe we'll see you there. Take care of yourselves. Let's do the intro,
the outro, actually. Hey, look at this. Yeah. I love this one. I also have the other songs too
that Florida made. I want to compile like all of these and be able to kind of switch to them
whenever. You'll be hearing this a lot. Anything else we can suggest for Wednesday's stream?
Wednesday's stream? I need some protein. Jesus. Yeah. I kind of want to do tier lists,
maybe some quizzes. Just kind of chill for a few hours. It was just a browser-based stream.
Let's see. Do Buzzfeed quizzes. I want to do ones I haven't done before though. I did a lot.
It's going to be hard to even remember which ones I did do. But thanks to the subs, everybody.
This is the list of subs. Still a lot of people. Even since pulling back to like once, maybe twice
a week streaming, no one here is obligated to give me any money. Surprising all the time. So
thank you. Ray Joel. Yeah, sure. I'm just going to listen to this music all day. Speaking of good
music. I mean, who could forget this? I mean, this is like classic, right? This song is also very
lovely. All right. Yahoo. I haven't rated somebody in a while. Joel, what's Joel doing?
Grand Theft Auto? GTA Spooky Mysteries? What is GTA Spooky Mysteries?
It seems interesting. Yeah, let's rate Joel. What? Okay. Ludwig's playing this game called
Super Auto Pets. This game's cool. It looks like really interesting. Like a tower defense.
The new Twitch meta. It looks really cute. I watched him play it for like 30 minutes or so,
and I was like, I didn't have any idea what was going on, but it looked cute.
I go say hello to Joel and whatever this is, GTA, the custom mod missions or something.
Whatever it is, we're about to find out. I'll see you guys on Wednesday. Take care of yourselves.
Have a great night. You can get that to 7K though. I know you can. You can get that to 7K.
Come on. You can do it. I've seen you do it before. Come on, Gwen. Come on, Gwen. I know you can.
Come on. There we go. All right. I'll see you guys Wednesday. Take care of yourselves.