How are you? What's up? What's up? Hey, somebody said, why is he doing the DLC?
Yeah, I played the main game, the base game. I played it pretty much on launch.
Resident Evil Village DLC. That's what is on tap tonight.
Play Roblox. No, all of you people that are saying play Roblox.
You want to play Roblox. So when I go into a server,
6,000 of you will join that server and like throw rocks at me. No, I'm not going to play it.
You guys are all collectively going to go into the Roblox server I go into
and body block push me off of a cliff. And maybe I'll do it one day. I don't know. No,
not right now. It's Halloween. I'm going to play Roblox on Halloween. It's Halloween in a few days.
We're doing Resident Evil Village DLC. I've heard this is only a few hours.
We'll see how it goes. Another couple of hours. We'll see. And if I get to the end of this and
it's, you know, well, you say it's like three to four hours, but you're not accounting for the
amount of time that I'm going to stop and tell you in like a 15 minute conversation about the
my favorite Tabasco flavor, right? It's probably going to be a little longer than that. Which,
by the way, original red is fantastic. But I think a lot of people are sleeping on the green.
It's a little thicker. It's a little more like pickled, almost like jalapeno flavor.
The green is great. I think a lot of people are sleeping on it.
I'm not a big fan of the Chipotle one. No original green. Green looks like baby food.
Doesn't taste like baby food. Will you ever do chat picks a Diablo two skill tree again?
I don't own hardcore, right? That's what it was. What a weird group of streams that was.
I played hardcore Diablo two. That was weird. No, no, maybe they were fun. They were fun.
Let's go over a few things. So first of all, today we're streaming here for the, you know,
until we're done tomorrow. We're going to be streaming at 2pm. I'm trying to pull the streams
back because the internet problem has not been fixed. I did get in touch with the ISP and somebody
is going to, the technician is going to look into it. It's going to be whatever.
But at like 8pm Pacific, we might run into like an internet wormhole. So we're going to,
we're going to have to ride it out. If that happens, I'm trying to pull the streams back.
And yeah, I pulled it back 30 minutes today, but I really want to get started at like 1 to 2pm
permanently until that issue is solved. So we'll see. Cross your fingers. It doesn't happen,
but somebody is looking into it permanently. Internet wormhole. I don't know. Like we just
run into some weird route at like 8pm that makes my internet shit. Sometimes it's on my end.
Sometimes it's not. It's very strange. I don't know. Guys, there's just like wires and boxes
that are connecting all of us. I don't know. It's a bunch of wires and like electrical boxes.
It's pretty much magic. It pretty much is. If anybody were to ever come and conquer Earth,
I'm telling you, they're going to see all this shit underground. They're going to come here
for the gold. They're going to come here for the gold, but they're not going to understand
what the internet is. And they're going to see all these wires in the ground and be like, yeah,
dig all that up. That's not the gold, but that's what they really should have been looking for.
It's the infrastructure. It's the internet, right? Our communication ability.
And they're just going to go for the gold. Why would they want it? Does nobody get this?
Nobody gets this. Oh, the movie came out like 10 years ago. Nobody cares.
Nobody understands this, what I'm saying. Really? What? I don't want to say the movie
because I feel like people are going to be like, what the fuck, dude? I've never seen that movie.
People know what movie I'm talking about, right? Bro, chill. I'm fucking chill. What?
Don't tell me to chill. Who are you? Who is that person? I'm perfectly chilled out right now.
Dude, I was fine until you said that. If you haven't seen this movie in 10 years,
all right, then you're probably not going to see it. Or you'll probably, you've ever,
it's Avatar. You've all seen Avatar. Who has not seen Avatar in this chat?
There has to be nobody here. And they're coming out with like 10 more of them. So whatever.
You chill. You need to chill out. I'm chilling out right now. I, yeah,
spoiler alert for the movie Avatar that came out in like 2012. He's aging. Yeah, I am.
And I'm fine with it. What is it? Avatar is a movie that is about plugging in
and like being in another person's body. It's been a long time. I haven't seen it in a long time.
All I know is that there's like metal in the earth or in their earth. Whatever. I don't,
oh wait, I'm done. What is it called? Unobtanium. The movie was fine. That was,
I thought it was entertaining. It was fine. I thought it was cool. Dude, relax. All right.
You can't tell me to relax when I'm about to play like a horror game. And in Resident Evil
Village is it a horror game? It kind of is. Anyways, welcome everybody. We're going to turn
on Resident Evil Village's DLC. This is where you play as Rose. It literally came out today.
I also have another thing to talk about, but I'm going to wait. I'm going to wait
until there are enough people here. I don't want to say it until enough people are here.
Wait. Once we have all of you are here, we'll tell you something. It's very good DLC. That's
good to know. NK is not enough. My thing doesn't say 10K. My thing doesn't say that. Has it not
updated? Well, just wait. Wait like 10 minutes. Do we need to take a roll call? Okay. Roll call.
Who's here? Are you here? Say, present. You guys ready for the village? We're going to have to
adjust the audio, I think. All right. So is it good? I'll put two headphones in. All right.
Shadows of Rose. I got to remember how to play this game. I don't remember how to play.
This is new content. This came out literally today. Apparently it's pretty good.
It's a short campaign. Looking forward to it. Are you ready? Here it comes. You look like you're
from LA Noir. What do you think? Dude, you're going to play it all up. Hey, K. Sorry I'm late.
It's okay. I'm just enjoying the day. You said you had something important to tell me.
I hope it's not about Chris wanting me to join his operation because
I already told him that's not happening. I see what he puts you and the rest of his
hound wolf squad through. No thank you. It's not about that. It is about you.
Play the new Call of Duty or else. Stop talking during the movie. How are things at school?
Seriously? That's what you wanted to talk to me about? That group of mean girls still
hassling you? You mean are they still treating me like a freak? Hey, uh-uh. Look at me.
You are not a freak. I am. No I am. That's why I keep my distance from everybody at school.
They knew what I really was. So you don't have any friends that you can talk to? Who is this?
Talk to? About what? How I'm hardly even human? How I'm some kind of horrendous monster?
Hey, it's okay. I hardly ever murder my friends. What if there were a way to get rid of your powers?
And get rid of them in a heartbeat. Get rid of them? All right. Well, I think there's something I need
to show you. Get rid of your powers? We already know about Miranda and the mutimized heat. How
she researched it obsessively and performed experiments on human subjects. Like me? Exactly.
Uh, what you don't know is that we recently found some of her research.
Apparently she discovered a purifying crystal that can remove the mutimized heat from a toast.
Purifying crystal? If we can get our hands on one of these we might be able to weaken or
remove your powers entirely. Are you kidding me? No, no, but her notes are incomplete. However,
I wouldn't want to get rid of all of them. I think I have an idea where we can find the rest of her
research. Let's do it. Let's find it. Where is it? In there. What? You just have to, uh, you just
have to drink that. Stores memories from people who pass away in close proximity, including Miranda
and everything she knows. Be careful, it smells like puke. You might be able to solve the mystery
of the purifying crystal. Wait, what do you mean enter its consciousness?
Yes. Okay, so you, your deep connection will allow you to explore the information within.
That sounds crazy. You sound crazy. Yes, yes, yes, Rose, but not dangerous.
Right? Think of it just like walking through somebody else's memories.
You really think this can work? I think it's worth trying.
What do you have to lose? It's just going to be like, how do I even do this in red Kool-Aid like
molasses? I don't know. Try reaching out to it. It's Halloween, Rose. Okay. Fine. What the hell?
It's reacting. Rose is so weird. Yeah, it's like she sees things that aren't there.
Creepy. What? Imagine wanting to be friends with her. Why would you not want to be friends
with a person that has fucking superpowers? Are you out of your mind? She's weird. Okay. She has
like Avengers level superpowers. Don't. I'm still here. Okay. Okay. Where are you?
If Captain America walked in the room, would they go, oh, he's weird. What's her superpower?
Super strength? She could have bugs come out of her hands or something. I don't know. With something.
What is it? It's mold. She has like powerful mold bugs. She has powerful mold that can
she could do like a venom arm like that can come out. Okay. Well, anyways, hi, I'm back. So let's
play. Miranda's research claims that the mega my seat preserves the memories of people who
passed away within its area of influence, absorbing them into its own vast consciousness. We also know
based on our previous encounters with the mold that people who are contaminated with the meta
what is that word spelled out phonetically for me? Meta my seat. I was gonna say meta mucil.
How is it? Whatever. All right. So you get on this mold network. So there's a mold network. If we
extrapolate from this, we can summarize that subjects with a strong affinity to the meta my
seat should be able to use the network to connect to the memories of the dead within the mega
my seat. It should be possible to verify this theory using the lab's mega my seat sample we
collected 16 years ago. We just need a suitable subject with a proven connection to the mold.
It's a network. Unfortunately, this presents a problem. Our organization's policies prevent us
from directly contacting civilians who are infected with muta my seat. Certainly, the ethical reasoning
is understandable, but it has rendered the confirmation of this theory impossible. It pains
me to think of how much mankind could stand to benefit from this preservation and indexing of
human consciousness, the possibilities of preserving or even reclaiming great minds. Perhaps there's
some way of cutting through the red tape. Okay. Why is this in third person game? Why is it in third
person? Did I pick third person? It's they just added it. Yeah, but is this is the DLC third person?
Wait. Yes. Wait. What? Explore. Wait, what's in here? I can't. I don't think I can do it. It's too scary.
Okay, this is so imagine you get like locked in this place. Like you got teleported to this place.
I really think the John Jingleheimer Schmidt routine would actually benefit you. It really would
because I mean, look, at some point, like you're you're you're fucked here. You know what I mean?
What are you gonna do? No, I would just barrel down this hallway screaming John Jingleheimer
Schmidt and just throwing stuff around and like dancing and making like weird sound effects. I
think they'd be like, what the fuck is going on? Send this guy back out. We want somebody that's
like scared. We want somebody that's like, like, no, we don't want we don't want this guy. This
guy's fucked up. Okay. What are you out? Okay. So it was from the last stream. It's a reference.
You need to out psycho the psycho. Just do the routine. We're like, are you not locked in here
with me? I'm locked in here with you. The other way around. It's me. You need to be afraid. Yeah,
just start screaming that right? What is this? Oh, it's a shoe. Have I rotated? Oh, or just pull
the routine, the routine on them. Just find a really echoey part of this castle and just do
their routine, you know, just sit there and just kind of go like they'll be like this. I'm supposed
to be doing that. Why are they doing that? It would just mess them all up. It would just walk
them up. Let me know. Okay, that's actually kind of scary. Oh, this is a memory. Anything I can do?
Is someone there? Dangerous here. What is? Why? Hang tight. I'm gonna see if I can find a key.
What? No, we don't know who's in there. That's such a Dark Souls room, by the way.
Talk through the door to like the weirdo. And am I just going to open the door?
Okay, let me find a key. Do I have a map? Probably not. Not yet. Mirrors. What is that? Okay,
we're good. What's on it? Stop it from moving. Because it's weird and creepy. Yeah, it's creepy.
Is there a key? I feel like someone's going to be in this room now. Oh, that's okay. That's my name.
I thought that was a cake for a second.
Me! Fucking YouTuber. It's still in me. It's still there, by the way. I used to be a YouTuber,
okay? Years and years ago. What's this say? To create art, simply add to the rabbit's carcasses.
Decay is not an issue. Spruce them up a bit with makeup. It makes them seem more alive. Ah, all
right. Find the crystal. Find the key to the cell. Explore your surroundings. So I'm currently
searching this area. I gotta view files in the journal. All right. Did the guy draw a picture
of himself? Oh no, I did. Pretty good artist. Okay, all right, all right, all right. Why did
I think he did that? Maybe he handed me these notes just in case you forget who it is. It's me.
Honestly, this almost looks like, this almost looks like she held the paper up to his face
and shaded with a pencil. Like, that's how this picture came to be. Does that make any sense?
Those things are cool, by the way. It's like a little, all right, whatever. All right,
so where do I need to go? I need to go, I already went that way. I did not go up to the top left. So
let's just check to make sure there's nothing else here. Uh-huh, this way. I don't have any weapons.
Is there a gun? Oh god. Okay, there's the key. Don't step in that. Can I not step in it? Okay,
I gotta sell key. I don't have any items. All right. Um, can I step in that or is it gonna hurt me?
I guess I can go this way. Do I die if I step in that? I think I die if I touch that.
Okay, just don't. It's in here, right? No, where is it? This way. Something's gonna break through
this door. Left? Okay, yep. How do I sprint? All right, it's right here. I think I need to make
the game a little brighter. Who's in here? Watch out. Whatever it is, it's alive.
It's you. It's me. Literally me. That doesn't help. That doesn't help. Well, I mean, if we're
together, we may as well harmonize John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt. I think it would sound
better. John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt. It'd be fucking sick. Yeah, well, I could do the high
part as long as you can do the low part. What are you doing? Oh, there's a way to sneak. Okay.
She's you. She can't do the low part. Oh, that's right. I didn't think about that.
Get in there. Someone's gonna jump out. Oh, okay. What's going on? What's wrong?
There's another one? Quick, quick, quick before she dies. John Jacob Jingleheimer. That's all right.
Never mind. I can do the low part. Why are there so many roses? Don't press any buttons.
Hey, are you listening to me? What are we looking for? Find the switch handle.
All right. I need the handle. We need to find the handle. Do you have a handle
on the ground over here? Can I? Is it just there? Can I touch it? No. All right. I need a handle
this way. Switch handles missing. Okay. Find that handle. Go deeper. What does this mean?
Oh, I can go up here. I locked in here. No, I'm going to go. I'm going to go this way first.
This looks interesting. Okay. That wasn't anything. That was an exit. Something's going to
chase. Something's going to chase us around here without a doubt. That's definitely a way to escape
when a monster comes out here and attacks. All right. Let's sneak down there. I have a light,
right? Yeah. Okay. This that way. Wait, what's the map look like? All right. What was that?
What the fuck is that sound? Oh, this is behind where? Oh, this is these all me.
So many bodies. This one looks rendered. It's going to this one's rendered. You know what I'm
saying? When I meet what I said, this isn't like a 3D rendered model. I'm telling you,
it's going to stand up. Nothing here. Ah, I'm telling you, these are rendered 3D models.
Anybody have a key? Nobody has a key. You don't have like the key or like on you somewhere.
Okay. Well, it's not here. I can't honestly, I've gotten jumpier in the last five years. I
really have. I told you they were fucking rendered. They were rendered 3D models. I told you
they literally rendered models. They've rendered 3D models. Okay. Unlock this. All right. We're
okay. Straight right left. I want I've run button so bad. You have no idea. Oh, what the fuck? Oh,
what are her powers then? Fucking electric hands. Are you kidding me? Just like force hands.
Oh shit. Why? Escape the monsters. All right. Press it. Press the button quick.
Oh shit. I'm sorry. Oh my God. They're coming from every angle. How do I get out of here?
Open up. Hurry. Oh, God damn it. Oh, geez. Okay. We're good. All right. Here comes
an invisible wall. Wait, can I go that way? I don't care. Excuse me. I have to go back. Um, how?
Huh? There's no way to go. I can't get out of here. I'm trapped. Get the fuck out of the way.
How do I slide? Is there a slide button? This is probably a slide button, right?
How do I get out of here? Get out of the way. You're blocking the entrance. This is not fair.
Get out of the way. You've blocked the entrance. It's not fair. I got by.
I'm so fucked up. Am I going to make it this way? This way? Okay. All right. I made it.
Oh my God. They were blocking the entrance. That wasn't fair. All right. There's only one way to go.
Did I heal? Crouch and press Q to do a spin move. You made that up. There's no spin move.
There is no spin move. Talking about like, like zangief, like go, go, go, go, go. You
spin with the fists out. No, you okay? What are you? I'm the narrator, not enemy friend.
What were those things? What is happening here? Leave now. What is this? Where am I?
Hell. Come on, write it. Go while you can. Not until I get this out of my body. There's a crystal
here that will remove the mold. I need to find it and I'm not leaving until I do.
You're dangerous. Who are you? My guardian angel? Sure. That's funny. Do you have a name? If you're
an angel, then Gabriel, Michael. Michael. Okay. Michael, what now? Dangerous here. Move. Who's
Michael? Okay. Where even am I? Okay. Oh, wait. There is a typewriter. Very cool. Game is saved.
First aid. Yep. All right. Open inventory. I remember this. You can medicine that heals all
wounds. Uh, isn't there a quick way to do it? There's a quick heal somehow, right? You can make
healing items too, from my understanding. I played the game. I, of course I understand it.
Why are you so wide today? I'm not. I'm gonna call it my hairline, a parallelogram. What does that
mean? These poor things. So it's, it's the Duke, right? Yeah. I saw the trailer. So what is, is
the Duke a bad guy? I thought he was a good guy. I thought he, I thought he helped us. It's like we
caught another. Lively now, aren't you? You should have put that effort into running. It would have
made the chase that much more thrilling. Let me go. Let me go. It would seem this little rabbit lacks
the necessary fortitude. You had shown a little grit and actually escaped. That purifying crystal
would now be yours. The crystal. Oh, now we have a new little rabbit to pursue. Let's see how fast
this one is. I love this actor. He's great. Okay. I'm back and I'm ready to run.
There's a lot. Um, wait a minute. Okay. Where do I go? I can't open that. Dude. Oh my God. Okay.
All right. What? Oh, come on. What the hell? A way out.
Um, back this way. I need to. Oh, all right. We're good. Need weapon. Gun.
Seriously. Where am I going to get a gun? Touch my words. What? Like this?
Okay. Well, if you didn't manifest me a rocket launcher in the first 10 minutes of the game,
here we go. Point and shoot. Who is this tutorial text? Okay. His bullets. Third person is back. So
what's going on here? Can I shoot? Should I shoot this? Do the spin move? Okay. It's just,
all right. I get it. Actually, that's a good, that's actually good for me to know.
Acquire the crystal. All right. I can't go down here. No, I can't. Right. Okay. So that means,
where have I not gone? Straight through here. There's a door over this way. There's the crystal
right there. There it is. Just take it. A large crystal is glowing with a pale blue light. The
disciples await their masks. Bronze, silver, gold with their, I guess I need to find these
masks to unlock it. Okay. With their garb array, the light shall be released. We need three masks
to release the crystal. Okay. You got it. Shoot it. Shoot the glass. Not that easy. It's not that
simple. Check out grottobeast.com. Grottobeast.com. Not enough people here. I can talk about it.
So, grottobeast.com is available right now. This, the website's not there. This is literally just a
placeholder. But what is there is for you to drop an email. This is, this is going to the merch
company. .net also works too. .com redirects .net is there. Yep. You can put your email in,
which will go to our fulfillment company to decide if you are interested in this product.
Grottobeast.com. That must mean it must be coming soon. The website is a placeholder.
We're only trying to see how many people are interested because what's grottobeasts?
Oh, we got a lot to tell you. So, grottobeast.com is a trading card game. It's been in development
for about a year and a half. Fake fan. That's not a fake fan. I mean, you could have been
started watching like six months ago, a month ago. New viewer Andy. But we're trying to see
the fulfillment company wants to kind of know how many people are interested because we need
to figure out how many we need to make to, you know, preliminarily. So, if you're interested,
drop it there. It's not, no, it's a physical card. It's not digital. We're trying to garner
some interest and see how it is. It's really fucking cool. There are 200 cards. It's a bunch
of characters from this universe as well as Grottobeasts. It's 200 fucking cards. It is an,
it's an enormous project. It is a game. There are 15 artists that have participated. I'm one of
them. That's right. I'm one of them. Physical NFTs. So, we're trying, what I really want to do is I
want to make sure that whoever wants them can get them. So, we really have no idea how many we need
to make first. I don't want to have it be a case where there's like some odd hundred or some odd
thousand amount of people that want them, but I don't, we don't make enough, right, in this first
pass. This is a huge project that has been, it's essentially like a gigantic community love letter,
essentially. It's tons of references to streams. There's tons of original characters that have
been created by all the artists. It's, it's really, really cool. Will it ship to the EU? Of course,
absolutely. This is not NA only. How much to ship international? These are questions that I do not
have the answer to right now. All, all this is, that placeholder website is just there to just get
an idea for the fulfillment company, how many people might actually be interested, and we're
going to go from there. Yeah, Holly had a huge amount to do with this, as well as all the other
artists, and obviously all the other people that worked on it. It's been a big undertaking,
and it looks, it's fucking awesome, I'm telling you. There's a whole game. We have contracted out a
game designer to make this whole thing. It's actually really fucking fun. It's actually fun.
It's very fun. Tweet the website, you monster. Yeah, so how it's going to work, because it's a
game, we want to make sure that, because there'll be packs you can buy, right? Just booster packs.
But, did you, wait, did you actually call me a monster or not? So besides these booster packs,
we're going to sell a kit, like a starter kit, to make sure monster packs? What did I say? Did
I just say monster packs? No, I said booster packs, right? Yeah, there's going to be holographics.
There's going to be all the shit that you are used to, right? But there's going to be a starter
kit that's going to be two full decks, so you don't have to worry about it. You can just buy it,
and if you want it, and have it. But we also thought it would be fun to have these booster
packs where you can open them and get like, oh my god, I got a, I got a, I got like a holographic
bugleberry. He's a card, by the way. And price point-wise, I don't want to, this is going to be
something that I want to make sure is affordable, right? I don't want to do a thing where, oh yeah,
the card packs are fucking unbelievably egregious. No, no, it's not going to happen.
I don't know what the price is going to be, but we're going to try to keep it reasonable.
This is essentially just really interesting, a really interesting merch project that came about
a year and a half ago after that stream. And we're finally almost ready to start showing it off.
So, if it's a success, awesome. If it's not a success, it was fun to do. I just really hope
you guys think they're cool. That's all I care about. It's just, are these cool? Is it fun merch?
Is the game fun? And the answer to those questions, I think, are all yes. So grottobeast.com,
grottobeast.net. If you have any interest, please just fill out your email so you can be notified
when it happens and we can figure out how much we need to make. Is auto a card? Yes, there are 200
cards. And the starter deck, Holly, if you're here, do we know how many cards are in the starter deck?
Like, the starter kit that you can get that has two full decks and all of the materials you need.
Do we know how many cards are in the starter? Do we have any idea? So, well, let me get this
accurate, but it's going to be, if you don't want to buy boosters and you just want, like,
I believe the two decks have 41 cards each. Okay. So, you're going to be able to enjoy it if you
don't want to just buy boosters, which I also want to try to do this meaningfully and have it
be like orders, right? Rather than have it sell out as like, all right, that's it. We sold 1,500
copies. Goodbye. It's over. It's limited. No, I don't want it to be limited in the sense that
it's deliberately limited. So, deliberately not as many people that want it can get it.
There you go. Just go ask her. She's in your house. I'm like speaking into the air.
How many cards are in each deck? Do we know? Yeah. We're just trying to get some interest,
and that's it. I hope you enjoy it when it actually does come out. It's been a pretty long project,
which I will tell you, after spending the last year plus overseeing the development and being
part of a card game, it's a lot. The artists have spent a ton of time working on it. The game
designer has put tons of tons of love into it. I'm just excited for you to get in your hands.
So, that was the announcement for today. What if nobody's interested? Well, and oh well,
it was fun to do it. Yeah, we've been waiting for the time to be able to tell people because
if you saw the Grotto Beast banner on the baseball stream was kind of there, and it's like, hey,
look, this thing's still a thing. Okay, it's okay, man. I'll buy it. If you are interested
and you think it's cool, then yeah, I hope when you get it, I hope it's high quality.
I hope you enjoy it. We're trying to make it as good quality and price point, right? I look,
I'm trying. I'm going to catch them all. Why did I just say that out loud? You're going to collect
all the cards. Whatever. All right, so let's keep going. So I have to go to find the three masks,
which is I have not been through here yet. I have eight shots. Ooh, shotgun. I need a key.
Grant me that which sees the truth through its three eyes. I need a big key. I'm never going to
open this. Cut the chain. Okay, this is where the chain is. I need like a pair of pliers, right?
Should I shoot enemies or should I just say bullets till the end of the game and then
shoot the boss with 150 handgun rounds? Did I turn the flashlight off? Do I have a flashlight?
Okay. Yeah, I. All right. How many shots does it take? You take way too many shots.
Oh, also there are two streams that I'm trying to do before the year ends. Two big ones,
two of them. Why do I like I needed to pause for that, by the way. Ooh, cutters. I do have some
very sad news. That is a bad reverse announcement. I did tease. I did tease that Mr. Green's had
something in the pipeline and I got a phone call from Mr. Green's and he backed out. Mr. Green's
is backed out. He told me to go fuck myself. That was literally his exact words. He thought it was
he thought it was a dumb project. He said no. So I was like, OK, that stream is no longer currently
in development. I have to say there are two others that currently are. So don't worry over here.
What was it? I don't want to say because if for some reason I actually do go through with it,
then if you really want to help, you could back me up against those things. Are you spawning in
ammo? So I'm on my own. Thanks for the ammo. You spawned one small ammo box, just spawn a huge
detonator or something. You know what I mean? Like, well, spawn a bunch of C4 throughout this
whole place and then let me. What are you talking? Why are you doing this? OK, I need I got the
bolt cutters, which was over here. Right. You can't dodge a battle. Yes, I fucking can. I'm
so sick of seeing people write that. I'll prove it. Don't worry. Oh, this is the same place. So
what is this? What is this thing? There's a gross lumpy thing growing here. Wasted a bullet. Right.
There's got to be some serum I pour on that. Right. OK, I'm looking for the shotgun key.
You can combine or urban chem fluid is a healing potion. Right. And then chem fluid and gunpowder
is bullets. Right. Refresh my memory is one of these big things you want to do. Dodging a battle
axe. It's trapped core. You mean that gross lumpy thing? How am I supposed to break it?
Use your powers. My powers. I literally came here to get rid of them. Only way. OK, fine. But how?
What am I supposed to do? I need an amplifier. Sorry, I'm biting my lip. What's that?
I need to get an amplifier that way. Why is it a battle axe? Why not just a regular axe?
Because that's not what I said. I said a battle axe. I'm very confident in my ability to do
just what I described. OK, so I have to find an amplifier to use my powers on these
plant things to get rid of them. Any ammo? OK, so those are obviously
just scattered around the world here. All right. This is by the way, this is a fully 3D
rendered model. It's standing up. Gunpowder. Nice. If you always want to tell if an enemy is going
to stand up or not, just look for like the aliasing, right? If something in the environment
has aliasing, it's standing up. Yep. Look at the hair. I see the aliasing. Cam fluid. I can use
these things and combine them. There might be more items to combine. I'm going to save it. I don't
really need it for now. All right. The tutorial wants me to do it, so I'll just do it. So where
are we going here? All right. I can go this way or that way. This way. That way. Come on, Gwyn.
That thing's standing up. How are you not dead? I shot you. OK. All right. We're good. Is that
gunpowder? Somebody's going to jump off from behind a curtain. I don't have any bullets. OK.
I need bullets like right now. Oh, do I have a knife or anything? I don't have a knife. Oh,
come on. All right. I just got to run. Did I get what I needed from here? Oh,
cam fluid. Eight bullets. Is this the thing I'm looking for? Is this a stove? What is this?
It's a pizza oven. It looks like the lady from Beauty and the Beast. What's that? That's the
lady at the big bureau. The cabinet. What is the cabinet from Beauty and the Beast? The teapot.
There's no cabinet in Beauty and the Beast? Is there a huge cabinet in Beauty and the Beast?
There is. Yeah. No, there is. The wardrobe. The bureau. OK. Sorry. Whatever. Yeah. This is
the Mandela effect. You're thinking of the straight to VHS sequel. No way I'm waiting
through that. Can I like step on this stuff? It's a ladder here. OK, let's go. The wardrobe. OK.
Yeah, it is. It is. Wait, this character was actually not in the regular movie. I think I'm
combining the teapot and the wardrobe into one character. OK. The wardrobe is in the movie,
but I don't think wardrobe talks. Really? Yes, she does. Am I missing like important stuff
because I'm just looking at off screen and climbing a ladder. I think we're good.
OK, stop turning the flashlight off. Yeah, keep it on. No, stop. Don't keep that flashlight on.
Why would you turn it off in a dark, scary house? OK. Oh, something happened here.
He's oozing. Am I? I shouldn't be. This. The juice box. OK. I have found a means of dramatically
destabilizing parts of the mutamycete network by introducing a disruptive force to block the
auto-inducers they use for communication. For example, the hard-packed cores of mold known as
slerotia begin to break down on a cellular level and disintegrate when this is disrupted.
Slerotia form when the mutamycete develops in new locations, serving as sort of an anchor point or
a foothold. They're often associated with a patch of liquid void for which the mold has spread.
When the auto-inducers of the slerotia are disrupted, it begins to break down. Any liquid
void connected to the slerotia will also disintegrate. The moths are putting pictures of
the wardrobe and they're contemplating if the clothes inside are the organs and guts and shit.
I just looked, I'm sorry, it fucked me up. It would appear that destabilizing the slerotia
sends a signal indicating that the location is no longer viable for mutamycete. Habitation.
triggering a full-scale retreat or why can i just take these okay so there's the power uh
increaser yes all right rw variant flask one actually looks good so what am i supposed to
do that's definitely an alcohol you've seen that on the counter it's called like focus ice vodka
that's what it looks like they make bottles like that that's just probably like 70 dollars too
i feel different somehow use on core try now all right let's see if this works
is it one to one because there's a lot of those things so back to the courtyard that means we
have to go just kind of down and out of here all right is there anything else that i missed
anything that's a oh camphor good thing i stopped please turn on tips trust me focus here destroy
mold cores oh i have like a mana bar does that do okay how many times can i do that
i'll take the bullets there's another one here uh-huh so that stops the flow of lava
okay well what's over here anything i can grab gunpowder good anything else
move your camera up yeah good call i don't like taking up that much screen real estate though
it's gotta be small still right back down to the courtyard am i right that hurt
fuck that hurt oh shit all right i'm okay i think i'm all right i think my knees would have gone
up through my shoulders it would have been like and my knees would be up here you know what i
mean they'd be sticking out here and i would be like oh walking around that'd be so horrible
can't get around it you need to get rid of it so where is it up here there it is
that's an interesting mechanic that's a cool mechanic where is he where all right where
shit i missed way too much i missed two shots i should make some bolts then right all right i
got eight 18 bolts back to the courtyard which is just straight through here
oh hold on i could do that better i just like fucked up my throat what did i just do
oh mrs potts that's the teapot's name right high capacity magazine nice uh what's the teapot's
name is it mrs pott no not mrs puff this is it's like miss mrs teapot right yeah i had it right
it's like none of you guys have even played among us and it shows
it's grabbing at my leg i can't why can i not do this voice today i'm just gonna run
i normally would be fine i think it's unlimited oh run i need to okay well i want to investigate
what's over there stupid motherfucker oh you know it's you know okay you wanted something funny
about streaming a video game when you stream a video game if if you if i miss one shot i sit
there and go fuck i can't miss a shot people are gonna make fun of me do you know what i mean does
that make sense like i missed a shot people are gonna omega l because i missed one bullet right
that's like always up here in the back of my head this is like oops oh you missed one shot
everyone's gonna omega l that looked like i had a hack enabled it was so good
yeah they're gonna omega l me because i missed one shot right okay i'm just trying to clear
this place out because there's definitely things here to get there has to be stuff to collect
right yeah there's something in here i cleared all this out what's here nothing no there's no
way it's a bunch of books really so i really should have just ran i just wasted like 15
bullets for no reason you can uh you can omega l now you can you can i'll bet so omega l bad
right yeah now you can do it now but one chem fluid i spent 10 bullets right all right that's
everything in here is it not one of those here whatever i feel like i could open this thing
can i open this so we're gonna go back to the courtyard and get one of the masks
but not yet what's in here you can't just all right you said so bad for like a full minute now
rendered remember what was that okay look pretty big all i have is a handgun all right i can't do
this yet what was that thing i think this is actually unlimited gunpowder very nice okay oh
there's a mask what's in the back monocular door deep in the basement it needs this mask
somebody will one of you guys remember that open this door yeah this is the dlc
okay i can't do i think i have to put the mask on and look at it right that makes sense to me
in my brain any more of those uh boo things i don't think so all right let's just do it let's
activate the first boss because that's probably what it is here we go first let me chug bronze
mask finally got it yeah okay i need three masks now let's open the door here can i open this
you can't use that here what do i have to put it on well i'm just gonna go back to the
library whatever it was go back to the dining room open the monocular door find three masks
oh equip the extended mag oops okay cool i have an extended mag now i'd rather have health thank
god why is your face crooked i don't know ask god ask god he's the one that drew me and sneezed
when he got to my nose in my right side of my face i don't know ask him okay rest what's wrong
everything of this was supposed to happen why not leave the reason i came here hasn't changed
i need that crystal thank you this person is annoying spawn 10 of them spawn 10 of these oh
here's how one uh thing of fruit punch like give me 50 of those so just literally just drop them
all over the floor go into your g mod your gary's mod tool whatever it and look down and just hit
like cue cue cue cue cue cue cue cue cue cue cue cue cue cue cue cue cue make it a joke
imagine going into g mod and pressing q once to spawn one thing i don't buy it person's evil
whoever it is no i want you to spawn 20 health packs and then i want you to spawn two zombies
and put rocket ships on their backs and then activate them so they fly around the room and
their arms and legs go everywhere and they smash into the walls and shit do it now you have the
capability so do it so bronze oh it worked one of the lord's name are you talking about
one of the lord's name all right so i can get rid of this let's just do that because it's here
i should probably save it where is there a save point writer god i love resident evil games like
this the new resident evil games are so awesome do you know why because i can just press v and
know exactly where i am and exactly where i need to go i know i know exactly what i don't know i'm
not gonna get what i'm right here and the red is like bro you didn't complete this yet it's like
it's perfect like do this something in here that you can do it's red all the blue don't even look
at this don't even pay attention to see this red up here that you can go up there man oh it's i love
it they really it's such great design it's literally not okay so this opens up back where i was
is this where the duke guy is oh my god these things are everywhere i know you think it's fun
to delete my beautiful creatures but you will find out soon enough why that is stupid of you
come on i know you want to do it let's just open this minus two that was not a bad impression but
the dialogue was like an ai writing it each word was after the next one you know what i mean that
was like oh i'm like the substance is not there but the voice kind of is it was i'm just saying
words after other words and the words don't really connect at all i'm but remember i'm being speech
jammed that's very that's very stupid of you you will i always want to hear that back oh this is
where the duke sat remember he was right here there's no way the duke was sitting in that chair
oh christmas lights okay i do not recall a single thing not who i am know how i came to
be i know nothing my memories are as broken as the face i hide behind this mask all that remains
is this feeling this hunger to see others in pain the despair in their eyes the sounds of their
screams who will be my next quarry i have my minion to do my bidding he has many faces but
no brains within those skulls he is my best hound and he will chase those rabbits down
oh here's the impression okay let me hear it i know you think it's fun to delete my beautiful
creatures but you will find out soon enough why that is stupid of you that guy does not have a
plan by the way that guy's over the pa and he's just like fuck oh i don't i don't have a plan
but i gotta make something up to scare this girl because i got no plan at all it's stupid of you
one more time that was bad i know you think it's fun to delete my beautiful creatures that was
fine that first part is okay and then it was like what do i say after this i don't know what should
i say after this but you will find out soon enough why that is stupid of you but you will find out
soon enough those are all filler words because right there i was let me give some acting skills
acting class that was me saying nothing to think of what i should actually say after that and what
i said after that was not good my brain didn't come up with anything why that is so remember
these are all filler words but you will find out soon enough but you will find out soon enough
it's just i didn't even say those words they came out they just started happening like i
didn't even say those why that is and you will find out soon enough why that is you can even
hear it listen listen to this noise voice it's i break a little and you find out why that is
stupid of acting 101 do filler words until you actually come up with a thing you want to say
blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah down the right hallway right like
i don't even know all right let's go oh the salon god i love this game
was there something else in here what else is here that i did oh okay it's because this is here i get
it so hmm i can go the main hall need is something here it's that's the actual mask thing let's just
go to the dining room and then into the courtyard or no up through here let's just go this way
can i go this way i can't all right well we'll go up yeah from here uh i could i could go through
the parlor but i want to check the dining room well down here in this entrance hall i think
let's do the down there okay stay safe are you spawning more stuff for me i'm trying but it's
hard when i'm being hunted by a demented giant and his creepy minions well try this
yeah and then like i can't like 30 combine spawn in this room
i'm just getting swarmed okay so then how do i get i gotta go down here because this is locked
all right yeah all right i know where i'm going up left left yes up left okay left
left you got teleported to gm flatgrass okay then left straight there we go oh thank god for
awesome game design okay did i miss anything here i don't think i missed anything here
i will check this safe here oh thanks for the chem fluid tired i'm fine but what about you weak
here is that why your words are fading yes try not to overdo it here have a pack of cigarettes
what is this okay handgun ammo okay i don't think i can do anything else here i can't so where do i
go from here up through the parlor that sounds like a plan to me so then we go up left right
where's lady um is lady demetrius here right can i i can't go through here shit wait what the
fuck was that is there a typewriter in here okay so wait so where the hell do i go it was all in
there upstairs oh because i took the goo away all right yeah yeah yeah i remember i completely
forgot i did that all right there's a key in the dressing room let's just take a look around can
these be broken you're gonna pause it i have to pee i'm sorry i can't i was oh okay so i was in
here this is the room with uh mrs potts okay so this waiting room is the mrs potts room i'll keep
that and up here pause it i'm not doing anything we're just kind of walking around exploring
handgun ammo i need that shotgun okay down this hall uh all right all right all right that was
you're just doing al pacino come on come on oh oh oh that you're right holy shit that's just
doing al pacino without talking all right it's on the other side of the door no there there
there please my bladder whoa oh what the just hit my head on the fucking ceiling
hey hey hey oh no thanks for the arrow that didn't help at all throw a grenade behind me
me you need to go that way that's the only door in the room dude what are you talking
about you manifest of fucking spikes on the ground those things chase me in here but where is it
i'm not binocular key i'm supposed to be here somewhere it's not in this room though it must
be close by go that way don't go too weak okay he's in this room oh wait behind fireplace
um all right but is there anything else in this room i don't think so okay you can mess with the
actual physical world i just so badly want to hear like in the very far distance a bunch of
like oh it's it's 10 aliens versus 10 combine right oh it's like 10 uh like gordon freeman
scientist people versus like two gordon freemans looks like there are more of these
source engine joke andy we're on that yeah i'm on that today i'm on that so what what did that do
stronger now okay source engine andy focus on enemy okay so is that it i did that
i did that all right focus on and i okay so it freezes them kind of
halt enemy movements oh go go go he's behind me this too sprig of white sage
an herb that restores some you to my sight power i don't want to use this right now
it's making me do it okay is it only one so i have slots now okay be careful open the door
and where am i going from here i'm going right left okay all right all right all right all right
all right what's in here what's in here what's in here take a look take a look what's in here
what's in here what's in here key key key key key key all right somebody else will read this just
screenshot it all right i'll read it all right now we're going to go straight right right right
left right straight right right right left right straight right right oh come on
straight right right right right left right straight right straight oh i forgot how to play
oh come on i can't just kill them i have to kill them
what's happening get off me how do i stop this shoot i can't shoot the gun
what are you doing use the heel why did she just like surf on a surfboard
i was like mm-hmm all right let's go give me all this shit i didn't pick up any of this by the way
i'm not going to even use it i have to i got everything all right go go go go go go go this
time don't be an idiot like this uh-huh you use that replenish okay back to where i just was
now this bullshit i i can't go down that hallway so let me just do this first so let me get this
these items and then get out i need to aggro them first because i'll get stuck you guys need to be
together get together i can't stop swarming around me all right that's it let's go all right so i
can't go i gotta go the other way i can't go this way right it's like this and then can i
go over here no so i can go this way right go move out of the way get out of the way please
okay what are you doing ah okay i'm gonna go right nice am i safe here all right we got animals
painting of a butterfly the picture is fixed in place and can't be removed i need a painting okay
spider painting okay so butterfly spider eats the butterfly frog eats the spider goat eats the frog
uh wolf eats the goat i think that's accurate i think that's what it wants me to do right
goat eats the frog i don't know what do goats eat no actually goats are like vegetarian
or sheep wait do sheep eat frogs i don't somebody's coming in the door okay this
can't be moved either okay so the frog does that say i fear the stealthy one it will surely bind
and suffocate me that's okay so the frog is scared of the spider okay so the butterfly is scared of
the frog because the frog will eat the butterfly the frog is scared of the spider whom is very
stealthy then the sheep is scared of the sheep likes to eat the spider the extra protein um we
fear the snarling beast they will surely terrorist his friends so right here okay frog eats the
butterfly spider eats the frog something eats the spider and then sheep is afraid of the whatever
though okay the predators stand united each staring to oh should have read the instructions
first that's it right there lion eats the sheep frog eats is eaten by that and then uh what eats
the butterfly like the wolf whatever what about the spider's description i didn't read that you're
right no notes they need to stare down their prey so this isn't this accurate
stop trying to come in here and let i think i'm missing a painting i think i have to come back in
here i'm missing a painting okay well that's fine where am i going from here i have the key
okay i can open the monocular door which the monocular door was downstairs right here all
right i gotta go back to the courtyard so let's get down the stairs you look ai generated that's
fine okay so from here i gotta go straight ahead and then to the right save it is he serious right
now what oh another present don't push so hard i can't not push myself this is gonna be ethan
or something right give up no way i can't stop now i've come too far who's she talking to as
careful as i can be all right now spawn me a chem packet no chem packet spawn 35 bullets 35 bullets
okay uh i can't do that yet wait is this that key no it's not it has a stuff on the sides
let's keep moving oh i can do this any more of these only four handgun ammo all right this is
all on the other side that's on the right side well hold on what's in here am i injured why am
i running weird oh it's just a shortcut back to here okay all right that door is over here
can you give a tldr of what the plot is uh yes so uh i sat down at a on a bench and there's some guy
he's like hey you know that people like apparently people don't like make fun of me because they have
like superpowers i was like hey you know there's a way to get rid of those superpowers if you'd go
and it's i have this lab and there's these notes that somebody left that like you can remove those
powers so you just are kind of a you go back to being a regular person you don't have powers
anymore uh so i touched this thing that was supposed to be this thing that gets me into the
memories of um of the mutant my seat or something and that's where we are it is easy to get your
grabby paws okay dude that resident evil 4 remake i think could be like the best game ever made
i really hope it is the resident evil 2 the resident evil 3 remake was was okay it was not
okay it was okay god the resident evil 2 remake is one of the best remakes i've ever played
what's that sound that was game of the year for me when it came out that game was so phenomenal
it was awesome i hope that it's the resident evil team team he hates elden ring no it's gonna i'm
telling you if resident evil 4 is it coming out this year resident evil 4 doesn't need a
remake resident evil 2 did need a remake um yeah it's it's interesting because when i saw the
the gameplay trailer for resident evil 4 i kind of my eyes were kind of squinting i was like
wait this is not the get i thought it was just a remaster i was like oh it's just a fresh coat of
paint but it that the whole thing is redone it's like weird to look at it's like whoa wait a minute
this is not just like a remaster it's they redid the whole entire game it's it's really weird to
look at welcome to the gallery of despair a wondrous display of those few who succeeded
in obtaining at least one mask set your sights upon those chosen few whose final moments of
despair are preserved forever in this gallery witness in this collection of the light of life
from a different perspective so these are all the roses that made it this far so i'm one of these
roses and i got to this i got to this point but they didn't make it but i did and we'll see if
i make it in quotes like i understand the story so far weird okay it's sick bastard it's locked
there i'm gonna get grabbed there's no way any aliasing yep tons of aliasing
jesus oh that one lit arrows the remake does look really good it just looks it's just the
game that i remember loving but it's been like turned up a couple of notches i just hope they
don't change too much i hope it's just like a full-on let's like squash the bugs let's make
it cool looking let's make it really high quality looking there really weren't even any bugs that
game was almost perfect wasn't it although i've just drowned the arrows bite doth sting they
hanged me long ago yet i feel everything but still the worst not last no first the sharpened blade
did ring they hanged me long ago but they hanged me long ago so that's like the i'm the choking one
but still the worst nor last nor first so okay a long ago i choked and then i drowned no okay i
choked then i drowned and the arrows hit me and then okay i choked i drowned the arrows hit me
okay i choked drowned and the arrows hit me what the choking happens first although i've just
drowned all right so i just drowned okay so i'm choking then i got stabbed then the arrows then i
just drowned okay okay yep and i got hit with the arrows and then i just drowned i just drowned
right now yeah other way around apparently choked stabbed arrows no then i just wait what did i
fuck it up yeah this way then i drowned and the arrows hit me yeah okay that's it dude there's
only 16 possible combinations come on okay cool this is going down i don't know if i want to go
down here just yet if i'm very honest i think i want to see if there's any other places i can go
here which there is i can go down to the hall and to the left good super creepy super creepy
okay it's locked it's super creepy so let's go down turn the light on you need to save
i do need to save you're right i'll just make sure i don't die i have a ton of ammo so i'll be fine
i save that now but it might be a dumb thing to say god damn it what's in here don't run
running is the worst thing i could do right now oh jesus christ okay um the silver mask is in the
small room in the back i'm so close all right i need to hide somewhere this dude can't crawl
right i hope not oh shit all right can i do this through the wall did you see me
it's not even fucking scary why why is all this saliva in my mouth what are you doing what's that
you can't throw something right where are you where are you going wait what what did it get
stronger did you get bigger i think he grew in size i have to run by him i think okay we're
gonna go for it haha you despawned stupid pipe bomb oh where'd it go all right pipe bomb
how do i i need to put this on shortcut on three where are you run run oh my god don't freak out
where is he which he runs pretty fast do you have any more pipe bombs i only had one pipe
bomb are you shitting me don't even start with this bullshit oh no get off me get off me get
off me no oh you piece of shit okay we're good he's gonna break through this wall in three two
okay i'm good okay
am i going the right way i missed an item it doesn't matter just go it's probably a fucking
i can't go back i need to go back and then i need to eventually get where i have to go how
do i get out of here guys do the thing get off me get off get up get up get up get up get up
where's this item that i missed i missed an item in here where is it oh he can come through the
fucking back window oh i forgot that was open oh i'm in trouble i'm in trouble it's over the game's
ah god damn it man it's not fair it's not fair
it's not fair it's actually not fair i it's mean it's actually not fair it's not fair i can't
fucking go down here out of my way he's don't you dare body block me just let me out just get
me out of here this is this is dark souls level of collision are you kidding me that's fucking
bullshit what where's the item i missed i don't care i gotta get out of here i wasted so much
shit i just want to die get out you can't come on man it's up on the ground crouch what are you
thinking what are you i'm actually fucking pissed crouch you stupid motherfucker what's happening
right now dude the collision hit window is so huge that guy's staff was blocking the entire
left side of the wall of the doorway i had so much health i'm not using it
well i got the mass so we're good i don't want to die here this is a huge problem because i'm saved
i need to use the heal yeah look at all this horse shit i have to that guy shows up again
and i get one swipe i'm dead this is a jar now uh thank god i got the mask i got it but
just barely this ugly brute turned up don't fight is right i can't fight something like that
here take this i'll take all the help i can get this is pre-recorded no two out of three
cool can you just help a little bit more i'm gonna wait till i get some more stuff all right so now
i can is this open it's unlocked okay leads out to here no items no i think this is two so i'm
going to use yeah it's two you better finish tonight i don't think there's a world where i
don't finish this in the next like hour and 20 minutes i don't need ammo right now so i'm
gonna hold on to it you're gonna spend six hours on a three hour long dlc i i mean unless there's
anything really really more than the third mask and kind of the last bits i don't know we'll see
it's been fun so far rusted scrap you can now craft new items use the craft command in your tab
shotgun shells are gunpowder plus rusted scrap pipe bombs are rusted scrap gunpowder and herbs
all right we're back here this is pre-recorded it's stop talking this is back out to this
weird area all right so i have the second mask all right this is this room which i don't need
to do anymore i got the mask when we had to oh wait what down here i can't move this might as
well all right so i can't open that door so i'm gonna go back to the i gotta go downstairs snake
painting cool all right so where's that painting room can you let us bet say something what there
were a big amount of subs oh yeah i appreciate it i really do thank you so much i really do but i
don't i don't shout out subs anymore four bits uh i don't i don't do it i really appreciate it though
uh i don't shout out bits or subs anymore because i uh i don't do i have to go through this
if i go through this it was 50 subs it's a lot of subs it is i appreciate it but i don't shout out
subs or bits anymore i just don't it was a decision i made a couple years ago and i have to stick to
it i am sorry if you uh want me to address big amounts of subs and bits but if i do that
let's say i start only addressing the ones that are 50 or 100 subs or something like that right
that incentivizes people that oh well that's now he'll incentivize people to give more
because if i don't say the person that's subbed just for one month or whatever
but if you do give 100 subs i will see it and i'll talk about it so that's kind of why and i
honestly i don't want to i don't want to put pressure on the community or myself if i'm on
us too because i really don't want uh the stream like i've talked about years in the past but we'll
bring it up again i don't want you to be essentially incentivized to pay me money for me to like say
something or talk to you i don't like that i never have um i think it's it's kind of healthier if you
just if you decide that you're you like the stream and you want to sub then that's all there is to
it right or if you want to give gifted subs i really appreciate it but i i don't really want
to turn the stream into a way to incentivize oh well if i give 50 subs or 100 subs then he'll
talk he'll he'll he'll bring it up um and let me be very very clear to whoever just gave 50 subs
that's fucking amazing um that's thank you but i you know i don't want to just you know what i'm
saying you get it he doesn't want your money i would rather you buy yourself a fucking nice
new pair of shoes all right i need to i did the thing where i walked in a circle and talked for
two minutes so we gotta go this way how do i even get back there oh there we go like this right
yes no how do i get back to the stairs i have to go all the way around don't i because i can't go
oh no no it's right here because i can't go through here so how do i get i have to go this way
and then no how do i get back over here because this goes to out here oh okay i can unlock this
door cool okay oh let's go three arrow dlc uh pepe laughie the thing's back isn't it
aren't you but you cannot simply do as you please there's only one more mask oh god damn it all
right so i gotta go left and put the mask on okay and then wait can i get the shotgun no i can't
i need where's that painting room where the painting room is upstairs in the gallery okay
let's go put this here go to the painting and then something on that no mask won't fit there
this one here no not the snake painting hang the snake painting here one more it's up and into the
gallery it's probably going to be for the key right yeah what is that i thought something was
on the ceiling okay so the predator what does a snake eat snake eat the frog mouse a snake does
not eat this right i hate that okay it's probably the frog snakes don't eat butterflies so who eats
okay they have to be across from each other this one can't move and this one can't move
so that's accurate right this one's also accurate but somehow it's not because then
this would be yeah okay the spider spider doesn't eat frogs do you make these puzzles to mess with
me hey can you please make it say resident evil village every time something big happens it would
be very atmospheric you make that joke and you say that to me but back in the day the first like
five iterations of this series when you pressed start it did that resident evil three so come on
the tricolor emblem begets glory onto thee that we couldn't read that what is it onto thee the
golden mask shall be granted all right so the shotgun room was i think on the first floor right
okay so first floor in between the main hall i'm gonna save it the big guy's probably gonna
be right here and it's where is it over here right through the where is it wasn't it just
wait i'm confused what just happened do you eat spiders i don't okay so now we go to the dining
room right yeah this dude eats roaches i don't okay shotgun hell yeah nice things easier all right
let me make some bullets for it shotgun ammo all right don't use this only use this when i'm
ending in an emergency i'm gonna make uh hold on to the the fluid i don't need it that's what
two okay two is a shotgun so now that door is up there can i go in the kitchen yet let me try to
go in the kitchen it might be something there that's it i'm making it up i'm not even scared
i went the wrong way okay so can i go in this kitchen the door is locked but can i get in here
no okay just checking stop interrupting the gameplay but i all right i'll activate the
mute streamer when the gameplay is active okay i understand i get it you want to make sure that
you can hear the uh the fuck okay well i'm not going that way because that's kind of dangerous
so we're gonna go this way through the dining room wait is it through that way i have to go
through the courtyard shit okay you know how we do on this channel we sing a note when we want to
make sure we don't scare ourselves i held that for so fucking long ah okay we're this is not it
it's on the bottom floor what oh yeah there are too many people here to for me to do that
there are far too many people here for me to do what i just did how many people have watched it
oh the mask is right here okay something's gonna spawn in this room and it's gonna be really scary
is that last mask looks like it i think i'm too far away okay well obviously i have to do that so
are you kidding me dude no don't step in it don't step it was saved in like all right i have to
kill these guys where's the other thing shit hold on i gotta i have to stand on hurry come on
what is going on right now why did it not fall there's one more dude where i think i have to go
up there must be more cores in here i can't get in here did he just talk yeah he kind of was just
like that's the place i can stand right i don't think so i gotta go on the balcony and look over
yeah so how do i with the balcony i think that's what i have to do is that right i think it no i
don't i have to go on that balcony look down i guess not really am i supposed to see that
there's stairs in the creepy room are there stairs in here uh-huh there are
oh hey where's that where is it oh my god
i'm going on a quick item run okay quick item run just unlocked okay where is it
did i not get the other guy i think i'm good yep let's run through here just because fuck it
let's get some items god okay i'm fine there's still stuff i'm missing but whatever
haha golden mask easy peasy oh what now
all right so does another rose come down to the beginning
it's this one
how am i supposed to tell the difference
i'll help okay so which one is it right lower than barrel left lower than barrel right left lower
than barrel where's the barrel this one lower than barrel what barrel do you guys see a barrel
oh lower than the barrel just do all the ones that are lower than the barrel
got it nice work next one big core broken wall deep shadow big core broken wall deep
shit are you kidding me deep shadow big core where's the help i don't know
oh up here center close center everybody who was like i have no idea
good luck okay i can climb this can't i it has the yellow paint on it you did it thank you
i couldn't have done it without your two ammo packs and two heels i guess this will do
pony i'll take it you need to save the game man i know when i get to one you bet your ass
i'm going to go it's in here did i just say what's in here this is the room i was just in
what's in here okay the room i just came from still stuff down here i don't really want to miss it
all right scrap is that it okay cool i like how it tells you when you're done oh i'm gonna take
this and i've got full ammo i'm ready to get out of here the last mask on and see what all right
there's something in here too ah this is that door that i couldn't open before all right they're
giving me a lot of shotgun ammo i feel like i'm gonna get to a pretty intense part of the game
it looks like that's the case so let's go ahead and do this now so i don't do it later okay i've
got three heels 13 shotgun bullets and i'm gonna hold on to this who are you talking to i'm friend
davis here he's i've been playing for him yeah what's up man so i got i got three heels i have
uh 13 shotgun bullets yeah i'll go back to the other room just to make sure you know i mean who
am i talking to okay this is clear i'm gonna get spawned on in here aren't i all right i'm gonna
save it and i'm gonna go to the salon there's something in there i didn't get almost time
almost time whatever that is that's a clock guy from beauty and the beast yeah i can finally get
rid of these powers but i have to admit i lived with them for so long it's kind of weird to let
them go i feel like this is bullshit i know and this person's like helping me and whoever this
person is is helping me and coaching me because they want my power because it's going to be taken
from me and it's going to be in this little crystal and the person that's coaching me is
the one that's going to benefit from this right that's at least i feel like it's happening um
before i placed that i do want to go straight and left i'm going to go to the salon it looks
like i know i can open the door now there's something in there oh there's that briefcase
in here oh right okay let's open it we got compensator what does this do lemme compensator
increased power okay so just make the pistols better now okay that's helpful compensator
save it again why are you compensating i'm not all right moment is truth uh what's going on what
happens here find out there it is well done little one you've more than earned this reward
almost looks like the real thing doesn't it it's a replica of course nothing that valuable could
ever manifest on this stratum did you really think i'd give away something so precious
i had to bait the trap with something they missed an opportunity for him to go while he was laughing
like like a huge like internal like acid burp they missed the option now comes the real fun
the perfect place for your demise let the show begin what sure thing i forgot how to
fucking play the game what happened we are tonight's entertainment oh shit i gotta run stop
all right i'm gonna use all the shotgun bullets we're gonna do two more shots
oh my god he's gonna grab jesus admire your tenacity futile
ah ah stop get away did i do it look at you so much feistier than those other little guys
this is becoming time to shake things up okay oh that's not good oh please oh my god dude
it's so easily stuffed all right i got it i got it i got it i got it open
go go go go go go go go go go go go go hurry hurry hurry
those insipid fight i've ever seen what do you what you call this a show
oh power juice all right i got a third flask refill the whole thing oh go go go go go go go
hurry up hurry up what's over here get it donna's back okay here we go ready get three no don't
disappear one two i can do that too useless creature such a disappointment
no matter your imminent demise is inevitable
oh run run here come now what where am i now he just did the same improv filter you did
you see the thing about that is your imminent demise is inevitable i don't want to leave
that's funny i'm tired of being a freak i want to have friends i want to live a normal life
about this curse if that purifying crystal can make that happen make me normal then i'm
not going back until i find it okay stubborn yeah so it's dad it's ethan it's ethan all right then
okay explore your surroundings we're here in a deeper dream world it seems uh i need to
i have to move this stuff around here how do i move shit okay like this
oh it's f okay i don't like this set i'm gonna be like right click because it's it's shift to
pick it up and then left click to do and then f to put it down yeah okay that's good all right
that looks okay yeah well i have to tell you very importantly you're imminent to my that's my
favorite so let's get searching there are subtitles for the handwriting there are i know where the
crystal is what's this everything's loaded right oh let's get the shotgun shells do i need can i
make anything i cannot i don't want to make any more handgun bullets i funny will you be my friend
nah sorry nah let's play i swear i've seen these monkeys before but what the hell let's play isn't
this where the doll was in the base game is the doll still alive so we're going down up what's
wrong and i'm oh okay but it's what i say what i say what i say i put it in front of me don't
why are you writing about something seems okay this is weird this is weird looks like a breaker
box for the elevator but it's a lot wait is this the way the big baby thing is i hated this i hated
this from the base game oh god don't tell me it's gonna do the baby noise and the baby thing
hope not today is my first day of school i've always wanted to go i'm gonna give chris a big
hug next time i see him there were so many kids my age it was like i walked into a tv show or
something i was so scared when i had to introduce myself to the class but i was still super duper
excited to be there i'm going to make so many friends i'm gonna try and talk to them tomorrow
okay here to you later i try to be brave and talk to some of the other kids but no one wants to
talk to me schoolwork is super easy it's all stuff i learned with mommy but i guess i shouldn't
answer all the teachers questions the boy behind me said something really mean my hands go icky
with white sweat when i panic it was really bad today the teacher yelled at me for always carrying
my hanky she says i'm not a baby anymore the boys at school keep saying how i'm icky but i take a
bath every night i always wear clean clothes and bring a fresh hanky every day it's because
of the stupid white sweat whenever it starts coming out of my hands i wipe it off right away
but sometimes it won't wipe off so i just hold my hanky really tight chris even told the teacher it
can't get anyone sick but it didn't change anything someone finally talked to me with this
is like this is a month later someone finally talked to me lucy from my class said she always
wanted to be friends we're going to have lunch together tomorrow i can't believe it i'm so happy
i hope lucy's friend catherine will be my friend too this is okay it's uh locked there's a crest
on here i tensed up so bad i put my feet on the legs of my chair why is there a picture of me
i hate big doors that are right in center frame okay i'm i'm checking all this first
why is there's nothing even in here why would there be nothing in there okay well let's see
what happens the crystal's right there but there's no way to get it you don't need that lights off
turn your lights off turn your lights off it's all right it's time i'll turn my lights off
let's see how it looks like no change am i still 60 fps all right hold on i could
my is it better i'll turn this okay why am i so shiny i'm like all right am i in 60 fps yeah
that looks fine lights off we're good scary time i have like a wax face but i promise you
it's just because the light's bright here like my t-zone stuff my stomach has been stitched up it
looks like there's something inside uh more items i don't even have any items but whatever shit all
over the walls what was that i need a pair of scissors okay it's oh two oh two what oh two
okay four four four four oh two uh and then trash four four oh two rusted shut four four oh two
there's one more number where is it not on here right the stuffed locker the picture on the book
shelf the desk covered in stuff there's a desk with stuff on it right locked not in here is it
go back i thought it would be in the room i was just in loud sound go to the corner desk
this has a lot of stuff on it oh okay 66 oh two four 44 i mean i guess whatever oh two six scissors
all right just not even it's a fucking sound effect back out here excuse me thank you what
was in here a key oh it's the crest is it gonna be a big one of these running around now lucy uh
lucy maybe you'll get the crystal once you get the campfire started doll okay that's lucy i bet
you can find all kinds of places to play with this doll okay anything in here all right well lucy
probably goes on with lucy right all right so i'm gonna put you here what's this shit on the other
side say the label is completely illegible illegible i need three more dolls i guess we're
gonna go um over here jimmy's room can't go in here okay so i can't use that so uh it's fine
someone really went all out okay put that in here i look so greasy okay here we go doll okay i think
i need lucy i think yeah i need lucy for this i need lucy fine i'll go get it okay got lucy sprint
punch this heads up head up sprint punch the head off that's what i would do so lucy is definitely
up here right because lucy is holding this yeah and then somebody's pointing at this so you're
pointing over there and then what goes here is another doll that i didn't get shelf somewhere
close please close close the door okay the doll is there a rusted shot no i'll save it though
hmm okay i'm missing a doll stop i knew you i knew you were there this doll can i pick up this doll
no three dolls maybe four fuck is this other doll so you want me to play with dolls oh oh god
damn it okay all right so i have i gotta go get the other two okay so you're cleaning and you're
pointing all right you're cleaning you're pointing and that's what i have to do so i have to go back
and get those is those kem uh-huh pod watchers you can skip oh no no i got it right now i got
the dolls i'm ready i'm good you should skip 30 seconds if you could skip 30 seconds then you're
gonna miss me completing this part of the puzzle right now you don't want to do that don't why
would you skip right now yeah yeah i get it key okay i got the key to jimmy's room i'm gonna pick
these back up all right fuck you all right let's go to jimmy's room all right i think this is like
kind of freaking me out because something's gonna be here right you don't get the key and then have
the mannequin not be standing right here when i turn the corner oh god
not funny fucking dork okay there's the doll this is so creepy still well all right i got all three
now i gotta go in the all right something fucked up is gonna happen right here all right let me do
some stretches because i'm gonna go like hey and it's gonna hurt it's gonna give me acid reflux i
know it okay so the other room i gotta go out here and kind of through the hall oh i knew i
told you this is gonna happen away just pick her up and just drop her down the well no you know
what no fuck that pick her up and just bring her with you just hold her like under your arm
right just carry this around right it can't appear in front of me and get me and scare me what if i
just pick it up and walk around with it okay i need three i need four dolls here i probably
get the next one by it's um in the storage room okay i need to save the game where's there a
safe point it's right here somewhere where's the safe point shit it's far away okay here we go one
two three everybody close your eyes okay okay all right now you are holding this
you are catching the present and you are pointing and that does what all right i got all the dolls
okay it's time uh i i'm i need to save the game all right so if i go out here
i need to bang a left this is left whatever oh my god it better not be the baby all right thank
god it's saved it's gonna break through there i knew it i should what i fucking tell you carry
it with you under your arm like a fucking football god damn it i knew it okay here we go you are doing
this you are um i don't know holding something holding that maybe yeah you're pointing is there
a safe point in here all right well i don't know where the fuck am i supposed to go you're
like i think you're holding sticks and then you're over there all right here we go seriously fuck
you and this is the breaker box key fuck you actually fuck off with this who is it hello hello
probably me from the past or something i think just open the door something just open the door
all right where's the elevator where is it straight okay straight right left right fuck
it's game over if they catch you yeah yep where's the save point give me it before i turn this on
don't look away what oh not one of these don't look away i gotta find the fuses where the fuses
don't look away don't look away all right all right all right where's i need to find a fuse
see if i had just carried you around i could just hold you in front of me like this have you
facing this way and just stare at you while i use my peripheral to do the mission you know what i'm
saying does this count okay get the fuse okay i have to get to the study and then it's in the
room past the study this door is right here right oh my fucking god okay this is fucked up this is
fucked i hate this shit i hate this i hate it more than anything i really hate this kind of shit
all right i just play pick where i'm concerned about me looking the other way like i want to
pick ross i don't know it's behind me i need to use the map all right where's it how do i get out
of here which way do i need to go okay i'm gonna back up this way there's only one okay i thought
there were two okay turn this way is this correct and back up like this oh i thought it was gonna
come behind me okay medicine room okay ah i thought it was coming behind me i think i
is it does it have pathing what kind of pathing does it take okay in here what you what do you
mean it's locked from the other side i'm in a corner what's the stupid map say where's the
kitchen that the game fuck you game you just tried to get me because that was coming from my left
side you just tried to get me to look this way in the game nice try i nice try really okay now
i'm gonna just open okay i'm in a new i'm in a new room i'm in a new room if the door closes
what happens uh okay okay oh uh oh is this am i is still looking in the right direction here
technically i think this is technically looking in the right direction is there any items oh my god
it's fine okay what do i do i have a minute i have a second or two oh fuck you are doing the
i'm walking around behind somebody that's taking a picture at an amusement park and you make direct
eye contact with the lens of the camera i know we've talked about this a few times before but
i always think about this me and holly were at disneyland recently right we went with uh
lebeck and cutie hanging out and i thought of us again how many pictures are you in where you are
just walking by completely in frame in somebody else's picture just like this it's probably do
you think it's more than 5 000 do you think it's more than 5 000 how many pictures are you in
where you're doing that you're doing this okay i have the fuse i just have to get the hell out
of here i think i just have to walk by is there anything in the wardrobe i don't know why who
cares don't look it'll be like a chemical packet um how do i go by uh if what if i touch her oh
man that sucks okay uh-huh uh-huh okay and then i can back up all the way here right should i go
do you grab people what's happening are there two are there actually two now i don't i can't move
what do i do is there are there actually two oh shit oh my god okay i please tell me it's not
two that would be so awful huh huh huh there's two there's two there's two there's two there's two
there's two oh what the who made this game you're a fucking maniac oh my god okay i have to
oh my god stop moving you fuckers
help me help me help me help me help help help help help
where's the other one going where's the other one going i have to start over i have to start over oh
my god i'm sprinting dude give me a chance okay no thank god all right all right all right i'm
just gonna sprint i'm sprinting now Jesus Christ fuck okay oh this hurts now because i know this
too oh this sucks i think i'm just gonna run dude i don't know how do i stop the other one from
coming at me too i think i did it shut up shut up what's the fastest way i can get out of here
i'm thinking just back i'm you gotta keep them both right here i think just go backwards straight
back keep them in frame and then i'm gonna go left that's fine that's fine that's fine that's
fine that's okay that's fine that's fine both of you if there's a third one i'm gonna shit my pants
on camera okay so now i gotta go um if i go it's okay they're all gonna come right here one two
three there you are okay we're fine here oh that you know what i would have been in a lot of trouble
if i didn't um which way do i have to go this way right which way do i have to go oh my god hurry
hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry how come there's not three why is there not three why is there not
three it's only one why is there only excuse me excuse me excuse me excuse me excuse me
excuse me there's a fourth one holy shit this sucks okay i'm sweating this is actually horrible
this is actually terrifying i think i'm just gonna go for it and you know what fuck it right like i'm
just gonna run straight i'm running straight i'm just gonna run this is so bad this is so bad okay
how fast are you like i give a shit just try it and run where's the other one there's a third one
all the air is out of my body hold on now when i turn my uh this one right here i'm thinking
i don't know i think i just run by
oh hi guys guys hi everybody oh
okay i'm almost there okay now
it's easy to be good at the game i made it now it's gonna turn here and
ah
what it's not going
that sucked that actually hurt my whole body that hurt that was painful oh my god
no no more of this i don't want to do
no more of this please give me my shotgun back at least oh no what is going on here no no no no
no no i'm so small the pictures i'm seeing over here are like you you fed a sour candy like a
warhead to somebody holy shit dude what animal this is okay let's let's look i don't know what's
what this is or what i look like but it's very strange dude oh my god i don't look like a real
person i look like i don't look like a real person okay stir used to say that i looked sometimes like
this very specific hearthstone card and now i see it what's the card it's the weird like octopus
looking one from battlegrounds not for yeah it's like a that's like a one one and it turns into
other things in your hand it's like a one one and it turns into something shifter xeris yeah dude
this is literally that card is that card looking at you right here right isn't that weird and i
remember when he first said it i was like dude what are you talking about can i'm can i'm on
put shifter xeris card art into uh the stream over here please thank you
you okay give me one moment let's overlay this a little bit more opacity i think that's
fucked up it's literally the same exact eyes hold on holy shit holy holy shit i can't look at this
anymore this is like scary wow they're actually the same fucking picture okay well let's go let's
play hide and see can you make it all the way here without getting caught oh okay i'm good
guess i should keep heading this way oh wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow
holy shit okay i'm alive um why am i still alive i should be dead no no you didn't hurry
dude what how the fuck are you supposed to get dude how the fuck are you supposed to get away from
that dude don't even this is not gonna work i'm so fucked up hurry up you piece of shit
what does that do for me what does that even do for me what did it open where did that open
i don't know where it opened is there a new path i don't see one back in the hallway i jump down
okay okay okay all right where are they not paying attention all right they see me i'm toast
it's gotta be something i can do what can i do ah whoa i thought there was gonna be an item in
there wait let me see how many are here that's a lot just have to get past them i can't do it
oh my goodness what are you talking about i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i
i win but i win but they're going where do i go where do i go where do i go where do i
I go from here where do I go I don't know where to go yeah
that's don't look under here you're not gonna look under here what did that what
I do that I don't know why I freaked out I thought she's gonna go like we don't
even get to see I thought I thought she was gonna go like this and look under
it's all right I'm right there okay so I gotta go when you turn around so when
you turn I gotta okay I got it I go now no okay right when you cross this I'm
gonna you gotta go that way all right here we go one two and I'm ready and here
we go and it's time this is it here we go one two what I can't run I have to
sneak I don't think I can run running is the problem I just have to sneak and
we're gonna go right now okay we're good what is all this shit what is all this
shit you're not coming through here are you all right all right all right excuse
me oh yeah right it's done I don't know why I have to say it oh oh come on all
right am I safe to go from all who found me who did who did stunning I just tried
to sprint and I was in collision oh no no no okay go okay turn it off yeah
stunning walk walk forward oh man that sucked that was rough
oh god not more of this oh shit oh okay hi hello hi yeah just making my way
through here yeah what dr. look mom that way that doesn't this was me mom wait
that's not mom I thought it was mom I thought it was mom I was like oh mom is
coming didn't work didn't they say like oh and watch out mom is coming didn't
they say that who is this person chasing after me oh you please I'm dead I'm dead
why is this not activating I'm dead it took so long to do that was stupid you
that was dumb I was zoomed in and it just stopped my arm just fell down
I just go and then turn around it's right there okay let's go I finally
found you let's go okay that was rough I can't take much more of this why are
they talking about my dad I never even met him do you resent him I don't know
it's either the first thing about him it's dad here we go
it's gonna be like three paragraphs that show up he died protecting me
sometimes I try to imagine what my life would have been like if he hadn't died
you've taught me to ride a bike helps me with my homework a story every night
but he's been there for me all right now man if we manifest a bike sometimes I
feel lost or afraid I try to imagine what he might have said to me oh it's
made up I have something you should see oh I was trying to walk welcome to the
family you're safe here it feels familiar like I've been here before
great decorations some kind of party is this is the house from the seventh
Ramirez of seven you do decorate the living room get wine put in dining room
Rose's other present in study I mean eighth game eight eight eight eight okay
cool she just cannot get enough of this stuff
what's that voice like in the discord call this must be my parents house that
was when I was a baby okay I bet other things also have my dad's memories just
a quick tip I would have added a little bit of an echo on that like a she she
cannot know like it's it's kind of otherworldly because that just sounded
like yeah like somebody was talking next to me here's a tip she bangs her spoon
every time I play this I wonder if she'll be a musician I wonder if dad
played any instruments yeah I had a shitty filter she's so little hard to
believe one day she'll be old enough to share a bottle of wine with her old man
sound that was a wine drinker take your time look around okay Rose is such a
picky eater I couldn't do it all she ever wants is fruit puree I guess I've
always left food fruit food I can't talk fruit it's the fruit puree it's the two
it's the use the few fruit puree why can I not say it's good to take these out
fruit puree cool what do you want to show me what are you trying to show me
upstairs take a look what is it you're trying to show me oh that's a don't look
upstairs this tune has always been special for our family think I've heard
this before it's pretty that's waiting for it okay nothing in here no I'm not
gonna say it this is my bedroom yeah and of course she's already growing out of
these onesies I can't believe I was ever this tiny she's growing so fast
getting bigger every day this crib is so little I can't believe you were a baby I
can't believe I was a baby at one point oh computer I wonder if she'll look like
me when she grows up I looked so happy oh okay picture of baby on the back key
all right what's on the computer everywhere second is roses half birthday
half a year in the blink of an eye I wanted to capture this moment these
feelings so I wrote something special I may have gotten a bit sappy though I'd
feel embarrassed if anyone stumbles across it so it's safe in the side
board for now the key is behind my favorite photo okay he just typed that
into notepad I guess I don't know why would you write that yeah why would you
write I guess to keep a document of where it is I don't know happy half
birthday Rose my gift to you is a promise I'll always be there for you no
matter what I'll be there every birthday to watch you blow out the candles on
your cake I'll be there to make you breakfast and walk you to school every
day I'll be there when you have a bad dream and sing to you until you fall
back asleep I'll hug you tight when you're troubled or worried and tell you
that everything's gonna be alright you are my precious Rose never forget that
that's sad that's pretty sad hey who's that who's that
guess what isn't here so don't have the purifying crystal of course not it's all
over me oh we have to go deeper
why are you doing this no one loves you and when you're dead
no one will
like oh where's Michael first I gotta make sure I feel up does she only want
you what are you talking about what go on the door what's going on excuse me
what's happening supposed to be happy no that I lost I don't get it
drown first first remember that joke does she only want you okay so I turn it
off here so what talking about go back I mean honestly what ain't this way okay
all right give me give me give me that's discarded no excuse me don't have any
heels do what the fuck get get out of my oh I'm slower than they can run this
sucks oh no I'm dead there we go finally geez oh geez this is bad
all right look look look at them I'm looking right at them I'm staring at
them okay when those dolls popped up I didn't even have a second to attack them
first first walk does she only want you what are you talking about shut up I'm
way stronger than you guaranteed okay here we go just so see it was it happens
quick okay go go go go go go go go go go go don't turn me around hey hey all right
okay I think it might be the Duke we're not safe okay Evelyn's causing this we
still can't get out okay well it's gonna go use your powers on her I don't have
I need some more fluid I can help when she's weak okay well I need fluid I
need some more of this fluid right give me that fluid please okay and there's a
heel use your powers on okay give me that heel I got full health anything else I
can grab oops okay don't panic you got this this is somebody in chat this is
really like supportive viewer all right make sure I didn't miss anything where's
a point this was a point in here where oh my god I almost missed it okay let's
go of course ow this way did I win I didn't win you suck you stink you're
doing it wrong you supposed to say you stink with Otto use it how do I use it
use your power on her how wait for an opening now use your just fucking die oh
my okay go okay I get it to hide get up what excuse me what are you doing
oh that's on that's unlucky that's very unlucky isn't it that's unlucky that's
unlucky as hell that's unlucky that's so unlucky it spawned underneath me it's
spawned under my feet do not ask me to change the difficulty how dare you watch
out for her wind blasts this way
whoa that's bad watch your step yeah you think so what this is stupid this is
stupid okay you know you're on like a five second stream delay dad now I'm just
annoyed all right whatever come on then over here okay now just wait because now
she spawns over here and does like a big omega bomb watch your step okay yeah
okay what oh shit no do I I'm sick of this fucking goose shit I'm sick of this
I'll do it again
no you're worthless what you have me okay over here keep focusing I'll help all right we're good
okay
who's this guy who's that guy who is that guy don't give up rose find that crystal oh
okay it's michael no it's he isn't ethan right michael are you there it's ethan from resident
eight michael michael ethan ethan michael he saved me but he didn't make it voice my dad's voice
is my dad don't give up rose find that crystal wesker I stole that from chat because of him
I can keep going I have to find that crystal this is ethan yeah it's ethan I'm on my own
but I have to keep going all right where's the duke all right there's got to be an explanation
as to why the duke was doing that the duke is a good guy everybody loves the duke why would you
why you're not gonna make the duke bad evil that's not cool what's all this doing out here
do I have my weapons back oh I do okay where the hell am is this place actually what the hell is
going on here isn't this the thing we we blew up in the eighth game versus here and they detonate
it right they drop the orbital strike on it what is that I can sense something from over there
I thought dad was gone I thought I didn't have dad anymore wait that's not that's me okay oops
okay that was a memory dream ghost oh he's fucked up I might as well craft some items
because I'm not gonna have a chance I think unless I could find an herb it's like in the castle I
know it's been four and a half hours but what's the heal button q okay it's not q is it t thanks
for the help oh I can guard okay it's that button right that's what I made it okay okay
is it no a listing check yep coming from that noise is so off-putting it really is
good I don't use all my handgun ammo what does that do can I open okay down I need to find that
how do I get is there a safe way to get down okay oh wait I have I'm looking wait I have
I got 1.2 billion views on tiktok is that a real number oh excuse me 1.2 billion views on
germa on tiktok huh that's more than every channel I have combined like times 10
and where I do what I don't know why am I not on that why am I not getting any of that
why am I not getting any of that what oh that's what are you kidding me it was seen at some point
during my experiments with consciousness an intruder made herself at home in my realm
this intruder was none other than the failure Evelyn who's been running about enacting her
own pitiful agenda which has led to a slight disruption in my own plans had Evelyn not
interfered Rosemary Winters would have been on the verge of despair dispossessed of her will
to live and her view to my side powers instead a new passion burns within her I shall have to
extinguish the duke talking that was a lot of bullets oh yeah it's final battle time I had
intended to duplicate Rosemary Winters with the hope that a perfect replica might serve as a
suitable vessel however the results were less than ideal it would seem that some sort of
interference is preventing me from creating a suitable replica instead I have succeeded in
making what is essentially a living doll it resembles the real thing yes but has no power
such a pathetic hus could never prove suitable as a vessel I will continue my efforts in hope of
discerning the source of this interference several hypotheses have come to mind thus far
the fact that rose herself is still alive some other actor within this realm me a flaw in my
methods of production none of these seem especially likely to be the sole reason or any of them easy
problems to solve perhaps my best hope is to somehow bring rose into this realm 225 million
views on another version of germa on tick tock do I have like two billion fucking views what
how many views do I have on twitch I don't think I have 100 million 50 million maybe
on YouTube I have like three 400 million a billion I'm shy I'm so confused right I'm shocked
flexing no guys I start these are not my accounts these are not my accounts I'm not I mean flex
this is not a flex hey two billion don't look at my fucking armpits get on tick tock I'm not
getting on tick tock I'm already there I have two billion views okay further experiments with these
rose copies as I've taken to calling these husks have you looked another interesting wrinkle to
pursue somebody uploaded all of the dollhouse across like 200 parts as like all right when
subjected to situations evoking extreme terror they actually begin to express some semblance
of roses abilities this warrants more research and I think that by first creation the masked duke
is just the one to wait hold on a minute this warrants more research and I think
that my first creation the masked duke is just the one to perform the stress test
so this is not the real duke watching me the entire time so the that's this is not duke this
is a masked duke okay we already saw that no he didn't did we okay all right I'm glad that
that's not the real duke the mega my seat absorbs the memories of all life within its reach but
there are laws which govern this world within it seems worthwhile to catalog them as they become
apparent the memories that comprise this realm do not strictly reflect reality only those who
are attuned to the meta my seat in life retain control of their faculties here in this realm
it aligns with my understanding of the mega my seat has revealed to me and its visions before
my death yes my death my physical body is gone absorbed into the mega my seat and yet I do not
despair this fate has granted me fascinating insights all those years I strived have continued
to strive they're not for nothing the memories the consciousness understanding and knowledge I
accumulated in life have transferred here to the mega my seat where it serves as a source of power
within this realm if I can harness this power I believe I can use it to affect the thoughts and
memories of others of course it's hardly a perfect arrangement with so many minds and memories
gathered here finding and retrieving a single person from amidst the rabble has proven an
immense challenge her memories are here yes but dissolute perhaps what is needed is the right
vessel into which to hold her and of course I know of the perfect vessel the only real candidate in
all my years of searching rosemary winters this is the guy we saw on the bench in the beginning
is this like this is his project or something I don't even know who that guy was okay so cool I
guess we know what we're doing now we're gonna pick up all this stuff there's a lot of ammo
let's take a quick look over here no one deeper you're losing viewers dude do a joke
oh fuck all right I'll do something wicked funny there's that feeling again it's so strong it must
be the crystal that pole I've been feeling is close but I just can't go any further I thought
I made it when I saw that blue light but no not quite only I've been braver faster stronger so
close I was so close I'm almost there it's your birthday today cake and ice cream is on its way
cool it's through here how would you even know that you you actually would not know that okay
here we go here's the here's the open book to the exact page presented on what happened in the story
here we go black god which lives in us in which we live create for us a new world as befits your
will your dark consciousness holds for us a second chance graciously offered and joyously
accepted you drink the blood of the lost lamb as it falls upon your darkened earth not to destroy
but to preserve and once again deliver it onto life what a twist what an ad what a twist I can't
believe it was Cthulhu the whole time I'm so sarcastic this one's the real deal feel it here
it is what do you think that smells like I think it smells like paint like that smells like a fresh
thing of paint it just probably smells like paint thinner or something is this what normal feels like
uh-oh here it is the person behind it all Evelyn who is this again rose Miranda I've waited so long
who are you my name is Miranda oh maybe she won't see it far too powerful for me to subdue
directly fully I knew where the crystal was I had to lure you into this realm I've been searching
you might willingly I know you know where it is no but case said did he or did I was an illusion
illusion very convincing wouldn't you say what are you hiding we're just doing references from
other movies game become the vessel for my evil shit he's not in frame no I wanted to get a picture
of him oh come on let's cut it off even more okay oh wait come on
wait what dude don't waste your bullets on a fucking shitty enemy that was a
shotgun bullet dad don't do what are you out of your mind
stop using shotgun bullets on the default enemies we're good we're good we're fine fine fine fine
why didn't you tell me who you really were why'd you let me call you Michael
I didn't want to complicate things I just needed you safe she just said hey it's me dad like follow
me trust me it's dad and like prove it by saying like what do you mean and I'm sorry I left you
but I had to find a way out I'm really sorry I just need you to have a twist at the end of
the game and I did it's just ahead I had to pretend to be somebody else so your expectations
could have been subverted for a minute dad help fuck I missed it it's all right
I can't wait to we're gonna see Ethan's face yeah you know we don't ever see Ethan's face
she wouldn't have believed him why are you grabbing me on the shoulder
Rose now's your chance go live a normal life make friends no one will ever call you a freak
but Rose just go that was not gonna work I love you but I need to know that you're safe
so please just get out of here come on it's Duke where's the Duke I need the Duke I think it was
made out of fucking quartz I don't care that was a fake item you're an idiot you thought you were
coming down here to get your powers I'll stop working on don't worry dad I've got this you
think your powers will allow you to stand against me in the heart of my domain foolish and t a and
you were on my this is oh how do I
why do you you cannot strike me
oh you were absorbed projectile what what would be the
moment you can say you are in control let's go what is this
there will be wailing and see you collect the projectile all right here we go
you're gonna do a thing wait what are you doing there's nothing I didn't catch that
offer yourself unto me how did I not catch that
it took so much to lure you're incredible what's going on reload reload reload
my dear it's your plan
ah all right stop you now become you bitch I cultivated this world within the mega my seat
to resurrect my sweet dog no matter how many vessels I created none had the power to regenerate
all right here it comes that is why it must be you are the only one who can bring her back
grab it what are you talking about I just grabbed it I will see this through you're doing a lot of
talking
uh-oh your time oops
strike me by my side did I not hit oh my
I have no more excuse what happened to my powers I don't I don't have any more powers
dude heading holding okay I would like a computer expert to tell me how to do this
how do you hold d with your index finger and press t to dodge I need a computer expert
dodging right I need to hold d and then press t d with thumb and then t with index excuse me
I'm changing that I'm not using a controller what's this t
it didn't even fucking work this it's t man I've been pressing t this whole time
I thought it was a double whatever I don't I thought it was a double
stop it this will all soon I forgot it's all right fuck you I have tons of heals I have too
many deals I'm fine why do you why suffer needs shut up let's see this
what did I do I just I fucking hate this fight there's five hours and you introduce a dodge
into the end sequence of the game they introduce a dodge and parry mechanic into the final fight of
the video game there will be wailing and gnashing don't resist okay do the thing again so I can
all right attack there is nothing you are
do you still not see there is no happy ending wicked witch at the end of her reign
uh-huh what is going on nothing changes your suffering will never end
can you stop please you just won't give up you really are
so that stubborn life that shines inside makes you the perfect best
shoot something at me you will fall just there it is how dare must that ammo
oh oops heel okay your time is all right now do it do it do it do it
be by my side I hate this game this game's a two offer yourself unto me
rich little girl I shall finish this oh god damn it there is no victory
and how was I supposed to know to do there these games are two this is games a literal two
dad it's not a two I'm just frustrated at how I can't dodge this shit I hope we get to see his
face because that's the whole thing it's like oh you you don't can't see Ethan's face please come
on zoom in right in his face I love you Rose come on return and yield your strength
come here so much power you truly would have been the perfect vessel for my
I'm not a goddamn vessel not some stupid copy I mean Rose and you're done
so we won all right Ethan show the face imagine if he's like oh my god that's pretty
my mouth is too slippery even though I wasn't there with you always watched over you I'm so
sorry I couldn't protect you all you've ever done is protect me not this time you lost your chance
I'm so sorry oh it was my choice and I don't regret it one bit
if I left you then we never would have had this chance he's just a guy face to face
no I don't think they're gonna do it so it's okay I'm so proud of you they want to do it so bad
I'm very proud of you you know they want to do it so bad the arm's gonna come down
the arm directly in the way oh hey they did stay true they they were like we're not showing his
face they didn't make that up they were they stayed true to their word we're not gonna show it I'm
back it's like 300 years have passed the guy that brought her here is just a skeleton in the corner
okay that was fun yeah it was do you think the little boy will be able to touch the moon
nobody can touch the moon it's too far away wait what if he has a rocket ship
okay then you can touch your butt it'd be very very cool you were being silly I don't think the
two out of ten mad mad no just that what for that one 10 second period it was a two out of ten
hey dad everything else was like a it was solid it was fun I think it was worth playing it was
okay sorry I missed I'll explain I have a lot of tests coming up you know how it is
I played some really shit DLC before this was this was pretty good
duty calls that second part with the the dolls where else today of all days wait we have a
situation you're needed Evelyn don't you ever call me that again it's just a joke this is the end of
the first end of the game I can show you things even Chris doesn't know I can do so this cut
scene takes place stand down I want you to keep it together Rose you're a lot like him you know
I know wasn't there like a weird ending here where they had there was somebody standing here
we're gonna see who it is I remember asking that same question at the end of the base game I enjoyed
that that was fun okay that one segment where I was having trouble with the understanding the
parry I didn't get it I thought it was it just suck I thought it was an absorb I didn't think
it was a parry that was two out of ten everything else was solid the horror parts were awesome
that was scary shit man I think it was a solid buy here this is a solid buy and there's still
more to see because I want to do the other stuff I want to look at the other stuff there's like a
whole other thing to do you can play as Lady Demetrius and um what's the other guy the
mechanical guy I want to try it I thought that was very I enjoyed that that whole second segment
was terrifying I actually honestly I really liked eight I did like eight I thought it was really
good as a complete picture here as the whole thing's done at this point right I actually
enjoyed eight what do you rate it I don't know I don't have it's a DLC how do you rate a DLC
it's like to me DLC is either buy it or don't I it's not an you know what I mean it's like an
edition the Resident Evil 8 is like an 8.5 8.4 for me at least what all right let's what did I rate
it like a year ago when I played it I gave it a rating I think eight's better than seven you gave
it a seven I think it was like it was a high seven I think low eight eight point two honestly it's
hard to say if I prefer seven or eight because I played eight more recently and it's been a one
guys something I think a lot of people might not know it's hard for me to give a good scoring
system here considering I played the entire game of Resident Evil 7 in VR I played that on the PS
VR at launch because it was exclusive and it was a I was like holy shit I'm gonna do that I don't
know why I did that that was so I should not have done that but I did the entire game from start to
finish in VR so I don't know maybe I'll have it I would have a different opinion if I played it
normally I don't know I'm feeling really bad after some of those streams it was funny all right we're
gonna get a post credits thing or should I just skip it just let us know now there's no after
credits thing hey wow this is great this is awesome because this is exactly what I told you was going
to happen exactly what I told you somebody said dude it's a three and a half hour experience if
you just play it three and a half hours right so 340 I've been streaming for five hours that is one
hour and 20 minutes of nonsense that's one hour and 20 minutes of me just talking and just like
pausing and talking and saying weird shit I told you this is gonna happen okay cool you've completed
the following challenge completion points can be used to purchase items in the extra content shop
oh did I just buy something I hope I just didn't buy something you mean I could have had this on
the whole did I have this the whole time or did I just unlock this what I feel like I had that
already okay so what let me see there's an extra content shop oh okay the mercenaries additional
orders this is the other thing I want to see but wait okay I got it special weapon 80,000 how many
do I only have 32,000 I thought I just had way more than that well you can play as the baby oh no
I was like how did they handle this okay um do I actually have to unlock them or are they just in
the game they're probably just in the game okay additional orders all right Ethan Chris oh there's
two other characters all right I'm gonna try it I'll go with Ethan how does this how do I play this
there he is that's the duke okay the mercenaries first purchase any equipment weapons you need
from the shop then you go out to the field you need to defeat as many enemies as possible
in the time limit get a good rhythm going and build up combos okay the goal will appear touch
the goal to finish move on to the next area okay this thing's pretty explanatory welcome
Ethan I have 20,000 this is all an investment Ethan bye um okay you're going to be so bad at
this I I just want to unlock the I don't think I can upgrade anything oh I can shit all right
well should I buy securing goods is more important than anything I buy the shotgun immediately my
friend I hope this one makes itself useful I'm gonna buy the shotgun and I'm gonna upgrade the
shotgun's capacity what an idiot okay now I'm gonna buy shotgun ammo I can't choose wisely
your luck till next we meet oh I got a lot okay all right let's I'm gonna just go make some um
let's go get an a rank in a normal stage you got it let's go what is this
I think that's pretty good whoa shotgun ammo load it load it load it load the shotgun
the goal has spawned wait what's this oh where's the goal where's it cool get an a rank or above in
all normal stages you need to get an s rank or above oh my god am I gonna be able to even do that
if it's just looking window shop away this simple modification can be done in just a moment
this is all an investment even till next we meet more kills and more points all right
okay let's just round everybody up then oh my god why is it so fucking loud it's
louder 10 times louder than the base game
where are they stop it stop it whatever use yep all right where are they where's where's the
enemies can an enemy spawn where where is an enemy where the fuck are the enemies this guy sucks
pick the gun gun gun man I pressed it like three times
easy this stage sucks ass fuck this stage worse stage in the game that stage was awful
like they're up here they're down here they're down here they're up there they're up there
they're up there oh fuck this area okay I was just thinking of ways to pass the time
choose wisely your life may depend on it okay more shotgun I'm doing rate of fire
and reload it's fine all finished and then rate of fire this thing is so slow
all right now that's better let's go thank you for your speed increased speed increase
why was this gun where did you whoa open it open it open it open it open it open it
where's bad guy where's bad guy bad guy
me bad guys where we at where we at where we at am I
fuck I don't know I don't know where you are you're all right it's all right it's all right
all right let's go oh um hey yeah that was pretty good let's go oh no it's getting fun
how do I know what I got for scores on them A I need to get an A in every single one of these
no in the normal stages oh okay so wait wait wait wait go back so I'm imagining that these are
probably only a few of these are normal stages you need A in all and S on the last one okay
let's see what I can do here I think I'm gonna go with um hmm all right this is I'm going for
a weird play here I'm gonna try to I'm not gonna spend any money I'm gonna buy the SMG
I'm skilled at all sorts maybe let's just do this for now this might be dumb but I'm gonna do it
thank you for your patronage oh oh my god I don't remember these guys how do I fight these guys
I don't remember how to fight these guys I think they're thinking they're back right
I don't remember I think it's on their back um what do you get stuck in the wall or
I don't know how do you kill these guys I need explosives
hey oh my god I just walked right into his drill I'm stuck against the wall
I need a key to get in here or something oh my god bullshit bullshit it's one more where's he
where's the last one ah fuck it I don't know where's the last one whatever I don't think I'm
gonna get A if I don't get at least an A on this then I quit I didn't really put time into this
mode but it's fun this is all an investment this is just a moment all right let's go oh it's so loud
fucking clean if I say where you at where are they oh my god they're right there
oh my ears that's a 40 hit combo dude I didn't stop once that was the cleanest gameplay version
that was clean that's gonna carry this whole playthrough I like this this one I think was
going one gun Andy I think right why was that that was so fast I'll do one gun Andy okay here we go
get that I don't even know I couldn't even read it dude I cracked out on that one I really did
it's too big the area is too big this area is too big I don't know the route it's all right I went
to the end first shit it's okay uh yeah I kind of just locked in just shooting and stuff where do I
go oh upstairs probably right how did I not go up that kid go up the stairs whatever ah whatever
I don't remember where to go no I went this way already it's too big there's three people
left ah this way shit that door what do you mean the pit stains are on your shoulders which door
all right I'm gonna stop moving what door I actually don't know I'm confused from where I'm
standing right now this one that I'm looking at right now and then go up forward then right
appreciate it oh my god this guy's got a demon head two more let's get out three minutes to spare
all right hopefully I did okay hopefully did all right you got to find pipe bombs a single weapon
like a shotgun and sell the all the others and then and the ammo for them really oh that's right
I have shotgun ammo okay so just sell all the shotgun ammo holy shit that's a lot oh my god
there's a hundred oh I could just went backwards holy shit okay how I say yes this should be oh
I probably shouldn't have sold everything oh I sold it literally every single thing
all right we'll just snipe a rifle can dodge that easily oh hey what's that oh my god you're
next to me oh my god oh hey boy okay come on come on come on come on come on come on come on come on
I did that was an I did that that was funny it was acting I swear to god I was acting
I swear to god I was acting I mean it the first part wasn't acting but the second part was
all right almost there excuse me oh my god oh you're flying away oh that's not good I don't
think I can kill this I don't think I can kill this oh yes I have to complete it I think I'm
not gonna get them all that's okay um how do I get the hell out of here how do I get how do I
get out of here I don't remember there's only one more it's just the one guy how do I get out of
here grab the mine okay okay okay okay okay okay where is he oh shit okay get him on the stairs
mine get out okay doors go outside on the second floor somebody said is that true
do the money did I get the money I got everything let's go go go go go second floor
no no no no no first floor first floor go go go go go let's go help help me actually help me I
don't know go towards the icon okay good I got I got it this is fun I like this mode a lot with
six minutes left not optimal but probably an A I don't care I wonder give me an A yes very cool
so now you're saying if I get an A here then I can play as the factory guy see rewards it's
probably down here right okay unlock get an A rank or above in all normal stages what classifies
a normal stage this is not pre-recorded stream I'm just gonna stay with Ethan what I know this
time I think I'm going shotgun Andy yeah I'm going shotgun Andy here this one I'm going for
this one choose why all right sell everything else may depend on it we want ammo capacity power
rate of fire okay that's good I'll buy a couple of heels or maybe should yeah pipe on all right
shotgun time see if I can do this you bought sniper rifle ammo I should have saved that that
was dumb are they standing up or what I don't know okay cool there we're gaming right now
hurry up running out of time here shotgun yep I lost the combo fuck oh what happens
if I run out of bullets uh-oh oh I did it okay I don't think I can do this anymore I think I gotta
get out of here I don't know I don't think so man no no I gotta leave it sucks but I have to leave
oh that's not cool maybe I probably won't get an A then that's bad oh well worth a try how do I
I can't get in here um why can I not open this little pipe bomb no it won't work is the subscriber
banner in your about section supposed to lead to a Gotham Knights page no it's not it's not actually
thank you for bringing that to my attention all right I'm kind of sweaty and I think that's
probably it for tonight this was fun plus I'm lost in the concrete level I'm lost in the concrete
level I give up I give up yeah I'll see you tomorrow thanks for joining me uh I thought I
kind of really got into this I didn't think I was gonna flame this for six hours but tomorrow
we're gonna be doing Phasmophobia with Vinnie and friends and then after that
I'm gonna play at dead of night and if I beat that then we'll do another scary game
should be fun I'm gonna quit that was cool though I like that maybe I'll play that on my own just
mess around is there anything else to see is that the FMV game I don't know it's like you're running
around a hotel or something third person for the main campaign yeah that's cool I feel like you
can play through the entire game in third person to be a different game and then on Halloween yeah
Halloween I'm doing uh the cooking show with critical with Charlie that should be fun should
be fun the internet held up today which is kind of strange we're usually pretty used to it somewhere
around like an hour ago dying so I'm just gonna pull my streams back an hour or two to try to
avoid it I am so sweaty Jesus the idea is I'm trying to avoid being live between eight and ten
so until I can get it fixed so I reliably know it's not gonna happen because it's just so weird
very strange but yeah I will see you guys tomorrow I'll see you guys very soon a couple more scary
games tomorrow what time tomorrow 2 p.m pacific tomorrow and then what time on Halloween that's
a good question I think they usually I think Charlie usually is around noon right I'm pretty
sure it's probably gonna be around noon on Halloween that will be live 2 p.m tomorrow what about stay
out of the house I'll play that tomorrow we'll do a bunch of we'll do at least two or three horror
games tomorrow because phasmophobia with Vinnie is not I don't think it's gonna be very long
I think we're only gonna do it for an hour or so we're just gonna get it and mess around for
like an hour maybe two so there'll be plenty of time to do other stuff you have you've had an
MRI before what was it like I've got one on Monday um it's it's really not a big deal it's you it's
all good it just makes a lot of noise they give you usually give you protection for your ears
and as long as you just it's kind of just while you're there while you're in there the way that I
have done MRIs before is I just kind of let the machine make a beat and then it's not like scary
anymore it's not weird anymore um because it goes like this it goes like
so while it's doing that it's just like
like
I just make it a music I make it a song and depending if you're doing it with or without
contrast um they give you a depends what it is but sometimes they give you an IV
but IVs are easy that's the honestly if you're doing it with contrast the IV is the only part
that's like oh wow they like you're doing an IV if you're not doing contrast then it's not a big
deal you'd be good I think you scared them with that voice uh thanks for watching though
well apparently I'm back hey yeah you thought I was over it is sorry press the wrong button
my voice sucks yeah but good luck you'll be good it's not so bad I'll see you tomorrow
2 p.m pacific take care of yourselves good night see you tomorrow