Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with Pit Fighter.
This is gonna be one of those games that's old, it's in that same category of, like, the Pac-Man games I played,
and the other weird, like, what-the-hell-is-this-game type of series.
And I can't, I can't even explain this game. It's atrocious, it's so stupid, it's a fighting game.
It's supposed to be, in quotes, a fighting game, but it's one of the worst games, like, ever made.
And you're gonna see why very shortly. I hope you guys enjoy it, live commentary's gonna kick in right now.
Just wanna do a brief introduction to it, and I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody, even though I think I say that again in the end of the video.
But anyways, we'll say it twice, take care, everybody, see you soon, bye!
Okay, so here we go. We have the choice of being Buzz, the ex-pro wrestler, he's 6'2", 226.
Bonnie Slim, headbutt, pile driver, he's got a couple of moves there.
Ty, the kickboxing champion, 5'11", weighed 186 pounds, agility-based fighter, spin kick, flying kick, and roundhouse kick.
Or we can be Kato, the third-degree black belt from the five-foot nine-
You know, none of this matters, none of this- there's only three people you can choose from.
It doesn't matter who you pick. You could pick any of these guys, and the exact same thing's gonna happen. You ready?
You see, the best part about this game is it has some of the most beautifully rendered animations I've ever seen in my life.
Take a look at how, like, the one or two sprites that were used to create the fantastic punching and kicking-
What? I've never done that before! What the hell was that? I just, like, pancaked him.
I'm gonna lose. It's very simple, there's, like, two buttons to this game. There's a punch, and there's a kick.
And apparently there's a jump, yeah, there is. That's just beautiful-looking, by the way.
Come here, you fat fuck- NO! Look, your health's in the top left. I gotta beat this guy! I got five, he's got five.
It's over, I lost. That was the game, by the way.
Another really stupid thing that you're probably going to realize is each one of these guys has the same stupid sound.
When you pick anyone- I just picked this guy. Ready, listen to this.
Look at how much the crowd just looks like utter shit, by the way.
I don't remember any crowd being, like, sepia tone in my life.
Alright, hold on, I might be able to pull this out. I might be able to pull this through.
Ooh, did you see that little spin kick? This is, like, the tutorial.
Oh, jam it. Jam it. Damn it! I got it! I got it!
Alright, that's the first time I've, like, ever beat that guy, so that's a good thing.
Gradually- why am I on a forklift? Alright, match two, you guys ready? Match two.
Look at my health! Why did I start with that little health?
I go-
Okay, I have 65 health. I'm gonna start the next fight with 65 health.
That's- that's fucking bullshit. That is absolute, complete, utter crap.
Look at- this guy has 260 health. This game is not possible to complete.
You can't complete this! How would you ever be able to do this?
It doesn't make any sense. It doesn't- it doesn't make any sense why that would ever be a thing.
Every fighting game I've ever played in my whole life, this is Street Fighter 1, this is Clay Fighter,
that's, like, a staple of all fighters. Why would you ever remove that? Why would you ever not do that?
Everybody starts with the same health when there's a new round.
Why would you remove that from this game? That's what I don't get. I don't understand that.
This game is so fucking stupid.
I just wanna- I wanna get past the first two guys. Is that so much to ask?
Who made this game? I don't even know who made this game.
All I remember is playing it for Super Nintendo and the arcade. This was in the arcades.
How much money do you think people wasted on this game in the arcade?
You probably had to throw, like, 30 bucks in the machine to be able to go past the first two guys.
It doesn't matter what you do. It really doesn't.
The guy with the cheap Halloween costume on is gonna beat you every time.
Unless you get lucky and you get him, like, in, like, a stun lock, you'll never beat this guy.
I wonder if there are, like, actual strategies. Did they make, like, a strategy guide for this game?
I wonder what the hell is in, like, the- you open it up and what does it say?
Press all buttons! That's- oh, yeah, that thing, and then the book closes.
Copyright 1991 THQ incorporated. Toy Headquarters.
What the hell- what does that mean? Toy Headquarters? Toy- like, toys?
I don't have any idea what that's supposed to mean.
What- welcome- oh, yeah, this game is made by THQ. The Toy Headquarters.
This is where Santa gets all his, like, fucking toys for Christmas.
I'm- it's over. I'm dead.
I'm using the controller, too. Can I, like, hack? Can I cheat to win?
I wonder if I can use, like, cheats.
What's, like, the code I have to put in? Like, up, up, down, down, B, B, B, T, T, T, T, T, Y, Y, T, T.
T? There's never been a controller with a T on it.
This is the type of game that you really- I really can't even imagine how this was even developed.
This game is so broken and so awful, I don't even know how this game was even developed.
What did they use? Did they use, like, a cereal box and a pen and paper to make this game?
Like, honest to God. Honest to God, how did they make this game?
They had some guy, like, take a couple pictures with his shirt off,
and then they put, like, a couple Halloween costumes on,
and then some guy took a fucking cereal box and started, like, drawing on it,
and then they, like, jammed it in a computer and, like, mashed on Enter until the game was, like, until, like, this popped out.
They stuffed it in the CD drive.
The elbow's working. The elbow!
Oh my God, did I just find, like, the strategy?
Okay, I got 144 health.
Okay, come on. I gotta beat the second guy with the elbow strat.
Yeah, you made it. Let's go. I don't care.
Elbow strat. Elbow strat's gonna kick this guy's ass.
Yes. Yes! Yes!
You can't fuck with the elbow strat.
It's working. I'm gonna beat this guy. I'm gonna beat this guy. I'm gonna beat this guy.
Oh, no. Come on. Come on.
Yes! Yes! I did it.
That's the second guy. That's the second guy.
Alright. 89 health. Bring it on.
Grudge match? What? What?
What?
Alright, well, apparently I hit you more times than you hit me.
I've no... What the hell is this?
Alright, here we go. Let's go, man.
What? It's something like Lady.
Just stick to the elbow strat. That's the only thing that matters.
As long as you do the elbow strat with the kickboxer, you're gonna win.
Or you're gonna get stun-locked and, like, instantly... It's over. I lost.
Nah, it's over.
If you think I'm gonna start over again and do this all again,
get out of your mind.
And what's with the money?
What is with the money in the top left? I don't understand. Like, I have $12,000.
There's no upgrade system. There's no... There's nothing. It's just, like, points.
That's points, and they put a dollar symbol behind it.
Whatever. This is... I'm done.
I'm done playing this game.
That's Pit Fighter, guys.
One of the dumbest, worst games I've ever played in my life.
But I'll see you guys all next time. Thanks so much for watching.
Take care, everybody. See you all soon.