What's up, Doc? What's up, Doc?
I don't think a motorcycle can go through these tiny holes.
It's duck season.
Hey, Jeremiah, I think we're playing a zombie game and I need you to cooperate.
I have so much of this in my mouth. I have to spit this out.
What's up, Doc?
Dude, come on. I'm going to break your arms with this brick.
Shit, E. Press E.
Come on.
One hand plays the game, the other hand pretends to be Bugs Bunny.
Get in this taxi.
Yeah, scoop me up in the taxi.
That sounds like a good scooper.
No, put the thing down. Put it down. Put the thing down. Put the thing down.
What the fuck?
I'm not going to make it, man.
Holy shit.
Okay, dude, seriously.
What's happening?
Let me get a car. Stop. Stop driving.
I'm trying to get out of here. We have to go.
I know, but I want...
There we go. Okay, don't do anything.
All right, now drive.
Okay, now lift me up. Oh, this is going to work.
Is it going to work? Who is this working for?
I think we are lagging bad because stuff is happening on my screen that's not...
Which actually is probably a pretty good thing.
So we should probably go do something stupid.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I am done. We are playing the game.
Let's go.
We are playing the video game Dead Rising 3.
There, I helped you get out.
Can my girlfriend come with us?
Absolutely, let's go.
Everybody loves Terra.
Oh my god, you...
Oh, made it.
Holy shit, that was a jump. I didn't even realize that.
Don't go back. I jumped out.
No, no, no, no, you idiot. Did you fall?
What are you doing? Get in.
I don't want to fall back.
I'm not going to fall back.
You seriously think I'm going to fall back?
What a fucking dummy.
I'm not doing this. Get in.
I'm not doing this joke.
Well, then you die. I surrender.
All right, get in for real.
Get in for real this time.
Get in for real.
I'm going to spin around. I'm going to do a three point turn.
I'm only doing this to get fucking, you know, able to...
What?
Physics. Physics, how is this possible?
Oh, there's a fucking thing in the middle right here.
Okay, it all worked out.
Look, it all worked out.
Now, climb back up.
Get in the car.
All right, I'll figure this all out.
Get out.
I'm begging you to come play the game with me.
I know, but this has to happen.
Push it off.
I want to see the big explosion.
No, it needs to fall off.
Don't just like throw shit at it.
Fuck.
What happened? Did you fall off?
No.
Hold on a second. I'm crashing.
I crashed. That's what happened.
I crashed.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I am done.
We are playing the game.
Let's go.
Come on. Fill me with bullets.
Come on. That's all you got.
I can take another 200.
Another 2000.
No.
I've been thwarted.
I don't know what to do here, man.
There's a car blocking this way.
Do you see this car blocking the exit?
I see the car blocking the exit.
How am I supposed to get out of here?
There's a window.
Did you know there was a window?
Yeah.
She's calling in her reinforcements.
Why did I just spawn next to her?
Yeah, you are right next to her.
Are you alive?
Yeah, the cutscene ended and I just appeared on her.
I have no guns now.
I'll kill her with flares.
See, you don't know where she is.
She's right there.
There's a grenade under your feet.
You probably should move.
Get in the car.
Get in the car this instant, young man.
No.
I got a call from Mrs. Rogerson.
Are you going to get a B- on your math exam?
No.
You get in this car right now.
Your father is going to hear about this and he is going to lose his shit.
No.
Are you going to make me come all the way into the hotel?
Yeah.
I don't even like this hotel.
They don't even serve breakfast.
This thing is going to go.
If you touch a wall, all of your gamer skills are coming together right now.
All of my gamer skills need to be here.
I'm playing Operation.
Operation.
The thing with the naked guy that lies on the table and you have to pull his bones out.
We're playing that right now.
No.
That game where you pull bones out of...
Operation.
I don't think I can even go out here.
It's buzzing so loud right now.
I've lost so many times.
This is the guys femur.
That was always the hardest one.
The femur was the hardest one for me.
Mom, I don't want to go into the hotel.
You're in big trouble, mister.
I've come all the way into the hotel to get you.
And now I've got you.
And you're not going to even get your cereal.
Just like in GTA.
Take out the driver.
I'm alright.
He ate those all in one bite.
Easy.
What the fuck?
I got you something.
I got you a burrito from Taco Bell.
It's Chalupa.
Try it out.
It's really good stuff.
What are you doing?