This place has like a weird playground mode. Wow, are you serious? No, don't fall in the spikes.
Please help me. I didn't want to die. I don't want to die like this.
Dude, this is brutal. I'm gonna turn.
Unbelievable. I'm still alive. I'm turning into a piece of trash.
I can't believe this is actually still a drivable car.
Well, it's okay. I just, you know, whatever. I turned into a fucking piece of trash.
Come on, you can do it. You can do it, little trash car.
No, I can't. I couldn't do it. I couldn't. You told me I could. I couldn't do it, mummy.
This is the thing from Double Dare. You guys remember Double Dare?
The thing on Nickelodeon when the people would slime through this thing and it like looked like
it was going to squish them? Double Dare, this is awesome. I can't wait to see what happens here.
Did you get the flag? Did you pick up the flag, dad? Oh, god damn it. Goofball asshole,
dad didn't pick up the flag at the end. I'm not going to get my Super Nintendo and my mountain bike.
You guys remember the prizes for Double Dare? They were shit. You got like a Super Nintendo
game and a bike. That is so cool. That was awesome. I love physics engines, man. There's
so much fun. What else is there? What other like weird toys can I play with in this game?
Yeah, I think I'm going to need your insurance information. You backed into me when we were at
the Walgreens. I could really... my car has a bump on the fender now. You need to get your
insurance, you fucking bitch. This is definitely the best thing is this thing down here. Just you
get absolutely destroyed in here. I seriously want to... I wonder how much car damage you can really
do. The thing from the Brave Little Toaster is my goal. I want to turn into a cube from the Brave
Little Toaster. I'm making a lot of references to old shit in this video. Hi, I'm Mr. Car and I don't
feel good right now. My tummy hurts. Welcome to the dentist. In my office, how we do things is I use
a super teeth grinder. And your teeth really need to be cleaned. Yes, yes they do. Don't mind,
don't mind the guy crashing into the wall. I gotta go look at that guy. The guy looks like a school
bus. The guy... oh no, he's gonna get crushed. Oh no, no, he can't do it. Yeah, yeah, okay, I hear you.
Yeah, so where's this cargo going? This really expensive cargo from Japan? Yeah, well, I don't
want to just be careful next to it because, you know, you never know what could happen if you
accidentally bump it. And if you couldn't understand the joke already, then oh no, all that expensive
Japanese cargo. Whatever will we do? Whatever will we do? That joke's getting edited out of the video.
Get in the jet engine. You can do it, Luke Skywalker. Use the force, just like in the movie.
Yes! Come on, get in the six, you fuck. Yes! Yes! And the four. And the four. That's ten points.
Are you trying to tell me right now that this person in here is not injured at all?
Is this even a person? Is this like, what is this thing? This poor guy's stuck. Oh no, I'm stuck in
here. Whatever will I... See, a lot of people didn't know that there was a boss battle in this.
The giant enemy spider.
I don't even know. Help. What have I done? My frames are going down. I just want to go bowling.
That's all I wanted to do. Just want to go bowling. I just want to go bowling. Cousin. Cousin. Let's go bowling.