Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2, Facecam Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
That's a lot of words. This is episode 1 of Facecam Fortress 2. Well, technically not episode 1, but it's episode probably like 4 or 5.
Heavy, you're gonna kill me and soldier behind me.
Episode 1 of probably 500,000. I'm gonna do this every Monday and every Saturday, and they'll be uploaded around the same time.
So expect a FCF2, Facecam Fortress 2, FCF2 video every Monday and Saturday at 1pm Eastern time. Standard. And that is, no, it's not a spy. Is it? No, it's not.
This is the Demoman with the default. Pretty much everything except for the halfs of Toichi. And this is on gorge. Let's gorge ourselves on gorge.
I thought that was a spy. I wasted it. Somebody come up there. Anybody? Anybody? Ooh, Heavy. Please don't kill me, Heavy. Don't come up the stairs. I don't want to die.
Heavy? Sniper.
My name is still Abrum. I didn't mean for that to be there, really.
I just got a couple of good kills. And...
Oh my god, I killed him. Oh my god, he was just standing in the corner.
Maybe this Heavy will not know I'm behind him. Or this Batic.
Oh my god, that was so unfair.
Oh my god. Does that guy have a bootlegger?
I need a Medic. Do we have any? No, we don't. We don't have one Medic. Maybe I'll change that after... Oh no.
Thank you Pyro for saving my life. It doesn't matter though, I'm going to die right here anyways.
I forgot to mention this because I was screwing this on before the video started. Well, not that I forgot to mention it, but...
You want to see the vitamins that I take? This is actually pretty funny.
So, Centrum Silver. I don't know if the camera is going to go out of focus, but Centrum Silvers.
Take a look at the age. 50 plus. I got to take 50 year old vitamins. Well, 50 plus.
And that's because of my Crohn's disease. I got to take old people vitamins.
For Grandma. Grandpa should be taking those, not me.
But it's because old people don't have as good absorption of nutrients into their intestines, I think it is.
And my intestines are a little bit on the slow side, because of course I have Crohn's.
But yeah, I thought that was funny. My mother showed those to me. She's like, these are the vitamins you got to take.
I was like, I do? That's a three piece. Oh, bump into that. How did I crit him? Oh, someone's behind me.
Or are they?
Soldier with direct hits scares me a little. Nah.
I had a feeling he was going to kill me. I had a feeling.
You know what? Where are my cough drops? I want one right now.
Ricola. Do I have enough time? I got plenty of time.
Oh, I got plenty of spies. Timing up and backstabbing scumbags like you. No offense.
If you manage to kill them, I assure you, they will not like spies.
Who the hell am I doing? I think we're going to win. They're not even at the first point.
Oh, he's going to charge shot me. Actually, you know why I said that?
I've been watching a lot of those YouTube poops of Team Fortress where they replace the sentences.
So like the scout will say something like this, like, oh, I kill plenty of birds, a diamond bird, birds, like you birds.
Like, I can't really replicate it, but it's very, very funny.
We win. We're going to win.
I never know what to do with myself after I die. I come just like, I could just sit here.
I could model. There's a fly right in front of here.
Do you guys see that? Fly bastard. Hope he lands right in my mouth.
I do not hope that. Gotta get on the point. Slow walk to the first point in Gorge.
Oh, come on. Smash. Smash. Come on. Get him off.
What the hell? Who is this soldier? There we go. Anybody else? Here we go. Cool.
Alrighty. Alrighty then. Let's do another one. He's not a threat.
How did I not kill that guy? How did I still not kill that guy? Oh my God.
All right. I made up for it because I smashed that guy in his teeth.
I can't believe I didn't kill that guy. Crit rocket. Medic? That's a spy probably.
I guess not. The way he jerked away. I could have sworn he was a spy.
Buff banner. Crush him baby. Smash. Somebody kill him. Somebody kill that guy.
Pop. Doctor, I require assistance. And that is going to be a cap right there.
I don't even want to be a part of it. I want to be forward. Forward motion.
We got engineer and you. Oh, you are a slippery one. I can't go up there right now.
Where's that medic? Medic my friend, where did you go? It's okay. I'm good.
I'm good. I'm not even going to need the banner. Maybe we will.
There's going to be a lot of dudes down here. There we go. There we go.
All right guys. That's going to wrap it up for episode one of ten hundred million thousand face cam fortress 2.
So I'll see you guys all next time and take care everybody.
Otto! He's not even here.