Time for balloons. Hmm. Smash Brothers? Flave Worms. Alright, that sounds kind of fun to me.
What do they got for balloons here? They have balloons too. We're gonna get like the good,
the fun one. GeoGuessr? Have you guys played GeoGuessr? BTD5. Alright, let's get it open.
You guys can play this one. You guys can play one level of this one. Me versus you guys,
tic-tac-toe. Now this guy's got a black bar on the side of his stream, which sucks. Alright,
so I have a... I think I know how to play this game, kind of. So I'm gonna let you guys decide
what the hell to do. Let me get this on the screen. I don't need to see that down there.
Make sure it's big enough. Let's turn off the BRB screen, get the audio on here. Actually,
I need to... Speaking of audio, because this is extraordinarily loud. That's better. Now
we can actually hear what's going on. Okay, so where are we going? Did we just play him?
Td6. No, we're on td5. We're gonna play. That's what everybody wants.
Play. New game. Okay, good luck. Here we go. This actually matters. Well, beginner,
we got... This is very evenly split here. It looks like we're going this way.
I'll give you a minute. Alright, it's time to close this. Whoa! No, it's Jesus!
What is... Oh, it's because I have the fucking click thing wrong. Hold on.
Alright, do it again. People were just spam clicking. Surprising that this is... This
is the hardest decision of the whole night, apparently. Alright, that's it. Let's go to
space. I can't even select Apocalypse, guys. Please do easy. I don't even... It's
gonna take so long for you guys to figure this out. Alright, we're going hard. On hard,
your towers cost more than normal. Alright, just... Alright, well, how long do we have
to the waves? They're gonna come from this way. Alright, so we're gonna do Dark
Monkey. Dark Monkey. Where? I can't put him... I can't put him right in the middle.
Right there? Alright, he's going right there. Now what? Yo, what is the solar system,
by the way? This is very crowded. Alright, where's it going?
Okay, I love and hate everything about what we're doing right now.
Okay, clear it. Is it time to go? Looks like it's time to go. Alright, clear it. Here comes wave
one. Speed it up. Okay, we gotta rank up. We unlocked a new tower. Share it on Facebook.
No, I'm not fucking doing that. What? No, this... You can't... Okay, level up,
Dark Monkey leveled up. Now what? I fucking love this so much. Are we adding a tower
or are we upgrading? I don't know. I don't know. Looks like people want to go over here.
Alright, we're doing the tac shooter. Where's it going? I can't put it here. Okay. Like,
right here? This is where... I can't get it on top of him. Alright, now what? Which one of
these am I upgrading? This one? Okay, no, no, no, no. People want to start. Let's go. Speed
it up already. Some of them are gonna get through. Zoom for better selection. Alright, hold on.
Let me see if I can get this in a better spot. We could... I guess we could cut off the bottom
here. Like this, right? Technically. You guys need that information for anything?
No, no, no. You need the information. Alright, well... Son of a fuck. Alright,
that... You can see that, right? Alright, let's go. A hundred percent. Every single person is
clicking here. Alright, upgrade. Long dart range. Makes the dart monkey shoot further than normal.
Got it. Now what? Have I ever played Bloons? Oh yeah, I know, but I'm not playing Bloons
right now. I am just a vessel for you guys to decide what you're gonna do. Here we go.
Everyone just clicks on that. Like, come on, let's go! Okay, dart monkey level up.
Rank up for sniper monkey. Let's go ahead. I'm not sharing it on Facebook.
Hmm, it could be any one of these. Okay. I'm selecting this one. Now what?
No, that's not the right one. The other one. Okay, I got the other one. Hold on,
hold on, everyone. Don't click yet. Okay, now click. Alright, looks like we're upgrading
this guy. Good choice. Alright, why would you make me upgrade and then sell it?
Uh, okay. If you want to vote, just click the screen. This can only go for so much longer.
Alright, enough people came in. Upgrade. Closing the poll in 10 seconds. Alright,
that's it. Alright, let's go. And more speed. Okay, the first green Bloons are coming next.
Alright, looks like sell, attack, or go. Looks like it's gonna be go. Yeah, let's go.
Alright, you got a boomerang thrower. Reset it here. I think, I think that's the, yeah,
the attack. Tack shooter. What are you, I can't do anything. We can't do anything with the tack
shooter. What are you talking about? Sell. Sell it? Damn. Alright, this is a unanimous.
Refreshing. Three, two, one. Oh, dear. This is, this is too close. I don't know
which one these people are clicking on. I don't, I have no idea. I have to zoom in for
this. Hold on. Hey, welcome to the 12 hour fucking Bloons tower defense stream. Alright,
looks like we've got a boomerang, boomerang thrower. Nice choice. The tack, the tack is
stealing votes. Why? Are you, what are you guys talking about? Use the windows zoom tool?
Well, I don't think that's gonna work. Wait, does magnifying glass even in Windows 10?
I wonder if that'll work. Alright, boomerang thrower. Let me get that out here,
because this is a huge pain in the ass. Yeah, this is actually, that's a great idea,
because then I could just put the, it doesn't go much smoother. Yeah, check this. Okay.
Magnifying glass. Magnifier. Is that gonna show up? Oh, my God. No, no, no, no, no. Back.
What the fuck is that? Lens. There we go. I don't think this is gonna work. Okay,
let's see. Ready? Uh, this isn't doing anything. Yeah, you guys can't see it.
This map is hard. Oh, wait a minute. Can you see this? Oh, shit, you can't see it. That's
unfortunate because it's zoomed in right now. Damn it. That's unfortunate. Capture the
magnifier window in OBS. This is like lagging the computer too. Fuck. Oh, well.
I wonder if I can do this. I have an idea. Yeah, here's an idea. I'm gonna screenshot
this and then I'm gonna make a huge image and I'm gonna cut to it.
Please turn off the music. Um, that's, that has to come to a vote.
All right, let me get the screenshot in the right place. Uh, can you guys even,
you can't even click it. All right, well, you guys are clicking it.
All right, give me one second while I get this image. This will actually work.
This will actually work. So let's do a print screen and okay, crop this out.
So then you can actually select it and I can make it huge.
Yeah, that's much better. Much, much better. Okay, side panel, add image, side panel.
There it is. How am I going to make it? Okay, somehow this is worse. All right.
So whenever we want to do this, I'm going to put that on screen. Look at that.
Better. All right. You ready to play? Where would you like me to go?
Oh, if you want a tower, then here's what you have to do. If you want a new tower,
you guys have to click here, like over here, and then I'll bring up the new, the window.
All right. Looks like people want a tower. All right. Let's clear that.
Do it again. Where would you like it? This is all right.
I can only do this for so much longer before I have to stop.
All right. You got the, just making sure it works. So we're going to do boomerang.
Where would you like the boomerang to go? This is the worst stream ever.
I actually like, think this is, I've actually have like a good time.
Reset it. Do it again. All right. It looks like you want them down here.
Can I, I can't even fit them here. Can I? Okay. That's where it's going.
And you click here. I can't do anything else with him. What am I supposed to do?
Somebody said I'm too drunk for this. All right. Here it comes.
Good placement, guys. Good placement. We did it. We did it.
Congratulations. We did it. Really? You brought him in for one turn.
Now my fucking God. All right. Now you want a new tower.
No, a new tower now is what I want. Give me a new tower.
I'll take one, please. What could you possibly,
you're not going to buy the boomerang again. You guys are out of your fucking minds.
Why? Where would you like me to put them?
Well, this is turning out to be a fucking huge waste of time.
Anything else? Three, two, one.
Why would you do this? This is not even, this is not even interesting.
Okay. Hmm. Let's buy another tower. That sounds like fun.
Sniper attack? No, boomerang again. Boomerang? Nice.
All right. So, I mean, where should I put them?
That's, you know, important. The placement of the character.
Where should you go? Okay. Pretty good spot for him, I think.
Are we going to play? Or are you going to keep, we're going to keep this up?
We're going to play the round?
There's an equal amount of people that are like sick of this.
Yep. There it is. Donezo. Let's play.
Oh, I can't, let's skip. That's my favorite part about this whole thing.
That's how quickly everybody goes right to the fast forward button.
All right, rank up. We got road spikes. There's a new, a new thing over here.
Here we go. Road spikes looks pretty popular.
No, I'm not going to share it. You guys already bought Pikachu socks
and a giant, like 25 inch whale.
All right. So where, you want whale spikes? Where are they going?
You want them here. Where do you want these?
You don't want them. Why is everybody clicking here?
Spikes are on go. That didn't do, no. What?
Where do you want me to put these spikes?
Okay. I'm going to clear this because I don't think you get this is correct.
Where do you want this to be? Here.
Okay. They're there. Now what?
More. More road spikes in the same place.
You sure? Doesn't look like it.
Looks like I'm just clicking the go button. 10 seconds.
And that's, that's it. I'm, I'm go. Go.
I had to close it right there.
All right. Look at the round is over.
That's a lot of balloons. You sure you guys are,
I don't know if you guys are correct about this.
We've got a lot. What about the money?
Okay. Level up. Dart monkey level up.
Unlocked access to enhanced eyesight and access to multi-target.
All right. Click on boomerang.
Sure thing. All right.
In three, two, one, we come back.
Looks like most people wanted this to be upgraded.
Some of you guys there are funny jokesters, pranksters.
That's fine. All right.
We're going to do a multi-target with the boomerang.
Anything else? Why am I playing a game I used to play in school
back in the fifth grade? No, I'm resetting this shit.
No. And I did, I somehow made it worse. Why?
I'm waiting until at least a thousand votes for this one.
700 votes. There we go.
Can people double vote? It's one vote per viewer.
New tower. Yeah, that's good. New tower.
Can we move our vote around?
You just click on the screen and it counts as a vote.
Can you click somewhere else to change your vote?
I don't, I don't think so.
All right. We're going to take the sniper.
Good choice. Pretty good choice, I would say.
Where's it gone? Hmm.
Doesn't fit here. It can't go there.
Right here? Why can this not fit here?
Is there a reason why this can't go right here?
This is the only place I can put it is right here.
It's got to be on land. Oh, I see. Okay.
Well, this seems like it's the best place to put it.
Somewhere like in here. Like right here.
Zoom in? I can't zoom in.
All right, right there. Very good.
What's next? Nice try, everybody.
4k viewers for a children's game.
All right, here we go. Again.
We're just going to go again. Pretty good call.
Let's play this game on cool math games.
Where we are right now, man.
Oh, no, we're not. We're on the actual website.
We're on the Ninja Kiwi website.
What's next? New tower.
Unfortunately, I don't have my screenshot.
It doesn't have...
You kind of need to remember where your things are
because that... Remember the spot that that's in.
Wow. Not one person has decided to click anywhere else.
That's actually pretty...
Nobody they clicked on the guy's nose over here.
That's crazy.
There was almost 600 votes at the same place.
Okay, let's put them down.
Where is it going?
I guess in this general vicinity.
That sounds fine.
Like right here.
All right, I'm gonna try to get right in the middle.
If I even can.
Right here. Right there.
It won't hit anything if it's in the middle.
Yeah, right there.
All right, let's go.
I can't believe this is still going.
Now neither can I.
For some reason, I'm still interested in this.
All right, dart monkey leveled up.
What would you like me to do with them?
Okay, I don't understand.
Wrong one.
Wait, get... Do it again.
This one.
Okay.
15%.
13%.
36% say they want razor sharp.
Could pop two balloons at the same time.
All right, again.
Okay, double upgrade it seems.
Where are we going from here?
All right, speed it up.
Let's see if it was the right call.
Rank seven.
Another new tower here.
But we don't have any money.
I don't have enough money for that.
Why am I saying me?
This is you guys.
You don't have enough money for this.
So what round do you think you guys are going to lose on?
Again.
Oh, no, no, this is the...
Hold on a minute here.
A lot of money.
A lot of subs came in too that I missed.
I'll make sure I touch upon them when we're done.
But thank you so much.
M.H. Harmless.
Thanks for the $50.
Now you have money for it.
Thanks for 50 bucks.
That's a huge amount of money, man.
Thank you.
It's funny, I don't even have to say anything anymore.
I just... Really?
Okay.
I don't know why...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Not sell strong because you can't click down here.
Why not?
You should be able to click down there.
That's kind of stupid.
So you want it strong.
All right.
Strong.
Okay.
We got it.
We got... We're good.
We're good.
Everything's fine.
You guys are doing a really good job.
Start it again.
How much longer am I going to do this?
I don't know.
Tonight was real weird.
But whatever.
Okay.
Let's open that up.
Make sure you know what you're clicking on here.
All right.
Looks like we want Cannon.
Cannon, where is it going?
Losing viewers?
It's all right.
We're just hanging out having fun.
Hmm.
Over here or over here?
There's a lot of different opinions apparently right now on balloons tower defense.
The general consensus for the majority is...
Well, that's not even a...
Yeah.
Right here?
All right.
Let's go.
Chat is min maxing.
The balloons have a powerful new advancement regrowth.
These balloons are distinguished by their heart shape.
If not popped quickly, they will grow layers back to their original size.
Make sure you guys are aware of that.
Is that it?
That was the whole round.
Okay.
Put on some music.
I'll put on some music.
That sounds like a good idea.
Rank up.
All right.
Let's put music on.
See, this is where it breaks up.
We're on round 20.
Coming up around 19.
Look at all these different opinions.
This is wild.
All right.
Looks like we're going to...
Got to go by what the highest percentage is here.
I got to reset it.
I've already selected this thing.
I've already selected the Cannon.
We're going to reset.
Ready?
Here we go.
Sell it.
No, no, no.
Okay.
It's not...
It's strong.
Is it strong or sell?
I can't tell.
All right.
Selected.
Ready?
Three, two, one.
Here it comes again.
What do you want me to click?
Okay.
We got the ninja.
All right.
Three, two, one.
What do I click?
Upgrade discipline, increase attack range, and attack speed.
All right.
Three, two, one.
Where are we going?
That's all you want to do?
Okay.
You guys are good at this game.
This is never going to end.
Are we going again?
We're going again.
All right.
Black balloons and white balloons are small but contain two pink balloons when popped.
They're immune to explosions and immune to freezing.
Okay.
Got to be careful here.
All right.
For 75 IQ, you guys are doing a real good job.
New tower.
Whatever it was, this is the ice tower down here.
People are still clicking on the tack tower.
That's my favorite thing.
All right.
Let's get the ice.
Where is he going?
I need to take a new screenshot.
Okay.
People are like, save it.
Save the game.
We're over here.
Right in there is where I can fit it.
I can only fit it right here.
All right.
That's it.
Three, two, one.
Waste of money.
Sell.
No, we're going, right?
Let's go.
Okay.
Save.
Save the game.
Log in to save your game.
I don't have an account here so I can't do that.
And I click on the ice tower.
Ice tower has been clicked.
And now what?
You guys just put it down.
It was just put down.
Wrong.
This is what you wanted to select.
No range.
No.
This is...
Wait.
We can do it again.
What do you want me to select?
Make it really clear.
Make accuracy here.
Accuracy.
Fuck.
They're right on top of each other.
That's...
Okay.
If it was this one, all the circle would be up here.
Now what?
Now it was just put down here.
Didn't you guys just put it down?
I have to listen.
Okay.
What would you like to do now?
I placed it wrong.
How did I place it wrong?
I'm going to be going back over here.
Hold on.
Are you guys trying to correct me putting it in the wrong place?
No way.
Really?
Okay.
I'm buying the ice tower right now.
Ice tower.
Let's lower this.
And where do you want it?
You got to be accurate.
Why do you want it back up here in the same spot?
Like here?
Right here.
This is...
That's where it's going.
Right in the center.
Set like here.
That's not going to hit anything.
Need zoom?
All right.
We do need zoom for this one apparently.
Hold on.
I'm going to zoom the fuck in.
Because this is important.
If you guys are making me sell...
Okay.
Where do you want it?
Jesus.
It can't even go over here.
Okay.
I love this.
This is so much fun.
I don't know why.
Just knowing...
It's...
This is one...
I love this.
Okay.
Now I have to fix this.
It's just in a worse spot.
You guys have to come to a determination
of where you want me to put the towers, guys.
Okay.
Are we ready?
No.
You got to be fucking kidding me, guys.
I'm waiting for more participation than this.
Come on.
Okay.
There we go.
All right.
With that...
Yeah.
We're about over 3,000 now.
Go.
Okay.
Did the ice even do anything?
I don't think the ice did anything.
All right.
Well, we're at 23 of 85.
You guys are almost...
We're getting close to being in a place.
A good spot.
All right.
I need some clarification.
Are you trying to click on the dart or the ice?
I think you're trying to click...
I don't know.
Am I going to have to zoom in again?
I feel like it's 50-50.
All right.
If you...
Okay.
Here's how it's going to work.
I'm going to refresh it.
If you want the ice tower to be selected,
you got to click over by the sun.
If you want the dart,
you got to click like up here.
Like over here.
All right.
Reset...
Resetting it.
Ice it looks like.
Okay.
All right.
Selecting ice.
I'm assuming we're going to do an upgrade for this.
Guys.
It's...
Sell it.
It's trash.
It's not a joke.
It's bad.
Well, how is it voted for in the first place?
I've sold this before.
And then you guys bought it again
and made sure it was in the correct placement.
And now 70% of you want to sell it.
Okay?
Stop asking questions, vessel.
Okay.
Another tower.
So this looks like it's going to be...
Is that...
That's a ninja?
I think that's a ninja.
Yeah.
That's very clearly over the ninja.
Okay.
Where's it going?
Over here.
I'm going to try to get it as close in the circle as I can.
Wherever the center of this circle is,
is where it's going.
Right there.
Enhance.
How do you vote?
You just have to enable the extension
and you just click on the screen.
That looks good.
We almost time...
It's almost time for round...
Round like 30.
Round 20, whatever it is.
Oh damn.
All right.
Looks like I know what people want to do.
What's next?
Round 23 of 85.
Incoming.
Fucking easy.
Again?
Okay.
Camo balloons are very dangerous
since most towers cannot hit them.
Any balloon types can also be camo balloon
and so will all the balloons that come out of that one.
They can only be hit by towers that can detect camo.
All other attacks will miss.
If you do not have any towers that can detect camo,
use road spikes.
Nice.
Bomb tower level up.
Access to extra range.
And a glue gunner has been unlocked.
All right.
Any changes that you guys would like to make?
We're not sharing.
We're never going to share it.
All right.
New tower.
So make sure you remember where those slots are.
You see?
Got it?
You see where they are?
Glue is being 100%ed right here.
Move the picture to the left.
Okay.
So it's easier to click on.
So the glue was selected.
I don't think I've ever played this game this long
to see what this even does.
But you've got glue now.
Where would you like to put it?
Up here.
Oof.
Over here.
What's the extension called?
Smart map.
Smart click maps is what it's called.
You should be able to just activate it from your...
You just have to click a button, don't you?
I don't know.
This is too...
I got to go in.
We got to zoom in here.
In fact, you know, I'm going to take a screenshot of this too.
And so we can zoom into it.
Because it's been so conflicted.
Print screen.
Give me a second.
Let's just get the area here so I can zoom way in.
Okay.
Let's get it on there.
All right.
So we're going to do it like this.
So it's easier for you guys to select fine...
Finite details.
Okay.
So where do you want it to go?
Sorry.
Right in the middle there.
All right.
I...
Right there.
Right in the middle.
You got it.
All right.
So you wanted it right here.
Right there.
That's as close as I can get it.
That's actually the worst spot.
Why?
What?
Surprisingly, I haven't even lost one life yet.
How have you guys not lost one life?
That's kind of ridiculous.
Indecisive.
It's going again.
Uh oh.
All right.
Ninja Monkey leveled up.
Now what?
We're going to have to enhance this.
I have no idea what you guys want me to do.
It's restarting in three, two, one.
I think that's click on the ninja, right?
Yep.
It's the middle one right there.
Okay.
Upgrade.
Yep.
Sounds good to me.
Okay.
I got the other ninja selected.
All right.
Upgrade this one to Seeking.
Oh, Selen!
There's a small percentage of you guys
that really want that sniper upgrade.
But I'm going to have to refresh here.
I don't know what's going on.
Sniper.
Sniper selected.
Three, two, one.
All right.
Shoots can pop through four layers of blue
and it can pop lead and frozen blue.
All right.
Now it's time for the cannon.
Cannon unlockables?
Shoots?
What do you mean?
Shoots.
Okay.
I got the cannon on.
Preparing yourselves for the next round.
You puny vessel.
You're no match for the hive mind.
We'll take over your computer.
Like those people in the unfriended horror movie.
Lead bloons are slow,
but they're immune to anything sharp.
They contain two black bloons when popped.
That was fucking easy.
How have you guys done this so well?
Seriously, how is this possible?
More?
We're going to go again.
Am I going to stream World of Light?
Yeah.
I'm probably going to play Smash Brothers tomorrow.
Next round, many zebra bloons.
Are we prepared for this?
People want to go.
Got some nervous people in the chat though.
Nervous?
Why are you so nervous?
All right.
I did it.
It had to do it.
Everybody's clicking on tacks.
Glue gunner leveled up.
Glue soaks through all layers of blue.
And exploding pineapples.
This guy.
What would you like me to do with this guy?
We want the upgrade.
Okay.
12%.
Always sell.
Strong, strong, strong.
Okay.
Selected strong.
Boomerang upgrades.
Sniper guys.
I have no say in this.
I'm only here to click buttons on the screen.
That's the only reason why I'm here.
Okay.
Make sure you see where you want these towers.
Because they're...
Here we go.
It's a good reference to see where they are.
Sniper tower.
It's currently destroying.
Okay.
Selected.
You want to know a funny tidbit of information?
This would be the only time I would ever have beaten anything on this game.
We might need an enhance here.
You guys are beating this while I'm clicking...
It's on my computer so it's technically mine.
Right, it's on my console.
So it's mine.
Technically.
Well, yeah, I got to enhance this.
Do it again.
Right in the middle there.
68%.
Yeah, just about 70%.
It's going to go right in the middle there.
I'm the host for the hive mine.
All right, it's going to go right there.
Right here.
Close enough, right?
Looks like right there.
Click them again.
And then upgrade.
I see what you guys are doing.
I see the...
I see.
Okay.
I'm just coming to this crazy realization.
Any one of you guys could open this up right now and play it.
And then put it on strong.
Anybody could just open this.
Why are we all sitting here doing this?
We are playing.
That's right.
That's true.
All right, good luck.
More dangerous.
Uh-oh.
Jesus.
Give me a fucking break.
Okay, so we're upgrading.
The collective is clicking here.
Oh, wait a minute.
Hold on.
All right.
All right, I got them selected.
Upgrade.
I can talk to my mother on the phone later.
Oh, what did you do today?
I sat in a chair and 4,000 people yelled at me and clicked on a screen for me to
monkeys down for a tower defense game.
Oh.
And then we're upgrading this?
I guess so.
What else would you like to do with your turn chat?
I'm seeing a lot of just goes.
Okay.
Let's hope you were right.
That looks like it's up here.
We got 74% going to the tax.
All right.
Where would you like me to put them?
I need to refresh.
Refresh.
Looks like all down here.
I think I'm going to go...
How many should I do?
One?
Do a whole line?
All right, I'm going to put down one right in the middle.
There's one down there.
Is that all you need?
You want another one?
Okay.
More.
55% of you still want me to put them here.
Okay.
Refreshing again.
Every time it's refreshed, more and more people are like,
you know, I think that's enough tax.
That looks good.
It really is a collective.
You guys are at 34.
Around 34 of 85.
New tower.
It's a good thing we bought those tax.
Okay.
New tower.
Make sure you see where it is on the screen there.
You know, some people pay $15 on consoles to play this.
Yeah, but you're playing it right now for free.
It's pretty unanimous.
You guys want the buccaneer.
I don't need to see anything else.
Oops.
Move that away.
All right.
What do you want it?
This might be an enhanced scenario.
It is.
It's going to be an enhanced scenario.
Please just wait till I refresh.
This is where the buccaneer is going.
You can't put them there.
He can fit there.
Yeah, he's going right there.
Thank you for voting.
He's going right in this little channel here.
Right there.
All right.
What next?
Didn't this game have music?
Oh, yeah, sure.
All right, here we go.
Which one of these upgrades?
That's the important thing.
No, I can't.
No, I can't do that one.
Is that all you want to do?
I can't tell if everyone is trying to get tips, save,
or if they're trying to turn the music off.
Okay.
Do you want to put it back on?
Tips.
Okay.
Tips are no longer on.
All right.
It...
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
If you want the music to come back, click on the boomerang.
If you want me to put the tips back on,
click up here.
Okay?
Put on the doom OST.
Oh, my God.
Hold on.
Okay.
Now what do you want me to do?
Time to go?
What now?
No, I'm not doing it louder.
All right.
We're selecting the monkey.
This one?
I think it's this one.
What would you like?
Sharp.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
Select.
And the other one too, huh?
Well, what did you do?
What did you do last night, honey?
Oh, well, I had 4,000 people in a chat room.
All...
We were playing a Balloons Tower Defense 5 that I wasn't playing it.
They were telling me what to do and I was blasting the doom soundtrack.
Kind of split here on what people want to do.
Turn it up.
Now what?
Go again.
No.
You want to select this guy.
Now what do you want to do?
My left ear.
Is it loud in the left ear?
So we're buying this one.
Thanks for playing, guys.
Anything else?
Again, this one too.
Both of them.
Sonic Boom.
Here's the wild thing about this stream.
Remember the first like 10 minutes when we were doing this?
I was like, oh, I don't know how to click this and then you vote.
Look at how streamlined this has become.
This is almost like scary.
This is almost terrifying.
Uh-oh.
Ooh, that was close.
All right, hold on.
I got to change the volumes here.
Hold on.
Wait.
Now I have to stop for a second.
I'm gonna turn this down.
The chess game is done.
Wait, what?
Okay, I thought I just X'd out of the fucking window.
I thought I just closed Balloon's Tower Defense 5.
And there's no saving.
Oh, that would have been so bad.
I would have just gone.
I would have gone crying in the shower.
Okay.
Uh, I need to put this in a different window so I can control how loud that is.
So give me one second, guys.
What?
Why am I just loading up a random web page right now?
What the fuck was that?
Was that an ad?
I have no idea what that was.
I opened up another tab and it went to like...
I don't have any fucking idea.
This is correct, right?
That was fucking weird.
I can do that.
And then that should be open now.
I'm spending a lot of time trying to get this to work.
There we go.
Okay.
So now drop this and then put this higher than that.
Now that should be good.
I'm ready to go.
Okay.
Here we go.
Tax.
I think we're just going to go.
I think you're going to lose.
Oh!
Now what, guys?
That's not good.
50.
All right.
What do you want?
Which one?
Does it matter?
Look at everybody panicking right now.
People are panicking.
I think we need tax.
Oh shit, let's close the game.
Get the ice monster.
Now what?
Oh, I got to refresh it.
I think people are panicking.
This is 23.
This is almost $2,400.
Are you guys sure about this?
Let me let the votes come through.
All right.
Anything else?
Are you clicking up here?
You guys want more health?
Yes.
All right.
Okay.
You can't do that.
Something else.
All right.
It looks like you're selecting the buccaneer.
Faster shooting.
You got it.
Come on, guys.
You can't.
We got it.
Come on.
We've got to beat this.
Is this tax or go?
This looks like tax to me.
All right.
Where are they going?
Where are the tax going?
At the end, we did three last time.
Okay.
We'll do one, two.
How many?
Let's make sure we get.
Hold on.
One, two, three.
That's what we did last time.
If you want more than three,
you got to click on that spot again.
You ready?
Oh, damn.
More.
Another.
Okay.
Here's one, two.
I did two more.
More.
You guys want more tax?
All right.
I'm closing it.
Do you want more tax?
All right.
Okay.
That's enough.
Apparently.
All right.
Let's go.
Are you ready?
Hold on to your asses.
Here it comes.
What?
No.
I think we're good.
I think we're safe.
Uh-oh.
You did it.
You guys did it.
You actually did it.
We're halfway through.
Let's go.
You want this one?
Which one is it?
I'm going to have to zoom in for this.
Okay.
Got them selected.
Enhance eyesight.
Increase attack range.
Even further allows dart monkey to shoot camo balloons.
Sounds good.
What's next?
More upgrades on this guy.
You want the spike-a-pult.
All right.
Three, two, one.
Refreshing.
Here we go again.
I'm going to let this one play for a second because
it looks like there's some uncertainty amongst us.
Everybody's panicking.
This is the one.
There's 4,500 votes here.
How is that possible?
There's more votes than people.
What?
All right.
I'm going to-
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Again.
Okay.
That's what the people want.
Again.
This is split here between buying this and putting it on last.
All right.
Last.
Now what?
This again.
Buy it again.
All right.
This is on Razor Sharp.
You guys have the confidence to win, do you think?
No, you want more?
Okay.
Take a look and see where you want it.
Oh, fuck.
Look at this.
There are some arguments going to be happening right now
between the ace and a cannon.
Looks like it's going to be an ace.
Let's go.
Where's it going?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Look at this.
Cancel.
You guys really are panicking.
Okay.
All right.
I have to cancel.
Cancel.
All right.
What do you want in place of it?
I'm scared.
Flank out.
I'm going to refresh it one more time just to make sure chat gets this right
because we're at the point where if you make a mistake, it's over.
Can it is?
Let's hope you get good placement.
Oh dear.
We have to enhance this one.
How am I even going to get it over there?
It doesn't fit over here.
Guys, it can't go over here.
It has to go on land.
I can't squeeze it anywhere.
Refresh it.
This is an enhanced scenario, I think.
Yeah, it is.
Refresh it again.
Enhance.
Ready?
Be certain about this.
Looks like you want it right up there on Earth.
Kind of right in the middle of those clouds.
Okay.
Pull it back right here.
Now we see the fight between what upgrades to do.
How much money?
535 bucks.
We can only do one of these.
Holy shit.
I'm going to refresh it again because a lot of people clicked up there still.
All right.
Ready?
Three, two, one.
Go for it.
Everyone's freaking out.
All right.
Let's do it.
Is it time for the round to begin?
Oh boy.
All right, guys.
It's time.
Good luck.
Ceramic balloons are made out of clay and they take 10 hits to destroy.
There you go.
41.
You did it.
That was really easy.
Enhance this because I don't know what the hell this is.
This is where the glue guy is right below that.
So click where you need to click.
Do I need to double enhancement?
Holy shit.
I'm going to refresh it again.
If you want the glue, you got to click a little bit further down.
You got to click almost near the bottom of that page.
Click on the cannon if you want the cannon.
You ready?
What the fuck is happening?
Chat is playing Bloons Tower Defense 5.
They've made it to nearly just about the halfway point and it's on hard.
All right.
Looks like it's going to be glue.
Okay.
What would you have me do with this?
Stickier glue.
Okay.
I don't know if there's any more money to do anything else.
900 bucks.
Now and the cannon.
All right.
Cannon is selected.
Frag bombs.
Okay.
That is 600.
There's another 100 bucks, I think.
Couple hundred bucks.
Now the cannon.
Same thing to the other cannon it looks like, right?
Okay.
Is that all you'd like to do?
Strong.
So I'm going to...
Okay.
This is 50-50.
We're going to do this again and we're going to do strong.
All right.
I'll go.
Do we need tacks too?
Are you sure about that?
Hold on.
I'm going to refresh.
Okay.
I'm seeing a lot less people clicking on that.
It's definitely down here.
I don't know.
That's evening out.
I'm going to refresh it again.
If you want tacks, please click over here if you want tacks.
Go can stay over here.
Ready?
Not as extreme as I thought it was going to be.
Okay.
Good luck.
I guess it's doing pretty well.
Nothing's even getting remotely by.
The cannons are syncing with the song.
Are they really?
Pretty stellar job.
I'm not going to lie.
Super monkey.
More towers.
All right.
Oops.
It's this one.
Make your selection.
Which one?
I can't afford the super monkey.
He's too much money.
He's $37.80.
We have $22.79.
Yeah, guys.
That's not going to happen.
I'm going to have to pull this back and see what else your other options are here.
Just go, go, go, go, go, go.
All right.
I hope that wasn't a mistake.
Uh-oh.
Are they going to make it around?
Oh, you guys are golden.
Fucking air level up.
Save.
I can't save the game.
I need to make like an account.
This is one and done, guys.
If you lose, it's over.
All right.
Buck an air.
Now what?
Grape shot.
Okay.
$2400.
What else is your plan?
I'm going to have to enhance with this one.
Or is it just...
Okay.
Do you want this one or this one?
That's the thing here.
How much money is it?
I got to enhance on this one.
Oh, fuck.
I got to take a new picture.
Hold on.
Hold on to your seats for a second.
Right.
New picture incoming.
All right.
There we go.
Which one?
Top one's winning.
It looks like it could be done with both.
Bottom one's winning first so far.
So that one is selected.
Pretty close.
But which one?
Doesn't even seem like a contest.
Night vision goggles.
Allow snipers to detect and shoot camo balloons.
All right.
Looks like people want to do that again.
Same thing on the other one, I think,
is what the consensus will be.
And it is.
They can see the camouflage balloons now.
$1700.
I think that's it.
Good luck.
Yeah, it's on hard.
This is on hard right now.
It's not on easy.
So a couple of mistakes could end the whole thing.
All right.
What now?
Again?
Again, it seems.
All right.
Holy shit.
I'm not fucking around here on this one.
What round is this?
It's getting up there.
Bomb tower.
Unlocked access to the missile launcher.
What now?
Ooh.
Get the super monkey!
I don't even need to pull the thing up.
Look at this.
It's so perfect.
You guys are all over here.
Now here's the really important thing.
I'm going to put the image on the screen.
Where?
Look at that.
And not one person thought otherwise.
That is 100%.
Look at you guys working together.
It's great.
I love it.
So right in the middle there.
Right kind of on the edge.
I see what you're doing here.
All right.
And there he is.
Now what?
$584.
Looks like we're just going to go.
Yes.
Shit load of boats coming in here.
Let's go.
Now the super monkey goes 100 miles per hour.
Damn.
45 of 85.
40 more rounds to go to beat the whole thing.
I don't think anything's getting by this for a while.
Somebody said I've never seen a super monkey before.
You guys are playing really actually very well.
Long round.
All right.
Glue gunner level up.
Corrosive glue.
Monkey apprentice unlocked.
That's all towers are unlocked.
Oh no.
That's not even true.
All right.
We have $3,000 to spend.
Enhance.
Go again please.
Thank you.
Seems to be the cannon.
Because super monkey is down there,
but cannon is over here.
Although I can't.
Yeah.
49, 23.
Cannon it is.
All right.
There's really only one thing to do with the cannon.
And that's missile launcher.
Which is what you guys are clicking on.
Missile launcher complete.
I'm just the RTS narrator in a video game.
Construction complete.
Selecting.
Super monkey upgrade.
Building constructed.
This is pretty split here.
2,600.
Another cannon.
I guess so.
Yeah.
52%.
I think we're doing it again.
Yeah.
Two missile launchers ready to go.
Locked and loaded.
Is this an enhanced scenario?
It can't be.
It has to be this.
Because there's no...
Nothing can be upgraded here.
So it has to be this one.
Put on the red alert OST.
All right.
I'll put on red alert.
OST.
Red alert.
Sniper.
Sour.
What?
How do you pronounce that?
How am I...
Is it sour please?
How are we still playing this?
Because you guys haven't lost.
Louder.
All right.
You ready?
Is that all we can do?
Seems we're pretty conflicted.
50% want to buy something else.
All right.
I think I know what you guys are going to pick here.
A wizard.
All right.
Wizard it is.
But where does it go?
Please let me know.
Where you'd like to put it.
Looks like right...
Right behind the glue gunner.
Zoom it out.
You want it right behind the glue gunner
or do you want it somewhere else?
Here we go.
If you want it right behind the glue gunner there
then keep it there.
Looks like you want it right there.
Like right here.
The thing is here or here.
What's with...
Why down here?
Lower.
All right.
Hold on.
Let's be more...
Can we be more precise on it from here?
Even lower than that.
Like down there.
Move the image up.
So you guys want it here.
Like right there.
All right.
Here we go.
Sure.
Why not?
All right.
I can't take the red alert OST anymore.
We need something calming.
How about...
How about 11 hours of ocean sounds?
All right.
That sounds good.
Now what?
Vessel stop.
All right.
Let's go.
Moab class balloons like Moabs and even larger
require hundreds of hits to pop.
Luckily for you, they tend to move more quickly.
So this is a Moab round.
They gonna get it?
Not even a problem.
Everyone was so concerned about that.
That was not even remotely an issue.
Destroyed.
Super Monkey has now laser blast eyes.
What?
What do you want?
Super Monkey.
Nah, there's not enough money.
Not enough money.
Gonna have to pick something else.
Go again.
Okay.
Oh boy.
No, it's still under control somewhat.
It's still somewhat under control.
Okay.
Is there enough money?
Now everyone's like, all right, I'll do it.
Uh-oh.
Split decision.
There are a lot of people that want to save money.
There's also a lot of people that want to upgrade
the Super Monkey right now.
You still can't do it.
Super Monkey cannot be selected.
It can't be upgraded.
Would you like to try again?
Well, you found a new Monkey.
Buy it during the round?
Well, all right.
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
If you want me to buy the...
Which one?
This one?
If you want me to buy this during the round,
click up here.
Do it up here.
If you do not want me to do that,
then pick a different thing.
You ready?
So click up here if you want me to do it
in the middle of the round or something else.
Damn.
All righty then.
All right.
Middle of the round we go.
Would you like for me to proceed?
Just was making sure.
Let's go.
Need 37.
Strong, strong.
I'm sorry.
That was not selected.
That wasn't the highest percentage.
That's the one I clicked.
All right.
Laser eyes.
I think you guys are going to beat it.
I really think so.
Look at those...
That's the coolest thing ever.
Well, there you go.
Spike a bullet level up.
Triple darts is now available.
2,700 bucks.
Oh, boy.
It is...
There's a lot of...
I don't know.
We're going to have to go in here.
But is there enough?
All right.
You know where they are.
I got to move the image.
All right.
Try to make it precise.
It's got to be fairly precise
wherever you're going to click.
This image is not accurate.
Well, okay.
You definitely want to...
It looks like you're clicking on the catapult.
The spike a bullet.
That's what is being clicked on absolutely.
And I'm sorry to burst your bubble here, guys,
but you cannot buy anything.
No upgrades available.
Oh, what would you like?
Don't sell.
Well, that's currently not was...
Okay.
So it looks like you're selecting...
Are you selecting this one?
Get in there and tell me.
All right.
Yes, that is the one.
It is selected.
Well, what do you want me to do with it?
Triple darts.
Spike a bolt.
Could have two spike a bolts at that point.
Did I sell the super monkey?
No, he's right here.
All right.
We're going to do triple darts.
Almost at round 50, right?
More than that.
Are we going?
All right.
This is moved.
I got to fix this.
Hold on.
That was not...
There we go.
Okay.
Here we go.
This is round...
What does it say to run?
Getting overwhelming here.
We only have 50 lives.
Keep that in mind.
Here comes one.
It's going to get through.
It's going to...
No, it's not.
Lucky.
Here comes the next wave.
I'm sorry.
I doubted you.
I really had a concern there.
Don't doubt us, vessel.
Longer cannons.
All right.
Lots of up...
A lot of upgrades at round 50.
Monkey village.
Monkey village does not attack balloons,
but instead lowers cost of all towers and upgrades by 10%.
It's many useful upgrades that help nearby towers.
Okay.
But that's down even further.
All right.
So if you want me to go down,
we're going to think of another...
Of a solution here.
If you...
Once I open up the list,
if you want me to go down,
you have to...
Let's see here.
Yeah.
If you want me to go down,
you got to click like over...
Like here.
If you want me to click on the down arrow.
All right.
Round 50.
Everyone's clicking over there.
Take another picture.
That's bothering me.
All right.
Let me get another screenshot.
Let me get...
Let me clean this up.
So give me one second.
Enjoy the ocean waves while I clean these images up.
Okay.
There's that.
All right.
Let me get one more for the other ones.
So it doesn't look as terrible.
You know what I'm saying.
What's that?
Let's delete this one.
And delete this one.
Just a moment.
Okay.
Get rid of that.
And this one.
So now this whole thing's up to date.
If it needs to be moved,
it needs to be moved.
You know what I'm saying?
Back to it.
Lord of the Rings soundtrack.
Hold on.
This whole stream is going down.
Play what?
Airport music?
Some Minecraft OST.
Minecraft has an OST.
All right.
Back to it.
What do you want to do?
We do want a tower.
We did it.
I'm going to put everybody to sleep.
Oops.
All right.
Which one?
Oh, fuck.
Whoops.
Sorry.
Looks like another super monkey.
And where will it go?
I wonder.
Should I bring up the...
I wonder if I should...
I think I'm going to have to bring up the zoom.
Yeah.
I got to bring the zoom up.
Hold on.
Ow.
You're side by side.
You want both super monkeys right next to each other?
Is the vessel okay?
I've been better, I think.
All right.
Good placement.
Let's get it there.
Make sure it's correct.
Got to get it right for me.
It's looking like it's right below.
Right in the...
Okay.
I see.
Let me make sure I get this right.
How did I do, chat?
What's next?
Oof.
What do you mean, oof?
That's in a good spot.
What are you talking about?
Do you want me to click on them and upgrade them?
All right.
Super range.
Let's go.
Even more than that.
All right.
Well, hold on a second here.
Okay.
Other super monkey.
Other super range.
Is that what I'm understanding here?
How have you not lost yet?
I'm going to be real honest.
I thought this was going to be like a 12-minute joke.
We've been playing balloons for more than an hour and a half now.
Vessels shall remain silent.
All right.
Fine.
You ready?
Uh-oh.
Nothing's getting by here.
You guys are going to beat this level on hard.
Another Moab coming in.
It does move slow.
Too slow.
Glue splatter is unlocked.
Round 51.
Where to?
All right.
Glue gunner is selected.
You guys will like this now.
It's crazy.
Only $18.99 left.
We are unity.
Just as we start talking about unity.
Uh-oh.
Is this where it all falls apart?
I'm going to refresh it.
So much for the unity.
It seems like we need to go over here.
They're both the same, so I guess it doesn't matter.
This one looks like it has more clicks.
Okay.
The stream title is still Nickelodeon Flash Games.
Actually, let me change that while you guys vote for this.
This is Twitch Plays Bloons TD5.
No, like Chat Plays.
What do we even call this?
Chat Plays Bloons TD5.
Oh yeah.
Chat Clicks Bloons TD5.
That's a good one.
All right.
We're going to get the double shot.
Clicks isn't capitalized.
Whatever.
Let's do it again.
You want them both?
Sure.
Striever is outsourcing entertainment.
All right.
That's that.
51.
I'm going to refresh this again because I want to make sure you guys get this correctly.
Hold on.
You only got $599.
What are you going to do with it?
Oh, okay.
So you want to go over here and click this.
Okay.
This is so dumb.
Are we ready for round 51?
Seems that way.
Here we go.
So many clicks.
More level up.
Cluster bombs are accessed.
You got 3,500 bucks.
Music?
I muted it.
All right.
I'm done with Minecraft.
I don't want to hit the Minecraft OST anymore.
How about...
Hold on.
Okay.
A lot of indecision here but mostly we're going over to here.
Can't even upgrade them.
You don't have enough money.
It's better for you to sleep a little more.
Thanks.
I'll do it.
John, I'm sorry.
I didn't catch your name.
Okay.
Where are you from?
I'm from the U.S.
What do you want me to do here?
I can't do anything with this.
I'm on holiday.
I have it selected.
What do you want to know?
What's your phone number?
Could I take your phone number?
May I have your address?
Are you on Facebook?
Who do you live with?
I live on my own.
This is a real creepy lady.
I live with my friends.
How old are you?
I'm 30.
What the fuck?
When's your birthday?
It's June 16th.
Excuse me.
Do you know where the bookstore is?
No, I don't.
I'm sorry.
How can I get to the train station from here?
Walk.
Excuse me.
Could you tell me how to get to the bus station?
Ride your bike.
Can you show me the way to the post office?
Take a right.
Excuse me.
Where is the hospital?
In front of you.
Can you show me on the map?
Right here.
Look.
What's the best way to get to the airport?
Take an Uber.
What's the fastest way to the airport?
Get an Uber.
And it's quick.
How far is it to the stadium from here?
15 miles.
What street is this?
This is...
Is this the way to the police station?
No.
You're on your way to the...
Is there a supermarket near here?
There are.
Can you give me directions to the gas station?
Yes.
If you take a left at the end of this road and you go straight...
Go straight on.
Yes, go straight ahead.
That's right.
Turn right at the crossroads.
Yeah.
Well, no, that's not correct.
Keep going straight ahead for about 500 meters.
No, I don't know why you're doing this.
You asked me for directions.
The bus station will be on your left.
Well, that's where you should go, then.
You should go to the bus station and get on the bus.
You're going the wrong way.
I'm not driving a car.
It's about one mile...
We are not in a car together.
What do you do?
What do you do for a living?
Online video.
I've got a part-time job.
Nice.
Where do you work?
I work from home.
Me too.
Hey, we got that in common.
I work in a factory.
How do you work from home in a factory?
What is your occupation?
I work as a doctor.
I'm looking for a job.
I'm a teacher.
I'm not working at the moment.
Oh, you've lost your mind, Lynn.
I'm unemployed.
I do the paperwork.
I have my own business.
Do you like your job?
Yes, it's great.
I completely agree.
I agree, too.
You're absolutely right.
I agree with you entirely.
Do what you like.
Have fun doing it.
I totally agree with you.
And, you know, if you make some money, make some money.
You know what I'm saying?
I agree more.
Right.
Exactly.
I know, right?
Absolutely.
That's what I was trying to say.
You're right.
Me too.
I know.
That's what I just said.
I agree.
Me.
I see exactly what you mean.
Yes.
That's exactly what I mean.
We both think so alike.
There is no doubt about it.
No, there isn't.
I agree up to a point.
Up to?
Hold on a second here.
Hold on.
That's partly true.
No, that's...
I don't know if I agree with you right there.
That may be true.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I see your point, but...
Well, I don't know how this turned so poorly,
but I don't agree with you.
That seems obvious.
That's a dumb thing to say.
I'm not so sure about it.
Yeah, I'm not entirely sure about this.
I don't agree.
No, neither do I.
I don't agree with you.
I don't fucking agree with you.
I totally disagree.
Yeah, you're an idiot.
An imbecile.
I'm sorry, but I disagree.
No, you should not be trusted ever.
Absolutely not.
No, you get out of my house.
How about that?
I invited you over here.
You took the fucking bus here, lady.
That's not right.
Yeah, and you asked for directions,
and I tried to give you directions.
That's not always true.
No, yes it is,
because I gave you directions earlier
and you didn't care.
Yes, it was what happened,
so stop fucking interrupting me.
That's not true.
That is what happened,
so stop fucking interrupting me.
No way.
Yes, it is.
You knocked on my door,
and you asked for fucking directions
to a bus-
Do you understand?
Are you following me?
Do you understand what I mean?
Are we ready for the next-
Are you ready for the next-
What are we doing now?
Is this tax or is this go?
I'm not sure.
All right, you want this?
Looks like we're gonna go.
Here comes the next round.
This fits pretty well.
You guys have made an unstoppable team here.
They can't do anything.
We gotta go faster.
Ooh, what happened?
Pretty good.
What are we doing now?
Super Monkey?
Are we doing Laser 2.0?
I can really start to follow
your guys' mindset here.
It's great.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Wait, wait, wait.
Have people seen Other Monkey?
There's-
I can't do Other Monkey.
This is the only one we can do.
Okay, make sure we're sure about this
because I'm seeing some descent here.
Here we go.
I completely disagree with you.
I'm not so sure about that.
The vessel is starting to turn into a leader.
It's time to revolt.
All right.
You guys got a chance to double check
to see if you want to do it.
And here you go.
Good luck.
Need to anoint a new vessel.
This stream keeps getting worse.
What?
Why?
The stream's getting worse.
I already know what you guys want me to do.
Plasma.
Plasma blasts.
Plasma vaporizes everything it touches.
That's it.
I can't afford anything else.
You guys-
That's it.
You're done.
What is going on over here?
What is happening over here?
Why are people losing their minds over here?
And this-
37% of you don't agree.
All right.
Let's go.
Look at that plasma ray.
We've only done five rounds in 30 minutes.
Because the rounds are getting more difficult.
They need to have more deliberation.
Buccaneer, level up.
Super Monkey, level up.
56.
Where to?
Okay, I can't take this anymore.
How about epic?
Put on RuneScape music.
RuneScape music?
I've never even played RuneScape.
It has music.
All right, here you go.
All right, looks like Buccaneer.
I'm gonna refresh it just because everyone was clicking on other stuff.
Here we go.
Can we please play RuneScape after this?
This is it for tonight.
All right, the people have spoken.
Three, two, one, bring it up.
The other one too?
Longer cannon.
Three, two, one, here it comes.
Uh, looks like Super Monkey.
Which one?
Could be either.
I think it's this one though.
It could be really either one of them.
Doesn't matter which one.
This seems to have more votes.
Are you guys sure?
Is this Yoshi's story?
Okay, time to start.
Let's go.
Nothing even stands a chance.
Did you see that shit?
Nothing even stands a chance right now.
It's 57.
I was at level 60.
It's just too easy for you guys.
You guys are making this look simple.
All right, we're going again.
Masterfully done, guys.
Balloon Dissolver for a glue gunner.
Moab Mauler.
And rank up Mortar Tower.
Rank 17.
There it is.
So here's the down arrow.
You get the village, the banana farm, and Mortar Tower.
Level 58.
I got faith in you guys.
Looks like it's split between...
I feel bad for all the people that want to upgrade the wizard so bad.
Boy, they have never had an opportunity to.
All right, we are opening up.
Ooh, one, two, three, four.
We got 14, 12, 11, 15.
Look at all the percentages here.
Half of the whole entire stream right now does not want to do this.
But that's what happens, man.
We got to stick with what we're doing.
Okay, let's open it up.
Which tower do you want?
And again, keep in mind, remember, if you want me to go down,
you need to select over here.
Ready?
Jesus.
Yeah, over here.
If you want me to click the down arrow,
but then we run into another problem where I need this.
I'm going to have to do this in a different way.
All right, so it looks like I'm going down.
But hold on here.
So let's go down.
So if you want the village, click up here.
If you want the banana farm, click up here.
If you want the Mortar Tower, click down here.
You understand?
Go.
Looks like it's going to be the village.
By a lot, actually.
So, all right.
Where do you want it?
Where do you want the village?
Let's see, do we need to zoom in for this?
We might not even need to.
You guys want it right in here, but I don't think I can fit it here.
It's too crowded.
I could get it right there.
Let's enhance.
Where do you want it?
There's a second Super Monkey though.
Just be aware of that.
Below the first Super Monkey.
The stream will never end.
All right, right next to the bottom left of the glue gunner.
That's close.
That's so close.
I'm going to refresh it again.
All right, you ready?
Go for it again.
Well, you've spoken.
It's going above.
So, right here.
That's as close as I can get it.
There.
Anything else?
Why is Runescape 07 music playing?
That's a great question.
Somebody wrote it in chat and I clicked on it.
I think we have to zoom in for this.
Yeah, try it again.
So, that's the second Super Monkey, right?
From my understanding.
So, you guys are selecting the second Super Monkey.
Or is it the glue?
All right, if you want this Super...
I'm going to have to take another picture.
This is the slowest stream I'm trying.
It's hard.
I'm going to have to go more zoom on this.
All right, show me.
Remember the Super Monkey.
There's another Super Monkey down there, right?
Yeah, there you go.
A wizard it is.
After like 30 rounds of people wanting to upgrade.
There's only one wizard upgrade.
I'm pretty sure I know which one it is.
What the fuck did I do to this?
All right, there's only one wizard upgrade.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait a minute.
What's going on here?
Sell the wizard.
Holy shit.
Okay, I thought that's surprising.
Might be strong.
Yeah, you're right, it might be.
But not even going to need to see it.
2250 bucks.
Where are we off to?
This seems like a go scenario.
Round 58.
Like the Glover soundtrack?
How do you even know what that game is?
Is it a video that I made 10 years ago?
I never made a video on Glover.
I don't think I did.
What the hell is happening?
What was that?
Why did they go back?
That was the wizard power makes them go backwards?
Now I know why everybody wanted to vote for that.
I'm going to sneeze and I'm sorry about it.
I have a mute button, I forgot.
All right, I'm going to turn off the Castlevania 2 music.
And let's get...
There's a lot of...
I don't know what people want in here.
FTL soundtrack?
I've never even played FTL.
Okay, zooming in.
There's a lot of people clicking here.
So try it again.
Looks like we're going over here to the left.
Doesn't matter which one.
I can only upgrade the left one.
So left one it is because the right one cannot be upgraded.
So left one, which one do you want?
Flash bomb or double shot?
Flash bomb is very expensive.
Sometimes throws a flash bomb that stuns balloons in a large radius.
Hopefully you spent that money wisely.
Can't do anything else there.
Round 59.
All right, let's go.
We're going to be here for hours.
I don't know.
It could go either way because from 60 and beyond.
I think is when it's going to start to get actually very difficult.
We won.
It's time to stop.
We can't stop now.
That would be a huge mistake.
100% want to go right to the village.
86%.
This is probably like 70% right here.
All right.
Beacon increased attack range of all towers within the monkey village.
Okay, where to next?
Tactical hive mind.
What is it being clicked on over here?
My special agent.
I'm not sure if this is the super monkey or the glue gunner.
Let me go ahead and zoom it in.
Which one is this?
Which one are you clicking on here?
Glue gunner, okay.
He is selected.
What would you like to do with them?
All right.
Balloon dissolver.
$877.
Don't think this is not about what you guys can do.
Good luck.
What is that?
Okay, that's the super moab.
The super moab turns into five regular moabs.
Just decimated.
Absolutely decimated.
That could have been really scary, but it wasn't at all.
Not at all.
Again?
Go again?
Sure thing.
Let's go.
This is the coolest tower.
Getting carried through balloons.
Hey, look at this shit.
They can't even do anything.
Apprentice level up lightning bolt.
62 of 85.
4,600 bucks.
And we are going to...
Looks like it wants...
I think this is a living entity.
Okay, it wants to select the wizard, I think.
Yeah, this is definitely on the wizard.
This is probably 70 or 80% of the vote over here.
And I guarantee it's the zap.
It is.
Would you look at that?
Unleash the power of lightning to zap many balloons at once.
What else would you like to do?
Oh, this is getting interesting.
Okay, now we're buying a special agent.
Not yet, no.
Start...
Looked like it for a second.
Okay.
This is...
Epic range is the only thing to buy here.
Even bigger range.
74%.
73%.
Okay.
Anything else?
Chat sucks.
What?
Here's round 62.
No, I didn't say that.
I was just quoting what somebody said.
Music change, I'll do it after this.
Nothing can even get by.
This is probably going to go all the way.
They can't even come down the first lane.
Excellent placement here, guys.
For real.
Nice work.
Sun god for the super monkey.
It is said that balloons who doth touch the sun
shall be cleansed and then there shall be peace.
Sun god.
Monkey fort.
Curses popping power by one.
And then dartling gun.
Darts like a machine gun.
All right, guys.
What's the plan here?
66% of you want to go in this area here.
I'm going to zoom it in.
Remember the super monkey is down here.
Click down there if you want to.
Because I don't know exactly where everyone wants to go.
And then remember there's a fort up here too.
You get the missile launch, the fort is up to the top right.
And then below the first super monkey is the other super monkey.
Understand?
All right, make it happen.
Fort?
All right, fort it is.
Fortnite.
There's only one thing to buy.
I'm going to assume that's what you guys want.
It is.
So this has increased the popping power of all the towers nearby by one.
1971.
Okay, pretty good.
Round 63 incoming.
Wait, we need new music.
Okay.
You guys need to seriously like listen up.
I want everybody to get up for this one.
I want you all to stand the fuck up.
Everyone get up.
Oh, come on.
Get it up for me.
I'll set you down.
I got four words for you.
I love this company.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Okay.
Good work.
64 out of 85.
Was that an office joke?
No.
You guys have never seen that video?
Come on.
It's like original, original meme status.
Come on, guys.
And then what?
I got four words for you.
Love this company.
I don't know why I did that.
I'm not sure what the reason to do that was, but I did it.
All right.
Where are we going?
That is such old shit.
Whatever.
Which one are we going to?
You guys are going to beat this fucking whole thing.
Looks like we're going right to the glue gunner.
This is going to take us two hours.
All right.
Glue gunner it is, but no, it's not glue gunner.
That can't, there's no, you can't buy anything.
Look, glue upgrade is, this path is closed and this one's rank 27.
I'm sorry, guys, but you can't do that right now.
Now what?
Nothing here?
The only thing that you can possibly do here in this whole area is you got either,
your options are wizard or super monkey.
You don't have enough money or enough rank to do anything else.
If you want wizard on this next refresh, click down here.
You can do both?
325, you can do both.
Okay.
No, I get you.
Wizard upgrade.
There it is.
And super upgrade.
But do you guys actually want me to do this?
You want that second super monkey?
People are going down here.
Now that all the people that got their wizard upgrade,
they're like, no, no, no, no, no, fuck that.
We're doing an agent.
That's what happens, man.
Okay.
I have no idea what any of this shit is.
Turtle.
Bloomsday device.
Mirror.
How much?
Okay.
Close it.
Obviously.
I don't have any money.
I only have zero dollars.
You guys found the microtransactions
and you immediately close the window.
I love it.
And that's like, all right.
You know, I guess we could do the upgrade.
Okay.
Fine.
Round 64.
Is it just only going to be moabs now?
Cripple moab.
Okay.
That doesn't sound good.
Let me see the general direction that you guys want to go on this one.
Let's put on...
Where's the music?
I'm going.
I'm working on it.
Spore?
Spyro?
Katamari?
I don't know.
I'm going to play that, by the way.
Let's get a sneak peek of Katamari Damacy
because I'm definitely going to play the remade one.
This has one of the best soundtracks of any video game ever.
All right.
Where are we going?
Over here.
Right into the...
We don't have enough money for this.
Sniper can't be upgraded.
This can't be upgraded.
None of this over here can be upgraded, guys.
You don't have very many choices.
Your only option to upgrade anything is down the bottom here to the boomerang.
So try again.
Here we go.
65.
Do not sell the boomerang.
It's not my decision to make.
Sorry.
This is the best song of the whole album.
This is the best one.
Did it.
66 out of 85.
I am impressed.
Oh, boy.
All right.
We got...
It's either these people wanting the super monkey upgrade plasma or jungle drums.
I'm gonna...
Sorry, all those of you that want to go over here.
I'm sorry about that, but it's all split over here.
All right.
If you want super monkey, put your vote down here.
Everyone else, do what you were doing before.
Good luck.
Looks like we're doing the village.
All right.
That's the only up here to do.
Jungle drums.
Inspire neighbor Tauzu to attack faster.
And...
Oh, shit.
This is...
Whoa.
Hold on here.
This is...
I think people want another tower.
Is that...
All right.
Another tower coming up.
Remember, if you want to scroll down, you got to go over here.
Holy shit.
Okay, we're going down.
So what do you guys want here?
I need like two screenshots.
All right.
If you want monkey village, go over here.
Monkey village, click up here.
A banana farm, up here.
Water tower, down here.
Dartling gunner, down here.
And if you want this, then go up here.
Like actually just put it here.
So again, just think of it in the corners, right?
Monkey village, up here.
Banana farm, up here.
Water tower, down here.
Gatling gun, down here.
And if you want the spike factory, here.
One, two, three.
Holy fuck.
You guys want a spike factory?
Nobody wants anything else.
I have 75 IQ.
These instructions are confusing me.
All right.
Looks like we're doing dart spike factory.
Spike factory it is.
And where the hell is this even going to go?
Over here.
66 of 85, coming up.
Looks like it's going right here.
Okay.
I don't think you have any money for anything else.
Maybe not.
Who knows?
No?
You ready?
Okay.
Pick up 66.
$2,700.
You guys really are such gamers.
I'm shocked.
Cluster bomb tower, level up.
67 of 85, you're very close.
Less than 20.
Now, some of you want to go,
and some of you want to upgrade.
Very conflicted in here of what to upgrade.
Then I hate to burst everybody's bubble over here,
but can't afford anything.
Here we go.
67, almost at 69.
Oh, I see what you mean.
Okay.
Never mind.
Attacks super duper fast.
And super monkey level up.
Robo monkey.
Radar scanner.
These are upgrades that I don't think even half of the people
that have played this game have ever seen.
4,800 bucks.
Should have enough to do a couple things here.
82% look like they want to go up here.
That's a large number up here.
Excuse me, Vessel, please increase volume.
Increasing volume.
Job done.
Okay.
Yeah.
Getting the radar.
Radar scanner allows all towers in this radius
to be able to detect and target camo bloons.
Let's hope it's worth it.
68.
Oh, big boy, big boy, big boy, big boy, big boy.
That was nothing.
69.
What's the deal?
Uh, cannon?
50-50 on the cannon here.
All right.
Looks like we're doing the cannon.
Yeah, that's what people want.
Attacks super duper fast.
Excuse me, Vessel, what round are we on?
We are on round number 69.
He said it.
I said the number 69.
Come on now.
What the hell is this?
You're at the final 15, chat.
Final 15 of Bloons.
Super hard tower defense map number three in the list.
Tack shooter upgrade tier four.
Ring of fire.
All of the towers have been unlocked.
You guys are in...
This is the end game.
Peter, Peter.
We're at the end game now, Peter.
I am actually very, very interested
in how you guys handle the last 10 rounds.
There's gonna be a lot of in-fighting.
New tower.
Okay.
Remember, if you want me to go down,
you know where to click.
All right.
For this one, I actually can't say them.
Tax.
All right.
So here's what's gonna happen with this, okay?
You want me to go down.
I'm gonna scroll this down.
But just pretend that this is here.
You know what I mean?
Replace all these icons
with the ones that are in front of you right now.
So with that being said,
imagine that it's all scrolled down.
Just replace the icons on the right
with the ones that are in the middle.
Good luck.
So this is monkey sub.
It's this one.
Some of you guys are helping.
It's great.
This one.
Remember, it's this one.
Okay.
Monkey's up.
What do you want it?
Over here.
We just need the king of the cosmos
doing his record scratch talking.
This is as close as I can get it right here.
That's right in the middle.
It can't go on land.
So it can't go over here.
It has to go either.
No, it can't even go over here.
It has to go here or here.
Reset it.
What's going on up here?
I can't fit it there.
It's got to be right here.
The one little spot which is right here.
This is the only spot it can go.
I'm putting it down.
God damn it.
Hold on.
It's too close.
Too close to call here.
Show me.
All right.
Right down there.
You got it.
It's been placed.
Thanks for the clarification.
More.
What else can we do?
Can't do anything else.
All right.
Final 15.
Good luck.
Speed it up.
I don't even need to see this bullshit.
This easy mode.
Super Monkey Fan Club.
Converts up to 10 nearby dart monkeys into super monkeys.
If it's an ability, I can't click them.
Balloon Liquifier.
Summon Whirlwind.
71.
Wizard, huh?
So many people saw a tornado
and they're just like,
give us the tornado.
You got it.
Tornado it is.
Anything else?
No, I can't do this.
I don't have the money to do this.
I don't have the real money currency income thing.
Bing, bing, bing, bing.
Lighten up the whole map here.
Let's go.
It's a small delay vessel.
Large piles of spikes per shot.
72.85.
Almost in the top 10.
Vessel music change to Hotline Miami please.
Sure thing.
And it seems that we're going to be upgrading the
spike generator.
Bigger stacks.
Generates larger piles of spikes per shot.
In one, two.
Okay, 72.
Wait, hold on.
No, hold on.
Just wait a second.
Okay, let's go to...
Let's go.
End game.
I did not think you guys were going to make it this far.
I would be visibly impressed
if you guys actually beat this whole thing on hard.
All right.
There's actually quite a few options at the moment.
He thinks we're incompetent?
No, I didn't say that.
I just didn't think this was going to be...
All of chat is doing this together.
Absolutely remarkable.
So you guys want to do plasma.
Vessel please skip one song.
Skipping ahead seven minutes.
All right.
There it is.
Plasma.
No more money.
Smoothening out here.
Jesus.
This is not even hard now.
You guys have done too good of a job.
And everybody just wants to go.
Let's go.
Fuck it.
Final 10 rounds coming up.
Can you guys beat the Galaxy level on hard?
Unbelievable.
Again, they say.
Again.
Do it again, they say.
75.
Nobody can even match your strength.
Holy shit.
Again.
You sure?
But we're in the top 10 here.
You sure that's not a mistake?
People are starting to feel a little bit of the heat here.
It's climbing.
All right.
Okay.
That's the sniper you're looking at there.
So which upgrade do you want for the sniper?
Semi-automatic or 5-0?
Look at the percentage of just...
No!
Go!
Save money!
Got to listen.
Okay.
Down to 5200 bucks.
Again, deadly precision, extreme accuracy, and muzzle velocity
cause up to 18 layers of bloons to be popped.
All right.
Well, here we go.
That's out of reach at this point.
Where to now?
All right.
You guys are ready.
Let the games begin.
That was five seconds.
77 of 85.
Again, be careful.
Wasn't there a video game that came out with the narrator that had a low voice
and there was a party of four people
and they went and they trekked through dangerous dungeons
and there was a big warning.
They were bowed over confidence being a very slow, slow bleed.
Be careful here.
Uh-oh!
Is this the end?
Could this be the end?
No, no, no.
That was a little shaky there.
Oh, fuck.
Uh-oh.
This is the first time we've seen it go around that far.
Uh, Monkey Town.
Faster Production Spike Factory.
And, uh, Sniper Monkey Tier 4.
78 of 85.
What are you gonna do?
Hmm.
And just like that.
Oh, boy.
The indecision here.
Well, it looks like it's this one.
Nope.
It's this one.
Yep.
Please select which one it is.
Or is it both?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, slow down, slow down.
Hold on, hold on, here.
Hold on.
Okay, hold on.
Let's do this again.
Clear your thoughts a little bit here.
What do you want me to click on?
With clarity.
You know, with clarity.
Oh, Jesus.
This is so torn apart.
What am I doing down here?
What's this for?
I can't do anything down here.
So...
Alright, wait...
Hold on, wait, wait.
We get the fifth.
this is too important we're gonna do this again everybody hold on everybody take a deep breath
everybody hold on a second okay you ready just do it with me here you feel it everyone's relaxed
now okay fresh clean slate no music no sound just you your thoughts and the half empty
Kraft macaroni and cheese microwavable bowl that's cold by now it's late and you thought
you were gonna help you were more hungry than you actually were and now you have to how do
I throw it away that sucks though I don't want to throw that shit away it's like food please choose
what you would like me to click with a clean slate oh all right this is where we are but
why are we clicking this why are you guys collectively clicking the village it does
what he said I don't know what okay let's try this again no one's ever made it this
far that's why we don't know what to do
no one's ever made it we're the only ones to ever make it to 78 okay it seems that chat
has moved from here to here that is the consensus that is what I've just clicked
because that is what the consensus is okay now wait a minute there are upgrades here or
they sell it or the what do you want me to do sell is in the lead by a lot I love the
people that are over here that are just like no just get us out of here what did you say for
the sun god I'm sorry guys say goodbye all right now what now you want to go over here who else
is going to are you sacrificing more people you can't do anything with this guy what do you want
to do with him 42 percent of you want me to click on this super monkey what's going on here
that's by a very large margin I have to click it now what you want me to sell the
super monkey here for $12,527 you guys you're gonna have to do you guys have to deliberate
on this for a little bit no no no I love this so much this is so interesting to me
I'm getting a click and go by a majority at this point okay here we go this is 78
sells the tower and then laughs mid-round what do you want to do mid-round what do you want me to do
mid-round what do you want me to do mid-round I don't know what you want to do show me on
screen I don't know what you mean what do you want to do show me this you want to click this
right now sell it okay got it okay okay holy shit nice work I don't know there's very
much many other things hold on don't go that fast what should I do what do I do what do I
don't know what to do some might get through no we're okay bionic boomer that's like my new
wrestling name boomerang thrower leveled up okay guys 79 of 85 you're almost to the last
five levels okay by a majority what would you like me to do with them oh look at the spread
here sell sell don't sell sell don't sell don't do it sell it do it I have no say in the
matter I'm just a guy look this is back in the fucking 20s when you used to call the
operator hello this is the operator yes can you please connect me to a bob elbertson please
okay sure and then I'm just I'm moving the stick over and plugging it in I'm the operator I
don't have nothing to do with this you guys are you guys are calling uh you guys are calling
the stream right now I'm not doing anything okay oh boy this is getting what the hell is
happening right now what if you're just spamming why did it go to that setting all right try
again again again again again again again again again again again again again again again
looks like it's the upgrade people have spoken thank you now what are we am I clicking on this
or this is what you guys want you want them both because this this is very clearly people are
trying to click on this oh yeah good luck after this round it's the last five levels okay let me
skip ahead in the hotline Miami soundtrack I don't know what music is going to be on but
here it is good luck play the music in max volume no no max volume you need to be able
to hear me in case we need to communicate I think you guys are gonna do it 80 cannon ship
adds a powerful independently firing cannon to the buccaneer final five 38 50 looking like
they want to go this way oh I'm so sorry for those of you that don't want to do this but
this is where we're going and you want me to buy the robo okay I think that's the only thing
you can do 80 last five levels the last like three hours has culminated into this
you guys don't even need the luck white hot spikes you guys don't even need the luck 81
this is a 50 50 shot here oh shit I don't know what to do what's a sun god I know really reset
of what I can't you want me to that's not fair there okay I'm home let me just tell you
something here if you get there there are 4 000 people watching and there are 829 votes right
now I voted I voted I voted well if you want to do your part and you want to make sure that
this gets done correctly then gosh darn it I clicked the screen I I voted
okay that's it which one are we doing wait hold on a portion of you want to sell this
I thought it well you both could is a possibility this is white hot spikes
cuts through lead okay reset it am I buying the other one or are we going
and I gotta let auto outside so give me a moment after I pick this
and this is what's gonna happen here so okay uh vote while I let auto outside perfect all
right 80 is 81 or 82 this is 81 spitting out these fire spikes now that's kind of cool
new song I gotta have a perfect song for round 85 sabotage supply lines for a ninja monkey
eye of the tiger this is definitely the wizard what am I supposed to do with the wizard
there's no upgrades for the wizard oh shit okay I see what you're doing
it's either sell the wizard or we're going choose wisely no it's time to go 82 three
more after this no no no yeah this is 82 oh they're not getting through they're not
getting through you gotta have some decisions to make here 83 supply drop moab assassin
or monkey intelligence bureau okay good luck well you guys vote for this I need to find
a better song acid bass no I'm not gonna play megalo what's it called megalovania play the
cleric no oh thank you for bloodborne we're gonna play a song but I don't want to say the name
of the song because it's like a spoiler but for those of you that want to play bloodborne
just know that I'm about to say the name of one of the bosses and it's a pretty big reveal
so just just turn off your whole house just like turn it off go flick up put the main
switch okay so I'm gonna play uh ready it's gonna it's gonna happen now I'm gonna say it now
I'm gonna play Ludwig the holy blade his theme song for the final round
and we're gonna do it I'm not gonna speed that round at all all right what are we clicking on
up here looks like 57 would like to go to the village but what do you want to do here
no no no no oh wait a minute hold on okay hold on it's the cannon you can't do anything
with the cannon I need to enhance all right you know where everything is right so make sure
you pick the right spot you guys know where everything is enhance but see I had it right
you guys were selecting the village this picture is like an hour and a half old
I know okay that's the village take a look so what the hell are we doing here wait why
everybody's so indecisive no the village no no no a cannon no sell it sell the fucking
thing uh okay uh another decision has been made we're going over here now uh please select
from this list if you want to go down remember you gotta go over there this chat is the new
york stock exchange floor is going up is it going down buy it is it going up buy it is
it going down sell it sell it at the very bottom and then buy it again all right another
cannon sure thing uh what the hell do you want to do with this where on earth do you want
to put this cannon that's not okay over here looks like right here 42 47 right here it can
it can only go like right here somewhere right there there it is is it in range of the village
it should be right I can't go over here though it cannot physically be over here
yeah no it can't it has to be over here there we go right there right there that's right there
we're good we're good we're good we're good it's in the range reset what do you mean reset
why is everybody freaking out what now you change your mind what it was you guys just were pointing
down here it was in range before what the fuck okay well now it there it is congratulations on
your new uh cannon ten thousand dollars to upgrade we're gonna buy this one I'm just
buying all of them right side right side right side again you know you guys can't even afford
this okay now and this one that's all that it can be done the 12% of you clicking sell you guys
okay whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa hey what's what is going on here what why do you want me to
do this oh strong strong strong strong strong okay okay it's on strong so this is the final
three songs here's what you're gonna get bing all right here we go bring it home guys
all right now shut the fuck up sonic rank up rank 22 84 of 85 while I get the next song ready
what would you guys like to do in your incredibly overpowered uh build here what can I play uh
another tower let's see what the next tower is gonna be adding just you guys are just beating
this game while it's down you want another tower another super monkey holy shit okay guys
where the hell do you want them down how the I can't put them down here
where is this oh boy um all right so the very bottom I can't put them here it's very difficult
I can't really find a space for him to go this is the only more this is the only piece
he can fit because he can't fit up here no he can't fit up here guys this is the only
spot where he can go is right here there it is now what left path left path now you
sure about this I'm gonna give you one more chance okay and then uh can't afford this next
one second to last level of balloons td5 hard on galaxy level then do the other side too
okay and said it's strong okay all right the second to last song isn't gonna be
hold on let me make sure that's there okay what second to last song
hmm dancing queen like the by ABBA that's what you want okay like that that's what you guys want
apparently here we go there's only one more round after this they're not getting through
oh yes they are oh wait a minute hold on should I buy tax should I get tax ready for this
no they have to go around twice that's it final level last level easy sell what are we
selling in here everybody's freaking out which what are we doing here we're selling the blue
guy for the sun god don't sell hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
precise precise clicking here please this is the person we're selling I need precise clicks
enhance air I'm gonna enhance enhance enhance all right I need precise clicks from you guys
right now so you're clicking that's the super monkey underneath that's what you're
clicking on right this is this is our before and after fucking weight gain photo
okay so let's see that's the one you want to get rid of okay I understand I'm telling
them this guy right here is the one you want to sell that's what everyone was clicking on
what do you mean no what what are you talking about no no what are you talking about you
sell him why is this changing your mind so quickly set him to strong
okay he's on strong now what the hell do you want me to do what do you guys
now sell him now we're not ready for this we're not ready are we ready I'm gonna reset it just
to make sure everyone knows what the fuck they're doing reset okay where do you want me to click
what do we sell I don't know I don't know what you it's time to go only 35% of you are clicking
over there get ready final level level 85 and I'm just gonna buy a shitload of tax
you guys ready are you sure here we go let's go bring them on let's go get them blow it up
oh what what is this who gives a shit I don't even have a Facebook I can't click that
god damn it fine I'll do it hold on I'm doing it this is such a fucking sponsored tweet
all right hold on let's turn it off turn it off turn how does okay so I completed
bloons tower defense five level 85 at five on the hard difficulty play your own game now
at www.ninjakiwi.com right it's just that's how that's when you share it that's what happens
right what's the name of this level people that aren't at this stream are gonna think
that I just fucking accidentally tweeted out me playing balloons no I did no you did it
we we completed we did it I'm just taking all the credit
I'm keeping it in his eye that's so funny to me I completed level bloons tower defense five
level uh on the map what's this map called on the map space trucking and then I have to put
like a smiley face like an absolutely like this ad this was not supposed to go on my Twitter
like I this is just like a shitty ad that I accidentally clicked uh how about like a crown
or something I don't know oh well I think I like a space like a solar system or something
like space there we go there's like an earth I completed bloons tower defense five on the map
space trucking earth on hard yeah on the on the hard difficulty I completed bloons tower defense
five on the map space trucking difficulty level hard and then I have like an oh wow like oh
my god I'm not gonna do a puke face okay call your mother and tell her difficulty level
hard difficulty I fucked it up did I there I clicked there share I shared it
I completed it well that was uh that sure was something and that is where I'm gonna end the
stream we deserve to be paid all right can you spell out can you guys do like a can you guys
put a heart on the screen come on try it I want to see a heart for how like fun that was and
how great of a community you guys are you know what I mean uh well that didn't work
IQ heart all right try it again there it is oh holy shit nice work well that's uh that's
gonna be it for tonight guys um thanks for watching thanks for sticking around it was a
long stream I didn't think it was gonna be that long but that was that was really fun
thanks for joining us uh the plan is I'm planning on streaming tomorrow
I might play smash brothers tomorrow although I don't know let me see time for more
akinator let's do this again sometime now that was a blast one more game now of balloons tower
defense that was like three and a half hours there is a possibility that I do not stream
tomorrow and there's one particular reason for it but uh I will probably I'm trying to think
if I can get that the thing that I need to get done if I can get that done and stream
at the same time or stream afterwards I was planning on going two days so tentatively we'll
be live tomorrow around the same time around like three or four pacific 3 p.m pacific something
like that and if not then I will definitely let you guys know here and in discord so
thank you everybody for watching we're going to take this off the screen now
I'm gonna play with more extensions I feel like there's a lot to be done with them
but have a fantastic rest of your night if you're taking off see you possibly tomorrow
and if not tomorrow then absolutely on monday so let us go out of there into here hey
look at that let's close these windows and we had uh quite a few bits and subs today
so for the purposes of it being fairly late I'm gonna try to go through these as quick as
possible thank you everybody for subscribing and everybody for paying money to stream you're
fucking amazing thank you see you in the next day or two take care let us click fine you
can click if you want enjoy your clicking so thanks to uh thank you sticks renegade for
the one dollar sing flash by queen I don't know how that song goes uh even we thanks
for the one dollar they say hey German big fan uh I just want to let you know I've been
signed by a record label and I sampled your voice for one of my songs the label is doing
a vinyl pressing which will be distributed worldwide just wanted to let you know that
you're gonna be on it give me a shout if you want to know more holy shit uh yeah what
do you what what song they still yeah when we sue him no hey what no don't
well I'm not gonna say what are you talking about you guys are just clicking
on such a random things I love it uh but thanks a lot man that sounds really interesting
uh I can now add people on discord which I couldn't figure out and do that before
if you want to message one of the mods and let them know what your discord name is or
tell you one of the mods what the song is or what it is and I can get it relayed to me for sure
but that's kind of that's pretty crazy man thank you uh thank you hike for the 10 bucks
sippy cup fund I'm telling you right now I'm never going to drink out of a glass ever
again thank you for the 10 bucks thank you devakitty for the one dollar good job dumping
coffee on your PC I fucking I was so angry you guys have no idea just how upset I was
earlier I was fucking furious I dumped a whole coffee without taking one sip all over
my new desk and all of my shit it was horrible and that was an hour before the stream started
I was gonna start the stream an hour before it started and I got all fucked up but it's all
right it's clean now pin man coming in with 10 community subs a bunch of people gave community
subs tonight and I want to make sure I recognize them so we'll get to them as well
but thank you pin man for 10 community subs thank you really appreciate that 10 community
subs coming in uh thank you also to uh yeah uh I have uh uh divas thanks for the three bucks
divas gives three dollars every single stream never says anything your continued monetary
support every single fucking stream man thank you so much a lot of you guys give money every
single stream thank you really appreciate that no message from divas but um thank you man
also thank you too it's time for slime for the 12 dollars and 50 cents buy him talking about
the pokemon socks yeah I will smelly boy thanks for the one dollar came in like 30 minutes late
why are you buying Pikachu socks uh it's a long story it's kind of a long story uh
tabarin thanks for the five dollars tabarin buy yourself something nice like Pikachu socks
I would say let's go ahead and refresh this why not twitch plays with your finances yeah
uh unfair unfair order thanks for the 10 dollars unfair order this is for the socks thank you
really appreciate it 10 bucks uh the nimble pickle thanks for the one dollar more socks
I will wear them Todd Florida thanks for the four dollars Todd we need more socks
Lord Vlad thanks for the five dollars 50 cents uh do it you coward do it now
I'm going I told you I'm gonna prove to you guys that I bought you I told you you guys
had power and I will let you use it thanks for the five dollars and 50 cents lord uh yellowist
thanks for the four dollars here I'll pitch in for that whale lord plush centerpiece for your
office that is absolutely gonna go right behind me thanks though thank you deep fried gundam
for the 10 bucks funds for whale lord thank you thank you wild fox one for the one dollar
hey jerma following up on a recent question uh what games you got obsessed with has there
ever been a game that you loved and even though you knew it was a bad game much love from Austria
thanks again for being amazing thank you wild fox one look at look at stream look at whoa
holy shit that's clean that's very clean wow but here's the real question can you get an
even percent can you get an even percentage on every single one of those good luck a game
that I thought was bad that I got obsessed with um no I don't I don't think so a game
that I knew was bad but I was I mean maybe I don't know Diablo 3 does that count but that counts
right because there was a point where I just like hated Diablo 3 and like the position that it was
in especially like a couple months after launch I thought it was like oh wow this is really
cool the initial six hours of Diablo 3 I mean the initial like 10 hours or 15 hours was
like oh this is oh cool cool this is actually kind of fun and then after like I put 50 to
100 hours into the game after like two months three months of the game being live I hated it
and that was in the middle of the real money auction house the game was a fucking mess
no close you guys have you had six percent on the m what's going on there but no what the
exp the the Diablo 3 expansion uh yeah I gave up on it for a while and then Reaper of Souls
came out made the game 10,000 times better and then the game I don't think the game at
this point they've just kind of been tacking on so much shit on top of everything that's already
there that it's just kind of very there's rift rift rift rift rift rift that's really all there
is in the game at this point now and for me at least but if that answers your question I
hope so but I did get a lot of play time in Diablo 3 hey thank you uh queso for the one
dollar for the sock fun thanks a lot Wombat from hell thanks for the one dollar stream
reminded me of this video shopper cracking contract wallace and grommet shopping cracking
contraptions shopper 13 thank you one fat from hell pie guy thanks for the dollar 50 this
should help cover the cost thank you bats thank you for the bits thanks for the laughs thank
you for being here uh lazy luke thanks for the one dollar please do a christmas shopping
stream where we choose what you actually buy for your family uh that would be very interesting
but I kind of have to be careful for very obvious reasons so I mean if I could set that
up in a way where that's possible um I'd need to be careful with that one that's interesting
thank you uh lazy luke for a pretty good idea uh kim plex thank kim plex thanks for the one
dollar you must purchase more for our entertainment and enjoyment thank you
actually would be kind of fun maybe one day to set something crazy like that up but
not for today thank you novi for the three dollars 33 cents whale funds thank you uh heath cliff the
friday thriller thanks for the two dollars ho ho ho heath cliff here number one funny cat
I was at my don't do this to me another one of you guys is making like a cat
comic book cat rp character heath cliff the friday thriller I was at my local sandwich
bar wondering what sandwich to buy boy oh boy was it one tough cookie choice
times like these I follow with one simple rule wwj do what would germa do turkey or tuna I picked
turkey and then I went to the kfc to order a tub of gravy just gravy and poured that over the
delicious turkey sandwich don't knock it until you try it yes nice internet purchases would
you consider buying heath cliff merchandise okay uh thank you gin for the five community subs
coming in much earlier seven hours ago now thank you gin thank you pin pin man gave a
shitload and they gave a shitload earlier 10 community subs from pin thank you so much pin
and then right after that garfield the monday killer comes in for a dollar germa I hope you
realize that giving chat control of where you click is like inviting an army of demons to
invade your brain if chat had their way we'd have you purchase 30 copies of garfield fat
cat three pack I'm astounded at how long I have a fucking that's a you know what you don't
fuck it we're gonna do that someday I'm going to load on a like separate amazon account
like 200 dollars in amazon money good luck that would be like fucking crazy looking over
at the percentages here and i'm seeing uh m is at four percent come on guys go to ebay
but thank you garfield thank you smelly boy for the one dollar you played a courage the
cowardly dog creepy pasta touched on it earlier but that's that was funny thank you
super seal thanks for the one dollar a plus stream germa thank you it was an interesting
idea from somebody in the chat that said play flash games and then I was like hey why don't
I just give control to everybody well they just pick what what games I play and then we played
fucking three flash games what even happened on this stream I don't even remember that was like
seven and a half that was seven hours of I don't remember technically it was two guys
that's that's true that's very correct thank you to double d11 for the one dollar I
graciously thank you for choosing me in my game oh double d that's ed is that what your name is
based off of counting meme thanks for the ten dollars nine nine nine nine dollars and ninety
nine cents hey germa long time fan keep up the good work I'm running out of generic things to
say and then he says gave one bit to bob ross well thank you counting meme for the
the ten dollars uh fat fat what is this fat fatten s said fatten said thanks for the ten dollars
they say we want the nose the nose what are you guys doing what is this 27 percent you're just
growing like a worm out of the ground to take oh you're just it's eating things you guys
are consuming your giant worm eating you guys are playing snake on stream you're gonna actually
you're gonna consume all these balls but thank you fat for the ten dollars I didn't bring the
nose back I'm sorry peter thank you peter for the thirty dollars thirty dollars from peter
glue man t-shirt announcement pogchamp not yet thank you for the 30 bucks we thank you peter
for the thirty dollars thank you so much and then s s ferg comes in with a t-shirt link
this is not a real t-shirt I don't want to link anybody to any fake websites but thank you for
the one dollar uh musky thanks for the five dollars musky appreciate it koi pond thanks
for the 50 bucks oh my fucking god you only take these privileges away from you guys
we will not be silenced okay all right well that was fun I'm glad we had fun with that
one thank you koi pond koi pond with the iq test suggestion fifty dollars from koi pond
thank you so much koi pond huge amount of money thank you for the fucking 50 bucks
much love to you thank you uh s ferg thanks for the one dollar new vegas streamers
single-handedly beats five thousand people at checkers I did and then you guys got insta
checkmated in chess I don't forget that one I remember that thank you though thank you
other guy for the one dollar I haven't laughed this hard in a long time thanks for the pick me
up thanks for hanging out uh the helping llama thanks for the one dollar welcome to germa park
germa raptor germa raptor is not a current emote but thank you nonetheless thank you super seal
for the one dollar I like how it took one guy to get you to install the extension but
despite all the messages you still don't have bt tv I don't want bt tv why the fuck thank
you super seal for the one dollar thank you flying sombrero for the one dollar germa where
do you get your two pay my grandfather thank you for the one dollar flying sombrero thank you
beckoo beckoo beckoo tae beckoo tae beckoo ta for the ten dollars here
no messages thank you appreciate that thanks a lot ten bucks coming in swiggity spanky thanks
for the five dollars a bit late but congrats on the green screen movie night took me three
days to watch the whole vod I recommend saving it to the stream's permanent videos so that
your legacy legacy will never be forgotten germa knows what that was a lot of fun thanks
for hanging out thanks for participating hey you guys are making a guy the moon is the face
no wait oh my god what the fuck it's not coming back you don't get it again it's
not coming back now you lost it forever you fucking jokers why no it's not gonna come back
no way you've had like 17 chances but the green screen movie night was a lot of fun I'm
happy that you got to enjoy it hey snoozing copter thanks with the one dollar hey germa
what's up I was thinking to me and a few others we're actually already talking about
it in the discord a germa discord smash ultimate tournament would be really fun there
are a bunch of sites to organize it too we're gonna do one regardless probably are you interested
uh for stream I don't I don't know I'm not sure if I'm even gonna stream smash brothers I've been
fighting against it for like I was gonna stream it today but I feel like it's just one of
those games that's hard to stream everyone is streaming smash I know and I know I know I know
hard to stream well it's let me put it this way there are games that I like to play on
stream because I think that a lot of people can enjoy them there are games that I don't like to
put on stream because I feel like I'm the only one that can enjoy them does that make sense
sort of because like I'll play through the world of light okay I'm having a great time
collecting stickers and it can be interesting some of those encounters are have been really
really interesting and I'm not against streaming a game and playing a game just because
you know I don't really have any rules for myself on this channel it's just what do I
feel like doing do I think I can have fun doing it and then do I feel like doing it
that's been the MO for this channel for like the last three years I mean for instance I'm
building a bird house probably in like the next couple days I've got building a fucking bird
house on stream like I what why the fuck do I want to do that one guy said you should build
stuff build a bird house build this and I'm like okay like that sounds fucking cool am I
gonna paint it oh you better believe it why did I spoil that well that's all right it's
not a spoiler you don't know what I'm gonna make but that's my mentality going into streams are
always what do I feel like doing and do I think it's gonna be fun it's not oh I want to play
this game or I want to let me do this as like a series no it every single stream except
obviously the ones that have to be planned months in advance or weeks in advance but
I don't really have a rhyme or reason to it besides the ones that have a lot of planning
the game and activity doesn't matter that much if you haven't fun the stream is fun
yeah that's true that is the mentality who is the fabled one guy uh sberg thanks with three
bucks I haven't been a kid in 15 years and my childhood was just completed with the balloons
tower defense game I'm hope you stuck around for a chat and me I was I was around I did it
too on hard oh 85 uh squiggity swanky thanks for the one dollar one last question I've been
meaning to ask if you could take it all back which meme would you remove from existence
the short joke or cosplaying as a rap short short the short one the short joke the short
joke the short one the one that went from just because short the short joke remove it a hundred
times I would rather be naked in that raptor costume then have somebody's do the short joke
again me too that answers your question thank you though thank you the milkman for the one
dollar money man thank you milkman where you're the money man and the milkman it seems it's time
for slime thanks for the two bucks your biggest mistake is that you think chat knows what they
want well they did collectively beat balloons tower defense so thank you mh harmless for
the 50 bucks now you have money for it 50 dollars thank you uh nfn thanks with three
bucks to think geoguessr is still to still to there to come oh geoguessr is still to come
it is it is not unfortunately extra cheesy thanks for the two bucks did you see that amazing youtube
rewind video this year it really shows how youtube is trying to connect and be relatable
with its content creators and viewers i can't believe they got my favorite streamer uh
jeremy985 to say keep it down back there while on the battle bus i'm truly blessed
thank you extra cheesy thank you uh thank you thank you your boy jerald for the one
doll thank you hey jeremy a long time fan it's been said before and i'll say it again you're the
best and most real streamer with the best community on the platform good enough to turn
playing simple flash games in one of the most the best and funniest streams i've seen all year
i almost died anyway here's my contribution to the sock joke maybe you could give a pair
to bf bilgabary or santa if he hadn't mysteriously disappeared last year that's our he's
he'll be fine he'll be he's dead but he might not thank you uh i'm glad you enjoy
yourself here thanks a lot spoilers uh thank you heath cliff the friday thriller for the one
dollar 75 iq chat thank you spence for the four dollars and 20 cents we need to play sorcery
with this extension oh damn that's damn that's a great idea that's a great no another choose
your own adventure book that has endless possibility we'll see super spy burger flipper
thanks for the one dollar you know while you're sitting here letting 4075 iq chatters tell
you what to do and buy pikachu socks remind yourself that you have enough iq to become a
doctor you know i don't i don't want to brag i want to be humble about the whole thing
thank you thank you dark star 700 000 games for the one dollar in his ravenous hatred
he found no peace and with boiling blood he scoured the plane seeking vengeance against
the dark lord who had wronged him he wore the crown of the night what is this this is the
beginning of doom is that the doom beginning oh okay the doom song that you were playing okay
hey meaty matey thanks for the one dollar this is just like playing video games with your dad
when you're four years old thank you super spy burger flipper for the one dollar even though
i was joking around a bit before i'm actually really invested in the balloons tower defense
game i'm proud of you us chat hey i helped i clicked on stuff i was the middleman sometimes
you need a middleman it's time for slime thanks for the two bucks germy you're awesome
this has been like you're the cool uncle and you're taking the time to play with
your sister in laws of weird demanding kid it's actually been a lot of fun so far
uh what a nice vessel uh erasmus thank you erasmus for the one dollar and one cent going
back to low budget uh nick games that reminds me i think you might like tune twister 3d but
in all seriousness thanks so much for all your streams man they're one of a kind take
care tune twister what the hell was that dr clay thanks for the one dollar hold on a second
i had to go check on something i had to go check on something real quick i had to talk
to kim for a second i want to ask her a question okay mom mom uh where were we here
we're at uh erasmus thank you for the one dollar appreciate that dr clay thanks for
the one dollar that moment with you arguing with the robot was golden i really want to
animate it now take care well good luck with whatever you come up with i should have played
this music says extra cheesy for a dollar here mr crabs walking for 10 hours that would just
get lost in the balloons popping that's just the balloons popping the sound uh thank you
extra cheesy thank you honey chain for the two bucks germa heart thank you uh it's time for
slime thanks for the dollar appreciate it bake me home thanks for the two dollars they say
i agree thank you but connoisseur thanks for the three dollars gamers rise up thanks to the three
dollars dark star thanks for the one dollar you see voting does something thank you voting does
something uh we're ruinous thanks for the one dollar we all did this together we all did this
together we did do this together i was a part of it don't tell me i wasn't a part of it i
was there uh awesome alec thanks for the one dollar i was here when germa 95 completed
five live on stream on hard difficulty frog champ thank you e dragon thanks for the five bucks how
could you not play the spyro ost i'm unsubbing immediately seriously though thanks for being
the best streamer on twitch um if you say so i i'm glad you think that thank you for
everything thank you thanks for the five dollars pin man coming in with more community
subs from earlier about 25 minutes ago thank you so much pin man tons of gifted subs
and we're getting near the end here thank you gonder lane for the one dollar is one of the two
guys who asked you to play flash games uh shout out to awesome tris i'm glad we made one of the
best streams possible even if this went way out of control i told you i would prove i i
prove it i'm gonna prove it to you on more than one occasion that if you sometimes you're
gonna be the one person that says something the one guy you get you're gonna be the one
guy there are four or five thousand people here tonight you i promised eventually at some
point you'll be the one guy or girl don't matter you know what i'm saying like you'll be the one
person it'll happen if you hang out here long enough uh kairalo thanks for the one dollar i
clicked the wrong spot on the screen and now do not have 140 bits i blame the pokemon socks
thank you timmy tim tim for the one dollar great stream thanks for doing my favorite bit
again i think i'm gonna talk over this thank you timmy tim tim for the one
dollar clueless sniper thanks for the one dollar thank you the spaz thanks for the ten dollars
first time donating to a stream i've been watching for a while hope you're doing great thank you
thanks for the 10 bucks first time donating
i'm watching for a while i'm glad you've been here for this long don't worry about
paying me money thank you for giving it to me in the first place though thank you
i think you should look for another job drosophilia thanks for the two bucks when i was a kid people
i can't drosophilia thanks for the two bucks when i was a kid people would always ask who is
your idol i never really cared so i would say something generic like abraham lincoln or john
glenn but now that i've gotten older i realize that i do actually have an idol someone i look
up to someone i aspire to be have you figured it out yet it's you if i can have that kind
of an impact on you man that's i'm more important as an idol than abraham lincoln if i have that
kind of impact on you that makes me really happy that's a coffee pasta no it's not don't
tell me that it's not abraham lincoln didn't beat balloons and need the didi but that means
a lot thank you the vessel's gonna cry the only goal i've ever had and i mean this for
real was just to have fun if you don't like if you don't if you don't think it's funny if
you don't think it's fun that's fine that's okay if you do cool i'm just gonna keep doing it you
know there's a lot of new stuff just came in kyra toby just gave another 10 thank you kyra
toby i get a lot of uh you know really really really nice messages and that's why
that's why sometimes you guys are wondering like oh why is he like why are you being so
hard on yourself come on man i don't know because i i just i don't it's not i don't think it's
anything to do with being hard i mean i fuck around a lot and we talk a lot of uh just
shit we have by the way job but gino somebody gino got one of those gifted subs nice but i
don't i don't look at people if somebody doesn't like what i'm doing and they're like
oh you should do this sucks you suck you know it's like all right man like whatever i
i always anytime i see something like negative and i don't this doesn't happen that often
but i always feel like there's so much wonderful things people say i never want to put myself
on like a pedestal you know what i mean and feel like oh like i read all these these
wonderful things about me people say such nice fucking things every day every single time i
stream and of course people can fuck around and chat and you know put dicks on the screen
and uh short and stupid bad but that's where for the most part everyone's just having a
good time short short stupid bad well i need to like reevaluate here to be fair a pedestal
might really help you out heightwise yeah but i don't want anyone to like hate me
you know i i feel like bad when people are like actually angry or like upset with something
that i do i'm just like fuck man like i don't want you to feel like that but i don't ever
want all the wonderful nice things people say kind of invade my head and oh look at me
oh look at me i'm the greatest oh i'm so good at everything like i don't i you know what i'm
saying i try to keep myself as grounded as i can i did do the look at me i did do it
tremor you're grounded oh fuck this guy he ruined tf2 with that spe shit and and i don't
want people to yeah i maybe i'm just trying to please everybody but i don't know but i don't
think i am either i'd say like a bunch of fucking i'd say a lot of shit that could come
become across as mean can we draw one more penis nice okay good one more for the road
no but it's something i think about a lot and then this this whole this whole kind of
tangent started by somebody talking about um it was uh it was drosophilia because you look
up to me and you as somebody that you aspire to be i always want to try to challenge what i'm
doing and if that inspires you then fuck yeah i'm happy more than happy thank you so much
for that message and thank you everybody for being here the yellowest again thanks for
one dollar i only get four dollars before that number bothers me here i have another
thanks for the five dollars one of the pikachu socks gonna be delivered probably like a next
week or something they'll just show up on stream don't worry uh bet three thanks to the five
dollars can't wait for you to play katamari neither can i it's gonna be great that'll
probably be happening very soon maybe sooner than you think timmy tim tan thanks for the one
dollar one guy for the next germa rumble that's not a bad idea i was thinking about
putting the the one guy in quotes uh in the rumble this year but kind of ran out of time
flying sombrero thanks for the one dollar the funny thing about the short joke is me and a
lot of people here in chat are your height or shorter too bad you will forever be a short man
ps good job chat we won the monkey war thanks thank you convo breaker for the one dollar
hey germa speaking of choose your own adventure games pyre is won by the guys who made bastion
and transistor also i laughed so hard this stream i need to go take a shower i'm gonna
do that too i'm gonna do that too thank you man bear pig for the 10 bucks appreciate it they
say hi germa hi man bear pig thank you 10 dollars uh at a mem atom a tame mango thanks
for the one dollar uh love you germa interested in hearing your favorite gorillas song seems good
that would be uh stylo stylo is my favorite gorilla song arabist the great thanks for the
one dollar i've been going through a rough patch in my life just want to say thank you
for being here and not only entertaining me but everyone else thank you rewind uh what we were
just talking about before thank you for consistently and constantly giving me support
both monetarily and you know mentally too and just like in every aspect of my life
thank you for real i'm sorry to hear about that sorry to hear that you're going through
a rough one take care of yourself it's 3 a.m yeah it's late sorry we're almost done kaira toby
with the 10 community subs thanks a lot dude that's a lot huge subs you're you're awesome
every day this channel grows more and more and more in subs more and more and more in bits
it can be fairly overwhelming sometimes but just know that whatever you give to this channel
a huge amount of it is going going right back in so thank you you guys take really really good
fucking caribbean let that be known uh the spaz thanks for the four dollars again one of the
few streamers i actually check out even if it means i won't get sleep from sweden you're up
real late very late well have a good have a good morning right good good afternoon good
morning thank you so much good morning it's nine in the morning here holy shit
good afternoon good morning good evening good night wherever you are
topac thanks for the one dollar it is a clip i don't know how those today that's like the
gnome of my own channel uh chubby funster thanks for the one dollar germa you didn't look
at the link bet three put in their message you you sure i didn't look at the link it's a gnome
well while i go looking for this here is the here are the credits we have an uncountable
amount of subs on the channel at the moment and here are just a small sample of that shit load
of people oh there it is all the subs and resubs tonight thank you so much guys i must
snap 50 of them where is this where is it i clicked on there were only a few links
did i not click on one of them are you sure let me go make sure it grows every day it's
fucking remarkable uh i see bet three from earlier can't wait for you to play katamari
but bet gave a few more times i think let me see i don't see a link did anybody have
the link that he had on his message because i don't see one oh here it is oh it's katamari
like balls what the fuck is this is that really what that was is that really what that was and
that's what i clicked on and that that's what i'm doing thank you guys it was worth the time
thank you thank you arabis the grape for four dollars right here at the end might as well
give you the rest of the bits keep on being amazing love you germa thank you arabis the
four dollars and the rest of the bits thank you kyra told me thanks for the one dollar i'm
just wondering how many subs you have now if you're not comfortable giving a number that's
cool no i i've told you guys before that there's a fucking insane amount of people here now
it's not it's not a secret over the last i'll give you some real numbers here that's just
fucking insane over the last six months this channel has in six months not even six four
not even six months like five months received over three thousand subs in the last not even
half a year and that was on top of what i had before that's fucking insane and especially
you know that means we're over 5k there are more than five thousand fucking subs on this
channel and a bunch of these happened in the last like 45 days it jumped up like fucking crazy
i think since moving to since moving to vegas there i think has been more than two and a
half to three thousand subs maybe even just since moving it's been an insane amount i did
a hundred of them last stream yeah i'm not i'm not even counting those so you guys see how
you know it affects me it does i i want this channel to be fun i want you to care i want
you to think it's worth paying for and if there are over five thousand fucking people
paying this stream every month i want this shit i want you to be fucking happy being here
i want you to have fucking fun and if i get that kind of fucking money i'm gonna i'm gonna
fucking do that shit i'm gonna try as hard as i can he's gonna cry no i'm not gonna cry
but this channel even in viewers not just subscriptions or bits or just take a look at
the view numbers that have happened over the last like two or three months the channel
has almost doubled in size in three months almost sometimes it potentially tripled in size
so but that i i don't want that to change the way that i do things i don't want
uh oh yeah you got 12 000 concurrent viewers a few days ago whatever it was like the last
week oh yeah you know you get 5 000 fucking subs on your channel i don't want to change
the shit that i like how i approach things if they were if they were 11 000 people here
versus 500 i'm gonna approach the streams the same exact way and now if there's more people
and there's more money coming in just get to i'm just gonna do other shit i'm gonna try to do
more stuff remember the hitman1 message you recorded for us yeah i yes i do i remember
that night very very vividly hundreds and hundreds of dollars came in that night and
that was one of the first times i'd ever had like six seven eight thousand fifteen
hundred dollars given in one stream but that's gonna be the end of tonight i'm probably i don't
i think at this point because it's getting very late i might take tomorrow off and come back on
monday with katamari edf yeah i wasn't sure if i was because i'm probably not gonna get to
sleep till probably 3 a.m now and i wasn't sure if i was gonna do it two days in a row
so we'll come back monday with katamari edf comes out probably gonna play that with a
few friends thanks a lot for hanging out thanks for playing thanks for playing balloons on my
stream for three and a half hours guys much love to you take care of yourselves very very
quickly at the end here we had a few more bits that come in that is the spaz with 100 just
want to show this vid real quick before i went off have a good night i wanted to show
this vid i don't have a link oh they corrected themselves here it is here's the
video i meant here's my uh here's my little video what the hell is this what is this this is
what is this video was that's not that's not the gnome right the gnome was like
that was let me let me make sure i get this right the gnome goes
that was all right thank you for the video spaz appreciate it uh thank you dinky duper for
the one dollar hey germa we've had trouble setting aside time to watch the stream lately
i usually end up just being a smelly vod man take care that's all right whatever you don't
have to watch every stream live it's all right man don't worry about it kyra toby thanks for
the one dollar greedy streamer won't cry until 10 000 sub lol not true thank you paradox
potato thanks for the bits when are you gonna get when are you gonna get german neptune
germa egg there'll be another wave of sub of emotes we just added so many of them i just
needed a little bit to have some more references and maybe replace a couple of
ones that i put on already hey thanks for the one dollar germa i've been following you since
your old tf2 commentary you've been doing this you've been doing you this whole time it just
depends on the medium you're given to express yourself you're amazing thank you and uh the
search for corbin thank you for the sub that just came right in uh let's just keep having
fun i'm not gonna let sub numbers or view numbers change anything so i'm not let's just
keep doing what we're doing have a great rest of your evening guys have a wonderful remaining
day or morning wherever do have if you're awake if it's the morning and you get to do it one
more time i'll see you guys on monday monday at around probably 3 pm pacific don't let me
down here don't let me down here don't let me down okay so it's just a guy it's just like
a guy it's the moon it's just a guy don't do it you actually aren't doing it and you're
wearing a hat okay very nice very nice guys it's peanut butter jelly time it's peanut butter
jelly time all right i'll see you later see you on monday take care guys goodbye