And I'm not ready for this. I don't I it's been a while since I've done a scare Saturday, but hey, what's going on everybody?
German here with SCP 432. I've been sitting here. Can I just tell you before the before we get going?
I've been sitting here for like
15 minutes just sitting here going I do I want to do this and the answer is yes
Let's go. So this is kind of like the other SCP games
It is very very dark kind of like the other SCP games where you would go investigate
things and stuff
That's a light. Okay
Apparently I got to pick up artifacts or something
the worst part is just the fact that it's just the same texture over and over again in this maze of a building and
There's a monster in here
Somewhere is a valve. Don't think I need to do anything with that. Okay, what's this?
You found an artifact the artifact. Okay. So what do I do with it?
I think I just have to pick them up and then escape just got to escape
Just got to pick up the artifacts and just get the hell out of here crying out loud. It's a goddamn maze
These pipes keep scaring the shit out of me. What was that?
I kind of don't want to go over to this light, but I kind of feel like I have to all right F is flashlight
All right, that's just the light bulb. Okay. Why am I shaking? Why is why is the world shaking?
Can hear noises that I don't like to hear. Yeah
What's that? What's this like fairy dust on the ground? Oh, this is roller skates sick
I got like the roller skates I can compete in like the roller derby
I got two not exactly sure what that means, but there's nothing over here. I wish there was like a map
Turn it turn the flashlight off turn the flash light off hold
What is that on the wall it's gone what is what is that it's not there anymore
My whole body just tensed up. I feel like I just lifted two hundred pounds of weight
I just did all my reps for like the week cuz like the thing with like the the flaming
Dr. Doom skull was looking at me. There's just no I just don't know where I'm going
There's just no indication of where you're ever supposed to go in these games. Good evening. My name is Jerma
I would like to sell you some land what it's
Oh
How long has it been I've only been recording for five minutes well
Okay, the tight corridors make it so much worse, but a quick little scare Saturdays guys
I'm a baby. I know but that thing was too scary and I almost died
Playing it. So thank you all so much for watching really do appreciate it. I've got a pretty good suntan today
I'm not red because I'm like scared. I'm red because I had a suntan but a SCP 432 link will be in the description go
Play it and and have your pants changed within like 10 minutes because fuck this game. I ain't doing anymore