What's up? Good afternoon, how are you? We're a little early today, yeah. There's a reason for
that though. We are early because I wanted to pull the stream back to be able to do two different
things today. Originally it was going to be like a three hour stream in Jackbox, but I've decided
and well I was asked to play Trine. So there's going to be, starting now, there's going to be like
a couple hours, maybe two, three hours of Trine with Star and Ashley. And then Star and Ashley
are also going to join us for Jackbox. So I'll, this will be, this will not be a three hour stream.
Pulling it back lets us do both. But I do have to hard stop this stream between like 5 30 and
6 o'clock pacific, 6 30, maybe the latest. Because I have to, I have to leave. I have to get on an
airplane. I've got to go. This is the week. I have to prepare and I got to go. For what? Well,
it's funny that you asked. Nobody. I didn't even see it. The Halloween stream requires a lot more
setup and time. So I'm going into the studio and I'm going back east. Nobody asked.
The one paid actor did. Yeah, going back to the east coast. I'm going to visit some family and
friends while I'm there. Gives me an opportunity to be in Boston for a while and hang out. I'm
not going to stream to the Halloween stream. After today, there's not going to be a stream
until Halloween. Just to let you guys know, the Halloween stream is the next stream after this one.
Back, back to Boston. Here we go. But yeah, that's the plan and I believe we're kind of just ready
to go. Let's just see if we are. Hello. How is everybody doing? Hello. Hello. Not bad. Not
pretty good. All right. That's star and that's Ashley. They are star and Ashley. Power and
wisdom and what was the other one? Oh my God. Courage. Courage. I didn't know it. She never
told me. How am I supposed to know if my wife doesn't tell me? Unbelievable. Where do we leave
off? What did we do last time? I don't remember. Okay. So last time where we left off in the
three trainers, we definitely paid attention to the entirety of the plot. I think the nightmare
prince ran away from us because he didn't want to be locked in the castle and now we're chasing him.
Oh, that's right. We are chasing somebody. Yeah. The nightmare prince who's having these dreams
and his dreams are coming to life. And the only thing he dreams about are a wolf.
Does he really deserve our help? I know he is a prince. Well, I think our characters were
touching on that a little bit, like that we were wasting our time and that he was a snotty little
brat. And why do you guys care about honestly, I have the power to create boxes. You think I'm
going to waste my time on this kid? Dude, we already said it before. Last time we did the
three trainers for lore mega lol. You're the one that asked. Oh, did I? I mean, you said,
where did we leave off? I explained it. I did not just ask what, what? No, I said, well, like in,
like in the video game, like where did we leave off? Right here. Yeah. But then you started going
off on like the story and I started to get fucking tired. Where else, like where, what else would you
be asking? I don't know. Like what was the last puzzle we did? Who cares? You don't care about
the lore, but you care about the last puzzle we did. I don't know. What's the context? Remember
the wizard hall, like full of mirrors? Yes. Thank you. Thank you. You started talking about like
story and I started to get fucking tired. Oh, we got a wall here. Oh, right. Fighting.
There is fighting in this game. There's the wolf you're screaming about.
He also dreams of platforms a lot. Wolves. Why wolves though? Can somebody explain it to me?
My chat's saying that he's a furry. Probably right. Boston accent. There's a deer in the
background. You guys just ran by. Wait, are you skipping all the, we need these, don't we?
Yeah, rowdy. I got one.
Oh yeah. And then, then I was doing all the dialogue from my character and it was a lot of fun.
We had a really good time with that joke. This is a new mechanic and you talked over the whole thing.
Oh, it is a new mechanic. There's things. I can freeze that. Oh, oh, thank you. And then
I think you might have to, all right, put the box over there so she can get the, uh,
the droplet. She already has blood. Yeah, Jeremy's blood. Not what we leave. Okay. Uh,
one of us is locked out. His blood. Uh, shit. He just shoved it right in the perfect spot. Oh,
thank you. All right. I've got that and I'm going to cut you guys loose and you can go on the ride.
You ready? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Let's go. Nice. Was that fun?
I sacrificed myself. You're missing the blood. Yeah, but I can't get that. You can get that.
I can't get that. Can I get that here? Stop Ashley. Stop hitting my box. I'm going to push
this. German watches the German watches the departed in Boston Red Sox baseball every day.
Um, you say that as a, you say that as a joke, but, uh, that's, I think that is like required
reading. If you live in Boston, like at least once every couple of years, that like is what
happens. I didn't, Oh, I didn't even freeze that. I was talking. We were having fun. Just jump up
here. Let's just get going. Yeah. Just get the blood. Hold on. The departed is amazing. Yeah.
Okay. Two boards. You didn't say it right though. You didn't put an A H in your,
in your word. It's the fucking deposit. And if you don't say the F word in the middle either,
you're dead. I know it's a true, I know who's a true Boston fan. If you don't say the fucking
deposit. I have no idea what you're talking about. Why was I trying to freeze that rock? Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. Take, you gotta take, you gotta take the boulder to the left to activate the
lotus signal. Should I freeze that? What about what's up there? But what's up there? I can do
this. See, I told you, I knew I was supposed to go up there. All right. So now how do you get over
there? Come with me. That works. Well, now when you need to block that. Oh, the fuck. Wait. Oh,
cause the boulder has to be over. Yeah. With your power, right? You do it and then you dash back.
Okay. I think I see these lamps are the fire. So if I light them, I just open the door. All right.
Nice. Yeah. Wow. All right. Fucking pot it. Nice. Oh yeah. That's where we left off. My character
can't do anything and I just make boxes and do everything. You got to remember that last time
we went over this. No, uh, we need to all get a boulder. I can do this. They're part of joke.
Plus two. How many elements did you hit? Oh, you got fucking destroyed. All right. I don't care.
I'm fine. My true strength is respawning. So I think we can, can we just all get up there?
If we jump from here to there. Uh, yeah, there's a lot of stuff. How do you get up there? You got
to go this way. When I got my upgrade points, I can't use
daddy. Help me. I can't. I don't know. Left, left, left. Well, that works. Left. I think that,
yep. Oh, there's a bunch of shit up here, isn't there? And there's a bunch of stuff up here.
Hold on. Maybe my box can solve this. If that, if that happened, that's seriously what happened to
you. She's just trying to kill it. Oh crap. Nope. Oh, okay. Well, we can do this without Ashley
stars. My real name is Danny. Mine. Yeah. Your real name is Danny. Oh, there's nothing there.
Right. Anyway, my real name is Jason Long, American dragon. Whoa, dude. Super boost.
My name is Ollie shot color. You blocked it. Was that a fortnight bus horn? I don't know. I've
never played it. Never. Not even the previous version. Um, does the PlayStation four version
count if I'm lying down on my side in bed, bringing a monitor into my bedroom to play
that game on the PS four, the regular original game for like 20 minutes.
Does that count? How about you? You hold your shield up for someone to jump on. How about you
do that? Well, you eat my ass. Well, I can freeze that. No, I'm just grandma. Just jump on it on the
jump on it. Please jump on me. Please. This is like the easiest. Oh, wait, I have to move.
You have to do it. Why is everybody yelling at me? Oh, no, no, pull it up. I can pull it up.
Pull it up. You have it there. Oh, my God. It's so easy. Okay. Get
it. Why is it activating? Wait, no, no, no, that that's how you do it. I'm not supposed to
be up here. Me being up here, fucks this whole thing up. Why did you tell me to go over here?
Put that back up there. Watch this. Okay, we did it. See, I just have to hang it. That was so easy.
God, then you're the leader. Glad you have a wizard. You think you're the leader.
Why can't we be friends and have fun? There is no leader. I have the biggest hat. We have a 33%
stake in this at all the same. Oh, my God. But I actually get 38% for hosting fees. And because of
the fire, I need my expenses for the fire. In fact, I probably like 42% because these are expensive.
Okay. 44% I think would be covered. All right, now what do I do? You gloat from up there.
I'll just take all of it. And then like, I'll give you guys like a little bit to like,
wait, I want all your shot. What is it doing? Why is it doing that?
Behold my power. I can now make balls. Do it. Wait, what can you do?
How do I do it? I made them bouncy too. It's a ball.
Wait, it said I unlocked bouncy balls. Wow. You just shaved off the corners of your boxes.
Great. Wow. That's what a power. You're just saving money.
Wait, I also learned I learned to blink, but it didn't tell me how to do it.
What a shift for me. Oh my god, I'm useful. I guess I have to spend these points.
Hey, he's using for an alt. So we don't all do the same alt. What do you mean? Because you get more
points than you can spend for your one character. So what are you guys using for an alt? There's we
don't have alt. I'm not doing that. You are the archer. Shut up and live with it. But okay,
can you get those blood? I'm just wait, you, you, you generate more experience points than you can
spend. What are you doing? I can do the worms. I'm supposed to bash this. Why would it? Oh, oh,
I think that wasn't a joke. There it is. I'm serious. I don't, I want to like, what if we need
to? I don't know. No, being serious. We can't switch characters. This is a, oh, well then this
is classic. Why does it give you extra points? Because you can play this single player and switch
for all three characters. I see. Okay. Well, we have to roll on your ball. Oh my god.
And I remain. Actually, just die. If we both die, we'll appear at him. Okay.
That's not working. You go forward. Go forward. You got, it's not working. I've been standing over
here this whole time. Come on. Keep going. What do you mean? I can't keep going. I need you.
I can't get this. See, I can't reach this.
Almost worked. Obviously now he appears over here. See. Maybe it has to be two people have to be
there. Possibly. These puzzles are going to get crazy once all our powers reach their maximum
potential and we're required. This looks too complicated. Let's just do Jackbox.
Now you have that in your back pocket. It's gonna be really annoying.
What? Playing Jackbox? Oh, I said it once. That's the first time I said it.
Well, you were thinking at the full plug. Hold on. It's hard to aim this
because it snaps. Okay. Now you should be able to get up there and then do the,
yeah. Sick. Now drop a ladder. Drop a ladder. Now you, here we go.
You mean go on without you guys? Okay. Oh, so Daisy. Okay. Now I do that. Oh, shoot.
Wait, what? What's up there? Fireballs. Mega. Oh, what's up on the left? I don't know. What's
up this way? Oh, shit. What's up this way? I don't know. Let's find out. Oh, this place is full of
blood. I supposed to be here. Oh, you can't go up. It's a, you can, you can. I mean you can,
but I hit them. What did I hit? I got to hold my ball. Is that it? Yeah. Ashley didn't even
want to come up this way. Can we go apart? See if we can go apart. Oh, shit. Okay.
It's like the way to go. Where do you guys go? We're doing the secret bonus area.
The super difficult puzzle. It's not that difficult. It's extremely hard. It requires
three people. Oh, come on. We also got a talisman. You lied. Yeah, it was really hard.
The two triners. Hey. Just momentarily, momentarily the two triners. She's trying to kill us.
Can you make it through? Almost died. You have a way to do that. Okay. Bring it down here. No,
what are you doing? Almost. I'm keen to your bullshit now. That was a hard one. There's a big
one. There is a big one. We're going to go up top left. So when you said, when you were making the
joke that this is a hard one, it is you have to do this. Give me a box. Get a ball. Well,
I can't grab the edge of that. Okay. Well, that's my problem. You're going to make fun of how I
just shaved the edges off. I mean, that was pretty funny. All right. Now give me another one. All
right. Now. Oh, look at that. Oh, you got it. No. Come up here. Do you need me to drop this?
Are we good? We're good. We're good. Okay. We are the three triners. Oh, my God.
Incoming boss fight probably.
Wait, why are you guys so far off the screen? Because we kept going forward. I thought it was
a cut scene. And then you have to roll down there. Oh, now. Okay. Hold on. Now it presses the button
to get the stuff. Okay. What about here? Drop a drop a ball down the little area.
It's going to open this door. Cool. Dude, we're so smart. Somebody said, is this paper Mario?
Yeah. You know, I've never played paper Mario. Same. Have you? Have you never played either? No,
I'm not a Nintendo boy. I played it. Maybe. Oh, I'm just going to make. Can I make a
bridge to the ball? Probably. Why was it not rolling? I was walking. Oh, only one person
can roll it. Okay. Oh, play it right now. Hey, what? Play it right now. No, I'm not going to play
paper Mario right now. Okay. I've got a bridge. If you like Mario RPG, you should love paper Mario.
It's not that I don't like it. It's just not the same. Oh, nothing's the same. I know. I know.
Why do we just break all the boxes? Maybe you might think to yourself we could use that box.
Somebody just said it's better. You have infinite boxes in your butthole. But I can only have one
box. That was access to multiple boxes. There's a box slot. Look how high we have to climb. What if
we had a box right now? There's a box slot right there. No, not a ball slot, a box slot.
The less boxes we have, the more useful you are. Think about that.
What? Well, I'd still be the one moving the box. Yeah. Even if we have more boxes.
But I like your boxes better. It's a compliment. He hates trying to break these boxes.
The wizard like they're my friends. Like, please. It's not with the box breaking. I studied box
magic. No more. Don't kill any more boxes, please. They're so nice to be. Boxes don't get enough
respect around you. As an awful old man, boys, you can do better than that. I know you can.
Okay. That was even worse. Quite a treasure there. You have a natural cube.
Let me step in here for you. These boxes are so hard to control. If only I had my scrolls.
That's an old man's motto. Fuck my stomach. I can't laugh. I'm not supposed to be laughing.
I think it needs to be you, Jermis. You roll on the ball. The ball is currently...
I'll take care of it. Let me step in for you. No, no. No. Yes. There you go.
And you get a bridge. This looks so stupid. Why would I need a fucking ball? Get that
fucking ball out of here. Oh, my. I'm so... Hold on. I gotta calm down.
You have quite a treasure there in that Herodric ball.
I got so fucking angry right there. Why? Oh, my God. What's wrong?
Fucking God. Hold on. All right. Jeez. Slow down.
You did it. Hey, look at all these boxes.
Oh, I'm trying to... Get out of here.
You can do it. No, I'm not trying to jump on that. I'm trying to grab the thing.
Jermis, this is psycho. Oh, there's a secret tunnel down here.
What? Are you kidding me? Let me see. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. You're going to have to
freeze these when my box or ball is in front of it, okay?
Stop making me laugh. All right. I'll get into this next time.
I was going to say if that didn't hit it, nothing will ever hit it. All right. Then you have to go.
Oh, fuck. Okay. I did it. Oops-a-daisy. No, I didn't. Oops-a-daisy. Oops-a-daisy.
It was the wrong... Okay, hold on. I was just... Don't let go. Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
I'm trying to cut it. All right. Now watch this. I don't need... There.
Come on. Fuck you. We didn't need you for this puzzle.
We got it. Oh, points. I still can't. So, was it just a secret area? Yeah. Oh, pressure.
Yep. Can't go over there. Yeah. Trying to get out of here without the ball.
We're already both out. I meant like this way. Oh. Did it. Oh, did it too. Okay. Okay.
You made that sound like it was going to be way harder. Give it to me. Wait. There's another
thing to break. Oh, my God. It's running. It's running away. Get him back. All right. Now you
got to actually pay attention. We got enemies. Bro's a big guy. How did I die? Wrong thing.
Okay. This is all you. Wait, me? Yeah. We, we died. Oh, my God.
Well, they did it. This game is way too easy. Um,
um, there's been a few challenging things so far. Yeah. What's the point of the game
if I can't brag about it on like Reddit after I beat it? Yeah. I only play games with like
2% completion rates. Oh, am I sticking the slot in the cube? Oh, the most powerful ball.
The moon. Okay. Oh, fights are meaningless. Yeah. It's like commentary on war.
Stop. Stop. Stop it. No more funny things. I'm supposed to be the funny one. You stop
making jokes. No, I like, I have like fucking side pain. Why do you guys think I played
Bushido blade last night? Cause there's no way it was going to be funny. And it was hilarious.
Yeah. He's on this whole new thing where he just wants to like not have fun anymore. All right.
Give it to that box. It's too much. It's too heavy. It's too heavy. All right. Now you got to
go on this one. You wait. I'm the lightest. Wait, I'm the lightest. Wait,
Triner telling you one more funny thing out of you and I'm out of this call.
See? All right. Now I can freeze it. That's good. No, it's good. Or whatever.
There's a hook over here. What is it? What's that hook for? What did, what just happened?
I think you just, did you cut my line? I did. I was pointing with my sword.
I pointed too hard. Yeah, almost. I think that's the cheater's hook. So you just skip the whole
thing. Kind of is, but cheaters or what? Uh, there's a little thing I can pull.
Pull it. What is this for? I don't understand the application here. Oh, to get us over.
Just to make it easy. Well, we can all get over. Oh, come on, dude. Nope. I'm your wife.
I'm your wife. Uh, statistically most murders happen with people that know each other.
Most husbands murder wives. Yeah. I'm saying like that's okay. You have to freeze this left one.
What I'm saying is they're going to catch it. What happened? You got to catch me first. All
right. So this, this is done. And then you got to put that up there. And then we put this one up
here that allows us to go up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up 99% of husbands.
I just die. Yeah. How, what? Oh, you might have to freeze this one too. Jeremy. Okay.
open the door can you have two frozen no all right we're good there we go okay
via control this is it wait you guys don't think I'm using like the mad cats
ps2 controller right now do you I have an Xbox one controller plugged in I'm
not using you've messed up when a moderator says how would you murder your
wife cat asking for a friend oh yeah even worse I actually like the Xbox
controller I like how it's bigger and fatter the Xbox 360 controller I think
is the best control is ever made the life some bigger and fatter the Xbox
360 controller is probably this is a pretty damn good controller or PS they
yeah they made the perfect controller but then made a new Xbox and we're like
we got fucked this up yeah how do we make it different you need to you need
to innovate no if I could use the ps4 with the Xbox 360 controller with the
switch mobile capability we're talking seriously best console ever made PC that
is it yeah that is a laptop yeah I'm doing that right now I got like yeah
that's a lap that's like a nice laptop nice get one wait wait wait here I just
like fucking played myself really bad right there I like the Xbox one controller
but I don't like this I don't like the clicky bumpers in fact the Xbox no that's
nothing there there are they worse on the three other than the 361 which one's
louder all right Xbox one controller but no but I'd like the shape of the Xbox
360 controller better I'm imagining you at a party having this conversation it's
like a group of friends standing around like having a drink talking and you're
just on this fucking thing on your own everyone's watching you watching you
trying to figure out which like which drink is the loudest Ashley right wall
I'm coming to these realizations I'm coming to these realizations right now
I'm not gonna hold on to this for like I'm gonna forget this six hours from now
you think I'm gonna remember like which is a louder click on the bumper why
would I even think about that in six hours he's got to inform you now while
it's still in his brain I just I have to talk I'm for me hold on there's a badger
talking to me just assume we're heroes yeah I had a really funny joke that was
right here ready for you I was gonna say I was gonna do an animal crossing
reference my god okay but which one of these is louder like if it is that
god dang it which one is is gonna be who's loud it was gonna be funny it was
gonna be really funny I know you were gonna laugh seriously where's fucking
dr. strange like use that and let's see what it was gonna look like I need to
you need to put the box right wait let me help you I need her to just stop
smashing it how can you not grab the top at this point but the we would did that
so wrong that was so wrong you're in the problem no people are saying this is
like too easy it's because we're like skipping the 20% of every puzzle no I
wasn't they were just ignoring me I was dropping some real J whoa so we got
launching and then dash through it no you're gonna have to you're gonna have
to stand on this freeze this you're gonna have to freeze this not when it's
back I didn't mean to I don't think I can unfreeze yes I can yes I can you
home okay and you got okay no I did I was firing another shot because I knew
I was gonna miss Ashley I didn't want to do that leader can't even defend my
what try it again right again you're fucking with me
like oh no thank you all right I got something else up there don't
worry oh that thing you're gonna freeze that up there probably oh well that
worked how do you guys do this I think you need a box it gives me a box
oh just just come jump on the box when to try and three come on which one did
we play look this up last dream and you yelled at me for like looking up one
like the old trying to came out no no I mean like I don't want to engage in this
again what I'm not let me have better questions when did when did you make
that video I don't want to engage in this yeah I think he's baiting us yeah
can't say that all right unfreeze that please refreeze that please look it's
actually you switch and you see it it's like not remember I'm on analog I'm I
haven't gotten digital yet I'm on analog still I'm not a lot on mouse it's not
like pinpoint most precision wait I'm on I'm on a bright analog stick there's a
left puzzle if you pull out this thing but we need an analog gamer what do you
need me to do ah forget it let's go who needs the bonus things when we have
extra points anyway no no no Ashley what over here no I was trying to get this
germa blood you got it and oh there is another germa blood I didn't even see
it you don't see why can't it be your blood all the time my blood is purple
jump over this actually don't pull for my box please your blood emotes somebody
wrote oh my god hostile dip we've been saying that this is my blood well it
started out as virgin blood and then it became your blood that's actually true
that's how we came to it yeah sorry walks up to me on the street with a
knife and it's like give me all your money and I go Ashley and I go hey get
the fuck out of here and what person next to me is gonna go hey hostile easy
I gotta go there's a wall break die here yes I'm called for camera just just give
them the money just give them just don't do it you actually are supposed to do
that going what there's no way over there isn't wasn't well why are we why
we still have sit here she was coming back with the blood for you sorry I was
saying I was in an argument with myself not with your tip no these balls are
really annoying for two people for multiplayer yeah here no here you want
oh I hate you no she hates streaming no I hate him I like other streamers yeah
same more like other people you keep talking shit it's gonna be your blood in
a second you gotta freeze it when it's when it's lined up right not quite it's
gonna be a little higher I think yes all right I had to get the I had to get the
Steve blood that's right I'm not using fucking avatar names anymore oh that's
not stars blood that's Steve's blood I don't think you're gonna get voted on for
the 2019 stream is your you're out well it doesn't matter cuz the same like four
people win that every single year since its inception does it really matter what
is the idea the game awards you're not gonna be streamer of the year I don't
care how much you spent on that carnival it's a fortnight streamer all right so
here you go I'm gonna freeze it or just go what do you know I mean I guess we're
just gonna freeze it Jesus well I figured that just hold on you got to
pull it up and freeze it well can you get your get your fucking toys out of
the way I'm telling you everyone thinks I'm insane it's the fucking it's right
analog stick it's more don't stop laughing at me it's not I wasn't a funny
thing it's real it's fuck it's I'm using the right analog stick you always you
always shoot one too high then one too low you always find a way like bread the
I don't typically do that no no no that looks safe in the middle there's an open
spot do you need our help over there yeah just make another ball yeah but I
can't the screen is in panning so I don't know what's going on there is okay
can you make it actually we actually might well here just come over jump on
it can't yeah can I do it from there yep yep no I wanted to see star wait I
didn't need to scare your ball like that get move your ball move your box no it's
auto-attaching wait wait wait wait wait wait I ain't dying I ain't dying oh my
god you made it I was gonna have like a 321 countdown kind of situation you
were weren't you how'd that work out oh I hit you hit your head all right when
you get up here I'm gonna drop it and then we're gonna jump cuz we don't we
won't hit our heads I'm just gonna go beat the level on your shield mine I
guess I just I mean I guess to get this stuff then shield there's another pull
pull thing up here this Badger's house is fucking enormous what about what a
joke Oh come into my tree he's very wealthy he
laid trap for us ahead of time just the average house and trying yeah you would
think that if you were living in it like a tree trunk shit would be like a like
400 square feet 300 square feet maybe just think about how far I had to go to
get my mail that's true wait up is it possible that we're just tiny like very
small like tiny tiny tiny that's possible but the bat no we're as big as
a badger not me but badgers are tiny how do they not get that I went through
the wall I thought we were gonna have to put a rock oh there's another one up
this way the ceiling here oh you know sometimes just come down here and do it
from here you get a nice like cup of coffee and you just play in a game there
yeah this is great it's like half the time I don't even have to do anything
this is fantastic seriously I guess is this is I like this yeah we ignores us
oops yeah but I think I might it's a slipper I'm not ignored you uh the only
problem is now you have to be drinking coffee I don't want to drink it I just
want the pride of him giving it to me you guys don't think I'm running man what
there's some sort of magic here I love coffee I really do that's fine I'm
fighting sequences I'm just gonna go the mouse whoa what's that oh there's two
balls I need I can I can do two conjuries I'm useful how did you get two
upgrades in a row that's stupid I can have a shoot oh you want that yeah well
you know what you're gonna need then oh to calm the fuck down you're gonna need
no oh there are any two boxes I know you don't wait I mean we need them now too
far no some of us can do that that's too far for me I'll still make it there's a
learning experience whoa okay in a real deep in this tree now yeah I don't think
we're in his house anymore I just don't think he has very good security we're in
the underworld now we got it that already what about's down here why is
there a thing to drop down hmm something down here but what oh I think you could
probably just grapple up to the wall I don't know that's just no other reason
to be here oh there is okay there is a reason to be down here there's a secret
room but can I do this on my own I don't think I can
maybe I maybe I can no I don't think I can I think I need a friend over here
oh there is a thing yeah I don't know how we get there I got a bridge you're
safe okay what do you need my son I don't know we have to do something oh I
think maybe you move that and then go like that and then get the get the
cheddar's rest and then get the super there we go nice and I think that does
it oh no there's I guess I saw it might I'm doing it using me to get out of
it yeah you do hold on oh my god yes stop saying that my new catchphrase
nope not like that we have to move this shit I'm making a kaizo block please oh
shit oh shit you're gonna help you're just gonna pop that box around I can't
destroy the box under you wait oh why did I why did I grab the box I was so
far away from it was that a snore okay well now I need a box you gave you gave
Chad a reason to do resident sleeper they've been waiting they've really been
waiting I can't jump we lost in whoa from the main whoa from the main menu
no oh whoo okay come on rowdy I can use all these skill points all right I have
two locks here I have a frozen lock and I have a fire lock that doesn't mean
anything holy shit that was actually kind of scary there's another wall over
here need a ball need to launch that one up here somehow how do we open this
door though behind this wall there's an ice key to the left I think you might
need to make a rope bridge for me to put a ball on either that or this ball will
knock another ball forward I mean that's I don't think I can place balls on ropes
oh I can you can so I guess that is what you do so then now how do we push the
key like oh how do you oh you can pick them up
they're can't put down sword see hello well you don't try it and you try and do
it I mean you try and do it beg me there's no begging someone say
something nice about me put that key in that slot or you're gonna have an
incredibly angry fucking person here put it in your slot okay this joke is done
no one like even one threatened I'm a fucking you know how you do that give
you money okay now so freeze it when it gets that's weigh it down freeze it we
need to break the ceiling so I think you need to make another rope that angles up
to launch a ball up I can't attach it to anything though unless you put like a
ball over here I can attach to like a to that it's pretty janky but it'll
probably work will it work just keep just keep doing it will happen it's I
think yeah no okay that what I did not make another ball we just we yeah yeah
we might need to swing the ball around the left one yeah we need to attach
that to the ball yeah so now you swing it like a pendulum yeah dude the three
Triners knew that that was testing everyone else oh okay all right bring
this night wait it's done can I just make a box every once in a
while demolish we did it the right way the way the gamer game makers intended
nice what what's happened you got hurt on these hold on let me freeze this get
on but give her yeah just use way down I want to actually went through it went
through I mean we we could push that the whole like Jeremy can't aim with the
analog but I mean that went through it did everybody knows that's what happened
yes oh that's bouncing okay I think we should go up in waves no I'll let me
shoot that okay wait we have his journal why don't we just go back we're gonna go
back I mean like we got the Badgers journal and he was at the entrance so
why are we continuing to walk forward you only go right in this game I mean
that's what I'm getting at you do only go right but it's part of the game we
keep going forward we're gonna find like his other like journal yes secret diary
we're going to break over here we do have a ceiling to break so I don't think
even well you know there's it's not there's nothing to hit over there well
I mean is that you get that purple stuff how come I'm not on the Diablo 2
Paladin scepter guy because I that takes it takes a lot more skilled than shoot
bow all right push it this way so I can get this or never mind see that's
exactly what I'm talking about like I didn't mean it's like every time I reach
for the jump button there's always instantly I think we have to move dude I
keep trying to make boxes in the spot to help people jump and then you just keep
like going like mashing on it like I'm twirling 720s why did that just stop
now you need we need to move this no we don't but I want to do it like that
because I want to play the game the game I'm gonna wait originally all right
just box speed jump let me box you oh that that wolf's wearing clothes he's a
furry what is wrong with you why can I grab this there has to be a reason I
freeze I can freeze that one fuck your box I think yeah we just jump up why
did you break my eyes I think the other thing the other yeah oh can you get you
want you want to freeze the other one again
get the ball out of the way get the ball out of the way what's up here
gems and gems gems and gems oh no I can't get this without a super help
hey somebody's come up here there's a big one up here and I can't get it on my
own unless can I do like jumping this twice and no okay this one's hard this
is okay okay okay I got the jewel but I can't get the things over here just
wait there Ashley oh this guy needs boxes he needed boxes I did and I
appreciate the help too much power respect I think it's time to switch
Steve off the wizard what do you guys think back to the wizard or you get the
horns don't you do it I mean I can say your character was standing there doing
that thing and I knew I knew it the way you were standing still all right hold
on who would built like what is the point of building is that enough I'm
gonna put our cat goes into these planks can you get up there because I can do
yeah oh I could in a second if someone gave me a box cuz I can can you grab
the edge if it's slippery I'll just do this not he's he's he's he's trying to
be funny I'm I was what that was pure help oh you were trying you guys
overthunk this shit out of that the first time you froze it you could just
jump up I'm talking about overthunker we overthunk don't you mean we were
overthinking it no whoa hey how many how many of those drinks did you drunk by
the way God yeah well I didn't over drunk them like you did you're gonna be
nice so I can put this key in again we weren't nice the first time I think I'm
I think I'm actually gonna make a stand this time you're gonna come you're gonna
get the other key Ashley it's the rope for this is too long watch so yeah it's
true I don't do it there okay now say something nice one for each key don't
okay something nice about what you about me you're very good at doing going
through things very fast without doing them what the way they're supposed to be
done and you do them very quickly and it kind of ruins the game but you do very
well going fast now now Ashley I like your haircut so hard it was that easy
little does he know hey this is too positive with the negativity I'd
explained to my parents what a zoomer haircut meant so we were still in his
house
all that crickets okay okay so the nightmare prince who summons wolves the
first place he ran to was a badger and now this looks like a porcupine 100%
nightmare prince is a furry no he's afraid of furries and that's why he's
tormenting right and break it why does what that other one what the first the
second one didn't break it what okay stop saying the word furry furry furry
what happened to Hillary's furries constant conflict I think I killed it
now can we say fuzzies how about fluffy I'm just saying that I'm trying to
figure out the more so we're not we're not direct the water you got to rope it
right now you don't worry and the flower oh you're missing most just rope the
water German is fucking weird what what did I do more about what do you have
inhibitions of doing I'm just you know I'm just hanging out man I'm just saying
that they're very specifically not scale ease like they all okay I'm the weird
one you talking about furries for 20 minutes I'm the weird one today I mean we
haven't gone into detail what we could ever read Redwall it was like the furry
starter kit he's so I know you can't I can't say that cuz that means I am what
no this it's a chat thing someone's saying something chat I can't if I say
no I'm not then I am so I'm not gonna say if I say I'm not that I am no I'm
mad the word is mad not what you know mad not the other one actually can you
put in the point to the double shield thing or something I cannot still walk
okay then okay you just need to come stand down here and I just move the
boxes who cares anyway German is molding that's like I don't know it's like you're
so bald you matter you're so bad that you've all it's I don't know I've been
trying to figure it out I've actually been trying to figure this out it's like
a new thing clearly it has a kernel of truth because it's getting you oh well
no we'll see we'll see and like okay like then like 10 to 15 years when all
you guys are starting to lose your fucking hair a little and then you
remember back when you I just almost killed that motherfucker you remember
back when you were saying all the mold shit and you're gonna be like okay I'm
going bald too because in a couple years you're actually going to be bald
no I'm not
from we're not not gonna equalize an age this is the point when I get up from the
chair and I go look in the mirror and I go Jeremy this is a purpose you're gonna
be fine did I just fucking with you everyone's just messing with you you're
gonna be fine and then I come back and sit back down but you didn't do that no
that's why it's just tough wait you guys didn't go left what's this here for I
was up here oh you were there were things though I got the juices I can
maybe put a second box there okay wait uh-huh
Oh secret room secret room a double secret room is there a triple secret
room triple secret room that's my real hair I can do with it what I want it's
my real hair yeah and they're always in a swimming pool it's always like look at
me I'm in the swimming pool that's what like when you can't hide your bulb
just don't go under Pontius now has the dream shield hold up shield and hit now
your shield can dream did I learn you know you two shields you got a double
bounce think about my shield really hard nice Pontius just walks around
thinking about it in like ten years for somebody just wrote and I'm gonna make a
reference to this so you know like they said like five to ten years ago don't
don't put dumb shit on Facebook don't put it because like what if you go to a
job interview and they see it right that was like the thing they told us like ten
years ago in twitch chat now somebody just wrote I can't stop farting your
boss in ten years is gonna see that just just to make sure let you know so
careful yeah he will no one wants a gasser what do you mean how there's
times that I can't stop party no matter what and Ashley got hired they're gonna
know when you was scratching your ass last all right you're gonna pull that up
and like linked up I did see a story really recently about a guy that like
had done this really amazing charity thing like raised like $200,000 like got
his name on a beer can for this charity and then they felt like two tweets from
eight years ago like everyone took their money back what a good thing we raised
money for but then like put his face on like a beer can or something and the
beer guy didn't want that that tweet guy so watch those farts guys why don't talk
parts are fine yeah we gotta get the light I think I think okay wait wait
wait we shield right the boxes get off the box off over here and now I actually
stand on the boxes and dream shield it down down down yeah what would you do
without me chat won't moving so fast my boss won't see this germ is a furry in
In ten years your boss is gonna go, who the fuck is Jerma?
Is this somebody that you made up in your mind?
Is this supposed to be you? I see it. Also, you know, it's
285 times over the course of six months. You wrote bald idiot
Who's that a reference to?
Who's the bald idiot? Who's this? I don't understand this. Who is that? What's that for?
Well, after the copy was easy to find, just two more flowers to go.
Oh, we're looking for flowers.
Okay.
Where's flowers?
And then he- and then he-
You look at his head, and it's like there's a fucking giant M receding hairline on his head.
I just- what's that? What's that? What's that? Is that funny? Is there something funny there?
You're gonna have to dream shield over to the box. I think.
The plant is in that wall on the right.
So you need to dream shield towards the box so you can second shield it into the wall.
I don't think I could use the dream shield thing when I'm moving though.
My father was the baldest man on earth, and he created this company.
Think I'm gonna let that fly?
Yeah, I'm like hitting F. Nothing's happening.
Can we make a box like right here so I don't bounce or no?
Just keep doing that. I mean, it's hitting the plant. Is it hitting it?
This is stupid. I feel embarrassed. Look how dumb I look. I'm a fucking warrior. This is cool.
I feel like I should be able to grab a- no, wait, but I can grab and make a-
You can, yeah, you can make a rope across. This is what they want.
Yeah, but I can't move it when it's roped and people are jumping on it and it's flying into the sky.
So you're talking about like bang bang.
There we go.
Is it not good enough? There it is.
Hey future boss, I want to go to Chili's at 3 today.
Well, what if- what if you turn out to be- like people dig up things you said from Chili's-
Eww, eww, Chili's is disgusting.
And you are determined to be a bad person, so in the future when your boss sees that in the past the current employee called you bald,
they're happy that they made fun of you because in the future you're bad.
Yeah, what if you go to jail forever for like murder?
There was a Bruce Willis movie about this already. Next.
About people getting promoted for making fun of Bruce Willis?
No, maybe. I need to- come on. I need to move- I need to move this to here.
Thought I had to. And then that means we can go like this and then we can box it up.
I think this is fine.
Oof. Whoa, don't even need it. Wait. Oof.
Wait a minute.
That's cool.
I want to be able to make the plank.
Oh, come on.
You did forget a spell in your old age.
Ooh, I do have- do I have one?
What the hell?
Why does the archer get less shit than everybody else?
Hey! Hey, archer!
Come be useful.
Hey, archer!
Archer!
Here's a hook below you.
That works too.
You can solve problems in like seven different ways and you're mad that you don't have enough things.
I'm molding.
Stop.
Molding. Because molding.
Stop. You're giving them strength.
I like that. Correct.
Break this.
Okay, we're gonna find out that these are the Nightmare Prince's parents.
What, these barrels?
No, the badger and the-
The hedgehog?
Yeah.
That would be stupid.
Okay, do you want to play the wizard?
You know how annoying it is to try and make boxes where people need them but they stand where they want them?
Bald.
He must be bald.
You need me to move these?
Do you need another compliment?
Yeah.
I'll move it. I can do it.
You got a dream shield, the fucking light.
What light? Where is it?
On the right!
Box away.
Just do it straight forward.
What? What was that? Why did that happen?
That's pretty weird.
Don't stop. There you go.
I just made like dice.
On the dashboard.
You almost got it.
Come on.
No. Look, it worked.
The speedrun text.
Oh, look!
You got the prize.
I've never been happy.
I wake up with tears already in my eyes.
What the fuck?
I have to watch the bedding every day.
It keeps crying in it.
Okay, so let me...
Where's the water?
Oh, I don't need water. Double shield here.
And then you stand on my thing.
Daddy up.
Daddy!
Daddy upy!
Daddy look! Steve!
You can't do it that way, dude.
Here, can you stand on that?
I guess you need to bounce. You need to do double shield, don't you?
This isn't working.
It would work.
Look, if you just hang a box
from the ceiling.
I think.
I gotta get like...
There you go.
Now can you get up here?
Yeah, do that.
Yeah, I need something to jump on.
Every time I look over here
there's something else that I just see and I'm just like
I turn back.
My chat is upset
about double shield meta.
What? Why?
Because we were like cheating it before.
No, it's a reference
to a game in my room.
Oh.
No, that is not connected.
It looks like it is, but it's not.
It's not connected.
I mean, you're enough to jump over it.
What did it say?
Do I even need to say it?
Alright, now I go like this.
Dude, you're so good. Thanks.
Dude, you're so good. Go!
You're so good.
Why doesn't someone build a road?
I know, really.
I think we need some boxes.
I'm doing this to like pretend
I'm trying to play.
I'm trying to get, like, maybe if I hit it with my arrow
I'm secretly trying to hit it in the fucking head.
Oh, remember?
Last turn had like the fish level.
Didn't it?
There was a big ol' mean fishy.
Was there?
I don't think we ever completed the last one, did we?
I don't think we did.
I don't think so. We played it for like three and a half hours.
Tops.
Remember when that fisherman like carried Germa away
Hey, there's a big nut up here. Hold on, big nut.
Big nut.
I'm waiting for you to get that shit out of here so I can pull this.
Nevermind.
I don't even need you to do that.
Big nut.
Ooh, it's gonna fall.
That was a lot less dangerous than I thought it was gonna be.
Light.
I don't know how you don't block that.
What, if you stand on a box?
Like, can you...
But then the box will block it.
Uh, okay.
Yeah, do that, and then stand, and then make a box like here.
Do it.
And then stand on the box and make it so it doesn't block the light.
If I can get it in a position where you can do it.
What?
Like this.
There's no hooks or anything.
Oh. I thought it was secure.
Good intentions.
Hey, there it is. Almost.
Just move these forward.
I don't think so. No?
No.
I don't think...
Wait, hold on a second.
Can this be used for anything?
If it bounces that way,
you have to stand here somehow.
I think I know.
I think I know, I think I know, I think I know.
Okay, hold on, hold on.
Brain is going maximum capacity.
You need to make a dream shield...
Okay, get off the box.
You need to make a dream shield
while standing on top of this
that's pointing at the flower.
Right now.
And now you need to get down
and shoot it at the dream shield.
Reverse though.
Nice.
Awesome.
That's cool.
Pretty cool.
I think if you stick something to that...
Oh, never mind.
I think I can just get this one now.
Oh, I didn't see the...
I didn't see it up there.
Oh, I can unfreeze with my butt.
Oh, damn it.
Got it.
You know everything is solved with boxes.
What just happened to me?
Oh, sorry.
I did that on purpose because I wanted
just to explode.
Why are you pushing that?
Box on head or pre-recorded?
Hurry up and do it.
What's he doing with that big toothbrush?
This is too kind.
I can never thank you enough.
If you are looking for the nightmare prince,
I think he was headed towards the northern lakes.
We didn't have to help these people at all,
by the way.
The heroes took the hedgehog's advice
and followed a path leading to the west.
We could have been much faster if we just beat it out of them.
Alright.
Swim level, wee.
Oh my god, it's swim level.
Dude, Ashley.
This thing looks like you.
Where?
It's Otto.
Fuck you, dude.
What are you getting, Cal?
Oh.
I gotta make a signature.
Oh, yeah.
Break it. Snap it.
That's a big nut.
Ooh.
Does it have to be an acorn?
Use the fire arrow to activate
fire switches.
So it stays.
It's not like the freezing arrows.
Please make fire into the water.
Uh-oh.
Well, you gotta drain.
Flash is filling it.
She wants you to have more water.
Still can't upgrade anything.
Oh, Otto.
And it loves it.
Oh, it loves it.
Oh, let's pound it.
Oh, that's traumatizing.
Best part of the game.
Whoa.
This thing's brand new.
Dumbass.
Hahaha.
What?
What the fuck did you just say?
I said, got him.
Alright.
Fire has been activated.
Now we swim through this.
So the stupid swim.
How do you do that?
Through the tunnel.
Got it.
Oh, yeah.
He can do that.
I haven't had to do that move in like
six hours of gameplay.
So I forgot I could do that.
I remember.
Oh, yeah, he can do that.
He can also roll if he has it done.
Just walk forward so you don't stuff
on the plate.
Almost.
Okay.
Ball. On to help.
Good.
Fight.
Water into the wheel.
There was a mermaid.
Oh, I wanna fuck.
Come fuck.
Alright, what's going on?
It's swimming away real fast.
Alright, fire over there.
Ice block.
Can I switch
abilities?
Before I get screamed at?
You can make that shot.
It's kind of hard because I have to
hold.
I have to hold the right
thumb thick.
The right thumb stick.
The right thumb tack.
Just compound us.
Let me get the pine cone on here.
Please.
He doesn't want to do it
the right way. He wants to do it the fast way.
I'm the person who
can lift these things and you keep fucking
jumping on it. I didn't do anything.
I'm pounding.
Now he wants to do two boxes.
I've seen this shtick
before. He wants two boxes over here for you to
jump on and skip the whole level.
I'm angry.
I'm not even close
to his balls.
I'm still mad.
Imagine how mad he is.
I actually may have more hair than you.
What?
Maybe.
We're going on a hair off.
My hair is higher quality.
I think it's higher to the ceiling too.
True.
Let's go to a hair salon and determine who has higher
quality hair.
I've been told I've got some fucking high
By who? Your mom?
Yeah, my mother said that.
Can you help me here?
Sounds like a mom compliment to me.
Will you put like a block on this?
Hey!
It's not my fault my blocks don't weigh enough
to satisfy you. Wait a minute.
Damn it.
If you're going to bring leg hair into this.
Hey, hello?
I don't know. Your legs are kind of scarred up
You have scars you don't grow hair.
Yeah, but the rest of my leg makes up
like I could probably make three sets
of Jerma's hair with a leg.
That's because your legs are so much longer than this.
Okay.
I mean, Jerma, honestly,
we were both able to do this.
Yeah, because you're putting boxes down
and you're talking about leg hair.
We get it. You got gross leg hair.
I do.
More of it.
Right in the car.
We got our puzzle.
Because everyone loves water levels.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm working.
Pull it down. Stand on it.
Oops.
I gotta freeze it.
Hold on.
Isn't that what we need?
Didn't we do it?
Yeah, now Jerma has to put the fire switch.
We did it.
Is it?
Shoot it.
Come on.
We did it.
Let's just leave.
Wait, is that the mermaid?
No. Oh my god.
I'm trying to shoot it.
You just crushed me.
Oh no, not Otto.
Bring it down.
Save Otto.
I'll save my own damn dog.
How's Otto doing? What's new with him?
What's in the news?
He's going to be a hot dog for Halloween.
Oh, that's a big surprise.
Yeah.
What the fuck?
This is somebody's arm.
It's a giant nightmare hand.
Okay, put it down here.
I need to jump on that to hit the flame.
Can you freeze the hand?
I tried it already.
I think we have to pull him forward and then I have to get up there.
Hmm.
I can't jump.
Put down another box so I can jump onto it.
What if I put the box here?
He breaks the box.
He's like, hey, fuck that box.
Oh, there we go.
Oh, you can do it.
Use the analog stick. Yeah.
Nice analog aiming.
Oh no, Otto.
I can just hold him, I think.
Then I have to...
What do we do with the water?
Get it out of here.
Water.
Oh my god, he's still holding onto him.
Worry.
Okay, that...
Hooray.
Yeah, that was just helping with that bubble.
You can now conjure a plank.
New shape. Pretty cool.
So much more advanced than a cube.
Wow.
You could not have done that without me.
Well, but now you're going to be like slightly annoying giant plank guy.
Giant plank, all right.
I know, it's already pretty annoying.
New letter.
That character can't read.
Anything down here?
I don't think so.
Steve!
What do you know?
He's throwing pool covers at us. Great.
He's declaring war is what he's doing.
Okay, here.
No, I gotta stand on this.
All right, guys.
How can a plank help?
All right, keep it.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
Okay, now I need...
Just jump up. Jump up and I'll elevator you.
Go!
Excellent.
They're dogs.
Yeah, I need to...
I'm gonna do this.
Nice.
Let's synchronize with the ball.
Anything up there?
Mister.
All right, stop.
You're hurting Otto.
No.
You just hit him in the head twice.
I can't.
Hold on.
I need to get on...
Okay, go ahead.
Now do the thing you were just doing.
How come this puzzle isn't solved yet?
I don't know.
I gotta phrase it. Phrase. Phrase.
Move, you thing.
I think this is a life lesson.
Just need a couple of boxes and it's pretty much it.
Okay.
Oh, balls are on.
I got a new upgrade.
Oh, you did? Well...
I'm trying to understand how to use it.
Wait, what?
Can get another upgrade.
Oh, this is the bouncy ball.
Oh, it's adorable.
Can we bounce it around together? Oh, that's cool.
I'm like ice farts.
I don't understand how this one works.
I should be able to push you off.
This thing doesn't make any sense.
It says, okay, okay, okay.
One conjuring an object, keep holding down left or right until the super throw is loaded.
I can't summon a ball or anything while holding down that button.
I'm gonna just hit.
Oh.
It doesn't make any sense.
Did you just push me off?
I mean, all we need right now is a couple of boxes.
Hold on, I'm trying to figure out my thing.
Here, take your stupid boxes and just solve.
I mean, there's not much to solve.
We just have to jump from jump to jump.
If I make another one, that one's gonna disappear now.
Oh, it didn't.
Okay.
What? What?
Oh, the spikes are coming through the plank.
I have fucking no shoes on.
Oh my god.
No, no.
Whatever, go forward.
I'll teleport.
Doesn't matter. Didn't happen.
We got a fight coming up here.
I can't figure it out.
So it's just a bouncy...
It's a bouncy ball.
Now, I've had the bouncy ball for a while.
Yeah, I didn't know how to activate it.
But now it's when I have something over my head, I'm supposed to be able to shoot it forward.
But the buttons don't make any sense.
Another water puzzle coming up here.
I'm gonna draw the object you want.
We'll see if I draw the object.
I draw a square.
I'm holding down left click.
And the moment I let go, the box is made.
But in order to throw it forward, it's saying to keep holding down left.
But I can't keep holding it down because I just fucking made it.
And I let go of left to make it.
But if I pick up an object, like I have this object and I hold down left, nothing happens.
You lost me. You lost me at like...
Hey, are you in the Discord?
Just start streaming.
Nothing's happening.
Honey.
Can I have a plank?
Little bit more to the right.
Little bit more.
Yeah.
Honey.
But this time it goes down there.
And there.
Look at that.
Hey, Koryn.
I think we can go up here.
There's a spike there.
Now how do we get up there?
Another one? Another rock?
Yep.
Cool. It was a big one.
It's right click. I've held right click.
I'm holding right click to pick this up right now.
It says release right click and it'll shoot.
I'm holding left click.
Like nothing it says is true.
Do you remember what a pine cone is?
And it says when conjuring an object.
So I can press Q to conjure this?
Or hold on.
I can press...
Which one is...
I forgot what button the box is.
Press F to hold left click.
Then once I hold left click I'm fucking moving it.
Nothing about this.
I'm just trying to get over to the other side.
Okay, there we go.
I have to hold left click and not on it.
And then it primes it in a random spot.
Okay, we figured it out.
Steve, they're all accusing you
of being bald the longer this rank goes on.
No.
I'm good.
You guys need help?
Fuck, no. I just did this.
Pipe incoming.
Wait a minute, but how do we block that?
So I can shoot the arrow.
I understand. Like if I pick up a box I can't launch it ever.
Because I have to do it when I conjure it.
Why is this moving like this?
How?
You can't even kill it.
I mean, it's fun.
Right now the star is in his own server
shooting bots.
Hello?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Yeah.
Okay. My mom was calling me.
I'm sorry.
You hung up on her?
No, she was calling me to come down for dinner.
So.
That's a lie.
Okay, now I'm going to shoot that.
Oh, no, I can't.
Can someone get rid of this bouncy ball?
I don't know. Maybe we should ask the wizard.
Get this ball out of here. Come on.
I like the balls a lot. I'm sorry.
Do you have a rock concert?
Is there a beach ball flying around?
No.
Oh, boss. Boss.
Boss prince.
Look at him moping.
You have to kill yourself.
So he's a bad guy.
Nothing.
No.
My mentor.
So we have to fight the
three of them at the same time.
The three gay dads.
How do we do this?
Wait, these are your three dads?
And we're all Pontius?
Why?
I don't even know how to play.
How do you do the dash?
Oh, shit.
I think we should bounce back his big ball
at our dad.
Oh, now is when the upgrades would matter.
I guess.
They switched me to a different Pontius.
That's stupid.
Oh, we got a launch.
Watch the top left.
Can we pick that up?
Yeah, I bet you guys wish you had a bouncy ball right now.
He just broke our shields.
Oh, shit.
I kind of do.
This is kind of messy.
We've got to get rid of their forcefields first.
Oh.
He's going to throw it.
Oh, that was a bad idea.
Oh, you have to dash and hit him.
Honestly, he's the strongest dad.
Daddy, why?
Watch the left.
No, we were too tall. He was too tall.
Oh, fuck.
Where did I go?
I don't even know where I am.
Oh, yeah. Dead.
Steve, you're alive.
Rez.
I just rezzed into a sword in the head.
Where's the heals?
Focus now.
Wait, I was alive?
Geez, we beat the shit out of them.
Oh, my God.
Look at that hot dad pile.
Fucking dead.
You know, we're not saving a prince.
Celius is turning into a villain.
And you know what we do with villains.
Zoya is right.
If we can't save the prince,
we're going to have to fight him.
We're going to bring him to court.
Well, geez, you just slaughtered your whole family.
Hello?
You have a problem? Hello?
Dude, heaven.
Crackling Maya.
Distressed by their last encounter with Celius,
the heroes continued their dogged pursuit
into the wild woodlands.
As night grew closer,
there was no sight nor sound
of Celius.
And the heroes found themselves
dreadfully lost.
Oh, no.
What? What are you doing?
I'm trying to start the level.
No.
It screwed up all our characters.
What do we do now?
What's the tool?
Instead of pursuing,
what is Jackbox?
Where's Jack?
Here, speedrun. We don't need the extra objectives anymore.
We don't have all our attribute points.
It's speedrun time.
Fine.
Fine. All right, fine.
It's time to observe
our place across the quest
and whatever she's saying.
The ground is made out of electricity.
Step on it! Let's go!
Jump into any ponds after strange ladies.
Oh, and that's electrified as well
because it's in the electricity.
Is that electrified? No.
That's wood.
That's electrified.
I'm just so used to jumping on stuff.
I know.
No longer electrified. Can I freeze it?
No.
You did it double power. You made it twice as more powerful.
Oh my god, I can kill you guys so easily now.
You always could.
I know.
Power was in the all along. Up top.
Oh, that didn't work.
We're just going fast now.
Jerma said I was good at going fast.
Yes, you are.
I didn't say the two of us were either.
Time for me to shine.
Race, race, race.
It's electricity.
I'm jumping in it.
Well, what do we...
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
Get off of it.
Oh my god, guys. Please get off of it.
Ashley, please get off.
You're...
Okay.
Okay. Pretty good.
Nice work.
You have to shoot the rope.
Shoot the rope.
Something happened.
You need to build a boat.
Ow!
That didn't look electrified.
I don't think we can get over this.
Build a what?
I thought you didn't want to collect these anymore.
Well, you guys were...
I was waiting for you to shoot the rope for like an hour.
Like a full hour.
How do we open this?
Oh, the connection needs to be met.
Right?
Pull the box out of the way.
You have to rope it again, I think.
Just lift up the box.
No, no, no. Get it out of the way.
Tell me what to do again.
I'll come to your house and say hello.
I'll say hi.
What?
I died inside of this thing.
That thing explodes.
That's a full party life.
Shit.
That's bullshit. I have plate mail.
I'm going to freeze the guy that's electrified.
He's causing all the problems.
There's the duck.
Ooh!
Two ropes at the same time.
That's so cool. How do I do two ropes at the same time?
I can use two ropes at the same time.
Okay.
Get it out of the way.
Me and Ashley are going over.
What are you doing?
We're going over.
That's really cool that you have two ropes.
Whatever.
It's so hard to tell.
It is.
Do I have a wood plank anywhere?
No, I don't.
Can you plank us?
They get electrified.
Anything I do gets electrified.
Even the bouncy ball.
Maybe the bouncy ball doesn't bounce.
You need a rubber.
It is rubberized.
It's only science.
This is hard though.
That was almost a full party life.
Without respawn timers.
At least somebody got up there.
That's definitely what you have to do.
I think we only need one of these
and the second one is causing a problem.
I was grabbing the edge.
I made it.
We have to be safe.
Move over.
I got a link.
Does that have to stay there?
What is it doing?
It's opening the door.
Is it?
It is.
The top door is opening.
Can you grab that wood plank?
There's a wood plank up there on the left.
He got too close.
Hold on.
I wish I could unsummon things.
I got that out of the way.
It's everywhere.
Every time I try to move something
someone touches it.
I want to die too.
I could have made it.
I'm stuck here.
You made it up there.
I can't freeze it.
Please stop touching my wood.
I'm touching your wood.
Now walk forward.
Watch that connection.
Why did I not grab the edge?
Pull it up.
Just launch me.
What?
The door is not open.
It is.
This box was slightly not there.
Have fun you two.
Get to a place where I can die.
Quietly.
You come across.
One at a time.
Very fast.
We're so good.
Maybe even the best.
That was slick.
What's this for?
Secret?
I was told no secrets.
No secrets.
Look at you trying to get secrets.
That wasn't a secret.
That was just trying to get the thing.
Trying to get the thing?
Oh my God.
Remember if another streamer
does a terrible joke
it's not my fault.
You endorse everything we say.
Just by us being here.
They just don't like when you do it.
Now they don't.
What now?
Now I'm going to freeze
this one.
Ball.
Give me that ball.
I'm going to sneak this way.
You froze it.
You're good.
I'm going.
They're trying to kill us.
Wait.
Why would we wait?
Oh my God.
The whole screen is death right now.
Don't break that barrel.
I'm paying you to never make that joke again.
I've got a few more.
I think you can just
I can just do this.
No. This.
I want to grab the...
No.
Maybe we need more weight up here?
That's a thing.
Get that box off there.
Oh God.
Hey.
I'm over here.
You can ice block.
The ice doesn't seem to be frozen.
We can't make that jump though. We need a box.
The box is frozen.
If you do that
that works.
Now we just have to figure out how to go from here to there.
Probably with
a box maybe?
A ball?
Wait a minute.
I think we can do this.
Hold on.
What?
Why did that happen?
You know what we got to do.
You know what it's time for.
That's what I just said.
That didn't work.
Start it over.
Wait.
Give me another one.
Come on. Give me that.
It doesn't bounce that high.
This is the worst thing in the world.
I thought it was going to bounce high.
It's certainly not what they want you to do.
Come on. This will work.
I definitely have to make a...
Put a box over here.
Not on the ice.
Put a box on the ice.
I can just do this.
Why did you die?
Something funky going on.
Game?
Now that's safe.
Just launch one of us up there.
Okay.
Yoink.
We got it.
Just solve it with box physics.
Do we need that ball for anything?
I guess not.
Probably.
This guy's got to go.
Skellington.
Those things can destroy my ropes.
Just block those holes.
No.
I just saved my...
Okay.
Just do rope, rope, rope.
Get this box out of the way.
It targets the box.
I can't destroy the box.
Okay.
There's that one.
I can do another one from here to there.
From here to there.
I don't know if that helps.
There you go.
Do bouncy balls.
Okay.
I can go across.
Just block both the holes.
Okay.
Oh my god.
I made it.
Good.
I think this is the result we were looking for.
I just can't die.
Just keep going.
I died.
It's impossible.
If I do this...
I can make that.
I can't make that.
How did that work?
Okay. I'm going to shit my pants.
I already did.
Same.
I need to shoot the one below.
Did I get it?
Where am I?
I'm currently still alive.
How did I end up back here?
Things are getting goofy, guys.
They are.
There has to be a button to unsummon.
I can't.
They're stuck.
I need to cut this.
Let me get this thing out of here.
Get that ball out of here.
It's attached still.
It has a rope on it in the back.
It shouldn't have any ropes.
I think it's wanting you to go under the bottom.
Attach to the thing on the top.
It's electrified.
Yeah.
Rope from these.
And swing to the other side.
Do you understand?
Hold on.
I have to have it be small.
I can now ride it all the way across.
Now you have a lever.
Pull it!
Don't destroy this.
I guess they just explode when they touch lightning.
I think they just exploded in general.
It's a little electrified.
You can rub it.
There's a rope.
It's sticky.
Very sticky.
Now we're getting high level.
That's not electrified.
Which one should I freeze?
Left one?
Sure.
If you can.
I think you can just get over here.
There's a safe spot.
There's a safe spot right over there.
Okay.
I can just launch someone.
Oh God.
Hold on.
Yep.
I can just hold on.
Now you don't have to worry.
Now you're safe.
Okay.
Enjoy your Kinect.
You get to play Kinect.
C-O-N-N-E-C-T.
Working for a second. Can you freeze?
We got to wait for this to come around
and it's going to work.
Oh my God.
Jerma!
Where are we?
Can you freeze the top thing?
No.
I said no as I pressed it
and did it.
No.
It breaks the eye.
Do it.
What? Now it's not breaking.
You have to electrify the top one.
Like that.
It broke last time though.
What?
Maybe because we didn't compliment you enough.
That was fun.
Jerma shot it, did he?
Did he ruin the whole thing?
I don't think he did.
Oh, she's pregnant.
What the fuck?
What?
The fuck?
Are you talking about?
What do we got for a time?
It was currently 3 o'clock.
Pacific.
Do you want a jack?
It might be jack time.
Did it jack off?
No.
What?
Jerma has it pre-scheduled every day.
Now that he's changed stream schedules,
it's messing with us a bit.
His house is full of alarm clocks
and they all go off.
3, 4, 3.30, 3.10.
Time to jack.
The next time anybody dies,
we move on.
we move on to jack box.
He's about to jump off the mat.
Try as hard as you can.
I guess we're in for another fishing camp.
Okay.
I'm trying so hard.
There we go.
Freeze it.
Fight.
I don't want to see any deaths here.
I got you.
Why is that frozen?
It has the fairy rope.
When attaching a rope to a loose object,
keep holding down.
Keep holding down.
What does that mean?
Tie the rope to the hook.
I can just walk it?
Can you get your ball out of the way?
I can't because people keep walking on it
and getting stuck on things.
I don't understand.
What did that rope do?
Hold on.
It just pulls it up.
So no matter what,
it's going to pull.
It looks like he just intentionally walked to his death
because he wants the jack.
Jack box.
That's right.
It's time.
Who knew that Germa would die first?
I was just trying to work it out.
All right.
Jack box party pack six.
You guys don't need it.
I don't think anybody needs it but me, right?
That's how it was traditionally.
I think we just need the website
and the code.
So don't give out the code on stream.
No, no, no.
You're pretty amateur.
No, I have sub discord.
I don't put it in the stream.
Give it to us.
I'm not in your sub discord.
I've been subbed to you
for like seven years.
I've never taken it off.
All right, let me switch.
Just give me one second.
All right, give me a sec.
Everybody take like a break.
How about like a two minute, three minute break?
Go pee, get some water.
And when you come back, jack box will be going strong.
Sounds good. Be right back.