Hey, how's everybody doing? Hopefully pretty good. I'm just hanging out here.
Everybody, you have 20 minutes to live. Don't worry, I'm gonna be just fine.
Let me just change this over. Just tweeted it. It's pre-recorded, it's not. Look, I'm getting
ready here. I'm trying as hard as I can to get ready. These are resistant gloves. I've got,
I've got lots of padding. I've got lots of padding. I'm ready for a fucking meteor to hit.
Get the other one on. All right, we're good. But not yet. Pocky pads too. I think these are for
children because I don't think I've got the correct one that were for adults. I think it
actually says in the back that this is for people in the eighth grade. It's all right,
it's okay. It's just Velcro. I could have taken, all right, it does fit. It is for
an adult because I have the strap still on. Padding breached. Don't say that. So you got,
okay, so let me make sure I get this correct. Let me stand up. This is like, this is for a
meteor, right? Resistant gloves. I mean, this is, on the package it said it was for gardening.
But I mean, there could be some acid that I could come into contact with that I won't be
touching here. I got my padding. Should get this on too. Audio is out of sync. How so?
Is it? It shouldn't be. Hello, hello, it's out of sync. This is my helmet to protect me from any
face related injuries. I feel like a Lego guy. No, hold on. I gotta like cover the logos.
I didn't cover the logos. Just stay right there. Sorry, I just had to find these. I had
to find the scissors because this tape is wicked fucked up. It's stuck together. You see?
Why is it stuck together? It just give me the roles. Like, look at this. This is not even a joke.
That works. No, it doesn't. Look at this. Why would you duct tape together? Duct tape.
Who thought of this idea? All right. Okay. There we go.
No, it's gonna shoot back in. As you can see, I put foam padding all over my room to be
able to participate in. I got foam in the corner. See? I foam padded my room.
Nice feet, idiot. This is a stressful day for me. Oh, my feet are protected. That makes perfect
sense as to why you would just say that. Exposed feet. I didn't think that far ahead. I thought
about my chest. What time is it? I got, I got 13 minutes. Ah, god damn it. I slept in late
because the fucking 12 hour stream last night. Get the helmet. I will. I will. I'm gonna get
the helmet on, but I don't, I, it's got like a big logo on it. All right. Here we go. Beer,
me, username. Thanks for the 10 community subs. Let's just get this logo covered.
Thank you for the 10 community subs. Don't worry. We're gonna make it. We're gonna make it.
There we go. I just don't want anyone to see. I don't want company names and all that.
I don't want anyone to know what company name that is. You know, company names gotta get
covered. There we go. Now I can put this on. See? We're good. I feel like I'm about to go
get a fucking massage. I hate this. See, I could like, I could like smash my head into something.
The straps gonna choke you. Don't say something like that. Uh oh. No variables. No variables
allowed. None. Okay. Okay. Eye protection. Don't touch anything. They're not gonna put,
this hurts. How do people wear these? I would rather dodge the fucking shot of glass
that's gonna come through. No, I'll be all right. Cause now, okay, if like the ceiling
caves in, it's gonna hit me right in the crown of the head. This only protects my cheekbones
and my forehead. I got an exposed neck. Don't worry. I got like a plan. I don't have a plan.
I'm gonna have to like lie down. I'm gonna lie down over there. How's it back look? Pillows.
Hold on. Fucking idiot. One, two, three. I shouldn't have got the mail like this.
It's not the right. I got it. Hold on. I feel like this is a doctor from like the 1600s.
All right. That's good. All right. I just look, I look like a nun. Crown of the head is covered.
Head. Shoulders. Acid resistant gloves. What time is it? I got 10 minutes. Not even. You're
gonna die from overheating. It's, it's very cold outside right now. Don't worry. I've had
plenty of water. Protect my neck. I'm just gonna go like that. Don't worry. And I gotta
lie down. I gotta like lie the fuck down somewhere. I'm gonna have like red cheeks.
What if you need to pee? That's, it's just gonna happen. You know, it's just gonna happen.
Look, I have only 10 minutes until it's over. What about getting hit by a broom?
I'll grab it with my heat resistant hands. He's gotta pee. I don't have to pee right
now. I'm just fine. Why would I catch fire? I am completely protected from the elements.
Rain. Ceiling cave-in. Explosion. Cross check. You know what I mean? Bar soap falling down.
Acid. Oh, I got some, hold on. Shrists. Shrids. Shins. Wrists. I'm ready. And I'm gonna keep
my, I, but you don't see down here as I have survived two big foot cases that I'm sticking
them in right now. We got, all right. I need to relax. What do you think? Where's
a good spot? I'm thinking right here. It's out of the way again. It's in a variable.
Get the variables out of the way. Check the closet. Remember, always go fucking acid gloves first.
We're good. All right. Any like paint that could fall on me.
I'm ready. We got like four minutes. God damn it, man. Getting fucking nervous now.
Feet. Feet. I told you I got, I got a thing to put my feet into in case something happens.
I was gonna stick them in here. Look, see? We're good. Seal the room. Fucked gas.
Toxic gas is gonna. I don't have enough time for this. I gotta get, I gotta go lie down.
No, I'm gonna lose my security deposit. I'm gonna, I'll be all right.
The door moved. The door didn't move. We're fine. All right. Okay. I gotta get,
I gotta get in the position. Position, position, position, position. Which position?
And we're gonna have on like some very easy relaxing music. Relaxing music. Relaxing sleep
music. This is as good. Can I even hear it? Don't put anything in your ear. That's good.
Okay. Okay. I'm gonna go. Here we go. Okay. Three minutes. Get out of the way. Right here.
I'm gonna lie, just lie down. Okay. Right here. Protect acid hands. We good? Oh shit,
what time is it? All right. All right. Nobody talk. I was relaxing. It was very relaxing. No.
Wait, what? How do I get in? How do I get back inside? You gotta be kidding me.
Can you see me? Can anybody see me? Oh, come on. This is not even possible.
I had the headgear on. I had on, I got the special belt. I duct taped the house.
Can I click? I can't interact with any of this shit. Fuck.
Hey. Hey, wake up. Oh. Maybe I saw this in a movie once. This is my uniform that I wear when I'm a
ghost. The same shit that I had on is just no fucking fat suit. All right. Hold on a minute.
I saw Freaky Friday with Lindsay Lohan and I remember they did the same thing.
I just, I gotta jump in and think about all the fucking memories that I've ever had.
Right? Every memory I've ever had, I gotta make them all come out in one second. Here we go.
Baby. Well, it was a pretty, it was pretty good, I guess. Just make sure to, uh, anytime that you...
It's great. I was in eighth grade. 440, 448. 448? I just put my head down. Was it four...
I was freaking out. Wait, are we still... Is that real? Four... I can't really see.
That doesn't make any sense. Can we confirm this is not a fucked up clock?
449. I just put my head down. I just, I literally... Holy shit. Well, there we are.
I just put my head down for a second. Strange. Um, okay. I did it. I made it.
Thanos' head. Yeah, it was easy. Watch out what happens on January 23rd. You're gonna be in
trouble. Yeah. All this for no fucking reason. Unbelievable. I spent through, I go through all
the trouble. Turn that music off. We don't even need it. He's behind you. I was, I panicked. I
was freaking out for nothing. Sometimes I'll let you guys get to me, you know? Sometimes you guys
come up with these fucking elaborate stories. How did this get on the ground? I may move my
chair back over here. I was pushed over. What is the after... What are you talking about?
I literally laid down right there. I blinked and I wanted to check the time. And that's
it. Like, I must have, maybe, I don't know. Maybe I, maybe I, maybe I was sitting here
and didn't realize it was like 445. Nice tattoos. Where? 7,000. Holy shit. There's
7,000 people here watching. Well, I'm sorry to disappoint you all. So we're gonna, we're
gonna transition here. We're gonna, uh, I really thought this was only gonna be like
a 30 or 40 minute stream anyways, but I mean, we're gonna transition. What happened
in the eighth grade? What do you mean eighth grade? Finished Lifeline. I could hook up
Lifeline and we'd give it another go. You sneezed in the eighth... When did I sneeze?
All right, I gotta get out of this. Because I was in it for, what a fucking waste. I was
in it for no reason. I'll be back. I, let me get out of this and like fucking
shake my hair. I'll be right back. We're gonna play Lifeline. What do you mean joke
incoming? No, I'm just, I'm taking off all this, like, fat suit padding. I just
don't want the camera on me. Hold on. I'll be back. I, I, give me, I got,
you're gonna have to give me, like, at least a few minutes here.