Hello. Hold on. Sorry. Welcome to the stream, everybody. How you doing? What's going on?
That was a really unenthusiastic hello. Hello. Let me just grab my tea. I got a green tea. Let me get
it. I'll be right back. That EU stream today. That's right. We're back. Okay. So today,
as you're probably recognizing, we've got a sponsor segment today. It's gonna be a good one.
This is Power Wash Simulator. If you remember, I played this game about a year ago. And what do you
know? This shit's in 1.0. It's out. I think actually literally today. Like right now.
Hold on. I got the wrong straw. All right. All right. All right. All right. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Yeah, the stream is sponsored today by of course, Power Wash Sim. It's out on everything.
Xbox, Xbox One, PC, Steam, everything. Go take a look. And so since a year ago,
I think they've added a lot of shit to the game. So we'll see what they have.
Is this on Xbox? Dude, I'm so happy you asked. It's on Xbox, Xbox One, PC, Steam, Xbox Series S.
Why did that take me so long to say that? No, I actually really like this game. This game was
really fun last time I played it. So I'll have a year of development, by the way.
Was this game in early access? Because was this only? That's a pretty awesome story there.
The game was in early access for like a year, year and a half, whatever. And now it's out.
That's it. Easy. Early access for like a year. Out. Released. All right. Let's go. This multiplayer?
What the? What? What? All right. Hi. Hello. All right. So what was it? What was in the game
last time? Was it just this career mode before? You're the same shirt as yesterday. No, what?
The shirt I had on yesterday was black. This is a gray shirt. How would this? This is not the shirt
I had on yesterday. This is gray. You're unclean. Well, yeah, maybe I could use a power washing.
It's the same background. I'm sorry. I don't have a funny Zoom conference call joke where there's a
roller coaster behind me. Dude, it has cross play with Xbox players too? Holy shit. Can I swear on
this? I think so. Okay. I hope so. All right. So what did I do last time? All right. I wait,
did I not finish this? Oh, it's so it kept the other stuff that I did. All right, cool.
What's specials? Clean the Mars Rover, gnome fountain, steam locomotive, golf course. Should
I do the golf course? Free play? All right. So should I finish what I started here?
I took a power washing job a year ago and I did half the house. I just left. And then
I called the same family a year later and I go, hey, come back and finish that job
that I did halfway. The same price, of course. All right, let's go. Yeah, this is,
I like it. I'm gonna turn the volume up. It's a little low. I don't know if it's too loud.
How did I turn it way down? Why did I turn the volume so low? Why is everything so low?
There we go. Okay, well, that that's why I did that.
That was a little too loud. That was a little too loud for my for my liking. Okay, there we go.
All right. So what's wrong with it? What's wrong with this? You were doing a bit the last time
you played. What was the bit I was doing? Oh my god, I hope nobody was at the front door.
This is like a laser. Okay, I didn't do anything. What was the routine I was doing last time?
It was oh yeah, it was all dogs talk like Scooby-Doo. That was a fucking year ago.
I felt like that was last weekend. How was that was that long ago? Oh, I love it. Oh, all right.
So I missed this whole side of the house. Taking care of your gutters for free.
And that's when I leave a card. I leave a card on the fucking front step. Oh, isn't there a button
you can do to see how much is left? How much of cleaning you have to do left? Tab. Yeah, there's
like there's like a hitman like see through walls thing, right? How did I get how do I get on the
roof? They're looking out the window right now. Honey, I don't know where you found this guy,
but he keeps spraying the same two sections of the house. And he charges $1,000 an hour. Oh,
you can rotate the nozzle to y'all. Yeah, you can. I remember this fast. Is this the new
phasmophobia update? No, this is power wash simulator. It's available right now. It just
came into 1.0 games. Great games fun. We played it. It's been a while. You can get it right now.
I highly suggest you do the game is fucking phenomenal. No music. What the hell is this?
Why did they why did they they added a VR mode? All right. What is this? No music. How did I turn
it off? Did I remove it from like the I&I files? I don't know. I don't think so. But somebody asked
but hey, is it out for Xbox? I'm really glad you asked that question. Of course it is.
Xbox Series S. Actually, is it on? I don't want to say something that's not true.
It's on. All right. Xbox has that service, right? Where you can it's a service that you can you can
pay for and it's something could be on that service. Is it on that service? Is it in there?
It's on that service. All right. All right. Somebody said, what did I do?
I mean, I mean, honest to God, I got to tell you, it's just good clean fun.
Like really, it really is though. I'm like, I'm serious.
What if this don't do the roof? How the fuck are they going to know? You know what I mean?
They're going to come out here. They're going to go. Oh, wow. Oh, you did such a good job.
Look at that garage door. Look at that window. It hasn't been clean like that in 20 years.
They're not going to go on the roof and look at their ceiling. Why would they do that?
And if Dad wants to be like, oh, can I check the roof? I'd be like, that's done. That's unsafe.
Let a professional go up there. And then I'll go up there and I'll look around and be like,
this is clean as hell. Holy shit. This is clean. And then that dad's going to be in like slippers
and he's going to have a newspaper and he's going to go, oh, yeah, but you'll lick the top of the
roof. And I'm going to be like, of course I will hurry up. You don't hurry up a job like this.
This is I'm power washing. You don't hurry up.
By the way, how did I go from 50% to 40%? I don't get it. You're making it worse.
There's not dirty water in here. It's clean water. You're going to spend an hour washing
the front steps. No, I'm not going to do that. Do I have a streamer mode on because of the music?
I don't think I do. Streamer mode, autosave, aim mode, stance, dirt details, FOV, obviously,
right? I don't think so. I think it's my game. I think I just, I don't know, try the YouTuber
mode. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. Maybe I like, maybe I think I screwed something
up. Wait, how about reset audio defaults? Should I try that? I don't, is there even music in the game
here? I need the, okay, I need this, the, the bigger nozzle. Give me the wide one. No,
always the wide one. There it is. All right. Every time I ever see anybody power wash,
they always do it so wrong. They always do this thing where they like, oh, did I do it?
No, what you have to do is you have to act like a, like a copy machine. You have to do,
it's kind of like robotic movements. Then you touch up. I love that sound. The sound effect
is actually really good. All right, now back it up. Do you remember thinks he knows everything?
No, but I, I've, I've power washed before. I've, I've done it before. Not professionally,
but I've, I've done it before. All right, no one messing around. Let's actually,
let's actually get this done. Okay, sure. I, I've power washed before. Yeah. And some of you clowns
that power wash, you do this. Trust me. I know the technique, the look it's clean. And then,
you know, dad comes out and goes, no, it isn't. And you're like, fuck. And then dad's going to
take it anyways at the end. I had him just do it all again. No, no, no, stop, stop. Let me see that
for a second. Let me, let me see that. All right. That's good. It's like, dad, you just,
you just did the whole thing again. And then, and then you go, no, no, no, dad, let, give,
give me that thing. Because it's fun to do. And you end up power washing the same thing,
like four times. All right. I think the front steps are fine. Did I miss anything? Oh,
hold on. I did. Watching your stream makes me sneeze. I, I think I would calculate the dust
in your room. Are you sure it's not when you're sitting at your computer? There's no time limit
on this. It's fine. Is this pre-recorded? Why, why, why would this be? No, it's pre-recorded.
Pre-recorded. Oh, that it's done. That's the only thing I've done though. How long have I
been playing? I've been playing for 20 minutes and I finally got my first ding. What? How long
have I been sitting here for? I just got my first ding in 20 minutes. That's impossible. This is,
oh, what? I mean, where's my ladder? That's the best part, by the way. That's the best part
right here. And then, and then when you see all the dirt just fly everywhere and it turns into
this like brown sewer water looking stuff. Oh my God. I love it. Okay. So 43 recycled joke.
How's that? That's not a recycled joke. What are you talking about? Recycled joke. You don't
remember what I said a year ago. Okay. You don't remember what I said a year ago. And by the way,
how is that a joke? That's me saying I like something. You know, like I'm not ordering food
at a restaurant with you. And it's like, Oh, what do you want, man? What do you want to eat?
Dude, I think I'm doing the like, I don't think I'm just gonna go with like the turkey club.
What are you really gonna order though? I'm ordering a turkey. I like turkey sandwiches.
It's cool. Dude, stop stop this fucking bit and order a tuna sandwich. What are you? What are
you talking about? Second ding in the night. There it is. There we go. All right. Is that
it's kind of loud. Let me turn that down. Just a just a tiny bit. Just a little. Let me turn this
up. Turn this down. Just a little. That sounds nice. Is that better? A little more. Now we can
hear the birds and shit. That's better. That's better. That's better. Okay. That's good.
There's up to six people in co-op, by the way. That seems kind of chaotic. I need the ladder
now because there's no way I'm going to do that. I'm not gonna be like it up there. Should I change
this? Oh, no. I had this upgraded once already. All right. So where's this still dirt? Oh,
this is the best part. Here we go. Check this out in one sweep. It feels good.
I was holding my breath for that one. Oh my god. The what the the whole top of the house
needs to be done. There we go. You're gonna start seeing dings every five seconds now.
Steps? Where? Concentrated blast. I'm pissing somebody off so bad right now. You know what
I mean? There's at least a few of you in the chat right now that have had a clenched fist
since I turned it on the stream. Doesn't it feel like it's something is adding more dirt to it?
That's every time you power wash. This happens. I feel like I did this five times already,
but I didn't. There we go. Where's my ding? Where's my ding? Oh my god. It's underneath.
The splash was like reflecting off of this guy's car and I thought the police were here.
I was like, wait, what? I how I can't get underneath. How am I supposed to get
underneath here? I need this one yet on spins. There we go. Let's see a ding
like this. I'm doing this so wrong. Stand up. Just get up. What? All right. That's good enough.
That's actually good enough. It is. No human can come out here and tell you're gonna come out here
and swab it and send it to a lab and test it for dirt. There's nothing else here. I'm sorry. If I
see out the window, this guy lying on his back aiming up at the same place, I'm gonna go out.
I'm gonna open the door and be like, that's good. That's good. You don't have to do it. That's all
right, man. Don't worry. Stop peeling the paint. It's the whole railing. Oh my goodness. Look at
all this. Got it. What? No way. That shit was here. That's part of the foundation of the house at
this point. All right. It's not, I can't clean it. All right. You look like emperor Palpatine.
I was going to give you a no. I was going to just do the laser hands into the screen.
I'm like, nah, I was going to laser hands you. Oh my God. What's this thing? Change stance.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Change stance. What does that mean? Oh, wait, there,
there are three stances. Okay. I, one of them is crouched. The other one is lie down. I'm
proning, crawling right now, crawling around. You imagine looking out the window,
you see like a guy like, let's go. Just proning and like, got him.
A guy proning in your front lawn, just like aiming up with the power washer. All right.
I'd stop coming over here. I keep doing the front door. This is going into their house.
I'm sorry. If you have this meticulous about this, this water going into the house,
nobody has weather stripping. That's that good. This is going like, this is going in the house
into their living room. The guys get over the front door. It's water all over them. Like it
took a shower. He's going to be like, is that supposed to happen? Standing there for 20 minutes,
blasting the door. I wouldn't, I feel like this would break a window, right? I wouldn't want to
do that. I can't still be there here. You physically can't get up there. Nobody can.
I have to, I have to ricochet it. I can't do it. Got it. All right. That's done. Good. What the
what? How I've done, honest to God, I've done this 10 times. How can this still be edges of the fence
that I haven't gotten? I don't understand. I feel like it's respawning. This is like resident evil
mold on this person's house. I've done this like five times. Well, duh, it's your enemy. It's an
FPS, but again, yeah, the stream is sponsored by power wash simulator. This game's actually really
fucking fun and you can get it on Xbox, Xbox S steam, everything, all this stuff. It's got co-op.
It's in 1.0. This is a different person's house. What the hell happened? Wait, what? Um, excuse
me. Okay. Well, where do I even start? Okay. I get up. Don't start this yet. Yeah. I know that's
dirty. I know there's dirt on this side. This is a Harvey dent house. No, this is, this is like two,
two roommates or it's like, it's a duplex. There's two tenants here. One of them is, you know, evil
and the other one's like an angel and they share a flat together. All right. Where's this? Where's
the, uh, how do I get to the, I'm going to go up on the roof. Although it actually is prone. It's
been blocked by my drink this whole time. How do I visit ladder? Oh, hi. All right. Let's, let's take
care of this because this is ridiculous. I feel like I should do this from the ground. All right.
Here's the one incredibly important factor in this whole thing. Don't leave until it's done.
You know what I mean? Don't leave until it's all gone. What I keep doing is I keep spraying and
talking and spraying and I just walk away. Don't leave this spot until it's, this is all gone
because I keep just walking away after spraying it. Okay. So far so good. All right. So that's,
this is done on this side. What about up here? Okay. So now I just got to deal with this.
You've sponsored the power wash and you can't do it. I think I'm doing just fine. I think I'm
doing just fine. You're at 6% an hour. Do you have any idea how long it would take to power wash
this house in real life? The condition of the outside of this house, it would take two months.
I would have to come back and do reverse coats of paint. You know what I mean? I'd have to,
I would have to come back on three separate occasions in like four or five separate weeks.
This would take three months to do. Here we go. Think someone could speed run this game.
That would be awesome. I'm sure people have already tried to do it.
I wonder. People already do. Yeah. I wonder. I wonder just this house in particular. I wonder
how long it took to do a 100%. You better believe that's going to be hard to do. I think we're
almost good. I have to have a ding coming soon. It has to be, right? Really? Get out of the,
what the hell? There it is. All right. So there's that ding. I like the beard. You should grow it
out. I can't. I literally can't. This is like one of those ads for mobile games where the person in
the ad is like insanely incompetent. And so you want to download the game just to show that you
can actually do it unlike the dumb ass in the ad, but that's so unfair. Well, then go get it.
Then go get it. It's on, it's on Xbox. It's on steam right now. It's on fucking game pass. Go get
it. Why don't you do it? That's so unfair though. You know why that's unfair? Because in those mobile
game ads and trust me, I've seen millions of them. I've seen millions of those ads. I play,
all I do is play iPad games. You understand that they, it's usually like, oh no, there's a fire.
What do we do to put the fire out? And there's two options pop up on screen here and here. And one of
them is a fire extinguisher and the other one is like a golf club. And it's, they try to drag the
golf club up on the fire. I'm not doing that here. I'm, I'm not doing that. I'm, I'm, I'm power washing
doing it the correct way. If I had a golf club in my hands and I was hitting the side of this house,
then I would understand your point. But I, come on. The golf club is your brain. All right. Did I,
I didn't finish this part. I'm getting tutorials. Oh, it's because I'd never pressed them. Okay.
So this is done, right? All right. This one's done. Keep going. Now with the, I'm moving on.
This whole side of the house has to get done, but I'm not doing that right now. 40 only,
of course it's 47%. I have the Satan demon person that lives over on this side. I have to do their
house. I want to try to get it up over the fence. I don't, I physically don't think you can. It
legally touched my truck. Therefore it's mine. It touched my truck. Therefore it's legally mine.
Where'd it go? I never put my hands on it. What was I doing? Oh yeah. I gotta go for it.
You're doing the mobile ad. No, even if I were to sit here and do this. Okay. Nozzle four. Oh,
what it worked. I would still be doing more than the mobile ads always do. You understand? Like
I'm actually still doing it. I'm still actually pressing the button and washing the side of the
house that like, even if I was doing it like that, you know, what's actually really funny about,
about mobile ads now, I think we've talked about this a little bit, but there's a, there's a game
that I see ads for all the time now. And it's like, aren't you getting sick and tired of those
ads that show the slide, the puzzle game, and it's never in the game. We have that in our
fucking game. We actually have that. All these like posers, it's so funny. And you know what?
They must be pissed. They must be pissed off because they actually have this slide, the puzzle,
watch out for the fire and get the gold game. Right. And everybody else just is doing that in
their ads. And they just have to sit there and go, well, that's our game. We actually have that in
the video game. It's like, do you want to play that game? We have it. If we actually have that
in our game, they don't, it's been debunked. No, I know. But my point is that there are companies
right now. I'm getting ads right now of somebody literally saying, Hey, those ads are bullshit.
Aren't they? I know we have that game. It's not fair. I swear. I promise you. But they don't have
it either. What? It's not in that game either. Hold on a minute. But how you can't how you I
don't know about that. I feel like that's inaccurate. You can't make an ad stating,
Hey guys, aren't you sick and tired of those ads that show that game and it's not in the game?
Download ours. Ours is in there. It's not in there. What? No, no way. That's impossible.
It's true. What? Okay, but hold on. It might not be the core of that game. Right? It might not be
the core gameplay of that game. But is it in the game? And can you actually do it? No. What? No,
it's not. It's impossible. Hey, fuck all those other games, man. We got that in our game and
it's not in the game. No, I cannot speak to that. I don't know how true that is. Dude, why doesn't
somebody just make one of those? Just make a slide the puzzle game. And then you can be the savior,
the hero of the mobile game ad world. You know what I mean? Just make one. Because I'll tell you,
if I downloaded a game and I saw that it had the sliders in it, and that kind of and that it was
just 100 levels of like 500 levels of that game. I'd be like, you know what? Nice job. Nice work,
actually. Actually good work. All right, now somebody has to edit edit me in to just like
interior of just like a living room. And you know, just like, you know, family just kind of like
whatever sitting around like a stock image or something, and have muffled audio of that what I
was just doing. And have loud kind of footsteps on the top of the roof. I think that would be
pretty funny. Hi, what is left? I'm gonna get more concentrated here. God, I'm just thinking about
this right now. There's an engineer move in TF2. Slow me down. Okay, let me rephrase that and
say what I wanted to say. A TF2 weapon as a power washer would actually be pretty fun.
Like a jet of water jet. Come on, give me the ding. The ding is so close. The ding is so close,
dude. Come on. Where's the ding on the side of the house? This one little piece? Where is it?
Right here. Come on. Ding. How come I'm not getting a ding? Is this why down here? You've got to wash
your sin. I think that would take a while. Only red is the wall. Wait, what do you mean? What do
you mean? What are we talking about? Hold on. I'm typing. Hold on. I'm typing. You need to relax.
Okay, so it's just the entire wall. How do I get from here to there?
God, that was fun. There's a much better way I can do that.
There's a much better way I can do that. So should I? Okay, for all you power washers out there,
it's big nozzle straight down into sections, right? So I start here and walk backwards.
This is poop from an airplane. Oh my god, dude. Yeah, there's so many bird shits on this house.
Honestly, you know what's crazy though? I wonder how much bird shit is on your roof.
It's probably awful. It's probably crazy. I can't imagine what everybody's just straight down
bird's eye view of roof looks like. Because unless you do something like this, it's probably covered
in bird shit. It rains. Not everywhere. It does not rain a lot in every location. Not here. Not in
Vegas. I wonder how many bird shits I have on my roof. Are you keeping track? How would you keep
track of bird shits? What are you gonna go up there every few days? Go for the clipboard? Just
see your neighbor just like he's making marks and you don't clean it. All right, so that top is
all right. Now I'm gonna go this way first. Don't forget about the chimney. You know, I have to give
the devs credit because that it's not just like, oh, yeah, just spray it a little and just go side
to side and you did it. You actually have to do this. You have to actually truly power wash this
house. I have to actually get in here and do all this. It seems like there's a lot more content
since when we last played a year ago. Does the game look better? I feel like the graphics are
better. Am I out of my mind? It's the same house. It's a year later. Don't fall. You're just spraying
into the chimney. Yeah, I gotta clean the chimney too. Oh my god, I can jump high. I'm looking at
the ding. I can't get in there. I can't get in there. It's unsafe for me to get in here.
I need that with the wiggle one. It's unsafe. I can't get it to ding either. Maybe I just spray
it up there. It's right. It's this tiny little piece on the left. Just get on the other side.
Can I can I put the ladder up there? You missed the whole right side. Oh, it's all good. We're good.
There should be a grenade. Why are you seriously making me contemplate if that would work?
If you had a device that was a water grenade, but what would you use it for? It was a pressurized
water system in the thing and it would just like shot out. That wouldn't it would work. No, it
wouldn't. It would clean soap and water in the grenade. Well, hire the cleaning service. Yeah,
you think I just shows up. He's got like fucking grenades on him. He's just like, yeah, I'm ready.
Everybody if we could get up out of the house, that'd be great. Everybody leaves. Okay, so what's
the dirtiest room in the house? Bedroom? Okay. It's just soap and just the bedroom's destroyed.
Phil's water grenades. That'd be $800. You walk out. Phil's like in his car. He's doing like some
paperwork and it's like, oh, thanks for coming, Phil. And he's like, yeah, yeah, it's all good.
Hold on a second. I'm going to clean my car. You look and you like, yeah, your car's looking a
little dirty, Phil. Don't worry about it. I got it. He just steps out. He just throws the
grenade in the car and it's just cartoon. Just the car just goes like, boop. There's just some
papers fucking everywhere. This is like, there's all kinds of like destruction. He goes to turn
the car on. Hey, look, buddy. I think I could borrow your car for a few hours. I've got a
few more. I got a few more of these jobs. I've been cleaning the safe spot for 15 minutes.
Yeah, man. I know. Let us bet on what? What do you need to bet on? Water, C4.
You just set them up around the whole house. What are you talking about? All right, slow down,
slow down. This is not powerful enough. You see, we got, I got to go harder. That's Splatoon.
Yeah, but nobody's going. I can't do this on camera. It's like weird.
You know, the exact thing I was going to do. Everybody knows the exact sound effects. I was
just going to do all of you. You saw my neck go like this, tilted. You knew exactly what was
going to happen. I feel like that's too predictable. We don't care. We want it. All right, mods, run a
poll, please. If it gets to at least 80% with at least 5,000 votes, I'll do the noise. I'll do the
thing that everyone wants me to do. Remember everybody, you saw my neck tilt. You know what
could have happened? So will you play Splatoon with it? I don't, I couldn't play Splatoon. I
don't know why something about it. Just, I just, I kind of just didn't, I didn't get it. I know,
I completely understand, but the counter, you know, I, it kind of just triggered old memories
of playing Tony Hawk with friends. And it was that mode where if you did a trick on something,
it would change to their color. I remember just doing really well and just like boom, orange,
but boom, orange, but boom, orange, orange. And I had the whole, and then I would turn around for
five seconds. And my, my dickhead friend has got like a 2 million point combo going. And he runs
over every single thing I did. And I just turn around, it's all blue and it's like, why am I
playing the game? So I, that's why I don't like, that's just Splatoon for me. All right, let's see,
at least over, it has to be over 80% and it has to be at least 5,000 votes. And I'll do, I'll do it.
Somebody just said, dude, it takes two clicks to vote. Come on guys. And there's some of you just
sitting there leaning back, just like, nope, I ain't doing that. I don't care. It's so funny
doing the votes and polls and just the amount of people that just genuinely just don't care
about any of this. It's just like, I don't care what he does. Just, I, I just like kind of hanging
out. Do we like applaud those viewers by the way? They just hang out, they just watch, they just
chill. They don't have to vote. It's time to do it. What the fuck? 95%? Are you kidding me?
I thought this was impossible. Okay. Well, all right, fine. I don't, somebody had to,
had bought a better fake that or something. There you go. That's why I don't do that with
a camera on. I'm available, but I probably won't show up. 95%. I don't think we've ever
seen that before. I, I've never seen a 95% with that many votes. Dude, I love this game. You know
why I love this game? Cause I can just power wash and we can talk about splatoon noises. It's
perfect. Hashtag ad. Yeah. Hashtag ad. That's right. Copium. What? Why do you think,
when you do an iPad stream? Um, you know, I set up the iPad stream, but I just, I just didn't,
I just didn't do it because I don't know. I downloaded 50 of these wacky wild iPad games,
but I would, some of them just wouldn't open. I, I didn't want to play them off stream because
they'd want to have genuine like, what the hell's going on reactions, right? But I would open some
of them. And this, this became an issue where I was like, you know what, like let's just see
if some of them work, right? Some of them just didn't turn on. Some of them would crash after
10 seconds. And if that became not funny. So now there's going to be a new system in place.
This is the stream that I want to do. I want to do a stream where,
and years ago, this, this concept was, was thought up that you play an iPad game with no,
with no premium purchases. And every time an ad comes up, you download that game and move on to
that game that you see every time, no matter what, that's the game. So I think we're going
to do that. Or you, it's because you might get an ad immediately after, after downloading one of
these. And I guess some of the rules we could make is it has to be a full page ad. It can't
just be something, a banner that pops up on the bottom or whatever, right? It's got to be a full
page ad advertising a game, a game that can be downloaded on the app store. That's the plan.
All right. Roof is almost done. 57%. 57. I'll probably get it if I do the other side.
All right. I'm going to speed run this. Ready? Three, two, one. Um, I'm not going that fast.
Let me try. I'm not, I'm not, I can't, I, I can't go fast. Maybe I can just go fast.
I can go kind of fast. Maybe it's enough to get the, uh, the ding because the other side is,
is immaculate. Oh my God. Um, hello. Is this the grind bandits? I need some help with my
poor little play school. Oh, another thing. Carefully go around the volcano. Wait,
am I getting a bunch of work requests? Oh no, it's Tony Hawk. Go careful around the volcano.
What volcano? We went down there to enjoy a smoky sunset and Jenny saw a UFO. Why am I part of this
group text? Don't fucking group text me. I'm so sick of this shit happening. Stop group texting
people. Don't pull, you know what? The dumbest fucking thing. I can't even understand how this
was ever a thing. You cannot leave a group text if there's people with iPhone and Android. Why can't
you just leave? Why can't you just leave? Just leave. I don't want to keep getting pulled in.
People will just be sitting there talking about a bunch of shit. And then at some point,
Hey, Jeremy, what do you, what do you thought? And I'm just like,
I don't want to tell them that I've had this whole conversation on mute for six or seven straight
weeks. Why did I give this guy my number? Hey dude, I'm going to come do a job for you. Yeah,
that sounds good. I'll come do the job for you. Here's my rate. Hey man, this is kind of an old
building. Isn't that interesting? Yes, it is very interesting. Yeah. What kind of stone do you think
they made this out of? I don't know. I'm going to get a look. I'm going to get a text. I'm going
to be like, what's your favorite pasta? And you, you know, like rigatoni. And then it goes in the
pocket. Rigatoni in the pocket. And then this guy's going to start sending me Morse code with the
amount of times I'm going to get a message. Go finish the house first. Oh man, there's different
levels of strength you need. Okay. Did they sell a UFO here? Dude, you came back after a year
and didn't finish. I stopped around their house, blew up one of their windows and
shoved the nozzle into the chimney and ruined their furniture in their living room
and then left. I'll be back in another year. And I'll put the group text thing. I don't hate text
people. I don't hate whatever. I just hate telephones. I just hate phones. You know what
is, you know, let me tell you something. Some of you kids, you know, back, back in the day,
like, you know, that everybody has a phone now, everybody will see everything they ever say,
you know what I mean? Even if you don't have read receipts on it, at least once or twice,
at least three or four potential times a day, people know that people all look at their phones
at least a few times a day. So there's no way you didn't see my text, right? There's no way you
didn't get my phone call. See, back in the day, everyone had a landline and it would be as simple
as I don't care. I'm not answering that phone. And then it was implied that just needless weren't
home. Or sometimes you'd pick the phone up. Hello. Hi, is, is, is, is, is Jeremy there?
And, uh, no, no, it's not here. Oh, okay. Thanks. Easy. Now everybody has a phone.
Everybody knows you have that phone. Everybody knows I have a, everybody knows you have a phone.
So you can't like, I'm so, I am very notorious for just not responding for a long fucking time.
I just, and it's not that I don't care. It's just like, oh, there's like, I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to say. I know you can set up like DND, right? Like do not disturb. And I don't
know. Shouldn't we all collectively have this message that we all agree on, right? Everyone
has a message that's a good, it's a separate DND box that you check. And it's just like, look,
I'm just kind of don't fucking give a shit right now. Like I, like, I don't really like want to
answer phone calls or I guess that's what, you know, like, but like a separate, like less,
not like serious DND. Like, I just kind of don't care. Like right now, maybe like I'll get back to
you in a few days. Right? So if I get that, that we all agree on that text, right? Like it's signed
into like a Congress gets it and they sign a bill. It's just like, all right. Like we all know that
that's like, all right. Whatever. I'll talk to you in a few days. Or no, it could be just like a
single word, like a code word. I don't like the peanuts. If you get a DND back, that's just
peanuts. All right. Yep. Got it. I got you. Don't worry. Got it. But it sucks because somebody,
people would abuse the peanuts system, right? It'd be like, Hey, where the fuck is Jeremy?
Where is he? We got, we got peanuts. It's been, it's been three weeks and he won't respond about us
going to dinner on Thursday. Like what the hell do you just, you're abusing the peanut system.
And then finally get back to him. You're like, Oh yeah. Sorry. Sorry. I just, I kind of was like,
dude, I was busy and shit. And I didn't really, no one actually cares this much if you don't
respond. You know what? That's, that's pretty accurate. But still though, I, I never want
people to think I don't care. I do care, but like sometimes I'll get a text and then I'll have
like Kathy Mitchell on the iPad. And it's just like, fuck, but I don't even know. I,
and for some reason, my brain says, just press play again and just relax. It sucks. I hate it.
Cause in my brain, in my, my, I don't know, maybe I'm, maybe I'm, maybe I'm weird,
but to me putting on like DND to me and like sending a DND automatic response back to somebody
is almost like a, huh. Okay. Automatic response. Not going to even text me back. I get like an
auto response, auto generated message. Like, Hey, what are you up to? I'm sorry. That person is not
available to speak right now. Maybe he'll talk to you later. Okay. Sure. Auto generated. And let
me, let me be also frank too. I talk to a lot of people every day. I'm usually on the phone
at least four or five times a day. That's a flex. What is a flex? I just talked to a lot of
different people. Weird flex. Uh, what are my favorite color schemes by the way? He talks to
people, but he doesn't, he never wants to talk back to people. No, I don't just want to talk
at people. And so it's like, when I call you, you answer. When I text you, you answer. I, I get it
too. If I don't get a response, I'm just like, all right, cool. I'll see you. I'll talk to you.
Whatever. I'm not demanding that they give me their time. I'm just saying that I have, you know what
I mean? You get it. You missed a spot. This one's going to take a while. It's this, this is, oh,
so you know what I could do here, right? Check this out. All right. You ready?
Make sure that looks good. Okay. So right here, I could take a picture right here,
just of this, me standing in front of it, being like, it's like, yeah, just cleaning it up. But,
at Dave's skate park, really showing him how to do a clean job, right? Arms folded like this.
And the power washers leaning behind me. And there's an ad for my business right there.
And what they don't know is that I just, this is all this. And I get to about here
and I'm just like, I'm done. There's some dirt still on the wall. Oh yeah. Take the photo here
and have me stand there and then crop the absolute hell out of this and zoom in so it's
looking blurry and artifacted. And then somebody gets the original photo and leaks the original
photo. Now, is that a dumb viral marketing campaign that would be bad for my business or
what? I wonder. It would be such an epic troll. Still 1%. Oh God. Use the big nozzle.
The big nozzle doesn't get everything. Do I have access to different nozzles?
Is there a bigger one? Where can I buy stuff? Is there a store? How do I buy something?
Where's the store? It's somewhere, right? Where is it? Oh, right here. Oh, all right. Okay. Heavy
duty. Shit. I need 40 stars. Dude, these. Oh my God. There's there's like skins. Oh, all right.
Hold on. I don't want to spend any money though. No, I don't want to spend any money. Should I get
some soap? What kind of surface is this? Is this plastic? What is this? Steel? Granite? What is this?
What is it? Aluminum or something? What is all this? Concrete? Oh, it says multi-purpose. Okay.
So I need multi-purpose cleaner. Multi-purpose. Should I have bought that much? All right. So now
what does that do? Okay. Now how do I put the cleaning liquid on? No cleaner attached. How do
I do that? I have like five. Press three. Oh, okay. Cool. Is it on? Multi-purpose cleaner. I have to
buy the attachment. You need the soap nozzle. Oh, okay. 75 bucks. I already own it. Change to it.
You own it for the other washer. Oh, it's for the other one. Wait, what? Oh, really? Hold on.
I can't get it for the other one. Huh. Okay. So that's for the other one. Well, let me try it.
Give me the stub. Stubby. All right. What's this doing? I can get it for the other gun.
This actually kind of works. All right. Wait. Get it for the other gun. How much money do I have?
Okay. So clean power equipment, right? Oh, $375. I don't have enough for that. I might as well use it.
So this just makes it easier to do. Rinse it. Finish the house. I'll go back in a year. I'll
go back in like a year. This doesn't do anything. That is way more than I've done in an hour sitting
in the corner. This is doing way more than I was doing. Now rinse it. Do I have to rinse it?
I don't think so. No. I'm going to use the rest of it. Should I go? All right. Should I go back
to the house? All right. I'll go back. I'll go back to the house. I'll go back to the house.
I'll come back to this one later. I'll be fine. Soap only gets most of it off the weaker one. Okay.
Hey, look at this place. This place looks beautiful. So this is wood. Does multi-purpose
work on wood? Probably not, right? That's actually really good here. All right. Give me the ladder.
Can I put the ladder over here? I can't. What the hell am I doing? Oh my god. That's so much
easier. All right. I almost have the whole chimney. This doesn't work. That doesn't work here.
It works on the chimney. Oh, my ladder is not big enough. The ladder is not big enough to get all
the way up here. This side, the one facing the neighbor here. Jeremy, are you high on bath salts?
No. What? There it is. Got it. Okay. Now I want wood. I want wood cleaner. I feel like it's going
to be amazing. Stone cleaner. No. All right. Let me buy some wood cleaner. Wood cleaner.
There it is. Let's see if this works. Wood cleaner. It's on. Fill it up and let's go.
Works pretty good. Maybe it has got a great sound effect too. That's got an amazing sound effect.
Get off the fucking ladder, you idiot. What have I done? I just like ran into it and hit my head on
it. Looking good so far. Just leave an outline of the ladder. That would be so stupid. All right.
I got to go for the corner here. That's all right. Now we move the ladder. Actually, maybe not.
Hell, this is the way to do it. This is the way to do it. For sure. I still have cleaner left,
right? Yep. That took me two minutes. Two minutes. Perfect. All right. Up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
All right. Move the ladder. Come on. Come on. Crap. It's okay. It'll ding any second.
That just scared the shit out of me. All right. Any more soap I can use. This is multi-purpose.
These are the railing. Okay. This is how is this? This is wood. Okay. It's all. Oh yeah. Let's refill
that. Yep. Fill it back up. Buy some more of that right now. Let's buy it all. Whatever. Check this
out. I'm spending money. How much money am I spending? Oh, that was 50 bucks. I'll make it
last and then I'll come back and just and touch it up. I'll touch it up. How's this wood? This looks
like stone. This is wood. Don't walk under the ladder. It's all right. I'll throw a fucking salt
behind me. I'll be fine. I'm asking a question. So if I walked under a ladder and okay, if I walked
through the ladder, but I walked backwards through the ladder, does that, does that negate it?
Does that let you say, okay, you went back, you undued. Does that, is that an undo?
No. Okay. So if I go through the ladder, then I take salt and I go like that. Wait, wrong shoulder
like that. Would that undo going through the ladder? No, it doesn't. It's the salt has no effect.
So what would negate going underneath the ladder? Nothing. Nothing. You literally nothing you do.
I feel like there's something you can do. You don't. That's not how it works.
What's wrong with going under a ladder? Somebody tell them. Somebody tell that. Somebody tell
that guy. Somebody tell them. It's 100 years bad luck. So if you walked under a ladder,
broke a mirror, threw salt over your left shoulder, opened up an umbrella, closed it,
opened up an umbrella. Do you just get struck by lightning right after doing that? It's a cheat
code. It's funny because I'm not superstitious at all. But I doesn't matter. I still wouldn't
open up an umbrella inside the house. Right. But I'm not super I don't I'm not I just just in case.
What if just in case like I would not right now open a umbrella in this room. I just it's
not that oh my god, I believe in that. But I just I don't know. I'm afraid of it. What if it's real?
What if it is bad luck? This house looks like shit. All right, we got all I soaked it up.
Is there any more what I can do? This is now this is multi-purpose. All right, well get rid of the
the wood one. Now we're gonna bring the nozzle back out. Okay, I would clean it. Let's put the
nozzles back on. I want where's where's my actual where's it? What? Oh, how do I get to the nozzle?
There we go. All right, medium duty. This one has extension though. I'm gonna put this one on.
I have to piss. Can I go pee? I gotta pee. I'll be right back. I gotta pee. And I'm finishing this
house and I'm finishing the gosh darn state skate park. I'll be right back. I'm gonna pee.
All right, I'm back. How are you? How's it going? You guys ready for more power washing? Oh, yeah.
You forgot to mute. We heard every last drop. You're disgusting. You're disgusting. Disgusting.
Disgusting chatter. Disgusting chatter. Disgusting chatter. Get rid of them. Disgusting chatter.
All right, let's do it. Back to the house. How much more of the house do I have to do?
Realistically, I'm at 73%. Do I get extra money for finishing the job?
I better. This got louder to me. Have I just gotten used to that sound? Did I get used to
that sound effect? What about baseball? Baseball. The German Baseball Association had its date
changed to August 19th. I know, Saj is in the chat. I know. But that is set in stone.
We're ready to go. This time, I mean it. This time, I mean it. You said that last time. Yeah,
but this would be, this would be strike three. This would be literally strike three. Set in stone.
It's no, it's set in stone. This has been etched into an etch a sketch. So you can just literally
go like this and it just changes. Dang. He's going to delay it again. I know I can't. So
if this gets delayed again, it's not going to happen till probably the fall. There's no way.
There is not a chance it gets delayed again. And I'm telling you, there's no way. No way. No way.
No way. There is literally no way. I know that's, that's copium, but there's no way.
Tag me. Oh yeah, that's, somebody has an account that says that. Somebody has an account that's
tag me when Jerma lies. That person has probably not logged into Twitch in like five years. That
account is probably inactive. It's probably been inactive for months, if not years. They were here
yesterday. They're actually here. Well, whoever this is, they're going to wake up one day and have
5,000 pings on their dashboard. You know what? I can't even buy anymore. Nevermind.
How does anyone know what the stream is? What do you mean? What happened? What happened?
Can you explain why it got delayed? Sure. One, two, three. It could have happened on that date,
but it would have been a show that was worse than the show I wanted to do.
Uh, we were pretty much ready to go. We had a couple of issues
that we had some, uh, some of the, some venue problems, right? So instead of just doing it
with those venue problems, I was like, you know what? Let's just make sure that we can do
the thing that I want to do. Uh, it would have been fine maybe, but after August and into September,
I'm going to be able to look back and go, I'm so glad we waited till August.
This whole process of trying to get, um, a venue, right, was way more difficult than I think anybody
anticipated. So we got one, then we got another one. Then we got told we couldn't do it at one
place. Then we got told we couldn't do it at another place. And then we had a date and then
that date had to change with this place. And so then we had to look and see if we could go
somewhere else. And it was like, no, I don't want to do that. So we ended up picking a new place
for August. It's pretty much what happened, but it's going to be, it's going to be a lot of fun.
I've been waiting to do this stream for almost two years. So when we finally get out there,
I'm going to be as happy as can be. Ding. All right. At what point can I close the job? 80%,
90%, 100%? When do I, when do I get to go? All right. That's it. You're on your own.
A hundred. Oh, all right. I'm focusing. Here we go. Focus up. Focus up. Always give 110%
Jerry. How long are you going to stream today? Um, I don't know. As long as I feel like it.
Don't mean to be a Debbie downer, but I've looked into the creepy symbols you found on
the side of that house you're working on. It's the demon person. It turns out that just
builder's diagrams to, Oh, telling the plumber where to put the gap for the overfill. Nevermind.
Nevermind. 80%. Is this the first job I will ever complete in this game? Especially a different
nozzle. I, I, yeah, but I like the green one. The green one is just enough pressure, but it's not
too much. This one has a good surface area, but it doesn't, it doesn't get down deep and you have
to pass through three times anyways. Hey, can you do the cat puke noise? Um, what is that?
What the, what are you talking about? I'm a sponsored fucking stream. Shut up.
That looks all right. Call for a vote. What are we voting on? This thing goes, this is the long
range nozzle. That's what's going on here. I was like, Holy shit. This is awesome.
Why did I not have someone from the very beginning? I could do the whole house like this.
That's so much. All right. This will be done in 10 minutes. Not even a poll to do cat puke. No,
that's on, that's on me. If I want to do that, whatever that is, whatever that could be,
that's something I've never heard of, whatever that is. I don't know. It's something strange.
Apparently nice. So much quicker. Come on, just get, wait, I can use the, uh, the, the spinner.
This is my favorite weapon. Well, it's not a weapon, but you know what I mean? It's my favorite
attachment. I would say I don't call it a weapon. It's not a weapon. Favorite weapon.
Got it. Plus that's two bucks. That's two bucks. Two bucks. Almost at 90%. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. I was puked. Yeah. I was just, I was cat puked. You're right.
How much more of this did before I get a ding? I'm being dead serious. There it is. I get it
underneath. Ding. Looks so much better. So much better. Can we see the before and after photos?
What a difference. What a difference that made, huh? What a change. What a difference.
What a difference. What? When is this going to ding? Somebody said, why are you so tall?
Holy shit. He's huge. I just realized I'm seven plus feet tall. What? There it is.
There's the ding. By the way, can we, uh, in the chat, can we tell everybody where they can get
this power wash simulator? Where can you get it? And by the way, I got a terrible job I've done.
What an awful job I've done. Imagine if you could show me up
on your own game. Just your fucking like two year old. I'm 90% sure it's on Xbox. You're right.
Xbox X. Xbox Series S. Steam. It's on that PC of yours. I believe it's also on Game Pass.
Potentially two. We're, we have, we've got a Corob. We've got to figure that one out.
Ding. More dings. Yeah, it's on Game Pass. Yes. You just downloaded from Game Pass? Hell yeah.
260. What do I need? 375? I want a different nozzle. Oh, what did I do? You made somebody
cry. I made somebody cry at Dave and Buster's. You made my little sister cry at Dave and Buster's.
You called her crying Andy and she cried. I'm nice. Just delete this. What is this?
Do I still not? Okay, come on. There it is. All right. What is missing on this side? This
side looks good besides this. This looks awful, but you know, whatever. It's fine.
Wait, you can get this on Steam Deck? That wasn't a bad first pass. Come on. Why does it feel like
this setting? I would be like, I wouldn't be able to control this. I'd be, my arm would be moving
all. This is a lot of power behind this. Do this to your house in real life. There it is. All right.
Wait, this side too. 90%. Come on. It's just the roof. Get in there. Nice.
I haven't got a ding in a while. Kind of getting a little pissed off about it, if I'm honest.
Can you get this on a Samsung fridge? Why is there just a, I don't know. I don't know if you
can get this on a fridge. That has not been play tested. I don't think so. That's at your own risk.
It's fridge compatible. Have you, did you do it? They said it's fridge compatible. Pog.
That's not official. That's not an official statement. That's one, one guy in chat said that.
I don't know. I don't know what that means. How did I not do this already? This hedge ruined
everything. Come on. Really? All right. Oh, oh, I, that was supposed to be a joke, but that actually
just died. Did that for real. That hurt. That did that for a joke. Flatter. Now it's just the roof,
right? And that's it. Broke your finger. I'm fine. It didn't even hurt. This was blowing out my
microphone, right? Cause that was disgusting. That definitely covered it up. I just did like
this internal burp and it was like, and this, I'm glad you didn't hear it because this, yeah.
Thank God I have this loud white noise just playing in the background. So you didn't hear that.
He farted. I didn't stop saying that. What's left up here? Oh, the gutter, right? Can I hold shift
and not fall off like Minecraft? This is really, really on there. This is algae. Is that, was it
algae? Is it, it looks like, did I get it all? There's still some here. Hold on. Let me crouch.
I got it all. Oh, that's actually a really good angle for this. You're floating. No, I've got,
I'm out of the way at the end. My, my big toe is over here. I'm fine. This is a, this angle is
perfect though. You can get all up in there. Okay. There's nothing else over here. 92%. All right. I
got to get the algae in there. I already got all that. Not over here though. Hold on. Ding. No ding.
Where's the ding? No ding. Dude, no ding. No ding. Here we go. All right. I'm in. This is, yeah,
this is algae. All right. What is left besides the very top of the roof here? This, oh, that looks
bad. What, besides this, there's nothing else. There's a whole left wall. Bro, that's a shadow.
Bro, 303. Do I get, do I actually get a bonus for this? If I do, if I complete the whole thing,
you've been doing this for two hours. Yeah, I'm having fun. It gives you a message. Oh, I got it.
40 bucks. Hell yeah. Come on. I want to buy that new nozzle. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Ding. Real voice.
You know, let me, let me talk in my real voice. I'm going to talk just in my real voice. No messing
around. No like putting on a projection to talk into a microphone or talk. So this is what I just,
this is what I normally talk like. This is how I just normally speak to somebody. If I'm talking
to somebody, this is how I just normally will talk. I'll be like, what's up, man? What are you
up to? Nothing. I, you, you, are you doing that thing on a, on Friday? I was thinking about going,
but I'm not sure. Are you, um, yeah. Are you, uh, I can pick you up and pick it up at like,
like eight. No. Yeah. Sure. Sure. Yeah. I mean, we can get a, we can get a breakfast if you want.
We can just get breakfast and shit. I was going to do it again, but I'm like, nah,
I'm not doing it again. 95%, 96%. It's just this side right here. That's it. 97, 98, 99. Oh,
it's coming. Come on. 99 still. 100. You thought dirt and grime could hide from me? This is where
it shows like a bunch of animated dirt and they're all hiding under the railing. He'll never get us
here. We're caked on algae. And then it blasts. Our washers use the strongest nozzles able to take
six coats of paint off. Our nozzles are so strong. We can turn steel back to its original element,
iron and copper. It splits the atoms or whatever it does. What? Wait, what is it? What is steel?
Carbon. Fuck. I fucked that whole joke up. You know what I mean though.
Iron and copper. I've been playing too many mobile games, guys. It's one bar of copper,
one bar of iron, and you put them together and it turns into steel. Window frames? Where are these
trims? Wooden trim. There it is. How do you make steel? Steel is aluminum. Okay, so what's a better
joke? I can bring a material that's combined metals down to their periodic table version.
Carbon and iron. So a better thing would be like, our nozzles are so strong. Our nozzles are so
strong. We can turn steel back into carbon and iron. Would that be better? Why did you say
copper? Why did you say carbon and iron? Split bronze into copper and tin. Did I get it wrong?
No, you were correct. Left side window. Ah, 99. I'm so stressed out. Relax. We're fine. Rail. Oh,
here we go. A nozzle like this would fuck this up. Probably. Iron and carbon is steel. Steel is
mostly iron. It's about 98% iron. All right. So I wasn't wrong. I physically can't get over here.
Hold on. Yes, I can. Another railing. More window trims. Oh, come on. Wait, that's it. All right.
Now window trim. You should say it splits atoms. Well, it's like an image of the guy shooting the
power washer. He's like, and it's just all of a sudden you see like a mushroom cloud. I don't
think I would want that. Window trim. Yeah, these were like, there's a couple windows here.
Up here. No, not this one. Wooden trim. Oh, it's not window trim. It's wooden trim.
Wooden trim and railing. Which railing? This one? There it is. Shit, I gotta go down here. I'm
almost at 100. Yes. Yeah. Yes. Yeah. Mm hmm. Mm hmm. Only a few more. And I got 100% on the house.
Very nice. There's three more. Where? Where? Last one. Extra 100 bucks. And we gotta get our,
hold on. We gotta do our post shave rinse, right? That looks good. Get the bladder out of the way.
I want a picture. Okay. No, wait. It's your perspective. So it'd be like this. Hey. All
right. Wait, this is from a year ago. This is literally from a year ago. The front part.
It's saved for a year. Wait, hold on. It actually kept it from a year ago. Why? Hold on. But why did
I exist later? How come I was walking around? Who is this walking around? They grew up so fast.
All right. I got some money now. Let's go back to the skate park. Steel is iron. All right. Here
we go. They added a player model and a patch. Oh, that's funny. Okay. Here we go. Update the nozzle.
You think it's time? Heavy duty. $2,000. I don't have that. Five grand. All right. I'm not
fucking around anymore. I'm not messing around anymore. We need to get money. Let's go. Ready?
Um, I need, I need some, I need some, I need some go fast music.
Multipurpose. I'm going to soak the whole thing. You ready? No, not doom. OST. Something that is
royalty free. It's gotta be something royalty free. Is penis music royalty free? Definitely not. I
don't know why. That's what I wanted to put on here. Put on Sonic X. Is that so? I mean,
it's video game music, right? Whatever. Put on the Flintstones SNES. All right. Hold on. Let me,
let me get something. Let's do, um, what do you think? No, not break core. Why would Sonic
doesn't make sense? Put on the one Sonic song and just put it on repeat. Flintstones SNES. I'm so,
what, I'm curious of what this is. What is this Flintstones SNES? OST. I've never played this
game before. Flintstones? By the way, this is the movie version of the Flintstones.
Holy shit. This is a fucking awesome. What the hell? Who made this? This is great.
Oh, hold on. Let's start this over. When you meet the Flintstones, your own new story.
Let's do that one more time. This just blows it out. Hold on. The skin on my mouth is coming off.
Why am I doing this? No, let's go over here. I need soap. What just happened?
This sounds like a really shitty version of this because of the white noise.
How long are they gonna hold? I can hold the will before.
Fucking long, dude. How long was that? That was at least like 30 seconds.
That had to have been at least 20 to 30 seconds. That was a flash. You flash banged us.
Is this Fred Flintstone? Dude, did I get the longest Wilma world record right there?
All right. I want to buy the soap. Multi-purpose. This song is amazing.
Shit. I'm spending money. That was like a minute. That was 45 seconds.
What? Based on the clip, that was 45 straight seconds. Do I submit that somewhere? All right.
I don't want wood cleaner. I want multi-purpose cleaner. The soundtrack is actually really good.
All right. I'm gonna start. Let's get this whole quadrant done like from here to here.
I'm gonna draw a line essentially. So from here to here. Ready? This OST fucks. It does. Hey,
we're playing Power War Simulator. Check it out. This actually cleans it really well.
Multi-purpose still, right? Yep. Oh, that's a dirty steak. I want to check out some of
the other little modes too. There's a couple of the modes I want to see.
Okay. After the skate park, I'll check out some of the other modes. I'm actually going to really
try to get this done quickly. Quadrant by quadrant. I don't want to go too far. I'm going too far now.
Already is looking way better. Right here. There's the line right here. We're going to
go over this again with the actual nozzle. And from this line, I'm going to draw the line here.
Ready? Okay. Do not cross this line. If I cross that line before doing the rest of it, right?
I'm going to do it right here. Let's make, let's draw it. See? In here. If I start going over that
line and I like, oh yes, let me tell you a story. So, um, I'm in trouble. Quadrant by quadrant.
Nothing else. I'm good. I'm not over the line. This, the line is right at the edge of this wall.
I'm going to leave a little bit of dirt so I don't, uh, so I can see where the line is still.
Okay. That's all right right now. Let's get this edge over here. And as fast as you can say,
bops your uncle, boppies your aunt, I have a delicious virgin strawberry daiquiri. All right.
This one's good. Now we're going to go in the corner. Perfect. Minus two. Stop immediately.
No, I don't think I will. Actually, yeah, I will. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. Don't miss anything. Just
go slow. If you take your time, you don't have to spend more time added on top, going back and
doing this again. If you spend the extra time to make sure it's done now, you don't have to come
back and do it again. Efficiency. Don't steal that joke. There's a bunch of, there's a shit
load of people here that don't know me really. Hey, did you guys know? Don't steal that joke.
I'm going to do it. Did you guys know that every day you eat over an inch of dirt every meal,
every single day? Isn't that insane? Did you know that? You eat over an inch of dirt every single
day. It's crazy. Isn't that like kind of gross? It's that's a weird statistic. Don't you think
speak for yourself? No, everybody does it. We all do. Every single person
eats over an inch of dirt a day. I mean, you got to be sitting at a table. You got to be at
least a few inches off the ground eating that food, don't you? What's the joke? That is the joke.
We're not listening. I don't get it. I'm not outside the line. This is, look, the line's right
there. You clown. The line's right here. See? Hot, hot, hot, hot. Somebody wrote in all caps,
what are you talking about? I don't know how it was. Is it really this hard to follow this
conversation? Sometimes I feel like you guys act like you're changing channels. Like,
and then here we are. We got. All right. I'm focusing on this railing and I'm going to make
sure it's done well. Play with the ball. I can't leave. I can't cross that. I cannot cross that
line. Not until everything here is clean. Can't do it. Do I turn the music up? Turn the music up.
I'll turn everything. I'll turn everything up. That goes up a little and the wash sounds would
go up a little too. A little up. A little up. That's fine. You need to do a monkey impression.
Why? For what? All right. This railing's almost done. Am I going to get dinged for the railing
or is this not a ding? Is this not a dingable object? There it is. Okay. Don't leave the line.
Do it because you love us. Where did you get that idea? This is still in the line. The line ends
over there. I'm not going to do a monkey sound. Oh, okay. You're hearing it. That looks good up
there so far. All right. That's good. Now I'm just going to do the stairs and that should take this
whole wall down. By the way, Power Wash Simulator is currently in 1.0. Just released into 1.0 today.
After a while in early access. It's available for you to download right now.
Free to go get it on various platforms. It's driven today's sponsor, of course.
We laugh at all your dumb jokes but you won't even do a monkey sound. Don't you think that is a dumb
joke? If I were to just start doing a chimpanzee sound effect, that's dumb. Why would I be doing
that? What's my motivation? Direct me. What's the motivation? Not bad because you've done it before.
I love this half pipe. I love the watermelon. Dude, if I owned this park, they would be a
watermelon scented plug-in or something or watermelon scented spray that we sprayed
all around the place and then open the park. People would come over here and be like,
what? Oh my, dude, it's watermelons. It would be awesome. I gotta slow it down. This song is good.
Who recommended this? Because it's actually fantastic. Should I play the Flintstones SNES
game? Sure. It's probably gonna ding here in a minute. Oh, that was a good line. Come on,
let's see it ding. Ding. Ding. Let's see it ding. This mold on the wall? Yeah, I know but I'm doing
the pool. Whatever this thing is. Yes. All right, that's done. This wall over here now. All right,
don't freak out. I think I can go wider here. Yeah, here it is. Yeah, it's the Flintstones SNES
soundtrack. No monkey, no buy. So what you're implying that if I do a monkey sound, you will
buy this game. Powerwatch simulator available on Xbox S, Xbox X, Steam, Game Pass. So that's what
you're saying? Liars. You should be getting the game because it's a quality fun game with really,
really, don't look at my lips. I just spit out something weird. It was gross. It was disgusting,
whatever that was. You should be buying this game because it's a fun relaxing simulator of washing
stuff. That's what you should be doing. It was a piece of spaghetti.
How would you have spaghetti stuck in your teeth? That's not, it's pasta. It's impossible.
You don't have spaghetti stuck in your teeth. That will disintegrate over time. Not like a piece of
broccoli. That's that whole wall, I think. All the tops, the tops of this, right? Yep. I know
that we have to be perfect with this. We'll get the ding. Shit. Madden, you saw this in real life?
Is somebody power washing a park? I don't think that's that abnormal. Anything else on this?
Yeah, here. What is this? I just made shrimp grits in your honor. I mean,
hopefully it's good. I don't really like shrimp that much and I don't really like grits,
but I hope it's good. I know a lot of people like it. Ungrateful, he made it for you. I'm not eating
it. I have nothing to do with this. Ungrateful. All right, our strategy is working pretty well.
Look at that. We're almost a tenth of the way there. I just said, I'm sure it's good. You could
be the most talented pizza crafter in the world. If somebody doesn't like pizza, they're not going
to really want to eat pizza. That doesn't mean that you don't have a very delicious dish in front of
you. You really might. I'm sure it's good. What's that term? Bad pizza is still good pizza? No,
it isn't. No, it's not. Bad pizza is gross. Bad pizza is like sex. It's still sex, right?
Then they take the grease and they put droplets of grease in their eyes.
I mean, how in the heck do you make a slope out of concrete? I don't know. You shape it.
I actually eat junky pizza all the time. I actually love shitty pizza, so please
do not take this joke as reality. Still though, sometimes you get a pizza that sucks so bad
and everyone's just like, well, who cares? It was still $18. Who pays $18 for pizza?
A large pizzas are usually more than $15. I get a large pizza. I don't get a small. $18. Yeah,
what do you mean $18? That's pretty normal. Did I cross the line? No. All right. Are we good here?
Take a look at that. It's almost perfect. Chad, he's not eating it alone. I mean, I've seen
people crush a large pizza before and I'm just like, holy shit. Dude, let's be real.
I'm telling you right now, I have absolutely gotten really damn close to eating an entire
large cheese pizza by myself and I could have done it, but there's two more slices left in the box
and you look at it and you just kind of go, that would be bad. That already is bad, right? That's
already bad. If there's two or three slices left in the box and you're the only one eating it,
it's let's box it up and put it in the fridge, right? Like somebody said he's talking about
sex on a sponsor's treat. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. The sponsor was only for a little bit.
I'm just still playing the game. I want to support the game. I think it's a great game.
The sponsor segment has ended. We're just playing Power Wash Simulator because I think it's a great
game, which by the way, where can you get it? I'd like to see it in the chat, please. Where's my...
There it is. I didn't even talk. I made one small offhanded comment about people's opinions on pizza
and did nothing. I didn't talk about whatever. All right. We are good. It's time to make a new
line. You ready? Let's just do it. Let's make it easy to the bench. Like right here. Don't cross
that line. Probably should just switch to the... I don't anymore. So we'll do first pass. You sound
like the radio guy from PT. Hello. Hello. Hello. All right. That's pass number one. I need the
stronger nozzle here. I'll go over it again. That's the phone guy. You should have minus twoed that.
You had an opportunity. All of you that just weren't sure if you should have hit minus two,
you should have. I'm telling you, you should have done that. And now it's too late because now you
look like you're doing it because I said it. This is on there. Ooh, family from the town of
Rock. They're the modern Stone Age family. When you meet the Flintstones.
I'm just kidding. This sound effect, the Super Nintendo wind sound effect that was in everything.
This sound is so scary. It's such a strange thing. It always gives me some kind of... It makes me feel
a certain way. This is an undertale. What's wrong with you? Seriously? Oh, yeah. I get that
question a lot, but I don't even know what that... What do you mean? I'm just sitting here and just
talking nonsense, just hanging out. Some of you guys act like I eat like bugs after the stream's
over. I just kind of hang out. I do my thing. For some reason, I think a lot of you guys think I
do. Oh, yeah. Oh, here it is. My dinner. Oh, a whole plate of cockroaches. That doesn't happen.
I'm just a regular guy. I'm just a normal person. Yeah. Hey, I get high and watch the same TV shows
you do. Oh, dude, I think he eats bugs. No, I don't. In fact, I'm one of those people that...
You know the... Oh, look. It's the bug in the popsicle novelty item. I would never eat that.
I don't want that. I would never eat one of those. People always point to a tweet that I made in like
2013 where I made a joke tweet about eating... I mean, I swallowed a bug and it was like, okay,
that was weird. I should tweet about it. And I'm like, oh, it's the greatest thing I've ever tasted.
What do I do about this? It was clearly a joke tweet from like 2012. I had people point to that
and they're like, well, he's fucking crazy. But you know what I'm talking about? They're in the
kind of golden, almost like amber. I wouldn't eat one of those. There's usually a worm in it
or sometimes just some kind of other scary bug in it. No, no. Just give me the lollipop.
Why do you have... Why does it have to be a bug inside of it? Right? That golden kind of amber
lollipop. Can I just have that? I don't want the bug inside of it because I feel like that
actually tastes good. Whatever that is. But I don't want the gross bug residue on it.
Stop eating valuable rocks. Those are not lollipops. I find like these ancient stones
in the ground. I don't understand why people eat these. I don't get it. No, dude, that's a million
year old fossil. Don't put that in your mouth. It tastes really sweet. There we go. Did the bug
taste good though? No, it was... You're the only person that makes me laugh out loud.
That's actually makes me happy. I'm dead serious. Gotta laugh sometimes, right? Will you eat bugs
for the fans? No. No. I gotta get up on top of the railing. Would you eat a bug for the haters? No.
I'm not eating any bugs. Then that's where that conversation ends. I'm not gonna eat bugs for the
haters. Bugs for the fans. I'm not eating bugs. I wouldn't eat bugs if my... If like my mother asked
me to. Talk about my biggest fan. Eat bugs for mom. I'm not eating... Nobody... I'm not... I wouldn't
eat bugs for anybody. What about a doctor? I would feel like I was getting pranked. What do
you mean? The doctor comes into the office and he's like, oh Jeremy, okay, you have a headache
and it's time I can cure that for you. You have to eat four cockroaches in front of me while I hold
up a fucking cell phone with TikTok open. What do you mean by that? Like, is there actual
scientific evidence that this works? Okay, if it was true and there was a data, a trial or a study,
and it was passed, you know, whatever, whatever, whatever, FDA, whatever, it doesn't matter.
If this actually worked and it was for a thing that I wanted to get like cured, get rid of or
something. Dude, you know, that like chest and back problem I've had for like four years,
if the doctor came in and was like, Jeremy, uh, you know, that kind of like center chest like pain
that's really kind of fucking up your life last four years. Uh, if you eat this whole
bowl of cockroaches, it'll go away. And he said, here's the study. That bowl will be gone in 15
seconds. So I guess, I guess there is, I guess there is a place where I would do it. But no,
if he just kind of came in and was like, oh, hey, I'm a doctor. Eat bugs. He just opens the door.
Hey, I'm a doctor. Eat these bugs and puts them down and closes the door. I'm not going to do that.
I don't, I wouldn't do that. What if he ate them in front of you first? I don't care. That's all,
that's the, that's the, whatever weird shit he's doing. I have nothing to do with that.
So he comes in the room and he's just like, okay, so we took a look at your blood work
and he's just, he's just eating them out of his pocket. Yeah. Your, uh, your, your, uh, HDL
cholesterol is a little high. Uh, your LDL is okay, but you know, and then he goes like this
after talking about my blood results. I don't know. What does the doctor look like?
Is he like six feet tall, like 200, lean cut? Is it how, what does he look like? Does he have
completely blemish free skin? Does he have flowing hair? And it comes up with his license
and he's like, look, 60, 60. And it's, and he looks fucking amazing. I don't know. Maybe
I'd have to think about it. All right, that's done. All right. Plan worked. Dude, why do you
only listen to handsome doctors? No, I didn't say handsome. When did I say handsome? I said he was
like cut up, jacked, healthy, blemish free, flowing hair. He's looks like he's, he's me and
he moves in a full stride. You know what I mean? I never said, wow, look at how handsome this doctor
is. How healthy does he look? Oh, you guys are fucking hilarious. Okay. So fine. Sorry.
So this wicked handsome doctor walks in. Okay. Now, what do you want me to say? Who gives a shit?
He looks healthy. He's, he's, he's clean. He's clean shaven. He's, he's going like this,
like that. And he's postures like this. And he's got the clipboard up here.
He's got big hair and he's so fit. He just got done cycling and he's got cycling shorts on
and a lab coat. Stop sharing your fantasy. So, so my fantasy is this wicked handsome doctor
in bike shorts comes in and we eat bugs together and have a romantic relationship of some kind.
This is what you think my fantasy of mine is. Sounds about right.
Hold on. You're missing an incredibly important detail. He rides his bike down the hall
of the doctor's office. You know, the door is open. I can see out into the hallway and he's,
he just slowly pulls up on his bike. It's a huge mountain bike and he gets off and kickstand goes
up and then he comes in. Right. That's perfect. And he's still got, he's got, he's got the helmet
on. It's a big manly bike. He takes the bike helmet off and his hair is flowing.
All right. This looks good. I need a new line, a real man sized bike. All right. New line is
right here. Don't cross that. Hey, you want, you want to eat some bugs, man? Would you eat the bugs
in Jerma's fantasy scenario? I doubt it. I doubt, uh, yeah, no way. It's going to be mostly nos.
Don't, this is not, don't call it my fantasy scenario. This fucking music.
What is playing right now? Why is this playing? Why are we getting this fucking romance music?
Just got, just got done with a quick bike ride. Kickstand comes in. Just like sweat,
just glistening off his forehead. So what brings you in today? Well, I have a little
bit of a headache. Uh, it's kind of like a migraine as kind of deal I got going on here.
One second takes the bike helmet off and just hair. It's a fucking, it's, it's like at least
16 to 20 inches here. It pulls up the license 60 by the way. And I'm like, Oh wow. Look at that
crazy thing. That's why you got that. What a head of hair. Yeah. I haven't had a headache,
by the way, in a long time, different music. You want to eat some bugs. The music changed
and changed everything. This is bug music now. Why is this music perfect for all this going on?
What the fuck is happening? Why this is forget it, forget it. What even sound this auto played
water world for super Nintendo. Just started auto playing after Flintstones.
I went five and a half minutes into this. Stop. No, stop it. I'm getting on cam. I'm getting,
I'm getting out of here. I'm gone. Put on block. I'm back. This music. All right. What's this one?
What's solstice title screen theme? What the hell? I did not expect that.
Oh shit. This is good. Who put this in there? Who put this in the chat? This is VR Josh. This is
lightning good. Dude, this is lightning good. This is called solstice music.
Title screen theme by Tim Fallon. Holy shit. This is crazy. Tim Fallon also did pluck.
Oh, all right. That makes sense. Was that new line? Yeah. Here. Okay.
Silver surfer. Shit. All right. That's awesome. The game was absolute blast. No, the game was ass.
Let me read that correct. The game was absolute ass, but the music slapped. Okay.
That was insane. Oh, somebody can somebody take ad out of the title
because we're technically not. This is not an ad anymore.
Let me hear a service. I can't even say that word. Damn. You know, it's wild to think about
this kind of stuff with the tools that are available now. I wonder what some of these
guys could have come up with, right? Some of them are still in the industry, right?
But this is what they had to work with back then and listen to this.
People still do it. Oh yeah. But I'm just talking about back a long time ago when this is you
couldn't do anything else with this. I wonder if whatever tools they had, if you gave them even
more tools, normal music existed. But I'm talking about the, you got me. You got me
because that was dumb. I look, I worded that wrong though. Like if they could have done this
with an actual orchestra or, and it could have gone on a CD or something, right?
If they had the tools now back then to put it onto the cartridge orchestras existed. I'm not,
I'm saying, look, I'm saying that if they could put more data on a disc, what would they have done
with the data? What would Silver Surfer theme song have sounded like? Would he have changed anything?
Just do a tie on bug juices. He did the music for echo the dolphin. That was sick. What did
let's do another echo the dolphin. Did he do echo the dolphin? Oh, that's all Tim fallen. Okay.
The playlist from earlier. I held the Wilma way longer than that. So this is the whole playlist.
What is, what is this? Oh, that's not it. Okay. So what's in, what's the next in playlist?
This is the whole Tim fallen playlist. Let's go. All right. That's good. That's a good volume.
All right. Let's go put on block. I've listened to block a lot of times.
Did this guy do the original NES Ninja Turtles?
No. Okay. Kind of sounds similar. Like it could be similar. Somebody said, yes, you're the only
person that said yes. Why? So if you're wondering how much content is in this game, I've played
this two different times now. Galaga. I played it for like six or seven, five or six hours before
about three, four hours. Now there's at least, there's a lot of content in the game.
There's a lot of just to do, just to chill in flight. You already know that. But what is
you don't know is that it could be on the Xbox one Xbox. Wait, is that might be wrong?
But it's all right. The ads gone now. I'm not doing an ad anymore. So it could be on that.
Can I get this with the, this one here? Yeah. The command is still there. That's okay.
They probably just shouldn't be in the title anymore. Do the boss theme for, for flock.
I'll put flock on after this. Oh, that is still there. Hold on. I'm gonna go harder.
I'm at 37% right now. Is it better with the sound off? You want the sound on? I feel like
it's just kind of in the background. Keep the sound on, sound off or sound on.
RT game, RT game of the raid. What's up, RT? RT, you did this in real life. How was that experience?
Yeah. Thanks for the raid. Welcome. Playing power washer simulator. If you guys don't know,
RT did this in real life. He did a power washer stream where he power washed shit in real life.
Hope you had a good stream. Welcome everybody. Always a pleasure to see, uh, RT. You're just
doing work in a video game. Yeah. But then we'll listen to the fucking chip tunes while we're at
it. You can do that as well. Do I have to, do I have to explain myself? The most time I have on
stream in a video game is a game where you clean houses. Um, so I don't know. I just, I like these
games. I like this kind of stuff. I don't know. I just do. I heard this one already, but whatever.
What do you want to do? Don't explain yourself. You're going to make it worse. All right. I'm
up. This isn't, this is looking good. This is actually looking pretty good. No, there's no
raid song. Guys, we don't do raid songs. I, all right. I, it's time to put my foot down.
The raid song has not been a funny joke since 2018. I cease this. Cease this immediately.
Cease this immediately. Oh, yuck. What the hell? Can I not stand up there? Can I not walk up here?
Sorry. Maybe I can get the ding from here. It's going to be close. So many shit stains.
That'd be weird if that was at a skate park. I got to help. Heck of a filthy sidecar. If you can
fit us in, I can run it up to you if that helps. Wait, you'll deliver it here and I'll do it.
There's one thing I know about concrete is that it likes to be as flat as possible. What's going on?
Why is that blinking over there? Because that's the quest. I don't have to do that immediately,
right? I can do it whenever I want. Now, now, hurry. All right. Sorry, one guy. I'm doing it later.
All right. These rails. Good. Oh, the gate too. This like fence here. You know what sound that
makes too. It's like I love that sound. That's like one of my favorite sounds is a power washer
kind of hitting a grate like this. Yep. This is like a 10 hour version of this song. This is looped
four times. Has it? Oh, it's almost over. Oh, it's from the ladder. What's next? I don't even
know. I don't know what this is, but it sounds good. Does this work? Oh, I can. That's not that
high though. It shouldn't be the few more steps. You're going to fail the quest. I'm fine. Section
is almost done. Beautiful. Beautiful. I'm not even halfway. Holy shit. All right. I'll be good.
Wait, what? No, I'm not there yet. I thought somebody said I hit a million followers.
I was like, oh, wow. Almost there. Yeah, almost. I'm going to take a screenshot. Just play among
us for 10 minutes and you'll do it. Now I want it to be natural. I want it to be natural. I don't
want to just have it be like a, let's go. I'm supposed to get up there. That's that unfollowed.
Don't do that. Okay. Did I complete everything over here? All right. We're going to take a break
from that. Let's go to, uh, we'll put on flock. Wait, Spider-Man and the X-Men. Really? I remember
this. I didn't. Wow. This guy did everything. Yep. All right. So now I can make a new line. New line
is here. Let's say from here to here from this, like right here, let's just go to the edge of
here. Yeah. All right. That's good. New line. Oh, you know, let's make it easy there. All right.
New line. Let's go. You can still kind of hear this. What's next? Is this the same song? Guys,
I got a better idea. I want to play the maximum carnage. OST. This is a good one.
All right. You got to guess my favorite song on this album. Put it louder. All right. You got
to guess my favorite song on the album. It's not this one. I'll let you know when it comes on.
That is the title theme, right? I believe it is maximum carnage. I feel like weird right now.
I'm just sitting here going like, yeah, while I'm power washing a wall, listen to maximum carnage.
Yep. This one's good. Do you guys know that venom is a good guy in this game?
Did you know that venom is a good character and he's a good guy and he's an antihero?
Don't ever say the venom is a bad guy. He's not a bad guy. He's an antihero. It's good.
Morbius is that now. No more. Nevermind. Where's my stool? And no, this one's good too, but it's not
my favorite one. This one's actually pretty banging. Yep. Mod chat's got it. Dr. Clay's got it.
No spoilers, no leaking. Morbius is in this game? Wait, Morbius is in the game as what?
Is he one of the summons? I don't mean like who does the actor Morbius play as. I'm saying what
does he do? Is he a boss or is he one of the summons? Because there's five or six summons.
Can't you summon Captain America in that game? In maximum carnage? Yeah. No, you can summon
Captain America. He comes out and throws a shield at somebody. So he's a summon. Yeah, he is a
summon. All right. Who is he in the game? That's so stupid. Yeah, who does the actor Morbius play
in maximum carnage for the Super Nintendo? Not this one. Where's that line? Wait, hold on.
Some of you will get that. Some of you will. Some of you will. I will just unlock a fucking
memory and you'll be like, holy shit, you unlocked an entire memory. I'm glad I just
unlocked that memory for you. That's when you first hear this song and you first hear that noise.
You just woke up sleeper agents. Like I never played video games before. By the way, I want
to make sure you turn your volume down a little. When my favorite song comes on, it's going at
maximum as high as the volume can go on my OBS. That's not true. I won't do that to you. All right,
right to this lump here. This kind of sounds like the thing that Beavis and Butthead do.
They put their hands up. This is like a midi version of that. Oh, wow. Right here is
like carnage always hit me with the axe arm and it always just pissed me off right there,
right when the music stopped. Okay, ladies and gentlemen, I think it's time that I turn this
shit way the fuck up. It's getting there. We're getting close. One more Beavis and Butthead
and then after that, I think it's time to turn it up. Here it comes. It's definitely right here.
Turn it up. You guys don't know this is a, this is literally just the mob rules. Black Sabbath
song. Oh, the line. Oops. Sorry. All right. So hold on. Right. Right. I know DMCA, but still.
So you hear that, right? You hear that one. Let's put a DMCA, whatever. That's an ad.
All right. You ready? So hear that. So now it's literally the same exact song.
It's the exact same song. Hey, this one's DMCA safe. Spider-Man wrote this one. This one,
Black Sabbath had nothing to do with this. Spider-Man wrote and directed this song.
No, it was Morbius. I'm sorry. You're right. Watch that line. Don't go across it. I wish I
had more soap. An uncredited version of Black Sabbath. The mob rules appears in the soundtrack
during the boss battles against the supervillain. It was literally just ripped. That's so funny.
Back to our regularly scheduled water noises for a little bit. I'll put Plok on in a minute.
We've got to take a break from the, you know, that those sounds to these sounds.
I'll make a little rip bozo. What? Look at this place. I'm, I'm, I'm 55% of the way there.
I'm pretty much done. What's and I know there's still some, but this should blink eventually.
This streamer is like a goofy, that person left and then not coming back ever.
And I probably always remember that time when it was like, Hey, you should check out this guy,
Jerma. He's funny. I like him. And he's like, I'm yeah. I mean, I went to his stream and I'm not,
I'm not a fan. This guy's so crazy. He's like such a w wow. That was so weird. What he did.
He did like a goofy laugh to this guy. Did you hear this guy eats bugs? Jerma was funny today.
Sad. That's not fair. All right. Should I do the work order thing? No, I need a new line.
How is this only 57%? Here's the line right here. So from like here,
that's good. Um, yeah, whatever. That's fine. Let's get right in the middle here. There we go.
First pass. Why will we not play tally hall? What's tally hall tally hall? What, what is it?
Why people saying play tell? What's the, it's a band. Okay. It's a great band. It's just,
but why, why would I, it's just DMCA that they're good. They're good. But yeah,
I mean, I, I mean, I might put some DMCA shit up here, but I am playing a whole album on stream.
He isn't going to get me in trouble. All right. Let's clean this up a little bit more. Where's
the line? Right there. Right. What is this? Oh, I didn't even go up there. All right. So
I have a funny story about them. Think of water and soap. So my mother visited here at one time.
This is, I don't know, let's say it was, I don't remember exactly, but it was like last year at
some point. And my mother watches the channel sometimes. So she came over and she, you know,
was making references to the streams and Hey, yeah. So, you know, like look at me and stuff.
And I'm like, Oh my God, you watch, you actually watch the streams. So she started, she started to
like understand Twitch lingo and started to use it Andy. And the reason why I'm saying this is
because Holly was, was washing her hands, like very, very lightly, right? So she's washing her
hands. And my mother comes over to her and goes, Oh, wow. Soap Andy. Then she had never said
anything Andy before this. She called Holly soap Andy because Holly used like two pumps of soap.
And we just started cracking up. We were like, Holy shit. Oh no, we have converted her.
Soap Andy. It was like, honest to God, it was probably one of the cutest,
just most adorable things I've ever heard. It was just so funny. Like she had just learned the lingo.
She's like, I got it. I got an opportunity to use it. I saw two or three pumps of soap there.
Soap Andy. Has she been among us the whole time? I don't kind of. So sometimes I will stream
and my mother will make a reference to the stream that I did a day or two ago.
And I'm just sitting there going, there's no way she would know that unless she watched the whole
thing. But then other times, I think she just kind of pops in randomly. I think like once every like
few months, she will watch a stream, but I will have conversations and she will say,
you know, she'll say something like, there's no way you didn't watch a lot of the stream, right?
So for instance, like today, if my mother would have, would have get on the phone with me and be
like, oh yeah, so Jeremy, I found this new product. It's called the the water grenades.
I feel like you watched a lot of the stream today. Like you had to. For the love of God,
tell her to watch without chat. I don't think she even knows how to use chat.
She just like puts on the video player. There's still gunk on here. What? What did she think of
dollhouse? She liked it. If you don't understand the Twitch extension stuff, it's hard to follow
a lot of that sometimes. So but no, she she gets it. She understood. She knew what was going on.
Did you see you have whoopee with death? I assume I'm assuming. Yes, we don't talk about that
very often. And I'm realizing that my mother does watch stream sometimes. So she just heard
potentially a long conversation about me going to the doctor and eating bugs in a romantic
relationship with the guy. So she's a hate watcher. She just hates everything I'm doing.
That'd be so funny. Really, really bad stream today. Really not happy with what you were saying.
But that wasn't it wasn't funny. You know, I minus two the most I've ever minus two being your chat.
I didn't raise you like that. I raised you to be plus twos, Jeremy. Holly said she I missed the
romantic doctor bit. What is that? Babe, babe, delete the VOD. No, it's chat was acting crazy.
Like usual. She's being informed. She's laughing over here. Yeah, I okay. Yeah, I ate. I I chat said
I ate bugs with a guy. That's it. Yeah, I don't know why I'm like, oh, don't worry. No, no,
I literally ate bugs with the doctor. And that's it. That's it. That's literally it.
Somebody just wrote it was hot. Oh, please. Honey, honey, honey, honey, they fucked up. Okay.
Do you see you read that? Did you see that? This is unfair. You came up with the meat of the story.
She said, Why did the doctor have sexy biker shorts on? Hold on. Hold on a minute. Hold on
just a second. Never in that story. Never in that story. Did I say sexy biker shorts? Not one time.
I pull back the VOD. I want all of you to pull the VOD back. And not once did I say sexy biker
shorts. I did not say I said I said biker shorts. He was in biker shorts, not sexy biker shorts.
I want to know where that's from. Because it's not from me. It was verbatim.
All biker shorts are sexy. Okay. No, he was biking. She said, Okay, honey. Okay. See, there we go.
Honey, we're good. We're good. Stop saying sexy biker shorts. He said he was a 60 year old hot
biker guy. Skin is falling off my mouth. This is no this is not a sponsored stream anymore.
I genuinely think this is a fun game. This is not a sponsored segment anymore. The sponsor segment
is well done with that. This is just a very fun game, which Oh, man, I just wish I knew where I
could get it. Well, I can tell you. On the Xbox Game Pass store. You can get it. It's available
right now for Steam. It's on Steam right now. Just came into 1.0. Just came into 1.0 on Steam.
I forgot my line. Stop activating sleeper agents. It's got six co-op players. I feel like that's
gonna be insane. Why is everybody president sleeper? That's just your mom in chat. God damn.
That was a good one. That was seriously holy. Wow. That was a good one. But what a good callback.
That's a great callback. That was an absolute zinger. I can't believe I actually did the skate
park. That's shocking to me. Isn't it shocking to you? Got it. German sexy doctor sitting in a
skate park. E-A-T-I-N-G bugs. I found that one adequately humorous. Me too. Why did you read
that? Because it was funny. Are you questioning me reading messages in chat? I read a chat message
that said I said I was going to shove a baseball up my ass. There's no I'm you know, then that's
gonna get you banned, right? But I'm doesn't mean I'm not gonna read it and be shocked by it.
I keep that lives rent free in my head. You have no idea. You guys have no idea. I've said it
yesterday. It's rent free. Every day I think about somebody just typing out. Oh, no. Yeah,
dude. Let me help you out here. Are you really a new viewer? Yeah, let me help you. He's gonna
shove a whole baseball up his ass. That's the baseball stream. There's so much. There's so many
layers to why that's funny. So many. It's one of the funniest things I've ever heard probably in
chat because there's so much of the going on there. This is big stream event. I keep hyping it up,
man. Oh, the baseball stream, man. Be ready. It's gonna be me putting a baseball in my ass.
And I'm hyping it up for months and months and months and months in a like in a baseball field
or even not. Am I just here? That's what makes me laugh so much is I'm the baseball stream. Oh,
he's gonna play baseball. No, it's me in this chair putting a baseball in my ass. You understand
how much is going on here? And why? Why would I hype that up so much? Why would I ever? But just
so nonchalantly just replying to somebody with a very basic question. Dude, baseball stream.
I wonder what that is. A new viewer. Oh, replying to that person. Just as being a mother fucker.
Dude, he's gonna shove and it was it's not just baseball. It's whole baseball.
It's whole baseball. He's gonna shove a whole baseball up his ass.
It's like, God damn it. So much goes into that what I hear and see in my head. Hey, guys. Hey,
bro. Yeah, welcome to the baseball stream. It's time. Get hype. It's the baseball stream. I've
been talking about this for a long time. You know the stream where I shove a baseball up my ass.
It's like, what the fuck? Why would I get it? It's read free forever. I'll never get rid of it.
It's always going to be there because it's implied that I've been talking about it for months and
everyone's like super excited about that. This is so funny. It's so funny. Maybe. Whoa, cool.
Maybe I am a childish and immature moron, but I'm sorry that's funny.
That's very fucking funny. You know, and that person's banned from the channel, right?
Mods like please refresh my memory. That person has been permanently banned from this from
German 985, right? They are permanently banned. They're never they're not allowed here ever again.
Or the way they weren't. Oh, they're all saying I don't know. Look up and see if they have
permaban. What do they get? A week? There are 30 days? Wait a minute. Hold on. This person has
been unbanned and they asked if I was going to play World of Warcraft the other day.
Jerma, play World of Warcraft from Ball Fondler. Yeah, yeah. What a legend. Hedges? What?
Average WoW player. Wait. Um, what are you implying? What are you implying with that?
What's the what are you implying? Average WoW player. Average WoW player? But why?
What do you mean? Why are you saying that? Because of the ball? The baseball? What is that?
Okay. Hey, by the way, I was a huge World of Warcraft fan, buddy. So let's relax for a sec.
No, you're making it live rent free in my brain again. I'm seeing the original messages.
Dude, what the fuck? This guy should be banned like permanently. Okay, how many times have they said
this? How many times have they said this? Wait a minute. How many times have they said this?
This is the hold on the rabbit hole just got deeper. This is fucking unbelievable. Hold on.
Give me one second. So here this this is the original comment that lives rent free in my
brain forever. It's the funniest fucking comment I've ever heard. So let's get this let's get this
done right. Because this this is a saga apparently that I did not know existed.
I don't think I can show this on stream. I don't know I could I can't show that on stream. That's
gonna get me in trouble. Not dodge is this guy. Okay, this is the this is the original message.
But it gets back. This this just kept going. I didn't know this kept going. I can't show the
rest of these but he goes on he goes on oh my god he goes he goes on to say how many
baseballs you think you'll be able to do at germa 985 what the fuck how many you think
it's hard to fit so many up there don't you think his it's pretty gruesome okay you know what
I bet he's gonna do vocal warm-ups omega lull plucking his ass hairs for the baseball stream
this guy's gonna get this guy's gonna get snapped this guy's getting Thanos snapped right now
this person this person's just been out there we've been this person's been out there in the
wild but anyways he's been banned I did not know that ball fondle had that ball fondler had that
much of a track record I did not know I thought he had that one comment and then was talking about
world of warcraft oh my god it's it's fucking funny I don't even care it just is you know what
I mean what the fuck man if you wanted the shit that that you look over and you see sometimes you
guys wonder you guys wonder like oh man is he reading chat right now oh yeah is it does the
streamer read chat okay oh my god you're enabling them now no no all right you will you're gonna
get timed out for shit like that I'm just being really honest with you just be careful we got
rules even though it might live rent-free in my head we have to have we have to have order here
oh my goodness I'm just chewing my lip now if he bans ball fondler how long do we all have left
I don't know don't talk about me shoving baseballs up my ass and I think you'll be okay if I you know
if I have to guess that's so funny though all right we got to move on but that what a saga
that is that is unbelievably funny we have rules on this channel follow the rules follow the rules
or you're gonna get you're gonna get snapped out of here but you don't follow them yes I do quick
put it in emote only emote only quick you understand that in the shower I'm gonna be
just sitting there just laughing all the water just like hits me in the back I'm gonna be laughing
in the shower about this whole goddamn thing oh you don't you break 50 percent of your own rules
well hey I I own the joint all right hey I can I can smoke in here if I want oh shit hold on
is that turn that off I gotta turn this up okay never I think I'm good I'm good just no sponsored
okay nothing sponsored on the screen I think I'm good we're good yeah yeah we're good holly
holly is sending me funny messages from ball fondler and I don't want to read them holly
sending me funny messages and I'm having a lot of trouble I'm having a lot of trouble
my goodness what is this buster scrugs whiskey is illegal this is a drag county
well what are they drinking whiskey these outlaws oh well don't let my white duds and pleasant
demeanor fool you I too have been known to violate the statutes of man and not a few of the laws of
the almighty you ain't no outlaw and we don't drink with tin horns sir it seems that you are
no better a judge of human beings than you are a specimen of one yeah whatever
all right okay streaming is so fun can I just tell you it's like this is so fun this is like
don't resident sleeper ban that person for six days I don't even know what we're doing here but
we're doing something fun right I don't understand what we're doing but I'm having a great time does
that mean is it weird I don't understand should we ban the sleeper emo to go no no no let him get
it out of this system let him get it out of this system where's my stool all right no no no no no
wait wait wait back it up but I know this okay the sponsor segment is over right but uh I do
want to say that uh thanks to power wash simulator because uh this was this was a fun one this is
really fun the game is really fun too absolutely go get it support these guys oh no you're gonna
make me look like an idiot although okay don't resident sleeper for this part because like if
somebody clips this and like was like hey well cool he said he like said something about the game
it's just gonna be resident sleepers but you guys love this game like I know you do
I'm certain you do so let's make it look a little less grim in here okay how much more do I need to
I'm gonna fall all the way back on my back oh bro oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh why is the volume so high
you can't resident sleeper this can you fucking jokers when is this thing done there's nothing
else here oh it's a base here I get it it's the base it's the base everyone's hype in the chat
yeah what these chatters don't understand is how would you be sleeping and typing at the same time
how is it possible that you can type resident sleeper and be asleep it implies that you're
sleeping on this at the stream yeah we know they're here I'm almost done just this little
section and that's it something's in my eye this looks so fucking stupid I'm sitting here
rocking out having like a great time and I look over it's just uh it's only resident sleepers
imagine just coming to the stream for the first time you'd be like wow this chat hates this guy
they fucking hate this dude they are not they this is they're always having any fun what else you got
clean lines clean lines there it is all right mods let them up let's see what they say let them up
let's see what they have to say see what they have to say for themselves after they've been in
sleeping time out free ball fondler all right yeah I'll do it uh for him okay let me go over here
and click look free ball fondler okay let me go to unban and okay and uh click okay got it now shut
up I'm a sleeping resident I'm a sleeping resident after a riff like that get out of here give me a
break when are you doing the power washing stream you best start believing that I'm playing it
because you're in one this just makes me want to just drink a pina colada this part makes me want
to be in first place in a mario kart race it's almost done 92 that's right taking everything
up in one pass 93 we're getting there this is one of the biggest maps so far clean lines this one's
really on there anyone music what else we got anyone music to play what's this one anybody
want to throw something in there I'll take anything whatever ace combat let's change it up
sounds good ace combat zero all right when's the baseball stream august 19th I'll get you a time
as well but not not immediately august 19th in the afternoon it sounds like metal gear what is
the baseball stream well it's uh that's bait don't take it you're gonna get banned don't take it
don't take the bait don't take the bait you're gonna get banned don't take the bait don't take
the bait you're gonna get banned I'm just saying be careful damn this is good 95 still what did
I miss besides this wall right here this is the only wall right I think this is it and maybe the
tops well just hit me something just smashed into me threw me forward I didn't do anything
97 I'm gonna it's gonna be such a pain in the ass to find where this is you might enjoy death
stranding no I don't think so here's why so somebody said dude you like these kind of tasks
you're a big fan of just kind of like a menial task or whatever no see the issue is this game
I can kind of pick up and jump in for four or five hours or so um not a hundred hours right I mean
I can just play I can clean up the skate park I can be done I can do this in a couple hours but
when the whole game is a menial task and it's like a hundred hours long I'm not into it I would I
wouldn't be able to get through death stranding I know that it's a good game but I just um after
hour number 20 or 30 I'd be like I don't want to do this anymore I'd just be like that's a bad take
jackass I just said just wait why I just said the game is probably a great game but I might I just
I don't have attention span for stuff like that I don't have attention span for anything that's
over 50 plus hours for a game um and you probably say what about Elden Ring that's a once in a
lifetime video game there will never be another Elden Ring that is the Super Bowl of all video
games at this point like it's just come on it's once in a generation Sekiro didn't take me 100
hours Sekiro was like 40 Dark Souls 3 was like 40 30 45 whatever it was what about Red Dead Red
Dead wasn't 100 hours okay oh that's what we're missing right here got it this should be it too
not quite um what am I missing this place looks phenomenal is it just all the bullshit on the
ground here is it all this crap it's all this stuff that's oh my god it's everywhere all
right I have to just do some sweeps here damn it I need the stronger nozzle come on did I already
get this no I definitely didn't there it is okay he's still on this you see how much was here
this is an entire skate park and we had to pause for like 30 minutes to talk about
me he who will not be named oh yeah there's other game modes I'm gonna I'm gonna try I'll try the
other game modes after this I think there's I think there's like a painting one I'm curious
don't try it 97 percent come on Gwen really where is there another three percent top of the wall
you might have a point there hold on yeah you I think you got yeah you nailed it it's definitely
the top of the wall all right I need the ladder yeah all that junk up there where's the ladder
there it is yep oh there it is good call good call
98 over that side I want to you know I want to see the the time lapse this will definitely do it
right here because I hope so 98 still I guess there's some more here you can't get it all
let's be realistic here check the pause menu oh the fun box the gallery bench all right the
gallery bench it's over here oh shit I didn't get underneath this at all there we go oh it's
the underneath right I need a little one yes the top left bar shows the progress almost got it
come on 99 let's go you have to finish it I'm gonna finish it look this is it how did they get
dirt on the bottom of this bench I don't know that's a good question almost there this will
probably do it come on ding ding god damn it god damn it what's the problem I'm not sitting on
that dirty bench look at how clean this bench is now oh my god it's impossible to even get over
there this thing is clean this thing is fucking clean bottom all right now fun box what the hell
is a fun box that railing is bad what about these railings are these okay yeah these okay yeah okay
wall skate park floor railing this is done oh there's the fun box dude I just got this insane
urge to piss this extraordinary urge to piss all this running water I gotta piss stop it's done
skate park floor every little speck of dirt it's all over here I gotta piss I gotta pee I gotta
be back I gotta pee soap andy all right let's finish this one up I'll check out one of the
other game modes or so and then probably uh call it hi all right where is this it's all over here
just sit right here and just go just sweep running the edges all right that's clean that's there's
no way that's not clean now you missed a spot stream from the toilet it would be like old times
um no that's that's that's time for me that's time for nobody else come on 100 there it is
all right now it's just this ground and it should be any second now oh okay that's all over there
too all right okay this level is hard it really is it just so much you gotta be very detailed I
was just I was just sweeping and running around I should have blocked it off this railing needs
it too underneath kind of yeah come on my like whole body wants to like springboard what soap
do I use um in the store ah that feels better harvest moon a wonderful life breeze 30 minute
extension sure why do I get so loud this is nice this is on game pass by the way if anyone's
wondering with cloud gaming oh shit is there a cloud gaming oh no okay so in the mod chat uh
they're talking about hey this is on game pass by the way it's got cloud gaming I played it while
he was peeing and uh we're like no no we're not talking about the harvest moon game cloud gaming
harvest moon Nintendo property that's a good question is it third party it's not they should
have gobbled them up a long time ago I just did that what not powerful enough I'm at 99
percent is driving me crazy I just need I want to see 100 so bad it's driving me nuts
stop rushing I'm not I wish I could play for you I wouldn't have missed this get it right now you
have an opportunity to pick this game up right now whatever the outlet you'd like to buy it on
game pass on xbox s series s x it's on on everything is it on ps5 ps4 do I have any gray hairs nope
all right wall ramp skate park floor dude I want to go in a helicopter and look down and see where
this is where is it come on the guy's not gonna whoever owns this place is not gonna walk around
and examine every single piece of the ground you know how you fix this you call the guy and say hey
by the way the park is ready for you to come check and make sure it's clean and the guy's
gonna get in his car grab a skateboard as the power wash person put the skateboard down and
when the guy pulls up in whatever car he comes up to check start just doing kickflips and skate
around a kickflip skate around you know I haven't tested it out but it's nice and clean and then
having a couple of random marks makes complete and total sense make sure he can see you doing
kickflip good oh I got a little scuff there it's all right yeah I mean I
it's parks clean I've been trying it out press tab I dude I'm pressing tab every five seconds
this one's already done ah where thank god okay which wall wall and ramp wall wall wall wall
where where what wall selected in the menu ramps two out of three where the baseballs
are pushing up into his brain it's so stupid get up hurt it hurts play a new song fine this is a
good one holy shit I was doing a dumb joke where I was pretending to be on a skateboard
this should not be happening kickflip kickflip grind kickflip grind nice all the way around
let's watch you can see me mark the line cool that was pretty efficient all right okay so
I want to there's other game modes let's challenge mode wash against the clock
free play specials clean the gnome fountain well I've went there a uh what's challenge mode
vehicles specials clean the mars rover am I on mars cool is there any sound effects
that's right all right mars rover let's go and do it hell yeah 13% oh it's really muddy
something walking around weird I keep thinking it's a pterodactyl mars just looks like jurassic
period the whole side what jurassic I said jurassic period not jurassic park how is he
cleaning everything what I missed what you said this is looking shiny nice and shiny how are you
cleaning everything and nothing at the same time oh I see I'm at 86% I've been here for like two
minutes all right what's what's missing here turn it off shake the hand out stretch back your
oxygen is at 21% get that toilet paper roll where this is this guy right here what's missing
footprints oh so this is oh you would have to come find it okay click the hidden gnomes I'm gonna
put them in the cockpit all right what's left what's going on here where the hazard cameras
I guess I got it tire wheel hub and tire other side right there I'm supposed to get it in there
I guess like that and then hazard cameras where the hazard cameras it's blinking it's glowing in
the front yay does it show me go to the alien cool all right what about challenge mode vehicles
all right how about the dirt bike challenge one minute 30 seconds three two this probably
people they're insane at this come on come on what the fuck what the fuck what the where
where is it what's a swing arm 25 seconds wait what wait this one is only using a certain amount
of water 15 liters conserve conserve I'm good I'm all right fuck off what excuse me okay that's
actually not a bad strategy you didn't think I saw him sneaking up on me shit I'm not gonna do it
look at all this bird shit shit it's over I got close I got closed I got close enough 93% that's
an A on a test I'm so glad I got that that would have bothered me for the next like three days
I whatever if I conserved a little bit more I'll be fine but whatever I don't care
wait a minute this whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa that was for gold okay can I get bronze
I'll take third place that's fine dude third place you still get your name in the newspaper
who cares bingo bingo get the fuck out of the way 25 and I get bronze I got it I have there's no
way I don't have it doing this inside of your garage would probably be a terrible idea it's
gonna get water everywhere all right just another mirror and that's it I'll take bronze that's fine
I didn't miss a spot I got everything we're good all right I'm gonna wrap it up let's wrap it up
I'm not gonna finish this one I didn't start another one did I I just want to see what this
is this one looks huge apparently oh this is the state this is like an overwatch character
I have the overwatch weapon all right it's a big train wow use your old oh let me let me get in
there okay stun all right it's time to ult I didn't hit anybody my stuns up in two stuns up
into stuns up into done got it good good go go go go go go go push push push push push get the flag
I don't even know how to play that game anymore all right that's it that was fun this one's really
powerful push the cart wait there you got your monkey there it is get up here this has been
yeah no seriously though thanks to power wash simulator for sponsoring a portion of the stream
earlier I just kind of played the game for six hours but you know whatever it's a great game
it's a lot of fun y'all knew that go check it out it actually is oh look a hidden gnome it actually
is pretty much on everything it's on game pass go buy it you get it on steam and they uh they
supported the channel today they sponsored the stream so really cool I will see you guys the
next stream will be what is today let's find out I will see you guys on Sunday I'll see you Sunday
we'll do a Sunday and then probably Tuesday Wednesday when's baseball August 19th August
19th will probably be fairly early again on Sunday so not 11 a.m. but probably two o'clock
not four o'clock we'll do we'll start at two I'll see you guys later good night
thanks for watching we'll do the credits that's a fun stream I think a lot of interesting thing
happens interesting things happened today appreciate it thanks for all the subs thanks
for the raid rt by the way if anyone from rt is still here thanks for the raid welcome yeah
there's a lot of fun now let me move this rip yeah let me go over here this this like monkey
just keeps yelling yeah I believe they're at at power wash sim I think right if you're looking
for if you want to follow them I think I got that right do I have that right because somebody
confirmed that is that correct yeah it's at power at power wash sim I'm sure they'll take a look
and see what they're doing uh I'm gonna dump you guys on tomato because tomatoes playing it too
tomatoes currently playing power wash sim go say hello tomatoes a really good dude really funny
guy time for more power washer aren't you excited and we'll see you later thanks for watching
goodbye good night I'll get the outro up there thanks everybody see you again goodbye no excuse
me get that right to 10k get that right to 10k right now come on let's see it come on let's go
let's go all right see you Sunday goodbye