All right, that was fucking weird. So apparently, I don't know why this is,
but I guess most of Twitch's servers are down. So let me explain why this is possible. I usually
stream to a server in Arizona, right? So I picked the Arizona server. That's the one I usually
stream to because Italics and I run from the same box. We both decided we shouldn't probably run
to the same server. So I was just like scrolling through picking new servers.
Which one of these is going to work? And then you guys saying this stream was fine. So I'm like,
well, let's just go to the same one. So we're both going to the same server and there's no
problems at all. So I was freaking out. I thought there was a major problem with like my computer
or something. No, it's just all the Twitch servers are all fucked up. I guess that's just
what's going on. So welcome. Sorry for that. I wish I was live 15, 20 minutes ago. Anyways,
I need a coaster here. I feel like I should retweet again, but it's all right. Let's just
get started here. What is happening on stream today? Well, let me give me a second to explain it.
I just turned it on. I just was able to be live for a minute. Just making sure it's going to
work now. Now, now, now, now, now. All right. Everybody relax. I just, I just like dodged a
major like computer bullet. Okay. And this is what we got here. Okay. Hi, by the way,
I'm a little flustered. I'm a little like fucking angry. I've just, I can't help that.
I got to come down off of like being upset because I was really upset. I was just very,
very irritated, but not anymore. I think I'm just making sure this is good. Nice table. Well,
this is a fuck you table. You don't know what a fuck you table is. It's a table that you
just do whatever you want on it. You don't really care. You paint on it. You play card
games on it. You like pick it up over your head and throw it down a flight of stairs.
Just because you felt like it. I got here three decks. This is the thing I was talking
about like last week. Probably like, why do you get a fucking iPad here? First of all,
I know people are going to talk about it, so let's just show it. Yes, this is broken.
I don't know if you can see this. All down there is a big crack down the middle.
I stepped on this out of bed one day and now there's a big giant lice down the middle
and it's cracked and the volume doesn't work anymore. I was lying in bed sleeping sometimes,
but I don't know why I do this. I'm just a fucking idiot. I have an end table to my left,
so instead of just putting it on the end table when I'm tired, I'm falling asleep and just go
hang it over the edge and let go. I don't know why. I'm just fucking crazy. I just get
so tired that I just like hang it over the edge and just and then fall asleep.
I forgot that I did that and I got out of bed one day and I just put the heel down
right in the middle and then stepped again. No, no, no, no. I'm not ready yet. I'm not
ready yet. Don't press this button. I've got to be so fucking mad right now. I was about
to elbow through the screen. I was going to WWE off the top rope through the middle of
ice cream. I was so fucking angry. I got to like, how do I, how do you, give me like an
exercise. Can I do something? How do I like make this right? How do I like change this attitude?
I've got such a fucking bad attitude right now. Give me a minute. I have such a bad attitude
right now. I can hear it. I sound different. I sound like an attitude boy. It's not like
let it go over the bed. Like whatever. I can feel it. But should I tweet again?
Everybody like, are we good? Or should I like tweet again? No, I think I'm all right. Anywho,
I don't know which one of these I want to play. This game is this like 20 of them,
right? So I got these three. I don't, maybe you guys could pick which one we want to do.
I don't, I don't know. I was going to just like randomize and like let my finger
stop on one of them. We've got the clown world, like clown in the town. We've got wild west world.
We've got dinosaur world. So I don't know which one of these three we want to do.
Let us click. Well, I think people want to do clown from my, from what it was before,
my understanding. Squeak and sausage. Now I have no idea how this is played. This might
be the worst spring you've ever been to, or it might be the best spring you've ever been to.
It's one of those like flip the coin. Which one of these is it going to be?
But each one of these has a deck, which I very specifically was yelled at
because look at this, ready? You open the box. Look at, oh, this is cool. Unlock. Important.
Do not look through the card decks. It's like, don't fucking touch this.
So I'm like, okay. So I haven't even opened them. They're just here.
It says, don't just don't touch it. So I just, so people look, I want people to know that I
didn't fuck with this. Sealed. Inside of the shrink. I haven't done anything to that. I want
to make sure you understand that. I'm not, I'm not trying to cheat here. The goal of these
decks is it is an escape game, which pairs itself with this. You pick one from here and
then you've got to escape the game. I don't know how the fuck. Yeah, I've got my
fingerprints on it now. All right. So you understand how it works. Well, I mean as much
as I do and I don't really just fingerprints all over this. Yeah. I mean, yeah. You want
to like dust this. You're going to find all kinds of fucking like fingerprints on this.
You'll find footprints on this too. You'll find nose prints. Okay. You know what a
dog when there's a sliding door at somebody's house and at the bottom of the glass with a
sliding door is there's like dog nose prints, like literally all over it. Like that's,
that's definitely on here. Like I've gotten close before and like my nose is streaked down
the middle. So this is my nose prints on here. All right. I think it was, let's just do the clown
one. That one sounds like the most fun. I think that's the one I want to do. And look,
these are supposed to take, you have your timed to do these. You have 60 minutes to
complete them. And I'm going to try just to do one. So how do I, let's see. Unlock ages
10 and up, 60 minutes, one to six players. So if they, if I had six, okay. I might go over a
little bit of time here because if it's 60 minutes and you can have six people working
together, I mean, I'm going to take the whole 60 minutes, right? It's going to take me like
a long time. All right. Hold on. Important. Do not look through the card decks before
starting to play. There's a 10 card tutorial deck and then a 60 card deck. Each deck is
a full independent scenario. Enter an immersive adventure and work together to complete your
mission. You have one hour in real time to overcome the many challenges. I got to go
like smell like a rose. I'm going to go get a flower. I'll be right back now. I was
about to leave. Nevermind. I'm not, I'm still here. No, get this off. I just,
God, I got to get this out of me. I'm going to scream. Okay. I think that'll work.
I need to like scream. Like I, I'm going to scream. I feel a little bit better. All
right. I think I'm good. Did that work? This is like a devil just sitting right here.
There's no angel here. There's two devils and they're both just like fucking throwing
darts into my neck. Just like, could you really go get like a drink? But it's like,
it's like fucking four o'clock in the afternoon. Oh, I got to just like relax.
I got to beat the clown game. Okay. It's over. I'm live. Everything's fine.
Everything's fixed. I got to like fucking get over it. Okay. So I'm like fucking happy
Gilmore Ray. I swear to God. All right. Welcome to unlock. I don't think I need this
anymore. Do I? Maybe I should put that up here. Feels nice. Get a better table.
Don't push me right now. I'm already fucking flustered. Don't push me.
Okay. So you guys are not going to be able to read these that well. So I just like
looked at the fuck. I just saw all the answers. I think the fact there's like a teacher's guide.
There's like a teacher's guide. No, I did not. I didn't. Right.
There's no, that's not what's on the back. Why did it? Why did it not say don't look at
the back? Oh, do I look at that either? Okay. I didn't see anything. I swear to God. How do I
get this open without seeing the answers? I swear to God. There is like a full on cheat
sheet back here. Do I, am I supposed to open the deck? I am right? The sick feels pretty nice.
These are high quality cards. I just, I don't know. I just want to see what it's not like.
All right. Tutorial. Welcome to Unlock. You will find all the sensations of an escape room game
in this game. You will be confronted with puzzles, codes to decipher, objects to put
together and tricks to discover. For this first adventure, you are in, you are at an interview
in the Unlocked Secret Society on the top floor of an office building. The manager who welcomes you
smirks and leaves you in a seemingly trivial room, locking the door behind him. Oh,
a secret society. All right. Here we go. All right. I'm ready. I got to get excited for
this shit. This is like in like 10 point font by the way. Hopefully they're not all like
this. All right. Launch the app, select the scenario tutorial. Okay. There's like all kinds
of weird shit on here. And then press start. You now have 10 minutes to get out of your first
unlock adventure. Are you stuck? You may ask for hints in the application by entering the
card number. Oh, okay. I gotta go. 10 minutes remaining. Turn this, turn over this card.
This is the office. Here is the room where you are locked in. Several elements are visible.
You may now search and reveal the five cards whose number you can see.
Okay. Search and reveal the five cards whose numbers you can see.
You guys get a good look at that. Make sure you can see that. Okay. Okay. Honestly like
I will tell you what's happening because I got 10 minutes. Okay. What is it? 20. What card?
Search and reveal the five cards whose number you can see. I need 11, 21. There's a fucking
million of these. All right. 21. 21. It's going to be 10 minutes to find these. 67.
Okay. I gotta put this out in a good area here because this 21 is down here. 67 is up here.
Do I have anything else in there that I need? I don't think so. Okay. Wait. Nothing else in
there? Okay. 21. 67 is a room up here. 35. 35. 42. Okay. Eight minutes and 33 seconds. Okay.
42. And then hold on. Let's get this in a better spot. And 11. All right. Here's the
room where you're locked in. Several elements are visible. Okay. I can see a trash can.
A desk. A window. A switch. All right. You may now search and reveal the cards. What's
over here? We got a key. We've got an exit door. We've got a grid with five centimeter
apart pins. Okay. We got a locked cabinet. And we also have a TV screen. Can you guys
see this shit? Do I have to like turn the brightness up on the sun? Okay. So we got
this is the office here. Key. No. Well, I'll play like this. You can combine this object with a
red object or the red number of a machine. To do so, add their numbers together. If the total
corresponds to a card in the deck, you may reveal that card. So I can combine this with
a red object or red number. I can do key and TV. Okay. So should I open the TV with the key?
Keys don't have TVs. Add their numbers together. To do so, add their numbers together. If the
total corresponds to a card in the deck, you may reveal that card. 53. No, I can't. I cannot
use the key on TV, guys. A locked cabinet. You can combine this object. Okay. Key on cabinet,
which means 45, 46. So 46. We're going to do key on. Yeah, there it is. 46. We could
open that cabinet with this key. So then here we go. Ready? Oh, sick. Very good. The
cabinet is open. Discard cards 11 and 35. Look closely at the picture. There are two
interesting elements. If you see a number, reveal the card. We opened it. We opened the
cabinet. 16. I see it. Okay. Boom. I gotta like turn the sun up. I'm turning up the sun.
And give me something like music too. No, that's for the dinosaur one. What's
up with the clown one, right? Let me turn up the sun. There we go. Okay. Now you guys
can like see what's going on here. Now you can see what's going on. Maybe a little too
bright. That's better. All right. There we go. So this is a... What is this? Did I
actually make it worse? Electrical wire. You can find it. Okay. Combine this with a red
number or... I'm running out of time here. Now it's too bright. So I got a red wire.
I can add it to a machine. If I have red wire on TV, I think that might be better.
All right. Red wire on TV. That's what I'm going to say. So that's 16 plus 42
is 52, 58. No. That can't... No. No wire on TV. Red wire on this weird grid over here,
possibly. This is a machine. Single... Your first... Your goal is to obtain a single red
number. Some of them... Then add that number to the blue object modifier. Single red
number. I don't have a single red number. Are you telling me I can't use that on here?
What about the exit? I need... There's a four digit... All right. I see a skull right now.
What am I supposed to do with this wire that ends in rings? I... No. I definitely have to
put it on here. That's definitely where that red wire goes. Obtain a single sum of one or
more black numbers. I don't know what the fuck that's even talking about. I can't like
just use that on here. I can use this on a machine. So that would... But there's no
cards in here for that. Just crawl under the door. TV is a red number. Yeah. That's... So I
could... But that... There's no card here that could make any sense. You add these two
numbers together. 16 and 42. There's no number in here that matches that. Should I just
flip these cards over and see what they are? I have two minutes left. It's definitely
this and this. Why would it not be? It's a single red number. I discard these. Should
I just get it a hint? Take the 16, add two of the numbers on the 67 card. I don't want
to just... 10 and up, man. I'm not old enough to play this, I don't think.
So I'll have to combine like two black numbers together? Not these. I don't even
have a hint. Oh, 16. No, I want a hint. Card number 16 could be inserted into the machine.
That's what I'm saying. So why... I just did that. So what the hell is going on here?
If the total corresponds to a card in the deck, you may reveal that card. It doesn't.
Two black numbers plus 16. Like, didn't I discard these? It's a... Discard cards 11 and 35.
So I discard these. How do I combine two black cards if there's only one available here?
Use the app. Machine. What? Wait, what? Hold on. No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. This is the machine? I'm dead. Combine this with a red object or the red number of
a machine. I have to add two num... Oh, I thought they were talking about like cards.
Single red number. Sum of one or more of the black numbers. Okay, so I thought they
were talking about like this shit up here. That's all right. We've only been dead for
48 seconds. We can come back. Okay, so we need a single red number from four, five,
four plus two. So then add that. Okay, so what about six plus 16? So we've got to get
two of these and then it's going to correspond to a card in here. Okay, so 25 minus 16.
All right, I fucking get it. Don't worry. Everybody relax. It's okay. We're just
figuring... This is the tutorial. So it's going to be nine, right? Seven, eight, nine,
plus 16. Okay, I thought I had to like do something with this shit. Apparently not.
What? Nine. Wrong. I'm going to flip the table in a fucking second and I'm going
to play like fucking pee pants. I have to enter 67 into the app? No, I don't. No,
I do not. Oh my fucking God damn it, dude. Are you serious? You lose one minute per error. It is
best to first understand which are the right pins before using it. Okay. All right. Everybody
relax. I'm starting to understand here. When you have a machine card, you have to use the
machine, the actual machine that you have in your hand, which is the iPad device.
Should have gotten that rose. Okay. So we need to have 25 minus 16. And we've got this here.
We need nine. So you've got seven in the top left and two in the top right.
And there you go. Thank you. Okay. I lost a minute. What are you talking about?
25 minus 16 is nine. I don't understand what's going on. Can you, can you help me?
I don't fucking understand. A single red number, some or more of the black numbers, right?
Sum of one or more and then add that to the, to this blue object, which is the wire.
If the total corresponds to a card in the deck, you may reveal that card.
So why did, why can't it just be, does it have to be a certain,
how was that? I don't understand. How is seven and two not nine? Why is six plus three,
nine and seven plus two, not nine. So why I did seven and two and it said wrong cabinet.
Look at the cabinet. I didn't know that was important information. I didn't know that I,
all right. I'm going to start to 25. Are you ready? Well done. You have restored the
electricity by placing the wire on the machine. Discard 16, 46 and 67. 16. Discard. 46. Discard.
I didn't know I still needed that. Where's 47? It's already discarded. 67 I mean. Got it. All
right. The power is back on. Plus six. Plus six is a modifier that you can add to a red object
or the red number of machine. Okay. If the total corresponds to a card in the deck,
you may reveal that card. 42 plus six. Well played. The screen lights up.
Seven, two, three, nine. Well played. The screen is on. This should help you out to get out.
Discards 25 and 42. There it goes. Hey, what you, you can enter a code into the application
thanks to these four digits. To get out and finish the tutorial, you must enter a four digit
code into the application. What's that? Code. Seven, two, three, nine. Seven, two, three, nine.
No. What? No, these are the correct numbers, but they aren't in the right order.
Oh, it's red. Red, yellow, blue, green. I got to pay attention to these cards.
It's color coded. Nine, three, nine, three, nine, three, seven, two. All right. All right, boys and
girls. I did it. I understand it now. I get it. I get it. Check your score. Your time and the
penalty is in court. 17 minutes. I used one hint. I lost a minute and I got two stars.
That's not bad. I've never even opened up these decks before. How the fuck am I supposed
to know? I'm ready. I think I'm ready for squeak sausage. I think I get it. All right.
All right, here we go. Can you guys see? It's all right. I'll read it to you. All you guys need
to know is that this is like the Simpsons. Now it is too bright. The sun's like going
up in a random. I'm going to zoom the fuck in. I got an idea. Is that, you guys can
probably read that a little bit better. I mean, not really, but that's better, right?
Enhanced. Now I got this right here for you to check that out. Yeah, there's no way anybody's
going to read this. So what I'm going to have to do is I'm going to have to like go like this,
but even still, no, you can't read that. Nobody can. Just trust me. I'm going to read
it to you and you'll get it. You'll get the gist of it from there. All right. I think
I'm ready. Are you guys ready? This is called squeak and sausage. This is the clown one.
So let's get some appropriate music. I need to go get like fucking drinks for this. Here we go.
I'm going to go get like drunk tonight for this. Not yet though. I'm going from like coffee to
alcohol. That's not, I'm going to slow down. Okay. Can you see? One, two, three, go. Blasted
Professor Nose-Side. Once again, your old enemy has stirred up an evil plan, but you have
courageously slipped into his headquarters to prevent it. While you wander in the corridors of
this old shack, a trap door opens beneath your feet and you fall into a dark and damp dungeon.
Your screams will not help you. You are prisoners of the professor. The world is lost forever.
Unless you can get out of here and sabotage the plans of Nose-Side,
you are our last hope. Launch the app. Use your iPad and launch the application to get
out of here. Kids, launch the app and select the scenario. Squeak and sausage. Then press
start. Oh, squeak and sausage. This is a hard one. This is like two, this is, look at it.
This is like two locks out of three. Okay, kids. Oh, look, it's got like its own theme too.
Cool. I'm not going to press the button. Can you see that? All right, here we go.
Press, what do I have to go to the bathroom? I might have to pee. Do I, can I, do you get to
pee in the dungeon? Is that, does this not work like that? All right, here we go. You
have 60 minutes to get out of this adventure. Turn over this card. I'm, you are plunged into
darkness. What? But what do I do? Is there a number? Anybody see a number? I see a J.
Is there a J? You guys can't even see. J, I see J. J. There's no J's. Is there, there's no number.
Here, I'll get you the better camera so you can help me. Does anybody see anything?
We're going to die down here. It's worse. Does anybody see, I don't see shit. I see a J.
G? I have no fucking idea. There's too much light in here. There's only a J. But what
about, wait, wait, what number is the alphabet? J, A, B, C, D, E, F, G, H, I, J, 10. Right? That's
the number that it's corresponds to. Wait, wait, wait. Oh, there are letters in here.
There are letters in here. There are letters. See, G, J, J, J, J, J. Look up a J, look up a
J. Come on. J, I'm going to fucking drop all these cards. Where's J? Where's the J?
Is T, does anybody see J? I can hear them. I can hear the aliens. Where is
J? No, pick them up one by one. A, 72, P, this is P, 4. I'm just looking for the flag
in Double Dare right now. I'm not even playing an escape game. Where is J? This is not even
in this deck. Am I fucking crazy? I must be crazy. There's no J. There's no J. It's a lie.
Okay, I take it. All right, I got it. J, you grope in the dark and end up finding. Yes,
it feels like a light switch. All right, I got it. So that's one. One. I couldn't
have just started at one. I don't, I don't see anything. Hidden object. What? I just
canceled something. I just got a hidden object. Wait, I just like pressed the X.
How do I get back to that? One. Okay, good. Whoa. All right. We can see now.
Get a good look. Okay, store room. Hallelujah. The room that you were locked in from the start
is a store room. Okay, we can look at all these other things. Finally, we can see.
So we got a fridge. We got a TV. We've got a cabinet. What is M? What the hell is M?
Yeah, you guys take a, okay, ready? Take a screenshot. Like put it up on your screen
like that. There you go. Okay, now you know where it is. I'm going to say there's a
little pouch over here. Let's go, let's go for M. I'm going to, what's this thing? M.
I don't know how much more of this clown music I could take. I'm not, I can't even hear it.
I can very faintly hear the clown music and it's like probably annoying a lot of people.
All right, do I discard these now? I feel like I need, I discard this. M. Can I just like
spread these out on the ground? I'm going to put these on the ground. All right, M.
Let's see what M is. What the hell does this mean? I'm appearing in, it's like a
25, 25, 79 and then plus one. They're all, they're all pluses. Strange. Okay,
so now I mean, I don't know what that means. 91? Let's check out 91.
It's 90. So I have to add those together somehow. I want to like make my own one of
these and have some of them like have like, never mind, 91. I'm putting them on the ground.
Did I already go buy it? No, it's of course the last one that I got here. All right,
91 is this cabinet over here. Let's see where it is. I'm going to get this in a right spot.
Let's move these out of the way. So 91 is like a radio, a dilapidated old VCR. So that's
here. That's what's over the cabinet. You're playing an escape room by yourself. Yeah,
I got locked down here by myself. I like fell down some weird hole. It's one to six players.
For those of us that are alone in a room. Okay, VCR. We also got 11. 11 is a TV.
I'm turning off, I'm turning that fucking music off. I keep hearing the same loop.
Yeah, I'm not having that play for like a fucking hour. 11. Come on, come on, come on.
I got 50 minutes. 11. Got it. This is the TV, an ancient TV VCR combo. And weirdly enough, guys,
what detective work can you see there? The rewind button is broken. It's popped off.
Why is that? I'm going to have to figure that out. I'm turning this fucking music off
and I'm going to put on, I'm not putting on doom. Has anybody uploaded like background
clown music? Here we go. This one, this is creepy circus clown music. Is that any worse?
Okay. I got, I got, I'm timed. All right. An ancient TV VCR. All right. Now we've got
avoidable. We got H. See, this is how, this is why you play with two people because like
somebody's the banker in monopoly. So this is the fridge. Make sure you guys can still see
everything we're looking at here. Here's the fridge. A high tech refrigerator. It makes ice
in different shapes. The instructions are simple. Add water. Choose the shape of your ice.
Enjoy. Okay. So we need what? So now let's see P. That's P, right? P is this door is locked
with a digital code. Here's the exit. And it's the weird doctor is looking at me. So this
is the door. And then we got 14, which is this little cabinet over here. That's pretty
creepy. Actually. He just like staring at the other window 14. There's a lot of little
scenarios in here. Why do they all have to have the alien sound? This is a different song.
This is a completely different video. Ooh, a bag containing little seeds. All right. Let's,
we got them all. Let's take a look. A bag containing seeds with this. I can combine this
seeds, high tech fridge, an ancient DVR combo to VCR. And then this thing over here with
pluses and pluses on it. 79 plus. Okay. Put seeds in the VCR seeds in VCR. No, that wouldn't
fucking do anything. Seeds into this here. So that's 14 plus 30 right now that I can drop
those in there. I can't drop them in the ice machine. That's like a little game. All right.
So 14 plus 38. So I need 48, 49, 50, 51, 52. 52. So we're going to combine these. We're
going to put the seeds into this little like weird machine. Oh, no, no, no, no. Wait, wait,
wait. No, I have to combine them, right? It's yeah, it's 52. How's your fucking Sunday
going by the way? What day is it? 52, 52. There it is. It's a machine. So, but yeah,
but don't I have to combine them? And then machine 38. This machine is special to access
it into the sum of the four pieces which form it. Some of the four pieces that form it.
There's one, two, three. Is it 52? The four pieces that form it. 38, one, 25, 79.
So just add them. Yeah, there's another piece of the maze. If there's another piece of the
maze, then how do I get from... I'm going to put the fucking seeds into the...
Makes ice. This is no water, right? These are just seeds. If I get one more of those alien
spaceships. What about that? 31. Let's try it. Let's do that. Let's try the ice machine.
31. Okay. 35, 30, 47. Which makes ice in different shapes. Do I need a shape? What about
this one? A star. 35. Add this result to a blue number. 35. 14. Can I put it in the bag?
Can I dump it up with the ice in the bag? I don't know. I don't have any water.
How do I get water? Can I turn the TV on? Put the seeds in the VHS. Yeah, but I don't
think that... Does a number correspond with that? I don't think it does. Melt the TV.
Pee into the ice machine. I don't think that's how it works. Pause it. All right. Hold on.
You can only combine... I'm just trying to think. I'm not cheating. I just had to take a sip.
When I sip, it doesn't count. A bag containing strange little seeds. An ancient TV VCR,
but these are... Can I put the seeds into the TV? I feel like I need to combine these two.
Ugh. 38 requires... I need the other piece of this. So where's the other piece of that?
Is it like... Hold on. Is there something I can do to find that? You know what I'm saying? Is
there something on this piece that will show me? Use the VCR. That's not a machine,
though. 91, that's not a machine. The machine is green. I can't use the VCR. I can't use the
TV. I can only... I can make ice, but I need water, or whatever. I can make ice cubes
in different shapes. But then when I have an ice cube, I have to combine that ice cube with a
blue number. But this is just a bag of seeds. Will it grow into a bush? Am I gonna do a hint
right now? Okay. I'm gonna... We're gonna do... Here's what I'm gonna do. 31, and I'm gonna
make... I'm gonna take the... I'm gonna make the... I'm gonna take... I don't know. How about the
skull? Add this to our tube. Okay, 30. 44. Let's just... What happens with 44? Is 44 in here?
Will it do anything? See, this is good, because you guys are part of the other people.
There'd be like four people all being like, hmm, where's the TV? And I'm just... I gotta
do it on my own. I'm the kind of guy that when somebody starts to say a good idea,
I finish their sentence with them, and act like I had the idea, too. So I can't do that right
now. It kind of sucks. So yeah, we take the seeds, and we put it into the... Yeah! That's
what I was gonna say. Exactly. Yeah, you and I are on the same page. There's no 44 in here.
So, uh, this 41, so that's not correct. What about one of the other ones? I'll go back.
Can I just put these two together? 38, 48, 49, 50, 50. I'm gonna look at 52. I'm looking at it.
That's what I would do. I would say that. That's not it. That's something else.
That's like a big rat. I don't know what that was. Uh, I don't know what to do.
The high tech refrigerator. 35 plus 14? 31. 35 plus 14. Ice to the seeds? I'm doing a hint.
I don't care. A hint for 14. You could always try to plant them, but without soil,
they're useless. Where am I supposed to get soil? I have 40 minutes to beat this whole
mission. I'm gonna just... I only have a few options here, and those options are
just combine these with these. So that's 35. So this is, yeah, so this would be 35
and 14. Let's just see if it's in here. That's 41. That's 55. 45. Is 45 in here? 41.
I don't think 40... I don't think there's any 40s in here, but that's 41.
46. Come on. What? That's not... What are you guys getting 49? 49?
Well, where are you combining 49 from? What's 49? 35 plus 14 is... Oh, all right. I'm a
fucking moron. Sorry. I forget sometimes. 49. I don't think it's even in here.
There's no 49. What's stuck here for... We're dead, and we're gonna die in here.
This is 46. We're literally going to die down here. Yeah, guys. We're dead. We're
dead down here. We're gonna starve to death. There's a fucking number on here. There's a
number. Do you see that? There's a number right there. It's tiny. It's 18. God damn
it. All right. There's 18 down there. Should I just grab 18? Do I have to combine it with
something? 18. No. The VCR has 18 down underneath. 49 and 18. No, no, no, no, no. Wait.
Why would we go water to seeds into the VCR? I just have to get 18. I see it. I'm like
looking at it, right? 18. I don't understand this at all. There's 18 on this VCR, but what
does that even mean? I'm gonna look at 18. If there's no 18 in here, I'm throwing the
deck in the air. 89, 39, C, 18. All right. Crisis averted. Got it. A VHS cassette comes
out of the video recorder with difficulty. All right. Now I got, now I got VCR into the,
uh, should I play it? Into the TV. 18 plus 11. Into the TV. That gives us 28, 29, 39. What?
It's 29. 29. It only took us, it only took me. I'll be honest with you. I'll be real.
It took me that much time. Gotta pay more attention to the random shit that's all over
these things. 29. There it is. What is it? Boom. The cassette is not rewound and the rewind
button on the old VCR combo is unfortunately damaged. It takes time to come out. Press
the penalty button. Three minutes at such precious time! What? What's the fucking point
of the VCR? So what do I do with the fucking, I discard this, right? That's what, that's what
that means. I think I throw this away. What is the point of the fucking, so I hurt myself
and now I have just a random tape and that don't work. Is there anything on the rewind
button? Use the, use the VCR back into here. 18 and 91. Machine 91. No, I've, what is it?
Is that going to work? 18 and 91 is... 90. 90. 90. 90. 19. Uh, 91. 99. 109. Okay,
there's definitely not a 109 in here. This is no way. They're all double digit numbers. No,
there's no triple digits in here. No, that's not going to work. I just spent all this time
for no reason. Putting a stupid cassette into a t, into a TV for no reason. No, there are
no triple digits guys and this is I 91 doesn't do anything so what the hell am
I supposed to do with this um I thought that was gonna be it too was the tape
the tape says please be kind rewind there's nothing else on it but I can't
rewind it I can't can I put it back in here and then hit the rewind button
no the rewind button is broken on here are there any more fucking like
numbers that are hidden in here I don't see any what about on the door
nothing on his face nothing in the pouch no this is still I need four of these
have we ever seen anything look at chat what are you talking about what's this my my kimasi
my kimasi 79 no but these are that's that's the artist fuck wait where is anything I'm
almost going to lose and we have like a thousand cards remaining 91 minus 18 what do
we mean minus 18 why would we mind that we don't minus from the cards yeah 91 is is
discarded at this point look see on the top 91 has an x through it once this came out
I had to get rid of 91 um I'm gonna uh I'm gonna get a hint for 31 I'm gonna get a hint
for 31 what shape might you actually need and most of all what for no a heart a skull or
star doesn't do anything for me at all zero what do you mean what shape do I need I don't
there are no shapes that I need there's a crack through the tv the rewind button is broken and
there's a light on the top left is it anything else I can't see anything else on here you've
made zero progress yeah I'm very well aware okay I'm gonna use a hint for 11 you must
rewind the tape manually what are you talking about rewind the tape manually this shit's 81
it's 81 are you kidding me are you fucking serious rewind the tape rewind the tape huh 18
becomes 81 why would why would I have done that is this the impossible quiz 81 come on
let me be right yeah yep 81 watch this shit ready yeah a rewind VHS cassette tape unbelievable
discard 18 unbelievable okay 81 plus 11 a bunch of bullshit you gotta start thinking
outside the box here all right 81 plus 11 get it together bang put it in it was 92
you found out my diabolical puzzle there was no puzzle bang there comes hey the despicable
professor no sign appears you're at my mercy I will destroy this planet and no one not even
you can stop my evil plan oh that's it discard 11 and 81 uh what's on the tv anything I see
hee-hee so what was the point of this I see hee-hee hee-hee 34 34 34 is it 34 plus 34
what are these puzzles is it just 34 this guy like vaped and blew up like a riddler puzzle
like give me a break 34 is it in here either that or it's 34 plus 34 32 13 come on I only
have 20 minutes to beat this it's there's no 34 in here 34 right what's 34 and 34 34 30 68
68 come on 68 no that was correct 63 56 32 57 13 58 83 50 foot stop bingo 68 what do you mean
t no it's not it's not t the mouse this is not it it's not t it's not going to be t guys
you can't no one not even you can stop me for the despicable professor inside
appears you're at my mercy I will destroy this planet I will destroy this planet
destroy this planet 34 34 what about the door that's what about the door
two wait what do you mean code 34 34 got it the door creaks open into a new room
take the card f I spent so much time like rifling through these f look at me okay
get rid of p and get rid of 92 I still have this fridge I still have the maze I still have
my pack of seeds so we've got a the hq the hq looks like we got a it's like a living room
a desk another piece of the maze a door and then seven is like a bunch of locks all over it
I gotta go all right see let's check the just the table first see I'm splitting them up we're
gonna have numbers and letters you might think that's cheating if it's not it's very much
not cheating z e c I need c c c c c c c c c c c there's c okay got it right here
okay great c bang it's a desk oh my fucking god we just another layer we just put another layer
on here um okay um a tidy desk it must be here that no side puts the finishing touches
on his evil plans look inside of z oh fuck I need like more don't drop these please
get this up here I can't handle this fucking music anymore give me something else oh my god
no thank god I thought it was not playing okay what is uh we got how about this one this one
seems fine this is scary uh creepy halloween clown music all right sounds good all right I
got 17 visit c c c c c let me look inside the maze there's a maze there I want to look
inside of it got it okay I got all these numbers now see there are one two three four
five of these numbers but wait a minute that's not this there's more there's another piece down
here this is not even the right one this is the wrong one that's that doesn't connect correctly
all right that was z t t is this like color-coded wheel down here no okay this draw is locked
with a digital code so that I gotta get inside the draw okay get inside I got that this is
like that's I got that's the ultimate goal here 24 24 is the glass of water it looks
like on the table here although good luck looking at seeing that good thing you got
me here to explain it 24 there's got a glass of water oh I just the water okay simple glass
of water this is one of my items it's going up here so I got my pouch of seeds my water
and then the fridge so I can do 24 plus 31 get the right hydrate you got it I gotta
all right hold on I gotta pull this out so you can see more oh don't I'll show them to
you but you guys you guys need to be able to see more because we're getting way too many
items there we go that's a little better okay I'm getting more items so you can know what we have
I'm expanding we're expanding okay so this is at 24 what wait don't go anywhere check this
before do you see anything on there I'm just waiting for somebody in chat to say something
I don't see anything no hidden numbers no hidden thing I don't see shit I think that's
it so that was c now we're gonna go to a a is the other puzzle piece I think on the side
of the wall there do you remember I told you how I kept on hearing the alien pause it
do you remember when I told you I was hearing the alien sound and I was like shut the fuck
up this fucking alien sound is pissing me off it's coming from here it's actually like
sounds on the ipad uh I'll show you how do I like turn the volume up all right
take I'm gonna take a pic of you guys you ready this is the maybe this music was just
playing that's enough of that all right what we're doing a right oh hey yeah here we go I have 14
minutes I turned off the music okay here we go oh music got it louder 46 minutes gone I know I
know we're just learning all right hey I need more space okay sorry I just fucking bumped into
a there's another one of these god damn it there's gonna be another one there's gonna
be four of these fucking things how the hell am I gonna figure this out there's like
10 numbers on here well that's the correct one there and this is not correct yes it is
fuck this fuck you table sucks okay that's a uh what about three four three or seven
let's go three there we go kitchen please do not enter so this is the kitchen can I like
skull on the fucking door get skull ice cube put it in the door got it uh before we go let's see
seven seven is an entrance and obviously an exit and there's also v there's another layer
here I gotta put these together I gotta fuck I'm this is starting to freak me out all right
let's move this so this is this door this code goes I'm gonna do like this because I'm
starting to get a lot of things here let's go like that so these are connected together
and then this is so I need v now which is another like a close-up of the door
v what did I just open the door the door opens onto a pretty garden in the middle of which
stands no sides shed laboratory you need to enter an aggressive guard dog stands in front
of it it's the impossible to get past it's impossible to get past while the monster is
still here okay so he has a guard dog that just sits out front all right um well shit now um
go back so this is the water I can do that I can get the cube so I have the water which
gives me number 31 which gives me 30 so machine we're gonna do 31 get the skull
add this result to a blue number 30 and 24 go back let me go back hold on one thing at a time
so this and this makes the ice cube which is 34 55 56 55 55 55 54 31 and 24 is 55 yes it is
is there no 55 shit what do you 54 31 41 oh it's the
ah it's not the number up here it's the number right there it's 54 no don't leave game
54 got it ice in the shape of a skull discard um what discard 11 h and 24
discard where's what is what number what is this h or 11 I don't have an 11
I don't see 11 what number is it is it h or 11 it's too blurry because this webcam sucks
and even though it's new it don't matter what did I not discard I h I don't have that all
right so now we're gonna do 54 into three which is the skull so we're gonna do 54 55
56 57 this is gonna get into the kit we're gonna have like a whole
another like thing to do I'm gonna have to get like another table
56 where's 57 57 opens the door fucking god damn it get rid of three and 54 you got it
the kitchen oh shit ah there you can see good good view this so we've got a stove
a microwave and then a weird thing over here next to the sink 40 we're gonna do let's go
to the stove first the stove is 89 89 I can do this shit in a minute 89 got it okay let's
open the stove it's an oven in which little cakes are baking a message is stuck on the
door and that's the message is 73 73 okay 73 is the I need to get 73 there's the stove
okay stove oven 73 is the note on the door 77 51 36 73 oh I can't read this fucking thing
it's so small dear the message left by the oven probably by the cook dear professor here are
the chalk cheddar cupcakes you asked for I've gone to do some shopping if you could just
add the cheese at the right time it would help me ps to stop the cheddar being eaten by you know
who I've locked it in the cupboard I won't give you the code I know you love deduction games
given your intelligence you shouldn't have any problems guessing it ps don't burn everything
like last time all right the cheddar if you just add the cheese at the right time would help me
stop the cheddar by being eaten by the mouse we already got spoiled on that unfortunately
it's locked in the cupboard I won't give you the code I know you love deduction so we gotta
get the code to the cupboard cupboard is 63 let's go go go I have to get another
fuck you table I think 63 bingo here it is a cupboard shut with a combination lock
contains cheese and flies so here's the lock to this so this is the lock it's a four digit
code we got E E is another one of these is the oh shit this looks like a sausage on it
okay so that's complete now but what the hell how do I get to the sausage okay hold on
I've got six minutes to beat this so hold on 41 is another I can get I look at something else
here 41 there's a little like a window to look through 41 is a window a poster of
questionable taste decorates the decrepit wall questionable taste uh purple red green
oh wait that that that that that that that hold on hold on hey look at this
how many purple all right I got it no I don't there are one two three there are one two three
four five six seven purple one two three four five green and then one two three four five six
orange but how does that correspond to this this four numbers is it just the same one two three
four five six so it's just gonna be six six we're gonna lose it's obvious very obvious
we're gonna lose this one but who cares this is fun okay so it's seven six seven six five six
you got it done seven six is gonna this is the desk over here so seven six five six
so I need to do a code into code seven six five six the drawer slides open it's overflowing
with papers and various documents what the fuck is wrong with me I forgot like where I was all
right pause it this doesn't count anymore what was it I don't even know what the card just told
me seven six shut up I don't want to hear you I want to hear my music the creepy one
and I already see people clipping it and that's great I'm pausing it no wait I need to
seven six five six draw opens I need card number nine card I'm pausing it I don't care card number
nine that's like I just got like a surprise birthday present number nine what's in it
all right what do you guys think's in here all right get rid of t and get rid of 41
finally I can start to actually discard this shit what that leaves us with these rooms the
maze the gold the cheese the ice box what do I still need this for the drawer is full of papers
and gadgets of all kind there's pills in here that's six there's also a number four in there
do you see that I need to like move the camera for the next one let's go six six
there we go what are these it's a sleeping pill on the dog I think it's a
pills the sleeping pill on the dog right the monster to get because it's impossible to get
through is it can the monster is still here I'm gonna hold on to that for a minute now put
the items up here do it right items go up top that's all I got in here that was in this
draw let me just put it underneath so we know there's also a number four with a purple
envelope there don't let me forget that or I'll never fucking stream again okay so
let's put the timer back on no where are we okay the oven the sleeping pill um
door the pill the monster this I mean let me see can I like what is this what do you start
where's like the entrance here I have no idea um 63 is up there I need the code to open the
cheese box I gotta get through here somehow I have the pill I have the bag of seeds I have the
this like sausage all right sausage I'm gonna here we go ready I need to do I gotta do the
maze I gotta do the maze to get to the sausage hello you will only find four useful objects
in the drawer what you will only find four useful objects in the drawer what are you
talking about holy shit there's a cupcake on here hold on there's a there's a 78
is that cupcake oh shit there's degrees on here too start time 12 17 300 degrees
does that matter 78 should I get 78 because it looks like a 78 and four 78 oh my god it's
like a whole recipe the page torn from a recipe book the beat three ounce softened
butter with 2.5 ounces sugar add two eggs and the melted chocolate sift in four and a half
ounces flour and a pinch of baking powder mix well then add one fourth cup of milk
fill the molds with this delicious mixture and bake for 30 minutes at 300 degrees
when almost ready add the cheddar and continue baking until golden okay and then four so that's
the recipe this four four four is another part of this book assembly instructions for a Swedish
toy kit thank you for purchasing the my key maze rodent maze to what do you mean cheater
cheating look at I said that already look at four is right there in the green book
we're talking about so here we go to enjoy it start by fixing the parts of the maze together
I did that it's right there then slip your favorite rodent in the right hole and watch
him happily romp around okay what fun for you and your small pet if he finds the correct path
a well-deserved reward will be released so we got to pick the right one of these
this is instructions for so we gotta pick whatever one is the right one that gets the
sausage okay so I gotta do this I gotta do this unpause I'm not gonna unpause
until I'm confident that it's gonna take one minute 13 seconds to beat the rest of the game
all right fine I was loose is this still horror music playing I still have fucking
scary music playing what do you mean no that would mean there never was what's playing
right now what is going I see the the levels going up and down what is playing
there isn't yes there is there is music playing right now you don't hear this
no that's a lie you guys can hear this you don't hear this that's bullshit
ah countdown timer I thought I heard like an explosion
oh okay the countdown has finished but time continues you can finish the adventure all right
well at least you got the background music all right so I gotta start let's put that up here
I gotta find the right one now bear with me here because this is really little
sausage out this way um up here no this way around no it's hard to do this they're not
connected right fucking come on man okay I'm gonna draw on this I need to I have to
they all blend together like a magic eye wait hold on fuck god damn okay it's not nine
what about this one 18 18 plus that's not 18 plus has to come through this way
god damn it I'm gonna get a pen use the iPad what do you mean use the iPad wait hold on this
is a machine it's a machine so uh 38 enter the sum of the four pieces okay 26 plus 21
plus 38 plus 15 38 48 49 51 53 53 63 73 74 84 94 100 no that's not right 26 36 46 47
57 58 to 9 60 61 62 72 82 now it's 100 there's no 100 in here oh my fucking god damn it
all right so um can I draw what do you guys think no not that way it is it's gonna be over
here somewhere so down here around this thing up and down right here oh it's that's whatever
is this one right add this number to a blue number one plus 15 15 because the seeds no
I don't have a number I don't have them I need them I the pills no wouldn't be well I
I need the sausage what am I missing here I need like the mouse 63 63 is locked I gotta pee so bad
the oven I gotta pee so fucking bad I brought back I almost just knocked over all this shit
I was really close okay so how do I I need to get a mouse or a rat or something
we're back okay I need a mouse or a rat to get the cheese inside of this maze
how would you do that do you think a cupboard shut with a combination lock contains cheese and
flies I have the recipe for the cheese recipe is there anything else on here
there are the sleeping pills the recipe the instructions and then there's a book ah there's
a book in here take a look at that book you can't see it that well but there is a 37 on that
left book I am seriously like sometimes I think that like I'm the smartest fucking person in the
room yeah I am I'm the only person in the room 37 37 so I am technically the smartest person
in this room but I also might be I could you know I could be the dumbest person in the room
oh yeah I am the smartest and stupidest fucking person in this room there's nobody else in here
I'm also the most handsome person in the room I'm also the ugliest person in the room
okay uh this is notes music score three three three one three five is there a piano
I don't see like a piano or something three three three one three five I don't understand
how that plays into anything else but it is a musical score nothing else on here right
this is probably the code this could also be just added together but if it's 18 then
but what would that why would that matter is there 18 still in here I don't think 18
still in here 18 was already out yeah well 18 was the uh the cassette tape musical score
maybe the stove I can't like put that away for now let me see if there's anything else
there's the door with the dog there's nothing else on there there's a doggy door there's the
cage with the cheese in it there's the fridge with the ice in it that I think I'm supposed to
yeah I'm supposed to get rid of that okay I have seeds I have sleeping pills
there's the kitchen the maze which is already done but I need the mouse so I need to do
this shit in the kitchen I gotta do the stove okay cheese and all right let me see this
page torn this is the recipe book the start time of the oven is 1217 and it's 300 degrees
fill the molds with this delicious mixture and bake for 30 minutes at 300 so that started
at three 30 minutes and now it's at 12 minutes and 17 seconds which then bleeds into
is could that be is that four digits is it just this oven timer thing let's see code 1217
now it's not 1217 that's wrong is it whatever was before that it's not 8008 it's not that
I have no idea add the cheese at the right time the cheese is locked up it's locked up
because the mouse is going to eat it don't burn everything these are in the oven already
is it maybe it's the time that it already was cooking for I think it's the time it was
already in there for it's a 30 minus 12 seven that's what 17 minutes and 17 17 um 30 40 17
40 to 43 come on what what the fuck what is it then how do I get this mouse what is
this musical score for what are these the pouch of the seeds for uh sleeping pill sleeping
pill for I did wait did I do that wrong all right I'm gonna use a hint hint for 89
the cooking started at 12 17 p.m. therefore oh that's that's what time it is
30 minutes it's a 12 third it's gonna be 12 47 got it you open the cupboard and take the
cheese that's hidden behind a cloud of flies take the card 32 all right sometimes you gotta
use a hint and we're like 20 minutes over but it's okay 32 a small piece of cheddar
matured for 18 months all right I got a lot of things to discard here oh don't drop the whole
deck well I must drop a whole deck okay get rid of uh 68 or 63 which is the one we just
opened 63 get rid of 73 78 so get rid of 73 78 63 89 okay so 63 73 78 89 freeing up some
space here all right get that over here so now I have a piece of cheese cheese plus the maze
I think cheese because that would mean the mouse would come in no I need cheese plus um
the dog door cheese in the in the sleeping pill because that no no no hold on can I add
no no no no no okay hold wait wait wait so hold on go back to here this was 100
and it was which one this one right I don't I really just don't remember I think it is this one
there's a mouse in the kitchen just yelled at me there's a mouse in the kitchen oh god
damn it guys deep deep deep in that hole there is a tiny little faint 20 you can barely
see it 20 there is a mouse hole 20 plus 32 is going to give us the mouse 52 it's right here
bingo found him he looks so sad lord by the cheese a mouse comes out of the hole you have
difficulty catching it but you succeed in the end now we do this and the fucking maze
well I gotta clean this up move this over here looks pretty good all right I think I can get
rid of this shit I don't think I'm okay so now I which one was it it was up here right this
one so now 52 plus so 53 because that's we already got that one 53 I think it's in the
back I thought I saw it already 53 no no just no no all right so what what do you mean no
okay I have maze correct maze and mouse is not the right answer correct what was it the wrong
was it the wrong place to go was the wrong maze all right um I guess like let's try this
one over here it must be this one then no it's not no these are all wrong none of these are
none of these are even right this music sucks I don't even know what it is what's the Halloween
music how about um here I'll make everybody happy for like five seconds let's put on Yoshi's
Island everybody thought it was going to be doomed but you're wrong all right that's cute
I'm getting to the end here in like another three hours so what's my no that was correct
because look at all these other ones oh shit okay hold on 52 plus nine
60 60 61 all right this is it right no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
I'm seeing a lot of resident sleepers I'm gonna have to wake you guys up oh no no that
was a bad idea because I'll just pretend I didn't do that I was trying to wake everybody up oh it's
because of the lullaby and here I am thinking I gotta like do something crazy to wake everybody
up and it's the fucking music that's playing and I'm I just added I just ruined the whole
playthrough for myself I thought everyone was like oh shit like this I'm bored and I'm just
like oh yeah fuck it's all right there's gonna be like 40 penalties but it's not real so
okay so what the hell is what do I do then so it's not that one's not this one maybe it's
this one the one that starts in the corner over here this is it that's not it got it 77
snossage all right I got it a sausage it was released when the mouse went over the opening
button of the maze's trap door big subs came you know fuck they did uh cyanide thank you
for the 10 community subs cyanide appreciate that thank you for the 10 community subs much
love to you thank you uh we got the sausage and that means I can get rid of all this
and I can get rid of c4 and 52 mouse is gone desk does not need to be used anymore
c4 and 52 okay all right we've cleaned up the space a little bit now I can take the
the sausage and the dog right so I can take 77 plus 49 that's not gonna do anything though
I have this sausage anything on the sausage sausage and the pill here all right yeah let's bingo
so that's 77 78 79 80 81 82 83 83 83 it's a sausage sleep but the sausage can send anybody
into the arms of Morpheus I don't know what Morpheus is supposed to be but now we have 83
which can be used on the monster right so 83 there's a little doggie door 83 and 7
put it like in front of the door that sounds about right I think that's a good idea so 83
and 7 let's get 90 maybe he'll come through the door there it is sausage on the door
you open the door slightly and carefully throw the sausage in the garden noises of something
being wolfed down can be heard immediately after a few seconds chewing noises are replaced by deep
snores the dog has fallen asleep he will finally be able to get out but no side's voice suddenly
comes from a loudspeaker did you really think it would work so easily and I let you go
like that click clack the door is now locked the evil professor really does not want you
to save the earth take card five 783 783 and v all right take card five this music doesn't
really fit but it's okay five what's the big secret here the door is now locked so there's
no reason to do any of that what which is back into the door is now locked there's just a big
key anything else on the door what the hell am I supposed to do now seeds on the door what's
that going to do a bag of magic seeds that's not going to do anything do I still do something
with this the musical note I can't climb through the doggy door it's not going to work can I do
seeds on but why would that work 19 no sprinkle the seeds in front of the door that's not going
to do anything there's nothing on here nothing did I lose there guys you can't see it but the
doormat in front of the door that's 46 on it I was trying to do something cool and it didn't
work you found a key that's that why do you keep don't keep your key under a rock in the
front of your house that's a really stupid idea I know a lot of you guys do that let me
tell you something that is the equivalent of having your password be password it's been
this shit's been happening for fucking hundreds of years why do people do that
oh where's your key oh I just have the the way to get inside of my house just right in the fucking
front of the door underneath the mat so just leave your door open the whole time criminals
will exploit that don't do that have windows open this time got him I saw I honed in on
the license plate I could see it all right so I got a key key 46 plus this is the goes
obviously into this door oh you'll never escape can I like break into his fucking bank account too
with the one two three four five six which is his idiot like boomer password all right 46
a charming little garden worthy of a house in the suburbs oh would you look at that discard
five and 46 so we got a faucet we've got a dirt and we've got an R here R is the lock
so let's take a look at 56 which is I'm gonna make sure you get a screenshot of that so you
can see what we're doing let's go with the water faucet 56 I'm almost out 56 is the water
faucet oh you guys remember the very beginning of the stream when I saw the card but I thought
was the teacher's aid like teacher's cheat sheet this is the one the water inlet pipes
have fallen down you must find the right ones to get water well it's a machine so I can I'm
gonna use the machine over here all right so let's not hold on don't get too hasty here
don't get too hasty we're still going 58 is just the dirt in the ground there it is
right everybody everybody do it everybody fucking do it I know you're going to so
let's wait like five minutes for you to get it out of your system I know I need a haircut
stop saying it a brown substance granular and slightly damp it's yes it's soil
didn't I need soil I need soil for the seeds okay hold on here this fucking
super Nintendo music I'm not sure if it's keeping people or driving people away
and thank you cyanide for the 10 more community I got it right away thank you for the 10
community sub sign I appreciate it 10 more on top of the ones you gave earlier too thank you
all right um R you need to get in this room contains a weapon of mass destruction
okay inside his shed is like a nuclear bomb of some sort okay so that's it so let's go
ahead and think about this we're going to do the soil and the seeds so that's 58 plus 14
is 58 69 61 62 64 5 6 7 7 7 7 172 tada the seeds are well planted in the nourishing
soil so now we've got seeds in the soil get rid of these two cards now we don't need them anymore
sick okay now we get the we got to do the water here so 50 machine 56 all right so I need to
the water inlet pipes have fallen down you must find the right ones to get water
but how do I which one goes first left find the right ones
once one okay hold on do I press this button and then hit okay no I'm trying but what do
you mean find the right ones I need one I need one two three I need like four of them
or three of them I can't like drag and drop though it's one connection two three maybe three
of them it looks like this one here so it needs to go like down down this one
do I have to press them all okay I'm an idiot all right so it's this one and then we need
like a little snake one so this one and then we need the this one how does that make any
sense we talk about lose one minute yeah because look it goes I need one that goes
down like this so it's this one here right that makes sense that's right there
and then anyone that goes bang bang bang which is bad it's this one here and then one that
goes bang bang straight down it's this one right here how's that wrong yes yes this is it
yes I did it right yes I did it everyone's five it's everyone's like dancing I must have
done it what so two three nine that's nine nine plus 72 wait wait wait it's not even it's not
showing the other side why is it not showing the bottom left hold on a minute this it's
not showing me the whole thing over here so it needs to go down down down down okay okay
I got it I got it so it's because this is not on here that's bullshit so it is this one
and then it goes this one and then it has to go to the other one down there so it's this one
I have no idea what the fuck is going on here because I don't know why it's missing these ones
on this wouldn't it just be all of them except for one because it would be this I don't even I
don't understand why you would even you got all these numbers here what are the numbers for
at least everyone's having a fucking fun time dancing I must be doing something right
all right so then 16 plus 72 because of obviously this 72 88 bingo was it growing
piranha plants massive subs just came in holy god 20 community subs atrox atrox give 20
community subs holy fuck that's thank you that's a lot thank you so much for the 20 subs
that's a lot of subs 56 can go 72 can go I can't wait till if I like Moran kids play this
oh the flowers grow instantly both a magical and beautiful show so what what did that even do
for us is there something wait a minute there's uh the different colors orange purple
orange purple orange purple purple orange what does that mean what is that for it's the musical
notes take a look at this shit look at this look at that three three three one three fuck
never mind there's an extra one three three one three five there's too many one two three four
five six one two three four five six seven eight so where are these this is that one
and this is that one so these two are both six or something son who's what the fuck is happening
right now flutters just gave 30 subs 30 community subs from fluttered 30 20 from match looks 30
from flutters that's a thank you for the huge amount of community subs you guys are way too
generous thank you I was just about to rip this in half but then how would my grandkids ever
be able to finish it that's a lot thank you for the fucking huge amount of subs
and I'm gonna turn the brightness up so you guys can see because it's getting a little darker
outside there we go okay um it's something to do with the notes the musical notes but what
it's really washed out now I got you hold on better no better better better okay we got
these the timer is broken no because I went like this that this this whole this is meaningless
we're just using this for the machine portion all right hidden numbers I don't see anything
on here that's a hidden number I'm gonna have a magnifying glass but when what do I need
to get in this room 98 what's what hold on machine no code fuck two three four
well they're three three three five three three three five is that it did I get it
incorrect are you lacking no I don't think so three three how about three one
three one five well three three three six three three three three one five three one six five
three one six five let's see if that does it god what does this have anything on it
it's five look it's this one this one's purple it's purple it's the purple ones
whatever the purple ones are there's a little purple face on it can you see that
you can't but I trust me it's purple right here it's a little purple guy all right so
then it's three one four five three one five four because those aren't on there three one five
four that's really washed out but it's okay uh the laboratory contains a huge screen showing
a satellite image of the earth towards which a hundred missiles are pointing how can you
stop it yes look at the ceiling take card 36 he has a bunch of missiles pointed at earth
yeah usually in like these saturday morning kids cartoon villains they like
they don't they don't do anything like this usually it's something like
I stole the ice cream maker and now you'll never make ice cream again and no one will ever
be happy or like oh my like rainbow machine is I stole it this guy is trying to destroy
the fucking earth with missiles this doesn't happen okay so get rid of pretty much everything
we got one more really clever puzzle to do to get rid of this one get rid of nine thirty seven
fifty one nine thirty seven fifty one eighty eight fifty one is already gone
now it's not okay that leaves us with this why do I still have the kitchen and shit out here
all right let's get these in the good view here so we got this machine
a cage is hanging by a chain from the ceiling choose the right maneuver to get down push the
lever to the left take card g to do that or push the lever to the right take card d this
might be a death scenario so push the lever to the left or the lever to the right so if
I push the lever to the right that would mean we would be going this way so this way which
would make this purple one go this way which would make you know it's the same amount of
it's the same chance as roulette so I mean just put it on black or red uh I'm gonna
say put it on red we're gonna push it over to the right this way means it'll go this way
which will spin this this way which will move this one this way which will move this one
this way which will move this one this way which will move this one this way and it'll go down
we're taking card d it's to the right d here we go nothing in my hand right
nothing in my hand at all got nothing the cage slowly descends creaking it is closed by a coded
lock hurry to open it and press the button that will stop the destruction of the planet
I think that already happened see I don't know I haven't been outside in like fucking probably
four hours so I might just be in the bunker and the earth is probably gone
hurry to open it and press the button what do you mean how do I hurry up hurry hurry hurry
okay the cage slowly what's what's the code I see okay I see uh dash you see that on the bottom
of the cage there's a dash star dash dash dash star dash star dash dash dash star dash is that
morse code I'll show it to you look these the it's so fine it's hard to see it so one
hurry up and do it before the before the bomb explodes one one three one three one one three
one three one um congrats what do you mean congrats why is everybody saying good job
congrats oh the music okay um I'm like we're getting like gross lips right now the cage
slowly hurry up or the planet will be destroyed dash star dash one three one three
one one three one one one three one one what's that mean one one two three four and two
I don't know read it upside down dash no that doesn't do anything uh code I'm gonna say
all right we got move this out of the way um it's four digits so I don't fucking have any idea
what this the star this is two different numbers one three one three one three one
one four three one one four fucking everyone's dead by this point this cage makes you think
of a code with bars where do we usually find bar codes how the hell does that help me I know
look for the answer on am I really getting that'll be solid right now this is not even
the right box where's the bottom of the box there's a there's the barcode uh it is you
gotta be fucking kidding me it's this barcode on the bottom that's the actual barcode on the
box that I would have never figured that out in a million years I would have gave up I would
have had to quit I would think that I would have just started I would have started flipping
cards over the code is three five eight three what no no no no no no no no the code is
five eight zero six that's that's some metal gear solid shit right there press the button
and no sides evil device stops after releasing a few electrical flashes well done you have saved
the world that's all folks what about these other cards now that was not 112 minutes I
pressed the button a million times 60 minutes of added stuff I would it would have been three
stars I would have been I would have had a nice three stars on this I would have I pressed
the penalty button like 30 times what's with what's with the other cards what should we
reveal these I'm not gonna play this again no no oh these are all damn it like you these
are all you lose cards no yes of course yeah these are all like you failed I didn't see very
many of these so all right that's well that one's done that was uh the sausage one so let
me ask you this uh for this I got two more of these there's a time to transition uh there's
a time to transition to um a little bit of wine or should we put this away this no more
what you didn't let squeak in sausage you didn't like this it was fun I thought it was good
what do you say I can't even see what you're saying what are you saying
what is all right get this shit out of here you scratched your ipad yeah it's fucking broken
I broke it a long time ago I'm gonna all right here's what's gonna happen I'm gonna
this is what you guys here we go now that I know how to play the next one shouldn't be this long
the next one will be a little quicker but hold on we'll see let's put on the brb for a second I'm
gonna put a poll in the chat we'll see if people don't want it you know we could do
something else here's here are your options am I already drunk off wine fumes um no not not
quite hold on I have to like reach over because this fucking fuck you table's in the way
all right okay here's one do something okay ah all right here comes Paul while you do that vote
I'm gonna be back I'm gonna go pee I'll be right back holy shit really I'm surprised 55%
want me to do another one and drink I thought I thought it was gonna be a lot different
he was still I thought I don't know I thought that was like kind of interesting was hopefully
I was just trying to play it just to see I thought people maybe thought it was just
fun to hang out but if you all right add drink to both of them well if I do something else I'm
not gonna drink it I'm not gonna be on camera thank you cyanide for the $50 fuck the poll
play salmon max thank you with the 50 bucks no no no no I've got my fuck you table here
all right I'm gonna I'm gonna if I don't how about this I'm gonna do on the people have spoken
I can't go back on this poll I'm gonna drink and I'm gonna try to beat this I'm gonna do if I
don't if I actually don't do this in an hour then that's it and I'm moving on like I'm gonna
if I do not beat this within the timer that's it and we have to move on I'm gonna go I'm
really gonna try get really drunk and then gamble with Mario I'm not gonna get that drunk
all right let me grab let me grab something to drink that was a little trial run I know
what I'm doing now I think what do we think dinosaur or Wild West plus I did the tutorial
was like 20 minutes for that I had no idea what the hell I was doing Wild West or dinosaurs
I'm gonna say dinosaur this one apparently is hard this is the hardest one that I have
so I gotta fucking get this shit done in exactly one hour and for every penalty I have
to drink I'm just kidding I'm not doing that is this one ages 12 and up this one is is
still 10 and up all right I'm not gonna reveal the deck yet and hold on you know what I'm gonna
make this faster I'm gonna make this quick hold on all right let me go let me go let me get
hold on let me go get a drink let's get started here and I'm gonna I'm gonna blow you all away
I'll be right back all right I got something a little different here this is not uh this is
not the usual wine unfortunately guys I'm sorry to say I got something else Kim was Kim was
telling me what are you doing where you going with that I was like no I'm not going anywhere
hold on I've got uh some sake and my company is out of fucking business shot glass look at
that and my liquidated company shot glass rip machinima you're drinking liquid evil
why do you say that to drink with every card poll I am not gonna fucking do that
pull for which deck all right that's the hour you know if this is gonna be the one
this is the one then this uh that's a good idea we'll pull with the dinosaurs or wild
wild west I am already messing up my words this is the reason why anybody voted for this
hey you want to do another fucking card game no no no anything but that do anything else
I don't want to see this again hey I'm gonna be drinking okay all right that sounds great do
that all right let's do uh dinosaur or wild west you all right give me another poll because
that makes sense we should do it like that you only do boring shit drunk would you rather
I do exciting shit drunk no I I make this what what can I do exciting well what can I play
right now that's exciting drunk we I might just transition to it whatever it is I got one hour
all right guys which one do you want to see which deck this is important this is the last
time you're gonna see this you should play just dance um why would I ever turn that game on
why would I I don't want this to be biased hold on there you go for our entertainment
oh but for those of you that I've got some news for everybody here
this is people are gonna like this there's something that I told you about that I was
working on that is gonna happen now probably got a good lead there is a very interesting
stream coming up here in the next I don't know I actually got like a good lead on it
you'll see talked about it a few times and it's gonna be more elaborate than I think you think
I don't I think people think this is gonna be a little one and done little thing but just
just wait there could be way more on top of this dino it is we're gonna unlock the dino deck
and just because I wanted to be completely prepared for this I am completely prepared
for this I've got super Mario dinosaur music and I'm not going to waste any fucking time
so here comes dinosaur music I think it should be at least I've got my uh my sake
I've got my fucking liquidated company glass what the fuck unbelievable all right here we go
survival guide this should not read this professor challenger very different like
dinosaurs in here okay that might is this a guide that might be like an answer guide
I'm not gonna look these are all the uh floors something like that I literally bought you
four bottles of wine for you to drink my drink I'll replace it I will I'm gonna replace
I'll replace it twice how does that sound pretty good deal I'm gonna pay it back in with
interest I'm gonna get you two of these with interest oh you can have it back never mind
this is disgusting I'm fucking kidding let's see but you gotta get a good view of this
I'm gonna spill this by the way don't drink unless you're fucking up by the right correct
age to be able to do it and enjoy it and be responsible when you drink go get a card game
and play it with some friends and shit I don't know don't be an idiot I've never even had
sake before what does it taste like does it taste like beer I only drink like Bud Light I
don't everything else is disgusting to me no this I don't know I don't know what this is I don't
like it I don't know what it is I don't like it it's pretty smooth pretty smooth tastes like um
um like the inside of a plastic bag with a hint of uh burnt mango something like that all
right are we ready I don't need to do the tutorial but keep the box though in case you
want to sit for 20 fucking minutes on a puzzle and not know what to do here we go
sealed what's all up my hands sealed in the package I didn't open this beforehand
I just everyone's like well what if he knows the puzzles before take a look you look
I didn't reseal this opening the seal on camera opening the seal on camera so you know okay so
the first thing I'm going to do here is I'm going to draw overdraw don't need the tutorial
I already know how to do this got it tutorial done are we ready yeah it's the same thing
it's office with the wire remember I also need to move this camera because it's in a stupid dumb
idiot place and it's going to be a problem for me so that's that's better what do you mean I'm
cheating is this your fucking card all right get this out of the way I'm ready to start
you guys can't read this but don't worry I'll read it to you okay get excited for
this one because this one is going to be top notch here we go no more fucking around
expedition challenger is this one we're doing here we are new theme it is a new theme um don't
fuck this up here we go ready I'm gonna beat this in 60 60 minutes sort the cards are we talking
about good idea very good idea they are they're already sorted there's no um there's no
letters it's already sorted a fucking million of these okay you ready a young woman knocks
at the door of your agency your private investigating agency sort by number that's
you know how long that's gonna take to do that I have to I'm not you want me to put every
single one of these in order we that would take like fucking 30 minutes what do you mean do it
no I'm not gonna sort it no I can't that's the part of the game that's I have to go
one I have to go one to a hundred I'm gonna throw I'm gonna I'm gonna fucking throw
them if you keep this up don't fuck with me I'll do it I'm just gonna whip them to the
back of my door don't do it don't make me do that I'm fucking gonna do it I see it if I see
one more of these you won't do it no I won't you're right that person thanks for saving the
stream all right here we go my name is Gladys Ungerton my friend Ned Malone has gone missing
you've probably heard about him he's one of the members of Professor Challenger's expedition
they recently returned from the lost valley full of strange creatures
I just received this notebook and this odd message and I don't understand a word of any of it can you
please go to the offices of Professor Challenger if you are true to your reputation you will
bring Ned back to me should you accept to help Gladys take the survival guide and card 53
I need that thing what did I throw it okay I need 53 and then launch the app and hit start
and then flip this card over when you start it so I need card 53 don't start that you don't
start the timer yet by the way if I do this in one hour and I actually get to the end in one
hour I want five thousand subs if I don't get to the end in an hour I want negative five
thousand subs so just kill my whole channel 53 I'm going all in on this one my big bits
came in cyanide another 50 dollars do it coward what do you think I'm doing okay I got my
survival guide I've got my 53 I'm not taking I'm just getting I'm getting it ready so don't
waste any time how many pauses am I allowed go if I get uh there a desk if we get a desk I got
a uh little light 53 53 okay I got a rock of I don't know what that means okay 36 36
15 36 8 42 15 36 8 42 15 36 8 42 15 36 8 42 13 38 42 48 4 42 45 45 36 38 38 35
15 42 31 35 585 379 892 15 1 2 3 4 5 4 2 3 2 15 15 15 they can get a uh 36 over here
this is what you do this is what you do 36 42 2 36 46 18 99 and 95 5 26 32 32
24 13 28 29 29
24 36 39 29 40 42 36 42 42 42
cane candle okay cane cane candle 15 was a painting painting painting
a book 1588 is inside the cupboard there is a book it's right here that's the book I need
to get into uh an edition of Alice in Wonderland it's impossible to open the book
as long as it bears this combination padlock so there's a combination padlock on it's going
to get a uh F and a C on it and one of them is cold F and C to 36 down here this is a
candle a candle and we got uh 42 is down above here it's a high quality shoe horn
okay so we got uh let's take a look at it we see if there's any hidden numbers here
nothing on there hidden numbers anything hydrate okay and they know the candle this
has a new book okay it's a code it's a padlock F and C Fahrenheit and Celsius
Fahrenheit and Celsius Fahrenheit Celsius cold uh thought and cold hot and cold cold C cold
survival guy cold C Celsius I think I'm stupid Fahrenheit Celsius three lines 15 and 10
50 10 code 50 10 ah it's 50 and 10 on
why what is it what's that mean 50 and 10 10 and 50 no it's Fahrenheit 1050
no no no no it's not 1050 it would be it would be no it's 50 10 I don't want to
lose any more time five fucking thousand subs around the line oh my god I just lost
fucking 10 whole minutes what's the wiggly line what's this painting 14 14 14 14 I'm
fucking doing I'm trying so hard 14 I can see 14 in the corner for the painting 16 80 99 25
give me who is fucking 14 what it's a uh a coconut behind the painting you find a strange
coconut coconut smash the coconut with it with the with the horn 42 okay a high quality shoe
horn smashed the coconut 42 plus 14 is 42 52 56 it's right on top 56 is right on top
smash the coconut I am so fucking I'm on top of this right now I ain't gonna lose
I need to discard pile up here the coconut opens in the middle it holds a mysterious machine
latitude longitude what is that 56 machine 56 enter destination latitude no longitude no
I need a map a map that's uh I need latitude and longitude all right I gotta get a map I gotta
find a map okay okay got a candle this painting still okay I don't I don't have it I got
nothing for that what how do I get in this fucking book was it supposed to 36 15 thought
of getting a fucking book f and c f I don't know how to get in the book I don't know what this
even means I know it's Fahrenheit and Celsius but there's nothing no other information on
this book to give me any leads I it's like not 50 and 10 so what the hell is it Fahrenheit
Celsius I got no longitude I got no latitude I've got a painting but there's nothing on that
painting I got this weird scissors rock paper scissors lemons can I burn these two oh 50 60
70 80 86 87 89 burn the burn it now come on come on 89 89 89 89 89 89 80 88 87 89 what 36
all right what the fuck after just okay discard 36 and 53 get rid of these I just didn't okay
discard what the fuck does this even say woods in the form of our voyage and a few of natural
history and g-toe could of interest to the general public help enter both latitude and
longitude rates by teleporter to our the five of us we are in great danger ned each coordinate
is made of a car followed by two I will nobody can read that each there's more of this I'll
help you with the it is for minute uh each coordinate is made of a car followed by two
I will help you with the it is the four minutes and look on the lower right side for the other
row beat the and enter challengers initials lower right side of what of the car look on
the lower right side of the car I have to get into this book Fahrenheit Celsius it's 50 and
then this is 10 but then there's that weird little symbol that's flying around what is
that symbol is there like a squiggly latitude no that's not it it's his initials and then
something I'd have no idea enter both latitude and longitude rates be teleported to our
the five of us we are in great danger hey what the rock n rock e scissor w paper
fuck does this even mean dot dot dash dot dash dot dash dot is it f and c on here
yeah but that's just morse code but how but that I need to translate that into four digits
50 10 I tried 50 10 earlier it didn't do anything this is fucking bogus this painting
is Japanese but what I don't have that information in my book how the fuck you
supposed to do this in 60 seconds I mean very clearly f and c are right here why would it be
f and c with that the the squiggles around it these are just the dinosaurs as in there's no
squiggly lines you see squiggly lines on here I don't it seems g e challenger is his initials
so it's g e 50 10 wait there was there was squiggly where were that where were we talking
about where what are you talking about what do you see them I don't see them what I mean
right there where do you see these no you're lying to me there's nothing here I'm I there's
nothing on this map that has squiggly lines on it I can't even get the fuck out of this first puzzle
wait wait wait wait is there f and c here g e but then I need the longitude and latitude
but it's a rock and paper scissor f c but is the the wave the is this the wave the painting
14 c is 14 no what the fuck there's no and no there's no lettered cards c is in blue is
for celsius f is for fahrenheit so what the fuck are you talking about game
f is clearly on 50 c is very clearly on 10 50 10 how does this make no sense I tried that already
g e 50 10 on this on this dumb machine no but this is like latitude latitude north
look scissors this doesn't make any sense this makes no sense
you I've rock paper scissor and then 50 and 10 is this like element shit
rock is north but what is rock sees north rock east scissor no fucking idea like like zero
idea what the hell they want me to do there's no way I'm gonna do this I'm gonna okay minus
five fucking thousand subs this is the it's not possible what the fuck are you talking
about okay let me tell you how dumb this is okay the apparently the red number is for
boiling temperature why would I ever ever ever ever ever think that how would I what information
is here boiling temperature what I'm gonna boil the card so it's two oh but boiling in
fahrenheit is was what two two twelve so two twelve and then the celsius is just what for
freezing which is zero two one two zero what a dumb fucking thing well yeah by the way that
means it's boiling now if you didn't catch that this game owes me five thousand subs
it's not over five take the card five padlock opens five a number is at the bottom of the
book page oh there's a really there is yep thank you for that I just I didn't I didn't
press that it scared me okay there we go 36 minutes I can do it discard how am I supposed
to read the book is open it's a it's it says 34 and there's a I'm not supposed to read that
okay it's a bunny and a lady 34 come on come on please I'm fighting for my life here 34
look at how do you see how much text is on this this volume holds in the form of a diary
the account of our voyage and a few short remarks about natural history in geology
that I believe could be of interest to the general public we needed to study the lands
and follow the right coordinates left behind by the previous explorer so to confirm whether or
not there was a hidden valley in which huge animals hid and needed to be saved from the
desert people who killed them out of fear we also wanted to check on the coordinate pointing
to a bird called the red cardinal presumably living on the highest point we were missing
several of the digits and therefore we couldn't find the latitude we went as far this is a joke
the text gets smaller they couldn't fit it so they shrunk it we had planned to we went as
far as we could to the south we had planned to stay but after a few seconds we were attacked
by a very big dinosaur and chased by an even bigger rabbit there's like lines going through
this l c d g the line is what disaster there's clearly a line here going through
they're supposed to do this in an hour no way more like two or three i have to read
this whole essay again hold on does this even mean cardinals check on the coordinate
pointing to a bird the red cardinal i want to see a dinosaur i got no fucking idea
bird called the red cardinal presumably living on the highest point we were missing several of
the digits and therefore we couldn't find the latitude we went as far as we could to the south
we had planned to stay but after a few seconds we were attacked by a dinosaur
camp i'm gonna smash the table this is like so convoluted i need magnifying glasses to read
this camp for stream central lake there's no bird on here rapid and a lady none of this
makes any sense to me just give me a hint i don't i don't even understand the rabbit has a strange
posture what is it playing at what is supposed to be like a constellation rock he's doing rock
but but who cares he's doing rock north rabbit north north rock north is she doing paper
north but what does the rabbit even mean is it like a rabbit up north a rabbit named anything
i don't even have this still up here have i tried solving the puzzle i'm returning this one this
one doesn't count no this one don't count it's like it's like you got to find like this one
little thing how did you not know that the f was talking about boiling water you're supposed
to know that the rabbit was pointing to a rock which was the cardinal which the cardinal
oh give me a break but i dude your driving exam your driver's ed exam has text bigger than this
when you put your eyes in the fucking microscope thing when you do like the test to see if you
need glasses for like the driving exam they're bigger than this so thankfully i don't need
glasses to operate a car we went as far south as we i rock north rabbit i don't know rabbit
north rock but what is rock rock is rock on here coconut painting doesn't do anything
they've hidden numbers 34 we already have 34 34 anything on the cardinal how is this ages 10
plus no no you got helped by like four adults you're not doing this at 10 plus you can't even
fucking read at 10 you can't read at 10 years old age is 10 enough no that's like
the fucking esrb rating there's no blood in this game no idea i'm just give me the
fucking solution i'm done i have the solution here i don't care uh this makes no sense
okay so it's here's listen to me okay it's north it's the page it's the pages in the book
that are the no no one would why would you ever that's not even like it's bullshit
uh and you know it you all know it i don't need i don't have to say anything you know it
it's the page is the page is the latitude not like any of this other it doesn't matter
i got a lot on the line here four and where's 89 already over there now what this okay this
just changed this is now uh very important apparently you have been you've been teleported
to challenger's base camp in the lost valley you must find ned to obtain a better score you
will have the opportunity to find and save the other members of the expedition their health
deteriorates every night use the app to indicate your movements and take the shown cards to
reconstitute the map to interact with a card with an anchor you must be on its space
the other objects are transported with you good luck and be careful now take card 81 it's
the first part of the map 81 the air is humid and stuffy so we got the tent and then the ground
so 93 45 did i go by 93 already am i is the timer still on 93 and 45 you got an empty bottle
and a used chalk stick day one okay chalk and bottle i'm i'm gonna any hidden numbers like
buried in the back of the tent i don't think so uh we're gonna go left you come to a mangrove
take the card 87 we're gonna get like that timer erupt 88 90 75 27 87 okay there's a
there's a pterodactyl here uh let's uh four i guess we're gonna see what the pterodactyl
does can we tame the pterodactyl this strange creature is playing with a rope
empty bottle and rope there's also an anchor though what's the anchor mean again
you must be on its space okay you have to be i have to be on the anchor space to use that
so i have to be here can i do rope and bottle what would that what would that even do
well let's do 26 a torch chalk bottle torch pterodactyl uh the torch is not
i don't think i can do anything about this day two a vast lowland is laying in front you take 52
okay there's a buck a huge deer stands in this lowland it looks peaceful 40 a huge rock
okay we got a huge rock torch bottle can i light the rock on fire i don't think so torch on
rock chalk on rock chalk on rock mark the rock let's go right swampy you're moving slowly in
a swamp 82 84 13 28 come on 82 82 i'm running out of room here 82 that is a huge animal's
trudge in the marsh we need seven and 21 i'm gonna have to fucking knock the table over and
just do it on the ground use rock on self like smash the rock into my own head i don't think
that's a good idea seven there it is a boot a lightly laced shoe okay shoe look at the swamp
water 21 what does that mean 20 21 23 19 31 21 there's a gun in here uh roxton's rifle his
name is engraved on the butt okay i got a gun machine 21 use gun how many bolts
i have two bullets left um hot god damn it there's only two bullets left look closely at the swamp
hold on 94 94 oh i found him leaning against a tree rockston speaks incoherently you must find
a way to lower his body temperature or he will die uh torch on rockston get the torch out
rock his body temp all right hold on he okay he's here we need a torch a bottle of warm
sake okay i got torch shoe uh let's go over here you retrace your steps that's a forest
okay wait what happened night is coming you make a makeshift camp wait wait wait he's right
there he's right there i found him so he these are the people that are alive still
i don't know what that person is there he's okay day two um all right i shoot the pterodactyl with
a gun shore of a huge lake it's impossible to cross it 10 lake bottle of water i'm going
to try to scoop up some water i think this huge lake goes all the way down to a dangerous
rapid and then this 32 there's so many fucking cards here you need like 10 people to play
this game to keep track of this shit i i'm going at unfair odds here so there's a paddle
over on that clearing so i've got a large lake maybe a boat that's nothing down here
there's nothing over here either i gotta go up no what i know that i know the ground is
shaking under your feet you hear an immense din 29 i'm just like picking up items i'm
doing these things a huge geyser periodically blasts hot boiling water okay boiling water
into the bottle and then like dump it on the guy so we get 28 or to make him drink it
28 bang a narrow fissure okay this is a machine so 28 so what what is it what about
well wait how is this a machine what is this supposed what am i doing here what does that
mean is that morse code if that's morse code then that's ridiculous 51 you're on a huge cliff
the faces of this cliff are too steep to be climbed up and there's something on 13
oh my god this is so i i'm so overwhelmed right now i have no fucking idea 13
a cave at the foot of a cliff so this cave i can go in torch in cave 26 plus 13 let's do it
26 and 13 26 36 39 let's go no i can't even press the penalty button there is no penalty
so uh no torch in cave unfortunately graveyard 97 no penalty just disappointment yeah uh i'm like
this i need this more cards out than i have room on my table uh give me 20 dollars just
gave a hundred dollars well you gave me a hundred dollars so it was apparently it's it's give me a
hundred dollars uh thank you for the hundred bucks if you stream layers of fear 2 please
bring back the orson wells sub sound uh well thank you give me 20 dollars for the hundred
dollars and uh i don't know if i could ever bring that sound back because that's all you
would hear the whole string he wants you to give him 20 dollars well i i can't speaking
of can't i'm about to drag my hand across this i've not no i don't have enough room for this
16 how long have been streaming for almost four hours why does it feel like 10 minutes
16 hold on hold on just give me a second a small claw seven there's too many cards
do you do i have a bowling alley or do i have like a desk like you can't couldn't
you just do this whole game in the app why do i need the deck of cards for i'm slowly coming
to this realization here recent chalk look at this this is a three star dip 10 years old
give me a fucking break a 10 year old is gonna do this 10 10 the skull of a strange creature
that's 19 unlock would like to access the microphone why do you want to access my
microphone hello hello hello hello hello hello hello hello hello 19 hello is anybody listening
to me why did i just give that permission to my microphone this is the skull of a
blow into the horn to communicate where is the mic on the ipad
i'm gonna pass out if i keep doing that approach your mouth to the mic of your device
and then blow into it where's the mic i don't know what the microphone is you hear heavy steps
getting closer it's the t-rex you'd be better off not provoking it for the time being
what was the point of that all right i have so many items let me just i thought that was a
siren like the cops were here i'm people are dying i have a look at my items all right you
suddenly wake up alarmed by raptors groans hurry you must flee from them the raptors
surround you are two five six are three oh that's incorrect what should i take the gun
the gunshot scares the raptors they run away you can resume your adventure i have one bullet
left but hold on ore chop knife um rock smash the rock with the ore step on the rock with
the boot put the ore in the fissure put the torch up the rock put the rock inside of the
fissure uh the rope the pterodactyl has a rope burn the rope the pterodactyl is holding and
he'll explode it'll be like a explosion um there's like hylogryphics here i take the tooth
take the put the boot onto the tooth but the all right it was morse code i can't believe it
get to the fissure where's that fissure 28 dang dang dang s o s there's somebody inside this
fissure but how do i get in there how do we get that there's somebody in there i need the
rope from the pterodactyl but how do i get that shoot the pterodactyl four here's the
pterodactyl throw hit him with the ore i still have to still shoot over here that i can't see
all right well this guy appears dead no dense forest i can't even go over to these
nothing why haven't have them on the map i gotta get the rope from the pterodactyl he's very close
when you wake you discover a dumbfounded that you have set up your camp next to a nest of
triceratops what can you do to pass unnoticed unlock would like to access speech recognition
speech data from this apple be sent to apple to process your requests this will also help
apple improve its speech technology useful for some riddles hey get out of the way you stupid
get out of my way hey oh oh do i really have to scream into this you slip through silently
and resume your adventure i was supposed to be quiet how do i get the rope from the pterodactyl
this is the ultimate expedition here glass boot boot on bottle on the tooth
what about 45 and 16 i feel like i'm going coupon hunting with you guys can i put the
tooth in the bottle boot on head is there a spongebob song playing in the background oops
shoe on head how much time do i have left chalk let me look at the chalk wait there's
maybe a number on the chalk hold on a u small chalk stick this is the worst scream of 2019
what's happening what what's going on what is why do i hear like screaming
why am i getting chased there's nothing here
what i don't know what card this is that's freaking morty who's
brick i'm not putting that back on i thought this is gonna be fun it kind of is but like
it's not i'll be honest i'm trying you know i'm trying it's it's i'm trying what do i do
uh okay um what the fuck am i supposed to do
okay i've got chalk i've got a gun i've got a paddle i've got a fissure i got an sls
i've got a cave i've got a pterodactyl with a snake in his mouth i've got um the horn
i've got my pamphlet i've got uh the boot i'm gonna shoot the pterodactyl shoot the deer
can i shoot the deer so there's a deer here it's 52 all right shoot deer i hope you're right
the deer runs runs away it comes back a few minutes later i don't have any bullets left
fuck okay um i need that rope i need him i have to feed this creature i need to feed
i need to feed the pterodactyl to get the rope from the pterodactyl i don't have any food
i can't get any food i just tried to get food by shooting the deer but the deer
wouldn't die paddle in the you think you heard a noise under the rock find a means to lift it
why would i ever do this though like the paddle and the rock it's just such an obscure
thing to do this card does not emanate a noise there's no sound on this card i can't
fucking hear anything why would there be a noise here that just said you heard a sound
from under the card i did the hint on this card why would i hear a sound from under here
why would i ever think to do the oar in the rock unless i did that hint 72 let's see if
there's somebody under the rock the huge rock wobbles and gives you access to a cave
progress let's go go in the cave 72 but how do i you how do i use the torch in the cave
26 and 72 98 like how do i can't how do i use the torch did the timer run out not yet
timer's still going sparkles could help you light the torch i don't i don't have
the torch lit so i can't go in here that was for nothing i need sparks didn't have a candle is
that gone what about the claw 26 and 16 can i like let's try that 36 42 let's see it let's
see if i can get some sparks there's no 42 wait 26 36 37 38 39 40 41 42 it's 42 there's no 42
i have to see this to the end torch on the boot like like tom and jerry style like a cartoon
i don't have the gun is empty what what did this what did the horn even do the horn didn't
do anything huge lake 45 and 10 maybe to get some water from the lake 45 and 10 55 let's
see let's see here we go bottle is filled with water now get rid of 45 all right i get
a bottle of water now so now i'm gonna give the bottle of water to this guy
rockston speaks you must find a way to lower his body temperature he's gonna die
give him the water how the hell do i bring this guy the water this this how do i do that
hydrate okay good call oh by the way people that are freaking out right now uh just be
aware the uh sake is a very low alcohol content so it's not it's like a little bit
it's like a little bit higher than wine it's not like drinking like shots of
straight liquor so don't worry it's essentially wine so it's not that much alcohol pretty nice
liquidated company um it's hitting me now not not this this i ain't done i'm gonna see this
shit to the end because this was like 50 bucks for all of these and i'm gonna do it and then
me and kim are gonna play the fucking wild west one on our own don't fucking blow it now
i'm almost done and then if i long as i beat this within the timer i get five thousand fucking
chops all right dinosaur how do i get the fucking thing out of his mouth have we got any ideas
i got a full bottle of water now sos i need the rope to get in there i need meat i don't
know i have no i don't know what to do i'm gonna uh boot and claw what's the boot for
i'm gonna throw the boot i'm throwing the boot at the fucking pterodactyl seven and four
eleven i'm throwing the boot at the pterodactyl now if this is if this works and it's a boot
and it's made of leather and the pterodactyl eats it then this is the worst game ever made
let's find out thank god i still have this cave down here but i can't that doesn't do
anything i need to light this i need to climb this i'm taking a hint uh a hint for 55
hint north 55 nothing to report why would they give me a like a north what are you talking
about 93 give me the chalk hint nah north 93 nothing to report nothing 16 this claw could
serve as a hook but you need to align to attach to it i need that fucking rope i need sparks i
need to get the rope i can't get the rope i don't i don't i seven what about the boot
only the laces could be useful to you would you what would you untie them what would you tie
them to um cliff seven and 51 58 16 and maybe the claw claw claw 16 17
23 oh you got loud tapeworm this tapeworm is primitive but it will do okay i've got a fishing
line i'm going to fish into the 2351 or fish in the lake 23 and 10 is the lake 33 33 33 that's
how old i am not for long though i got a fish 33 and four we got to be on when was to play by
the rules i gotta be on that card 33 and four is 37 oops the pterodactyl grabs the fish and
let's go the rope all right i got the rope the rope now um goes into the um the cliff
37 and 51 50 67 80 88 i'm almost done 88 at the top of the cliff you find a stone slab
arrows have been drawn with chalk sticks get rid of 37 get rid of the rope i have no idea
what the fuck this is i don't know what any of this means at the uh so this blue
pointing up red white green green this is not a children's card game somebody said i'm going
insane figuring like a children's card game it's not a children's card game this 10 plus
bullshit is not real hand that to a kid and you say go ahead figure it out little tim
he's gonna go i don't know what to say i like baseball t-ball they play t-ball
a 10 not this shit this doesn't help me at all green and this there's like a what the
fuck does this even mean i'm getting hit i don't care only one of these colors will be useful
but which one red white green orange or blue um challenger used a white chalk stick to help
you follow the color arrows they form a symbol then pair it with the inscriptions in the
desert are you 10 10 they make a symbol let's say say that shit again follow the color arrows
they form a symbol then pair okay so so it's like a it's like this there there there
dun dun dun dun dun dun dun was a symbol guide diagonal line and then it's like there
there there 75 what it's this one it's this one right here that one so what is that what the
fuck does that matter it's this one right here but what does that even matter can you see it so
what so what what does that even mean what i know what symbol it is but what does that even
who cares four rows with nine white symbols which one to choose on each row oh i got it
this is fucking ridiculous okay i got the code i got it i got it i got the code the code is three
oh one two three four five six one two three four five six seven one two three i'm not the
right place where's the hieroglyphics i don't i don't remember where they are up here where was
the hieroglyphics where were they i got the i got the code right here where were they which
one oh oh shit the cops he's dead who cares one two three six seven four the stone shows you a
path in the desert take card 31 i wasn't looking at the camera i was looking somewhere else
discard at 75 i still i got the i still got the timer 75 88 93 bringing up some space
take 31 the village of the desert people 76 and anything on here 76 and 90
76 is the boat hey what do you know i got an ore no i don't an old pierogi okay and uh 90
where's 90 these bowls contain various plants it's a machine 90 is you get that when when do
we get to the fun we don't sorry i have to finish it though 90 you have to have to cook
why would i cook what do i have any information of what this what like recipe this is um let's go
down from here the bridge that crosses this has been destroyed you cross the lake by pierogi
oh oh which which way do i go oh come on what what am i supposed to how do i figure this
out what's the what's the game here to oh man i should go to a casino you finish crossing the
river rapids you arrive on some devastated lowland a violent battle between the desert
and the jungle people occurred here you can freely cross the lake now take card 79 get
rid of 57 i will wherever the hell that is where's 57 i don't i have no idea i'm not even
sure it's still on here 57 did we see it i don't see it i don't see 57 oh well take card 79
a merciless battle occurred here and somebody there 25 get rid of 57 and 86 it was 86
i don't know 25 uh this should be talking to a person got you you find a man on the
battlefield he is alive but exhausted i am zombo he whispers all right i am zombo give him some
water 55 and 25 80 do i got 80 yeah drinks like salt water 80 zombo regains his strength
appreciative of the help he gives you this map 25 55 save zombo at least i got one that means
i win 55 as well and then zombo give me a map and there is a map like that in here i
think from the campsite i remember seeing those three tents where are they am i wrong go straight
then make a left and make a right go path to the town going crossing the forest straight left
right like straight left straight left right straight left right through the forest can i go
down here's the forest 38 easy to get lost in this jungle 38 that's two dead zombo's alive
save zombo so i need machine 38 straight straight left right right straight left right straight left
right straight straight straight left right straight left right right straight left right
right straight straight left right right straight left right right left left right
64 i'm almost done in front of the palisade of the jungle 64 it's the it's the drums
what would that be is this morse code two that's too many that's too many that's
many things three five one three one five four three five one four sorry i got around three
five one four take the car 99 a young jungle man opens the door and runs away when he sees
you you enter the deserted town 99 found him you find ned tied up and you release him
but dozens of jungle people appear suddenly they surround you and any ski escape seems
impossible how do you get away from them just gotta reload the fucking thing i just gotta reload
it the gunshot take the jungle people back but it's not enough to get you out of the
situation you need a greater threat i don't have a greater threat um um night the medicine
i don't know 19 oh god
oh come on the ground shakes under the t-rex's steps that is charging at us
the jungle men run away when they see it you seize the opportunity to make your escape and
back to london with the survivors i did it in less than 60 seconds less than 60 minutes
three stars only 16 hints and seven gunshots 60 minutes less than 60 minutes that's a five
thousand fucking sub congratulations see look 60 minute oh it's like it's bad it's backwards
that's a bug or something 60 cheater that's pretty quick that's a six six zero
wait wait wait wait wait turn turn it up turn it upside down turn it your
i didn't tell you if it was going to be right side up or upside down i just said it was going
to be 60 i was going to stick sick in 60 minutes that that could be upside down or that could be
right side up i didn't specify that i just this is six and a zero here i mean i mean
you win when you win you have to just you know you win three stars that was painful who
wants to see the other one no i'm kidding play just i don't have just dance on why would
i do that right now all right that was like look it's something different you know that's
something different i tried something different try to do i what was the medicine even for i don't
know no i'm not going to do the wild west one i want to do that with kim me and kim
i'm gonna do that i'm gonna replace her sake i'm not i'm not done streaming
i don't know maybe we'll just hang out i still got sake to drink well that was the unlock
adventure um some of you guys liked it it's cool you can play with your friends you can play as
long as they're 10 years old you'll be able to have a group of people hanging out just drink
from the bottle that's what am i a fucking barbarian um i got my table in the way here
i can't what am i what can i do what is what is going to do on this table there's
got to be something else i can do i'm still in the just chatting section so like what who
cares what can we do that's not gonna work the knife game i hit it already arts and crafts now
i wish i did some magic tricks i actually do know a couple magic tricks but they wouldn't
work on camera here because you're too high up there let me let me move this shit out of the
way let me like get back in front of the camera we'll hang out and do some some stuff
talk to transformer yeah that sounds fun let me get this fuck you table out of the way
and we'll talk to transformer give me uh like a couple let me that's gonna
move some stuff out of the way i'll be right back