Hey what's up everybody, it's Germa here with the answers portion of my Q&A.
Before I get into this, I want to just say that the background of all this is going to be the TF2 super crazy fun time event that I had last week at some point.
I think it was like three or four days ago. We did like Scout on Scout Melee only. We did Demoman only Demo Night versus Pyro.
We did a bunch of crazy, crazy crap so hopefully you'll enjoy it and it's kind of funny.
I couldn't really do a gameplay commentary on it because obviously it's just a bunch of like insanity so there's no way I could have done a gameplay commentary.
So I'm going to let it go in the background and if you want to pay attention to that, that's cool.
If you want to listen to my voice, that's cool too.
So here we go, time to answer your questions.
I'm going to start off with the basic questions first. A lot of people ask these so I'm just going to get right into it.
How old are you? I'm actually kind of old. I don't look that old but I'm a lot older than you might think.
I'm 25 years old so if some of you thought I was like 19 or 18 or something, you were so wrong.
I'm 25.
Where do you live? I think I've answered this before but just for the sake of it.
Boston, I live in Boston, not New Jersey, not New York. Boston.
What do you do for work?
This is kind of a difficult question because I do a few things.
For most of my money, I am a freelance videographer.
I have a big expensive HD camera and that's what I film.
I film weddings, I film events, promos, music videos. I do a lot of crap.
So that's kind of what I do for money.
And I used to before, recently, maybe like two or three months ago, I kind of stopped doing it.
But I was a substitute teacher at a middle school.
So there you go, that's what I do for work.
How did you meet Leptor?
Leptor, I met him by, I asked him a question.
I sent him a message because I was getting kind of big.
When I say kind of big, I mean like I was at like six or seven hundred subscribers.
And I was just looking for advice because the channel was growing so fast and so rapidly that
I was looking for somebody that had a big channel.
What to do about all the people and how to go about growing even more.
So I sent Leptor a message. I sent IRSnipeR.
I sent Shibya a message. I tried to talk to Star.
And I got a few replies back. I got one from Leptor.
Leptor most notably because Leptor said,
Hey, why don't you go on my channel? Your stuff is great.
I will put you on my channel because I like you.
And I said, well, you know what? I like you too.
So that's how we kind of became buddies.
And we, to this day now, we're still good internet buddies.
The next question is not really a question, but it's more of a request.
And it was from Leptor, actually, who we just talked about.
So I'm going to take his request into consideration.
And for the next two questions, I am going to fulfill Leptor's request.
If you knew what it was, then cool. If you don't, well, I'm sure you're going to find out.
Why don't you use the fast switch on TF2?
Oh, listen, okay, let me tell you something.
Fast switch on TF2, it's just a little hard. It's hard to do it.
You know, I can't do quick switching. It screws with my brain, you know.
It really, you know, makes me look like an idiot, you know what I'm talking about.
It makes me crazy. You know, it makes me a stupid fucking idiot
whenever I try to upload a video.
I'm getting tired of this. I'm getting tired of fucking doing this every day.
I didn't even answer the question. So anyways.
Why don't you use fast switch on TF2?
Fast switch on TF2, it's because whenever I hit one,
I'm always accidentally hitting buttons in this game.
So if I accidentally hit a button, it's going to switch my weapon.
So I like to accidentally hit a button and see, no shit, I didn't want to do that and go right back.
So that's why I don't use quick switch.
The next question is, what would you do for a Klondike bar?
I got this a lot. Too many people were asking about Klondike bars,
which, you know, Klondike bars suck.
I'd rather eat the heavy sandwich, to be honest, because he's a fat fuck.
You know what I'm talking about.
But anyways, I don't think I want to eat a Klondike bar because Klondike bars kind of suck.
They kind of, you know, they taste kind of like dog crap.
You know what I'm talking about? I'm not going to eat it.
No, I would not do anything for a Klondike bar because I don't really like Klondike bars.
They're too messy.
I mean, if that's your goal, if that's your goal in life is to be a pawn star.
I've been watching too much A&E lately, sorry.
A pawn star, if you think you can pull it off, then once you get old enough, I guess go for it.
And absolutely, brother, bring it on.
You bring the knives, I'll bring the beer.
Even though I don't really drink beer.
I know some classes and loadouts can be more useful depending on the map, but which is the most fun?
In my opinion, the most fun thing to play in Team Fortress 2 is a Huntsman Sniper.
Huntsman Sniper with the Jurati and the Bushwhacker, I think, is the most entertaining thing to play.
Because it's a lot of fun just aiming at people, shooting arrows, pretending like you're in Lord of the Rings and stuff like that.
It's just a really fun, interesting setup, so that's probably the most fun class to play.
Soon, soon.
When I say soon, that could mean like a couple months from now, but I'm going to try as hard as I can to get that sooner.
Me and Leptor were actually talking about buying a dedicated server together and splitting it,
so there might be a Germa Leptor server at some point in the near future, so look out for that.
No, I hate Jello. It is the worst.
Yes, before I started doing commentaries, believe it or not, I talked all the time on the mics in Team Fortress 2,
and now that I've kind of gotten a little bit of a following, I've shied away in public servers doing that,
because I don't want to give myself like a bad name, like, oh, dude, Nihal Medic, hit the Uber next time, you idiot.
Like, I feel like I could really get myself in a little bit of trouble now if I try and do that now.
But yes, a couple years ago, I used to do that quite frequently, so.
What kind of music do you like? I got a bunch of these, so I'm going to put these all in the same category.
What music do you like? What's your favorite band? What's your favorite song? I'm going to do them all right now.
My favorite band is the Gorillaz. I think that they are the only band you should be listening to right now,
because everything else is this, you know, pop dance floor crap that everyone seems to love now.
And if you love that, then that's your own opinion. I'm not going to say that it's a wrong opinion.
I just say that I don't like that crap. Let me reiterate that. I don't like that garbage.
I'm just kidding, obviously. But Gorillaz are my favorite band. My favorite song is Stylo from the Gorillaz.
If you've never heard Stylo, please, God, go listen to it right now. For the love of God, go play it.
And what's your favorite type of music? My favorite type of music is alternative, kind of like alternative rock,
alternative like trance. Not like techno, but like I said, the Gorillaz are my favorite band.
So that type of, you know, electro pop, electro alternative, that's my favorite type of music.
DMACDouble asks, what's your favorite thing about Tim Robbins?
My favorite thing about Tim Robbins is probably his incredible acting experience, his great demeanor on the stage and screen,
and how nice he is to people that are on set with him, because that's what I've heard.
How did you react when you saw that you had so many subscribers with so few videos?
Happy and shocked. I guess that's the only thing I can really say is I was really, really happy.
Here's a really quick story, actually, for you guys. I'm sure some of you would think this is actually kind of interesting.
When I first did my first Team Fortress 2 commentary a couple months ago, I did two in a row, and I uploaded them on the same night,
and the next morning I woke up and I said, I don't want to do this. No one's going to watch me. I'm too old for this. I can't do this.
So I deleted all the videos and I was going to delete the account.
Then I talked to a friend of mine who said, you know what? You might as well just go for it, and you might as well have fun with it,
because what are you going to lose? What are you going to lose? People are going to think you're a dork or something?
I already am a dork. I've been a dork my whole life.
So one of my buddies actually was the one that convinced me to continue doing it, and I brought the videos back.
So if it wasn't for my real-life friend, these videos would not exist, and I'm so glad that I did,
because you guys are all so awesome, and I've had so much fun so far.
So I look forward to a nice, real long-term relationship with a lot of you guys.
Hopefully you stick around in the months and years to come, because I'll be here.
So I hope we have some good times.
That's two questions. I kind of molded them together.
I have owned Team Fortress 2 since the very beginning, since it first came out. I played in the beta.
They did like a promo where if you bought the game, like a pre-order of the game, you could play for two or three weeks before the release.
That's when I bought the game. I played in October. It released at the end of October or something.
So I played like two or three weeks before everyone else did in the beta.
And it's been three, four, five years since the game came out, so that's how long I've been playing.
How many hours do I have? I have 600 hours played in the game, which is not that much compared to a lot of people,
but you got to remember I'm 25 years old and I have other obligations and I have other things I have to do every day.
So when I was in college, that's where a lot of those hours came from when I was in college.
Did you become friends with most of the other Team Fortress 2 subscri- I think he means to say commentators.
So did you become friends with most of the other Team Fortress 2 commentators before Leptor featured you or after?
Because it seems that recently everybody knows you.
Uh, no. Leptor is the only guy that I really have a speaking relationship with.
So before Leptor, it was just me. It was just me.
And then I think it's because the fact that I have almost 2,000 subscribers now
is the reason why people are kind of starting to pay attention to the channel and the channel is actually starting to get a little bit of legitimacy now
because you guys are all still coming.
So keep coming and this channel will get even more legit.
Have you ever kissed two girls at the same time?
No. Unfortunately I have not.
What is your favorite Engineer Melee weapon?
Definitely the Jag and I know the Jag is a gimmick weapon and some of you guys are going to say,
that's a gimmick weapon, come on, it's got to be like the Southern Hospitality or something.
No, I really like the Jag only because building up a dispenser,
saving that 1.3 seconds, whatever it is,
it really does help in some situations and it looks really cool.
I like the weapon and how it looks. So that's why it is.
Do you want to fish slap Star for pure randomness?
No, I don't because I don't have a speaking relationship with Star.
I've never had a conversation with him really so.
Do you own Killing Floor and if you do, would you be willing to record some gameplay of it?
I do not own Killing Floor.
It's a game that I thought when it first came out it was sort of a Left 4 Dead clone
and I already had Left 4 Dead so I didn't want to get it.
But if people want me to play it and if it's good enough,
then yeah, eventually here once I'm done with all these other games I'm doing,
then maybe yeah, I'll try doing a Let's Play of it.
Will my comment be in the video? Yes, it will.
Nerayuxa32, Nerayuxa32, of course it will.
Why did you start playing TF2?
I started playing TF2 because I played Team Fortress Classic
way long ago when a lot of you guys were too young to even play video games
or to even understand some of these games.
Team Fortress Classic is Team Fortress 1.
I believe it was like 1996 or 1997 when it came out and I was like 14 or 15
and so your Team Fortress 2 is my Team Fortress 1.
You know how some of you, a lot of you guys are 13, 14, 15, 16,
a lot of you guys are pretty young.
So I was your age when I was your age I was playing Team Fortress 1.
So that's a little bit of info for you.
But obviously when Team Fortress 2 came out, the sequel,
it's a much better game so that's why I started playing it.
Why do I always check to see if you uploaded a new video?
Because you're the man and you're a critical viewer
and I love people like you so that's not a bad thing.
What is your favorite class and what do you think about the new soldier weapons?
I combine these two because a lot of people ask both of these questions so
my favorite class has changed over the years.
At first when I first got Team Fortress 2 and in Team Fortress Classic it was the Spy.
The Spy is just a lot of fun to play.
More recently however though it's been the Engineer.
The Engineer is probably my favorite class as of right now.
So Spy, Engineer, definitely my two favorites.
What do you think about the new soldier weapons?
I think that they are stupid.
I think they're just complete gimmicks and I think Valve
should never have added them into the game but you know,
20-20 hindsight you can't look back and say that because it's already here.
Just deal with it.
And they're actually kind of, the items are kind of fun to play with
but that's all they are.
They're items just to play with for one round and never use them again.
Can you fake Chao your friend's babysitter's aunt?
I have no idea what that even means.
So I'm going to say yes, no.
Do you love Jamps? says Jamps96.
I don't know, does Jamps love me?
Should Pluto be considered a planet?
Of course it should because you know what?
I say screw you to the scientists.
They can't do that to my boy Pluto.
He's been a planet since I was a little kid and it was the coolest thing
knowing Pluto was like the smallest, coolest planet
and now they're going to take it away from him.
Give me a break.
How long did it take you to become so sexy?
And any tips on how to achieve your sexiness?
Okay, first of all, the first part of the question is DNA, I believe
is how I became so sexy and my parents, I guess by genes
and any tips on how to achieve your sexiness?
Yeah, be yourself and have some confidence.
Only two tips I can really give.
Boxers or briefs, somebody says.
Funny, boxer briefs is what I wear.
Boxer briefs.
What is your favorite food?
Oh God, dude, this question is going to take a while.
No, it's not.
My favorite food is probably.
Oh God, it's like two or three options.
I'm just going to say the two that I'm going to give you two.
One is General Gao's chicken, like the Chinese food.
I think that's it's unbelievable.
And the other one is chicken cutlets.
And I'm not talking just regular boring ass chicken cutlets.
I'm talking about the real thin pressed crispy fried chicken cutlet.
So those are my two favorite foods.
This question is just potatoes.
Potatoes?
No, no potatoes.
What do you do when you're not playing video games?
Oh, that's a good question because I do quite a few things.
First of all, I am in a men's softball league
and we're currently going into the playoffs next week, so wish us luck.
So I do that.
I play men's softball.
I used to play like baseball, softball, you know, when I was younger.
And that's just continuing now.
I love sports.
So that's the reason why.
What else do I do?
I do lifting.
Like I said before, I do a lot of workouts.
So, you know, three or four or five days a week, I'm in the gym.
So I do that when I'm not gaming and obviously just hanging out with friends,
hanging out with family, you know, just doing the old thing.
Do you like Borderlands?
I got that question four or five times.
Yeah, I do like Borderlands.
And you'd probably know that if you watched my Borderlands Let's Play with Leptor.
So the answer is yes, I do like Borderlands and go check out Leptor's page right now
because it has like at least 14 or 15 episodes right now of us playing Borderlands.
The next question is how big?
This big.
What do you think of people that always say, mainly in tutorial videos, go Google it.
I don't have time to add links, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Ah, I think that if you're going to make a video for people that's going to teach them something,
I think that you should have all the information in the video, not like go, go do this, go do that.
I think if you're going to do it, especially a tutorial video,
you need to be able to tell people exactly what you're doing, where to go, what the hell.
You know, you have to give everybody all the information.
So I think that I agree.
I think that's a dumb thing.
Why does Google Chrome spell check say that Google needs to have the first letter uppercased?
Well, because Google is a noun.
It's a company.
So Google is a company, which is a noun, like I said.
So it has to have an uppercase letter at the beginning.
What do you think of the VAC, the anti-cheat system?
The anti-cheat system, I think it's great because it allows people to be afraid of hacking.
A lot of games don't put that fear in people, you know, like, oh, I'm going to go play, you know,
this game and there's no punkbuster or there's no VAC.
It's just I can do whatever the hell I want online.
VAC might have its flaws, but at least it's that wall that makes people afraid to do anything.
How did you get to know Shibby and why is he always so drunk?
Well, the first part of the question is pretty easy.
Just like Leptor, I sent Shibby a message and he sent me a reply back,
giving me some advice for the channel and he was a nice guy about it.
And as the channel grew, he, I guess, started to notice that people were hanging out here
and he was like, oh, who the hell is, hey, hey, what's going on, dude?
So and then we started talking and we became buddies and that's kind of how that happened.
And why is he always drunk?
Because he likes to have a good time.
Nothing wrong with that.
I'm not going to tell anybody what they can and can't do.
If you want to be drunk, if you want to have fun, I mean, he's only 23.
That's like the prime age to be like going out, having a good time all the time.
So I'm down with that.
That's fine for me.
What's your favorite game type and map in Team Fortress 2?
My favorite game type is Payload and my favorite map is Badwater.
I know that's like so cookie cutter, but that's the truth.
When will Team Fortress 3 come out and will it be microtransactions again?
Hmm.
Well, because I work at Valve, I'm going to tell you all the development plans of Valve.
And Team Fortress 3 is on pace to be released on January 16th of 2017.
And it's going to be all microtransactions.
And we're adding 18 more classes for a total of 29 classes, I think.
No. Yeah. Yeah.
So we're going to have like 30 classes in Team Fortress 3.
And it's going to cost $455 for a hat in the Manco store.
iAnimeKid3 asks, can you give me a hat?
No.
Because if I give you a hat, then I have to give everybody else a hat.
So once I end up with like 12, 15, 16, 1700 hats, sure, I'll give everybody a damn hat.
What is your favorite weapon in Team Fortress 2?
The Frontier Justice.
The Frontier Justice is the best weapon in the game, in my opinion.
It's my favorite. I've named it.
So, you know, when you name something, it's like your favorite thing.
Either that or the Connivorous Kunai. Those are my two favorite items.
What other games will you be posting?
If you've been watching the channel so far, you see that I have The Witcher 2.
It's kind of a semi-serious let's play I'm going to start doing.
I'm going to do it maybe once every two weeks. Once every week I'll put a new video up.
Don't worry for those people that are freaking out.
It's not going to take over Team Fortress.
It's a secondary let's play. I'm going to say that again one more time to reiterate.
It's a secondary let's play.
Where did the name Jerma come from?
The name Jerma, it's pretty self-explanatory.
It's my first name, kind of changed a little bit.
My name is Jeremy.
So Jeremy, Jerma, it's kind of a nickname I had in high school.
So that's where it came from.
Do you play Minecraft and do you play on a server?
I play Minecraft very, very, very infrequently.
And no, I don't play on any particular server.
I kind of just jump around whenever I feel like it.
Haven't really played Minecraft in a few weeks.
The last time I played it was actually a couple days ago, but it was just for fun.
We were playing on the Hunting Wolves server.
And he was really cool about it.
And we were there with Shibby and Leon was there.
There was a bunch of dudes there.
So it was a fun time, but I don't really play Minecraft at all.
I only play it when, like I said, it's going to be just a goofy fun time.
Do you think Mars is a cool planet?
What did I tell you guys about asking about the stupid Mars question?
Oh no, Mars is actually kind of a cool planet.
Yeah, it is.
Katy Perry or Megan Fox?
Megan Fox all the way, definitely.
Do you live alone and do you have a girlfriend?
For the first one, I do not live alone.
I just graduated college about a year and a half, two years ago.
So got back to the home with the parents just hanging out here for now.
Trying to find my own place somewhere in the near future.
But I'm at my house still living at home.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No, I do not currently have a girlfriend.
But this does not mean I am going to accept inquiries of inquiries of people asking me,
Oh, hey, you don't have a girlfriend.
Like, let's chat.
Like, no.
So you can forget about that already if that was your plan.
What is your absolute favorite setup in the whole game?
Kind of hard because I have one or two,
but probably the one that I go to all the time is Engineer,
and it's the Frontier Justice, the Pistol, and the Mini-Sentry.
That is my absolute favorite setup in the game.
I love it so much.
I wish I could play it every day,
and I wish I could just do all Engineer gameplays.
But no, that's a joke.
But no, that's my favorite.
You are pretty funny, so I was wondering what makes you laugh.
Do you have a favorite comedian or a favorite movie or a joke?
I have a favorite comedian.
My favorite comedian is Bill Burr.
He is hysterical.
He's from Boston, too, which makes it even better.
He's hilarious.
If you have never heard of Bill Burr, you never watch Bill Burr.
He's kind of on the 17, 18-plus side,
so I'm not going to recommend that to anybody right now.
But if you are of age and you like funny comedians,
then go check out Bill Burr.
Favorite movie?
I don't really have a favorite movie.
I don't really watch movies, to be honest.
The last time I went to the movies was probably to see
one of the Harry Potter movies a while back,
so I don't really have a favorite movie.
Every gamer eventually noms on something during their hours of play.
What do you normally snack on?
That's a good question because I don't snack on anything.
I'm a drinker when I play games.
I'm not talking about alcoholic beverages.
I'm talking about like fruit punch or a soda or something.
I'm more of a drinker than an eater when I play games.
Do you like cheese?
And if you do, what's your favorite cheese?
I do love cheese. I love it a lot.
And my favorite cheese is Swiss.
Swiss cheese is amazing.
What's your favorite survival horror game of all time?
Probably Resident Evil 4.
That's one of the games I beat two or three times
and did all the other extra stuff, so probably Resident Evil 4.
What would you add or remove class-wise in TF2?
I would not remove a class and I would not add a class
only because the game is just so balanced around the nine classes.
If you took somebody away, it would just screw everything up.
Definitely it would ruin everything, so I wouldn't add or remove anybody.
What would you like to work as?
Huh, probably this, to be honest.
If I could somehow get to a position where I was doing this every day
and you guys were all involved and everyone was having a good time
and I could do this for a profession, it would be huge.
That would be huge for me because I'm getting kind of old
and it would be nice in the next couple years to have something where I could go,
you know what, this is a whole lot of fun.
I go to work every day with a smile on my face
and this is what I would love to do.
Now, the question is, will that actually happen?
I don't know.
That's solely up to the amount of people that come to the channel,
the amount of people that stick around, and that's all up to you guys.
So that's what I would love to do, though.
I'd love to, you know, be a machinima partner or something
and make money doing this. It would be amazing.
Can you do a backflip?
It's funny because yes, I can.
I can do a backflip without my hands in the air.
That's not a joke.
And if anyone wants to give me hate on that,
I will post a video of me backflipping in the air without my hands.
So yes, I can.
Kind of an odd question, but yes.
Digimon or Pokemon?
Uh, neither.
Not a fan of either of them, but if I'd have to pick one,
probably Pokemon because it's the original, it's the older one.
What is the best thing to ever come in a Team Fortress 2 update?
Definitely payload.
Out of all the weapons, out of all the items, all the hats,
absolutely, it's definitely the addition of the payload game type
because that changed everything
and it made the game so much more popular,
so much more interesting, so I definitely would say payload.
Do you read, and if you do, what is your favorite book?
I don't really read a whole lot.
I don't read as much as I should.
I know that you're supposed to read at least like
five to 12 paragraphs a day to keep your brain working or whatever,
but I guess I do kind of read these comments.
I read graphic novels.
I don't know if they count, but I count that
because it's plenty of words, and if you want my favorite book,
if you want my favorite series, I guess you could say,
go look up a guy named Doug Tenapel.
Doug, T-E-N-N-E-P-A-L, Doug Tenapel.
He is the guy that created Earthworm Jim,
and he has insanely funny, insanely interesting graphic novels,
so go check about if you have never heard of him already.
What is your most hated class in Team Fortress 2?
As of right now, none.
I think the game is very, very balanced,
but two, three, four years ago,
it was definitely the Demoman and the Soldier,
and I'll tell you why.
A lot of you guys don't know this, but way back long ago,
the Demoman and the Soldier used to have much more ammunition.
I think right now the amount of rockets you have is 20.
It used to be somewhere around 40.
Same thing with the Demoman.
It's 16 pills you get in the grenade launcher.
It used to be like 36 or something.
It used to be insane, and it was a huge nerf.
When they did that, it was an enormous nerf to those classes.
What is your favorite hat in Team Fortress 2?
Definitely the one I currently have on the Heavy right now.
The Luchador, the Lodge Luchador.
It's hysterical. It's the best thing ever.
Do you have any dogs or cats?
Yes, I do. I have two dogs and three cats.
Yeah, my family's really crazy about animals.
Who is your favorite Team Fortress 2 commentator besides yourself?
Uh, I think all of them.
I think every single one of the TF2 commentators right now
bring something to the table.
Guys like IRSnipeR, they're really skill-based.
They have really, really high-quality skill videos
where they kill a bunch of people.
Star is really relaxed. He's really easy to listen to.
He's really good on the ears.
Guys like Shibby are just hysterical. He's hilarious.
He's one of the funnier guys you could ever listen to.
Leptor is also in that category.
He's like funny, but he's skilled too,
so he's a good combination of both worlds.
And I really don't know what category I would fit into,
even if there is a category, but out of all those guys,
I think all of them bring something really, really good to the table.
And I think they're all good. I like them all.
How much meat do you eat with your hands?
Uh, none.
I don't really eat, like, bags of meat.
What is your favorite game of all time?
Easy question, easy answer.
Super Mario RPG.
Definitely the best game of all time, in my opinion.
Below that, it's probably Diablo 2.
Soon to be Diablo 3, I'm hoping.
And then below that, number 3 is probably...
You guys are gonna hate me.
World of Warcraft.
Wait, before you freak out,
the reason why World of Warcraft is in my top 3 favorite games of all time
is because the sheer amount of time I put into that game.
I put hundreds, thousands, thousands, and thousands of hours into World of Warcraft.
I don't play it anymore.
I haven't played World of Warcraft in probably a year.
And I'd never plan on going back.
I'm done with it. It's over.
But for a good six, five or six years, I was really, really into it.
Made a lot of friends on there.
Had a lot of good conversations, a lot of good raids.
It was a good time, so...
Do I think the game is the most fun, the most balanced, the most interesting?
No, but it's definitely the most social, and I had a lot of fun on it.
So that's probably why.
Where are you or your parents from?
I think that means... I think what he's asking is where...
What's your nationality? I think is what he's saying.
My nationality is half Irish, half Polish.
My father is from Ireland, and my...
No, he's not from Ireland, but...
My father is Irish, and my mother is Polish, so...
How many push-ups can you do?
I've never really tried to max out my push-ups, but...
Normally I do 60 in three sets, so I'll do one 20, 20, 20, and that's pretty much what I do for push-ups, so...
As the scout, do you have urges to smash relatives in the face with a metallic baseball bat?
And or drink hallucinogenic fizzy drinks?
All the time.
Why make commentaries of Team Fortress 2?
Basically, Team Fortress 2 is one of the only games that I've been good enough at it,
where I could potentially join a competitive scene,
and I'm not really that good at most other games, I'm good at them,
but to the point where I could really be like a competitive, professional player,
I think Team Fortress 2 is the only game since...
I mean, there was a time in World of Warcraft where I played it for so long that I became very good at it,
but Team Fortress is definitely the only game where I have real professional competitive skills in,
and that's why I think it's my best game,
so I figured why not make commentaries on the game that you're good at, you know?
Time to wrap this up, guys, only one or two more questions, so...
Thank you all for putting your questions in, I'm sorry if I didn't answer your question,
just you gotta remember, you gotta realize there was about 150 questions that I had to answer or potentially answer,
and I didn't want this to go more than 30 or 40 minutes, cause people probably wouldn't even watch it, so...
I had to skim through, I had to cut the fat a little bit, so I'm sorry if your question did not get answered,
so let's wrap it up here.
Do you like Finnish people?
I don't have a problem with Finnish people, I...
They're just as good as anybody else, I think, there's nothing wrong with them.
What is your favorite element on the periodic table of elements?
Barium, baby, barium.
I don't even know what barium is or what it does, but barium.
That's gonna wrap it up, guys, thank you so much for inputting all your questions, it was a great time,
I'm so happy that you guys were that enthusiastic about it,
I didn't think I was gonna get more than maybe 30 or 40 questions,
because it is kinda tough to come up with a question for somebody,
so thank you all so much, there's a little bit of gameplay left,
some real funny stuff happens, I'm sorry that you guys couldn't see the whole event we had,
but like I said, it's just too long,
so enjoy the rest of it, and I'll see you guys next time, take care everybody.
No, throw it, throw your stupid jorati.
No, no, no, get this out of here, get that out of here.
Get the sentry out of here.
Alright, so ready?
Everyone line up, shoulder to shoulder.
Ready?
Three, two, one, let go!
Dude, I got killed before I could even throw my anything out there.
Hey, I'm some dude, can you pick people who aren't?
Alright, now this is free for all.
You just crushed him.