Open up, please. I'm gonna have to lower the volume on it, too, because it is pretty loud.
Oh, I'm already getting the chills. And Abracadabra, can you see it? I hope so.
I think you can. Oh, I gotta get the chat up here. I cannot hit escape, though. That's one,
the one big thing. Cannot hit escape. So I can see what you guys are saying. There's that.
Oh no, the chat just can't fit anywhere. Hold on, can I move this? I can. Excellent. Here we are.
One more second, guys. This here. Perfect. Perfect. Now I can see what everybody's saying.
Time to play Slender. Oh boy, oh boy. So the goal here tonight, guys, is I'm gonna try
and get all the pages. I'm gonna try and beat this game. I'm gonna do it.
Let's go! Gonna beat Slender. I'm gonna beat Slender. Definitely not gonna beat Slender,
because it is like impossible to beat. Because once you get like seven pages,
he just eats your soul. All right, here comes page one, guys. Welcome to the Scare Stream.
Happy preliminary Halloween. Let's do... Oh, wait. Hold on. Oh, that just ruined my whole entrance.
I hit E, not click. Here we go. I only have the headphone in one ear. I know. You can call me
whatever you want to call me. I thought I just saw him. I thought I just saw him. I'm gonna try
to upload this to YouTube, so if you are gonna miss some of this, I'm gonna try and get the whole
thing up there. If you're watching this on YouTube, hey, what's up? How you doing? Did I just walk in
like a circle? All right, let's see. I'm not looking behind me. Everyone's like, oh, behind you,
behind you. I ain't looking behind me. I need to go left. Whoa, I hear static. Where is he? I hear
static right now. Where the hell is he? I hear static right now. Where is he? He's probably right
there. What? Where is he? I don't even know where he is. I don't know where the hell he is. Where is
he? Oh, my God. Where is he? He's probably like right... If I... Ready? He's right there. He's right
there. He's right there. Run to the tree. Run to the tree. Run to the tree. Run to the tree. The tree
of life. Don't look for him. You have... But that's the thing. You have to look for him. You have to
like turn and look. Hello, page two. He's... As long as I know where he is, he's fine. He's right behind
me. He's right up my ass. I'll tell you a thing or two, slender man. You want to mess with me?
I'll give you the one, two... Why am I taking my hands off? I'm like... Oh, let me make like a joke
and die. That's a great idea, Jeremiah. Is there anything on here? Can I like go in there and go
to the bathroom? I thought he was like right there. Come on, get three. Go. He's still behind me. I
know exactly where he is. I wish I could run. Damn. I wish I could sprint. I can sprint now.
I love reading the chat. It's so fun. I can't believe I said I was going to beat this game.
There's no way I'm going to beat this game. Are you kidding me? Are you kidding me? Did I just walk in
a giant circle? No, there's... I can't even see. Yeah, that's the next part. I got to go there.
You needed something to fall asleep to. Larry, I'm sorry. This is what you have to fall asleep to.
It would be tough if I was you. Slender and SCP containment breach. See, it's good having you guys
here in the chat because when I play this game alone, whenever I play like scary games alone,
there's not a whole lot... It's so terrifying. I can't... I'm much better looking over and seeing
all you guys in the chat. It makes it so much better because now I won't crap my pants,
except I already did in the first 30 seconds of this game starting. I'm scared right now.
My teeth are chattering. There was no indication that that was going to happen.
One down. It's like only three more games to play. Oh, man. That hurt my whole body. I thought it
was supposed to play static whenever it gets close to you. Jeez. All right. We're going to do this
again. Let me load it up again. We're doing Slender again. Yes, of course I want to run it.
Honestly, like that, I really did not think that he was there. I really did not think he was there.
How does that look? No, I didn't want to do that. I wanted to go to here. Okay, looks fine.
Not big surprise. All right, looks good. Let's go. Drag you over here. See, the bad part about
these SCP and Slender and stuff, if you try to hit escape or get to a menu or something,
you just close the game. So you have to be a little weird with it. Try to keep it on the
side and drag the chat over. Hey, do I want a hug? Yeah, I do. Especially after that. All right,
what'd I get? Three pages? Four pages? Yeah, that was great. Great job, Jeremy. You did a great job
there. All right, I got to get ready for this one. Last time I was stupid and I turned around
and looked at him and said, hello, page one. All right, I got to think of a plan of action here
before I pick this up. Where's the page? What the hell? Okay, there's the page one. I'm going
to go straight through here. No, wait, do I want to go there? Or straight down there? Let's see.
I'm going to go straight down there. Here we go. Ready? Go. You can't run. You can't hide. You
can't get away from the Shenderman. Do I already hear static? I think I already hear still. No,
I don't. Oh, great. Good thing I decided to run into a fence. Now I'm going to turn around. He's
going to be right there. Cool. Great. I shouldn't have ran. That was a dumb idea. I should have
sprinted. Oh, you know what I wish? I wish there was a stamina bar. Somebody said the
stamina is like, it's hard to read. I wish there was a bar right there, like right on the screen
that said, oh, you have like this percentage or this amount. I just walked in a circle.
Man, I hate this. I hate this guy. Where's like the gun so I can turn around and just
just unload on his and touch static or is that water? I don't think there's water in this game.
Oh, is that water or static? There's no water. I'm not looking behind me. I'm not making that
same mistake. See, last time I looked behind me, that was a massive mistake. What are you guys
saying? Let's see. Strafe jump. You can jump in this game. I don't think you could jump. I thought
that was him right there, by the way, like whatever the hell that is. Oh, we have some moss on the
tree that's painted just like Slenderman's body. No, I'm not looking behind me. Don't ever look
behind you. Worst idea. You know, it's people that talk about the spy and Slenderman. Think about it.
He's in a suit. He has like no face. He's got like a mask on or whatever. I don't know. Maybe
doesn't have a mask on, but tall guy in a suit that gets behind you. Slenderman is a spy. What?
I hate being in here. Get. Oh, hi. Fantastic. How you doing, man? Good to meet you. Get me
out of this hellhole of a bathroom. I don't even care. Screw that frigging paper. I don't even
care. I'll lose the game. I don't even, I don't even want to be in there. If I get stuck in there
with him, I, I'm dead. It's over. I'm dead. I'm so dead right now. I'm going to back up right into
him and it's going to scare me. I'm not going to get scared. I'm not going to get scared this time.
I'm going to look him right in his eyes. Run. I'm going to get, I'm going to spit that out.
I was, if he jumped at me right there, I would have spit that all over my screen and the stream
would have had to like end. Getting stuck on trees now. That's not cool. Probably right behind me.
It's going to make that noise. Move faster. You piece of. Oh, there's so many things I could say
right now. I don't even know what adjective to use. What's, what's somebody say? Jerma is Slenderman.
I don't know. I don't even know what that said. I'm too scared. There's another one right here.
He's probably this asshole is probably going to be standing right here. I wish I could just take
my headphone out and not have to hear this music. I'm going to have to turn around. Yeah. I got to
turn around. Great. Is that him? No, it's not. Go. I'm going to, I can't look. I seriously can't
look at the screen. He's, he's like to the left of me. He's like right there. And I, I need to go
that way. This is the worst, especially because I can't run anymore. This is it for Slender. I
can't take Slender anymore. It's, it's, I can't take it anymore. He's, he's, when he's going to,
you know what, you ready for this guys? I'm going to run right at him. Wait, no, no, no. Opening,
opening. Make sure, you know, we're going to just, we're going to check. We're going to do a quick
check. Hey, where are you? You're right behind me. Yep. He's right behind me. You know, now I'm not
so scared because I know the son of a bitch is right behind me and he's a slow slug. He ain't
catching up to me. Good luck catching up to me. I got legs. I can run. He has legs too. What's
that? Okay. Definitely still right behind me. I'm going to grab it. Oh my God. I can feel him
behind me. Is there a note there? I don't even care. I can't even turn to look and see if there's
a note. I think there is. What if I do this? No, I just got to keep moving. Oh, there's another
note. I see it. Is that a note? It is. Okay, good. Grab the note. Grab the note. Hey, can't run. Yeah,
I wish I had more stamina. Oh, is that him? I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. I don't know. Who knows? I don't know, man. Did I already get the one on the tree? I don't
remember. I don't know if I got the one on the tree. I don't think I did. Go. I don't want to
turn around to grab this. Got it. Hello. It's going to do it. He's right here. He's right here. I
knew it. See? I told you. I knew it. I knew it. I could feel him. I could feel him like right
up my... He was grabbing onto my butt cheeks and squeezing them. That's like how much I felt him.
Slender Man. I'll punch Slender Man in his Slender face. I'll knock his teeth out. All right. I
can't play Slender Man anymore. I can't play you anymore. I got to move on to Containment Breach.
We'll play Containment Breach. Actually, Containment Breach is probably worse than Slender.
Containment Breach. All right. This game is loud as hell. Memory access violation. What the hell
does that mean? Memory access violation. I'll give you a violation. I'll like park my car at
double parking after seven o'clock and I'll get a violation. I'll show you. That was a bad joke.
I apologize for that one. All right. Looks like we're playing SCP-087-B. It's next up on the list.
Next up on the list. Let's do it. Here we go. Oh, wow. This is loud. This is loud. Got to turn you
down. Oh, God. Ow, my head. Wow. That's loud. You are loud as hell. Wow. Sorry about that.
That was bad. That was loud. Hey, hold on a second. That was weird. That was weird.
Hold on. Yeah. I'm going to turn it down the window. Was that loud for all you guys too?
That was like, I felt like somebody shot me in the side of the head. Okay. I can turn it down
from here. All right. Let's do this again. In fact, hell no. I'm going to turn this all the way down.
Can I open that up? Open up. All right. Oh, can I, I gotta, no, no. Why am I stuck again? What in the
name of God? It keeps on locking up my mouse and I can't change anything. Let's see if I can catch
it quick. Yeah. I gotta, I gotta hit the, I gotta make direct show go through. I know it's a black
screen. I'm sorry. Let's try this again. I gotta catch it right when it pops up. So I need this open
and come here. You come here, come here, come here, come here. Oh, I had it. Oh, move over here so I
can catch you quicker. Got it. No, now it's at zero. Damn it. I'll get it. I'll get it. There we go.
Okay. Bingo. Bingo. Please proceed with caution. All right. Here we go. Oh, wait, seven B. B is for
ball. You know the rest. Going down the stairs. So this is like a hallway simulator and stuff jumps
out at you and scares you and it's horrible. I get, we got three. I don't want to go down there.
Screw that. Screw that. Oh, eight, seven B. You are now entering. Whoa. Hello. What the hell was that?
It's been a long time since I played. Oh, eight, seven B. So I forget whatever. I forget what
happens. It's been a while. Can I, can I just say that we, we, we live in the 21st century.
How can you have a radio that sucks that bad? I mean, really, seriously, where did you get that
radio? Dude, your radio sucks big time. You might want to replace the batteries. Why is everything
getting all weird looking? What's going on? Why is there something, is there something right here?
Why, why? Everything's changing. Everything looks like weird now. Maybe I'm just going absolutely
crazy. Floor seven. Oh, I don't know how much longer I can do scary games. Oh, hi. Thanks for
closing in on me. I appreciate it. Come on. Something jumped out at me. I'm ready. I'm ready.
I'm ready to just, just, just throw up on my screen. Come on. I know what this means. I know
what this means. Something's going to happen right now. Something's going to happen right now. I know
it. I've been here before. We've been down this road before, man. Yeah. I see you. I see it. I can
see it. What? Yeah. Hi. What was that noise? What is going on? What is going on? I am, I'm ready to
just jump and run. Oh, no floor number. No. Okay. Hey, whoa. Hi. Damn man. Come on. Hey, how are
you? How's your, how's your kids and your wife and your, and your son? How's it? I heard he plays
baseball now. Good to see him. Yeah. He's growing. He's big. I need the chat's help. Hold on chat.
What do you think? What do I do? All right. Okay. I got, I have the support from the chat. I'm ready.
I'm ready to play the game now. Oh, I don't even want to see it. I don't even want to see it. I
know it's going to be something to be. Oh, was that a bug? What the hell was that? I don't know
if you could just see that right there, but I did. A bubble just came out of my mouth, a floating like
soap bubble. Don't ask me how the hell that happened. God, I'm about to rage quit this game
because I can't handle it because this game I know is horrible when it comes to things jumping at
you. What if I just put my head down? Oh man, this is worse than, this is probably worse than slender.
I'm about to hit escape. I'm, my hand is on escape right now. I'm about to just exit the game.
It's on, my hand is on escape. The second I see something I don't like it, I'm hitting it.
Man, come on, show me something scary so I can just insta quit the game. It's throwing all kinds
of noises. Bye. See you later. Have fun. Have fun. Slender man, whatever the, who the hell you are.
Did you see that damn thing? It was like right here on the screen. That was hard. That was horrible.
Oh wow. That was so stupid. Oh, all right. Give me a second. That one took a lot out of me right
there. Oh, I think I might have to change my pants. Let's see. Let's, let's, let's check. Nope, I'm fine.
Oh, all right. I need a break. I need like a five second break. I want to play containment breach. I
don't know why I can't get it to load. Hold on. Let me try loading this again. This is, this is stupid.
It should load. Open. Yes, I want you to run. No, why? I had, I ran earlier. Hold on a second. Give me
a second. Let me go options. Change this to 1600 by 900. I haven't set to launcher. Let's do launcher.
Okay. I think I got it. I'm going to get it. I got it. I'm going to get it guys. Watch this magic
right here. Watch this magic you're about to see right here. Are we ready for the magic?
Here comes the magic. Here it comes. And for my next trick, I'm not going to be able to do the
magic trick because it still doesn't work. Wait, wait, wait a second. I could get this to a hold
on screen. False launcher enabled. Yeah. I mean like, hello. Of course. Damn it. Yeah. I'm getting
that memory access violation, whatever the hell it is. Run it as administrator. Good call. Good call.
Those of you that said that, good call, because that's probably what's going to happen. It's
going to work right now. I had this working too. I made sure it worked before I started the stream
and it worked. Now it's being a real piece of crap. All right. Run as administrator.
And that's what I want. That's what I want. Launch again. That's what I want. Launch. Nope.
It's not going to launch. Oh, it looks like I'm going to have to drink a bunch of Dr. Pepper
that. I mean, come on. What if I just like freaking puked? How many like, how many like people
you think would want to see that if I was just like, oh yeah, you know, I'm going to say drink
some Dr. Pepper. I just like hurled all over the place. I would, I wish I could see something like
that. I would laugh my absolute ass off if I got to see something like that. I do. Me, me, me, me.
That's so funny. Well, it looks like we're playing contain 087B again, which is my favorite game of
all time. After this, I'm going to play some TF2. So stick around. You're not going to want to miss
this. I can't believe I'm loading this game up again. I did not want to play contain 087B again.
I wanted to play it once and that was it. I didn't want to have to do this damn game more than once.
Here we go. It's going to be like, so I prepare your ears. I'm warning you guys right now, turn
your headphones down because I got to catch this. If I don't catch it immediately, then it's going
to be an issue. So give me a minute. Let me make sure the face cam is nice and big in the corner.
Here we go. I got to make sure the mixer is here. Wait, wait, wait. Why does it say containment
breach is in the background? Hold on a second. Hold on a second. One second here. I think the reason
why it's screwing up is because it thinks it's running in the background. Oh, whatever. I don't
want to waste your guys' time anymore. You guys have been patient. Let's do it. You guys have been
patient. Let's do it. Here we go. Here we go. I'm just stalling as much as I can. Here we go.
Super Crate Box? That's a great game. I don't want to click this button. I don't want to play
this game again, but you know what? I'm going to play it again because you have to man up sometimes
and do it. So here we go. All right. Please proceed with caution. Please. I'll give you.
No, what's this? Oh, Smite. That game's fun. What if I just don't look at the screen once?
What the? See you later. Bye. No. No. No, I don't think so. I don't think so. I don't think so.
See ya. That's not happening. Did you see that? It just was like, all right, fine. Fine. Fine. We'll
do it again. We'll do it again. I don't want two in there. If you missed what just happened,
something just flashed on the screen. Like a face just flashed in my face.
It looked like the Cheshire Cat from Alice in Wonderland. What happens if I go down here?
What? Third time's a charm, guys. I can't believe it. You gotta be kidding me. Oh,
make sure you don't fall down the hall and die. Let's go. This is going to be the real one.
I'm not going to do any dumb mistakes and I'm not going to leave right off the bat.
Yeah, I know. I'm pretty sure. I'm pretty sure I know that that's where I am at this point. You
don't have to keep telling me. Well, let me get like the dust off my screen because it's making
me think that there's stuff on there. You are now entering some gauntlet legends. You are now
entering the crypt of the spider kingdom or something, whatever it was. Just keep talking
and I won't be scared. Just keep talking. Just keep making noises with your mouth and you won't
be scared about things that are jumping out at you on the screen.
You know what, man? I am just so sick of your- Why do you have to keep doing that?
What? What? What is this? What the hell is this? Why is there- What's this?
Stair- Why? Where am I? I don't have a flashlight. I don't even know where I am. Do I go in there
or do I go over here? I don't know. I don't- I don't know. Do it with one eye. If I do it with
one eye, it's not that bad. If I do it with one eye, it's still as bad. It's still just as bad
with one eye. Forget that. Never mind what I just said. It's still just as bad with one eye closed.
What about both eyes closed? But I can't see where I'm going. Things are getting weird looking
again. Things are getting like green and like opaque and- Oh, this is it. Get me out of here.
Pinkies on escape. Stop it. Hi. This is what happened last time and then the thing jumped
out at me. Floor 10. If you- I gotta think of a song, a nice happy song. Hold on.
Raindrops keep falling on my head, but I don't believe my life's a true beauty.
Red, red, the super bad, red, the raindrops keep falling on my head. They keep falling,
but blue, blue, blue, blue, blue. I don't know the lyrics, but it's helping lots. It is helping
lots when- No, it's not. No. Just get- Oh, man. I'm down pretty far. I didn't get down this far
last time. I think I did. I don't remember. It's just a blur at this point. 15. Hi. Itchy nose. Itchy
nose. It's a way for me to pretend like I have an itchy nose so I can not look at the screen
kind of really maybe. God damn it, man. Get them. I'm not going down further. I'm not going down
further than that. Containment breach. This game hurts my head. Wow. Beatbox the Halloween theme.
I'll do that. Well, how does it go? Here we go, ready? Let's see if I can do this.
because it's halloween makes sense right well it's not halloween right now but it will be
here we go i can't even do it it's too hard i'll slow it down hold on
that was better that was a little bit better i tried to do it like way too fast the first time
like that wasn't gonna work all right