Hi. Wait, what was that? Am I drowning in the game? No, I'm not. Wait, am I dead? How did I die?
Oh, I drowned. All right, well, that's all right. I didn't have anything. I just turned it on. I was
just testing it. Get the intro back on. I'm not here. You don't see me yet. I'll be right back.
Okay. Hello, everybody. I'm back. Another day. Another stream. Today, but the surprise is ruined,
even though if you were there last night, you knew. We're gonna play VR. Back in it again.
We're gonna start with Minecraft VR. That actually hurt to say that. It's already set up.
Apparently, I didn't know this before setting it all up. Look at my outfit today. I'm super
springy today. I'm like really summery today. Look at this. I got my fucking beach outfit on.
Don't you think? Like these? I do. I got that wave. I got a haircut too. What do you think?
Didn't get styled. I shaved. I was ready for you guys tonight. I was ready to do VR.
The wave? What's this called? This called something. The wave shirt. No, no, no. What's
the shirt called? I look like Ric Flair. I'll take it. I'll fucking take it. I'm pumped up today.
Not even at all, actually. I'm kind of tired. But let's go. I'm just wasting time.
Hope you all had a good day today. After today, you're not gonna see me for a few days.
So I figured I might as well do some Minecraft VR. Is this the right hand?
Before I strap these up, let me. Also, by the way, boring. What's it got in the wine glass?
Water? Boring. I can't drink in there. I'll fucking die. All right, let's go.
I'm gonna get this over with. Somebody has given like 20 community subs with the name
Jerma lied about Minecraft VR. You have to change your name now. This is the stream
where you change your name. You all thought I was a liar. You thought I wasn't gonna do it.
Here we are. I don't really know how to play in VR, though. So it should be, uh,
it should be interesting for all of us. This is all untangled. We're all good to go.
Did you see my fucking summer outfit? I didn't even get any compliments.
We're already tangled. No, we're not. Yeah, that's fine. All right, going in.
This shirt probably has sweat stains. It's worn to bed quite frequently. I'm gonna
unmute the game too. Don't worry. All right, there we go. So we are in Minecraft now.
So what was it? One hour, right? I said I'm gonna play this for one hour
and then uninstall the game. I told her I was gonna just dig down until I find
diamonds and I'm uninstalling again. Which one is right? Which one's left?
This is kind of cool. He went, he came under water to do this?
Okay. This is actually really interesting. I don't want the full experience. Not yet.
What happened down there? All right, this is the right hand.
Because I had to, because the left hand has HUD info on it. See this? There you guys are.
Because there's no HUD info. I know this is the right hand. You're gonna drown? I'm already
dead. I already died. It's weird seeing the game like this though. This is kind of strange.
The blocks look huge. Destroy the tree. Hold on. So we're gonna have to get
the whole tutorial here. I know how to play Minecraft, but it's been
fucking, and the last time I played it doesn't count because I was shit faced.
All right, here we go. So how do I respawn? How do I spawn? Did I get softlocked?
Oh, the game window might not be in focus. It's, wow, you're right, it's not. There we go.
All right, respawn. Here we go. I hate this already. Okay, so that's inventory. How do I
walk? Okay, it's left trigger to walk. It looks like you go towards anywhere you're looking.
Destroy the tree. Hold down left button. Okay, how do I get this tutorial out of here? I know
what I'm doing. Wait, what are you doing? What are you doing when you first start Minecraft?
This is, I hate this. I feel like I'm tuning a TV. Whoa, all right. So you automatically
just go up. All right, sick. Let's go. How far is the breach? All right, I gotta stop fucking around.
Wood, right? Okay, I got this. How do I place blocks? Okay, it's this button here.
Then you can take them away by hitting them again. All right, so say the lines. Not until
I know what I'm doing. Plus that wasn't part of the deal. Oh, destroy the tree. I know.
This takes too long. All right, where's my inventory? Right over here. All right, so you
can slide. No, they're actually not bad controls. So take the whole tree down.
How do you make torches? It's light and charcoal, right? How do you, what is it? It's,
how do you make a torch? It's charcoal and wood stove? All right, I got enough wood.
Light, yes, yes. Just harvest some light. Press E. What's E? Well, that's how you,
that's how you throw. No, that's, that's a menu. What is E? Top left button? Yeah,
that's what I just pressed. One of the grips, maybe? What is E? Just press E. I can't just,
there's no E on my hand. Where'd that go? Press E. Didn't I just do it? Ah, okay,
wait, wait, wait. Okay, so hold on here. It's up. You have to press up. What's down?
Let's just get the buttons ready. Down is jump. What is right? Okay, everything, it's,
okay, I got it. I got E. There's the crafting menu. So this is your click to open key showing off.
And this is, I make, oh, well, this is a lot different than what I remember.
Then, okay, so you just put it up here and then take them. He got it. Okay, then you do
sticks and then I need to make a tool, right? That's enough tools. So crafting,
I need to make a workbench. That's this, right? How do I split them? How do you split?
There it is. Crafting bench. All right. And then let me just make a little shitty fucking
house first. Just hold on. Get out of the menu. I got to make a house. Right on the
beach. Perfect. What do you think? Hell yeah. I'm so ready for a 24-hour stream here. It's
not going to be 24 hours. Good thing you have your beach outfit on. Yeah. All right,
so I'm thinking a long dock here and then the house. I don't want to, no, actually live
on a beach is fine. I need a shovel. This is very overwhelming. So just put the fucking
crafting bench down. Who cares? Not like that. Go get it. So crafting bench, just put it over
there. I'll open it up. So does this count that I'm like standing near it? Okay, there
it is. Let's get it all in there. I got pickaxe. Let's get a, wow. Does it actually
work? Does this work? That's actually really cool. I don't know if you can actually hit
stuff with this. Okay, shovel. That's important. All right, now let's go get what we need.
Forget about all the, I don't know, I'm not going to do any of this shit. I'll be
lucky if I play this for more than 30 minutes. Well, it was supposed to be an
hour, but you get it. You understand. You can hit. No shit. No fucking way. That's
too much for anybody's brain. No, I was going to do it like this. That's too much.
I don't want to do it like that. Let's get this place cleaned up. I don't need that
big of a house. I do have to, I gotta go down. Uh, there's a basement right here
with this water. Uh, this way. Let's go over here. There's stone. All right, my
house is over there. Is water gonna get in here? I need, I need coal. Check
your recipe book. I know. What about over here? Where the fuck am I? I don't
want to be on this waterfront. I need to get coal. I'm just going to go straight
down here. I will say this is probably the the coolest way you could play
Minecraft. All right, you see coal? It's getting dark out. I need coal right
now. Okay, you can burn wood too, can't you? Stone axe. I know. I don't have a
weapon. How long is the day night cycle? I'm actually fucking getting scared
though. This actually is scary. There's a creeper over there. All right,
I gotta go burn wood. Is that what you, I gotta burn wood, right? Where's my
house? Over here. Okay, at night this is a much different game. Who cares if I
die? There we go, right here. I need to make a, uh, furnace, right? But this is
gonna be the house. Might as well. Is that a creeper face right there?
That's a creeper just staring at me, right? It's coming at once. That's
a, that's a wart creeper. Must have been added in the fucking 1.2 update.
All right, let's see here. I need, that's not a furnace? That's not a
furnace. How is that not a furnace? It's eight in a, isn't this a crafting
bench though? Am I, is something, what's going on here? Am I in the crafting
menu? This is the crafting table, isn't it? That's not the, I haven't
played Minecraft, actually for real, without being drunk in like four years.
It's the crafting table. Isn't, that's not what this is. This is not a
crafting table. I just was trying to open this. What the fuck? Is that,
is this gravel? God damn it. Just give it back. Give it, just, just get
it, just, just get out. It's kind of awkward, the commerce, the, the,
it's kind of awkward menus. All right, so, put this down. This is,
don't take it either. All right, move over here. So, I gotta put some
wood in here. Does that count? No. Charcoal, I can't just put, like,
I can't put like a tree in there. It's gotta be like a block of wood,
right? No, I don't even have an axe. I need a regular fucking bench,
like a storage unit or something. There's something fucking here.
So, left button is, it's up here, it's odd, because every other place
you press is jump. This is place. It's hard to see. It's like a
tint, it's like hard to see it from here. Remember, I'm working with
like half the resolution that you guys are seeing. Let's just start
making a fucking house. All right, here we go. Whatever the fucking,
that's way too many creepers. That's a joke. I'm getting stream sniped
by like seven creepers over here. You knew I was going to be
streaming over here. Are you fucking serious? There was at least
five or six right there. No joke. All right, let's go. How do I
sneak? Not like that. I don't give a shit. I can fix it later.
Uh, the ceilings are way too high. I don't know how to sneak
like on this controller. You don't know how to sneak? You're
just crouching in real life. That's a lie. That's not how you
do it. Close your closet. I can't do that right now.
Let's just, I gotta go over here. Everybody starts with a
dirt house for shelter. I gotta come out here a little.
I'm close to something. What are you doing? One more? Look at
that. Okay, now. What am I near? Only non-pro gamers use
dirt. The desk is over here. That's a new monster. How do I
take care of this monster? Why is he faster in water?
Monster hunter. All right, get the fuck out of here. Hurry
up. Climb back up. Sun's coming up. The monsters are
huge. I guess you are just the same size, right? All
right, where was I? I gotta find something to light the
house with. Alright, that's fine. I just need a wall over
here. Anybody know how to sneak? Turn on the music.
Music is on. Change your scale above 100%. I actually
like it like this though. Alright, there we go. That's
all I need then. Just this way. And this is it. Then
I'm gonna build the roof. I got two. I think it's
coming along alright. That looks fine. This is just a
placeholder until like, okay, I gotta go on a search. I
gotta go on an adventure for diamonds. Not diamonds, fuck.
Stone. Home sweet home. Hello ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to episode one of Turbocraft, the series where
I play Minecraft. And if you can get yourself into a
nice seated comfortable position, hands inside the ride
at all times, we're gonna make our way over down
there. I think that way. Maybe there's some diamonds
over there. I got myself a I got a cider. I hope you got
one too. That's good. And there you go. There's there's
the clip that I will see posted to my channel 5000
times a week until the day I'm dead. At my funeral,
one of you guys is gonna show up and fucking put
that on like a tablet and place it on the casket. We
need a comparison. Alright, first of all, lambs. I'll
take one. I was just fucking fell over. I need that.
Alright, I got the meat. Am I not supposed to be doing
this? Get this fucking break it with your hands. No,
kids are gonna love this. I'm serious. Kids are gonna
love this. I didn't kids play this yet. Alright, what
was I doing? Okay, I got wool. I can make a bed now.
Now, I just need three pieces of wood. How about this
one? Looks good to me. This is a different kind of
wood though, right? Okay. Now, bring that to the
crafting bench. Make a bed. There it is. This is my
house. You can always tell cuz it's a wall of
dirt. Holy shit. I'm not gonna read that one. The
house is ruined. It hasn't even started yet. Oh,
that makes me wanna throw up a little bit. I'm not
gonna lie. Okay, now, I need I need an axe. I need
no. God, it's it's so it's so much going on in my
brain. Open this up with this menu. Okay, so I
need to make this shit. I'll take it. All of it,
please and it's 123 and then bang. Got yourself a
fucking bed. Perfect. So, now, when I die, I
will spawn here. That's not how I don't think
that's not how you place it, right? You have to
which way do I want the bed? Who cares? That's
your entrance right here. The door. Okay, there's
the door will come in here. Put a staircase
there. What do you guys think? The bed is near
your spawn point. What do you mean? That is the
spawn point. Alright, and let's just get some,
I need some, do I have enough wood for it,
right? I need to jump. Jumping is a little
weird. Let's go with, no, that's sand. How do
you make an axe? Like that or something? How
does it, how do you make the the chopping
tree axe? Oh, okay, like that. I need a box.
How do you make a box? It's like this, right?
Yeah, put that here. Alright, get out of
this menu. Get out of the menu. So, now,
let's put this here. I just need to put a
bunch of dumb shit in here. Um, I don't
know. Put like the, can I send it there
quickly without having to tap like a
million times? There's got to be a way I
can like press that and just have it send
over there, right? Or do I actually have to
physically do this? Because I have that
pick throw. There's a button to do it. Just
try everything. Try everything. Alright,
that's right. This is left. This is up.
This is pick up. This is right. Down.
Left. Button. Nope. Button. Try jumping.
There you go. You got your clip. You
might have to send it in the control
menu. Ah, whatever. Alright, gravel,
cobblestone. It's not actually that
big of a deal. It really is not. That
kind of sucks though. Alright, I got meat.
Let's get that in here. You die, right,
if you don't eat.
Keep the dirt. Keep the sand. Just fucking
throw this in the trash.
Uh, these are almost broken. I don't
know. I need more cobblestone.
Okay, this is, this is spartar.
That wasn't me almost puking. That was
me just burping. Everything's fine.
Wood. Let's go. I'm just gonna get
this shit. I'm gonna cut down every
tree.
And I'm not gonna replant them. I
don't want them here. I'm gonna, I'm
gonna plant all the trees over there.
Okay, I'm gonna get like maybe 30 or 40.
Probably 30 to 50 more full trees.
Can't, Microsoft owns this company now.
Can't I just pay some money?
Like 15 bucks to already have leather
fucking jackets on
and already have, what is that noise?
I don't know. Yeah, like where's my
like 12 dollar? You don't have to
cut a tree down anymore.
I'd buy, I'd buy it twice. Times two
speed.
Okay, that's good. Did I get them all?
Wood tools.
I know, I know. I'm fucking terrible.
Wood. He's using wood tools.
What is that? What is this thing? Is
that a fish?
This fish in Minecraft? How long ago
was this put in?
What happened to that guy? It is a
fish.
That's so cool. Can you deserve
fishing rod? I thought that was an
error.
Like a source, a source engine error
spinning around.
They come up with a massive ocean
update, really.
That's pretty cool. Punch the fish.
No, not now. That's too busy.
Maybe in like a little bit, hold on.
All right, I need,
I need, I just need stone. Just get me
stone.
There's my stone cavity right here.
Just give me a bunch of it.
This is gonna break.
Is that, I need to make it stone
pickaxe. Just go quick.
With a bed, you need to be even
shorter.
Yeah, I'm too tall to ride that ride.
I know, right?
Crazy. Fish? No. All right, let's get this
going here.
No, not what there is. I need sticks.
Fuck.
I'm safe. Am I safe in the house?
That's
a glass of milk. Why does the moon
look like that?
Why is the moon a fucking rectangle?
All right, um, here we go. Just make
a ton of these.
Can I do this faster? I guess just by
tapping it.
I have, what's the fun to make this
happen instantly with everything?
Just, I'm gonna have to go in the
controls and see what it is.
Not now though, I'm only gonna week.
All right, so now let's get some,
what the hell is that?
No, I just want, I just want some
sticks.
All right, they have to be on top
of each other.
20 sticks, that sounds good. All right,
give me some good tools now. Now I
can
break iron, right? Let's make two of
these.
No, that's the worst item in the
game.
All right, let's make a sword. Gonna need
that.
And, all right, looks fine.
Put the sticks back and throw the,
actually no, these are extreme backups.
I need them.
Cobblestone, put it up here. All right,
I'm ready. Let's go. Get in the bed.
No, I'm not, I'm not, I know this,
the trick here, guys. If I get in
this bed, they're gonna be standing
over me.
They're gonna be hovering over my
face.
I have to sleep with my knife out.
That's, that's old. I thought if you were
sleeping out in the open, then monsters
just spawned like in your
face. No, I know it skips the night,
but that doesn't happen anymore.
They patched that out. That was a
reason why I quit Minecraft.
War, Warcraft server mod. Why do I
have a Warcraft mod? What?
Why do you have Warcraft? I do not
have that.
No, that's not it. Let me be very,
very, very clear. There's not a joke
reveal there.
This isn't like, oh, he's just
pretending to play vanilla fucking
Minecraft,
and all of a sudden the sorcerer is
going to show up, and he's going to
start casting fucking spells at people.
No.
Everyone thinks that's, but that's,
no. I'm sorry, guys. You're going to be
really disappointed in like 20
minutes.
All right, let's go on an adventure.
And by adventure, I mean let's just
go break stuff until I find diamonds,
and then we're going to stop playing.
What do you say? I need to leave a
remember trail here.
Yeah, I'm like a dog, guys. I need to
have this.
Okay, so if I just, just follow the
fucking
Hansel and Gretel trail. Here we go.
Let's go right here. I'm going right
here.
Nipro. I didn't get a show.
Don't matter. I don't even need it.
Here it is.
Got it. This is it, right? What is
this? This is,
this is that, is that what I need?
No. It's like little coal pieces,
right?
No, this is like the easiest
resource in the whole game,
because then I can make torches.
Oh, I remember this song. What did this,
what a nostalgia stream this really
turned out to be.
Guys, remember, remember when you were
three years ago? Who are you? Okay, let
me, like look, look, look, look. Hold
on.
I'm 39. Listen, this is, I'm, how
many viewers in here?
Like 4k? There's probably at least,
people probably only are at this
stream because it's Minecraft, and it's a
great fucking game.
I'm gonna stop swearing. I remember
when I was 11,
like 10 years ago. Wasn't that long
ago? Absolutely not.
Change the FOV. What do you mean the FOV?
Is the FOV bad? What's wrong with the
FOV?
Wait, hold on. You mean like in here?
Dynamic FOV?
What, what a fog start, where is it?
The FOV on the webcam. Why did you
decide to play Minecraft? Because I
lost a bet,
and I'm going to be very salty
about it. What a messy closet.
That's just an optical illusion. He's
answering the FOV prayers.
Well, is it a, is it a, I don't see it in
the menu.
Performance? Chunks? Other?
Max frame rate? View bobbing off? We use
bobs?
Dynamic FOV is not the same. It's not
in the video settings.
It's in the actual VR settings.
Stereo rendering. Stereo rendering?
Mirror display?
Hold on, back it up. HUD, head HUD.
Hide HUD. World scale.
Locomotion. Controls?
Let me just see, yeah, this is quick
commands. Crosshair size.
Maybe it's scale. Oh, wait, wait, wait,
hold on.
Rotation? No. FOV comfort reduction?
Shrink? Shrinks the field of view while
moving? Can help? No.
That's not it. It's under controls.
Sensitivity. Touchpad mode. Auto jump
for mouse.
There is no FOV. You guys are just
fucking with me.
Turn down the, it's actually on the
vibe.
Turn up the brightness.
I'm trying to do this nostalgia trip
for all of us 40 year olds that when
they were 11, 30 years ago when they
played this game,
and what I was going to say, I might
even talk in the right direction,
what I was going to say is the
reason why I said that comment is
because it's probably people that I
hear that I love Minecraft and are
like
love this shit and they don't watch
these streams
so I'm gonna stop saying bad things.
This is a nice house. I think I'll
keep this one.
All right, I'll turn the brightness
up. I'll at least do you that.
How do I do that? Dynamic lights?
Quality shaders? Oh, dog that's my
entire IP address.
It's every IP I've ever had. Anybody
know where this is?
Am I blind? No, I- okay. Brightness,
moody.
I see- I see the- I see moody.
I don't- that's not a-
this doesn't even do anything.
Fucking Minecraft VR. I almost just
clicked that thinking that you guys
were going to appear.
All right, let's go back. I'll put
brightness up to like plus 20.
There you go. Now everybody can see.
Now everybody can have so much fun.
Oh boy, Minecraft. Remember we did
that pit cross level that we cheated
and now he has to play this? That's
why he's here.
This actually is- this is really cool.
Like if- I'm not gonna fuck around.
This is actually really cool.
Okay, don't- I'm gonna hurt the fucking
vibe.
Here we go. Can I please get back to
what I was doing now?
Just give me- ooh, we found ourselves
a cavern.
This is what you play for. All right,
there it is. There it is. There it is.
There it is. There it is.
This is gonna kill me. Oh shit, is this-
will I die from this?
This is really interesting like this.
I just get this and then that was a
big chunk, right?
Is that it? That's all that was here?
Oh fuck, look at that. Oh well, I'm
getting like Warcraft stones.
Do I actually have a mod of stuff? Why
am I getting the Warcraft stones?
That's a mod, right? That's like
mag- mana?
It's a joke. It's a- I'm kidding. It's a-
I'm making that up.
I know what it is. It's experience
points.
Oh, my germ is getting like real
salty lately.
What's going on with that?
I haven't watched the streams in like a
few weeks. Germa's like really salty.
What was that? Okay. Oh, where?
Holy shit, that's so much worse in VR.
Jesus.
I got his gallbladder. Okay, I need to
make-
I'm gonna make some torches here.
Finally, I have light. All right, close
this up.
Wow. Oh, turn the brightness up,
Jeremy.
I can't see, Jeremy. He's looking
real salty, ain't he, Jeremy?
Human fingers. I know it's here. I see
it.
Is that it? Do you think they'll be
talking about Minecraft?
That's not a real wall. Uh, do you
think they'll be talking about
Minecraft as like one of the greatest
human inventions
in like a hundred years or something?
Do you think like kids,
like a hundred years from now, this
will be in a textbook?
I think it will be. I really do. I
really think they'll be talking about
this. Like, there'll be the,
you know, the invention of the water
fountain wheel
and then like the washing machine
Minecraft. They'll all be in a row.
This goes really- all right, there's a
creeper down there.
Is that- no, that's not a creeper.
What the hell is that? Is that one-
that's one of those bow skeletons,
right?
I can't reach them mice. What the
fuck is that?
Is there bats? They- what else is in
this game?
All right, I'm gonna be- there's so
much shit down here.
That does just hurt my fucking neck and
back.
I don't think it's worth me doing this.
Let me just go over here, get up the
sword.
Look at all this shit. Okay, hold on.
Diamonds. This goes so deep.
I'm almost out of pickaxe fluid.
All right, it's time to go back up. I
gotta go back up.
Almost. I got plenty though. That's
good.
Let me get them all before it
breaks. Good. Okay,
time to get out of here. I hear
water right there.
What the hell was that? Why did a
horror movie door just open?
Is it a dungeon? All right, I'm gonna
remember this then. Remember this.
All right, let's go up. I- I can't go
up.
I have to- I have to make a crafting
bench down here.
No, I have a secret one. Okay,
never mind. I heard a car.
All right, let's go- let's get the
hell out of here.
I can get a couple of these if I
really want. I'm doing that the
worst possible way.
Might- might as well get them all,
right? This has got to be some kind
of record of
coal in one spot. It just never ends.
Oh, we unveiled the secret iron. Go on,
is that it?
That's it. All right, I guess go up
here.
I see- there's dirt right there, which
means I'm at land,
where I will be in a second. The best
part of Minecraft is when you come
out of the sewer hole.
Ugh! Uh, and you just look around and
see where you are.
Uh, okay, a little bit more. Now let's
see where we're gonna end up.
How far did- uh, down did I go?
What? I can't be that much further.
Uh-oh. Where's my- where's my trail? Where's my trail?
Where was that? That was real cool.
Where- okay, where- where's my trail?
Right there.
Oh my god, I'm dead! Oh my god, I'm dead!
Oh, go! What's happening? Go!
Okay, here we go. Cook. Eat. I got
seven out of ten.
All right, let me- let me go- hold on.
Let's, uh, no, no, no, no, no. What do I need?
Focus. Focus, Mike, focus. Don't say
your real name, though.
People will fucking know. Don't know who you are.
All right, let's just make a fucking bunch of these.
I'm gonna make 64 of them. Perfect number.
All right, now I need to- I gotta put them in here.
So give me the hell out of here. That's all I want. Just enough so I can see
what the hell I'm doing later. All right, where's that meat?
I need to cook the meat in the furnace, so let's get that meat.
Okay, put it down here. Gotta eat the egg sack.
There we go. Perfect. Why is this screen flashing? It's because I'm
dying. Once I have a couple of cooked
meats, I'll be just fine. For instance, how do you eat it?
You actually have to put it in your mouth, though. Okay, um,
don't kill it. Is that rare? Were the squids- I think they were squids
when I played before. I don't think I can really remember.
All right, let's move. Let's- I gotta make some gear.
Let's make some iron helmets. All right, this is just a joke.
Why is there no sell button? How come- why can't I have like a little
thing over here that I can just drag and it just sells it?
All right, get the spider sack thing out of here.
Wheat seeds, oak saplings, get out of here.
All right, I need to make a bunch of shit. All right, I'm gonna make my
house out of- I'm gonna make the floor out of wood.
And the walls out of stone. Get all this. What the hell?
Andesite? D.O. Wright? What are these? The new materials?
I'm gonna hold on to them just in case I need them. I need- let's make
some shit. So I need sticks. Let's go over here.
All right, we got- just make a bunch. Now let's go with
one, two. I'm going to make- oh, you have to smelt the iron into bars,
right? We need to start that process. Come
here. Go for it. And then I can make iron
pickaxe, iron sword, iron shield, iron armor. So, did you see any good
movies? D.O. Wright, Andesite, and Granite are
cosmetic stones. Okay. You can dual wield? Why am I in my swim
trunks? Guys, it's a nice day today. And
I didn't go swimming. I wanted to though.
How did something get in my eye? How is that possible?
How is it possible that something got in my eye? I was locked in. I was
pressured closed in here. How long has it been? Have I
been playing Minecraft for an hour? I've been in Minecraft VR for an
hour and six minutes. What the fuck?
Yeah, I've been having fun. Told you, I'm gonna get to diamonds.
I'm gonna make a diamond pickaxe. Then I'm gonna swing as hard as I can down
through my stomach in an uninstalled game. All right.
That was weird. Oh, I need water too. Where's my-
Can somebody guide me? Recipe for disaster. Recipe for disaster. Recipe for disaster. Recipe for disaster.
I need a fucking straw. I need a tube. Drinking is really hard when you
can't see. Why? We do it so often. We do it every day.
Thousands of times a week. Why is it so hard to do anything?
Where's the other iron? Right there. 14. Let me get this.
Close this up. What? Just happened. Green's
tea sip has made the advancement. Why is this in my other hand?
How do I get that out of my hand? How do I take this off?
Maybe do I want- How do I get this off? Okay.
Let me- I don't like that. Is there a reason why I can't grab this?
No. What happened? What did I do? Too far away?
I don't think- No. They usually have the cursor. It's in the slot.
Yeah, but- Okay. Ready? See? Open the furnace. Cursor's gone.
It's your finger. No, it's not. Did the game lose focus? I don't think so.
I didn't- It did. I don't know how. I told you.
Can we get a round of applause for VR, Josh? This is my favorite song.
All right, so let's make some good tools.
Over here. So let's do the most important one.
Solar paneling. I'm gonna make two of these.
What- This is a helmet, right? This is a chest piece?
What's the chest? I know this is legs. Or I thought it was.
All right, should I make boots? Should I make- Should I make tools first?
I'm gonna make tools first. I don't care if it's wrong.
I might never see iron ever again. Extreme backup.
Make another sword. Another pickaxe. I have three pickaxe- three iron pickaxes.
I have two right now. And I also- I want a shovel, too.
I want two shovels. And- Wait, wait, wait. What are you doing? What's going on?
What's going on with my axe? What's wrong? What's wrong?
What's going on? You only need two- I'm fine. I'm good.
I use the shovel a lot. Okay, so that's
one, two, three. One, two. Let's get this down here.
I'm not going to use that right now. All right, storage.
Is it an iron pick? Yeah. Put the the deal right of the shit in here.
Put the iron in there. I'm gonna keep the meat on me.
I'm gonna keep, oh, some coal. Not all of it, just in case something horrible
happens. Eleven. That's fine. I'm gonna put that
there. I got this here. Sticks. Don't need them.
Birch. Planks. Sand. Don't need sand anymore. Don't need dirt. Get them out
of here. Let me just get rid of these.
What was it? It was like- it was some weird button. I did it before.
There it is. Okay. Time to build the house. You ready?
You ready for the most boring part of this whole stream? Or it could be fun.
I'll do it quick. Don't worry. I thought those were all monsters.
Oak. Cobblestone. Let's at least get a nice floor.
I can't believe he doesn't even have a texture pack. Unbelievable.
Use your shovel. I know. I know. I know. I know. I know. I know.
That's why I made two. This is sick. Really not bad. Not, not bad.
Just as a method to my madness. Just wait. Clear this out.
It's not gonna be perfect, but at least look alright. There, there. Shit just
floats, right? Yeah. Yeah. Is it all-
Should I just keep- should I have the bodies down here?
No, no, no, no, no. Don't sleep. Leave the bed. Not yet.
What are you doing? Get- Alright. Looking good.
Okay. How do you- how do you even like do
Minecraft commentary? How do I even like say what it is?
Okay, there we are. We got wood here now, folks. Alright.
Looks pretty good. Hey, did I tell you I had jury duty?
Yeah. Here's a kind of chair. Ah, it don't matter.
Does it matter if I don't have that here? Switch shovel.
Oh shit. Is it button on my hand to it?
Alright. Holy shit. People must so support.
Wow. This is- you can't do this in regular Minecraft.
You can? Oh. Well. Oh, well. No, don't do that. Alright, that's good.
Something I think a lot of you guys might underestimate
or overestimate is the fact that if I have a piece of green here that I'm
not- it's okay. I'm gonna be fine. I'm not gonna look- I'm not
gonna look at chat. I'm not gonna look. I already know what
you're saying. I already know what you're saying. I don't need to look.
How do I use this? This is slower than doing it with-
This is slower. I should be doing sword in this hand.
No, I didn't see the short joke. I saw that I'm not using my shovel.
What the- that- why do I have two ice creams?
All I need is one. And why the fuck is this one not chocolate
is what I want to ask. Kill fish. I got it. Look at that house.
That's worth a million. That'll be worth a million someday.
A million of what? A million racy's pacy's.
So let's- it's not done. Don't say it's bad until it's done.
Just wait for my walk-in closet in my open kitchen.
Just saying. I'm not even gonna look at the chat. I don't even need to.
Why would I need to look at it? I already know how to do this. I don't
know how to play this. Guys, I think I'm moving forward. I
think I'm gonna have no chat. Yeah, I think- what do you think?
Shit. I mean now I'm just- I'm just playing Minecraft.
This is what I do every time. Every single time I've ever opened this
game. It goes the same way. No differences.
This is the same house that I make. It's only just dirt on the top,
wood on the bottom, cobblestone on the sides. And then I put a door on
and then I go down and I look for diamonds. I've groundhog day'd this
scenario probably 40 times. The only- the only
this time I'm actually in it. I'm here right now. So like I said
there's a lot of the potential like this. Some
you know young kids here right now. Made a reference to it before.
I'm not that good. I'm pretty- I do some like inter- I'll make like a
kitchen eventually here. But I don't expect me to like know
how to do the lanterns or the
electric stone cubes, redstone. I don't know how to do that. I'm out
of stone. I'm actually out of stone. All right.
Now I'm good to go for another adventure. I got meat.
This is what I like to do. Hey kids this is how I do it. Find a corner of
your house and turn it into the basement. And then
the basement goes down into the mine. This is how I do it. So let's go over
here. You know I'm gonna just take this
off. Like this- this- this is not happening.
I'm gonna be honest with you. So for instance now I'm gonna- there's a
front door. Open. Here we are. This leads down.
It's gonna go down like this. This is my basement. See we're
gonna get some steps. Move it more forward again. Another
step. What is that? Okay. This is gonna be
paved. I'm gonna pave that whole thing.
Here we go. One, two, three, four, five.
Go down again. Make sure you bring enough light.
I can take that one back. All right. One more.
Right. Are you following along? You following along here?
There we go. What do you think? Too deep. Too deep.
Keep torch in left hand. That's not a bad idea.
Resident sleeper. There's 31 torches in my hand.
Holy shit. I didn't even know you could do that. Look.
I lost a bet. That's why I'm here. I think that's good for now.
This way. Gonna carve out a little section.
A little more over here. How you doing? Sleepy yet?
How you feeling? You okay? Got a headache? You got a running nose?
Fucking sorry to hear that. Oh sorry. I'm flipping sorry to hear that.
All right. Let's keep going. This is where it gets interesting at.
Uh what? Negative like 20 below. I didn't dig straight down.
I clearly came down on a little staircase. Don't be afraid to say you
like this and you're enjoying it. I am. This is fun. You know I'm just
I'm just talking shit guys. That's all. Don't take anything I say seriously.
I'm just kidding around. I'm just talking about. Never mind.
Okay. Actually I won. I hear something.
We're getting to a point where I need to get prepared with a sword.
Is that a special song? And I think it's behind one of these doors.
That's it's kind of stone. What is that? Granite. They had so many different
cosmetic rocks. Can something happen?
Stop. Calm down. Calm down. Where's my little like
uh seismograph meter? Don't I have one of those?
Look up. Are those motorcycles in my room?
I'm in VR. I can't tell. Damn it. I gotta get up there.
Oh shit. There's even more. I just realized something. This was not
intentionally planned or anything but the next game that I'm gonna play
is having a realization about something. You'll see.
Oh no. That was the thing breaking. Okay. How about
uh I feel like everyone might leave on the next game.
Everybody came here because like oh Minecraft VR. Cool.
I don't get lost down here. Those are more for breadcrumbs than
anything else. Am I playing this on peaceful? You know it's on survival.
At least it should be. I'm playing this on creative mode.
Always get away back up. We're getting deep. I hear running water.
Right. I think I'm in the ocean right now.
This is baffling tile. What is this? What kind of
rock is that? Does it have a name? Get it.
Okay. Oh I was already down here. All right.
There was all kinds of shit. There's more of uh that whatever the hell that is.
God damn it. I tried. Light. I want more light.
I'm going all the way down. Hey. Oh I'm fine. Can you come up here?
I'll just farm him. Come on up. Was there a baby?
There's a baby zombie. Where's the baby? Where'd the baby go?
No don't do that. Jesus. If I drop down there I'm just gonna die.
What? What the where? I'm so confused. What happened? Where? I just got
something. Nothing even hit me. Why am I wearing bathing shorts? That's not
important. Hey. Hey. See you later kid.
Double cigar. Please think it was funny. Please think it was funny. Please
think it was funny. Please think it was funny. Please think it was funny.
Yes. All right I'll come back to that. Is it gone?
Yeah. Made it out alive. Minecraft VR. Not even a problem.
I can smell diamonds. I think I'm gonna fall into a diamond pit right here.
How can you tell when you're close to diamonds? Look at how they're even
deeper. Wow. Do those hurt you? Or are they just
annoying? Found it. Oh my god there was one in my face.
Oh no it hurt. God. Minecraft is really just a horror game.
In VR it's just scary monsters around corners.
Have I been here before? I don't think I've been down here before.
That really did feel like I was playing and
somebody in chat was just spawning stuff in front of me.
Like I have twitch enabled and it's spawn creeper.
No. I'll take more iron. I've missed a bunch of it too. It's been
panicking. What is that? No. Sick. Okay. Might as well get it all. For one
second I thought I was back in my basement and was like how did that
happen? I can't wear it. I hear the music.
That means I'm getting close right to something. Doesn't the music start
uh trigger when you get near something cool?
I'm going in too deep. I'm going in too deep. I have to stop. I gotta- I don't
know where I'm gonna end up. I'm gonna end up in a completely
different place. I gotta go back. Did it keep going? I need to- I need
to know where I am. I'm- I'm gonna be lost. Seriously I have to put
these everywhere because I'll fucking forget.
Not gonna lay without you anymore. Yeah. Yeah. You're hiding on me. It's fine.
All right. I'm almost out of- I- I can't keep going.
I'm almost out of power. Got it. Redstone. There it is.
Now I can not know how to make anything because I have no idea.
What's this? Bluestone. All right.
Bear back. I'm gonna go uh I'm gonna take this so bear back.
First rule. I know. I know. I only did- I did it like three times. I haven't done
that the entire game. I dug down three times. I didn't do
that the other times. The one time that I do it. I do it
like twice. No that's not even like-
What if- I'm fucking so stupid. I was down so deep too. I should have known
better. I haven't played uh whatever. Don't dig straight down. But it's
different when you're uh- I can't even give an excuse.
I'll be right back. I'm gonna take piss because of water in my face.
Refill my cup after I drink it. There are literally shirts that say that.
I know. I thought I had at least like one or two seconds to do it.
Oh whatever. I'll be right back. I can get back there. My stuff is still okay
right? It burnt in the one square. It had
to be the square right there too. I'm so embarrassed. God damn it.
Because that's like okay. That happened to people
four or five years ago and that was like oh what don't dig down in
Minecraft. It's 2013. Watch this guy burn because he
fell down in a cube in Minecraft. Oh by the way no it's not 2011.
It's 2019. Uh did somebody just give a hundred bucks right now?
I just pulled my headset off. I'm looking at a hundred dollars
from CabBadger. That is a fantastic shirt Jeremy. Where'd you get it?
Uh it was a gift. I actually don't know. But thank you CabBadger for the
hundred dollars and Jerma lied about Minecraft VR. I can't say that now.
Thank you for the community subs. Thank you. Yeah it was gifted to me.
Are we gonna go swimming later? No. I even did the JermaCraft thing.
All right one more thing. I just want one more try. I just want to get-
hold on. Let me just get down. I'm gonna do
one more try and then we're gonna move on.
Like I'm so pissed off that that's how it ends. People are gonna watch
that clip and it's gonna be like- the people are just gonna shake their heads
and be like oh well that good- good job.
How many did I go down? How many did I go down?
One, two, three, four, five. You guys let me do that six times?
I can't believe I did that six times. I just got complacent.
All right can I- what is this putting me? Your house is missing.
All right can- is really every single
solitary item burnt completely. Every single item is burnt
in that one square. It's not even hard to get that shit.
Oh Tetris. No it's really not. Plus didn't I save some-
I saved some stuff didn't I? There it is. We're going back in there.
Look I'm about to sell somebody a watch.
Oh let me see the diamond on that. Let's see.
It looks like it's gone through a little bit of
erosion. Hold on. 250. I have a request. Lose the shorts.
All right. All right yeah I just pulled it out of my fucking ear again.
Let's go. What is- something's pulling my hair.
Explain the shorts. There is no- something is odd here.
What is doing this? I don't- what do you mean- there is nothing to explain.
I still can't believe you did that lava thing. Look it- it's a- look I still
have iron. I can make a sword or I can make a-
probably make a shovel. No I'm gonna make a sword. And then I
can make- everything's fine. Don't worry.
Let's do it. That's why you make these.
Not total- actually it's probably for the best that that happened.
I had so much trash. All right now- hmm.
Any shovels? Where's the audio? I feel like I'm missing audio here. Okay.
My torches. Fuck. All my torches are gone.
That should be good. Maybe- maybe uh- no. I'll get some more.
I know that's fine. 64. Maximo. I'm going back in there. I don't have
any food but it's all right. What the hell? All right let's go.
Are you ready? Back in there. Back to get something.
Salvageable. We haven't seen a solo in stream
juke for so long. Bring woo- wood. What? Bring wood?
I don't have any food. It's all gone. All right I guess I could just go kill
something. I got a nice weapon here. I just
need like a cow or something right? Perfect. Okay food. Okay we're good.
Don't kill it? How am I supposed to get food? I got plenty of food now.
Food. 12 o'clock. I'm not gonna drown. Now I'm gonna store this food. I'll cook
some of it and then I'm time to go. How do I go faster? Okay fishing.
What the hell was that? Do they have like drowned zombies?
All right that's good. Time to cook it. Back here.
I'm going down there one more time. I'm gonna try to go down to where I
was and then get- and try to get diamonds.
This is actually pretty fun. You're doing shots of tequila for me.
Oh that's right. It's St. Patrick's Day. I'm playing Minecraft. What are you
doing? What are you doing on St. Patty's Day? How are you?
Bone meal. Raw salmon. Raw cod. All right let's do- let's cook the
chickens. Cook the chickens and eat the eggs
and have two full chickens and two sammons.
That sounds good to me. This is the sad song.
Why would Sour Please be here? I'm gonna eat that egg. How do I eat
the egg? It's raw? You can eat raw eggs in this game. I
thought you could. I can't eat a raw egg? Says who?
You don't eat eggs. And now I'm gonna knock down one tree
and get some wood in my inventory and then I'm going down there and
that's- that's it. But if it happens down there it's
over. I didn't even build a whole damn house.
It's an open floor plan guys. All right let's get some wood.
I'm gonna eat this. Let's go get some wood and then that's it.
Time to go adventure again. Down to the hill.
All right let's go. Just in case I need it for anything.
All right let's store this. Um I- I got a full chicken. I got plenty of
food. Torches. Get this out of here. Get
the rotten meat out of here. Kelp get it out of here.
Good. What's this? White wool. Don't need it.
Here we go. See I didn't do it here. I only did it in one
fucking place. I got all this dug out. What?
Oh shit. How did I even manage to do this?
Then I went down here. Right. Let's get some more padding for this
ball. All right I'm remembering. And then there
was a big fight down here. I panicked. I ran
that way. What the fuck? Okay um I don't know where I went.
I see an arrow. Where do I want to go back? Why do I want to go back? That's a
really actually- that's a great new point to go from here.
All right perfect. Build the inventory back up.
This way. That way. Let's just keep going across.
So I'm- I'm down pretty deep. Maybe I should put a bed down here.
Just keep progressing. I'm gonna go down.
I'll do that again. That shit's not gonna happen more than once.
Hello? Uh okay. Thank you. Does that mean something?
What does that mean? I'm not gonna get misdirected in this right?
And you're wondering why I brought so many tools? This is why.
Dump. When do I get to the- I'm gotta be close to getting to the bottom of
the world here. What cube is the bottom of the
world? Like cube 300 right? It's like 320 or something.
It's going so deep. First of all I'm-
I need to like- I'm about to- I can see there's a wall right there.
Well there's iron. Thankfully. I made it. I'm at the bottom of the world.
Yeah you can't dig through this right? I don't have an iron pickaxe.
Fuck. Smell the iron? All right yeah. Good idea.
Okay. Iron. All right here we go. Tools.
Why do I have these shorts on? Can we move on from the shorts?
Can we get away from the shorts here? I need-
I need a pickaxe for that. Do that right now.
One, two, three, and then here we go. I need a shovel. No I don't.
Um what's that? Armor? I'm gonna do a helmet
or a shield. How do we make a shield? I've never seen that before. I've never
made one. The shield is 10 shovels. 10 above
bedrock. Just open the green book. Ooh.
Isn't that fancy? So it's planks and then an iron
bar. Okay let's make it. Okay. Shield.
Now let's make helmet. Suit up. Yep. Helmet and we're gonna do with five.
Can I do anything with five? Boots. Things are looking up.
Things are looking up. I got a full chicken here. All right let's get out
of this. Boots. Helmet. Shield.
Shield. This shield. This is a cutting board.
Is this a stamp? How am I supposed to hold it like this?
I feel like this is an old-fashioned flash photography ball.
All right that's pretty cool. Put these torches back
and I'm good. Get the shovel down there.
I'm ready. I'm ready. I think I'm ready. Am I ready?
Block arrows with the shield. Nice. Make an iron bow. God damn it is what
they said. I can't. I don't have enough. I don't
have enough. I can't do it. Shears or flint and steel. That's
not real. I'm ready. I got chicken. I got my
sword. Is that this blocks my whole inventory?
All right I'm ready for minecon. You know what's the what's the chance that
there's lava in here? It's pretty high right? No get me
the fuck out of here. Get me out of this. I'm not doing
this. Okay safe. All right I'm good. Let's get the
hell out of here. I'm gonna go like up that way. Oh
god damn it. Okay um I'm gonna poke a hole in the
walls and I'm so paranoid about lava now after that happening before.
I'm just gonna stand up and like poke fucking holes in the walls.
Clear a nice section here. I'm also not going to use this
for just this bullshit. I'm gonna use this. It's a waste of resources.
All right let's switch back. Nice. What am I gonna do with this stuff?
It's not like it matters. I'm not gonna spend like all day in here.
Okay don't do that either. Right that's bad too. That's just as bad as
going down. What's going on up there? Nothing.
Okay it's safe. Kind of. Kind of safe. All right am I- I'm on the diamond level
right? Down here. What the fuck was that?
What the hell just- is that ASCII in 2019?
Oh wait have we got Justin TV? Oh is it Justin.tv or are we Twitch now?
Okay I'm ready. I'm gonna go this way. I'm at the diamond level.
Is it all I need? Is it all I want? I just want to get it and I want to
make a diamond sword in the diamond pickaxe and that's it. And then I'm
done. And then I could say I've done it all.
I've done it all. I've traveled to Japan. I've been to
France. I fucking- I fucking have a giant
empire of merchandising right? I sold like fucking
422 shirts. Empire. I played Minecraft VR got diamonds.
It's more than that by the way. No wrong. Can you imagine
running a fucking empire clothing company?
What's your day-to-day life like? Do you like hold up shirts and you're like
ah it sucks and you like tell them to start over?
Come on Minecraft. Where the hell are the diamonds? Press
F3 and see if you are at level 16 or below.
Um I- I can't do that right now. Iron. I might be able to make some more
stuff. Maybe a blouse. Maybe a t-shirt. Is
that it for- give me like a diamond patch.
That's all I want. I don't care. I don't even know how to get back to my
house. Do you think I care about what's going on at my
residence right now? No. That- but it wasn't even a house.
This is weird. Why is this here? This is dirt.
Okay. I got a straight shot. Is dirt this low?
Why is there dirt down here? Okay. I think we're good.
I'm so confused. Why is this here? Oh my god. Eat.
Eat. Eat. Eat. Eat. That's pretty good. Yeah!
Resident Slaver. What is this? What does that look different?
All right. I'm out of here. I'm done. I'm just gonna do it or I'm just gonna
smelt it right now. I'm not waiting. There. Eight diamonds.
Look at those diamond eggs. And put that down.
64 redstone. Put it in there. Uh diamond axe. That's not what I want.
Diamond pickaxe. Got it. There it is.
Diamond sword. Diamond hoe. There it is. And she built. Yeah everyone's
talking shit. You talking shit about my fucking gonzo blade?
I did it. All right. I beat Minecraft. That was fun.
I didn't get like- I didn't use my diamond sword though. I can't just
not- I can't just give up now. Diamond sword. Look how fast it is.
What about it in real time? Way better.
You gotta be close though. That's the only thing. In before lava.
Uh I'm gonna be some position. I can just run that way.
I want to find a cave system. This is dark. This is really fun though.
This is a whole other way to experience playing this game.
In three dimensions. Uh what's that? Houston.
We've got a cave. Where is it? Was it this way?
So one person said yes. I listen to you. To heal. I got full health.
We're not only supposed to play this for an hour. Well I did have to
get diamonds. How long have I been playing this? Did I
just lose track of all time? It's almost three hours. Holy shit.
I'm- I am just me and I'm enjoying myself.
I'm gonna have to wake up a little bit though for the next uh game that's
coming up here in a minute once I find uh anything.
Is it- is it- no I'm safe. I'm safe. It's fine.
Everything's fine. It's right here. It's this block right here.
Come on kid. We gotta get out of here.
What does the Indiana Jones say? I'm surrounded by lava.
It's all here. Good thing. Good thing. I think it's actually up there. Stop.
I hear noises. I can hear skeletons and shit.
Where are they? There's lava somewhere over here.
They might be in like three or four different places. I think they're above
me. There's something above me. All right. I'm a safe place. That would
have been fucking really bad. Really? Where are these?
To the right. Okay. Found it. How big is this? This is gonna
lead to a bunch bigger system right? The lava's flowing this way.
Does that mean anything? Oh it is still here okay.
I'm playing with fire here like actually. Am I trying to make this hard
on myself? I need a light. Come on give me- leave
me somewhere. Leave me somewhere. It ends. I- I'm
getting out of here. I have to leave. I gotta- I'm leaving. How on earth am I
gonna navigate my way out of here? I'm not gonna dig up into lava. If I do
I can make a run for it. That looks all right.
We're safe. We're safe for now. Oh come on.
Give me something. I hear water. I don't think I want that to happen.
I might just turn around and go the other way. This means that this-
they're waterlogged right? Okay. Safe. Safe. Let's keep looking.
There's a spider. That means that there has to be land. Where's the spider?
Something going on up there. Water? Is there water up there?
I still hear the spider. I should be fine.
All right this- oh my god. Get rid of this.
I have so much cobblestone. It's like someone hasn't been paying attention
right? Something up here. Getting closer.
I'm gonna open up what- and there's gonna be just a window of somebody's
face. This might be water right here.
I actually have to be very careful about this. Did I just punch somebody?
What? I'm very confused. I don't hear anything.
They were right here. It was almost like I was standing right in front of them.
Anybody got any ideas? All right. No. I gotta stop fucking around. I gotta go.
I have to go up. We're just going up. If I die, I die.
It's all right. I'm over a cave somehow. I should have enough time to
run if there's something horrible right there.
Okay. I ain't even dealing with you at all.
What are you doing? Oh. Oops. Did I just sneak around them?
I mean I know this. I don't know what I'm stepping on. No.
I can just go all the way around them. They cannot fit through that.
There's not somebody behind me. You have to be right here.
He's like right in front of my face. Jesus.
Goddamn diamond pit gas! What's this thing even worth? Come on.
Get down here.
What the fuck are they all doing here? What the fuck are you doing here?
There's one of those spawners up here, ain't there? I gotta eat.
Do I have any more food? This sucks. Okay. There's a
bow and arrow. Why did that not block it? Why did that not block?
It went through the shield. I'm gonna die. I need to eat again.
What's happening with food? How do I throw these away?
I don't want them in here. No! Don't touch. Don't. I made it. I think I've
been here. Have I been here before? I don't think.
No. I haven't. I think there's another one. Oh.
No. Not deep. I don't want to go deeper. Oh my god. This looks like.
This looks like man. This looks man-made. This looks man-made.
I think this is man-made. It's man-made. Is that man-made?
What? There's no more lava to worry about down here.
We'll be fine. Almost there. Almost there. Then I mean on
water. Get down! All right. I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine.
I, I, I'm fine. I have no idea. I have no idea what's going on with the back of my
head. What happened? What is it? What's,
what is this? Why is it doing this? I'm cheating right
now with my left eye. What's, what's going on? Is this going
down? What's this connected to? The cord is all the way up here.
What the fuck is this mess? How am I gonna get rid of this?
It was yanking me on the back of the head. Oh this is, this
is gonna take like 20 minutes to get out of this. I've been spinning around
that much. What was that? What was that? Why did
my house just fall down? Like what was that like crashing wood sound?
Where am I? Did I pull the cord out? I think I may have pulled a cord out.
Okay. Oh my lord. There's real tension here. I have to, I got to fix that
before we play another game. All right. What the hell happened?
Why am I, why is it just black? Am I a lot? I'm inside the wall. Okay
let's go back up. Am I dying? Come on. Go. Get up there.
Oh no. Where's my house? What's one of the four
horsemen doing here? What? What is that? That's rare?
What the fuck? Should I like go back and kill it?
It's split into, I don't even know where I am, where this is.
All right hold on. Let me take a look for a second. So
that's the creeper island. Is it that way? I don't know where my house is.
Where the hell was that? Maybe back, I think it was back here.
Down there. There he is. There he is. There they are. There they are. What do I do
about this? How do I do this? Okay. I'm gonna, what do I do? Run, grab stuff,
and then leave. I've got, I've got a diamond sword.
I have to at least try. Are there four of them?
What is he wearing on his head? What? There's a giant sea turtle?
Hello. You can, can you ride, you can, you can ride his back can't you?
Of course you can. No you can't. Where's my stuff?
You can't go in water right? No you can't. Come on you son of a bitch let's go.
Did you get everything? Most of it. Oh shit.
Damn. Gotta kill a fish and eat. Come here.
Should I try to go over that guy? Should I try to kill him? If I have full health
and it's just one, can I just bash his head in? I need more fish.
I'm going for him. Maybe if it's only one.
Oh fuck that's one of them. All right give me some more food.
Mind the like eyes of being blocked by my hair.
Don't I, I don't think I have one of those damn things.
No what are you doing? Give me the food. I want the food.
Ah. I'm gonna start healing now right? Good.
I'm gonna go after the ones over here. I feel like I can do it.
Because I had, there was like four of them at the same time. So that's why I
couldn't do anything about it before. Let me get some more food. Give it to
the boy. Oh my god I'm just hungry. I'm starving
the whole time. No. Give it. Am I supposed to go make
this food? I'm wasting so much time. They'll be there. See if I can get
this little school of fish. I got three.
Okay I'm good. Whatever. Just go. Back home.
Store the other shit that I have. Hey look I got another one.
Didn't even need to do anything. This makes me want to pick up
Minecraft again. Good way to de-stress. Yeah I know this is fun.
Get it. Don't let it just sit there. I would have moved on already.
But I'm just, I'm gonna do it. Might as well just do it.
Spend at least a few hours in here. Seems like they added a lot of
interesting stuff. That's the coolest part. Am I even
talking? I am. Weirdly enough I'm talking
right in the right direction. The last time I really gave any
care at all about this game. Had to have been at least four or five
years ago. I really wasn't into it that much
anyways. But coming back after all these years.
Hold that thought. There he goes. Coming back after all the years it just
seems like, like the sea turtles in the game.
That's odd. That's equally parts interesting and
like wow I'm surprised that they're still adding content to the game.
All right where where's my house? There it is.
This many years later. Is this a copy pasta?
It is now three hours in Minecraft. I'm surprised. Let me just fix this.
I'll go try to kill him and then we'll move on after that.
Let's eat. Get my shit together and I'm just gonna go
put up my hand. Oh all right. Food. I still got the shield still.
I can make some more armor which is good.
I don't think I have any. No god damn it.
I don't have any uh anything to make to burn this
oak. I have to use my like trees. I have wood yeah.
I don't have very much of it though. I need to make
look I have 23 iron ore. I might as well just get decked out.
Are they gonna despawn? Do I have to run back there quick?
They do so I gotta get the hell back there. I don't have time then.
Just put on. I got my clothes on right. I just gotta go over there and start
whacking them. My shield. Put it on. Armor.
There's no time. There's no time. He's there. This is the thing. They despawn.
One right there. One right there. I think there's another one. Let me get
a better view. Look at this one. What is that?
What is that? An Enderman. Right. Don't you need to look at them?
Wasn't I looking at them? Or are you not supposed to look at them?
It's one of those two. Don't look. I thought you were supposed to look.
Right. He came across the whole game. All right.
You. Is he still gonna be up there? Give me my stuff back.
Where's my sword? I have an arrow in the back of my head.
Just eat the raw salmon. Just twice. I don't care.
Whatever happens. Whatever happens happens. I'm going to
practice. I hear an explosion. All right. I'm going in.
Here we go. Where is he? Here we go. Through the trees. Through the bushes.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Good luck. I'm killing this one.
Where is he? Where is he? Motherfucker. Where'd he go?
Shit. Okay. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Oh fuck. Shit. Motherfucker. Did I do it? Did I do it? I think I
No. He jumped up. You already. You saw what happened. I don't need to explain it.
I gotta use the shield. When I used the shield last time, I just fucking killed me.
Oh, give me my stuff back. I'm blocking a minute. I had it.
I'm so upset right now. His body got up on the.
His body got up on the thing that I put up and he gave the perfect headshot.
That was it too. That was the one. I'm so sad about this. Look at that mess.
What am I doing? It's not funny. What are you doing?
I can still do it. Fuck food. Fuck everything. I'm gonna get up there.
I'm gonna get. Oh no. Don't look at me like that.
Okay. Here we go. I gotta make this jump. It's gonna be worth it.
I didn't fucking even jump. Un-fucking-believable. Video game.
Why didn't I jump? He's just perfect. He's perfect.
The cord is. I don't even. The cord is part of me now.
It's that. I did it. I did that. Where is he? Down here? He's right there.
Okay. I can do it with dirt. I'm trying this one more time.
Can I get my shoe? Nope. You have boots though. Here we go.
All right. Fuck you. Now you're dead.
Ah. Ah. Ah. Ah. Come on. It's right there. Get it.
Why can't I place the block? Stop. What the fuck is happening, Vi?
I gotta get on the other side. Oh, it's so hard to see.
You're looking far that. When I put my head down,
everything is blurred. Everything. It's so difficult to look down in any VR game.
I'm still alive? I got a better fucking idea.
Don't. Stop running. That's gonna drive me crazy.
Why do you keep doing that? I feel like I'm playing Fortnite.
This is just Fortnite. I'm playing Fortnite.
Bill, Bill, Bill, Bill. Bob 06
Come down here. Do it. I'm setting a goddamn looting tunes track for you.
You coming?
Get in right here and then I'm gonna go bang, bang.
I'm gonna fucking scream in a second.
Okay, hold on. I gotta plan this. Get in here.
Come on.
Look, I'm over here. I'm right here. Don't you see me? Hey, hey, where is he? Where'd he go?
Oh, that's fine, that's fine. Stay there. Stay there. Right there. Anything else blocking his way?
You can't get in there! You can't fit in there. He needs two blocks. I don't have...
He's never gonna fucking get in here. He's never gonna go like this. Is he in? Is he in? Is he in?
Oh my god, oh my god. Don't move. Nobody move. Nobody fucking breathe. Don't breathe.
Nobody breathe. Nobody breathe. Nobody breathe. Don't breathe. Can you hear me talking?
I got him. I got him. I got him. I got him. I got him. I got this motherfucker. He's done.
I got him. I got him. I actually got him. I trapped him. I trapped him! I did it!
Wait, what about over here? Stop it, Vibe. No, it's so dark. Oh my god, I hate this thing.
Get better goddamn technology for Christ's sake. It's cuz I'm putting my hand over my head.
Because I'm blind when I go like this. Is he in? Is he in? I can't tell. No, he's not.
The horse is dead. What? What do you mean the horse is friendly? What do you mean he's dead?
The rider is dead. So I can... Horse is not harmful. You sure? Oh man, are you sure about that?
So what do I do? What can I do? Oh wow. What happened? What happened? What happened again?
Goddamn better technology, I swear to god. What happened? I can't even... I didn't touch anything.
How would I suffocate in a wall? I didn't do anything. What happened? I gotta get back here now.
Why can I not touch any fucking thing on the screen? What? Why didn't it minimize the window?
I'm getting this fucking lobster, whatever it is. Quickly. Where is this way? Over here.
He's gonna get back over here. He's still there. We're fine. Slow down.
You guys are still questioning his sanity. So what can I do with this animal?
So, okay, I have... Do I, like, touch him? Can I pet him? How do I do this? Tame it.
Break the blocks. I need a saddle. Break roof. Break all the blocks. They're tamed.
Need a saddle. Break the blocks above him. Like up here. I don't need a saddle. Oh,
so much information. Touch him with an empty hand. The dirt blocks. That's wood. Like these.
Why do I need to get rid of those? What's he doing? Now ride it. What? Does he have a mind
of his own? I don't even have any items. I can't get out of here. What about my... What? No,
no, no, no. Don't do that again. This way. Out here. Wait, how do I get off? Grab
these shit. How do I jump off? How do you get off? Jump. I can't jump. I can't get off of
left shift. Okay, I got my sword. Okay, I'm ready. So, where do we go? That... I almost threw up
from that. I almost just fell down. Okay, I don't like how he moves out of his own.
How do I tell him to go? Go! Go! I need a saddle. What's going on with the world?
Oh, stop doing that. All right, do something! Can I... Will he go anywhere? Now you're
going to leave. You're a real... He's pointing at him. What happened to that guy? All right,
I need a saddle. Where's the crafting book? Saddle. How do I get him to come with me? Will
he come with me? Like, craft a lead and take him home. Oh, I need to find a saddle.
Oh, well, this was cool. At least I got to see it. Bye! Be free! Just spawn a saddle.
I... I don't... I... Pet the turtle. That was outrageous. Look, there's another one.
Well, that was cool. I gotta take a break. I gotta go get... I gotta go get a fucking drink.
That last 30 minutes kind of just killed me. I'm gonna grab a drink. I'll be right back.
Water. And I'm not even talking in the right direction. That's the rarest horse in the game.
At least I got to ride it. I got to ride it for at least a second. I got to put the coin
in in front of the fucking Walmart. All right, I'll be right back. We'll do another one.