Hey, what is going on everybody? Jermach here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, I'm gonna be playing as the Pyro using the Degreaser, the Flare Gun, and I believe the Neon Annihilator.
I didn't take it off from the Pyro Shark video, so it's just still on there. I don't think I kill anybody with it.
I don't think I do anything with it, it just kind of sits in the melee slot.
Today, we have something very, very interesting to discuss. A very, very crazy thing was just announced this past week by Valve, and it's Steam-related.
Those of you that don't know, there's gonna be a link in the description for you to check this out, because this is completely game-changing when it comes to gaming with your friends, your family members, and that sort of thing.
Steam has released an idea called the Sharing System. It isn't in beta yet, it's gonna be coming in beta soon, and essentially what this does is makes it so you can share your games with your close friends and your family members.
Now, you're probably wondering, well, what the hell are you talking about? You mean like somebody can sit next to me and like watch me play? No, no, no, no, no.
You give them access to your Steam library, and they can play all the games that you've pretty much ever bought on Steam. This includes single-player games, I'm sure it's gonna include multiplayer games.
I don't know what their restrictions are going to be, because this is, again, just been announced and no one's really sure exactly what's gonna be happening, but you give them access to your Steam library and they can play all of your games.
Now, what this means is that close friends of yours, if you buy a game and you want them to check it out, you don't have to log in with your Steam account on their computer and install it from there and log out and change your password later because you don't want your dickhead friend coming in and hacking your account.
That's gonna change. They can just have access to your games, and as long as you are not on your Steam account playing any games or logged into that same game, they can play anything they want that's on your Steam account.
And the reason why this is a little bit strange and sort of, I don't want to say unnecessary because this is a very cool feature, but it's gonna make people buy less games.
You know what I mean? Like, if you have a buddy that bought Bioshock Infinite, which is a solely single-player game, there is no multiplayer, there is no, oh, I want to jump in a server with a buddy of mine and play Bioshock.
No, you're gonna be able to play that game and get the whole experience of that game without paying a single dime, unless they have some type of requirement system where if a new AAA game comes out, you can't share it for like two or three months, which I think that's what's probably gonna happen because
Can you imagine if all your friends on your friends list, you went into like a pact with them and you said, oh, hey, I'll buy GTA V, you buy like Dinosaur D-Day 2, and he'll buy Super Mario 6.
That's not on PC, but you get the idea. And you all just share it with each other, and you spent like 60 bucks and you got four games.
Like, I'm sure they're going to have something in place where you can't do that, but still, the point still stands. It's a very strange feature to be announcing and a very cool one, and I'd like to get your guys' opinion on it.
So if you have anything to say about the new Steam trading, not Steam trading, Steam sharing, why can I not think of a damn word, then leave it in the comments below and kind of transitioning to this next topic.
It's part of the same topic, but the reason why they're doing this, I believe, is because of what Origin has decided to do.
If you don't know what Origin has decided, Origin is the EA kind of Steam competitor.
And what they decided to do is they said, okay, if you buy a game on Origin and you don't like it, you can return it and get your money back within a certain amount of time.
I believe it's like seven days or 14 days or something. I don't know the exact time, but I believe this is a direct result of the Origin refund system.
Because never before have you ever been able to do that. You've never been able to refund to return PC games.
That's been a huge thing ever since PC gaming was invented.
You would walk into GameStop, and this is all before Steam had any retail system. You couldn't buy anything online.
There was no online retailers where you could buy digital downloads of games. It was not really a thing yet.
And you walk up to the counter with your copy of Warcraft 3, and the guy behind the counter would tell you, oh, you know, you can't return this.
And you're like, well, why not? Well, it's because you could just copy the CD key down, return it, and have the thing installed on your computer.
So never was there ever a way to return PC games unless it was broken, unless you opened the box up and the disc was in like 11 pieces.
That was the only way you could ever return PC games. And Origin is kind of changing the game with that.
So I think this is really a direct result of Origin's moves, which I guess makes sense because Origin has kind of been like 10 rungs down on the ladder behind Steam.
And they're trying to find ways to bring themselves back up to get more people that want to use Origin.
And that's definitely one of the ways you can do that. So Steam, likewise, where there's competition, there's going to be compromises and there's going to be things are going to change.
Probably said to themselves, well, we should probably do something similar to stay competitive, to stay as number one, because Steam is number one.
There is no competitor to Steam, in my opinion. It's the best platform for games. It really is. Everybody uses it. Everybody loves it.
And they're trying to keep their, you know, the throne, the king's trying to stay on the throne if you get much drift.
And it should be coming out soon. So I can't, I can't wait. I cannot wait for the Steam sharing system. What the fuck was that?
All right, guys, that's going to wrap up this video. Just a quick little talk about what's been going on with Steam.
And if you have any thoughts, please leave it in the discussion board is the comment section. And one more very important thing.
I rolled the person that won the Razer and Ostromo. So please check your YouTube PMs. Check them like twice because I'm still waiting on a reply from somebody.
So I might reroll it in a day or two if this person does not get to me in the next couple of days. So check your YouTube PMs, please.
Okay. Good night, everybody. See you all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.