What up guys, it's Jerma bringing you another gameplay commentary. This time I am the Spy on
Hoodoo. This is Defense on Hoodoo. I think this is the last part of Hoodoo. There's a few different
parts. I think this is the last part. I jumped in and they were here. So I'm using the Enforcer,
the new Spy Revolver, using the K'nai vs. Kunai, which is pretty much my default knife. I love the
K'nai vs. Kunai. And the Dead Ringer. I'm sorry, I promise you guys I'll give you an invisibility
watch gameplay at some point, but I love the Dead Ringer so much I just can't help it.
So I'm going to give you guys a very, very quick spy tip. This is something that I never see people
do. Most spies do not do this and they get themselves killed. Within the first five seconds
of the gate opening, do not go anywhere. This is absolutely essential to succeeding in the first
minute as a spy. You'll see what happens here when it gets down to about 10 seconds. What you see
most spies do is they'll get right up in front of the gate and they'll either have the Cloak and
Dagger and they're cloaking or they're hiding behind a wall right next to the gate. And then
right when the doors open, it's like boom, they're dead instantly because there's so much spam and
there's so much crap going on in the first 10-15 seconds of a match. You're never going to get
behind anybody and you're just going to get killed by spam. So just don't run up to the gates and
try and do something in the first five seconds. See, about 20 seconds went by and there's a lot
of options that I have here now. I kind of got a little screwed over there because I went for a kill
that he was already pretty much dead. But now I'm behind a bunch of people and I'm not guaranteed to
die instantly. Even though I do fail pretty miserably right here, the point still remains.
Don't just run out into the gates when the gates open or don't run right into somebody the second
the gates open. Stay back, count to about 20, and I guarantee you you'll have more success than you
did before. So they're starting to get on the card here. There's about two or three of them.
They get very, very far up in a very short amount of time. This seemed like it was going to be just
a throwaway gameplay. I didn't think we were going to win. I didn't think anything was going to happen
or it was going to be that that cool because, as you see, they're really rolling up to the point
here. I get a few kills here. I get this demo man because he's going the wrong direction. I don't
know where he was going. He was going over here for some reason into this little nook. Don't ask me
what he was doing. Maybe he was looking for ammo or something. I'm not sure. I get this sniper and
then this sniper. Watch this. This is kind of funny. He's just kind of aiming all over the place and
standing still. He might have been a free to play guy, but welcome to Team Fortress 2. My name's
Gabe Newell. Hopefully it'll have been worth the wait. So anyways, Hoodoo is one of the best spy maps
there is. If you want to practice as a spy, if you don't play spy that well, go to Hoodoo and play
Hoodoo. Get familiar with Hoodoo because there are so many nooks and crannies you can hide in
at Hoodoo more than any other map in Team Fortress 2. It's almost like they made this map
specifically for spies to do well because there's a spot back there. There's like three or four
nooks and crannies here. There are these tall rocks that you can hide behind that are just as
big for a person to get behind them. Me and this Pyro getting a little duel. I end up killing him,
but it comes back and bites me on the ass in a minute. But see these rocks? See these really
high rocks? You can just stand behind them and decloak and no one will ever see you.
So 100% this map is completely recommended if you want to learn how to play spy better or hone
your already spy skills. So this soldier walks by on fire and this sniper is in the way, so I think
I'm going to shoot him, but no, I just decide to stab him instead. Pyro comes up behind me,
gets his revenge with a nice crit with the power jack. And now that I have about a minute or two,
I want to just quickly describe and answer a question that a lot of you have asked me.
I get at least one pm a day or one comment a day asking why my graphics are so low
and why my graphics look like they're from like 1998. I play in DirectX 8, so I'm sorry if that
bothers some of you guys and I'm sorry if you have to deal with it, but there's not going to be a
change anytime soon. I've had to play in DirectX 8 since way back when I think it was like almost
a year ago. Team Fortress 2 came up with an update that changed the way that particle effects were
rendered on computers. Medigun beams were changed, pyro flamethrowers were changed,
teleporters got like a new glow effect, and when they did that, when I was in DirectX 9,
my frames per second went down to like 25 or something ridiculous when they used to be at like
60, 70, 80 frames per second. I went to DirectX 8 and the problems completely and totally went away,
so they still haven't fixed this because I've tried to go back to DirectX 9 before. Right before
I was going to do these commentaries, I tried it and it still didn't work. I still was getting
terrible frames per second. I've tried everything, so don't leave a comment telling me to change my
video drivers or something because I've already done it. So I come up behind this heavy, get him
with a backstab, and I want to talk about another tip. Look at what I have equipped right now as my
disguise as a medic. I'm using the bone saw right now. You can switch what weapon you're holding in
the disguise if you hit B while you're holding your different weapons. Too many spies walk around
if they're disguised. Let's just say you're disguised as the medic, right? If you're walking
around with a syringe gun out as the medic as your disguise, people are going to know you're a spy
because what medic walks around with a syringe gun when there's no enemies around? So make sure
you're aware of the different items that people are holding in different situations. It'll save
you a lot of spy checking. So me and this sniper are going toe-to-toe. He covers me with the
G-Roddy. I think he's going to get me with a kill because it would take one shot, but I end up getting
him. This revolver is really, really fun to use. It's really, really powerful. The whole point for
me coming back here was to take off the teleporter. I figured it was going to take too long for the
sapper, and I was right because look at these people coming out to try and get me. I get away
with my life intact, and I decloak right behind this rock. Like I told you before, this place is
fantastic for decloaking because look, nobody seems to know or care. So I'm following this line
of people, and this is where the dead ringer shines as you'll see in the next second or two here.
Get this engineer, get the sentry gun, pull out the dead ringer, run behind everybody. You know
you're just going to die. Just use it. Don't be afraid to take this thing out. Get behind every
single person again. Make sure you don't decloak right next to somebody because they'll hear it.
Come right back up with the way I came originally, and we're going to do it all over again.
This time I get about three or four kills in a row. I get this engineer,
get that medic, and the heavy he was healing. Pull it out, rinse and repeat again. That's the
best part about the dead ringer is if you have a set route, pretty much plan out a route you're
going to take and just do it every single time. People are very, very ignorant to dead ringer
spies. They never check and they always lose their ground whenever they're looking for you.
So I get that sniper, I get this scout, pull the dead ringer out. We turn around,
we try and do it again. This engineer knows I'm around. He is starting to wise up a little bit to
dead ringer spy, which is me. Cloak right behind these rocks because it's awesome.
Hoodoo is awesome. Come up here. I try to jump and get that sentry. It doesn't work. It's too far
away, and right here is a completely and totally horribly embarrassing thing. I could have
guaranteed killed this medic with one shot with the revolver, but I slipped up five times in a row
and I took off the sapper and then I took out the disguise kit. So that was pretty embarrassing,
but it was a pretty good run. I think I killed maybe six or seven people in that life, so
pretty good run. And a million people are going to comment telling me,
Jerma, you used the quick switch. Why are you using the stupid slow switch thing?
I'm just so used to using it. I can't do the quick weapon switch. I cannot do it. I refuse to try
because I've tried it before. It's just not happening, so I have to deal with that sometimes
because I can't do it any other way. So I get this sniper, pull out the dead ringer, try and
go back to my usual position, my usual spot, get some more cloak, get some health. De-cloak,
I come back up these stairs and this is another embarrassing moment, so I can't explain this.
I should have just sapped that stupid mini sentry because otherwise I would be in no trouble at all,
but nope, I'm a moron and didn't sap that sentry. I looked at it and I was like,
I should probably sap that, but I didn't. I just went straight for the
engineered kill and that was a dumb move. But I guess to be fair, this last part of
Hoodoo here, this huge choke point up here on the right, you could potentially see 10, 12,
maybe if there's a 15 player server, 16 player server. Everybody comes through this doorway.
Very rarely will you see, maybe one or two people will go the other way to come up about what that
cliff is. But for the most part, people all go this way, so it's hard to get behind people.
This soldier knows he shoots me and I die instantly. I had the kunai, so obviously I die in one rocket.
But it's tough with this last point. This is a huge choke point. Everyone's just stuffing,
both teams are just stuffing into the small area. And especially if you're playing with
the regular invisibility watch or the cloak and dagger, forget about playing spy at this
point in the match. Go to pyro or switch to dead ringer because it is just not possible.
So I don't even try to go into that room because of what happened the last two times.
I sit out here thinking that maybe somebody will come around the corner and I can pick them off.
And this is actually kind of funny. They get an uber and I'm an engineer right now and I'm just
going to stand right behind the heavy and no one's going to do anything about it and bang, he's dead.
So I thought that was pretty funny that I'm just an engineer just like,
hey, we're going to get this captured. We're going to do it. Just standing behind the heavy
and no one. People are like, oh, that's normal. That's okay. So I'm pretty screwed here. Everybody's
in this room. I think I get one kill right here, this sniper. No, I do. I do. I do. I do. Don't
worry. I'm watching. So I kill that sniper. This heavy's coming around the corner. See,
this is what I was talking about. It is like bumper cars right now. Like what was I supposed
to do in that situation? You know what I mean? I mean, I guess I could have gone up the stairs
and around the corner or something, but there were a lot of people up in that room too. So
I don't think that would have been successful either. And you saw what I was doing. I was
just smashing into people just like like a fucking fridge, like a walking fridge is pretty much what
I was. So I come up around here, try to get the dead ringer up, try and make something happen with
the last minute here. And this is the actual noise that I made when this happened. I kid you not.
This is the exact noise that I made in this situation. You ready?
I saw him come around the corner and I just was like...
There's nothing I could have done though because I'm an idiot and they built a sentry. So they're
starting to do a little bit of a push. We end up winning it anyways because it's only about 20
seconds and the cart is now moving backwards. So I figure I have to make at least something happen
here at the end. That medic comes out and tries to uber that heavy, but he has to go with an
engineer instead, which I think is hilarious. He has that stupid treasure hat on. So I do make
something happen in the end here. It's five seconds left so this doesn't really matter.
But I get the engineer and his sentry gun and look at the cart. I was freaking out. I was like,
oh shit, I better get out here. And I kill this heavy. I sap him. See, I sap that heavy.
So we end up winning. They don't get enough people on the cart and I believe I get top
score. I think I do, but who cares? Who gives a shit about that anyways? Thank you guys so,
so, so, so, so much for being here and for watching. I appreciate it. And we're getting
closer to 500. There's like 420 or something now or something like that. So we're getting
close before I start to show myself. So keep it coming, baby.