What are these tags? What? Tags. Where do you see tags? English tournament arc. Dislikes goat cheese.
The sus guy. Have I ever had a tag on this stream besides English? I hate that the sus guy is on here
because I feel like people really probably type that in and I don't want him finding me like that.
These were added last stream. That's funny. We should change it to not the sus guy. Not the sus guy.
Stop asking. So people feel like, wait, he probably gets this a lot. This must be really annoying for
him. He probably gets that a lot. Anyways, hi. How are you? Good to see you. Gonna be playing
a video game today. I don't know why I think that's, I don't know. I don't know what's wrong
with me lately. Gonna be playing Disc Room today. It's a fun game. Somebody said, hey,
you probably found this because it was on Game Pass. Yes, that is exactly where I found it.
I played it on Game Pass for like five minutes and said, this seems like it's something I would
want to play and stream and have fun and just hang out. That's what we're going to do. Also,
I want to talk about something really quickly. Some very exciting news. I'm incredibly excited.
I will wait because I feel like a lot of you probably know what I'm going to talk about
already. We'll see. We'll give it a few minutes. I want people to know this. I have to tweet still,
so give me one second. I'll be right back. All right. You guys ready? I think we,
maybe another minute or so. I'll talk about it a few more times over the stream. It's not like I'm
not going to say it ever again. This coming week, you will be able to see me on Ranboo's
generation loss streams. I'm going to be playing a pretty major part.
I have an accent, but yeah, I'm really excited for it. It's been something that's been in the
works for a very long time. I cannot wait to see the whole thing play out because it is a three-day
event, May 24th, May 26th, and May 28th, 6 PM Eastern time. I'm going to be in it. You'll see.
I don't want to give anything away, but you'll see. Can you teach us how to beat box?
Yeah, sure. First, you go like this. Then you go like this. It's fucking easy. When are you going
to play Tears of the Kingdom? Never. Let's just get that out of the way. I want to say that because
then if I ever do play it, you'll be surprised. But if I don't ever play it, then I already told
you I wasn't. So let's just say that because then you're not expecting it. But who knows?
Yeah, a ton of time, a ton of efforts gone into this. I don't want to talk too much about it
because it's a very, very interesting, very intricate project. Just know I will be participating.
I cannot wait. It's going to be fun. We'll probably have the mods put up a sus for it.
Don't make promises you can't keep. Oh, I absolutely can make the promise that I'm
not going to play Tears of the Kingdom. I can promise you that, right? But like if it happens,
then whoa, what? It's Tears of the Kingdom. He's here. And I'll do a huge, elaborate, annoying intro
where I dress as Link and it's a full cam. And it's like, I play the song and it's like,
oh my God, he's going to play it. We'll make a whole thing out of it.
And I'll bring up the the Ocarina and I'll learn a bunch of songs for the Ocarina.
Dude, do you hate this game? Why? I'm not mocking it. I'm not. I'm not mocking. What are you talking
about? No, I don't. What am I mocking? No, I'm not mocking. This is not mocking. This is just
fucking around. I'm not. I'm not mocking. This dude hates Zelda. No, I don't. I'm not mocking.
The Ocarina is pretty easy to learn. Can you stop stalling and just survive the discs already?
Yeah, I get a few minutes. This is me time right now. I said this last stream too. This is me time.
My intros, the first 10 to 15 minutes of every stream, this is me time. This is me. This is for
me. But interrupting. Turn your cam on and do the rump shake. That's like kind of funny, but no,
not today. Just starts working. Not today. I don't know. Who knows? Maybe one day I'll do a
rump shake just like Tears of the Kingdom. I'm not planning on it. I don't have a plan to play Tears
of the Kingdom, but you might get a rump shake one day. You never know. Please don't. Don't. Don't
do it. I don't even know what that means. Does that mean what I think it does? Like just, I'm
just going to shake my ass. Is that what it is? That's what it is, right? It's just,
I'm going to shake my butt. That's it. Is there anything else to that? Or is there more to it?
Is it something else? What else would it mean? I don't know. I have no idea. Stop mocking rump
shake. Oh, okay. Here we go. All right. Here we go. All right. Let's play this game. I am to the brim
of excitement. There's things. There's so many things. I just want to scream it at you,
but we'll wait. We'll wait. We'll wait. We'll wait. We're going to wait. We have to wait.
But yeah, keep an eye on the sus. Keep an eye on, but he's do the roar. This is end of the stream.
I just turned it on. This is me time. Okay. Let's go. I'm, I'm turning it on. There it is. All right.
This is disc room. And yeah, I did get this on game pass. I don't, I mean, it seems like it's
going to be really fun. This is a game about concentration. It's a game about, uh, keeping,
being good at dodging. It's one of the only things I can do. In 2092, a giant disc is discovered in
orbit of Jupiter. A crew of international scientists is sent to investigate. Oh, cartoon.
Left stick is move. I'm, this is going to be fun. You just have to live. That's it.
The only thing you do game about precision. It's the, it's the sans fight. I guess it kind of is,
it is kind of the same undertale concept, isn't it? Kind of feels like I'm doing pretty damn good
already. This first room you would have, you would have died at five seconds. All right.
That's all right. All right. So survive five seconds. I did that die from four different
discs. I can go left or I can stay over here. Well, how do I get the, um, doesn't usually,
well, let me see. How do I start starting here again? Oh, I think I'm, I have to do tutorial
stuff. It's like asteroids. All right. Survive 10 seconds. That's all I have to do. I think it
usually shows the developer time, the person that made the game. Okay. I was looking at chat. Shut
up. Four seconds. Yeah. I, I got it. I already did. I beat it already. In fact, I should just
hurry up and get to the next room because this guy sucks at this. I just did it. I'm over time
right now. Opportunity right here. One, two. Oh, sorry. New best time. How does it, I think it's
supposed to show the dev time. How come I can't see that? Hold on a second. Let me restart this.
How do I show that? Yeah. Dev team time. This says it's on. How come I can't see it? Yeah. See
ready? Look, uh, game. See dev team times on. It should be on. I can't do it. The devs never beat
this. It's not in the tutorial. Oh, okay. All right. So I already did this one. We can take a look at
the, take a look at this. So this is the game. This is the whole game. So kind of like the rooms
are connected. That's pretty cool. So we can go up. We're going to go up. All right. Die from four
disc types and survive 10 seconds. Easy. Let's go. That was just a practice one. See, I didn't get
that move. That's why I couldn't do it. All right. Hold A to dash through discs. Here we go. See,
you give me one button that's a dash and an analog stick. I'm going to beat every single
fucking record in this entire game. Is this Omega gaming weekend? No. In fact, this is Omega short
weekend. This is exceptionally small weekend. That's all right. I'll take it. I'll take it.
Where should I go from here? I'm going to go up. Dude, you suck. I'm beating every level.
I'm completing every level of man. That's all right. I didn't do it. Come on. Come on, man.
Nobody said chill, please. Are you talking to me? You're talking to the chat. I don't know who you're
talking to. Here we go. Oh, I want to talk about this. This is really important. This is food
related. So I know everyone's going to be really excited to hear that. I know at least 10 people
in the chat heard it was food related. So they just, yes, let's go. Okay. Let me ask a question.
I don't want to be rude. I'm trying. I'm going to try not to be. Can I go up? Oh, no, this is a dead
end. Oh, there is no complete this one. All right. All right. So here's what I want to talk about.
I don't want to be disrespectful. I don't want to be mean about this, but there's anyone has
anybody in this chat and of all the 13 plus thousand people that are here right now,
13,000 of you, have you ever, ever bought heavy pulp orange juice? Any of you, a single person
in the whole chat, because honestly, I think, I think that's like my first test to see if you're
a psycho. If you drink heavy pulp orange juice, is that like, is that weird to say that?
I'm not talking about medium pulp. I'm talking heavy pulp, heavy pulp. One of the mods. Wait,
we are Josh. What the fuck, dude? I don't look, I don't mind pulp. Light pulp is good. Medium pulp.
But at some point it's, I feel like I'm drinking wet wood shavings in my orange juice. I feel like
I'm drinking bugs. It's heavy pulp is, is, is ridiculous. It's, it's sludge. It's not even
orange juice. I like pulp. Hope is fine. But too much of too much is, is too much. Wait, what
heavy pulp? It gets like stuck in your teeth and shit in a smoothie. All right. Yep. Okay.
All right. I want to say, I'm not seeing the dev times. I might have to restart.
That makes sense to me. I get it. All right. 10 seconds. Survive zero seconds or less.
Okay. So survive 10. I could see a smoothie because you want some of the actual orange in it.
I get that. But anytime I've ever seen heavy pulp get poured, it reminds me of sour milk,
where you pour it and it's like, you know what I'm talking about. It's that like,
slop, slop, slop, slop, slop, slop, slop, slop. Fucking gross. All right. Survive zero seconds or
less. Did I do it? How do you, how do I die in zero seconds? It takes a second for it to spawn.
Did I get, I got it right there at zero, right? How do you, how do I die instantly?
Zero seconds or less. Hey asshole, I'm drinking milk right now. Don't ruin it.
I just imagine you with a 24 ounce glass of milk. How 0.007. I don't think this is possible.
Die from 15 disc types. All right. Well, this one, this one is a different one here. Yep. Any more
in here that count? Yep. That one counts. I gotta go left. Defeat the gatekeeper in 10 seconds. How
do I do it? Can I hit him? Oh, okay. I get it. This game is going to get,
when's the dog food tier list? What is the tier list that I actually wanted to do? I forgot to
bring it up. There's a tier list I want to do. What was it? Shit. Oh my God. This is going to
drive me crazy. What was it? No, no, no, no, no, no. I never talked about it. Shit. This is why I
write everything down. I just, I didn't write this one down. It'll come to me in a minute.
Oh, what? Oh, right. I wanted to, cause I saw the, the MK one trailer, which was
fucking ridiculous by the way. Uh, I wanted to do a rate, put every like a tier list for all the
Mortal Kombat characters ever. That would be kind of fun. Do a Mortal Kombat character tier list.
Do it now. No, I mean like an, like a, I don't know, like six to 12 months. What does this do?
I still can't see the time played total deaths. Oh, it's keeping track of all this.
That'll be in a year. Oh, that's all right. All right. So I want to go up. It's keeping
track of my total play time. Do it right now. You weirdo. No, and like, like six or seven years
or something. I have to last wait. Why is that not counting anymore? Oh, you have to stand in the
middle. I think I could do at least 30 seconds here. It didn't mean six to seven years. You're
not even going to be streaming then I'm talking about on Mars. Oh, we're good. I'm still here.
Oh, that had to have been pretty good. That had to have been pretty good.
Don't have to die from, yeah, I have to be killed by a few different discs, right? 15. I haven't
been killed by this one. That opens one of the other doors and get over there. Yep. Oh,
you have to pick one. I'll try slow best time. 30 seconds. I can do better than that.
That lasts a long time. Oh, it doesn't recharge. I think it does. This is way better than dash.
Maybe not. Oh, hold on. I can do better than that. What's this game? This game is called disc room.
And you can get it right now on, you know, sound is good. No, it sounds great. What was my record
on this 30 seconds? Oh, oh, shit. I can do better than that. I have to beat the record here. Die to
the golden disc. That's actually true. That's really true. Are you ever going to do a beer
drinking stream? No. Oh, all right. I did it. I need to go to undiscovered disc survived 20 seconds.
Oh, shit. I got to do that down here. Let's go. But you want me to like rate beers. I mean,
I could do that. I could. Do you want me to do a beer drinking tier list? Like where the,
where they belong? Okay. I don't know. I'll figure it out. I'll set it up. I'll figure that out.
God damn it. They're all going to be put in F. That's not necessarily true.
I have to survive 20 seconds. There's probably another tier for a minute, too.
Not just American beers. No, I know. I'm thinking maybe the top, the most popular three or four per
country. That's very doable considering that's probably four or five thousand different beers.
Sure. I got it. All right. I got to go right and up because this one is 20 seconds.
Armored gatekeeper. Best time 10 seconds. So how do I do 20 seconds here? Is that possible?
Survived 20 seconds. Undiscovered disc. How do I do this? I have to get 20 orbs. Oh,
I thought he explodes after 10. Irma thinks there are like 20 countries. No, I just said
there was that was thousands of beers. Every country has its own beer. Every country has its
own beer that it makes. They all everybody makes a beer. Every country. I'm telling you every.
I got it. If OK, if you name a country and then go to Google and type in
what is this country's beer, it's going to give you a like, oh, it's a 40 percent hop to say
flavored with pineapple extract. I don't know. It's going to be something.
All right. Well, we can't let's just say most just say most countries. That's I mean, come on.
You can't you can't take literally. I mean, like I don't ever speak in literal terms. I'm speaking
in like most mostly terms like every country has got a beer. Oh, yeah. Well, what about this
country? This country doesn't have a beer. Yeah. All right. Well, maybe they do. Maybe they don't.
I don't know. Well, don't say that. Well, I don't know. Literal Andy, you said every. Yeah. But
like I'm sure there probably is something. Name me a country right now. Just I'm going to. OK,
let's let's I'm going to let's do a random country. OK, what is Spain? Spain's beer,
Spanish beer. Oh, interesting. What's Spain's most popular beer? It is called a San Miguel.
A San Miguel Classica is the most traditionally and best known among the Spanish population.
Would you look at that? What about Brazil? Brazil's beer? Here we go. What's the most popular
beer in Brazil? Skoll, Brahma, Antarctica, Nova Shin. Huh? These are Brazilian beers.
Come on. Those are craft Brazilian beers, and they're probably fucking wonderful.
OK, yeah, but not every. OK, not every single country on Earth will look. There's some countries
that this is not going to happen. Backtrack and Barry. No, it's called it's called nitpick.
Nancy is what we got over here. All right. I have to do this. I'm going to freak out.
Shit. Why don't I look at Chad? Yeah, I mean, that's a lot of beer.
Maybe you know what I would do? Maybe the most popular beer from most countries.
I feel like, wait, I'll get shit faced. It's too muddy beers. I can't drink like 100 plus beers.
If I take a sip out of 100 beers, how many beers is that? Can somebody do the calculation?
Like if you take how much how many ounces of liquid is in one sip or two sips? And how many
beers is 100 sips? I didn't even do it. You do it lazy. I'm playing a game. 10 beers is one sip.
Maybe maybe for some maybe for some YouTubers. Do you know who I've been watching lately? I just
like it's just I love it so much. It's a L.A. beast. It's just that his videos just go so wild.
They're just so they're just fucking outrageous. I never really watched much of his content,
but sometimes you just want to watch a guy eat like fucking 30 White Castle hamburger.
And he pukes. He like pukes like he pukes and like shits and some of these
those are rookie numbers. No, they are not. Are you kidding me? I also have some more
interesting news to share with everybody to share with the class. I remember when I told you
that I had never had White Castle before. I did. I did have it. I have to get to 20 seconds.
I had White Castle. Let me tell you, I want to give it a rating. This shit was at least
at least a B plus. At least. I don't understand the naysayers. It's like it's fine. It's good.
It's just yummy. It's just a delicious simple just little cheeseburger slider. Come on. I got it.
Shit. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. You know what? I'll give you. I'll give you a hot
take. I think a lot of people don't want to admit that they like simple things because it's like
makes them simple for some reason. Like, oh, White Castle. No, gross sucks. It's stupid.
I almost feel like a lot of people, they probably do kind of like it, but if they say they like
something that's too simple, does that make me kind of like boring or something? No, it doesn't.
It doesn't. Don't worry. Just eat it. Now, some of you probably really do think it sucks and that's
fine. And I know there's a lot of you that have eaten it that were, you know, maybe you were in,
maybe you're in the car or maybe you got back to when your friends were all there and
y'all took a bite at the same time and two of your friends were like, oh, oh,
gross. And you were sitting there silently. I kind of like this. You were like, yeah, it's like,
man, whatever. It's too hyped up. Who was he talking to? You. I haven't admitted to you guys
that I liked the Venom movie. You know what I'm saying? I feel like it's kind of similar.
The thing is I didn't like the Venom movie because it was full of nutritional value,
right? Let's use this as an example. I just liked it because the movie was fucking dumb and like fun
and stupid and weird. And then it was like one of my favorite characters. So sorry. This is,
I'm addicted to trying to do this, but I just can't. I'm going to be quiet until I do this.
Why did I, I didn't pick it up. Ollie is calling me out here. She's saying, but how did you get
the White Castle? Yeah. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I'm in big fucking trouble now.
It was the frozen shit from the grocery store and I still thought it was a B plus
fucking hate me all you want. I don't care. Go ahead. Go ahead. You don't like me anymore.
You don't like me anymore. I never did. Oh, so if I had the real thing, would that be an A?
I, I would still eat a hot pocket and go, that's fine. That one's unfair where it is. Got it. Let's
go. Nice. Feels good. Yes. It's okay. I got it. I got to go here because I need 20 seconds here as
well. Use the bumpers and triggers. What does that do? They kind of zoom in a little. Whoa.
Wait, that's speeding the game up. Oh my God. Okay. That's, that's hard mode. Were you high
when you ate the frozen white castle? No, no, I was not. Was not, you know, time that first
enough for even asking that question. You know, like how dare you talking about drugs, talking
about marijuana or something. Devil, the devil, devil, the devil. Oh my God. I have, I don't have
to get 20 seconds on every single map, do I? I kind of do. What saws have I not died to? Oh shit.
Come on. I got killed by the golden saw, didn't I? Do I actually get anything for doing 20 seconds
on each map or is that just a bragging rights? Oh, that was close. Sorry. I got it. All right.
So I got to go left and then up. What about down? What's down here? Survive? Yeah. Zero seconds.
I don't get it. How do you die in zeros? Whoa. I know that's how got it. Cool. Okay. Really cool.
What's this one? Stay sharp. I don't think I got killed by that one yet. I'm not actually quite.
I think the dash might actually be better, but feel more comfortable with this one. Wait,
this is important. One of the mods trotter. I also checked out the beer thing. A sip is about
four milliliters and a can of beer is 12 ounces or 341 milliliters. One sip from 100 beer cans
would be roughly just a bit over one beer at 14 ounces. Really? Huh. One sip is about four
milliliters. I could probably do that then. The one thing that I'm afraid of, of doing that stream
is offending an entire country. You know what I mean? I definitely don't, I don't want to like
do the, oh, the what country has the best tasting beer test. And some countries like they're ready.
Oh my God. I can't wait to see. He's going to have our beer. I take a sip out of it. I'm like,
I feel like that would really disappoint a lot of people. They all got their, their beer branded
hats on and they've got like a case of it. They're like, I'm ready. And then they have to question
everything. Well, no, actually this is fine because then they would just go, no, he likes
White Castle. Nevermind. We're good. They don't think this is all calculated. You don't think I,
this is incredibly calculated everything I'm saying every day. Give me a little bit of credit.
Frozen food tier list. That actually sounds kind of fun. I don't think this is even connected to
anything. Shit. 20 seconds. Come on. Damn it. When are we going to get Otto's augtastic adventure?
I don't know. I just thought of Otto. The trail is so long on these things.
Almost there. Oh yes. Thank God. Okay. I got it. We got the whole bottom row cleared. Where should
I go up? I'll try to see what's the criteria. Ah, I have to die to three more. What have I not?
There are four disks in this room. I have not been killed by. Oh, but there's one that I haven't
been killed by. Which one? Second phase of this one. Ah, okay. Oh, you were right. All right.
Cool. I've been hit by everything here, everything here, everything here.
Is there one that I haven't been hit by? I think I got them all. All right. Let's just go up and
then right. Survive for five seconds. Easy. Protect your bowels. Dude. Don't do a frozen food tier list.
I got to get at least 30 seconds on some of these. That was pretty damn good.
I'll take that one. That's pretty good. Will you do an Arby's full menu tier list? No,
no, that doesn't sound like fun. I really don't think I would really even hate Arby's, but
no, it doesn't sound good. Survive five seconds in all unlocked rooms. Okay. Defeat two gatekeepers.
And I'm already doing a pretty, pretty good job already. What? Die from this?
Okay. What about a Febreze scent tier list? That's the fastest way to get a migraine.
What about an orange juice? Didn't you promise a BLT today? A few people are asking about it.
I love how that's what people are asking about. This community. I love this community. It's just.
Hey dude, like, um, where's the BLT stream? Like I've just, we're just kind of curious about it.
We really just want to know like if that was bullshit or not, or if we should expect that or
I'm kind of waiting around to see. It's like, I don't know, man,
but I don't, I don't like any of you individually. Okay. I like you collectively. Make that really
clear. I just said, fuck you. Hey, he hates us. I didn't say that. You said that. I said that.
No, I'm just saying that. I mean, no BLT, dude. I mean, not right. Not today. Guys. I don't even
have the ingredients to make a BLT. Doesn't that seem strange? But it's true. Think about the
ingredients of BLT. I don't have them. I don't have, well, I mean, you need to sub roll. Oh no,
you don't. I don't have no bread. Now I need to go to the store. I don't have no bread, no bacon,
no lettuce, no tomatoes. The only thing that's on a BLT that I own right now is mayo. They don't
have any bread. We just ran out of bread. It's not a infinite resource. You have to go and get it
again after you go run out. There's not a bread machine that's in your house that just, well,
you might make your own bread, but that's pretty cool. But it's not what I'm referring to. Just
use the mayo, dude. So you want me to take a bacon, lettuce, and tomato sandwich,
remove the entire sandwich, and eat a spoonful of mayonnaise. So why don't you just say what you
want me to do? Bro, eat a spoonful of mayonnaise. It would be funny. Childish. That was pretty good.
I have 10 seconds. Is this, oh, this is a gatekeeper. Uh, you can kill me though.
You can kill me. Okay. There's one more disk in here I need to die to.
Okay. Mayonnaise is your entire diet. I mean, you make one jokey food pyramid joke
and everybody thinks you eat mayonnaise with your hands out of the jar. Is that the one I have to,
well, let me beat it first. Also the ad campaign that a lot of mayonnaise is doing right now,
they're doing kind of like the Reese's campaigns. Like the kind of like, sorry, not sorry. Not sorry.
Yeah. Mayo. Not sorry. It's like, it's just mayonnaise and I like it. I don't care. Oh,
those of us that like dip our sandwiches in mayo. I don't do that. I love mayonnaise,
but I don't do it. Not sorry. No, stop. Why are you so dramatic? I'm just kind of messing around.
Who's that? Hey, can you wish me luck? I got finals tomorrow. You do. You do. You do you.
No, I can't. I was going to say you do as best as a job as you can. God damn it. You do.
You, I can't tell you, you're going to do good. I don't know what if you didn't study.
I don't want to be responsible if you don't do well. Do your best. I hope you'd fucking studied
for it and get at least a C or a B. You'll be all right. You do you. It wouldn't be funny
if it wasn't true. You know what I mean? Why not A? Because you can't tell somebody to get an A.
You can't say, hey, yeah, get an A. No, that's too much pressure to have to think about.
Get an A? Get a near perfect score. What? I'm sorry. I'm of the opinion.
You don't have to have a perfect score. You just need to know the information.
There's a difference between retention and memorization. You understand? Retention,
knowledge retention is incredibly important. Knowledge memorization. Is it really retention?
High horse Andy. You know what? You do you. High horse Andy. High horse Andy would be me saying,
I got A's in every class. Therefore you should too. I'm way smarter than you.
That is not what I said. That's not high horse Andy. That's me saying I got C's and
I don't give a shit. Bad role model. Your role model should be like fucking Abraham Lincoln and
shit. Not me. Your role model should be like, I don't know. Wait, what's this? Clone yourself.
Oh, that's kind of cool. Dude, pick somebody that's alive. That's true. That's true.
Okay. Can I keep pressing it? How many times can I do this? I feel like this is cheating.
Oh my goodness. That was only nine seconds. Oh, every time I spawn one, I lose a second.
That's the trade off. Okay. I get it. All right. We're going, we're going back to the other one.
I like this one better. 20 seconds. Can you please explain the stream tags? Hates having enough
fiber. I don't know. I, the mods have access to this. They do whatever they want. Oh, whoa.
That was really cool, but I didn't get 20. You don't like goat cheese. I very, very, very much
don't. I, goat cheese to me is, and it's so, I hate it. If I ever am out at a restaurant or something
with a bunch of people and hanging out and somebody gets like a goat cheese appetizer
and everybody's eating it. It's like, I, I don't want that. Or there's like salads or something
that has it on it. And people see that I'm doing the thing where you take the knife and you just
scrape it off to the side. I just don't, I must have my, my DNA must be different than yours
because you know what I mean? Like we must have a completely different, however, like the food DNA
part of your brain is because I find goat cheese to be absolutely revolting. And I mean, and, but
I like blue cheese and you think that that, a lot of you think that's absolutely revolting
and that's all right. I think blue cheese tastes like yummy, creamy deliciousness. And I think
goat cheese tastes like dirt, like a soil out of the ground, like a spoonful of it in your mouth.
Shit. I need 20 seconds. You only like blue cheese to be different. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
One of my favorite flavors on all right. I'm shutting that person down. That person needs
to get that person needs to get shut down right now. Blue cheese and hot sauce is my favorite
flavor combination in the world. If you have, if there was a flavor tier list, no, sorry. It's not
blue raspberry. Stupid. It's, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You do you. All right. That's the end of the
story. All right. In real talk though, I would put blue cheese and hot sauce at over S and it's
probably the only thing that's there. Why are you being so strange? I don't know. Just fucking around.
Now I don't put it on everything. I, I like blue cheese where I think blue cheese belongs.
I think blue cheese belongs on Buffalo chicken, a Buffalo chicken sandwich with blue cheese on it
is unmatched. It's undeniably unmatched. It is the best single probably food item in the world
is a Buffalo chicken sub in the world. And I really don't think anything can compare to it.
The second thing on that list would be a perfectly cooked piece of salmon. That's number two.
That is way above blue raspberry. And we're talking flavor, like flavor profile. I don't put blue
cheese on salmon. No, I'm saying that, that, that what we've moved on to a different topic,
a different flavor. Where is mint on that list? Very low. Spear mint is, is okay. It's high.
Peppermint is, I like peppermint tea, but I think mint is it's a, I don't hate it. I don't love it.
I think it's fine. I like Spear mint. Oh, Holy shit. You guys need to know this. I have to tell
you this and I don't care. You can call me like, like brand shill Andy. I don't care.
Do you want to know what the best hot sauce in the world is in the world? I got killed by,
Oh wait, I can go down here now. Yep. Best hot sauce in the world is Tabasco,
but it's a very specific Tabasco. It's one that I have not had. Oh, and I just burped a little,
it's one that I haven't. Ooh, this is weird. It's a different flavor of Tabasco. Are you ready?
The Tabasco Habanero sauce is un fucking believable. It is probably the single greatest hot
sauce ever invented. Trust me. It is, there's a lot of truths here and I'm so glad. I am so glad
that a lot of, you know, Tabasco Habanero is, it makes everything better. Everything. Did somebody
say you've definitely never had it? What? Why would I say I love it? That's weird.
I can absorb a disc. It's really hot. Old A to absorb. I said, I've never had it. What?
You just said you'd never had it. Wait, wait, wait, wait. What's going on? Wait, what's happening?
You've never, I've never, this, you, can somebody give me a clip or something? I said, the bottle's
gone. I haven't had it. Somebody clip me. What? You definitely said that buddy. That means you're like
mad. If you say buddy at the end of a sentence, that means like you're pissed at me. What? I'm
serious. Like when did I say that? I don't see a clipper. He's not had it. So it's one. Yep.
Best hot sauce in the world is Tabasco, but it's a very specific Tabasco. It's one that I have not
had. What? Why did I say that? I'm so confused. I feel like, I feel like you edited this clip
and made me say that. Well, I had to have been talking about something else. Best hot sauce in
the world is Tabasco, but it's a very specific Tabasco. It's one that I have not had. I, I think
what I was trying to say is it's one that I haven't talked about. One that I have not said, I think is
one that I have not said. Had, yeah, I said that completely wrong. It's okay. Best hot sauce in
the world is Tabasco, but it's a very specific Tabasco. It's one that I have not had. One that I
have not said on stream or had till recently. That's what it was. Yes. That's what it is. Thank you.
It was one that I've not had till recently. I got cut off because somebody made fun of me.
It was the one that I, because I, I, me and Holly just started eating it like over the last month
or two. That's what it was. Somebody called me a fucking name. So I had to pause for a second.
Um, but yeah, it's one that I haven't had till recently. That sounds so stupid out of context.
All right. But yeah, it is unfucking believable. It's really hot though. The habanero Tabasco is
the kind of sauce where you eat it and it hurts. It's ha ha, but I think it's tolerable.
If you don't think habanero is tolerable, it is very hot. The other one. Um, oh shit. I've had
also the, I think it's, what is it? The, the scorpion sauce, whatever it's called. It's,
it's red. It's a bright red Tabasco, um, scorpion or something. That one's really good too,
but that one is really, that one's like dangerous. That one hurts a lot.
One drop of that is really painful, but it's really good. He's eating bugs. All right. I got 20.
What was the hot sauce? It was Tabasco habanero. It's hot. It's really hot. So don't fuck around
with this stuff. Both of them are. I might get a minute on this one. I did not absorb it. Oh,
well we can go right. I'm going to go down. Yeah. The, uh, the habanero one, it's interesting
because it's got like bananas, mango, tamarind in it. It's good. Is there any pulp in it?
There's a little bit of bits, nothing much though. It's pretty clear.
You ever have the ketchup one? I've had Tabasco and ketchup before. It's good. Shit. Oh God. Okay.
Where are they going? Oh, oh man. It's over. No. Yes. Okay. I'm good. 30 seconds. Oh my God. I'll
try. I remember you would probably bail Willy Wonka's chocolate factory tests. No, I wouldn't.
I'm not touching anything there. Are you kidding me? I don't know what the fuck is in it. All that
shit. Never last and gobstopper. It never ends. Why? What's in it? Well, that's a secret. I don't
want to put that. I'm not putting it in my mouth, Willy. It's a secret. It lasts forever. Why? I
don't, I'm not eating that until I know what's in it. Listen, Bill, I'm not putting that in my mouth.
I want to see the ingredients list. What kind of preservatives do you have in there? The high
fructose corn syrup in that too, Bill? Yeah, that's what I thought. Uh, how would I do this?
How are you supposed to beat this one? Survive for 10 seconds. Maybe with the clones. This is. Oh,
okay. Slow. Dude, this one sucks. Wow. Okay. Shit. Come on, man. I had it. I'm alive. Damn it. I
didn't have any left. I got it. Nice. Thank God. 20 seconds on this one. No way. Not a chance. I
almost had it. Not this one too, right? No, we're okay. Oh, that's kind of helpful. I wanted to get
hit by the discs. That was unpleasant. Yeah, it kind of was. I don't think we have to do it again,
though. How's the garden going? Probably get some updates there in the next, uh, next week or so.
Sprouts have, uh, have crested the dirt. I know people really asking about the beetles, but, uh,
I don't have them. Let's take it slow and I should get this one fine. I might get a minute on this
one. This one's probably the easiest one of the whole bunch right now. Let me get a minute. Nice.
Very nice. Oh, just keep going this way. We're good. Get all the way down, all the way down.
Let's go for two minutes. Clean. Right there. I can't use that anymore. I gotta wait like 10
seconds or so. Oh, this could be it. No, I might get it. That's it. 146. Damn it. Do this one now.
All the way down. All right. Star map. Have you seen all the memes about your stream getting
nuked the other day? Yeah. Yeah. And now there is a hard limiter on my computer. I, that ain't
happening again. Ever again. What's the deal with this one? Absorb it? Maybe. I generally hope you're
not too stressed out about that. It sucked. I had it on really loud, but I haven't, I still don't
know what happened. I, I, dude, I went, I did a full like diagnostic of my entire audio equipment
and system. Nothing. Nothing. But there's a limiter on the stream now. I ain't having that
happen again. Yeah. I've seen a lot of the memes and it's fun to laugh at them, right? Cause like
one of the things that we said is it sounded like somebody shot a grenade launcher into my room.
It's just like, it does. It really does. It sounds like I was like, it sounds like I was
fucking like somebody threw a grenade in here, but you gotta be careful with that kind of shit. That
shit is not good. And whether it was the game or the game communicating with the computer or
something, I don't know, but I ain't, that can't happen again. It was, that was fucking crazy.
What do I do here? Whether it was a rare, incredibly rare bug in devil may cry three
HD collection. I don't know if it is a rare bug like that though. Whoa. Whoa. Really? Like,
holy shit. That's, that's ridiculous. What do I do about this? I woke up laughing the next day
because it was so funny. I'm glad people think it's funny, but at the end of the day, that's,
you're going to be careful with that kind of shit. Maybe clones. Oh, I got to do.
It is clones. You haven't had a limiter this whole time. I have a limiter on my voice
and I usually have, so I have a thing where the audio is not supposed to go over a certain
threshold through OBS, but it, it went, it went through that. And I think it's because the amount
of sounds that were happening in a row, it didn't matter. It like went over the threshold, but now
I have it, I have it baked in. So that should be impossible now, but what a ridiculous bug.
I did it. Best time. Is that? Oh, I got it. I have 120 seconds. That one's going to be hard.
Ooh, I can just teleport. That's helpful. All right. This one's long time. Wait,
how does this work? How do I add time? This thing just, all right, this thing just turned on. That
was weird. Why did this one light up? Do I have to circle them? Clones maybe stand in both spots.
Let's try it. No. Yeah. When they bump it into the walls, it's when it's activating and I've
changed that. Can I move them? Can't make them change direction. I don't think I can absorb the
gold ones. Trying to do it right now. No, maybe I need a new power. This one's 20 seconds. I didn't
do. Let's change that. This one. I like this game. Are you breathing so weird? You can hear my
breathing. Oh my God. Breathing stream overlay, but there's like a little, like a little balloon
in the corner that inflates when I breathe in and deflates when I breathe out. I got it. What do I
need to go to the left room? Oh, it's from here. 120, 10 seconds. We can do that. Had to die to
that. You have to die to every single saw. Don't forget that. That would make it way easier for me
to be in sync with your breathing. Please do that. Plus two. Oh, you're the reason why I'm not going
to do it now. Hey, you do you. Yeah, you do you. I didn't even get it. Do a silent bob impression.
That's why I didn't even read that because okay, there you go. 20, 20. Let's get 20 right here.
Let's get 30. Yeah, that's what we call split second decision making. Whatever. This one's 10
seconds and feed. Feed what? Well, I'm going to die to this. I think I have to go inside of the
mouth. No, I would have met. Okay, it is. Yep. Feed it four times. Wait, what? That didn't count.
I get it. I get it. Wait. Okay. Yep. I have to pick up four of these. Get them both. Yes. All
right. That's it, right? Oh, my goodness. All right. We're fine. That's not it. It was four.
Yeah, I got it. All right. Now it's going to drive 10 seconds. I need to do your stand up.
I wouldn't last going to stand up. I'd get up there and I would tell one joke that I thought
was going to absolutely slay and it wouldn't. And then it would be over because that was my
best material. I would be like, I'm leading with the best thing I got. And it would be crickets.
And then I go, oh, fuck. Everything I'm about to say after this is not as good as the first
joke I just said. It's over. What do I do? I wish I had dash right now. Shit. I can do it.
Just give me a dash. You got to improve. Sometimes you got to sometimes you got a
bomb to improve. Yeah, no, that's true. I think that's accurate. I think like you got to,
you're never going to learn. Nobody starts out perfect. You got to, you got to learn, improve.
I figure out what works and doesn't work. Everybody gets it right the first time.
Allow yourself to grow. What do I always say? What do I always say? Yeah. You're part of the
story. I have to get 20 seconds on everything. What do you always say? You always say stones.
Yeah. Well, besides that, as other things I say, besides stones, stones, great movie.
Be greedy. I got it. Does it just keep getting harder and harder and harder and harder and
harder until you have to lose? I imagine so. Does each room have a completion survive 120 seconds?
This wants me to fast forward. Oh, I was going to say the, the DVD things never going in the corner.
It did. Oh shit. 120, right? 180. I thought it was 120. I was just lost right there.
Guys keep going. I'm just going to keep going. Wait, one, I was at 93. It's not 120, 60 plus.
Oh, I was reading the, whatever. It's two minutes, pal. What's with you guys today and calling me
pal and shit. Like, okay, pal. All right, buddy. Hey, listen, pal. Hey, buddy. What's going on here?
Hey, listen, pal. All right, bud. Hey, buddy. What'd he say? You don't call me your friend.
Don't call me your, don't call me your friend. I'm not your friend. Like, why is that? That's
so funny how they're like that. That's the thing to like really, you know, get into somebody's skin.
You know, you just called me a friend and pal and I'm not, I'm not your friend at all.
You don't even know it. Hey, don't say that. Call me your friend. I'm not a friend of yours.
How dare you call me a friend of yours. Okay, pal. See wise guy to me is, is not the same.
Wise guy is implying that I'm already upset with you. Hey, wise guy. Like, oh yeah. You're,
you're a wise guy. This is a baby game. Uh, this room is, is easier, but I wouldn't say that.
All right. I just go until I don't. Do you think it's possible that an alien could be watching
your stream? Uh, no, I don't think so. And a network reaching that far into space.
I mean, that would imply that the alien has some kind of wifi or why are you implying that there's
an alien here now among us is watching the stream. They're on earth is what you mean. What do you mean
like another planet? Oh, I maxed it out. Three minutes is the max. So this one, this little
disk in here I have to die to. What is it? Not that one. This purple one here. Nope. There we go.
All right. Now let's actually get it. You're the first pick for mankind to talk to the aliens.
Uh, what would your first choice of words be? Uh, that's a good question. Okay. Do they understand
me? Is there, is there a part of the movie or is there a part of the, the scenario you're,
you're painting here where the aliens go, hello human. Like they can talk like, oh yeah, we've,
now we know your, uh, your language now. Like they can just like, they sense it in there. Okay. Now
I can speak English. Is that what you're implying? So that we can talk to each other and they can
understand context, what I'm saying. Okay. Uh, first thing I would say is get out, get out while
you still can. This place is fucked. Get out of here. Leave quick. Leave quick. You got to get
out of here now. You got to get out of here now. I don't know what's going to happen. Get out of
here now. Quick. Abandon this place. Abandon it quick. That's probably the first thing I would say.
And then before they left, I'd be like, you got anything weird that you can give me that I can
sell for like a million dollars? And then say, take me with you. Take me with you. Take me with you.
Yeah. And they fly away and I'm like, oh yes, I get to finally go with the alien.
And the big beam comes down and I'm looking up. Oh, joyous of me. And they vaporize me.
That's that part of the movie. I don't know why this has to be a movie, but
I guess I just decided it was. How would you try to explain the sus guy meme to an alien who had
no prior knowledge of humanity? Hmm. Well, how do you explain humanity to an alien? What kind of
life form is this? They can understand me, but do they understand anything about the planet? Do
they know what water is? But I, we would have to start at zero. Like we drink this and eat stuff
or we die. This water here, this liquid in this glass, every single being on this planet
needs to consume a certain amount of this a day or we die. I think that's where you start.
Honestly, that's probably where you start. And then they go, interesting. Now we know exactly
what to obliterate. First, go for the water source. No, no, no, no, no. No, you bastard alien.
How dare you. Take me with you. Take me with you. This room is fucking crazy. What? I need slowdown.
Yeah, we already went over how hot sauce would be an act of war. We already talked about what food
or what beverage you should not give an alien because they're going to see it as like an attack.
How would you explain porn to aliens? I don't know. I don't know. You probably feel like
what would they wouldn't be. I don't know. What kind of life form is this?
I don't think they'd even do they know what sex is. Would they? I don't know. What kind of life
form is it? Not again. Not again. Not again. All right. All right. Fine. Fine. Fine. Let's start
with the subway or whatever. Oh my goodness. This was hard. Okay. Explain this to them.
This is great, Dr. Clay. This is fucking hilarious. Okay. This is actually like a 10 out of 10 joke
from Dr. Clay. I got it for this. We got to talk about this because yeah.
Okay. Dr. Clay says, how would you explain this to the aliens? Okay. Let's try. Hold on. I got to
save it. Okay. How do we describe this? Save it. It's annoying. I'm just going to try to drag it
from here. Okay. Here we go. Yeah. Excuse me, human. What is this? Well, I mean,
I mean, it's a video game where we were shooting and killing. Well, do you find this amusing
to shoot and kill aliens? No, of course not. You see, those are frogs. What is a frog? Oh,
it's a life form here and it's a frog. And that's just like a jokey. We like, oh, look, it's a frog.
So you think it's funny? You think frogs are something that you kill? No, no, no, no, no,
we don't. I find that to be fucking disgusting and not amusing at all. In fact, this looks
kind of like Jerry. Jerry's like standing behind him. No, of course it's not. They're crabs.
Imagine if space invaders was the thing that got us like alien nuked.
That's like, yeah, that's like incredibly insensitive to the aliens. Right? That is the
plot of pixels. What? Oh, they're it's little cartoon characters. They're not real. It's not
it's not a thing. It's they're not what I don't even understand what they're supposed to be
depicting. First, you said it was some type of animal, which was ridiculous to even consider
that concept. Yeah, I'm sorry. Honestly, I'm just trying to make it so you don't fucking shoot me
with that thing you're pointing at me. Take me with you. Take me with you. This is hard.
You got to go quick because the longer this takes. OK, go. Come on. It's right there.
No, coward, coward move. Seriously. Damn it. I did it already. I don't care. I would be in 20
seconds. It can be the one room I don't do. Humanity is going to delete our entire media
catalog when the aliens show up. Yeah, there are a lot of media about how aliens we wipe them out.
They show up and we try to get rid of them as fast as possible. They're awful. We like hate
aliens. We hate them. We hate aliens. We paint them in such this crazy light where they show up
and fucking kill all of us and we have to kill them. How would we explain the thousands of
pieces of media about how much aliens are are are terrible and they're here to kill us all?
Or I feel like if you were an alien, you'd show up and you would see some of this shit and be like,
we need to get the fuck out of here, man. This is what they think we're doing. This is what
they think that we need to get out of here as soon as possible. We let's go to the next one.
I don't think I can do this. Let's go up here. Defeat all four different antibodies in a row.
How do I do that? How come you made the aliens stop sounding like nerds?
Because I want to stay alive when they show up. They're going to watch my stream and they're
going to be like, why did he make us sound like that? Why are we standing straight up?
Why is our posture always straight up? And we always have this kind of a voice.
That's not that's nothing what we're like. Why did you do that? You don't understand.
You called them idiots. Take me with you. Take me with you. I promise. I'm a good human.
And I go down, right? I'm like, no, please. I go down on my knees. Take me with you. No,
you don't want any of the other humans. They're awful. They're terribly filthy.
But here's another thing, right? In reality, what do you do with the take me with you guy?
If the aliens leave, right? What do you do with the take me with you guy?
Do I get in trouble? Right? Do I do I get like arrested for that? The aliens show up and I'm
like, take me with you. Leave. Leave with me and all these awful, horrible pieces of shit.
This filthy fucking humans on this planet. Take me with you. And then the ship goes away and it's
like, hey, dude, what the fuck was up with that? And what the hell do we do about that?
You okay? Work stress. Sorry. Somebody said, I say I hate humans all the time. Yeah, that's
yeah. But I think this would be this is more real, right? If the aliens show up and you're
like actively wanting to work with the aliens, does that turn out to be like treason to humanity?
It's not illegal to want to leave Earth. Yeah, I know. All right. Does that change if
all right. But how does that change for you guys? Like, okay, so does it change for you if
the aliens land and the take me with you guy goes and walks over to the other side where the
aliens are turns around and stands with them shoulder to shoulder and is like, huh, does that
change it for you? No. Why would it? Does it? What does he kill other humans? Huh? Yeah. What's the
line though? What's the line for you have joined the aliens and now the aliens left?
Where's the line? Are the aliens killing people? Yeah, let's let's talk about like,
like a total takeover alien invasion scenario. And now take me with you guy is there.
Are the aliens evil? All right. Let me beat this level and we'll talk. Are the
aliens hot? Uh, I don't. That's a good question. All right. Let's say they are.
Let's say the aliens. Let's say they let's say they are. How many of you are going to be the
take me with you guy for girl? Huh? Oh, no. Now we got a whole lot of traitors to humanity here now.
Very interesting. Now we got some traitors to humanity all of a sudden because the aliens
are hot. Very interesting. All right. I gotta beat this level. Did someone say that the aliens
party? Um, no, not at all. Not in the slightest. Sorry. Childish behavior. What is this party?
Loud sound effects come out of device. Beverages are served that make you stupid. What is this
nonsense? Yeah, but yeah, yeah, yeah. But then that happens. But then one of the aliens during
the course of the time, during the course of the movie or whatever is seen smoking out of a bong.
You know what I'm saying? They got to cut to one of these aliens smoking out of a bong.
And that alien is the one that joins the humans. But what the hell you've got all this alien
technology and you've got, you're so smart and you, you know everything about the aliens,
but you're just smoking a bong as a comedy character. Fuck. We can't get you to help us
at all. Even though you're on our team, you're the comic relief of this whole scenario,
but we have that alien here. That's, that's on our team. Oh, but he's like looking fucking high
over there and he's, he's got like red eyes and he can't help us. Dude. This happens in the movie
Paul. Oh, nice. Okay. What is this movie, Paul? What is the subject matter of this movie?
All right. I got it. I don't know what this defeat all four in a row though that you just
described literally the exact, the whole movie. That's the whole movie. Is this movie 15 minutes?
Please beat the level. Are you even trying? Please dodge the attacks. I just want to see
the gameplay. This person's watching the stream muted. This would be an unbearable muted. Yeah,
that's true. Okay. Defeat. How do I, I got one. Do I just have to pick them up really fast?
One, maybe just really fast. I don't get it. Eat all four different antibodies in a row.
Watch the Paul trailer. I'm curious. I need to know. I don't, I don't, I remember this movie
coming out. Let's watch the Paul trailer. Okay. Hold on. All official trailer. Are we about to
watch everything we just talked about? That's, I'm going to laugh my ass off if that's the case.
Okay. Hold on. Let me get it at HD. It's not even in HD. This is 360p video. All right,
let's give it a watch. I got to mute this. Let's see if it is, it is word for word,
the exact scenario we just said. Okay. Three, two. They do exist.
They don't do that.
I'm closing in. I can feel it in 24 hours. He's going to wish he never set foot on planet Earth.
I want that little green prick dead ASAP. Hi there.
I got my people primed and ready to pick me up. So what happens if you get caught?
I'm going to cut out my brain.
Buzzkill. Let's lighten the mood. Shall we Clive? When did you last get laid?
The individual that you're traveling with is highly dangerous. He's not dangerous. He's kind
of rude. This is small on my planet. A couple of times I've seen him scratch his face and
why was that edited? That was weirdly edited. Sometimes I've seen him scratch his space man
balls. This is small. A couple of times I've seen him scratch his space fan balls.
Why do they edit and splice them together weirdly? She's talking about space man balls.
We look like a family. Hey, we're just a couple of regular guys walking down the street.
Where's the bong? Where's the bong?
This is the most fun I have ever had.
I like this song. Stoke the fire.
There's no bong in this movie.
There's no bong in that movie. You did that joke. This is you.
I'm going to watch that. I'm watching that movie like tonight. Bro, this is the trailer.
All right. Let's get going. You've done that bit before. Yeah. Well, come on. It's true. He
smokes weed. I'm going to watch the movie. I'll come back to you. I'm going to give you. I'm going
to. I will live. I will give live notes to the movie call and I'll come back to you.
This one doesn't have a. It's kind of loud. There we go. One hour.
Holy shit. That's a long time. An hour. Please live tweet it. I got it.
Dermot, why are you such an anti-noise old lady now? What does that mean?
Ooh, new power. And I actually think I need to die to this. No, wait, what? Just do it.
There's still two things I didn't die to in here. That one's no.
This is a good one. I'm putting this on the stream for a minute. I like this one.
You would have no idea how often this happens, though. I do this almost every single night.
I told you this before. It sucks so bad. If this is a warning to you all, stop, get off of
YouTube shorts, get off of TikTok. And I'm telling you why. Those of you that scroll that shit in
bed, you can relate to this. And I've done it only a few times, but my God, I have fallen asleep
to a YouTube short that just doesn't ever end over and over and over and over. It never stops
in a place for like four hours. It's just like, get it. Can you set a limit to how much something
can play? Is it like, OK, after 50 times, it should stop. Does it just loop forever? And then
I wake up and it's just burnt in my brain, this 25 second clip of just the exact same
cadences in the beat and the whole thing. It's just TikTok will tell you to take a break after
an hour. Instagram stops after two hours and your phone is at zero percent. It should be like
10 times or like 100 times. Like that's a lot. What is the original pic?
The original picture is me watching XQC play slots.
You're a mega fan. What is this room? What is this? God, how long did it say?
Give me some stimulation. I am. Oh, I'll try to get 30. Yeah, I fall asleep to something sitting
on my chest every single night. And it just that iPad just sits there and God have mercy on your
soul. If it is a YouTube short for a TikTok. And then do you guys do this too? Where you
you refuse to give it up. You'll wake up with one eye open and painfully put this like decrepit
finger out and slowly push the screen up and then slowly go back to bed.
I almost feel like it's one of those like an old man finger from like the old animated movies
where it's like a bony and bent and like it's like all decrepit and the fingernail is like
five inches long and you know what's going to happen. But for some reason you don't just
turn it off. Just close the just close it. Just get off YouTube. Why? No, I just I want to see.
I want to see what the next food hack is real quick and then I'm going right to bed. I swear.
Oh, oh, that's how they do it. Please repeat 100 times in my sleep and fuck up my dreams
and screw up my brain in the process. Shit. I did it. I did it. I don't need to do it again.
I already got it. What's the criteria for this one? Survive five seconds in all unlocked rooms.
This is how I watch your streams. That's that's fine. That's cool. That doesn't bother me. One's
10 seconds. Are you going to do anything when you're going to play a Miku game? I don't know.
When's the next Miku game coming out? I don't know. What's the first thing you'd show an alien?
Miku Miku concert. All right. There's equal parts of my brain would say the alien would turn to you
and go. I hate this or turn to you and go. Your planet is now saved. We are going to move on.
Carry on with everything you're doing here. It's all up to speed with us. That's a 50 50 coin flip.
That's either a planet gets obliterated or we get new alien technology. I don't know if that's worth
the risk. This one is die with over four disks in the room. OK, there's only two. How do I get more
of these to come out? Sir, die with over four disks in the room. Absorb. What are the zero?
Wait, am I spawning them? That was weird. I kind of OK, I can spawn them, but I don't know.
I don't know. Survive five seconds in all unlocked rooms. OK, so we're not quite there yet.
Defeat or gatekeepers. This will end your current. Whoa, no, no, no, no. Wait, what? Wait a minute.
This is based on runs. So end your current run. Wait, what's going on? Am I out of am I out of
run tokens or something? This will end your run. Oh, OK, I was OK. I get it. For a second,
I thought it was I was ending my game. I was going to start over or something.
He is so stoned right now. No, I'm not. I'm not. I just have massive attention problems.
Dude, you're definitely high. No, I have not. I have not consumed any cannabis products since
the Saw 2 stream. I think on stream, I can do way longer than that. Defeat four gatekeepers.
All right, this one more boss somewhere. Let me try to get to a minute. Oh, that was weird.
I got 20 seconds of art. Defeat all four different antibodies in a row. I don't get that one.
You have to die from everything. Second I see a new song, I'm going to die from it.
Oh, it's right there. Old one. You like about doing weed on stream for that one or not?
You both said you were high during that stream and not. Oh, you must have missed when I when
I told everybody that I lied. Yeah, you're thinking of the Hitman level and Hitman 3.
There was a level that was this big concrete level that I was walking around in circles and
it was it was awful for me. I couldn't figure it out. I was really frustrated.
So everyone was like, dude, you have to be high. And I was like, yeah, yeah, I am.
Yeah, you got me. I just made that up. That did not happen. That was I made it up.
Give me that. I have to I have to get hit by this gold one. Nice. OK, honestly, the last time that I
was truly inebriated on stream, like inebriated, like really inebriated was probably, I don't know,
maybe at some point mid last year, last year, not this year at all. It hasn't happened at all since
Resident Evil 7. No, it definitely was after that, too. That was that was a long time ago.
One of the V.R. streams probably I always drink during the V.R. streams, which is both the best
and worst idea ever. Period cart. Um, I don't I wasn't really I'm talking like drunk. Is it Morrowind?
I don't know. I don't remember. It's been long enough where I really don't remember.
And it is the infamous Minecraft run. Yeah.
No, fuck. I already got 20 seconds. Who cares? What about the Among Us stream?
No, I don't think I I don't think I was doing anything on that.
Did I have a few drinks during the Among Us V.R. stream? I don't think so.
Yeah, I was I was sick. Yeah, I had like I think I think I had covid. Yeah. Or I did I have covid at
that point. That was around that time. Yeah, it was during the covid. Yeah. This one is pretty
difficult. I need to get to 20. Damn it gets so overwhelmed. I might actually do the clones with
this one. You're going to play Among Us again? No, probably not. I don't think so. All right,
there's 10. Damn, this one is hard to get to 20. Am I collecting them too fast? What's the what's
the issue here? You got to be faster. I think you're right. I think it's all about speed.
That would have been sick if I had done it. I don't know if I get this one.
Shit. Maybe I'm going to be slow. You beat Virgil. You can do this. That's true. Yeah,
it's it's definitely slow. Fuck. I only use the slow when I'm at at least 10 to 12 seconds.
Holy shit. This was really hard. Damn it. All right, come on. Let's go. Yes. Got it. Let's go.
Yes. Let's go. There was no enthusiasm on that one. What was the problem with this one?
Oh, yeah. And one of you guys can do this. 20 seconds in the room. That's fish black. No.
Ignoring. Ignoring what? Phantom gatekeeper. Do I die? OK, there's one song here I didn't die to.
Not that one. It doesn't even read chat. No, I mean, maybe like once like once or twice a stream.
I'll look over and be like, I'll read like one or two words. We recorded. It's my birthday.
I mean, it's been yes. Oh, I want to announce this because I know people have been waiting
for this real announcement. Ladies and gentlemen, at some point in the middle of June, Sorcery
will return. We'll do a recap. We can figure out exactly what was going on and where we were.
Sorcery is coming back. I'm actually going to play the third episode. No bullshit. I'm going to play
it. Sit back with a nice hot cup of coffee. Just relax. Play a choose your own adventure game.
Oh, that's sad. Damn it. I need that. Sorcery equals dog shit. I just want to make sure you
understand. You just sided with the aliens in this chat. That's a that's a treasonous statement to
humanity. Now you have to start spamming. Take me with you quick. Take me with you.
There we go. What's this? That guy's brave. Yeah, we're getting close. Die from 45 different disc
types. There's still one in here that I didn't die to. When's the hexes and spells stream? I need
to request work off for that. I still don't understand this one. They die from 45 different
disc types. Does that count as one? There it is. Absorb discs and bring them into the other room.
See, now you are thinking you are thinking. That's that's a lot of thought. Does that actually
work? OK, so now I'm going to die. Or do I have to beat the level? Well, I can't beat the level.
OK, let's die. I just fuck it up. I might have. OK, now kill me. OK, it does work. It do exist.
OK. Wow. Wait, what? There's only three. Hmm. Get a disc that duplicates. That's very smart.
I'll come back. All right. Ten seconds. Survive for 10 seconds. Oh, this is different.
All right. Survive for 10 seconds. Do I have to clear this? I wonder what this means.
I don't think I have to do this. It's kind of cool, though. Yes, I do. It's the only way to make
time go up. I would kick your ass and swindle stones. I'm sorry. Nobody is as full of shit as
me. So I can guarantee you that is one thing that I know I would beat anybody in this room.
It's swindle stones. If I didn't have to be in the same room as other people and not be like
and like turn red and shit like I would be so good at poker. I'd be amazing at poker.
I'm Mr. Albertson. It's time for you to bet. I have to do the thing. I've got like I got pocket
aces. I'd be like. And I start turning purple and shit and people would be like, oh, I know he's
I know what he has. It's so funny. That's one of those things where, oh, hey, don't tell anybody
what you have. You're going to win. I don't have anything. Could you could I. All right.
Could I wear like a ski mask? Would that be like, OK, could I wear like a mask?
No, you can't. So but you're allowed to wear sunglasses at a poker table.
Why couldn't I wear like a why couldn't I put on like a Ronald Reagan mask or something?
Or how big can the sunglasses be? Could I have gigantic, goofy sunglasses that cover
my whole face? You can't hide your face is put as isn't sunglasses hiding your face.
Give me a new power. This is not good here with an alien mask.
No, I'm talking about like a private poker tournament, like a poker tournament or something
where a full fursuit. Damn it. This one's kind of hard. Slow would be best for this one.
There's no time. So let's do it slow or those in a timer. They might be.
Fuck slow. It's definitely slow for sure. Oh, if I was in like a private poker tournament
and I had like a voice changer and a ski mask on stuff, people would still know what I had.
The only difference is instead of it being you could see, you could still see my expressions
and stuff instead of being like, oh, it would be like, oh, oh, last. I still didn't do this one.
20. Does it cost to do that? It doesn't. That's a big deal. I'm trying to use it too often.
No, give me slow. Wait, maybe carve the middle out first so I don't have to go as far.
But no, go on the edge first. Damn it. I can. It's really this one's not even that hard. It's just
they're doing the same pattern as the spiders and Isaac. And you know that I can't handle those.
It's that erratic like pause, go pause, go pause, go pause, go damn it. I had it.
Come on. I got it. I got it. Not even three out yet. Here we go. I think you imbecile.
That one was stuck up there in the top and I just fuck. That's another villain word.
Imbecile, imbecile, imbecile, imbecile. This is one of those that I have to get 20 seconds
or I refuse to move on because I'm so close. I know I'll get it. No, I thought it was going
to go the other way. OK, go. Yeah. OK, thank goodness. 10 seconds in this one.
You should play Google Snake. Snake infuriates me. What was that snake game? It's an EO.
It's an EO game. I played it for a little while and I was obsessed with it.
Yes, slither, slither, slither. Yep, slitherio. I was obsessed with it and it was I hated it at
the same time. You would get huge and then somebody would just do that thing. Some little
new spawn Andy would just fly in front of you and drive next to you, next to you, next to you,
cut in front of you. This has ruined everything. And you know, you're sitting there thinking like,
all right, buddy, you got to work your way up. You're coming to the big leagues right now.
Get out of here. What do you think you're doing? Right? Like that's a what? That's a who do you
think you are scenario? Who do you think you are? My name's up on the leaderboard. Yours isn't. You
just spawned. Get out of here. What do you think you are? Who do you think you are? I am. That's a
great video. All right, I'll take 29. Still two discs. I had to get hit by survive five seconds
in all unlocked rooms. What was this one? I think I could probably get it. This is going to be like
annoying to look at though. So it's going to be kind of hard in the eyes. Just be aware of that.
It's already over. Damn it. What was this one? Survive 10 seconds in all unlocked rooms. Survive
90 seconds total in this zone. Play Breath of the Wild. I stubbed my toe last night and it
really hurts. I don't think I can. I don't think I can perform that well. Play tears of the kingdom
then instead. I would. I just, I said I have an appointment I have to get to. It's an important
one so I have to get to it. When did you say you wanted me to stop by? When did you want me to do
that? When? What time? What time did you want me to? What time is it? Like 7 30 is when you want to be?
That's that's fucking crazy. My appointment is at 7 45 but I'm not gonna do man. Sorry.
Wow. Shit luck. What? I was thinking about doing it. I was thinking about playing it at 7 45. I
have to. I have an appointment I have to get to. That's what's weird. That's crazy. He's done this
bit before you can tell. I'm sure I have. I don't know. I mean unironically I do. There is a lot of
work to do this week. Okay. Like on a completely unironically. There's a lot going on this week.
So I mean that's hey I can't play. I cannot play Breath of the Wild or tears of the kingdom.
A lot going on. Okay. I want to absorb one of these because does that does that count as
four? You got time for disc world. This game is called disc room. Just say you don't like it and
move on. I do. I'm just fucking around. Guys I cannot start tears of the kingdom which is like a
6 000 hour game before I beat the first 1500 hour game and beat it already. Yeah but I just don't
want to right now. I got a lot to do still. You don't start the first Hobbit movie then skip to
the next one. I actually feel like you kind of do. No you don't. I'm making a dumb joke. Absorb it.
All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. So this is going to count as four discs right.
It's going to spam a bunch. There it is. Thank you. Thank you. Wait what? I would. Can I just do it?
How come that didn't count? It just said I had it. I just said I did it. That's weird. With a gold
one. Okay. I just picked up a gold one. What is it? Will that? Can I bring that somewhere? Die with
four discs in the room. I guess I'll just do this one. When I unlock everything I'll probably have
a clear picture of what to do. I wonder if there's a final boss. How did you find this game? Um uh
there's a game path. What's wrong with that? Game pass. What's wrong with that? Oh I almost had it.
I mean it's a month and you get access to games and game pass is actually good. Yeah yes it is.
Um at that person say that you're fucking awesome. You know what I mean? Are the elder
wilds dlc? Oh I I really liked outer wilds. I was really confused by it though. I heard the dlc was
more confusing. I got it. There we go. Oh shit we're almost to the last few rooms.
All right this is out of 25. What is this? Well I need to die from that. It is but a guide is acceptable.
Okay. I mean as long as if I could use a guide and people wouldn't be like wow dude
you stink. I mean you guys would say that anyways but shit. These need to spread out. I'm gonna get
killed. This dude smells like a game pass. Damn it. Come on stop. I can do this. 25. You stupid.
You hate sorcery? I just gave you a date. I said when I was playing sorcery. I gave you a hard date.
June something. Oh my goodness. All right come on. Stop. It's it's not even hard because they
change cores. I need to do it. It's objective. It has to be done. Oh my god. They just track you.
Can you finish tf2? Do you know I got this massive craving for a man versus machine because I saw
that overwatch was just like oh no we're not really doing that anymore. I was like oh well
it's funny that was the one thing that I really actually wanted to play in overwatch
if in overwatch 2. I was like oh okay that's the only reason why I would play overwatch 2.
That was my sole reason to play it because like I don't I mean I had fun with overwatch
but then I was saying when they said oh we're doing a pve thing I'm thinking you're talking
about man versus machine is that what you're talking about is that what you mean by that
because if that's what you mean by that you've got I'm signed up now so hearing that it was
kind of not really what they're doing anymore was well now I but I want to do that oh oh it's
right there yes 13 out of 25 what does that mean 13 is it how many of these get spawned
no 15 out of 25 wait kill me 12 out of 25 what am I looking at here 12 out of 25
question mark the question mark 14 out of 25 13 out of 25 I don't get it 19 out of 25 hold on
9 out of 25 how many tiles are there 5 10 15 20 25 there's 25 tiles what 11 what 11 of what
wait there's okay there's different kind of shades under here there's gray and then there's black
does that matter only uncovered the gray ones all right now kill me zero out of 25
is it only uncovered the black ones that's here oh shit oh okay it's gonna be that's gonna be hard
oh damn it that should be it right yes survive for 20 seconds
it's my favorite track of the whole night oh I almost had it first try that would have been so
cool oh shit we're good there it is that's fine the ultimate gatekeeper is right here
this is not a tile one all right we're gonna find where these are this one's gonna be weird
isn't it no same one same pattern I think it's the same pattern okay well let's go get a raid
from chibli thanks chibli welcome everybody currently playing I was about to say attack of
the clones I don't know why I was gonna say attack of the clones but thanks for the raid
welcome how are you hope you had a good stream where was the end too no thanks for the raid this
is one's called homesick it's one of the last levels in the game and that's why and there's
a difficulty and that's why actually it's kind of horrible I think any dash for this that thing
just expands or blast would be good too oh my god I don't think I can get close enough to do that
now I'll go back to dash I dash through it find out I cannot he'll complete breath of the wild in
my dream move I need that last tile now move thank you all right survive 10 seconds in all
unlocked rooms did I do that uh-oh really which one is this one again I didn't live 10 seconds
in here how how this is easy you can play devil may cry 5 yeah I want to I'm kind of traumatized
from devil may cry for a little bit though oh my there we go this one's still weird this one
okay I have to unlock this how do I unlock this one survive all five seconds in all rooms we have
to survive in here all right this is this is it this is the ultimate gatekeeper let's go let it
kill me this is gonna be horrible there's still one disc I haven't been hit by oh damn it I had
that I got the pattern a little bit but sorry no go outside first that's the way to do it
good I need to get hit by that but I'm not gonna yet that was a really bad idea oh my god all right
did I even get hit by the right thing shit I got caught where's the sweaty pick you promised
oh that's right yeah uh maybe I'll put it in discord or something in like
this one's just all you just gotta be patient I'm trying to go too fast
for no reason damn it oh you slowed me down at the same time I'm kind of in trouble here
all right halfway come on really sorry don't be stupid get out of the way oh this is bad
I did it no I got it I do need to get hit by the second phase I have to get the phase two and then
we're good shit this game's fun yeah it's just like a it's an addicting it's addicting game
you must defeat it I will try to defeat it in a minute oh good thing
all right I need to get hit by one of these that's not it what's the one disc I didn't get hit by
survive 10 seconds oh it's this one where I need to make the time go up to 10 this one's 10
this one this is the only one well surviving five unlocks one surviving 10 unlocks one
this is an undefeated gatekeeper I actually do have to do it all right let's do it then
shit I got that thing gets me every time just don't move all right this part's really easy
there's no world where I should actually get hit by any of this the next phase on the other hand
is awful it sucks you into the oh I got it no I didn't did I big bang I think I did it
is it gonna explode okay that freaks me out big time because of a couple days ago oh cool all
right well I want to see the other rooms you have to restart it I liked it hello Mr. Albertson this
is the sorcery enjoyers high council speaking once again and we are happy with your agreement
of more guaranteed sorcery in mid-june for now we shall off our plans of making flanker real
but we could go back on that in an instant if you once again lie we're looking forward to mid-june
good day Mr. Albertson the council's happy that makes me happy I'm fine how many wood planks do
you think you could eat zero wouldn't I wouldn't eat wood what am I a goat who eats what is an
animal that eats wood who eats it that's kind of cool 499 deaths not 500 deadliest room I died
67 times in the lobotomy room and the golden disc killed me 60 times how termite yep what's
going on now we're going ah this is new stuff okay can I go back oh this it just makes it hard
hard hard all right but I let's try it survive 10 seconds new game plus yeah you gotta go backwards
it seems wait there's okay if the other player dies do I lose because that makes this way worse
I don't know I can't tell I didn't lose I guess it's still fine maybe not it's hard to tell
this one yeah this is definitely way harder geez okay yeah I think you just go backwards
it's kind of like uh what dark world and meat boy what about your appointment
oh yeah I hey my what was my um what was it for uh it was it's actually really funny because
I really do have to leave it's not a joke I like have to leave very soon I do those of you that
don't know you trickled in here I would implore you to check out Ranboo's stream on the 24th the
26th and the 28th I will be a major participant in the generation loss project it's gonna be crazy
yeah the it'll be on night button everything dude what the fuck are you doing at 7 p.m.
dude I said there's still plenty of time in the day at seven what because this isn't this isn't
like a diner that serves breakfast food it closes at two there's still plenty of day but no I don't
have an appointment I was just making that up we made a joke there are a lot of things I have to
do though before uh before these shows it's gonna be really really interesting I I definitely
check it out again that's the 24th 26th and 28th of this month of this coming week
and one of the mods link uh stream I'm lying no I'm not I'm I'm gonna be on this show
uh I'm not making that up prove it okay go to Ranboo's Twitter and go look at the teasers
that have been put out I don't want to okay then yeah I don't want to
I have to get 20 seconds in the dark world or I'm gonna be pissed is it even possible for the
purple yeah I don't even know if the purple character can live maybe that might be a part
of a really really hard challenge each room the purple character has to stay alive all right one
more try and I'm moving on this is too addicting this is the kind of stuff that I would have played
just in my bedroom all night I would not have stopped an old flash game oh I'm in trouble
this would have ruined my sleep in high school yeah damn it honestly the corners are the biggest
problem that was pixels that was pixels mate pixels duh that sucked I thought I touched it
no what about uh n plus I actually didn't play that much n plus I played a lot of meat boy
and what was that there's a couple of the really big ones the ones where you had to shoot
people out of cannons and go further and further and further and upgrade upgrade upgrade upgrade
upgrade stuff like uh burrito um what was it get learned to fly was one toss the turtle
what's the one I'm thinking of though burrito bison that's the one toss the turtle I would love
a those dominated for a long time then they kind of went away forever I missed those games
I wish somebody would make a new version of one of those I feel like those would do really really
well now can you imagine that with a bunch of content and a ton more to do there's been a
couple of remakes right and kind of re-releases of those but not a brand new one and if it exists
please tell me so I can obsess over it damn it burrito bison's on the app store yeah I've beaten
it already though that came out a while ago that came out a long time ago on the app store
toss the turtle remake what about tank artillery game I remember artillery dude you know what man
why don't we just play some of those one of these days I would just sit there and play burrito bison
or learn to fly or toss the turtle all day just sit here and just hang out and play it let's put
that on the list that sounds fun I have to get this uh you should do it right now uh I I can't
I actually can't what about I want to be the guy yeah let's revive the kind of old flash uh nights
that I used to do here DOS nights flash nights they were fun I can't leave until I get the 20
seconds I can't leave flash is dead but I believe there are certain things that you can still play
them with I did a absolutely minuscule amount of research but I think there is a way to do it still
uh yes flashpoint I need to look into it a little bit more there's a couple other old games that I
really want to try to track down again I'm trying to remember what the context of this particular
game was let me see if I can figure it out no one adult swim unicorn game that's right
it was one where you had to like bounce stuff you had to like throw it a certain distance or
something and it was insanely insanely frame perfect detailed I forget what it was called
no not angry birds no not not angry birds I almost just beat it and I wasn't even looking
monkey kickball was that it shit backyard baseball I don't think it was backyard baseball
I saw it wasn't a wasn't will neff playing that for a while you see he's like he's the
goat of that game right this is the one right here guaranteed oh I thought I had it that was
doing so good I gotta get them out of the corner that's death you piece of shit I have to get
through that oh I can't leave we're gonna miss my appointment stir said hey man where are you our
appointment was a bit ago yeah but I my uh my stomach hurts I don't feel good I don't feel good
I can't I can't go take me with you why did you write that I don't there's no context for you to
write that take me with you yeah stir thinks he can beat this game let's see him do dark world
like me and I'm doing right now give me the dash have you been in this level for like 15 hours
yeah I'm I got to 19.2 seconds it was 19.2 no I think it's it's definitely slow
what is it maybe absorb why is this one what is the right place why is that gold it is not that
power at all it's slow this is the one right here I'll get it right now that didn't even touch me
come on no yes short stream Andy yeah I know I know I'm just streaming you can stop now I
yeah I know I mean I'm already I'm already late to this appointment so hard mode is 10 seconds to
clear uh yeah I know I just trying to get the 20 20 is the real completion of the level it might
even be higher on some of them how am I even going to touch the squares in the middle I've just made
it down here oh oh dear oh dear oh there's no getting out of that that's true get him right at
the beginning that's right what I do just stay out of the corners and I'll be all right oh he's
got to move how he's got to move I was close oh my goodness that was so perfect too it just they
he just spammed it at me keep getting purple guy killed the purple guy hey I'm not in control of
the purple I already blew it I didn't go in the middle first get the ones in the middle and I'm
fine no I can't stop playing this dude that void whatever it is pushed it over you saw that that
was annoying sticking with this formula you should be able to get them all needs to go backwards
they're gonna shoot it oh come on why am I doing that I'm getting worried about you I'm fine don't
worry about me hey don't worry about me I didn't go in the middle well these ones are definitely a
lot more precision based it's a great play gonna work out though I can't move oh I was pushed up
to the edge of the thing yeah I couldn't move you can't walk into this you can't dash through
it either oh I thought I had it somebody should make a compilation just um and have it have to
be no time in the middle of every time that I've gone oh just string them all together I wonder
what it sounds like be like I sound like a banjo kazooie character probably get out of the
fucking way oh my god I can't touch it I how am I supposed to touch that there were two that
were spawned by then it almost took up the whole entire map all right 10 more tries and I'm done
this one doesn't count it only counts if I clear the middle first okay this now is a real attempt
10 more real attempts I don't count that one either oh none of these counted I have to make
one full revolution around here and get to phase two all right this is a real attempt now oh sloppy
that one doesn't come that is so annoying why is that that keeps killing me and I just shouldn't
I'm getting just too a hair too close that doesn't count either I've done two I'm in trouble
I should play Hearthstone instead no it happened again I just I what I don't those things never
killed me until I gave myself a amount of times I can do this still I I can never touch the ones
in the middle from here I gotta get the ones in the middle right now yeah they have to get
him first otherwise it just becomes I don't think becomes possible oh you piece of shit
that didn't even touch me all right five more that's it no that doesn't count either I'm getting
sloppy you never told us about the skunk dream oh that's right I I mean I told it in um what
pre-stream or the discord or something I had a dream that I mean the extent of the whole dream
it really is not that intriguing it's not wild it's not something that is going to make you go wow
what a crazy dream I had a dream that they were what I thought were cats in the room like oh yeah
like there's just cats in here and they were just kind of walking around and hanging out
like oh yeah of course there's here's here are the cats and it turned out though that they were
skunks and I looked down and realized that they were skunks and was like pet I had been petting
these like oh hey like hi like kitty it was a skunk but they were cats in my brain and they
were really friendly they wasn't like weird it was just yeah I just hanging out with some skunks
that's the whole dream there was a baby skunk from what I remember and I'm a petting the baby
skunk's head and is doing that thing it was closing its eyes and leaning its head up
did you know just barely holding its head up like oh yeah I like that that's it and then I woke up
what does that mean I have not seen a skunk I have not talked about a skunk I've not heard
anything about a skunk why did I have a dream that I was hanging out with skunks and we were cool
it was like oh yeah this is cool they're with friends it means you smell all right 10 more
I have to pull I gotta pull a plug right now yeah I gotta I have to pull the plug
I have to I will I'll never leave yeah this is the end I'm uninstalling the game damn it it didn't
work I can't wait for the toss the turtle stream that's gonna be fun that was it right there I just
got pushed up when they spam all in one direction at me I can't even it's over just like you
uninstalled breath of the wild you got me why have I not gone back to breath of the wild when
I said I would well because I needed to make room oh my god that was it too it's never I'm
never gonna be able to do this yeah I needed to make room from monster hunter rise and I thought
I was gonna free up some space by just deleting this fucking game and I really wanted to play
monster hunter rise and I just I accidentally uninstalled it and now my games are gone all my
save files are out of here and I was really unhappy about it I was really pissed off about it
and then I smashed my wii over my knee I had to switch dude what yeah I went into I went into the
into my closet I got the wii out and I smashed the wii instead of the switch for some reason
apparently people heard that is weenie yeah I got yeah dude I gotta get pissed off I was
fucking furious nice I smashed my weenie uh I smashed my weenie really hard I was pissed
all right I'm done I'm done after this I have 10 minutes to do this that would be four hours on
stream that's it I have 10 minutes to get this done you can't do it it's pushes you people got
timed out earlier for saying penis flattening stream yeah but that was completely out of context
context where's the context you got context if you can't if you just say hey when is the penis
flattening stream you're gonna you're gonna get timed out but if I had if we had just talked about
how I dropped a book on my penis then okay now you there's context for you to just discuss you
just where's the context it's important I never told I didn't tell you guys this but it's it's
funny enough to tell you no no enough time has passed remember when I went on break I went on
that break where I was like okay I'm gonna be gone for a few weeks the first day of that break
first day okay let's go over it very quickly I um it's like all right it's time I'm on my break
I'm gonna I'm gonna just relax for a little bit and and look it's just so you know sometimes I
just want to it's time to relax right it doesn't happen all the time doesn't happen every day
but I want to relax and I'm I'm gonna you know 21 and older in a state where it is legalized
I um I put took in some marijuana product okay there you go so a little while goes by and it's
fine and it's this is everything's good just hanging out it's like all right this is cool
start of this break I feel like I kind of needed it a lot of stuff is going on um stuff that you
guys don't really know that you probably will very soon but it's very exciting but things we'll talk
about and one of those things obviously was rambo's show because that's a huge deal and
it's really cool but I digress I shit my pants I shit my pants and I went up to take care of this
and in the process of taking care of this I clogged the toilet so I shit my pants
went to the bathroom I can take care of this this has not happened in a very long time a very long
time so I clogged the toilet and I realized there's no plunger I don't have one the one that I did
have I wanted to replace because it's like you know every so often you get rid of a plunger
you get rid of it because like it's kind of at some point right you need to replace it
so I couldn't go anywhere right like I'm I'm I'm I'm what am I gonna do so I'm a little bit
you know I'm a little inebriated I'm obviously not gonna not gonna get in a car
so I contemplated I was like I think I have to I think I have to call italics and see if he'll go
buy me a plunger and deliver it to the house it didn't get that far because thank thank god
thank god it ended up just it went down and I was like oh thank god yeah and imagine that
conversation that I would have had to have hey man um yeah I uh I shit my pants and then I clogged
the toilet and I I'm not I'm not gonna drive anywhere but of course it's not happening
can you you know maybe we'll give you a plunger and come and deliver it and I'll pay you I was
gonna I was gonna pay you know I was gonna pay whatever it took why are you self-reporting all
this I don't know I think it's kind of funny don't make a moment out of this why that's just a stupid
story my embarrassing it's so funny because I ended up you know just kind of I think Holly
knew something was going on because like obviously you don't want to tell anybody like oh hey by the
way hey honey I shit my pants and clogged the toilet um I have I don't think I've seen her laugh
as hard as I did because no no it's both things happened both things happened in the same like
20 minute period so it's a come on come on you can't do that to me I'll take one of those things
as enough of an annoyance but both of them happening that's not okay that sucks oh that
was it how long you been on this level for I I haven't really been paying attention how long did
you how long did you clog the toilet if it because I didn't guys listen I it's not like I dropped an
you do you do you any idea what I'm referring to when I say this I think a lot of you might think
that there's like a cartoon dump in my pants when does that that's not how this plays out
that's not how that happens it's not like what stop talking I need to explain so people get
the real picture why was this topic brought up I've been sitting on this topic for like
four and a half weeks because I thought it was really funny afterwards like first day vacation
all this they all this happens in a row we don't want you to visualize it you don't have to just
listen to the sounds listen to my the sounds my voice talking all right this is the one right
here watch bro this is impossible did you flush your pants no I didn't flush my pants down what
are you talking about you guys are really overestimating like how how you're thinking
too deeply into the first part the first part is a oops it's not a whoa oh what the holy shit
whoa it's I can't even move no it's a oops it's a oops you guys are seriously putting way too much
into that first part yeah Holly just said you were being really quiet it's just silent why
yeah and that's abnormal because I'm usually just doing like Thanos impressions walking around the
house that's abnormal already okay you know when you kind of haven't seen your dog in like a few
minutes and it's like wait a minute where's the dog what's going on it's like what this I think
the dog's getting is a dog dog's getting into trouble I think the same with kids yeah stop
camping the middle you're camping the middle I would have had it oh shit it's been 10 minutes
come on move it's not fair oh no that's how you know he stopped it I am inevitable shits his pants
and is quiet now like wait a minute where's the next part of that usually after that you hear
slow footsteps in there I know what it's like to lose know so deeply that you're right it failed
a little that follow-up did not happen so where is he all right that's it I'm done I'm done I'm
done it's too addicting and I've it's challenging and hard and it's fun it's a fun game and I I want
to beat this level so bad but it's so tricky I'm done I'm done and I'm gonna install it that's it
all right goodbye that's enough I'll see you later that's enough that's the end of this one
I'm a new strategy new strategy let's see if it works all right I actually have a new strategy
let's go I'm leaving the bottom right corner and I'm gonna pull him to the bottom right corner
actually right now go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go I got it I think I got it
you can't move you actually can't move there's no escape the dash no you can't dash doesn't go
through the uh the void or whatever it is what are you doing all right this is the actually the
last one what the fuck are you I'm done what are you supposed to do I'm done that's it that was
cool and take a look at how much other hard shit there is to do in this game there's also
secrets and stuff that's fun I like it I like it a lot oh also I think um the 4k non crusty version
of the grotto beast commercial I know people have been asking for it looking for it it's
going to be going up on the grotto beast channel I think in the next little bit tonight you want
to see it without the crust you have to end on a win no that's a that's a fallacy that's a fallacy
but I'll see you later uh let's actually raid someone it's been a while I feel like
I've been streaming really late at night I haven't really had an opportunity to
pick anybody that I know uh who's live right now let's see hmm yeah Vinny's doing Sunday stream
awful games yeah let's go say hi to Vinny all right next raid we're next right I do we're
going to change it up we'll change it up change it up yeah Vinny obviously everybody loves Vinny
come on yeah all right so I'll see you guys the next time you see me will be on uh Rambu stream
I have a pretty major part of the generation loss project it's gonna be really really wild
really looking forward to it I would pay attention on the 24th the 26th and the 28th 24th the 26th
and the 28th and the 24th the 26th and the 28th okay you got it should be fun exciting
uh let's raid Vinny and I'll see you guys uh I will not see you live on my channel but I
will you will see me live um in the coming days to come okay 24th the 26th the 28th the 24th the
26th and the 28th sounds good don't shit yourself let's get the credits up thanks for subbing
everybody it's fun it's a fun day I did want to make sure I got some time in though before I
go do all this and where's the music where's the music dude oh it is up there okay the 4k HD
grotto beast commercial is there without the crust again studio yada did an unbelievably
beautiful job so we did want to make sure you got to see it clean as well of course the fine folks
at indie film factory go check it out if you want to check it out on the grotto beast channel where
are you gonna be on rambo's channel you'll see that's all I'm gonna say go check it out what
month is this one the 24th the 26th then the 28th go check it out this is next week oh the right
that's right I forgot about the music uh okay let me put the music on that's right I don't I
didn't put the music on what was I thinking ladies and gentlemen welcome to episode one
of food for thought the podcast where I talk about food and food stuffs sometimes maybe even
talk about other things that have nothing to do with food but we'll see how it goes on the first
episode so I don't really have a plan with this I just knew that it was something I wanted to do
eventually and something I've been thinking about but I think I'll first before we get into anything
I'll probably should probably list my favorite foods why would you be listening to a food
podcast before the person tells you what their favorite foods are I mean I I wouldn't listen
to it either my number one favorite food well I should probably start from my least most favorite
is that how it would probably go my least most favorite food is grilled chicken it's very versatile
to be used in a lot of different ways a lot of different casseroles and sandwiches you can put
it on a plate with some rice and and it'd be great it's just a very versatile piece of equipment
to use in the kitchen I eat grilled chicken probably every few days it's very easy to keep
in the fridge it's very easy to keep in the freezer but besides that I think my number nine
least most favorite food would probably have to be spaghetti spaghetti again also very versatile
you can put beans sometimes I would put beans on it excuse me oil red sauce white sauce doesn't
matter pasta is incredibly especially pasta spaghetti meatballs how many meatball fans do
I have out here I'm sure I have quite a few but I think that my favorite food would probably be
meatballs number one again how many times have you been at this grocery store you think yourself
what the heck am I even going to have for dinner tonight and I I don't know I had the answer to
that question is I don't know but it would usually be meatballs for me if not grilled chicken and
some bell peppers and asparagus um I think I I think that's probably it for this episode
I'll check back in with you all um on the next one which is probably going to be this Sunday
is sunday or saturday I I don't really have anything else to say I just those are my favorite
top 10 favorite foods and I just um yeah I I this is uh we'll we'll come back next week and
we'll talk about uh we'll talk about my favorite restaurants there's quite a few so we'll go through
those too because you really need to know this stuff before we get into anything really important
but that's it that's episode one this has been uh food for thought with me Jeremy Elbertson
78 years old today it is 2060 and that's how old I am today well it's not my birthday but I
would be I am 78 have a great night see you next week all right bye see you