It's a late night tonight, late start tonight.
Shay, don't wake up your parents.
How's everybody doing? How are you?
You know me. You already know who I am.
Finally, now it's time to go to bed.
I've had a very disappointing day today.
Are you ready to get vented at?
How this could have been a much more anger riddled rant.
Maybe three hours ago.
Some of you were in the chat.
And I was a little irritated, just maybe slightly, not very much.
Let me just open up my... I deserve this, okay? It's a powerade.
Yup.
I need these electrolytes today.
I deserve a purple powerade.
Uh, my Vive is broken.
That's not even a joke. It sucks.
I don't know what's wrong with it. I don't know what happened.
I streamed VR.
Like, what? A year ago?
Eight months ago?
I finished with it. Okay, we'll put it in the box for a little while.
I put the damn thing in the box.
Close it up. Nothing happened to it.
I didn't, like, dropkick this thing into the closet.
But, I got it out today. We're gonna do VR.
It's gonna come back.
And, hey, look at this. I already was streaming on this thing.
I've already got it to work, like, a year ago.
So I take it out of the box. I start plugging shit in.
And things are going fine. My lighthouses are fine.
They're connected. They're green. Everything's fine.
But the headset doesn't work.
I cannot get the headset to get recognized.
No matter what I do. I was sitting here for six and a half hours.
I was about to reinstall Windows.
That was the final straw.
But it was gonna take too long.
And I can play this game that we're gonna play tonight.
Not on VR. I'm gonna be the one person in this lobby not playing VR.
I'm gonna be a default regular screen guy.
Which, that's stupid.
I'm gonna be playing with Vinnie, Ross, and Giwi.
Hope I'm saying that name right.
It should be fun. I mean, it's a ghost hunting game. I'm sure it'll be cool.
But I tried everything.
Different USBs.
Different connectors.
I've reinstalled SteamVR. SteamVR Beta. SteamVR Alpha.
I uninstalled Steam. Reinstalled Steam. I restarted my computer a hundred times.
I did every Reddit fix. And usually the Reddit fixes work really well.
The Reddit fixes work very well.
None of them worked.
It's error code 108.
And I think my headset's just fucking broken.
I don't know how.
Drivers did them all. Did all the drivers. Updated every driver.
Guys, I even updated the drivers on your computer that you never update.
I updated my like, HID mouse compliant driver.
You don't even need that.
And I got it.
I got it every single driver.
I don't know what happened. I'm getting a new computer. Fuck this.
I'm gonna have a new computer.
This time, next July. No. Soon. Within a month.
I'm getting a new computer within the next month. Within the next couple of weeks.
We'll see.
But for now...
I'm gonna be joined pretty shortly here.
By Vinny.
Well, you know I love Vinny.
Me and Vinny been trying to... Hey, you wanna do something? Let's do like a stream together.
Hey.
Bingo.
VR stream.
That's right.
Oh, but my VR is broken.
Oh.
It's alright.
It should be... It still should be fun.
This is probably not gonna be a very long stream because it's starting so late.
And we got FTK to look forward to this weekend.
Which not much anybody has to do to prepare for that.
I'm probably gonna go live.
On...
Friday or even later today.
Like tonight before I turn this off.
And to kind of answer questions.
We'll see.
Server version mismatch?
What is... Why are you saying server version mismatch?
Why is everybody saying that?
That's what Vinny is saying.
Wait, I have the wrong version of the game?
Wait, can VR people not play...
With non-VR people? Don't make me even more sad than I already am today.
Don't make me even more sad.
No, they can't. Alright, alright.
I'm gonna... Let me reboot the game.
I'm gonna reboot the game.
I guess there was an update today.
Okay.
Don't make me even more sad than I already am.
Restarting game.
Let's see if there's an update.
Oh, and by the way, we were gonna like add each other on Steam and shit.
And I went into my friends.
I have like a thousand group invites.
I tried to decline the first one to make some room.
And my computer hanged.
Steam like crashed.
Come on Valve.
Do I have to individually click on every single one of these?
Mr. Popular?
No, no, this is over the course of like eight years.
This didn't happen like last weekend.
God, I need some of this Powerade right now.
Oh, let's see. Is it updated?
Alright, my Phasmophobia is updated right now.
Should be good.
Yeah, we're just chilling.
We're just chilling.
Guys, this is a late night stream.
This is an extra late night stream.
Get some of those fucking electrolytes to me.
Alright, loading game.
I'm probably gonna have to give a new friend code.
It's more like extra early for the...
Hey Storm, thanks for the 10 subs.
I know I'm gonna have Facecam on tonight.
But I haven't switched over yet because I don't want to leak the friend code.
Private game.
Let's see.
Alright, I got a new...
They can just join off the friend code, right?
I don't know what...
Yeah, they can.
Cool.
Is it game?
Ah, is it game?
Here.
Ready?
Ready to see me?
I don't know.
Am I ready to be on camera?
I didn't leak it.
I'm good.
I got the invite code.
Oh, don't you wish you knew what that fucking friend invite code was.
Oh dude, Vinesauce just joined my lobby?
It's been a rough day today.
Hang on.
Sorry about the noises.
Fire alarm going off?
One second chat.
Is this fire alarm?
Is this fire...
Is there a fire in Vinny's house?
How do I...
I can hear him.
I can't look at the board because I think the code's up there.
So, um...
Jerma?
Can you hear me?
I can see him.
Jerma.
Wait, hold on.
Can you not hear me?
I don't think he can hear me.
Press V.
Can you hear me?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, nice.
It's V.
The code is on the screen.
It's Vinny.
Hi.
Hey.
Well, it's V to talk too.
What's up, man?
Oh, V did...
Oh, hey.
How you doing, man?
It's nice to talk to you again.
I thought there was a fire alarm going off in your house.
Wait, what?
Does it sound bad?
No, I just hear like a...
Rii, rii, rii, rii.
Chat, do you hear it?
Fire alarm.
No, don't show my fucking warthand.
Why do I hear that?
Is that in my house?
Are you okay?
Do you need assistance?
What is my house?
It's like burning.
I hear crickets.
I usually do when I stream, but that's...
Yeah, me too.
Me too.
Is it weird?
Can I make it so that I don't have to push the talk?
This audio is like sounds pretty good.
It's good.
Yeah.
Um, I don't know though.
There's, there's some options, but it's, it's a little lacking in the VR end.
How is the VR by the way?
It would be better for you because you have a Vive, but it's not very index-friendly.
Yeah, I wish I could be there in the VR.
It's cool though.
Yeah, so chat, Jerma has some VR issues, headset, like just not turning on issues.
Yeah, I don't know what happened.
I've been trying to troubleshoot for the last six hours.
I have no idea what's wrong with my computer or what's wrong with the headset.
All I know is that I'm going to throw it into the garbage disposal and turn it on as high as it can go.
Six hours, you'll never get back, but maybe this will be worth it.
Hey, hey, it's, it's always worth it.
It's always worth it if, if we get to do something together.
That is just fantastic.
Thank you, Jerma.
Remember the last time we did something together?
It was Red Dead Redemption 2.
My computer sucked on that one too.
Should I, should I just like go stream at an internet cafe or something?
Um, you could go to a McDonald's.
No, I think that was Rockstar's fault more than anything.
Yeah, maybe.
It was still funny though.
So we can just blame Rockstar.
I have a question for you.
Is the code of this room on the screen right now on that wall?
The way that you did that, you're just like presenting.
Yeah, it's, I think it's hidden, but maybe it's only hidden for me.
Should I look?
I don't know.
Can you see it?
You're gonna need a new code, my dude.
New code?
All right.
Yeah.
Well, I guess, I guess I can't hide it for everybody.
Shit.
Well, hey, look at this.
Nobody's joining.
Oh, give them a minute.
Um, Ross is probably still doing the tutorial, but, uh, yeah, I'll just take a
seat while this is happening.
Yeah, I, uh, I, I did the tutorial a little bit, but I kind of don't really
know what it means.
I know that we, we have devices and we have to put books on the ground and
the ghost writes in the book and something like that.
You get a flashlight, you get a computer, a camera.
I have no idea how to play this game.
Yeah.
So there's, um, I got a kind of an idea.
Have you ever watched Ghost Adventures?
Ghost Adventures?
Or, uh, any of the Ghost Hunter shows?
Well, I've seen, uh, the ones with everybody's green.
Uh, there was lit up and overexposed in green.
Right.
Yeah, I've seen, I've seen clips.
Yeah.
So, um, it's just a variety of tools that you use to discover
spoopy ghosts.
And, uh, who is this?
I don't know.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, this is weird.
I think I can boot them.
What happened?
All right.
New code, new code.
Let's, I'm going to turn this off.
I don't want you guys to see it either.
I got to make it so I can fucking not have pushed it.
I don't want to do push to talk.
By the way, this game records all of everything you say.
There's like a, it's like speech recognition.
You're like, you actually talk to the ghost.
All right.
Hold on.
Audio.
Where is it?
Controls?
PC settings.
Local push to talk off, right?
That's just keep that off.
We booted Vinny.
Well, I don't know.
That guy might've just started screaming swears.
We've got to be careful.
All right.
Let's try this.
I got a new code.
I don't want you to see it.
I'm going to type it in here.
This is a late night stream guys.
Relax.
Okay.
Late night stream.
Got chocolate hair.
Whatever.
That doesn't bother me right now.
What bothers me right now is my vibe being broken.
I was going to play Half-Life Alex next week and like, no, what am I going to do?
What am I going to do with this thing?
I got to get like a new computer.
Oh, Ross just asked in the discord.
Hey, I'm out of the tutorial.
What now?
I just wrote a series of numbers.
Uh, that I don't know if they know what that means.
Hold on.
Oh, oh, hey.
Oh, can you hear me without the push talk?
Yeah.
Yes.
So we can change our characters too.
Apparently.
Yeah, we can.
We could be over.
We want.
Wait, we can all be the same person.
There's some people.
All right.
So when we select a job, what do you guys want to do for a job?
Um, not too sure.
Also Ross and Kiwi.
If you guys are talking, we don't, we don't hear you.
Yeah.
You got to hold V or you got to go in your PC settings.
You got to scroll all the way down and turn off the local push to talk.
I think they're in VR though.
Oh, wait, their hands are wacky.
They're stuck in VR.
But yeah, you know, you don't hear the, uh, like the fire alarm.
No, that's so funny.
I wonder why.
What about, okay.
Jobs selected job.
No contracts.
I don't have that option.
Okay.
Um, it's like a power puff girls, uh, Gendi Tartovsky version of the United
States and Canada.
We have Edgefield, which is California.
Rafton farmhouse, which is it looks like in Texas or Ridgeview Roadhouse,
which looks like somewhere in Michigan.
Um, Michigan sounds pretty haunted in general.
Yeah.
I mean, Michigan's bordering Lake Erie, right?
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
It is.
All right.
So this is called difficulty amateur recommended team size two.
We got four.
We are right.
That's the movements you do when you're like in the shower, Ross and Kiwi.
Once again, if you guys are talking, we don't hear you hear you at all on this
end, your karate chopping pretty nicely in the air.
I was going to say that's like, that's like that's when you do that.
When you're like bathing, like when you're trying to get like under your
outfit.
So this is this is a two story, four bedroom house with a basement.
We just got confirmation of a possible ghost sighting here.
This one sounds it guns in this game.
Like we're going to get, we get done work.
This one sounds dangerous.
You'll have to be careful with this one.
Gather evidence and leave as soon as you can.
More info when you arrive.
The guns are for each other.
Like in case we betray each other and scare each other.
Looks like all right.
Who is who here?
I keep people keep.
No, is that me?
Yeah.
So every like we're kind of all the same character right now.
But I imagine when we spawn in we'll all be a different character.
Roblox.
That's Ross.
Yeah.
That's pretty good name.
I'll be this dude.
I'll be Zuckerberg.
That's fine.
I'm just going to be I don't know guy with jacket too.
So so Ross and Kiwi are both leaving and they're going to do some settings
and try to come back.
Okay.
I'm good, babe.
We're just chilling.
I usually how are how are you?
I've been pretty good.
Hope you've been good too.
Yeah, I've been doing all right.
I I've adapted to our nightmare world a little bit.
Yeah, it's been kind of chaotic.
But yeah, you know, you just do what you got to do.
Hopefully we can get back to normal soon in the next few months.
I hope yeah.
I mean until then though, we at least have ghost hunting.
At least we have ghost on it.
We have green overexposed face show.
Yeah, I'm sorry green overexposed face show with
camera pointing up to chin getting like weird profile like below under
profile of face.
Really like just disturbing visions of humanity from that show.
But also you have to wonder like when they when they do that,
like do they accidentally pick up semen that they have to edit out?
Where you like like what's that stain on the kitchen table?
And it's like, oh, oh God me and the husband we were well.
Ignore it.
It's everywhere.
This whole house is just covered with ectoplasm.
How did it get on top of the cabinets in the kitchen?
Well, I mean, of course must have been up there and probably
still got a late-night snack.
Gordon Ramsay on the case.
He did a hotel show.
He did a hotel show where like, you know, this is a Michelin star
winning chef and he like goes into these like disgusting hotel rooms
and he like shines the flashlight the black light on like the bed
and he's like, oh, oh, it's fucking disgusting.
Jesus.
While you're telling this I just this still somebody's house on
fire.
You still hear it.
It's it's it's like makes this whole conversation that much funnier
because I'm just not even we're apparently not even paying attention
to the fact that the room we're in is on fire.
Oh, no, my my room is all good.
I don't I don't hear it.
I don't hear a thing.
I hear crickets, man.
A minute.
Wait, wait, wait, walk.
Keep walking.
I'm walking.
Walk really close to me walking.
I'm in I'm I'm through you.
Okay, now walk backwards and go far away.
You're the fire alarm.
You're the fire alarm guy.
I'm the fire.
Oh, yeah, the fire alarm guy.
You have do you have like a like a pager like a ghost pager that's
going off.
I have nothing.
It's like one of those tools.
People are saying it's v-sync effects of voice chat.
No, no way.
V-sync effects on voice chat.
Isn't that a video thing?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
It's your mic feedback probably.
Is it though?
All right.
Hold on if I walkie on shoulder.
I have a walkie talkie on my shoulder.
Hang on a minute.
I don't think if I was just gonna cut I was gonna cover my mic with
my hands and be like, okay, talk now walkie talkie.
I wish I could look left shoulder because I have to stare at the
board.
You do because I'm Mr.
Lobby.
I missed a guy that runs the lobby.
Oh, they want to get in a call like an actual call like discord
call.
That's gonna be tough because I'm sitting on my couch.
Like this headset is not set up for discord.
I wouldn't be able to like broadcast it.
I could relay what they're saying to you.
Vinnie stand up you bum.
I wish I was on VR on the couch right now so bad.
I know but you can't do sitting VR.
You become Goblin when you sit.
Hey, do you still hear the walkie talkie the fire alarm?
I do but it's I'm kind of used to it now and it's kind of just
there and I kind of if you turn it off, I'd probably miss it.
The proximity in game chat is way better than discord for this
as one of my chat members.
Look down on your left shoulder.
Somebody said that this game is meant to be played without
discord because it's proximity.
You cannot take it off walkie on left shoulder.
I promise you chat.
I'm grabbing I'm looking for walkie.
I can't find it.
Check it out radio does not work in the lobby.
It's inside your neck chat.
I swear to Christ escape.
Oh shit.
I can move.
Let me see if I can turn it off for you.
What's it?
What are you sitting on?
I'm not sitting anymore.
Why do you have a hula hoop?
Oh, that's we all have that.
That's our utility belt in VR.
You don't have one but that's I know.
Okay, I'm going to walk this way.
Is it something on the thought that was a gun?
I thought you just shot a gun at me.
It's just like trying to find a smoke detector that is running
at a battery.
It's like dude is it in the fucking wall?
Is it in the brick?
It's somebody a hundred years ago leave one in the wall when
they built the house.
Oh what you can do basketball.
I want not that fun.
It's more fun than it looks.
Yeah, let me try.
Oh, hey.
Ross.
So we can't actually verbally communicate if you can hear
me nod if you can hear me do this.
They can't hear you.
He's not getting your audio.
You can't hear me.
I can hear you.
Can you hear German?
Can you hear me?
Well, I talk it up.
What's this Vinny?
Do you have like trying to communicate non-verbally you
have the the like the five like headphones plugged in the
microphone.
Is it a microphone?
I don't know.
I don't I forget how it works.
Um the the index it's just it's just in there.
Oh, it's just in there.
Yeah, we all the steam VR audio setting headset audio output
device headset audio input device headset audio mirroring
on one restart should just restart the game the headed.
What is it?
If German can hear you and Ross can't you need to reboot?
Yeah, you're the only one I can hear Vinny.
I can't hear anything talking.
I can't hear them.
Someone said make sure the check marks are blue blue check
marks have better opinions.
You have a blue check mark Vinny.
No, neither do I what the fuck?
Yeah.
No, it's all it's all good, dude.
Don't worry about it.
I want my like four tweets a year to be proven that it's
me and not some fake Baker when I get like a red check
mark instead.
Just don't listen to me.
Give me the red check mark.
Yeah, the red check mark is this is this is like worse
opinion central stuff.
You don't want to listen to this guy.
I don't even good enough to be fake but I took two sips
of this and I feel like so much better.
What are the sips?
What is it?
Is it this this oxygen our purple powery?
Oh, oh in real life.
Oh IRL.
Okay, just trying to like whoa, that's trippy weird sounds
coming from your shoulder.
I love that.
You just have this weird of loud beeping implant on you
somewhere that you can't find.
It's so funny.
Like tell me can you hear if I do this?
Can you hear me?
Do I do I cut out at all?
No, you're good.
It's solid.
It just stopped for a second.
It's it's it's restarted.
It's off.
It's gone.
You just did it.
You just turned it off and now it's back on.
I didn't I didn't it's back on what if I don't move?
I'm not moving.
Wait, are you so low to the ground because you're sitting
on a couch?
I'm sitting on my couch.
So you are sitting but you need to be walking in VR.
So you're just going to be like you're just going to be
I'm going to be a crab.
Yeah, yeah.
Is it is it is the beeping still happening?
Yeah, you turned it off for like two seconds and then it
came back on.
I'm going to restart and I'll be back.
All right, the code shouldn't change.
All right, that's so funny.
He's sitting on his couch.
There is constantly disease is going to be like shifting
around it stops.
Yeah, the late night stream or stream 2020.
That's not that's not true.
You can't say that this didn't this doesn't count.
This is a late night stream late night bonus spring.
Can you hear me?
Hello, I can hear you.
Hello.
Oh my god.
Okay, so I figured out I figured I figured out what it
is if you alt tab on this game.
It kills the microphone.
Oh, all right.
I won't so I wasn't able to hide the code.
There's no way to get in here without me.
Yeah, okay.
We got everyone.
Can you hear me?
Hello.
Okay, so Chad explained that this game breaks if you alt
tab is can Vinny hear us?
Oh no, Vinny's gone because he how come you guys you guys
aren't beeping why none of you guys beeping?
Beeping before.
Oh, no Vinny has like a fire alarm thing on his shoulder.
We can't turn it off.
We're trying to figure out how to turn it off.
He has a fire alarm.
Yeah, I saw a fire alarm.
Our houses were on fire.
Hi.
Hey Vinny, is your Vinny is your is your house on fire?
No, can you hear me though?
Yeah, we can hear you.
Well, you're very loud.
I'm loud.
Yeah, Jerma's real low and you're loud.
You look insane.
You're like dog bum wiping on the ground.
Come get my butt.
What are you doing?
What is I'm just sitting but we okay.
Is volume because am I still am I a fire alarm still?
Yeah.
A bit.
It sounds like can I turn my volume down?
Yeah, I can hear my voice like I can hear my voice through
your mic.
Oh shit.
Okay.
Hold on this game.
You guys just did the Spider-Man thing.
You guys did the Spider-Man things pointing each other and
saying I have you apparently you can't just what?
Yeah.
You can adjust people's volume when you're in game.
So oh, oh, we'll just do that.
Would you prefer it if I talk like like this weird weird VR
stuff?
I'm jealous about Jerma.
Help me.
I wish I could I wish you put my hands out in VR and grab
your hands.
I can't.
I just have a I have like just like an overwatch crosshair
cool.
You want to like do a first-person shooter ghost hunt.
I can I can arrange we can find a game.
All right.
So we have a job going off shields up.
Hey by the way, you guys know how to play this game because
I I didn't process the tutorial at all.
We have a flashlight.
We have yeah, it was kind of weird.
I got the tutorial a little bit.
We'll never lose Vinny.
Just like for the free crap walking around.
Yeah, let me let me check my chat chat.
Do you have any idea how to fix this?
Please help.
Should we ready up?
I just said I was ready.
Good, dude.
I'm ready.
I'm going to scare the ghost.
Yeah, really much.
Okay.
Do we get like chase Michael Myers style?
Do we get like attacked or anything?
How does it work?
Yeah, if if anybody wants to see what it looks like come to
my screen and look I didn't even tweet this.
What a terrible screamer.
The is it gone?
No, do our characters like change once we under game?
Because right now we're all at the same.
Yeah, I think they should.
Are you sure you your house isn't burning down?
Then my chat doesn't hear it.
Literally come come come watch from my perspective for a
second.
You'll see exactly what we're all hearing.
I hear it through your microphone.
You can hear it through my mic.
Yes.
Yeah, I can.
Are you guys ready to go?
It's so stupid.
Are you guys ready to like scream?
Yeah, yeah, everybody ready up.
You guys ready to scream?
Vinny, you got it ready up.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
I'm ready.
Let's see.
Hopefully it'll stop when we get in game.
I hope it doesn't for some reason.
Is that bad for me to say that?
I hope it does not stop.
Someone said it's the crickets on my end.
I switch hat.
Those are in those are the crickets.
All right.
Is it ready?
Start.
Wait, do we have enough like stuff?
Oh, yeah.
Duck tape.
Scott gives a shit.
Let's just go.
Let's just go scooby-dooby-doo.
I'll show you the ghost face at the same time and burn them.
The power of Christ compels you.
Hey, welcome to streamer, buddy.
This is a little play.
It's a I don't know the name of the game.
I forgot it already.
My mic is really loud.
No, I am aware chat.
How do I change?
How do I the volume the mic?
Oh, yeah.
Where do we do that?
Press options.
Yeah, you just press B in the index B.
Oh, I see it options.
Oh, no guys.
You can turn me down.
I can't turn you down.
Yeah, turn me down.
I'm going to talk normal blah blah blah.
Today.
I had rice for breakfast.
You got it.
You hit B on the well, I don't know if you have an index.
We go.
Yeah, that's right.
You don't have a yard.
I guess I'm not going to change anything.
I might turn up Vinny.
No, I can't wait.
I'm going to turn my mic off for a second.
Tell me if the beeping stops.
Yeah, it stopped.
Are you sure your house is not on fire?
Yeah, Vinny is your house on fire bro.
Like what is this?
No, no, I'm good.
It's the end game Mike.
I'm reading chat.
Give me give me a minute here.
Let me try something.
Tell me if it tell me if this fixes anything.
Vinny has a condition.
Yeah, this is so he's in a constant state of alert.
Does this fix it?
No, it's still here.
No wonder what that is.
Still going.
Please disable plugins.
What is it?
It's fine.
Honestly, it's not bothering me.
It's pretty quiet now.
I've turned you down a bit, but I can still hear your voice.
No, I'm going to keep it on.
I think it's awesome.
Haunted bike.
Pretty scary.
Hello.
Okay.
Sounds like Mike issues.
There's a buzz in the background of your audio for some reason.
No, that's the in-game thing.
Vinny, you're running an index through your DAW.
No, that's clock.
That's only for chat.
I just turned my DAW off and it's still happening.
This is so much better than before.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is the weirdest fucking problem ever.
Do you have another Mike?
No, it's not that easy because headset.
All right, I give up.
Let's just want to find some dude.
Find some ghosts.
Well, you just like a bat using sonar, dude.
You're going to be fine.
It's such an interesting bizarre strange problem.
That's like hilariously strange.
Yeah.
All right.
Everyone grab a flashlight.
Okay.
Is there like a camera?
Yeah, by the way, I like this.
Oh, you got the camera.
There's two though.
Where's the other one?
Oh, I have the other one.
Oh, you got the other one.
Okay, cool.
Cool.
I will go naked.
That one.
What is this book for?
Because we've got the journal in our head.
This is the one where the ghosts, right?
The ghost right in that like for their diary ghost writers.
Then we have all the videos or then am I still the default
player character?
No, you're the shaggy guy Caucasian man with blue eyes
and brown hair.
Yeah, my character choice didn't seem to take but that's
okay.
All right, so
that makes sense.
What did it say?
The ghost was flashlight.
Wait, do you have all the flashlights?
Yeah, I don't have a flashlight.
How did I?
There's a little what you do.
There's a tiny flashlight and there's a big flashlight.
You have the big flashlight.
Who's this?
Oh, I can.
This is me.
That's that's Germany.
Are you all right?
Yeah, just knocked my helmet.
Oh, I sounded like you.
Are you okay?
You okay, baby?
Okay.
Wait, you can put stuff on your belt, right?
Yeah, just like that other game.
Did anybody get the key?
Dungeon night.
Oh, was there a key?
Oh, we got the key.
Yeah, I grabbed it.
Yo, anybody home?
Another person in the house.
Wait, did I just see something floating?
So, okay.
I know how to do this.
Who has the
the thing that lights up the ping-ping green?
I got I think I do.
Was I supposed to bring that?
Yeah, so I got it.
Let's follow the dinner plate.
Wait guys, I think there was actually another thing.
Who got the white thing?
I do.
You got the white thing.
This is the EMF.
Yeah.
Okay, I've got a dinner plate.
So, we'll follow Kiwi to start.
You smashed that over somebody's head?
I mean, I'm thinking about it.
It's kind of side-tracked.
Borslem can really cut.
Yeah, let's wait till we see the ghost to smash any dinner
plates.
Burglar alarm.
So, Kiwi,
I guess we'll follow you.
When you get activity, let us know and then we'll set the
book down and we'll ask the spooky questions.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, I like the sound of that.
How do I turn on my flashlight?
It's pretty dark.
You use the trigger, the right trigger.
I think we have to pick it.
Is there a certain room, right?
You got a flashlight on your shoulder.
How did you do that?
Yeah, but it's not illuminating.
It doesn't illuminate anything.
It's like an area flashlight.
Okay.
How did you guys turn that on?
I don't have anything.
So, I'll follow whoever has the flashlight.
The big one.
Well, I don't have anything.
How did you guys do that?
It's pretty pitch dark.
Where's the ghost?
So, Kiwi will lead us to the ghost.
Oh, okay.
Using the Pee Pee.
Using the Pee Pee?
What about the Pee Pee?
The Pee Pee Vee?
It's like a device that...
Oh, yeah.
...texts ghost activity.
I want you to smudge stick.
Okay.
I have the camera, by the way, if you want to set it up in one of these rooms.
I think we should find some paranormal activity before we set the camera down.
Hello.
Is there anybody here?
Oh, shit.
What was that noise?
I guess my flashlight just went out on its own.
Oh, I think that's a sign.
Wait, did it respond?
Is anybody here?
Hello?
What is your name?
Can you give us a sign?
What data center are you mining this from, developers?
What are you going to do with our recording?
Jesus, Vinny.
It's okay, Vinny.
Oh, what room is this?
This is the bathroom.
Guys, we don't have a reflection.
That's Vinny.
This is the spirit box.
Guys, I'm going to wash the dishes.
Wash the dishes.
Oh, God.
What's going on?
You're in the wall.
Traditionally, you're not supposed to wash dishes in them guys.
I think I went through the wall.
That's fucking weird.
Can you return to us?
Guys, I don't know.
Where are you?
Wait, did you actually just?
I have like teeth.
That was scary.
That was scary than a ghost.
I saw inside of his brain.
What is going on?
I think I teleported.
Is there anybody here?
Guys, can someone come get me?
I'm a little scared.
Where are you?
Give us a sign.
I'm downstairs.
We might have a ghost downstairs and not upstairs.
Yeah, we can just turn the lights on guys.
What the hell are we doing?
Guys, I'm downstairs.
Oh, what?
Yeah, that's right.
Well, the ghost won't talk to us.
Oh, can you guys come find me?
Is there anybody in this room?
Oh, that's helpful.
That's actually really nice.
Guys, I went through a wall.
I think I'm the ghost.
I think Ross is dead.
If you can hear me, let me know.
Ross, are you dead?
You can die?
Chat, am I dead?
Did someone...
What is that noise?
Maybe.
Oh, that's a spirit box.
I'm going to try to clip through the wall to find you.
I think somebody stays.
Somebody stays.
I got a video camera from what I read in the tutorial.
Oh, wait.
Put the camera down in a room.
Somebody checks the TV.
My black light has found some schmutz on this mirror.
Oh, there is.
I'm just going to curl up into a ball on the floor and just scream.
At least it does light up.
I want to go find him.
I got an idea.
I'm going to put this camera down right here.
Check this out.
I'm going to put the camera right here.
Guys, we have five minutes.
We have five minutes before this.
You have five minutes?
Can you guys come find me?
I'm scared.
I'm alone.
Well, maybe you should have not split from the group.
Can anybody get in the truck and look at the TV?
What's going on?
Turn this off.
I got a camera in here.
But we don't know.
We got to find the room.
I'm stuck.
We got to find the room where the ghosts so so Kiwi your your meter
should light up and that's where it hasn't lit up.
Okay, so let's go downstairs and find old B for walkie-talkie.
Can you guys hear me?
Hold B and talk.
Yeah.
It's a walkie-talkie.
Can you hear us Ross Ross?
Hello Ross.
Where are you?
Oh, I lost the flashlight.
What is this game?
Turn on the light Ross.
Can you hear me on the walkie-talkie?
Go look at the TV in the truck.
I set up a camera put on night vision and see if there's anything
in there.
Yeah, look for orbs.
Wait, how are you guys using the walkie-talkie?
Is this walkie-talkie?
Yeah, that sounds like you.
Okay, Ross.
Can you hear me?
You can just hear him in the truck talking.
So Ross, if you want to talk to us through the walkie-talkie,
here's what you do.
Reach over your left shoulder and pull the trigger.
This is like when you hear your neighbor and like talking
through the wall in an apartment.
Reach over your left shoulder and pull the trigger.
Can you guys hear me?
Yeah, Ross.
The front, I don't think it's the right camera.
Hold on.
Let me change camera.
Okay, now I see a bedroom.
That's yeah, I set the camera up in there.
Yeah.
All right.
I see the two pillows.
They look secure on the wall.
I don't see anything spooky.
What's the timer say in the truck?
Like how much time do we have?
Yeah, there's no time left.
Oh, we mean no time left.
Yeah, you pissed off the ghost.
We either haul and have to find the ghost.
I think we may have did this out of order.
We gotta go downstairs.
All right, let's go.
Ghost, are you here?
Give us a sign.
Give me a sign.
The right person is there.
Okay, make noise.
Ghost, are you here?
We have a ghost.
Give us a sign.
Check your PKE meter.
Ross, check the readings.
The readivity?
Right.
It's our black light.
Hey, where are you going?
I hear some noises.
I hear it too.
I'm upstairs.
That was me.
Okay, so...
Something's in this fucking house, dude.
Something's in this house.
My name is not important to you.
What'd he say?
Where are you guys?
Where is everybody?
Where is that?
We're gonna go see Mr. Plinkett.
Sorry.
That's a YouTuber.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, fuck.
I don't know.
Wait, is somebody a YouTuber?
It's a good joke.
May I?
Or you can point down.
Are there any ghosts in here?
Hello?
I don't think ghosts usually have a name, though.
Spooky Spockers.
We hear ghosts.
Hello?
Is there spooky ghosts in here?
How old are you?
Phantasmal Spirit ASL.
We gotta find the light switch so we don't...
Give us a sign.
You're the piano man.
He chimes in.
I'm not really sure how it goes.
Oh shit, I've been caught.
Guys, what's this button?
Guys, I found a button and it just made it go green.
Wow.
What do you need my flashlight for, Vinny?
Who made PT on floor?
Ewie, was it you?
I'm a little scared.
I'm gonna level with you.
It's been green this whole time.
I don't know if I'm using it wrong, but so far nothing.
I think he might be in the kitchen, guys.
You're supposed to say ghost's name.
It's limited.
It's written on the wall in the...
Guys.
We didn't learn his name, that was rude.
Why does the manual say a survivor's guide?
Is there a chance we could die?
The ghost isn't killing us or anything.
Oh, hey, this ghost sucks.
Here I am, just walking around by myself in the fucking basement.
This ghost is a piece of shit.
Ready, lame ghost.
All of a sudden my neck just goes...
The air conditioning in this place must be really loud.
It gets so much louder when you step in.
They shouldn't be running AC in a dead person's house.
Info?
Lone.
Me, oh me, me, me, me.
I think the camera's in the bedroom.
Camera's in the bedroom.
Why can't I get jumped?
Steven...
Steven Johnson.
Steven Johnson, I know you're here.
I think...
I think somebody scammed us.
And just, they just went on vacation and told us the place was haunted.
And they, they had, we had to pay like ten grand to do this.
Congealy man?
Yeah, I forgot where the bedroom was.
It's a pretty large house.
Over.
I got the camera.
I got it, I got a camera.
Yes, I will turn it on.
You see?
Oh, I can, I can do a camera light.
Okay, I got the camera.
Where do you want me to go?
Where's the guy, where's the guy with the big balls supposed to go?
Hey, somebody walking.
Steven Johnson, Steven Johnson's behind me.
Steven Johnson's behind me.
I'm upstairs.
Steven Johnson's probably gonna kill me.
I have the camera.
I can hear you, but I think somebody's behind me.
Oh, that's a, no, you're just sitting.
You're sitting, seated Vinny.
It's seated Vinny.
You are a monster.
Steven Johnson.
I'm trying to get out of the house.
Let's head, hightail it out of here.
Hey guys.
I really, you're all pretty close to death.
Especially Jerma.
If we look at the, the, the readout here, Jerma was about to die.
He's at 18%.
Actually, wow, this one really hates Jerma.
It's going specifically for you.
I'm fine.
Where were you Jerma?
Just throw me back in there and like just wait till I get eaten and
then take a few pictures and then send it to the fucking National Geographic.
You guys are millionaires.
All I ask is you build a giant statue in my name.
But if a ghost takes the picture, you're gonna have a lawsuit.
So we can, we can use some of the evidence that we found already.
Because this thing going to five means that it's, that limits it.
Oh, okay.
So do we, do we have, we have evidence?
So EMF level five is considered evidence.
So we can put that in.
Did the spirit box go off at any point Vinny?
Okay.
Did anyone see any fingerprints?
I don't think bathroom mirror schmutz counts.
No one saw it.
Did you see a ghost orb on any cameras Ross?
All right.
No orbs.
Did anyone see any ghost writing in the ghost book?
I don't think there's any writing.
All right.
Let's bring the ghost book in there and the did anyone see their breath
or free have freezing temperatures happen?
I don't have freezing breath this time.
Okay.
I'll go.
So I'll do it.
Well, who's got the highest sanity?
I shouldn't accept me because I'm scared.
Where is the ghost book?
What happened to it?
I don't know.
Is anyone moving the camera?
Oh, it's here.
Vinny has it on his eye.
I got the camera right here.
Digital photo camera.
Why does Vinny something muffled now?
Does anybody else hear this?
Yeah, I got the video.
This is a video camera.
There's nothing written in that book now.
Your voice is really muffled.
You're yours is too.
Really must be an audio bug then.
Let's German.
What room were you in when your sanity was going down like crazy
and you saw what's his face?
I don't even know.
I might just be like placebo affecting myself.
I thought I saw a guy on my left when I was walking in the
hallway upstairs.
Well, your sanity was the lowest.
So it would make sense.
Yeah, did we see it?
Was there a guy on the left side of the screen?
German, can you hear me?
I didn't see a guy but I was downstairs.
German, I'm going in.
Going in?
You going in?
You gonna bring the diary?
There's a bathroom.
Check the bathroom.
Check the upstairs bathroom, Vinny.
Give me the camera.
I'm going to take the camera.
You got the camera?
All alone?
Yeah, you can watch the camera.
He doesn't respond to people who, you know, who's got the
other camera.
Not that one.
Oh, that's a still camera.
This is the money camera.
We get money for taking snapshots.
Ross, I see you took a selfie on it.
That's the video camera.
I got it here.
Was that me?
Let me grab that.
Oh, right.
You're on VR.
I forgot.
Sorry.
Yeah, I got that.
I got that.
You got it all?
I'll be right back.
All right.
Let's do it.
What about the camera?
I think he's got it.
Unless someone wants to go in with the snapshot camera and
take some some snappies.
No, I'm good.
I don't want to do that.
I'll take it.
All right.
Do it.
The more snapshots you get of ghosts, the more money we
get.
Oh, shit.
No more film in that camera, Roger.
I snapped all the photos.
There's no more film?
Oh, well shit.
Wait, dude.
Are you do you have the the camera on right now?
Yeah, right click.
No, that you're on VR.
You're in the fun mode.
Yeah.
Okay.
Vinny, Vinny, we see we see you.
You need to use Vinny.
We see you.
Should we fuck with him?
Vinny, you left the camera on the counter.
Take that into the upstairs bathroom.
Yeah, you might want to bring that with you, dude.
Bring us with you.
Yeah, if you if you can have the flashlight at the same
time, but it blinks.
Oh, we're all just total fucking what's this here, huh?
Yeah, we're bitches.
Hey Vinny, go that way.
Vinny, you dropped the camera.
Is he dead?
Vinny.
Oh, no.
Dude, he's dead.
Look at his sanity.
He's fucking he's fucking dead.
That's why he dropped.
Okay, let's make an educated guess because I don't really
want to know coward.
I'm going to go hit him in the head with the radio.
Like are you hearing the radio going to dark right now?
I think it's horrible.
Scary noise.
Is that actually real?
Is that the game?
Not for me.
Oh, yeah, now I hear it.
It's it's German.
It's mine.
It's me.
So wait, he just died in there.
He's fucking dead.
He's dead.
Where's the camera?
Watch on you.
You keep watching.
I'm going to open up.
I'm going to run in and run out.
This is my job.
I want to be in communication the whole time.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm going to watch the camera.
I think this is the dining room.
I think it's right in the front door, right?
All right.
It's pitch black in there.
He's dropping real quick.
Actually, I think we need to get out of here.
I'm in constant communication with you.
Do you see me on the on the I need to flip of light that
will give us some sanity.
Oh shit.
I'm in a dream to say you tell you in a dream when you
flip a light switch.
It doesn't work when you flip a light switch and it doesn't
work.
That's how you can tell you're dreaming.
That's how you start lucid dreaming.
Yeah, I think that's true.
I think actually, yeah, I think he's dropping really fast.
Jeremy, you're at 14%, dude.
All right.
I hear gas.
Where's gas?
We'll just gas.
I leave.
Maybe you should leave, dude.
You're nearing 10%.
Oh, okay.
I found the door.
Yeah, come to the front door.
Yo, do you have the ghost book?
No, I get the ghost radio.
I'm still using it.
That one's kind of tricky, I think.
Vinny's ghost was behind you.
Hey ghost.
Fuck you.
Wait, is Vinny still in the game?
He walks around as a spirit.
He does?
Oh really?
Yeah.
Yeah, he's a ghost now.
Vinny, show us where the flashlight is, man.
Everyone just stay back to back to back like the Spartans
did.
So apparently sanity will go down in the dark.
Where are we going?
We got to snap a picky.
Ross, get to the camera.
Well, is it down here?
There's something on the ground.
Guys, I found it.
There's a flashlight up here too.
No, no, I'm going to go.
I have like the wicked shitty from Walmart thing you plug
in on Halloween that does the cool thing outside shining
on the front of your house.
You're going to die?
None of the lights work.
Hey, something's coming through the radio.
In bedroom one.
Something's coming through the radio in bedroom one.
Before you die, you're 5% by the way.
It's saying it's saying I think it was the weather.
I really think it was the weather.
It was like sunny out.
You hear me?
I'm good, man.
I 1% I can live the car over here.
Yeah, but he's bouncing back from zero.
He keeps surviving.
I'm good, man.
Okay.
All right.
I'm coming back down.
I found Vinny.
I found Vinny's dead body.
Yeah, I'm good.
Nice.
Find any fingerprints or anything like that?
Yeah, they're everywhere.
They're all over the place upstairs.
Wait for this for real.
Yeah.
I mean like seriously they're all over the door handles
and everything.
Yeah.
Oh shit.
That's great.
Great.
We can probably guess from that.
Come on.
Let's get in the truck.
So what which one had which one said it needed we need to
he has massive plot armor.
So our other evidence is it was fingerprints all over the
door handles and we also got the spirit box to work as well.
Right?
Like it did some noise.
The radio was freaking out up there too.
So they did it talk.
We didn't see any writing.
No, no writing or anything.
I think I think we got spirit box.
Let's let's give it a shot.
Yeah, let's give it a try.
Says not discovered.
You put an EMF five fingerprints spirit box and it's not
giving me anything.
Ghost type.
What about Banshee?
Well, did we we don't have a cross so we weren't able to
test that.
Oh, yeah, Banshee needs to we need to have a crucifix, but
we need to buy one of those.
I think you're probably nothing there fingerprints.
What about a revenant?
Revenant.
What's a revenant?
Ghost type.
Let's look into it.
Let's have a look.
Remember you're an overconfident clueless guy.
And I make it to the end of the movie every time so it could
be a Banshee or a revenant.
How's Vinnie doing?
Is he just kind of hanging out?
I wonder like what is he doing?
He must be super bored in there.
Oh, it says.
Okay.
Yeah.
Revenant could be EMF level five fingerprints and ghost
writing, but we never got ghost writing.
Did we never got ghost writing?
You got to put ghost writing in the right room, the room
that has all the stuff we didn't we never did that.
So we can take a stab at it when you almost died and
you found the the black light in the hallway.
I had all the problems in the bathroom and then in one
of the bedrooms the bedroom has
had the fingerprints all over the door handle.
All right.
Okay.
So he probably haunts the bedroom.
We could go up there with the with the ghost book and
see if he does anything.
You got to lock in your answers.
Apparently are we out of time though?
Like can we even do this still?
Do we all have to lock in our answers?
No, we're alive so we can do it.
That time means like countdown until he's pissed off and
starts the in range.
That's the enrage timer.
That's different.
Yes.
So let's see.
Lying.
How am I?
Why am I lying?
I'm not lying.
There was the ghost goo all over the handle to the bedroom.
Oh guys, apparently guys.
Apparently we all have to individually lock down our
own answers.
So what was what was the first one?
Can I copy your homework?
Evidence found was EMF level five, right?
Level five.
Yeah, and the second one we found was fingerprints.
Did what we didn't have a third one.
Fingerprints.
Fingerprints number two.
Two.
Oh, but the spirit box did go off, right?
I put fingerprints twice.
But you said that you heard the spirit box radio go off,
right?
Yeah, it was going like.
Okay, that sounds good.
He was talking to us too, but I don't know if that's the
spirit box or if that's like an in-game thing that you
hear in your ears.
Because when I was with Vinny, he was like legit talking
to us.
So I would say we can say I think Vinny had the spirit
box, but I could not yet discovered.
So we but we don't don't don't we have to.
Yeah.
How are you alive?
Let's be that purple power, right?
What do you really have to test this?
What do you want?
Yes.
Do we want to guess?
Yeah, I think we should guess.
I think it's pretty close.
Let's do let's try that.
Yeah, that was our first game.
Yeah, let's just fucking guess.
We don't know what we're doing yet.
Let's get Vinny back in here.
I agree guessing revenant, but we haven't got ghost writing.
I'm sure if we brought the book up, we might get that
emf level 5 ghost orb.
No, we never ghost orb.
Got a bunch of crazy ghost shit on this camera.
Yeah, leave it for some old lady in the neighborhood to
fucking find it.
We never got freezing temperatures from it.
So it can't be a banshee.
Yeah, we wouldn't know how to test for that.
Anyway, let's go.
Revenant.
Emf level 5.
We're not the freezing temperatures.
Freezing temperatures is your breath.
I'm going revenant.
Yeah, I'm going revenant too.
Okay, wait.
So how do you lock in your answer?
We just close the door.
Last page you put in.
But it won't let me it won't let me do that.
Maybe if we all guess something else.
I'm clicking it and it won't.
It's fine.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, you got you got to do you got it on the evidence.
You got it.
You got to make it you got to choose the evidence.
We get it.
Welcome back.
There's some jobs ready for you guys didn't take my body
20 bucks.
Were we supposed to take your body?
No, I just wanted a eulogy.
Oh, well you rub a dub dub.
Sorry you died.
Rub a lub a dub dub.
Hi, what's up?
Welcome back to the land of the living.
Did you win?
We got that completely wrong.
No, we got $20.
What can we buy with 20 bucks?
Candle no glow stick.
It says here sick for us all to share.
We can get it.
Yeah, what's this?
We get a smudge stick, right?
EMF reader is $45.
A flashlight is 30.
We get all guys.
We get by to look to lighters.
Yeah, let's get some lighters.
No, I can't find any lighters.
I'm hearing an echo.
Is that my computer?
Maybe am I still a fire alarm?
Yeah, buddy.
A little bit.
No, you're not not anymore.
There you are.
It's like proximity.
So, you know when you're getting near him, it's actually kind
of useful.
I got some smudge sticks.
What are we buying?
I bought two smudge sticks.
I don't know.
I think they're just my sticks are good.
Journal also has description of all ghost types.
I've been told.
Yeah, we were looking at that.
Somebody else the host of the Lobby.
No, I can't select job anymore.
Open VR chaperone setting is what's making the noise.
Open VR.
What's open VR?
Oh, it's because you're you're on the edge of your VR play
space.
Wait, you're sitting down on the couch away from the lighthouses
and the thing is warning you that you're going to walk into
the wall.
But but it's warning.
It's not warning me because I don't hear it.
So it's going through the wrong audio device.
Maybe you could go to this advanced settings and turn that
light that warning off.
I've don't even I didn't even know that was an option.
Okay, I'll turn that off.
That's so weird.
Like Vinny, you're gonna hit your head on the wall.
Vinny watch out, but it tells you that I'm gonna hit my head
on the wall.
Not me.
Chad, do you know how to turn that off?
Wait, if I stand up, do you still hear this fire alarm?
Yeah, dude.
Chad.
This was erroneous information.
Can you walk like in range that kind of way your lighthouses
are like can you like get in and you're like right in the
middle of it right here move further into your play space any
further chat and I'll be like fucking merging with my
computer guys.
Someone told me that zero sanity doesn't kill you.
It makes the ghost hunt you watch activity because when it
hits 10 ghosts want to kill that person.
Yeah, they start they start hunting.
Okay.
I kind of like the sound.
I'm not even kidding.
It's like it's fun to me.
Yeah.
No, it's not gone.
It's fine, dude.
It's fine.
It's it's it's a good bit.
Let's just let's just roll with it.
All right.
Sounds good.
We always know.
Did we decide on a did we buy something I bought?
Oh wait, did we share money?
I saw 20 bucks.
Okay, good kiwi.
I bought two smudge sticks.
Do you is that an echo?
Maybe you have my stream open.
No, wow weird like hear my voice coming from your mic.
You should turn me down then probably.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm gonna do that when we get in or maybe I should turn you
down.
Yeah, I think I think you need to turn you're gonna have to
do that when we get into the game.
You can't adapt your weak chat echo of me.
We guys apparently we got guys people said we got $20 each.
It's not for the group.
I just had 10 bucks.
I bought a lighter.
We said turn off your shower on settings.
Oh, we should buy candles and smudge sticks then because
that can keep us from going insane.
Really?
Yeah, the candles if you light a candle in a smudge stick
in a haunted room, the ghost won't attack you in there
for a little bit.
If you burn sage and also if you put like powdered egg
shells on the back of your neck that also keeps spirits
away in real life.
Oh in real life.
Yeah.
Is somebody somebody the host again because I can't
select a job or anything.
It's oh, select job.
Yeah.
Yeah, you must be the leader.
Is somebody Vinny said somebody said turn off your
I think Ross.
Yeah, that I tried that that's that's capes.
Ross just accidentally left.
Oh, we do.
Well, the code is the same.
He pressed leave.
I think we can just rejoin.
Yeah, I think the code is the same.
So ready or I'll be fair though.
You probably I don't know if you should put leave right
next like eight pixels next to start.
That should probably be down here a little like in a
corner.
You're sitting too.
Yeah, I've you know, I'm taking a little break between
back and haunts.
Can you walk forward so I can see what I look like when
I walk?
This is what you look like when you walk usually with
your eye.
Well, actually your arms are like this.
No, I do that because it's the edge of my couch.
I can do that.
I'm just chilling.
Wait, so are we not able to ready up or something?
Oh, no, we're good.
Yeah, I think I hit select job and it like kicked me
out of the lobby.
Oh, what really?
Yeah.
Oh, it's me.
I had to do it.
This game is made very well.
Where do we want to go?
I have a cool game.
Actually, maybe like a tropical ghost.
That is absolutely not an option.
Okay, it's one that looks like it's sort of in the
middle of the country one in sort of like the Northwest
and one around LA or Nevada or something.
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, guys.
Look, they keep our memories here from all the time.
That we failed.
Oh, there's the picture.
What?
Why?
Oh my God.
Look at the good.
How did you take a German of the camera?
Your eyeball is popping out of your skull.
It is my okay.
You don't see it.
I think that's the flashlight on his shoulder.
Chat, you're seeing this, right?
Oh guys, we got to ready up.
Oh, we're already up ready.
You got to take a screenshot of this.
I could show them later.
Yeah, let me see.
Eyes is bugging out of his head.
We have one person who is not ready.
Yes, Vinny.
I think I'm sorry.
I got it.
We're good.
You look like you're walking around a house in a towel
that's about to fall off your waist with like a whole
group of people over your house.
Oh shit.
Don't look.
All right.
We start.
How do we start the job?
I think we're good, right?
We're good.
Everyone's ready.
So we just think you have you started.
You somebody has to be a serious first start button.
Let's fucking go.
I can't go ghost time.
I want to play the ghost game some more.
I'm so fucking amped up right now.
Chad, the chaperone settings definitely do not seem to be
a thing.
I'm just saying advanced settings show.
99% already.
I didn't do anything.
I've got a candle.
I think this is a sponge sponge.
Oh, is that a sponge?
I thought it was a candle.
No, this is a blunt.
Oh, dude.
It's like a blind me up baby bird poop.
It actually waited actually is.
Oh, we shouldn't be lighting this shit.
I think this is our very smudge things.
Fuck that.
That's the smudge sticks.
I paid $15.
Put it out.
Shit.
Fuck.
Oh, no.
It we use them fall.
What do we do with the sun finder?
Okay, Joseph Williams is the ghost looks like a pickle.
The ghost of Willie with a crucifix.
Oh, wait, do we have a crucifix?
So we just wasted that, huh?
Oh, it's sage.
I thought it was a blunt.
Yes, it's sage and we just use all our money to buy those and
the lighter to light them.
I like to think that Vinnie's house is actually full of smoke
and he's just like, I don't care.
I just want to see a drawing of Vinnie playing virtual reality,
but they're like, this is fine dog.
Just yeah, exactly.
Fire all around him.
It's not it's not a good place for VR.
I'll tell you that much.
It's not conducive, but I make do.
So now this is the view of my crotch.
So we'll be using this to find ghosts.
It's on your belt.
Can I do you have who has the not the blunt?
Who's got the thing that makes the thing light up and do the
thingies the flashlights?
I have this.
The thing that I have got it.
I think that when you trade you this for this.
Yeah, see how strong you are.
Let's see if you're if you're a baby boy or if you are strong
Superman gonna grip it as hard as you can.
It's only two quarters.
I think you have to drop what is this sex?
What is this?
TOS.
Oh, you dropped it man.
Oh, there it is right there.
Here it is.
I'm going to throw it up.
You got to catch it.
Good job.
All right, I'll bring the spirit box.
Now with that you when you turn it on my sense of adventure,
I'll actually know I'm going to bring the book.
It got free recorded stuff.
I mean, I don't want to make sure you guys don't think of Joseph
Williams.
So that's the guy Joseph Williams because the pen is mightier
than the sword.
The pen is mightier and Jenna, I think I'm going to watch
I'm going to be security guy.
You're going to do that this time.
Yeah, you were the brave guy last time.
I think you earned it.
I've got to do the cabin.
This house is scary.
The cabin.
I think it's nice.
Did you want to turn down me on the volume by the way?
Oh, let's be real.
Let's be a list 30.
Dude, this reminds me of the thing we did with lolathon.
Yeah, it's sort of like that Mrs.
Mrs.
Whatever her name was Fletcher.
I was there for no filter.
No, no, this is a different thing.
We did.
It was like when we're doing like VR horror map with Aaron Mrs.
Fletcher.
That was right that Mrs.
Oh, no.
Someone in the chat just said y'all are at the cabin.
Say you're probably bone.
Oh, everyone said that the cabin is hard.
Fuck.
Fucking game is so hard.
You guys have got four minutes and 40 seconds left until the
ghost gets angry at you.
I can love this movie.
Jermo, what was his name again?
Was it Stephen Williams?
What's that Roger?
No, no, there's something else.
There's something else.
It was John Williams.
What is that as a composer?
What was his name?
Did John Williams do the Little Rings soundtrack?
Joseph Williams.
Joseph Williams, are you here?
Yeah, I got the book.
Just got three minutes till we lose.
We got three minutes till we lose.
Yo, what up bitch?
Is my camera on Jermo?
Yeah, I can see.
Yeah, I got night vision on.
I can toggle it.
What is that over in the corner there?
That's something scary over there.
Hey, what's down there?
What's that weird large like fireplace cover thing?
Yeah, what is that?
What's that right there?
I see nothing.
I don't see any orbs or any ectoplasm.
Not that I can tell.
Everybody sanity is doing okay, by the way.
We, by the way, had some activity.
We had some activity.
Somebody saw some activity.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
Hey, Ross, have you seen anything weird lately?
I just went on upstairs automatically.
I'll mark it.
Yeah, you two have seen something weird.
All right, no more making fucking jokes.
You guys have 22 seconds.
What are you holding?
What's he holding?
And about in 15 seconds, you guys are about to be,
he's going to be real mad.
I see the bunny.
Are you doing a puppet show for me?
He's trying to like listen, like a conch shell.
Hey, see if you can hear the ocean.
Guys, we got, we got large activity happening right now.
Whatever is happening right now.
There's large activity happening right now.
Large activity.
Can they, can they hear me?
I don't see any orbs, but you guys are surrounded by activity.
Not anymore.
I am pressing the button.
I'm holding B.
Joseph Williams.
I should just go in there and fucking just stand in the corner.
You guys, your sanity is dropping.
You guys are at 74%.
Yeah, fuck it.
Listen, I'm going in.
I don't think they can hear me.
I was going to walk in slowly and be like,
guys, your sanity is at 75%.
Hey guys, your sanity is at like 75%.
Just want to make sure you guys know.
All right, do you have the black light?
Let's, I'll grab that for now.
You want that?
Yeah, if you want to go to the,
Oh boy, I threw it on the ground.
It's right, it's right here.
I got it right here.
For any ghost babies.
Can you take it out of my hand?
I'm going to put it on my belt.
You know what?
I like that better.
I'm like, I don't think I can.
Okay, I'm going to put it out here.
So it's really easy to get.
Holy shit.
Yeah, you are right there.
All right.
It's on the ground right here.
So we lost our radio, but I guess we can still hear it.
We lost the radio.
I'm looking for the radio right now.
I got to stick with you guys because I have nothing.
You guys tried touching the like home alone trap.
Joseph Williams, give us a sign.
If you are here.
Uh, I heard that.
I heard, is that you?
No, no, that wasn't me.
Ross.
Thanks Ross.
Why are we doing this to each other at both games?
Well, why are we doing this?
We haven't won a single one.
What about in the attic?
Joseph Williams, are you here?
How old are you?
Joseph Williams, how old are you?
What the fuck was that?
Joseph Williams, are you here?
Radio.
Joseph Williams, put on the Red Sox game.
Don't touch that dial now.
We're just getting started.
Turn off.
Oh, I think I just turned off all the lights.
Oh shit.
Lights are flickering up in the attic.
Lights are flickering in the attic.
Somebody's in the attic.
In the attic, in the attic, in the attic, in the attic, in the attic.
Somebody's talking to me.
Somebody's whispering to me right now.
I'm in the attic, up in the attic guys.
I'm here alone.
I heard a whisper.
I have a fucking flashlight up here.
What did I do up here?
Somebody just whispered in my ear, up in the attic.
They went like, yo, I don't know.
There's something like that.
Okay, turn this back on.
Did the lights just turn back on?
Do you guys have a radio?
You guys have?
I can hear you.
Okay, I'm freaking out in the attic.
I can't, I can't see.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, Vinny.
Vinny, activate your fucking sonar powers and walk around.
We'll find each other.
No, just the beep, just the beep.
If you, if you just have, if you just walk around.
Vinny, if you, if you walk around the house and you just move slowly,
we can find each other because you're, you're the beeping.
I can hear you.
I'm not on radio.
I'm, I'm in the attic.
No, I got glue.
I'm just trying to find the ground.
Yeah, we can't, nobody can see anything.
I'm trying to find the, I'm up in the attic and I'm trying to find the staircase to go back down.
Do you?
I can hear you.
Yeah, I lost you Vinny.
Where'd you go?
There's crazy noises happening right now.
Yeah.
Oh, I found the stairs.
Hey, yeah, you found the stairs and then the fucking stairs found us too.
Uh, hi.
Hey, there you are.
Oh, dude.
I see you.
Yes.
Okay, good.
We have to figure out how to get the hell out of here.
Let's go.
Is this a flashlight?
What was that noise?
What noise?
Did you hear that a loud ring bell noise?
No.
I got a light.
Jerma, that's the best light we have right now.
That's the best we've got for navigation.
All right.
Well, that's going to help a ton because we can actually see some color.
Can you navigate?
Do you want to go ahead so we can follow you Jerma?
Dead body, dead body, dead body.
Dead body?
Oh, Danny boy, the pipes are calling.
That might mean that there's a flashlight nearby.
Yes, I would.
I was at admin.
So, oh wait, rest in peace Kiwi.
Sleep tight princess.
I've never fucking played that game once.
I was in electrical.
It wasn't me.
Jerma, you don't see a flashlight on the ground anywhere?
No, I just got the the black light one.
Can you help us find?
Look on the ground quite a little bit.
Yeah, would it be down right here somewhere?
Maybe.
It's possible.
It's probably by the body or under the body.
Oh, she had grip around her body a little bit.
I just reached in her.
Never mind.
I'm gonna grip around her body until I find something.
I'm really there.
Come the allergy.
Yeah, a little bit, but I'm okay.
I don't I think it's the smoke in LA or something.
I don't know.
It's gross.
I don't see a flashlight.
No, I can't we get.
Yeah, I think we need to book it.
I think we need to get the fuck out.
I can't with the exits that are not us.
Okay.
That's a good question.
I flashlights flickering Joseph Williams.
If you are here.
Fuck you.
Yeah, fuck you.
Is that a bloody skull friend?
You jackass.
Jerma, where'd you go?
I'm right over here.
Yeah, we're here.
Flashlights flickering above us was above us above us.
I hear noises above us.
Yes.
Well, all right.
Oh, I see Jerma.
Hi, Jerma.
I do.
Where are we?
I was just up there.
I heard a whisper.
Jerma help us find the way out because we can't see shit without
you.
All right.
I got this little rinky-dink light.
So let's go this way.
No other way.
I'm follow me.
I don't think this is you guys.
You guys see me?
Yeah, I don't this is an exit here.
You're pointing.
This is a door here on the second floor.
We're on the second floor.
But let's see the door here.
This is a this is a this is a bathroom.
Oh, there's a bookcase.
Or maybe we should have left someone back in the truck for
the night vision.
I was in the truck and then I
I left the fucking camera upstairs in a room.
God damn it.
Oh, wait a minute.
That's a window shit.
This is a fucking wretched experience with only one flashlight.
Yeah, we definitely need to save up for more of these things.
I need to get really close to my screen.
Right.
We chose the hardest one.
Oh, this is the hard one.
The flashlight keeps flickering over here.
I can see the truck.
Okay, guys, we got to get downstairs.
You see the flickering light?
No, you don't.
Oh my God.
There's somebody near me.
I think my God.
Oh my God.
I help help help help.
It's a screamer behind me screamed at me and he made a noise.
Oh shit.
I found it.
He's right there.
It's a skeleton.
We get get back get back get back to the truck and it's a skeleton.
It's just a bloody skeleton.
I know I found it.
I can't see shit.
You guys just left me.
You know over here over here over here.
Oh, there you are.
I saw it was a bloody skeleton.
Wait.
A bloody Skeleton.
Yes, it was a blood ghost is that I don't know what he did.
He disappeared.
We got evidence.
Jerma, fine.
You gotta you gotta you gotta lead us but why you here is weird
a mug I look I just got to say caffeinated, bro.
You doing like a duct tape challenge.
You're really hard to follow.
Did it kill Vinnie?
Yeah, he said where are you?
I don't know where you are you don't see me we don't see each other he's right
nearest he's right next to us somewhere I can't see you you you you are way your
flashlight works like unless I maybe took it I don't know like what am I
looking at my not on your screen I'm right next to you yeah no I see you I
see you okay you leave there's like a beep there's a heartbeat in my ear what
does that mean um I don't know I'm gonna find the staircase down we're in a
bedroom right now we're in a bedroom let's communicate Joseph Williams we
mean you no harm Joseph Williams we mean you no harm Joseph Williams we come in
peace how about we move very slowly okay but you like point the camera a little
bit at the ground because if you that if you block the direction of the camp of
the light I can't see you I lose you completely are you good now yeah I can
see where you're pointing on the ground okay so we need to find the stairs out
of here good luck I have no idea where the hell we could do I don't know where
we even are or the house remember I'm just shimmying shimmy shimmy this is a
wall Joseph is his name yeah Joseph right spot Joseph Joe star the bathroom
that's a toilet so that is wrong I don't see you saw a bloody skeleton that's
probably like a big clue wait is that stairs right there wait wait turn around
yeah bingo what's this stairs going down you go first out of here let's get the
hell out of this frickin place whatever whatever is a bloody skeleton we're
gonna look through the journal and see what like a skeleton with all the skin
off is I think that's just a skeleton did it have muscle or is it just a
skeleton I don't know it's kind of like waterlogged waterlogged okay like that
this is good this is good strat okay we're gonna be close to the door now
look in front over this way this is working this is working okay I don't see
this looks like a living room yeah I think we're gonna you okay our breath
our breath is cold it's very cold holy shit what a clue so that's another clue
that's a clue that's a clue is he gonna get back alive equals keep pointing at
the floor that's the truck he's in here somewhere I think he's in here
we got oh I got the the the writing thing the book down down Joseph it's on
it's right here on the ground yep it's walking you'll write something bitch
don't anger him like where are you gonna anger him I'm right behind you it'd be
nice I mean the walls could start shaking do you want to get out okay here
we go follow me do you see me okay yeah I see I see it just keep pointing at the
ground it's the only way I'll see around you yeah yeah beautiful beautiful is that
the door right there because we saw the truck out the window oh this is the door
we're out hey that was easy we did it easy dude we lose two babies introducing
ghosts okay hold on oh wait no we got it Jack we got it we totally got this we
got this easy I got the book in my hand right now spirit you do yeah it
definitely wasn't a spirit okay we had a cold breath right yeah we had cold
breath and we saw a skeleton damn we were really close to dying and we were
like it was definitely hunting us I had 0% gin the flashlight was in the truck
the whole time guys the flashlight was in the truck the whole time I saw it was
like a it was like a scary looking thing it looked like a it was like a like a
hollow from Dark Souls with blood all over him a gin it could be a gin let me
have a look a mayor is powerful in the dark evidence with cold breath right
we definitely put that down that we got called we definitely got called breath
what about nothing else besides that that we have well we got a we got a
let's see it'll be phantom so we we got a what was our EMF level did we ever see
it was is that six I don't even know at the maximum activity look spirit box we
didn't see done to see fingerprints I didn't see ghost orbs I didn't see ghost
writing we did get freezing temperatures though so there's one clue and he said
get the book the book to get the book the book why I don't know but he's trying
to tell us to get the book he left the book in the house is the book but why
would we need it I don't know I got a flashlight now though where was it in
it where was where is it in the house okay yeah yeah yeah again where's that
was that HD DVD camera HD DVD can you do both light and camera or I'm gonna try
to get a picture of this motherfucker's where to go all right if I get a cool
pic of this here that's worth a lot of money even if I'm dead okay so we got
freezing temperatures just skeleton one of the options it looked like a skeleton
skin hanging off of I'm gonna get a picture how do I take a photo oh just
like that okay are you gonna stick around there
oh my god he locked the door he closed it on me and locked the door and I was
too afraid to take a photo oh the electrical box is out here I think I
hear him I don't know he's making noise he's walking I don't know where he is
though yeah I was I was walking around the side of the house if I can get a
picture man we're gonna be millionaires he locked the front door he closed it on
he slammed the front door in my face locked it I'm gonna try the back door
pretty good we can we can send that in yeah see if you can figure anything out
I'm gonna try to get a photo of him I'm in the house just I'm just trying to get
a picture man it's all I care about wish I had this camera earlier oh it doesn't
yeah the camera that did track back to the truck was left upstairs looks like
someone was holding it when tracking it oh shit alright this is the still camera I might die
you hear me Roger yeah I'm gonna try and turn on the light of the lights on
lights work oh my god I didn't get it I didn't get it it was that I'm dead I'm
dead I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead this is
where I die oh really maybe he's upstairs then maybe he doesn't hang out over here
wait wait wait did Vinnie say the book was oh shit I found the book and there's
writing in this book it's a it's a it's a it's a sub it's a doctor's thing no it's
not it's a triangles with going down it's a infinity eight symbol sideways
with a line going up top and two lines going through it brimstone okay this
brimstone on the left and I'll just get it we got freezing breath and brimstone
he's gonna kill me I'm dead in like five seconds hey dude it was it was really
nice knowing you I'm dead in like two seconds I can hear him coming over here
right now brimstone and then hello brimstone and then
who's this you guys hear me at least we read the book I got it brimstone
brimstone and what was the other thing on the other side I hope he figures it
out that was Lucifer's sigil oh that's demon for sure oh we get it it's a
demon for sure I can't take the like fucking noises I should have taken the
book and ran yeah but I mean here's the thing I didn't know I couldn't read it
I was freaking out ghost or ghost riding freezing temperatures what else it's a
day it's fucking demon it's a demon it's a demon it's a demon he'll get it turn
my lights off oh wait what does that mean I got 20 bucks I did get steaming
yeah I did well I got 10 bucks I got man flashlights are expensive no it
wasn't did we find out what it was no it says the ghost was a demon right there
oh we got it then we got it yeah we got it nice we got it
Oh team so when we were ghosts none of us could hear each other is that right I
heard germa but I couldn't I couldn't hear you guys I could hear both of you
but you didn't hear me wait when you die do you lose your inventory or is it this
is like one time you stuff I don't know it says experience gain I'm almost level
two parabolic mic I think we keep keep the stuff we buy yeah I think we keep it
I think eventually we're just gonna be like gods we're gonna be like the
mystery mystery machine crew scooby-doo where are you if you die you lose can
you imagine if you did this in real life and lost three of your friends and made
twenty dollars honestly do you think they like put these kind of jobs up on
task rabbit yeah it's an app where you can put in calls to like a carpenter
someone to be like fiber but for someone to come to your house and put shit
together it says make sure someone doesn't leave the flashlight in the van
this time yeah we can't leave that behind we have to be very I thought we I
thought we brought it what should I buy um I'm gonna save up I want a bigger
flashlight like a novelty size flashlight I want a floodlight tripod
you get a tripod yeah for the camera for the camera oh we should do that do we
want to go one more yeah yeah yeah I think so maybe like okay let's let's do
chat what's a good one for us to do as a start yeah like for babies what's a good
baby one do an easy map tangle would tangle would yeah all right live cameras
with someone in the truck is an OP I'm gonna say crucifix is really important
you apparently when you buy a thing you have to add it to the you know you got
to add it we don't have does it nobody has a crucifix right we don't have it at
Christmas no we don't have one if we cut we would need those for banshees and we
got to make sure we pay attention to the whiteboard whiteboard okay right at the
beginning we got a there's objectives on it and that's how you get the money oh
we got to add the gear okay total items sitting or something so apparently yeah
we don't get money unless we fill out even if you're dead you can still fill
out your journal but oh I was you gotta do your when you're ghost you got to do
your tasks just like among us yeah I know that game okay wait it says select
do I do that yeah do tangle would Ross Oh tangle would okay is this the only three
houses right now they've randomly generated I guess all right I'm
readying up ready all right you know what it is like ten times this cream already
power it oh yeah I'm bleeding through to you guys sorry I'm just trying to talk
to my chat sorry about that yeah yep chat there's we've done everything we
can to try and fix Vinnie's beeping we don't know what's causing it it's just a
way of life now so from what what I understand is it says it's partially
random missions and ghosts are random so you have to unlock new maps yeah so
German you're when you're ready yeah I was looking at I was looking at chat
they were saying some things are you are we ready to go guys I think we're ready
this one we're gonna win again oh wait wait we did when that last one it was a
little sloppy but we did all right we did good got the key okay
right objectives we need a photo of the ghost we gotta get a photo of the dirty
water in the sink that's like a ten dollar objective and then we need to
find evidence of paranormal on the EMF reader I'll carry the blacklight the
ghost name is Joseph Brown Joseph Brown Joseph Brown Joseph Brown if I'm doing
the flashlight if anyone wants to use my glow stick that sounds like the
innuendo it's not who wants this I think the can I got a candle got a
candle does anyone have a I'll take the glow stick oh yeah you take the glow
stick do we does anyone want the game does anyone with the Gameboy I mean I
guess I'll take it I think him boy yeah you think gameboy German you think game
boy I got the I have the photo camera too I'll bring the sage for good vibes
no don't don't bring it why because if you drop it and die we don't get it back
and we can't use it because we have no lighter gamer pocket all right they were
ready let's roll out oh it's this house again tutorial house yeah wait this
house has got a serious ghost problem we're here every week yeah we just an
escape room oh look at the kitty Joseph Joseph Brown are you Joseph Brown are
you here Joseph Brown I need to get out of Brown guys they've got a bread box
you know their bread is fresh Joseph Brown are you here all right was the
dirty sink give us a sign Joseph Brown let me try something guys hey yeah Joey
how you doing it's me Vinny okay you know me from the block I need you to
tell me a little something okay no no more hey Joey you're here so we're gonna
get a picture of the scum in the sink yeah where's the sink yeah if I see that
ghost you know I'm gonna do I'm gonna tell him to fork off Vinny this picture
that we get I want you in the photo I want you in the photo like throwing up
like the peace sign with you I think he's a fan of the culinary arts Joey that
sound what the fuck is that who's flatline Oh already serious already
sink you Joseph Brown hey no crouch down here crouch down here in front of the
sink no I already got it I got it I got it all right here we go all right
well I teleported wrong thing good okay we only got a couple photos left so I
think we have to be very careful what are the keys to several keys okay so the
lights go out guys this is the room we have to go to there's a breaker box the
breakers here I think Joseph Brown are you here Joseph Brown I get the radio
that's Jerma Jerma's got the radio oh sick Brown are you in town Joseph Brown
how old are you nothing detective how now brown cow Joseph Brown are you here
no we don't know you finger prints
yes yes there's a print oh guys you had a fingerprint yeah mark it in the journal
please okay another finger another handprint handprint handprint right here
all that fit get a photo get a photo get signed it on there I don't have all
the time boys there you go that way some film yeah oh don't don't not too much not
too much not too much okay is there any are you any nasty business on the rugs
on the on the on the pillows oh god it's a fucking mosaic of semen where's the
where's the dirty show those ectoplasm ghost goo all over this room all over the
bed doesn't look dirty he's got ectoplasm all over me this doesn't look
dirty at all are you here in your own closet yeah let's look at the mirror
guys I think we might be vampires I've got no reflection where's the dirty
where's the dirty sink that explains a lot wait hold on there's a guy this is
a reflection of a man what the fuck you see that I hate that why is there a
reflection of a man who's that he's wide who the fuck is that he's like super
wide dude he's like large and in charge guys there's like picture yeah that's
weird Joseph Brown how old are you Joseph Brown are these your shoes if so why do
you collect so many and women shoes aka are you Quentin Tarantino he likes the
way they feel I should let's check them with the black sink no it's not Quentin
Tarantino what's over here nothing should we go upstairs or downstairs the
base oh there's upstairs in here yeah I think there's a basement room I turn on
a candle you with a with a fire oh shit we don't have any fire whoa did you hear
that down there that was wait yes the game boys going off are you here can we
get a flashlight down here he's talking wait Joseph Brown are you here hello he
said attack attack I he said he said attack I'm gonna attack well that means
he's threatened Joseph are you here my fucking headset where's Kiwi Kiwi Joseph
are you under attack wait we're in the basement dude rush be he said attack
what does that mean I don't know he said like yeah okay so that's evidence guys
that's that's what I like to call evidence so we have two pieces of
evidence currently spirit box and fingerprints yeah okay fingerprints and
so now we just need either writing journal or EMF right so I have the EMF
thing does anyone want to come back with me to the van and get yeah I'll come
with you let's go all right I don't know I left the journal it's right here we
need a journal we got the journal on the ground so if we leave the room he might
he might write in it when we come back yeah we'll do that but someone should go
to the van and look at the footage of the camera so that way we can see if
there's a hold on oh shit I'm coming me and give you go to the car
I don't know where this dirty sick German German German German take take this
take that take take that with the EMV thing if it goes to read that's evidence
oh shit okay I'll be here and take this fork for good luck it served me well if
you get hungry take this fork and have yourself a little snack there's a bread
box right here sick yeah all right let's go to the car all right so I should I'm
gonna walk around this thing I need a light Vinny do you have a light nice when
you guys get to the van take a look at the camera I'm Vinny's gamer chair thank
you this is nice fuck I thought I could get a picture of your teeth
yeah okay we've got a vision on German can you turn the lights off yeah good
how's that I got the the green thing on Joseph yo I what's his name what was his
name Joseph Brown his name Joseph Joseph Brown how old are you but any of the
thing I didn't do anything that was not us yes yes yes yeah yeah there is alter
guys bingo oh we gonna check the book we check the book check the book oh this
motherfuckers in the basement the camera the camera is missing right in front of
the basement door right in front of the basement door you see me any Vinny the
cameras back here somewhere on the on the stairs
yeah we lost the camera through the ground yes Roger plate we can just turn
the fucking light on what I'm stupid what are we doing we got it got it it's
on the other side it's like in the wall completely oh nice
but then it teleported oh I think it's outside Roger he might be in the wall
actually oh shit Joseph Brown are you here Joseph Brown how old are you any
any guys do you see any pants walking around by themselves like wrong trousers
I don't see pants is a pair of pants just walking around is that just me
you're seeing any Vinny but we're gonna go take a look but look at the book
let's go for the go get that book yeah we're gonna go get that book any writing
it empty book Joseph Brown are you here Joseph Brown are you here oh shit I've
lost again I'm gonna make the trek to the power I'll come with you oh nice
beautiful beautiful trusty cameras right here yeah it's right there let's let's
turn on the lights oh you guys did it already nice it's here but it's through
what are the rooms are in this house first tee I just do another room yes
change we got all the evidence what about the sink we did chat chat
members are saying yeah what the dirty sink you get the emf we didn't get emf
we got to check the sink still like there's another hand guys there's
another handprint right here yeah that's already we got it this is a
poltergeist based on the handprints oh I heard I heard some radio was emf I'm
being told there was emf which one of you had the emf reader hello Germans
made contact stocking German make contact Joseph Brown are you here an
adult but he's an adult he's an adult that means his age Joseph Brown how old
are you he Joseph Brown where are you Joseph the light scared him off you
turn that off any yeah Joseph Brown how old are you Joseph Brown he's a he's
just around are you friendly are you angry
he said attack the fuck out of here hey Joseph wrong see what happens yeah we we
got that that's close enough in my opinion it looks like it could have gone
up to a five I mean it is at a three and a four here and that's so we got
fingerprint spirit box and you got a five we got a five okay I'll believe
chat I'm not seeing anything come up for ghosts with that we didn't get a we
didn't get a photo of the dirty sink yeah yeah fuck the sink we don't need a
picture of the thing no matter it's ten bucks whatever like that's nothing
right Joseph Brown what are you doing or something I don't know okay there's a
line here and like I'm seeing that this is his line and I'm like stepping over
it a little bit hey Joseph Brown I'm not over your line yet Joseph Brown not over
the line yet not over the line yet not over the line yet not over the line yet
hey we should drop this book in here and see if he writes anything come back
that's right you're gonna make him angry what did you say to him typical banter
you know he said his age was e he kept saying yeah I don't know he said when
you when you asked what his age was he said e he said are you there he said
adult yeah he said adults this fucking guy died like 10,000 years ago in this
spot where this house was built of course he's a attack me I don't me
attacking like this dude died he was a caveman like he was killed by a mammoth
like there are 3,000 years 4,000 billion years ago
can the other stuff kill kill kill me kill attack mammoth let's find out love
it oh big bird in sky rip the skull off head big egg try to I try to get egg
from nest lost lost head and scalp
spirit box fingerprints and ghost orb the only thing we didn't get was a ghost
orb but our camera is now fucking in a wall so there's no way that's gonna
happen we're never gonna find out if there was a ghost or that's that's it
what's what's the other shit out my face oh I believe we are poltergeist I'm
gonna yeah let me let me let me lock in poltergeist too before we we confirm
that I'm just reading up real quick before we also German we should you want
to get in there and take a couple more photos it or you uh you're good I think
I got zero left to take I'm going with poltergeist yep just because I saw that
thing fall off the wall I'm sure it's guys this is fun by the way once we got
it all figured out it took a while but yeah it was a good game I didn't I had
to change the control scheme though because I had tons of problems so yeah I
think it's a folder guys too having read all these this is great yeah it's
here's what here's what we have here chat guys it says here discover what type of
ghosts we're dealing with subjective one that we're working on okay we think we
got me capture a photo of the ghost we don't have and we still didn't get the
dirty water in the sink so it looks like we only got the EMF reader evidence
was it freezing in there think picture we didn't get good sink picture do we
need to take a picture of the EMF reader we got we got the EMF one okay that's
why it's gray took me photos accidentally camera ever again you guys
took some really nice photos though they look great memories after a photo of
what links probably the best we can do yeah the photo the ghost is probably
gonna be in the same room where the orbs are you just go in with the camera take
a picture with but we can't do much without the camera we can't see the orbs
yeah so we're we're done so we're boned yeah let's lock it in everyone entered
for ten bucks give me that ten dollars well the journal I did didn't it was a
race what the right what is a race race race what I wanted to know why it was a
race shit god damn it well how we had it I thought we had it too I really did
mega low that's my fault I was convinced it was poltergeist that's my fault I took
too many photos of things that it was the game's fault the camera went through
the wall hey that's true that's true the camera did go through the wall we had a
little bit of a glitch there it's fun to take the blame and put it on like
something else like the game yeah it's cool like I agree yeah I think I would
much prefer to do that then take the blame myself well is it is it is it is
it past midnight where you are now I guess it would be right it's it's 1 40
a.m. for me oh so happy happy Halloween ish I guess
first right yeah we started spooktober with spooky month and like we have ghost
activity except it wasn't a poltergeist but that's okay mm-hmm we should do this
again what I agree when the game is a little bit more worked on as well like
apparently the updates are frequent so that's good that's cool that's cool it
seems pretty good I mean I didn't I didn't think there's gonna be any
actual monsters that like attacked you but I very clearly I've saw like at
least once or twice very clear monster you saw skeleton we died what skeleton
dude yeah what does that say that barrel what does that say oh cock oak
oakleo oil oh cock Leo oil oakleo oil garber oil gotcha oh gotcha well that was
fun yeah it was good let's do something again
sometime yes it was I was actually was pretty fun I had actually really good
it was also mega spooked in VR it was it was really good if you ever get your VR
fixed Jerma we got to do this again because I think it's very different it
hits different as they say yeah I'll get it working all right
peace out guys thanks for joining me and thank you for having me as a part of
this team we'll ghost hunt more and we'll buy some flashlights next time
cheers lots of flashlights okay bye guys I'm gonna I'm gonna quickly go talk
to my stream okay me too goodbye later I'm gonna leak the
fucking lobby if I have this game what if I just like open it what if I just
leaked the lobby right now and then bailed I got almost 10k people watching
right now this bound to be somebody that's gonna come in and start like
fucking blowing eardrum music that's a bad idea that's a very bad yeah that's
yep very bad idea very bad idea but yeah I knew this was gonna be a very long
stream I'm gonna hang up for a little bit though we'll talk about a FTK for a
little bit just really wanted to play something Vinny I know those two were
also really fun to play with so Vinny and I've been talking about trying to do
something for a very very long time so I thought that was actually pretty fun
but you can do chubby bunny not I'm not doing I'm not doing chubby bunny right
you want alone you want alone oh I don't fucking want to do this alone
yo let me join no dirty waters dirty water in the sink I just want to get a
picture of the sink key on table key on table got it
whoops that's a well one down one down oh I don't like playing this alone it's so
much better to play this with other people because then you can just like
bounce off of them and you know it's scared as much this is really scary now
that I'm doing this of alone scare Thursday hear that that was phone just
vibrated was that phone just vibrated that wasn't me right what about the sink
where's the sink they got a sink I was gonna take a picture picture of every
sink in the house turn on the sink turn on turn the water on I can't I can't
turn the water on I just got a photo of him and it didn't do anything that guy
was like a foot it was the butcher was I too slow it was too slow it was
actually that was fucking scared we didn't see that once it's cuz I'm the
only person here so the East she's just like camping me I get it yeah this is
not for people to walk around for him to fuck with I can't believe I didn't get
him not even like an arm even scary yeah it's way scarier alone
everybody like telling jokes in my ear I gotta get a photo of this guy though I
like have to Joseph bra I don't know the guy's name Mike nope not that one
Charlie Brown Charlie Brown I'm sorry that Lucy used to rip the football
underneath you when you tried to kick the football and you got really mad
about it that was a long time ago thought that was just him hanging
outside the window this is cool this game is fucking cool I'm just like
realizing this is cool game it's been like two and a half hours I'm just
realizing now this is pretty fun oh shit alright get a photo photo photo photo a
good one and then I'm gonna turn stream off I've been waiting for years for a
ghost hunting game it's probably the one I turn the lights off no he was over
here he was in this room here freaked out what I was yep okay here we go this
teddy bear or something here we go here we go here we go I'm gonna get it I
gotta get it Charlie Brown enough is enough old cold there he was come on in
come on come on right in the lens right in the lens let's go come on right in
the lens let's go hello hello hello hello hello hello hello hello hello
hello I think it's gone are you friendly are you friendly how old are you I need
a radio this game sucks silent I can hear every creak yeah what I heard a
I heard a vibrate I heard a vibrate I heard a vibrate I heard a vibrate hey
he's here here he's here he's here he's here he's here he's here he's here he's
right here open the door open up right in the camera right open it right in the
camera what we should are you here let me in let me in the back let me in the
bathroom I'm gonna show up in the dark now are you alright I'm done that's fun
I can't find him I don't know where he is he jump scared ran at me and then he
disappeared now he's scared he won't come back out and I've right I want
somebody to take that footage I want you to slow it down when I went like
I want you to sub frame by frame he's not coming out he's scared I scared him
away with a flash okay he's a holy shit I heard a door open to get him what is he
I'm leaving I'm leaving I'm leaving I'm leaving I'm leaving I'm leaving I'm
leaving I'm leaving bye I'm out okay alright he was frozen breath he had a
he had a he was he looked like a butcher alright I got it frozen breath he talked
to me and looked at me and shit that's a mirror close it up that's a horse 20
bucks for those photos that's the most money that we've seen all game he's not
in one of these is he phantom disappears in photos right a phantom
literally disappears and fucks off if you take a photo alright I'm out of here
no no more no more let's talk about FTK for a second let me do that I can just
sit here so as you know on Saturday FTK is going to come back what that means
I'm looking right at you I see the chat the chat is going fucking crazy right
now I can see that's going so fast can't fucking talk no FTK is going back on
Saturday still trying to figure out exactly how we're gonna do some of these
systems because I know I told you guys that it was gonna be a white listing
system you just need to be an active sub and I think that's still gonna be the
case there's a really really simple UI that they these guys have made where
just in the game when you connect to the server you're just gonna check to see if
you're a sub just an active sub it just actually goes to twitch is like API and
goes oh you are okay you're good but because I've delayed it like an extra
three weeks I don't I don't know I'm trying to still figure out what I want
to do about it because I said that like a month ago oh you just just just be
subbed to the channel you just have to be subbed and then it didn't happen for
like a month but I feel bad that people may have subbed for that and then now
they didn't they're not subbed anymore and they're just like oh well thanks
dude like I was subbed to your channel for like a month or two and I thought
you I was supposed to do that so I'm trying to figure out what I want to do
obviously the last three or four weeks have been a little hectic a little a
little odd some stuff happened that I wasn't really necessarily like ready and
prepared to do but I'm gonna find out what we're gonna figure that out I get a
300 word essay I just subbed for that thing but it's gonna be a lot of fun
it's not what you think it is it's not just running around the server with an
arrow and a bow and shoot at the guy it's gonna be a very elaborate stream
there's gonna be way more servers this time it's not just gonna be one that
everybody just dumps on to there's gonna be a whole hub system where if you die
or if you initially join you go to this little hub server which is like a bunch
of servers connected to each other so you can hang out in there and just chill
out and you'll get pulled in in a first-come first-serve basis
they're gonna run advertisements like right now on FTK no I don't I don't
want to do that drop the IP what's gonna happen here is over the next few days if
you're not part of the discord I would really highly recommend you become part
of the discord because there's gonna be a lot of info put in there the actual IP
for the server the actual website it's not on yet and they're not gonna turn it
on till probably a day or two before so keep an eye on that discord I'm gonna be
in the general chat over the next couple days and you're gonna get everything you
need I'm perma banned from your discord well why did you act like such a bad bad
boy you got pro what do you got by got perma banned from the discord what did
you do it's cool gov stop don't be so bad watch your watch your mouth your
mother uses that computer too you know I'm abandoned from twitch too just to
just to complete the circle but that's probably gonna be tomorrow night into
Friday morning I'm not gonna be streaming the next two days because I
want to really get on this ball and make sure this goes smoothly Saturday's the
next time I'm gonna turn the stream on 3 p.m. Pacific on Saturday 3 p.m. that's
when it's happening that's when the streams gonna turn on that's what I'm
gonna start this specific events I'm gonna look at you here I don't need to
look at you down here you're right there I'm looking at you it's gonna be like
three or four specific events that this streams gonna entail so it'll be a lot
of fun I'm not gonna tell you what those events are because why would I do that
that's spoilers and I'm not gonna spoil anything for you so why would I do that
I feel uncomfortable when you look at the camera yeah I don't I'm looking at
the chat right here who'd have rested to it no I'm gonna I'm it's getting late
but minecraft 1.8 1.8.9 or 1.8.8 I'll get the exact details but it'll be much
more stable there'll be much more to do they were working on this for a long time
and it shows and the server is gonna stay up by the way after this I'm not
just gonna turn it off anybody that did not get to participate in the events of
the stream are going to be able to participate whenever they want for about
a month after the stream turns off so you guys can just join it you can play
it do all the activities whenever you want so for those who that didn't get a
chance to play it on stream and it's gonna be a lot of you because I think
there's only about three or four hundred people can be in the game server I
believe thousands of people can be connected to the hub server but in the
actual game server only a few hundred at a time I lost my sub feels bad man
yeah let me let me see what I want to do about that is that right I feel like I
feel shitty telling people to sub to do oh yeah sub through 50k oh sorry didn't
happen I'll see you next month you don't know you didn't want to sub again
tough shit I don't want to do that we'll see if there's a solution I'm looking
forward to it though so you'll see the stream turn on again for FTK but before
that join the discord I'll be in the general the mods will be talking about
it too we'll know we just got a bunch of community we got a lot of stuff but
there was a lot of subs and shit today but because of the nature of the game I
didn't kind of just want to talk over everybody and like oh hey thanks for the
fucking next to the sub say hey thanks oh wait hey where's the ghost I don't
want to there was like four of us at one I want to kind of clear the air there
but that's a lot of money oh shit I missed a raid too didn't I box box rated
long time ago box box thing if you guys came from box box thank you box box is
awesome really appreciate that I missed it I was very engrossed thank you box
box if any of you guys still here from there thank you I really appreciate that
sorry I missed it earlier I don't know how I did I just get sucked in sometimes
Edmund Hakari thanks for the 10 subs storm GC 10 thanks for the 10 subs $100
from FS woods holy fuck I'm so happy you got a haircut you look like a human now
I need another one I need another haircut I've also gained about 12 pounds
like let me be real about that too since the last time you saw me on camera I was
pretty I was looking a little gaunt I've gained about 12 pounds in the last like
two months three months if you remember the green screen stream I was looking a
little thin as the I was there was a bunch of shit that was going on it was
hard to keep my appetite up I was trying but I'm back up to kind of where I was
before which I'm happy about big healthy boy hmm I'm not quite at my target yet
getting there though I'll do what you gotta do but thank you FS what's next
the hundred bucks thank you a Jax the mediocre for the five subs should be
for the five community subs ready dread gave $300 and I think it was like a
little while ago and I missed it that's there 30,000 bits that's that's too many
bits to give ready dread ready dread with $300 in bits that is an extreme
amount of money and not to talk about extreme phylactery lich decided to give
69 community subs which is also an extreme amount of fucking money that's
69 subs insane both of you are insane listen to Freddy he said germa I'm
scared but thanks guys boiky 10 subs stormy to five subs it's a sky five subs
snar boses 10 subs destroy dude five subs and then thrag now 20 community
fucking subs right now it's a storm oh thank you guys seriously that's you guys
if you guys shower this channel with so much money almost at the end of the
time thanks a lot dream with ready dread fucking play like Scrabble or something
Freddy yeah I have I have an open invitation to Freddy by the way for a
Las Vegas Denny's steak dinner hope it settles down on her any steak power at
dinner purple power it's the only power I like it's way better than Gatorade it's
way more flavorful but that's where this is gonna end I will see you guys on
Saturday for FTK hop in the discord I will be around over the next few days
give you more details I've subs from Johnny boy thank you Johnny boy right at
the end so let's move over here let's show the credits let's show all these
subs of a lot of them and I'm really happy to do something with Vinny Vinny's
awesome Ross awesome too or that's the first time I've ever like had an
experience at all with Ross and swell swell guy and Kiwi to give you they
would great players sometimes you know when you're in a group of people that's
more than like three or four you don't really know what to expect because oh
shit oh that felt pretty that felt pretty comfortable I felt very
comfortable I had a lot of fun first 30 minutes or so we were really trying to
set stuff up but I had a look this is gonna be just a late-night hangout
stream I'm glad we got to do it well thanks for watching
well tired on this side only on this side though I still can't believe it I
was you have no idea I was sitting here just seething in rage over what did you
see it you didn't see it right which finger today's I use this hand right I
didn't use this hand did I I use the I use the gross hand all right I'll see you
guys on Saturday thanks for watching everybody show us no that's that's
disgusting guys I'm not gonna just show you that I'm sure I'm getting rid of it
it comes up yeah my VR is fucked up I tried to spend all day trying to fix it
I have no idea what the hell's going on a lot of people were trying to help
earlier I was just so angry sitting in this chair up until I'll be honest up
until like Vinnie got in the call I was insanely angry about my VR not working
I was just sitting there going like stupid fucking VR yeah VR sucks
everything sucks this is stupid why is why is my computer suck and then like I
started the stream and it's like okay here we are and Vinnie cheered me up so
Ross and Kiwi as well so I feel a lot better it's a lot fun second I heard the
the video fire alarm I was like yeah I don't even care if it's not VR that was
insane by the way I I really wonder what that actually was I can still hear it
yeah I kind of can yeah how are there this many subs the stream is only like
two and a half hours how is it this many people subbed this is a shitload of
people still even over two hours all right we are going to end the night we're
gonna just we're gonna raid Vinnie because I mean obviously we were just
playing with them so let's just go rate them cuz I'm turning the stream off
what is he doing right now Legend of Zelda Zelda Oracle of Ages yeah go say
hello to Vinnie you just saw him but a wave he's still going I will see you
guys on Saturday for FTK good night goodbye take care yourselves thanks for
watching very very late stream don't don't expect these very often take care
guys good night