Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with
Star!
And we're gonna be playing some Bloody Trapland. If you don't know what Bloody Trapland is, it's a bloody fucking good time, mate.
It's gonna be it's like Super Meat Boy.
Let's do the duck in every video. My name is Star. And Boo is in the call. Why are you Jerma too?
I want to be Jerma too. No, you're gonna confuse people. You need to change your name to Star Undercore.
You can't do that. It asks you to set your name when you start the game. You seriously picked Jerma too?
Yes. Are you a fucking idiot? Deeper into the cave we go. Do you just kill me?
How are you supposed to beat this part?
Oh my god. Oh, well you fuck up.
What? How did you even get by? Oh! Oh! How did you get by? Fuck, I just-
All right, I got this rat. We got this- something tells me this is really gonna suck.
This is level three. Fucking god damn it. No!
Calm down. Seriously calm down. Go one at a time. Okay. I'm bored. I just want to look at my cat's butt.
How come you're not facing the camera when you bend over? Oh, kitty cat. Yes.
I'm busy like winning the level motherfucker. See I like turn the- I turned to like say something to you and I like died.
Oh my god. I'm not even having fun. That's your own problem. I'm having the lots of fun.
I'm having tons of fun. You're gonna have to beat this stage then. I don't think I can do it.
You just don't feel like playing anymore. You just seriously gonna give up like that? Yeah.
I'm just gonna be here to annoy you and see if I can jump on your head or anything.
Wow, is this the boss fight? What's the first boss fight? I don't think there's any bosses.
There's no- if you- you really need to fuck off right now. Need a clip? Need a clip? Need a clip?
What? Oh, I thought we started on the left. What?
What just happened?
We got air shot. Why is there friendly fire like that? This makes it so much more difficult to do anything.
This game takes way too much concentration. I just want to play something nice like Rest In Peace Department.
Why won't you ever play Rest In Peace Department with me?
Funny thing is this video is gonna be going up before you put that one up so that joke will make sense.
Shit. Oh my god. No. No, I don't even know- I don't know what to do. I'm so- I don't know. I don't know. Fuck!
I don't see you getting that far. Look where I am. I'm up here. You go first because seriously, this is just getting stupid.
I'm trying to beat it.
You're an idiot, you know that.
Well, look at you. You did the same thing I did. Oh, good joke. Here, did you joke? Need a joke? Oh, shit.
I was gonna shit talk.
I'm kind of confused as to do right here. Well, how do you get over that? Oh, oh, okay. Do it. Do it up.
You can do this.
Nice. I wouldn't like this game if we weren't furries. How did you just seriously do-
You would kill me, asshole!
I'm sorry. You had a thing going there and I just fucked it all up.
I triggered it. Will you go? I triggered the fist. Go!
I just triggered the fist right there and you didn't even do- you didn't do anything.
You figure you're just gonna sit there and keep doing the crouch. Oh my goodness.
I'm making progress.
Oh, yeah? How do you like that?
Trigger the fist again.
No, you're not gonna do anything. If I trigger the fist again, you're not gonna do anything. You're just gonna stand there.
Yeah, I triggered it. Nice. Can we just sit back and let me do it? No.
Yes. Just sit back and just enjoy this. Enjoy this presentation of greatness.
Shit. That was- that was not planned. Good presentation.
Is this strike two? Strike two? Strike two? See that swirly thing? That never happened before. Strike three.
That never happened before. You're out. You're out. No. Here's the preview.
Can we edit around and just do it like I did at first try?
All right. Yeah. Can we just pretend like this is the first time I'm going in?
Yeah, let's pretend this is the first time you went in. Yeah, all this blood you see is like we just got to this stage.
Yeah, somebody- some like real- some scrub
was here before us and died like 300 times at this stage. It wasn't us.
Oh, there's even more to this bullshit. You better pull this through because there's no way I'm doing that. God damn, that thing is just
right in my ass. There's a pattern. There's a pattern. There's like an actual pattern to this.
I'm just trying to do it- I'm trying to do it ASAP Rocky.
Oh boy. No. What? I did like the lightest jump you could do there.
Whoa. Whoa, dude. Whoa. Okay. Whoa.
Yeah, how long do we have to play this so you can like have a video?
How long is this gonna keep going on? Like I don't think you've had any fun.
You do realize I'm putting that part in.
You do realize. Yeah, I know that's like how you conclude your video. Yeah. Oh.
What the hell is wrong with you?