Ah yes, the the return of the dentist. I almost just said happy Halloween. Hey, happy Halloween
everybody. That whole month has just been deleted in my brain. Quick, slime them. See what you guys
don't know is I have all those actions still. I might just turn a stream on one day and if I
do though something happens. I have those forever. I get to keep those. But uh yeah, we're starting
a little bit or I almost said early too. First happy Halloween then hey we're starting early.
Now we're starting late because it's Thanksgiving and I wanted to give some time to not just
start streaming at one two o'clock pacific. I figured it's probably better this way. So
we're gonna continue the Outer Worlds. This is gonna be the last stream you see from me for
a little bit. I'll be gone for about three or four days because I have a procedure I have to do
and it requires some annoying fasting as of tomorrow and then I have to do it
and then I have to be on drugs. So you won't see me for a three or four days. So after today
this is just gonna be we're gonna end the Outer Worlds tonight. Even if I don't get to the end,
I'll probably just finish it off stream. It depends on how close we get because I really
don't know if this stream is gonna be more than five or six hours. I don't know. It might be five,
it might be four, it might be six, this might be eight. But happy Thanksgiving if you're celebrating
it or if you've not celebrated it yet. If you just got this notification and you're at the dinner
table, then put me on as loud as it goes, put me on speaker and sit me on the table.
Yeah, can I get the um, can you get, can I, can I get the peas? Thank you. The turkey is absolutely
delicious by the way. It's one of the best turkeys I've ever had and I really am not, I know I say
that every single year. I know I say that, listen mom, I know I say that every year, every time you've
ever made a turkey, I say it's the best turkey I've ever had. But this one is for real. Damn,
that's good. Oh, sorry, I mean darn, sorry about that. All right, now turn me off because I'm gonna
start swearing and I know like your grandfather's not gonna like it. Am I off? All right, good.
Anyways, let's play the Outer Worlds. All of a sudden, grandpa's like, Outer Worlds?
No, no, keep that on, keep that on. Hey, anything to take me away from your family like arguing
about politics? We can argue about like the fake politics that are in the Outer Worlds,
right? You don't need, you don't need, listen grandpa, we don't need to argue anymore.
Just listen to me. All right, let's get going. I like this song. I wish it was not just the
level up screen. What about those emails? Well, I've read tons of emails on computers already.
I've read a lot of emails. Yeah, we'll see how this goes. Just gonna keep playing it. If you
don't know, you probably, if this is the first stream you've been to and you're like, why is
you, what does this have to do with dentists? That is a 15 plus hour long build up for the joke
and there's not much I could say. It would take me 15 hours to explain it to you.
So let's go. I just love dental health, yeah. All right, let the game load. Hold on. All right,
so the last thing we did was, I remember I was like really tired last night. I didn't listen
to a single thing this person said. I think I specifically said this guy's born the fuck
out of me and then like I turned off the stream. So I did what, I don't remember what this was.
Then I killed him. No, he's still alive. All right, here we go. This is, we have to go back to
the information broker promised to find the location of the chemicals needed
by Phineas. Problem is he hasn't delivered the intel on time and hasn't provided an explanation.
Travel to Monarch, find him and obtain the data. Okay, this is where I am now.
The broker can't deliver the location of the chemicals until you stop the Iconoclasts and MSI
transmissions that are interfering with the tower. Okay, so Sanjar leads MSI out of Stellar Bay
and Graham Bryant leads the Iconoclasts out of Amber Heights. Earning their favor might
convince them to stop transmitting. Complete the quest, bolt with his name for Sanjar to start
earning MSI's trust. All right, so what do I want to do here?
Should I just go just take a chainsaw and just cut the tower down? Well, let's go to,
Sanjar needs a bolt 52 cartridge. I remember this part. All right, let's get into the good graces
of Sanjar. So we need to get into the arms building. Now, where the hell is that? Oh,
fuck. Sorry, I forgot. Yeah, I forgot. I forgot I was going to shoot that guy in the head right
when the stream started. Oops, I forgot. Yeah, I was like actually planning on doing that too.
That's all right. Damn it. Oh, I was too busy like thinking about Thanksgiving. Oh,
that was going to be fun too. Damn it. I really like was going to do that. I was going to actually
do that. Begin Broadway. I can start. I can turn the stream button on. Authorized broadcaster,
don't even try to pretend you're unaware that all broadcasting is currently locked down.
Please return to milling about the break room and lamenting that internship and corporate
arbitration that you never finished. Or to override the lock on recording, simply enter your admin
username and password in the command line. Oh, you can't maybe you should have been nicer to Val.
That's not good. All right, let's go. Wow, where is this? Is this on the other planet?
Time to turn on the webcam. Not time to turn on the webcam. All right, now where is this thing?
That's very far away, but it's not far away from here. Show us those teeth. Hurry up and do
something funny. Hurry. Hurry, quick. You'll get used to it. Hurry, quick, quick. Rush a joke so
I can do minus two because it wasn't funny because you didn't take the time to prepare
something interesting. Quick, hurry. Are you all right? My investment.
Shoot that rat with some knockback. You pull out of the archive here and start saying like
words that you like. When in doubt, say a word that everybody likes. Automatic comedy increase.
You're good. Game's too loud. I got you. Solved. I don't want to find all these stupid monsters,
but I guess I kind of have to. God damn it. All right, user special. Don't call them stupid.
Well, they are stupid. I mean, their intelligence level is not very high.
That doesn't mean I don't. Neither is my character. Yeah, that's okay. Call me stupid.
This character is stupid, but so is that animal that's right there. This animal is also stupid.
Why did I shoot the Colossus? I probably should not have shot the Colossus. That was stupid.
You are absolutely inclined to call me fucking stupid for that. Time to run. Wait, it's in here.
Holy shit. He just almost insta-killed me. Oh, I can't even open this door. Oh, he still sees me.
I'm dead. Heal. How do I heal? I don't have any heals left. Oh, okay. Well, that's a disaster.
How do I not have any heals left? God damn it. I'm just gonna go the other way.
I only have one heal. Who took them all? Wait, hold on a minute. I gotta go to Stellar Bay.
I gotta buy some heals. What happened to Sam and Max? They're still on the ship.
I was just trying two other dentists. Oh, yeah. Okay, well, that's still there. You guys,
that's true. All right. I need just a vending machine or something. All right, do you sell stuff?
Not the stuff I want. There we go. Buy them. Okay. What is this? Baked beans? No. Oh, fuck me.
Really? That's the same goddamn syringe. I bought the wrong thing. All right, where's the medic?
Where's the person that sells medicine? There you are. I would like to buy something.
Oh, god damn it. Why can I not buy anything from you? Aren't you the town medic? What?
Steal? I can't even steal. I already took everything from our house. Is there a vending
machine in there or do I have to go find the vending machine? You don't sell, do you?
If it isn't the famous hacker enjoying Stellar Bay, what can I do for you?
Nothing. Vending machine. Vendor. Okay. The yacht club vendor. Can I not see what these are? Vending
machine. Like, I can't. It's just there? All right. Well, it's just there apparently.
Go buy a yacht. Wasn't this the one I was just using? Maybe not. Okay. What's in here?
There's no heels here. Don't tell me I have to travel to like another galaxy to buy heels.
That's not going to happen, right? Where's this other one? In here? What was I just? Okay. So
where's this one? All right. Time to get in a spaceship and travel across the galaxy to buy
stim packs. Well, well. What? Isn't often we see new folk in Stellar Bay? First drink some.
I'm sure I'll take a drink. Enjoy. If you're keeping Neoka company, you'll need a few to
keep up with her. Sure. Do you have any heels? I need a person on this planet who can keep up with me.
Wait, we are talking about a drinking contest, right? Now what can I do for you?
No, you just have booze. All right. Well, what is the, what's my, what's my actual ship?
This is a heel, right? Injectable healing enhancer. Heals 20. Okay. My goodness.
There we go. Good. All right. I got enough. Oh, where is it? There it is. All right. I got 39
and I got this, uh, what do I want to use? Critical damage plus 15%. Yeah. Let's like use this shit.
How about the wrong thing? No, it's not. Heals 25% health over two seconds.
Isn't that just like a quick heal? You're going to get addicted to drugs. That's all right. He's
already addicted. No, I've been breathing in all kinds of gases and my character's fine. No,
the only thing that's happened to me this whole game is I'm afraid of monsters. That's it. It's
given me a, it gives you a choice if you want to be afraid of monsters or not. Okay. Let's go.
It's like, you know, you've seen quite a few monsters. Are you scared of them? Yes. No. Okay.
But if you were scared of them, we would give you a point to put in. Ooh, I'm scared of monsters.
They terrify me. I'm just like lying on a fucking job interview. It's like, all right, let's just
move. Don't attack the Colossus. Oh, for the love of God, I'm just running. I don't even have it
selected. Yes, I do. I get into the arms building. I can't even, I have to like find a key card or
something. I can't even lock, pick this fucking door. It's so dead. There's a whole entire town
of monsters is chasing at us. Why are you using that? Good. The big one can't even get in. Just
feed them in here. Okay. Uh, how am I supposed to get in that building? The bolt 52 is an abandoned
building north of stellar Bay. So I need a key card to get into there, but I don't have one. Or
I have to get up. I need one of those lock pickers. You guys just, you're doing fine out there.
Oh my God. I need one mag lock. Is that seriously the only way I can get in this building?
I almost just shot you. It has to be another way. Where's the big guy? All the way down there. Good.
All right. So front door. I needed one of those, uh, lockpick things. This doesn't work or a key
card, but where the hell would the key card be? I can't jump up or anything. No, I have to go in
the door. There's no way for me to climb, right? All right. Well, let's try to find the, one of
those door openers. I can't seriously be the only way you can get in that building. Let's try to
find one. That's a good question. What about here? Can I open up like a panel in the back?
Let's find a door opener. I just need to find one of those, uh, not the stunts, like the, the mag
picks. Evicted. Can't go in. Uh, nothing was in here. What about in here? Over here? Well, all
right. We're going to keep looking. Blue bodies. Monsters will have a door open, a pick on them.
I don't think so. Only monsters live in this whole galaxy here. This whole planet is just these
aliens. I don't think they're picking locks. I think they're eating people and knocking doors
down with their tails. Give me in here. Come on. No, shit. I think I've seen more weapon mods than
I have mag picks. Just meat. Everybody's evicted. I'm just like going back to the town now. What
did I do for Thanksgiving? I did not do very much because, uh, at this household we did the
Thanksgiving a little early because I, as of yesterday, could not eat a lot of the stuff
that is served at Thanksgiving. So no peas, no corn, no nuts. No. So I was kind of like,
let's just do it early. So we did it a little early. Okay. Am I about to literally just bust
a door down with my fucking face? How do I get up there? There's a ladder there, but can I jump
from here? I can't jump from here to there. You can. I mean, maybe I can. Oh my God.
I wonder, can I get off of this planet? This planet sucks. I have to like de-aggro the gigantic
guy. What's the aggro range? All right. Well I de-aggro him, but I have to cross the fucking
mode again. I can't kill it. Don't turn around. Don't turn around. Don't turn around. Don't turn
around. Don't turn around. Don't turn around. Good. Keep eating. Keep eating Ellie. All right.
Now turn around. He's going to see me. Maybe not. Okay. So can I jump from here to there to there?
I like guys saying that there's a ladder. I don't know. I don't know what you're talking about.
I see that one, but not over here. Is it a ladder on the other building? If I have to kill one more
of these Warcraft monsters, I swear to God, anytime I like go up here and then cross from the top.
Okay. I see. I mean it's a ladder in another game. I didn't realize this was here. All right. I made
it. Let me in, child. Let me in. Sorry. Couldn't help it. Who's there? Why don't you keep that
going? That would be hilarious. This person would think that you were a conscious, thought-thinking
raptidon. I ran in here and now the door's locked. Help. You got locked in? Well, I need to get in
that room. I need to get in there, but maybe I'll let you starve first. That's terrible.
Open the door. I'll just go in. Don't worry. I'll get in there. 50. 40. That's a lot. All right. Can
I go up? Do I go up and around? Oh, there's the mag pack. That's what I was looking for.
View executive reviews. Loading last access document. Sandra has a bad habit of padding
his reports with numbers and statistics. Not very good with slogans, jingles, and or taglines.
Presentations tend to be dry and lacking in emotional appeal and funny references.
Like the first 20 minutes of this stream. And it's really pissing people up. Sandra also displays
a noted tendency to complete work rather than delegating at a trend unbecoming in upper management.
All in all, Sandra's work habits suggest a preoccupation with details and a startling
lack of vision. Needs improvement. Okay. Screenshot it. Screenshot it. Hack. Wait. What?
Accessing restricted file. Spoof login credentials. Ooh. Graham's understanding of product messaging
and branding is impressive, especially for a relatively low-level editor. Has a knock,
is a knack for memorable slogans and taglines. However, Graham has issues with brevity and
shows consistent disregard for prescribed fonts and formats. Some of his work has been flagged
for subversive under... What do I care? Just delete all their emails. Fuck it. I don't care.
Oh wait. That was... I was supposed to... I was supposed to do that. Force is...
Well, looks like we're going the black hat route because I just did the thing that the bad guy
just wanted me to do because I was too annoyed to go through the email so I just deleted them.
All right. Well, let's keep going. I'm getting in that room. I know you can hear me talking right
now. I'm coming in that room. I'll be there real soon. 75. Fuck. I gotta go find the rat that ate
him. Seeing as you're trapped, you might as well answer me a few things. We don't... Fuck it. Let's
go get it. Uh, arms key. Mm-hmm. Right. It's in the... It's in the colossus's stomach.
Well, we're safe up here. That was so easy. How did I not be... Why did I say I couldn't do that?
That was simple. That was the easiest fucking enemy in the whole game.
Why did I think that that was scary? I was actually scared of the monster and it's
built into my character's DNA. I could have just got that like 15 minutes ago. God damn it.
I was... I'm going in. Hi.
Uh, normally when you help someone, they give you something for the trouble.
With the trouble you caused me, you're dying here. Normally when you help somebody, you get something.
By being saved by me, you entered into a non-negotiable contract. You now owe me.
Give me something or I'm stuffing you back in here.
Agreed to be saved if I'd known that. All right, here.
Okay. Thank you. 600 bits. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Beat it. You sure you're okay? I don't care.
Beat it. Yes, sir. If Max were here, that would have ended a lot differently.
I learned this in prison! Max is... Oh, wait. Can we do this? Let's do this together. You go over here
and let's talk through the wall together. Whatever. Thing sucks. Let's go. All right,
I did it. All right, I have a criticism of the game. This whole game has... It's almost like I
just got out of a pool. You know, when you look at shit, when you get out of a like a chlorine
filled pool, they have the chlorine pool filter on this whole game. Uh, I have too much stuff.
Security blade. Get rid of it. Break it down. Uh, side is cool. Uh, the Furman. What is that?
I need to look at this stuff. What am I at? 148. What's this dude talking about? I'm talking
about when you when you're in the pool for way too long and you have you have a ton of like wrinkly
ass skin and when you everything has like a haze that you can't get rid of for like 45 minutes.
Have you guys never been in a pool? What? What? You guys don't know the pool eyes?
You did no way. You guys have to know. You have to know this. I'm not going to get I'm not going
to get fucking fibbed on here. Wait, I have options. Let me see. Return the bolt to Sanjar.
Uh, Sanjar leads the MSI so I got to complete the bold quest and maybe he'll like me.
What are you talking about?
You know when you just when things have are so normal to you and you talk about how these
doing these normal ass things and a shitload of people tell you that that is not normal.
If you go into a pool with chlorine in it and you like are going underwater and you're like opening
your eyes underwater you get the like haze around lights and what are you talking about? Don't do
that. That's not what? Why are you opening your eyes in a chlorine pool? No one opens their eyes
in the chlorine pool. What are you talking about? Don't open your eyes. You guys didn't used to try
to see really hard. You'd go underwater and you'd rip your eyes open and be like look around and I
want to be able to see underwater like Aquaman. You guys didn't do that? I know for a fact at
least half of you did. You touch your eyes you like eat oh please don't even give me this like
he's chlorine's getting in the in his blood. You get out of the pool and you like grab the
sandwich and you take a bite out of your ham and cheese sandwich by next to the pool with the
at the cooler with your mom. Well you didn't wash your hands did you? You got chlorine in your mouth
now. You're forever contaminated. Who eats with wet hands? I don't know 10 year olds. You guys were 10
once. You had a sobering effect. Sir please stop. Forgive me Celia. I couldn't help myself.
Anyway what can I do for you? Okay hold on this is important. Pay attention everybody.
Found your view on a terminal in the arms building. I need MSI to stop broadcasting your jamming
devil's peak station. Found the cartridge and deleted that data for you. Look at this smug look.
Hmm I found that cartridge and accidentally deleted that data for you.
Oh yes I'm going to be up all night with this. All those blanks waiting to be filled. Boxes
waiting to be ticked. Try to control yourself sir. Have you any idea how powerful this is?
Corporations have been toppled with less. Oh okay. How exactly is data cartridge going to help? You
made it sound like you were sending me after a weapon. I don't think this will fit in any
of my guns. See Celia he gets it. I told you he would. So you did sir. The world isn't changed
with guns and speeches much as Graham and his followers would like to think but rather with
meticulous documentation. Chlorine. Hey by the way all of you health nuts in the chat right now.
When was the last time you drank water? You know what they put in the water right Chlorine?
If you ever drink water out of the tap you're drinking Chlorine unless you got yourself a
Berkey unit then it clears it out. Use a filter. I do. I use a full Berkey water filtration system.
Pool water and tap water are the same.
You've ingested Chlorine in your life and you know you have.
And you're sitting there now going you're doing the cartoon like Bugs Bunny. You got your nails.
Both your hands are up in your mouth and you're like ear of corn on your nails going wait a minute
he's right. Spare me the details of what comes next. Corporate espionage. How was that Celia?
Did I sell it? Fast delivery yet sir. Do you filter your shower water? No I don't shower.
Wait well you guys you guys shower in 2020. I just wait till it rains and then I go out there
with a bar of soap. That's a true natural way to bathe. It kind of spoils the effect if you
have to ask. Promise me that once I've helped you with this MSI will stop broadcasting.
Yeah you killed it. Celia? Already noted for your review sir. Go into the pool
with a bar of soap. Imagine if you were at like a community pool and you're just sitting there
like with like soap and you're all suds'd up. I'd be like I'm out of here. I'm not going in this pool.
What's what's the plan? I have reason to believe that one of the other corporations is operating
on Monarch illegally and in secret. Those bastards leave us to our perils then come back just to
reap what they can. If we can find proof I can use that as leverage to encourage certain powers
that be to accept our Bolt 52 and reinstate us on the board. Now what does that mean for me? If
someone is operating here then Catherine's almost certainly supplying them out of Fallbrook. Perhaps
she could be convinced to tell you where they are. I remember me and Kim one time went to a community
pool and we walked in and nobody was in the pool. We were like what's going on here? Why is nobody
in the pool? There was a bunch of people there. They're all sitting around the sides and we're
like this is all right cool we got like the we could just go in and Kim went to go in and she
put you know she got it maybe to her shins and there was one of the lifeguards get out out out
oh what's what's going on oh somebody threw up in the pool so they have to shock it it takes like
an hour before anyone can go back in and is it weird for me to say not only do I not want to
go in that pool but I never want to go in that pool ever again is that like somebody threw up
in that pool and it's just mixed in there forever you just don't just dump chemicals in it and then
I got me thinking how many times has this happened because they were very nonchalant about the whole
thing it was just like not not yeah no just an hour or so yeah take about an hour whatever
that happens like five times a day how many times has somebody thrown up in the community pool
or like shitting it or whatever I don't know I don't does that make me does it make me like
a weirdo if I'm not wanting to go in a community pool it's a shitload of chemicals a ton of
chemicals to counteract a ton of puke and pee and shit this probably maybe 40 percent actual
water in that pool the rest is like made of gel with all these chemicals and human pee 99
people pee in pools that's what I'm saying and then people well what about the ocean but the ocean
is huge I feel like diluted human pee in the ocean you know you're talking about like 30
decimal points to the right for a while what actual human pee is in the ocean that pool is
a concentrated small area but as much as I love your can-do attitude and dangerous gravitas would
you rather have those chemicals or brown yellow water if you could leave her in one I don't know
what's worse how you people put it it's both they both suck what is he saying leave her in peace
what the fuck are you talking about of course I didn't mean to make assumptions
once you uh subtly work out whether centrist bring back proof of its operation maybe some nice
leather head you gotta pick you gotta pick pee somebody peeing in the pool versus chemicals in
the pool oh what a fucking centrist how about the pool is just normal I think now this would be
interesting if you had to sign a waiver before you got in the pool that said hey uh if I piss
shit or puke in this pool I have to give everybody else at the pool 20 bucks I yeah I probably sign
it because everybody has to get out of the pool and you like ruin everybody's day if you like
diarrhea in a pool you should have I mean come on like this should be a waiver you signed before you
go to a community pool yes I am not going to throw up in the pool and if I do then I'm going
to pay everybody at the pool their admission fee because then they can't go in the pool that's
what they came there for imagine getting out of the pool to pee yeah we got you motherfucker
now you're gonna yeah you're gonna bet you're gonna give us all five bucks
I bet you won't do it again I bet you'll think twice imagine the look on that person's face
that like ever went through and again it's like we have pee in the pool we have a device that
tells you if somebody peed and like the guy is just in there just sitting there like oh
shit they found me come on get out they go to the ATM they have to take out like
$1,500 in cash and have to walk around and hand it out to every single person I'm sorry about this
I'm sorry I'm pissed in the pool I have a great rest of the day happy Thanksgiving by the way
oh yeah you came here with all your kids yeah they're crying because they can't swim I'm so
sorry here's ten dollars I didn't mean I just had I just pissed in the pool I'm sorry about that
my name's Frank by the way oh the couple here on their honeymoon I'm sorry yeah good to see
I'm really really sorry about ruining your honeymoon and shitting in the pool but I had
to go and it was all free to go I have a happy Thanksgiving that would be fucked all right listen
I gotta pay attention to the video game who pees in the pool here so I can block you do you get
banned for life if you like pissing if you like throw up in a pool do you have to like sign
something how do you get do you get banned for life you don't you throw up in the pool
they wipe it all out they pull you out and then they like close you behind the gates like
you're never allowed back in the kingdom again pool puker psycho don't stop pissing in pools
I am going to oh I am god I got you all now I got you all now I don't care if we've hit it
for another 10 minutes remember when everybody was talking shit to me about peeing in the shower
every there's a lot of people in here that seem to think that peeing in their bathtub is is okay
but increase your bathtub size by a thousand percent and then let a bunch of other people
in your bathtub while you piss in it but that's okay so you so then you piss in the bathtub
and then invite all your friends over and say let's get in let's get in the pool
I got I got fucking people went and people went on me hard for the like pee in the shower bit
and a bunch of you could talk about how you pee in pools I cannot believe it peeing in the shower
is fine peeing in the bathtub is not correct why would you pee in the bathtub you're lying there
just that would be disgusting wouldn't it because you're surrounded by it give me a break I piss in
the pool from the outside well I hope you got arrested because that's crazy listen listen to me
that's crazy right if you were to just piss into a pool from the outside like a giant urinal that
would be the most fucked up thing you could ever do in public in a scenario where you're at the
pool but why is it when you go under the water that it's now okay for you to do the same thing
you're just getting caught in one of those scenarios because no one else sees it yeah that's
that's crazy all right time to reset reset we have he's just been listening to this the whole time
right this is these are the eyes that he's giving me right now these are the I agree with everything
you're saying but I'm not gonna like speak up about what you're saying but keep going keep going
keep doing it see those are the eyes that say keep going go into the lair should I
Sanjay should I go another lair that's like to go on come on you're doing a good thing here
all right rewind reset a foolproof plan if I ever heard one I'll leave the execution to you
really I need MSI to stop broadcasting you're jamming the I found your review on a terminal
in the arms building I asked you to delete it sorry it was open you could have told me what
was on it yeah you sent me into a raptidon infested mess to clean up after you I didn't
mean for any harm to come to you yeah I read the emails my albatross a great shame of my career
I give MSI everything my work my youth my left kidney and for years I was a joke to them your
left kidney oh one of the executives required a transplant he's lucky they didn't want a liver
or a heart I thought volunteering to donate might improve my prospects
God did it apparently not who cares what they think you're in charge now that's what you get
for giving so much of yourself over to a corporation perhaps they were right after all what have I
built stellar bay is barely keeping afloat you're in charge yeah take it easy you've kept the city
running against all odds do you want a medal you're right this place is a garbage heap
take it easy you thought of it that way perhaps there's something to that thank you for that
don't see was there something else did I even say happy thanksgiving I did right I did yeah I lost
all memories when I was talking about people pissing into a pool from the outside that's
where like I lost I got amnesia for like the last 12 hours uh all right uh should I make them stop
broadcasting or should I just say who cares that guy bored me I don't like who cares
okay radio free help the broker deal no I have to do this
complete the quest unseen errors unseen to earn and the size trust the broker can't deliver the
location of the chemicals until you stop msi's transmissions so I have to do it thank you again
for retrieving the bolt it's every bit as complex as I'd heard but I'm up to the challenge anyway
what can I do for you stop broadcasting you think we're the problem have you even heard the
nonsense graham is spewing it isn't easy keeping a town like stellar bay afloat especially without
the board's backing not doing a genocide run has really hurt your reputation as a wacky streamer
you need to reach your trading partners I'll deal with graham right now I'm talking to you
of a situation don't you it's warm in here is anyone else warm what he means to say
the stream just derailed for almost 15 to 20 straight minutes talking about pissing and
shitting into pools on the board is also active on monarch that'll give me all the what's a wacky
strange conversation to you guys is that nor was that that was a normal guy that was a normal
conversation apparently no you have to kill npcs you have to shoot npc then it's wacky
don't worry I'll I'll kill an npc and it'll be super wacky I promise all right if we can
find proof that one of the companies on board is also active on monarch that'll give me all
the leverage I need fair enough I would understand wacky hey anybody here want to get wackified
which one who am I gonna do it to your expectations just got fucking shattered this guy
all right let's go do it error is unseen let's go recover proof of corporate presence on monarch
that's what I'm gonna do save it what I have for ammo give me a workbench it's time to level up
jerma leveling up is not fucking wacky jerma you're supposed to play the game for 40 minutes
and then spawn death claws angry face all right where's uh where's the workbench
did I run past it did I run past a workbench oh shit I didn't mean to do that I forgot like I'm
I'm not allowed to do that out here all right oh shit all right where did I where's the error it is
okay blind blind blind blind blind repair how many parts do I have a pretty good amount of parts
let's tinker this no this no let me look at some of this new shit this is heavy weapons
this is a flamethrower but I have all okay here we go the vermin hammersmith this is a big handgun
we're gonna replace this with yeah this thing sucks this is base 187 dps get this off my bar
tinker 120 is what it goes up to it has knockout already on it 200 dps
213 I'm gonna spend a ton of money on this I'm just gonna upgrade the hell out of it
240 253 273 that's what we're talking about oh this is junk that's what it is I'm not gonna
like fucking sugarcoat this this is junk this one is good 300 do it again 323 do it again
do it again no that's a lot of money no no light machine gun what is it just do it once twice
do it again one more time all right this thing's gonna come off the bar repair let's repair
everything not this because fuck that thing yeah fuck all this stuff now it's time to break down
I have two flamethrowers just break them down I'm not going to use that I'm not going to use the
hammer plasma rifle no sawed-off shotgun no bolt pistol no side it's cool but no light pistol
it's shock no this I'm gonna no all right about for everything else repair it's all repair tinker
modify here we go okay I'm using my like really really like low voice because I'm just not trying
to speak really at all okay what can I do with this so I can do power plasma not plasma
magnum range weapon one magazine increases the amount of am
munition the weapons magazine carries 50 magazine size that's pretty huge
zap zap or what's in there now I think I'm gonna do I think I'm gonna do zap
yeah that's not a bad idea makes it shock damage it's in can I have more than one
no that's the barrel I need a barrel modification shit all right what's in there now mag two power
exacto site extendo site or the exacto site 25 more range versus what's on the
oh chats board what are you going to do about it scream at them tell them to settle down
talk about pools something wacky you have to be a wacky streamer
now I'm trying to figure out if this game's good all right I'm trying to figure it out it's tough
no I'm not doing anything wacky we need organic wacky not manufactured wacky I only work on
organic wackiness okay I don't want the store bought wackiness I want it to be organic from
the source gluten-free all right I've leveled up there how what are for ammo nice all right so
that's poison fire these things are better damage get this out of here what should I replace this
with flamethrower shock cannon maybe just keep this with poison yeah I'll just keep it with
poison just in case I have some kind of issue with it I only have 197 shots let's get some ammo
wacky fucking wacky all right I need where I need a vendor vendor like you
and will you guys stop huffing and puffing so much you're at like Thanksgiving dinner right now
you're gonna upset your whole family that's how you got me on you got me on a speaker I'm at the
dinner table like we were saying before it's just silent just quiet nobody's talking there's like
15 people at your dinner everyone just you just hear like the clang of
of plates and knives no one's talking after about 10 straight minutes of me just doing this of me
playing the game and not doing anything is it uncle fucking roger just says that's it he hasn't
done anything wacky turn him off and then it's like everyone let's go there they're utensils
oh he's right and then you chime in yeah sorry I thought he's gonna be funny today
and mom chimes in I'm so sorry everyone's dinner is ruined and then dad chimes in I wasn't a fan
of his from the very beginning and you brought him into my home and then after a few more pieces
of deliberation of talking about how unfunny I am you come together as a family yeah he is
sucks he's not funny at all I know he's small too and then everybody at the dinner table is like
yeah that was a good one that was good and he's streaming on thanksgiving like grandpa's like
yeah and also and grandpa like grabs his chest and everyone's like whoa and then grandpa goes
I just jebaited everybody and then you just turn me off and you enjoy your thanksgiving
and you all come together and everybody is so happy and it was because of me
so I'm okay with this I'm fine with that I actually prefer it I didn't realize my
face cam was on what are you talking about what the fuck are you talking about
what
I'm bringing families together this thanksgiving all right I can just teleport here so what are
these both for let's just go here UDL lab oh the research the research oh this weapon is sick
let's rewind a day when I said that handgun sucked that was not true okay here we go
research I think I'm gonna need uh something up there he saw the ladder
pepehands finally the marauder ringleader
oh you're bigger than I thought is there somebody next to me
there is somebody next to me burning me wacky thanksgiving oh how exhausting would a wacky
thanksgiving be if you had to go to like uncle jeremy's and it was like just themed with the
party balloons and everything was wacky and it was like jokes and shit you'd probably be exhausted
all right I got the key I really don't want to go to uncle jeremy's for thanksgiving he does this
like he's just he does this annoying shit can I just go with my friends we all have to like
pretend to laugh while he does like his routine research data okay uh rich sulfur pockets made
monarch a prime site for testing and experimentation early results show promise but further research is
necessary UDL this avows all knowledge of and responsibility for lorem ipsum all data in this
report is considered proprietary knowledge of UDL recorded it what who's Katherine who is Katherine
I don't know uh all right cool messages screenshot that one login oh if Valdez wants a better title
see how she likes these she's going to be furious if she ever finds this list and I'm not covering
for you make sure these are good and hidden eggs mayhem thunder dog skunk parade fuck you Valdez
and I want my raise all right all right I gotta start deleting the shit I gotta break um what am
I 154 what do I don't need okay this is this is completely broken okay 24 armor parts I was at
one all right I could have so much more armor he's got a wacky mascot all right so I got
this return to sand jar with the data cartridge let's go still can't run I didn't destroy anything
uh I want to break down something heavy uh this thing's pretty damn heavy how many playing I
got a guy got two plane throwers who gives them all right bathroom cool terminals cool
energy cells fast travel back we've completed our quest no copypasta no copypasta fuck you hey
that's not very nice I did it you should know you're getting excellent reviews from across
the company can I do for you I have found a data cartridge with details excellent timing
on your fingers to nubs but I finally completed the bolt 52 form I dare say it will be my second
greatest achievement after the reformations you're getting ahead of yourself again so I am
do you have this cartridge what hold on what the hell did you do to me
he's scared that's what I would look like if I put on a bunch of prosthetic turn the facecam
off I did I know I was like pissing everybody off with my facecam all right give him the data
not so fast oh what are these reformations you're talking about oh what are you going
to reformat everyone's files oh did I say I had data cartridge that's just what I call my left
nut that seems unnecessarily complicated it's actually very funny thank you now I'm confused
do you have evidence against UDL or not oh all right here you go I knew there was something
going on this is exactly the proof we need the board will have to welcome us back now
I'll transmit this data along with the completed bolt 52 right away cool sit back and quietly wait
MSI elite armor no more broadcast from us
now we've just got to deal with the iconoclasts believe me you've got your work cut out for you
there did I just get a motherboard else I feel like that's the name of one of the mother MSI
elite gaming armor edition all right let me see what that is all right buddy I have 117 lying I
don't need to go more than that I'm lying I mean I'm I'm overlying handguns all right I
got this new cool handgun get it to 60 armor penetration is up and then let's do a little
bit more into hacking lockpicking yeah new perk okay uh carrying capacity dialogue skills
interactable highlight range what's that mean consumable weight consumable okay shut up
50 less weight okay uh what do I want to do fast travel wow no that's stupid you just this perk
is I think the that just should delete it and replace it with anything else it's so easy just
to break down anything to just be able to fast travel and sell everything why would you ever
use this this is 100 useless turn off the face cam not staying on uh science weapon this is not
this is not bad six bit movement penalty to accuracy that's not that's pretty good too
I'll do this one all right you guys have points too tier three companion ability damage
now swaps weapons and reloads faster when Ellie is in the party any damage that would kill you
instead heals a small amount of health yeah okay plus 20 damage to creatures yeah and let's get
you something better these weapons are terrible I need to get you in something better actually you
yeah you that's actually better whatever wait now I can't die I mean maybe not immediately
okay so now um you found a way to end MSI's transmissions I did gram okay I gotta sell
or break down let's break down let me take a look at my armor because
I'm very killable right now where's my MSI elite motherboard there it is I mean look at this thing
it's an MSI elite gamer board I why would I take this off skeletal adrenal simulator
geographic scanner plus five all skills you're no longer the dentist you're now the dentist's
chair I'm okay with that that fits into the lore what is this 38 this is so much better now I'm
not gonna die instantly it came with a helmet it did where's the where's the MSI elite helmet
it's not this is it no this is quite the dentist's chair I don't think I want to sit
in a like robot's lap to again lie back on the robot's body to go to I don't think I'm gonna do
that all right where's the where's the MS MSI elite look at that now I'm a real elite gaming
chair weapons range weapon spread minus 10 percent how would I put this on inspiration
lying one-handed melee is there a one-handed uh stealth skills block tech skills block
lockpick plus five long guns plus seven that's really good perception engineering
I'll keep it on for now my chat why's my chat not loading um I don't know that's weird I didn't
even delete anything all right it's time to get rid of um well I have something heavy ass shit
that I want to get rid of okay let's help with this one this thing's heavy just junk it break it
down uh get rid of this get rid of the goggles no the goggles fine this is a one pound what do I
have this taking up so much weight am I just holding up into the creams what's the heaviest
thing I have and why do I have so many heavy ass things okay it's these plasma launcher
I'm not going to use this the scythe I'm not going to use it it's cool but I'm not going to use it
this pistol not going to use it okay now we're doing all right sort by weight sort by weight
this thing's five pounds sort by weight oh I have much like raptor meat all right just fucking
get rid of it wait base health plus 25 percent two minutes eat one just I don't care eat them all
eat a bag of flour too meat and flour what a good diet all right I'm good let's go
let's go back to graham and tell them all the news
jerma read this message are you okay I'm fine all right amber heights if you can't read chat then
you can't read my messages once per stream on average so why am I even here what just like me
what a great adversary
I'm on I'm on your side just so you know all right what do we got free flour
no just stop picking I'm not even eating this stuff I'm just hoarding what are you playing
monopoly cool I don't smoke why am I picking I'm just a weirdo I pick up everything okay save it
here yeah we fell dead mine we lost two runners and five gunheads a total failure then who's where
the banoids are they never showed I'm sure they're ah let's talk later it seems we have a stranger
oh this is the guy that was speaking into the teleprompter if you're looking for a teacher
I am one welcome to the iconoclasts what do you teach I'm told you're out of pamphlets that's
a shame this is amber heights I expected more alters or incense or both I just need you to
stop using devil's peak let's get right out to it and just jump right on the issue at hand
stop no spreading the truth is the only way to combat the board's poisonous campaign of
propaganda against their people your broadcasts aren't working nobody's listening
you know the board is going to let its citizens listen to your propaganda
and nobody's listening to your broadcasts I realize the board has blockaded our efforts but
devil's peak is an interplanetary radio tower surely somebody is listening
no surely sorry uh you're only transmitting on a single radio frequency and very few people
can actually receive it this is not even a lie this is a science I'm just telling this guy the
truth gram we should be focusing on survival anyway food ammo and medicine maybe now is the
time to pivot pivot if radio isn't working we might try another way it seems the captain's
time let me try another way serendipitous it must be fate I've had my sights on an old printing
press for some time the board uses magazines and advertisements to subtly focus the colony's
is to use app no those are all things you should not ever be doing that's all terrible advice
don't do that bucket of a radio tower hey here's how you get his attention do all these things that
like you shouldn't be doing and do them all in a row what no don't do those things help me clear
out and repair the press and I'll have no need for that rust bucket of a tower um that's too
much work I'll just kill you now and be done with it if you want to get his attention just
use the fish emoji that's that's cool that's pretty true that's pretty close hold on you're
saying you want to print propaganda in their magazines actually have better reach people read
that stuff all over the system even in Byzantium you see citizens of halcyon are glued to their
periodicals even I find myself occasionally distracted by their fish propaganda quality
of editing and unacceptable disregard for grammatical structure my literary prowess
will hook them and the eternal truth will reel them in what's into me I'm starting to sound like
one of Sanjar's fishermen wait what do you say well my oh you said I I comprehended what you
just said cool entirely all right I'll help uh you're starting to sound like a bitter writer
all right fine wonderful I requisitioned replacement rollers for it some time ago
Huxley should have delivered them yesterday speaking of which where is Huxley uh well sir
they'll be dead in about 10 minutes when uh germo wacky 985 Albertson takes care of them and brings
a ring back to prove that they existed Huxley's still recovering he won't be up for a run for a
while seems we're out a runner if you intend to help our cause I'll ask you to meet our MSI
supplier in her stead yeah it's called spread out 10 give 10 support to everybody and then
now everybody everybody I'm just playing every single field oh you get 10 support and you get
10 support you get 10 support you literally know I'm just collecting bits I'm just collecting bits
the whole time my master plan oh the runner from the northern ruins I helped her get out of there
wait isn't she dead wait where's the supplier meets us in the ruins of bayside terrace from
our compound follow the road north I'm a mercenary I'm a mercenary for hire people are just making me
do tasks so you're her mysterious savior she sings your praises no I want you to sing my praises no
I'm a mercenary eager to learn so bright-eyed so tone deaf all right I'll be back wonderful
while you're at it I wonder if Carlotta still has those high capacity cartridges grab a few
will you there should be some funds left over from the last shipment I want one of your pens
we can use them to copy and modify radio serials no I won't do it I want one of your pens not just
magazines but their precious dramas unbelievable give me one of those I hope I don't have to tell
you this but if there is extra money would you mind buying I don't know food and medicine
Graham if you need me I'll be in triage when we get high capacity cartridges or extra supplies
for how much what do you what else do you need anybody would anybody like a coffee
what do you want just all right just text me the order of the entire village
and I'll it's gonna be a pain in the ass but I'm gonna have to get like three trays
my god I'm taking these I don't care don't look fine the commuter wait this is a faction quest
fine fine fine I'll show you guys that I'm not just a dentist for hire I'm much more than that
dentist the centrist that's supposed to be like Dennis the menace
you stop being a dentist the second you became a gamer chair
wait a minute I hear something oh I like that revolver reload animation
dentist no wouldn't the sam the robot be the dentist chair I'm just taking the place of the
robot is there a reason why every video game that's one of these open kind of RPGs takes place
at some point where we've only developed our media to be 1940s jingles it's like this weird
look it's like the 1940s but it's not it's like 2000 it's like 4000 ad I don't I mean I guess it's
cool but why is it every why does it always have to just be like hey we're singing jingles like
the 30s they would have not developed media past there's like old ass tv shit all right who's
expired copyright all right we're good that's 340 fucking damage it's only open public domain
media you still have to make the song it follows that same formula of like high octave singing
quickly about a product now you can say what about McDonald's they do like bada bada that's
not the same if it was if that was true it would be like McDonald's McDonald's they're delicious
burgers McDonald's happy clowns that would be more in line what it was they all follow that same
formula okay the wrong way am I dumb what's going on here oh it's sealed why is it sealed
can I sneak no you almost died don't ever stand in the way but this area is off limits
what are you stupid don't just stand that's my nice way of telling you to saw it off okay I'll
leave fuck off give me the sniper wow I just got a headshot let me see your head don't no don't
blame me blame the blame your doorman this wouldn't happen a little bit of customer service would have
prevented all of this okay you in here don't worry don't worry ma'am we took care of it
the intruders are dead open the door a lot of dead folk out here I'm guessing there was a tragic
accident yeah well I happen to be a guy that you know I'm just doing yeah that's Homer Simpson I
can stop I'm Junko Graham sent me to collect supplies just your friendly neighborhood iconic
class doesn't matter who I am here to pick up Graham's supplies Graham sent me do it no do it
uh hello thanks for clearing out those goons please don't kill me next you asked real nice
rollers and what's right I want for a printing press here take them like I said this is my last
run why have you been helping Graham it's an enviable thing he's doing free people and all
that I can't live that way I need my structure but I respect the iconoclasts for doing it
do you remember please kill a person I just killed like 10 people
and the guy at the front door who just told me to leave you just you just want me to kill this
person no I don't have a reason to kill this person I am a honorable that an honorable person
that does dishonorable things that's what it says on my dnd character sheet you'd have to ask him
all I know is that if I get caught I'll get arrested where would they get the supplies now
law help them I don't know maybe sublight can lend a hand I should go look Graham's got a bit or
two left in his account I can send one last drop now what would that actually put me at so what do
you want delivered okay so I I do what I want and I do the things that I want to do I do I'm
dishonorable but I do honorable things but I still look both ways when I cross the street
right uh that makes me a coward what do you mean a coward to what that's a sensible
a centrist dentist coward all right grant uh I need we get any extra food I always took that
woman for the sensible type see good on her I'll send them along give them all my regards
and delivering delivering the extra food and supplies to the people that are in need at that
village but then headshotting this person before they leave the room that never mind that makes
me a you know I've I brought the supplies back all right don't just take everything all right
this is a big one this makes you an idiot music box revolver mk2 troop helmet wooden parts
adreno did you guys want some of this too bad it's mine jeremy jeremy jeremy jeremy
you can't jeremy what I'm sorry I just you can't just take everything I'm fine
god I'm not gonna use it anyway okay where we going the commuter bring the needed parts back
to graham at amber heights I'm in I'm encumbered to get rid of this uh whatever what I 162 break
it down millionaire streamer steals from the needy no gives food to people in the community
and then takes everything from the person's house that they were just in but I'm not bringing that
stuff to the community I'm bringing the food to the community that the good thing and then I'm
just taking everything from this person's house holy shit that's kind of good that's really
good I'm not I'm never gonna use this stuff I'm really not it's just the truth it's just the
truth and you all know it yeah you all know it I know it you know it everybody does two-handed
melee and just no one's gonna use this restricted area requires ID I don't know shit yes you do
don't ever think that there's definitely something that you know more of than I do
come on I mean it is pretty rare but you might know something a little more than me
ego ego his ego is inflating pop that fucking ego balloon quick all right let's go deliver the
supplies hey hey on the pool thing what if you get diarrhea poisoned in the pool do you still have
to pay what do you mean you maybe somebody like poisoned you I'm telling you the van we're like
20 30 minutes away from that bullshit graham they don't just abandon orders and they weren't at the
ruins where in this sulfur sodden hellhole did you send them they're on a very important
ah we'll continue this later welcome back captain got your rollers the rest of your account went to
food and medicine thank the eternal that someone's got some sense in their head thank you Carlotta
usually schedules the next drop during the meeting when's she coming well we've got bad news
Sanjar has made it illegal to sell to you guys I don't know I just I don't know it's
terrible in the safe but I'm just messenger supply lines on monarch Sanja are all about to cross a
dangerous line about to that idiot just declared war hold on I we will deal with his subversion
wait hold on a minute for now we must redouble our efforts to spread the truth to the colony
uh what's next I've already sent a team ahead to scout the press one of our best meet them there
and find out if they've been successful you sent the van noise there didn't you oh for fuck's sake
graham we needed them in the ruins our people died out there they weren't willing to fight for
our cause so we need reinforcements we need new recruits the van noise saw the printing facility
with the same importance as I tried to repair the hell's the sense in recruiting if you're just
gonna get them killed I have to repair the press I have the utmost confidence in there I just want
to make sure I'm clear on what I have to do friends we must have faith that the men and women we
recruit can handle the duties for which we recruit them spreading the word has to be priority number
one otherwise how can this movement grow you could have sent them after backing Zora up right
you to ever stop this is worth bickering over the iconoclasts can't keep their heads in the
ground forever or they're going to starve and die slow look just if the van noise are still alive
get them out of there with sanjar pressing the issue like this I have a feeling we'll need them
the printing press comes first no promises the printing press comes first retrieve Zora's team
and repair the printing press you got it how you liking that new model of the leapfrog
1200 you're learning your math okay I'll let you go to it am I still over-encumbered who are you
hold on I don't know what the fuck is happening something hurts oh I don't know I can't I'm just
coming over here why the fuck what are you well what are you putting in chat fishes cool that's
cool I kind of like those all right um let's have a set throwing stuff in the trash
I have so much junk all right this you know this reminds me of I feel like I've been deleting a
bunch of stuff but it's still so you ever cleaned out your hard drive before and you're like how do
I only have like four gigs left on a 500 gig drive and you go through and you do everything and you
delete shit you don't need and don't want but somehow you've only recovered like five gigs
and you're like this is not even fucking possible how where's this stuff coming from
five ten fifteen twenty twenty third is it the bananas it's like all this stuff all these apples
and cranberries and all right I'm getting rid of it all right all right I'm getting rid of it okay
I got rid of it let's do it pay for the printer I can't wait to go get printer ink that was a
whole lot of look at how ridiculous and how this conflict for go get printer ink from Walmart
good thing I can just fast travel oh shit look out hi august van noi may van noi the van noi twins
neoka you're a sight right now I'll tell you what we are up a creek I bet you really come this far
north for a printing press yeah I know I know that's the mission don't suppose y'all are busy
right now oh I'm here to secure the press if you guys are going after the press then
yeah I'm here to help thanks but I ain't sure the mission is worth it keep spewing that sulfur I'm
liable to leave you to the wraps what my well-meaning idiot of a brother intends to say is
we appreciate the assist you're assisting me let's get something clear I'll take it from here
would that we could we ain't leaving our men behind and they ain't moving on their own
our medic has got our trauma kit but we got separated we ain't seen him in a couple of hours
oh my professional medical advice is to get out of here as soon as possible
good advice might kill him but rats definitely will good advice good dental advice
went into that word of wisdom sorry did you just talk shit to the dentists
about our medical background need to find our medics so we can do exactly as you say
get the hell out I don't have time to play doctor here you're on your own you don't
no I don't have time to play doctor because I ain't one one two three four five shots
help help help help I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'll find your friend
just kidding how about your friend printing press medic oh that's a big one that's a big one I need
my help over here are we ready and close in on three two one go what happened all this to save
this all right all right watch it watch it watch it watch it where is it where is it where is it
oh there's two of these motherfuckers over here ah this poison good thing I'm a gamer chair
I just knocked him out what holy shit kill him kill him quick progress repeated encounters with
raptidons has lessened your effectiveness when they're attacking I'm scared of other monsters
except I'm just scared of monsters two different kinds of monsters all right consumable weight
this is the one I'm doing all right that's pretty great all right all right all right all right all
right all right what happened to you medic all right I'm just gonna give it a I'm gonna give her
a wake-up shot oh you're dead you're actually dead oh no oh no you're actually dead euthanasia kit
what the fuck is that where is that where is that it's a weapon what the fuck is this thing
oh I thought it was a like you'd stick yourself with like a syringe or something
this is a long gun 392 oh man let me check this out it's a shotgun nice all right we're
gonna replace this with the I'm never gonna use the melee for any reason let's try it all right
here uh your friend is dead sorry I don't know what to tell you any luck out there today uh uh
oh fuck well that's better than nothing trauma kit thanks oh wait wait was that the weapon
no no that's the euthanasia kit sorry okay yeah you can have the trauma kit I want to
keep the euthanasia kit thanks for the assist you're welcome okay bye it was fun let's get
that printing printer light assault rifle mk2 ammo ammo bits whatever this is okay we've got some
monsters but oh tinker here we go let's make this thing much hello uh anybody hear me
that is weird what the fuck okay hi uh we're back what happened I I have no idea my internet
just started going crazy and then it turned off but it didn't it was still it was still on
but I don't know it's working now so that's that's all we care about uh welcome back it's working
now that's all it matters drama I tuned into the stream and it was off and people were saying
f and so I think it was my fault it was not I'm telling you right now it's not your fault
all right well uh let's keep going I'm here you're here we're in here all right what was
I doing oh yeah we were all right we declared this place out open this door all right there's
aliens in here that's my opinion on corn I can't eat it right now so I don't have an opinion on
corn I used to have an opinion on corn all right hold on wait wait wait wait I don't want to die
shooting through the wall oh reload the gun reload the gun please dude I mean the debilitator
is kind of good but it's not that good how many of them are there in here all right you upgraded
it like 80 times not that many so let's go in here go go go go go there it is all right the
printer right uh it was never going to be that easy was it nope I can't just open a door I have
to go all the way around don't fight them he's doing morse code that means help me my internet
sucks all right let's do uh terry's birthday happy birthday terry we're leaving
hope to see you maybe sometime soon here's this uh defense logistics cool happy birthday
terry happy birthday there we are wait can't open it install rollers it is now repaired
you've lost printing press who's running in here are they mad that I've repaired the printer
why that was the noise what do you do 20 testing why is there testing one two three in the chat
testing one testing two testing five all right the printing press is operational return to
graham with an update I'm here graham okay let's teleport back to amber heights spider-man update
there was a whole new spider-man game too it was a very good spider-man game I should have done
an update I didn't damn it I'm gonna have to wait for the next one listen no no more listening
no more preaching we are losing people left and right we need to act enough zora I'm not putting
the torch to innocent people do you want to bring the board's cruisers and gunships down on us
captain apologies but our situation grows dire our people talk of foolish endeavors what news do
you bring hey uh I fixed it excellent did you find the viennese I did yes they are
are they on their way back thank the eternal maybe one step closer to bringing the truth to every
man woman and child in halcyon this plan's brilliance is in its subtlety for the time
being let us cease our activities on the tower lest we bring premature attention upon us
I have much to do articles to write sermons to ponder we live in such an exciting time
all right let's go back to the information broker hey I need to see to the wounded but
drop by the clinic when you can I want a word I won't this is the last time either one of you
are going to see me I'm just being honest with you I'm just being real I want this to get to 40
now I can open most doors and I'm going to put some more points into handguns
nice nice job nice all right bye oh he's done streaming he's leaving all right bye you won't
see me again well let's hope the internet lasts otherwise you actually won't see me again for like
four days and hope it stays on back to devil's peak yeah I was talking about I don't even know
how many uh what was the last thing you heard me say before the internet before it actually turned
off I was talking about all the people on thanksgiving after eating like their dinner
they're just on something about peeing no no no like the last thing you heard me say
before everything turned it turned off you couldn't hear anything it was your tears
no that's not the last thing I said you said god I hate streaming it was don't be a fool
who was I talking about don't be a fool don't be a fool all right where's the I have to go upstairs
wait don't be a fool holy shit look at all the stuff in here damn there's a lot of cool stuff
elite troop armor I think I already had this I did examine don't be a fool would be some great
last words don't be a fool can I sell through these yet do I have enough do I have enough
so yeah sell the junk there we go is that good enough it is all right let me up let me up
did I go up what oh that's not to go up that's just to open the elevator oops I didn't want
to shoot you how do I go up this guy is in such a dumb place why can't you just meet me at the
front door don't be a fool it's the blessed sound of radio silence which leads me to believe you
have sweet sweet news for me I do MSI and the iconoclast are no longer transmitting is the data
ready yes indeed I am back in business but before we get down to it might I ask how you handled
the problem none of your business does it matter job's done thank you I couldn't have said it better
myself I hope to both MSI and the iconoclast get what they wanted you're an information broker if
I want if you want to know it'll cost you oh I believe it will the price I pay won't be to you
no we've a bigger deal to settle I don't doubt that you are working with Phineas but my contract
specifies I relay any acquired information to the purchaser and to the purchaser alone
however if you send the data I will need your assistance in cycling the antennas
everyone always needs you to do something like okay how do you hook up with you
tell me how to fix it and I bet I have a whole new checklist of crap to do before it works right
do it yourself first I never leave the tower no exceptions well you will be in a body bag
in about 10 minutes you don't do here to key in the sequence to the tower system when it resets
or the calibration will fail normally I'd beg Neoka to do the honors but it appears she's
following your lead now it's simple truly I merely need you to waltz outside and throw
the lever to cycle the power I'll key in the numerical adjustments if that is not what I
have to do if that's not it then this guy's gonna die just press the lever outside that's it someone
has trust issues though I can't hardly feign surprise yes that is all no I am not mocking you
much just step outside lock the door on me the switch depart forever understood good marvelous
we're in agreement this is why I stopped helping out I'm gonna close the door and lock it it's
always throw this lever shoot that marauder save my life just one thing after another with you
don't burst a blood vessel I'll give whatever terrific I'll be here waiting with bated breath
give a shout if the panel electrocutes you it's hard to not do it all right just press the button
you don't know that I have time travel mechanics see right now I just put a time travel spot right
here because if you close the door and lock it on me I'm just gonna time travel back and kill you
all right let's see what happens here that's cheating that's not cheating that's holding
your hand in the choose your own adventure book with your finger in between the pages
testing one check check but that's it I was gonna start saying all kinds of
fucked up stuff oh and I also dispatched Vinny as his data it'll make me come back in there
there's no need to assert your dominance I doubt I could make you do anything you don't wish
look I am well aware that at times I may have the tiniest iota of a prickly exterior
but I must admit I have grown rather fond of you as Neoka can attest I do not form attachments
do take care why he told us to leave without flinging insults at our purses
he really does like you captain well I don't like him we blasted hell is that told you no
somebody just like somebody just crashed what was that whose ship was that
it's one of the board's blockade oh whatever oh maybe they'll be all right I agree
they're like invading each other's channels
10 over here 10 over here 10 over here everybody gets some time on the radio
you can't hog the game oh it's a reunion
uh you're acting like children
half of the course really while you still could use its targeting module
imagine turning on the radio and hearing this
private channel guys can I say something over the internet broadcast we did it I did it see
where the ship looks I don't care captain hi return time is within 14 percent of the expected
I want to talk to Phineas
it's the first time I've been here too this is new area new content
all right let's go back to the original dentist crew
hello can you hear me does this work damn it blasted I'm just securing my ongoing experiments
get off the radio you're on the same wavelength
visitors since in fact I've never had a visitor I have now
shrink ray science weapons are unique weapons that have strange and powerful
effects science weapon damage and the strength of their effects both increases your science skill
increases did they get a funny voice that's all I care about max you know what to do
remind the wall of bulletproof glass I don't know how you did it
but Hiram Blythe just sent me everything I needed nice I did it according to Hiram's message
minister Clark has ordered a suspended time of scarcity once I have those chemicals we can
revive the hopes colonists and put some decent people in charge so good news you're going to
seriously those chemicals exciting okay what's so important about these chemicals
that is the reason you're essential to reviving the hopes colonists okay I need you to steal as
much as you possibly can imagine getting along better will stop the board from destroying this
colony all right so what's the plan ah yes the detail I'm not about to ask you to rampage
through presenting bullets with the board's agents we'll have to resort to subterfuge
thankfully I don't have to drop ten thousand dollars to get it find Carmen
steel chemicals got it you're lucky you behind the glass tested if it's bulletproof
I know it's bulletproof turn the shrink ray on yourself
you can't do that I will try it though I mean it's like a funny laugh out loud weapon right
how many what is it 1300 ammo yes there what happened
what is going on
stop stop it
no I don't I'm about to walk by a companion quest no I don't fine since when Byzantium there's
something I've been meaning to do no we're not doing it anything else
you know I'm in a bad mood today you got in my way and you're trying to talk to me
really I think we I think I think we should part ways let's go never mind dentists this is
further than I got in the game good night well see you later hope you have fun with the rest of the
game massive spoiler coming up this is the part of the game when Phineas actually rips off a
rubber mask and he's the bad guy the whole time hey Carmen do you mind I'm needing someone
I'm sorry we're gonna have to part ways uh what a coincidence me too I oh oh you mean I'm supposed
to be meeting you all right let's keep this moving yeah you're looking to make contact with minister
magpie right I guess it won't be easy he spends most of his time in this estate which is heavily
guarded so has it got to be a way to catch the minister someplace less protected can you get me
into the minister's estate how exactly did you get involved in all this there's got to be a way
to catch him somewhere afraid not he almost never leaves his home and his guards never leave him
can you get me in there whoa I'm not one of your bne specialists I just provide intelligence
vulgar eater birds are kind of my specialty code names too but I can give you some information
some of the guards hang around Billingsley's house of inebriation between shifts
okay so they get drunk maybe you could do some reconnaissance there you know swipe a key while
nobody's looking a booger and a booger and eating specialist thanks for the tip just remember you
didn't hear it from me okay it's just me is there everything and everything feel big out here
you don't feel this I didn't even do anything I just made you small for a second I mean that
would have probably hurt a lot it would have like crushed all your bones then why does it not last
that long how much can you shrink them what's this look for contact cuckoo don't mention
Phineas by name tell cuckoo minister Clark is at his estate under heavy guard that
there's something else you're supposed to tell cuckoo oh well you'll remember it when you talk
you've got this golden eagle will you call me cuckoo I miss her look I had to test the shrink
ray the at least one npc was killed that was unintentional though that was I wanted to test
the shrink ray I didn't know it was gonna make people hostile and run away all right let's go
to the let's go to the minister's guard do you think I'm cuckoo I could spend hours reflecting
on the secret working so tell me not your cuckoo long elevator ride something exciting happened
here for once nothing wrong with stability it means everything's running like clockwork
don't you ever want a little maybe see a marauder ship get blown to bits overhead
what a thing I got content for you I can't jump I was gonna jump over okay get away from get away
from me get away from me yeah kid you got presence natural magnetism know what I mean
hmm where this is going what you're gonna like once we start talking bits all right listen then
you got an agent some kind of representation you got an agent except that representation
why are you talking like me I'm freelance fresh natural talent I know it when I see it listen
you got a real special quality raw energy I see you in pictures kid ah the favored mindless
entertainment of the unwashed masses hey thousands of viewers and millions of bits
can't be wrong what are you offering I'm making a feature space pirates of moros prime I get to be
in a movie but we still need a star and I think you got the chops I'll do it no job is too great
too grueling or too gruesome for a Sam he's not talking to you model there might want to lease him
for a Macbeth production no no I'm the one that I'm the one what do you say let's do it ready for
the chance of a lifetime yes terrific we're holding auditions at the studio head to Odeon
pictures and take the elevator yeah all the way to the top baby yeah finally uh finally a fun mission
let's go FPS city all cleaning jobs have been in FPS city be a fool I'd have to request a
counter waiver and you know how dreadful the paperwork is don't I ever my dear fellow why
I spent three hours filing a discussion authorization just to commence our little
test how we suffer in the name of commerce no I don't know what accent this is but it's in every
single thing that is referencing older potentially wealthy people what is that accent oh my dear boy
this is not English or American it's something strange in between it's as if you took a record
and held your finger on it while you try to play it back normally it's the monopoly man accent
that's a warped there's a warped record it's about that accent is the mid-atlantic accent
it's a cultivated accent of English blending together prestigious American and British English
ways of speaking adopted in the early 20th century by mostly by American aristocrats and actors
there's not native vernacular or regional American accent wait they were doing that on purpose
that's a fake accent really it was Americans larping as British
so that was just Americans doing a poor bad British accent role-playing
wow all right let's go time for my audition British people do it too what why do British
pretend to have a British accent wait hold on what why do okay got it you should know I drank
a lot of water before coming in here about to piss in a pool what wait I have to I don't think
that's a good idea I don't even what's the what's my motivation wait this is the scene um I don't
even know I don't know what movie I'm in hold on I leveled up medical and you know let's just dump
it all in tier three big damage while under 25% health headshot kills still 25% of the damage
to enemies within 2.5 meters damn you can attack after killing an enemy your next attack that's
killing is a gap I don't even need to see the other ones all right you guys have some levels
up to do charges should I give him the funny weapon ability damage yeah I want you that
ability is just powerful let's see damage to auto mechanicals chance to resist ability cooldown
on ability use ability damage swap reload and weapon swap let's just make you a beast
okay uh it's time for me to be an actor I'm supposed to be natural okay I'm gonna bad just
act natural you call these crates we need at least twice as many and grungier as grungy
as you can get this supposed to be an authentic space adventure and real space adventurers have
crates the next time I see the set there better be loads and loads of fucking crates or you are
fucking fired all right um I'm here for my audition I'm just gonna take everything off the set
and leave all right I think I'm ready ready here to stop us at last captain steel
you're too late all of this settlement cnp hungry time food pills same nutritional valley but now
with added filler are ours with their patented stomach stuffing effects and baseline vitamin
content we will be nigh unstoppable jokes on you idiot those crates are just decoys you foul pirate
I won't let you get away with this whatever as long as you stop monologuing how did cnp manage
to fit more in something so tiny they're geniuses jokes on you idiot those crates are just decoys
they they are what an unexpected twist you may have fooled me for now but not for long
which side is my good side do you remember the last time we faced each other out of character
come on staring one another down across the void of space while flaming debris felt like rain
around us the thing you just described are scientifically impossible hey I didn't write
this just go with it I had you surrounded and outgunned but you overcame my superior numbers
with tactical thinking and a hammersmith limited edition grenade launcher yeah I've been waiting
five years now and at last my day for vengeance has come you've ran like a coward then you'll run
now if you know what's good for you is this where is this where we're dumping backstory because
that should come up earlier um when is that day you ran like a coward now you'll run now if you
know what's good for you I just got chills but still you'll not stop me now I have this whole
port wired with some micro energon transistors once we're away I'll activate the gamma particulate
field and the quantum chronic chain reaction will turn this whole place into vaporized plasma
ah most of those words are made up and the ones that are real don't work like that
the script is awful and I spent three hours learning how to pronounce them terrible writing
I hope you've paid your burial fees and signed your personal death and dismemberment waivers
because this is the end for you be careful well finally a hundred intimidated no it's the end of
you let's see you try never mind I think that's seen to the break room everyone I need my moap
fizzy tea wait what no that's my guy turn those cameras off oh hey look at me run to the green
what do I do why does wait why is that person so what happened wait did I ruin the quest
oh how long ago is this choose attack in dialogue there it is all right rewind reset back to one
back to everyone back to places well well they are what exposure to germicidal fumes kills
brain cells do you remember the last time we why is he talking for me the battle of axa jacks
stare science yeah uh excuse me you run like a coward uh excuse me uh most of the things
you said are made up I'm smart I let's see you try oh he was behind the door there's my star
walk and talk with me are we gonna walk that was brilliant stuff do you write your own material
mm-hmm you bet amazing just firm up that jawline and you'll be a triple threat
I'm gonna have to fire the writing staff what do those anemic fuckwits know about dialogue anyway
I'm thinking a whole new script more pirates bigger explosions you flicking a stogie slim
into a barrel of gasoline marketing says that kind of action sells tickets here this is for
your work today I'll be in touch once we get that script how much 17 000 xp and reputation with the
board and 1100 bucks low budget all right cool so now I can keep doing that good uh all right
now that Phineas knows minister Clark's been hoarding dimethyl sulfoxide speak to the minister
oh no the minister's guards right ciao got you all right where we going down I gotta go down
there how do I get out of here oh the elevator no hello funny shot person
actually like gives me chills listening to that
what's wrong
in this city work anymore I'm gonna help hey can I kick it for you
I can't get it to work sorry vending machine discovered 450 experience
a new anti-cleo spatial mask perhaps or experimental pheromones none of the above
all these rich wealthy bureaucrats
and brightest of our society live trespassing here this property is off limits solicitors
loiterers visitors will be fined to the fullest extent of company policy this ultimatum brought
to you by universal defense logistics I'm here for minister Clark oh no goodbye goodbye goodbye
see you later I'm gonna go goodbye I'm gonna go money of drunk friends is gonna ruin everything
uh-huh oh wait whoa ID badge there it is okay let's get a key card do you have a key card
hey hey stand back you I'm part of minister Clark's personal detail that means you
gotta keep five feet back didn't relax I'm just looking for the bathroom oh yeah it's right here
good thing too because I may be headed there soon all right so the others took me out to
celebrate why would you tell me that me just getting hired and all um all right I'll leave
you to it where's the bathroom this is the bathroom where's the bathroom I have to talk
to him I thought I thought he said he was gonna go to the bathroom so I could steal his key
he's gonna leave the key on the fucking table he's basically the most important person in the
colony which makes me the most important guard in the colony that means I got a key
to the minister's estate my own personal udl assist issued shotgun they don't give those out
to just anyone you're very important congratulations yeah I've nearly made it to the top my friend
I'm just two promotions away from on-the-job bathroom breaks
all right all right settle down settle down bro jack tell me about mr. Clark oh um he's a
medium height with like medium colored hair and kind of a medium face just like in his posters
all right how descriptive you definitely recognize him if you saw him he's very important you know
how about it buy you a drink to celebrate your promotion that's a great idea I'll have a spectrum
vodka uh spectrum vodka for you you know we both are talking really really low gravelly voices
how about a uh spectrum vodka for your promotion that sounds good to me I think
there's to you yeah of course hey you're really no not yet no friends wow
oh
another spectrum vodka for you not every day you get your dream job right all right
oh that was you got a crazy energy has anyone ever told you that like a
like a manasaur you got a manasaur energy oh loss I'm not going to talk like that for the rest of
the stream it would hurt let's have another one I really shouldn't I'll have the worst hangover
tomorrow if I don't stop that's a problem for tomorrow you know that's a very good
supposed to taste like purple very crunch or am I just tasting breakfast preparing
oddly waste collection receptacle I don't feel so good don't puke don't puke dude
key oh he's gonna puke he's gonna puke if you can do like the broom closet where are you going
he's dead holy shit he's dead what uh what did he drink what did he just drink okay I'm out
the gag sound and the instant death ragdoll all right I have access wait can I prove this
I can just go in haha key card into an appropriate waste receptacle
fine bye I'll go through the minigame I don't I have that ID card how am I supposed to do this
wait hey can we talk there's nothing to see here move along you know that's just the sort of thing
folks say when they're trying to hide something I have no idea what you're talking about sir
I'm here for Mr. Clark that's funny the minister isn't expecting visitors
and you don't much look like one of those couriers from hps I am sure you are and what is it you're
delivering today death excuse me I'll be right back oh I'm on my legally allotted break really
I'm supposed to be after repeatedly falling no reject here oh um what are you doing here
what are you doing here nothing nothing why uh does it does it look like I'm up to something
laws I knew it you got me I'm caught aren't I okay whatever's going on yeah you're in big trouble
you're in a lot of trouble I work in the lab at the ministry of accuracy and morale
some of my sprats went missing but it's not my fault okay maybe I let them out more often than
regulations allow but they need to stretch their little legs and so what if I occasionally forgot
to latch their cage everyone gets a little distracted now and then you're not helping
your case here they escaped and before I could coax them back they've made their way to the
maintenance tunnels even if I did dare go down there they're among all the common sewer sprats
and exterminator mechanicals boy that's not good good luck they're gonna fry you I have a package
nothing exciting ever happens around here block him don't let him turn around block him stay there
okay where's this probably like the key in here mustard should I steal his mustard
I'm afraid I can't help you at the moment have a prosperous day due to the removal of the suggestion
box all customers with complaints ought to be directed to window c as our policy for customer
complaints is not to deal with them window c will remain unmanned you have a complaint what seems
to be the problem I don't have time for this do you need help what do you need I want to get that
but I can't stealing where'd the guard go uh hey uh udl security attendant
where do I get anything to open that door how do I get in there I need to like talk to somebody
maybe I should go in the front I need 55 lockpick all right do I have any lockpicking skills
wait I can do this I was gonna down I'm gonna drink something where's my coffee where's my
like caffeine inhaler vodka right here no right here no where is it right here cool down punch
all right I don't know the hell this thing is called fizzy soda caffeine all right here we go
mind attributes all right drink an energy drink it's not enough there's a stack with lockpicking
I know I have one there it is shit okay hold on lockpicking suit that's lockpicking five
with lockpicking anything else is it technically a stealth skill
oh it is all right tech skills tech skills stealth skills where was it dialogue sneak
long guns two-handed melee tech skills tech skills stealth skills no I didn't want to just
do drugs again don't okay now I gotta put my clothes back on I didn't open this door
what was I wearing oh the msi um gtx 280 whatever it was I wish I could just go knock them out
fuck am I is he gonna be mad that I'm in here what do I can I just be in here now
give me the eraser and the chocolate okay um okay where is the package got it pocket watch
any other stuff I can just take shit ah I don't care wait I can go up here what's the point of
being up here that's the point right there let's move engaged returning to customer see what
mail fraud is a felony I'm not committing mail fraud I'm delivering a package to somebody that
I'm not opening their mail I'm just I'm stealing their mail from the mailman to deliver their mail
to them hello fellow oh I forgot I don't like that guy I'm taking the parcel from like the
postal service and then just bringing it to the person and I'm not taking it it's still getting
to its intended destination unopened all right now I got it I'm ready to deliver I'm back I
remembered what I had now I got it delivery let's see it got this parcel right here looks like your
papers are in order all right go on through thanks kill okay minister Clark okay it's technician
okay let's go from this office or wherever he is all right um how did you get in here
what do the camera pointed at you you you're not one of my guards what are you doing here
minister Clark what a remarkable honor it is to meet you if this is about another wave clip
or radio spot you may kindly fuck off as the parlance goes I'm not doing anymore
oh cut the crap I'm here for the self oxide oh of course what else would it be I don't have any
drugs you should try a vending machine or a purveyor of curative goods what is this system
coming to when even the earth minister is disillusioned beyond hope will that be all
there why do you keep talking like that they're getting denser by the day
I shall endeavor to speak more slowly is this better slower and louder into my good ear what
was that a joke sarcasm even oh this is such a relief you've no idea how long it's been since
I spoke with someone intelligent enough for irony great so how about you tell me about those
chemicals this again I really don't know about any chemicals process of elimination the only other
person with access of course of course it's Rockwell again who else and I thought he was
only holding me here to keep me out of the way what I mean you're locked up here you are a quick
study indeed I've long suspected Rockwell of transacting business in my name but this proves
it he's attempting to game the system but he won't be able to get away with it forever
eventually Rockwell's house of cards will topple I dearly hope so and you might be part of the
equation okay one dart you hear Rockwell through the window just into his neck
and that fucking syringe is full of salicylic acid it'll kill him less than five minutes
why would he go through all this trouble should I know I've been under house arrest for years
but there is a way to find out and perhaps to set things right whatever Rockwell's doing
he'll be doing it from the HHC headquarters your best lead is to look for details in his office
captain we must investigate Rockwell an injustice like this cannot go unchecked
I trust max it cannot I can't trust the urgency of the matter if it's dirty it's a job for Sam
it's filthy indeed my mechanical friend rife with the worst sort of corruption why this is
starting to sound like an issue of dissident hunter we're discussing you're too excited
espionage legal redress a possible salvation of halcyon is this not exhilarating
also this is the longest conversation I've had with someone else in quite some time
uh if you're the best we have to offer we're screwed I assure you I didn't ask to be locked
up and made to perform like a trained animal but I'm attempting to make the best of an opportunity
I only hope you can do the same now we've got to get into the HHC that's in the Acropolis district
along with the other major corporate and government facilities but only board employees
corporations government government corporation guarded checkpoint just down the street the board
there might be a route through the maintenance tunnels but I'm afraid I don't know specifics
most people avoid the area for obvious reasons a few guards don't scare me that's good because
there are sure to be more at headquarters when you reach the HHC building this access card should
get you up to the executive suites where the chairman's office and what used to be my office
are how did you hold on to your access car keys are none too bright I simply claimed I'd lost it
and hid it somewhere no one would think to look government corporations corporate government
all right I should get going wait rockwell has one of the only terminals capable of transmitting
to the earthbound message drone this is our chance please take this and transmit it from
his office rockwell hasn't given me any messages from earth for years he's desperate to keep me
out of contact with the earth directorate but they need to know what's happening here
all right you can count on me is in dire need of someone like you
hey everything in the in you it's a bolter pistol it's the revamp the refined byzantine
all right what is that plus five skills range weapon skills plus five that's pretty good
mine never mind I got excited for no reason all right let's do it steel book why is there
a book in the shape of cheese what's the cheese book what's the cake book what is that
that's freaking me out how do you read that book that's a magician's book yeah there's like
look at all this weird stuff here all right so get access to this person's office and
yell at them and scream at them down there the chairman's office pizza is the shape of
a triangle so press triangle if it were only that easy oh there right there can't you just
see the stench of impropriety radiating off of him for the last time access to
besant him is impossible without a proper analogy now if you'll excuse me i need to be
somewhere else how much have you ever lost on a coin toss how about i don't understand it's a
simple question how much i don't know maybe i can't reckon i'd say you can sir how splendid
another rung leech wandering through the streets of besantium why just this morning i thought to
myself as lovely as the gardens are what they really need is more greasy vagrants
frolicking through them and here you are frolicking gracefully might i add what a
coincidence just now i thought i'd really like to sock this lady in the face
how utterly expected you must be one of those violent vagrants i've heard tell of wandering
the system in search of brutality honestly what is the board thinking letting so many of your
ilk into the city proper it's madness if the board isn't supposed to let people into the city how did
you get here i earned my place here just like everyone else my grandfather was the cio at tile
you see cio chief idea officer he came up with all the best ideas for their products you know
the font they use for stogie slits that was him so you mean the guy that showed up to work
once a month their font development team in socks and sandals a blazer it was a very long list
oh what did he come up with let's see he picked the colors they included in rainbow chips no one
else wanted purple but he insisted everyone loves the purple ones and you know how the cosmic smokes
logo has an eye in the middle of a heptagon he said that one came to him in a dream
he was a true visionary so far ahead of his time
wait but what did you do i just told you my grandfather made millions of bits as cio
and i earned them from him so you came into it you married into it of course it is wealth is
the most visible objective measure of success and success isn't given to you it's earned my
grandfather taught me that if you have wealth you're successful and if you're successful you
must have earned it what time do you close it's a simple concept no what time what time do you close
i had darker darkness not the time what time do you close
you're welcome now do we have any further business or are you just here for the repartee
what's wrong with people what's wrong with you it erodes the very pillars of our society
merit decorum personal hygiene this city is meant for us the system's finest we earned its luxuries
but now we are overrun with the unworthy and the ungrateful and this early retirement nonsense is
making it even worse and that's terrible attitude you shouldn't look down on people like that
early retirement what are you talking about the worst thing to happen to halcyon
a contest that gives even the lowliest to most inefficient workers a chance to live in Byzantium
by simply winning a lottery those early retirees get an exclusive district of Byzantium to
themselves no one else is even allowed to go there tell me how is that fair life's not fair
well it should be if you pay enough it's not right i deserve to see any district i please
why if it weren't guarded i'd hmm you know you look like you've been shot at before
what say i hire you to investigate this travesty you want to hire me to do so oh we get paid this
time i like this plan yes listen to your your friend what is that person doesn't seem like you
have very many are they your secretary personal masseuse or do you just keep them around as a
mobile armrest well it doesn't matter what's important is that you think this is a fabulous
arrangement and you'd be thrilled to lend me your services aren't you why would i ever help you
with something like this did you miss the part where i said i'd pay you that's all the reasons
someone like you should require i mean it's not i like money but give me something better than that
better than money let's see there's no the thrill of discovery like in an aetherwave adventure
people love those right don't you want to see what the retirement district is like
fine i'll do it but not for the money fantastic consider yourself employed vagrant i hear the
chosen retirees all enter the retirement district via the port landing pad but it's completely
locked down you'd never get in that way unless of course you had a wealthy beautiful benefactor
of impeccable social pedigree which you do not i'm not gonna let her not gonna let her have that
over me guys these codes will get you past the lockdown you'll encounter security afterward
that's her power that's what her power comes that's what that's where her power comes from
how did you get these access the same way anyone gets anything here of course i made friends with
the right people bits might earn you a place in Byzantium but that means everyone here has
little need for more of them you're being paid with exposure like this you need to spend
let's call it social capital social capital that yeah that actually is paying with exposure
all right i'm done with you max are you saying anything about this mind where you're pointing
that thing just checking use the password to access the terminal let's try it we're
already right here though it's down there terminal um we're already we're right here let's do this
first the acropolis district is off limits move along mind if i take a breather i'm pretty tired
after hauling around all these bits what in the law's name are you on about uh these 2783 bits
have been weighing me down all day oh my back is killing me this is killing me sure
i'd say restricted area slip of the tongue what i meant was welcome to the acropolis district
thank you i can go wherever i want i can even go in the trash and eat out of the trash cool
there's a lot of people whoa he's up there hi i have an appointment welcome to the official
headquarters of the halcyon holdings corporation board today's greeting is brought to you by
anti-cleo a subsidiary of colway pharmaceuticals i have to go through like the scanner i clearly
have a bunch of weapons nothing exciting ever happens around here take your business
please step away this entry is for high priority hhc business only uh well
well is this official enough for you huh i didn't realize we were still using those
iridescent stickers but this looks right i'll just need you to register your weapons with
a revised request to carry 32b form each weapon will need a separate form i'm not doing that
that's ridiculous it's procedure i'm not doing it now let's see when did i run out of forms
what a shame you don't have to be sarcastic about it look you don't have time to wait on new
forms and i can't afford the citations for impeding h.a.c business so i'm going to save
us both some trouble and wave your forms okay just know there are a bunch of guards upstairs
and they're all high on dervish mist and low on patience so try anything funny and they'll paint
the walls with your guts so they're all they're all high thanks for the info now i know that
they're all high i'm not hi cool dude to let you in with guns i don't have any guns look
do you see any guns on you no do you have any guns no this is toothpaste i don't have any guns
there's a reception before the reception i have i can unlock this door wait what do you okay what
now what i understand your maverick johnston's new star well done what are you doing here
personal assistant to adjutant akande and chairman rockwell i'm also responsible for
organizing the adjutant stationary which is more of a hobby uh i want to meet chairman rockwell
ah oh you were being serious i'm obliged to inform you that chairman rockwell is unavailable for an
indeterminate duration will there be anything else okay fine it's gonna be like that all right
fuck your halo sword we're out of here and speaking of halo halo reach releases on december
3rd so you'll be catching this streamer play that when it releases oh my fucking head ow
just blacked out for like 20 seconds that was weird uh okay can i get in here will they see me
do this i mean the game just saved itself why
oh you guys didn't come in quick enough what he's running in here
you should go back to your desk i saw somebody eyeing your stationary what oh dear thank you
for reminding me i can't stand the thought of someone else's hands touching my custom
letterheads i know another's fingerprints yeah sucker uh broken snow globe oh what a view
where where are they hack a hundred damn it view priority message halcyon is on the brink of
starvation the board scientists are working on a solution workers can look forward to the
lifetime employment program don't worry i'll make it i'll make sure it gets properly edited you'll
see the current version when you print your key card i'll take administer key card thank you
what afternoon chairman rockwell is issue facing us as you all know our colony has been successful
beyond our wildest dreams unfortunately we've recently discovered that our food supply will
not be able to sustain halcyon's population in the long term everyone everyone will slowly stop
living together that's what matters there's way too close if someone doesn't give you something
to read that will placate the masses soon all of you will find yourselves violently unemployed
i can assure you there's nothing to fear we've got a solution it's called the lifetime employment
program is most of the colony to preserve resources it's called bringing back overwatch
same actor
so obey your supervisors take your vitamins follow your corporate mandated grooming rituals
and rest assured with the board on your side there is nothing to worry about
quite distressing information i know i think you should be in charge i was hoping for a word
let's make you the ceo anyone with eyes to see would not be shocked to hear that the colony is
dying but the board's solution on the other hand choosing to save themselves and their families
and friends at the expense of the rest of the colony those fucking bastards what are we going
to do about this i want to dig more into the issue i fail to see how it's our problem i don't know but
someone's going to die i don't know well when you figure it out you can count on me to back your
your ceo your instincts haven't filled us so far anything you'd like to discuss
uh ceo you all right i got the info where is this person got expensive booze steals
you got spectrum you got spectrum vodka up here really only 60 dollars oh send the message to
earth let's fuck the whole thing up message aren't pleased with a lot between three and nine months
for your message to complete transit chairman i've made inquiries i can confirm that we have
plenty of food stored away from our inter-colony trade continue to decline it's been too expensive
something something evil overlord corporation something something destroy them all right now
what oh the the chemical this is door locked uh the chemical you've learned the sulfoxide is
the ministry of accuracy and morale along with whatever chairman rockwell is working on
let's go progress as always now i can put my gun back up any corporations in chat um
probably not that was not allowed to go in here i'm going in anyways okay let's get that chemical
and get the hell out of here where is it it's the chemical i only walk forward to green indicator
where is it where's green indicator oh it's there okay found it good work restricted access
bullshit looks pretty restricted yeah that's very restricted i need a id card not so fast
the ministry of accuracy and morale is off limits to everyone without x36 level clearance
basically if you don't work here or for chairman rockwell himself they're not getting in
uh how's this for clearance i got the key card i don't know how you got that but i still don't
know you and i don't have any new clearances on the list let me through right now or your official
record won't be fit for polishing floors what waste my time and i'll bury you so deep in
citations you'll die of paper cuts before you ever crawl out and people like me never repeat
themselves oh no you must be from chairman rockwell's office i'm so sorry no one told me
fix it please five four three two one saved by the bell mr hold stay by the bell excuse me get out
of way make way for my weird fucked up friends but you know who i am we're going down in the
basement to drink why am i not allowed in here what restricted area
um
well this is a huge dentist office this is great actually i feel at home here and it's nice to
look at green green now let's see the dental work going on in here let the record show that
subject 23k's cause of death is cerebral vascular incident brought about by a ruptured aneurysm
uh he's got to be the other way
and i had such high hopes for this one oh well i suppose it could have been worse
yeah they could have ended up like those poor bastards in containment
hmm cool all right bye central lab all right let's go get the chemical
i was gonna make a fluoride reference like they were in fluoride
and it was too late all right so i can't i'm not allowed in there
no no no no no all right i have to sneak around
nice kill all right i'm not allowed in this area i know it'd be sneaky somebody right here
central lab save it right here oh shit something's not right we've got trouble
oh
nice commentary i got nothing to comment on i need to wait till you go where maybe just wrap
around let me try going this way anybody in here all right i don't think anybody in here
okay okay there's a workbench over here but who cares all right there's that guy
keep going all the way around
i paid three thousand dollars to be allowed in here this is bullshit
come on don't turn don't turn don't turn don't turn don't turn don't turn don't turn
stay there stay yeah yeah all right where's the other one right here which way are you going
oh yeah what the hell is this where's this so where is it oh shit i gotta go up and around
it's a somebody right here all right slow down slow down what was that noise stop wow
you are allowed fuck off i have to drink a bunch of drugs put on my suit and everything all right
where's this lie suit where is it stealth skills lockpick five that puts me at 50 and now drink
a bottle of where it's down here caffeine gel there's rubbed caffeine gel all over me
mind attributes drink it okay open the door any guards no all right i'm gonna get it
warning discontinued due to severe adverse reactions transfer to canister procedure
this procedure may result in the invalidation of experiment results in the death of human test
subjects sudden what's raw from sulfoxide is highly lethal and will result in the cancellation
of any in-progress experiments oh transfer 26 percent what who somebody talk talk me up a little
bit here somebody talk me up i did something bad talk me up a little anything uh oops okay um
what about the colonists right right i'm saving millions uh right let's get this up to
30 50 oh let's do handguns and okay so that's done i got a hundred percent of that stuff
i can now go back to phineas no i know no no no no i'm gonna do the retirement quest
yeah all right exit what's the fastest way to get the hell out of here without being spotted
run fast no that'll alert everybody i can get out like this lazy lazy hold on stay right here
oh fuck whoa huh idiots because cause of death is cerebral vascular incident
right all right i'm almost out
don't shoot all right i'm up good good good good good see you later nice to see everybody
you did what you had to i will tell myself that over and over again in the shower
let's do the retirement home thing archery dalton and archibald harris are redecorating
with real crystal faux windows laws don't they know those went out of style three weeks ago
so did their marriage apparently i'd wager my inverted bathtub she backs out of the contract
inverted bathtub fearless can you go to the sewers
down here we go this way retirement home retirement home retirement home
retirement home down how do i get there retirement home
how do i get down there
need to go down that's a bit i take the fast way i tried jumping over there already
there's definitely a way to go down from here elevator or something fast travel um i guess
we're going in here retirees that's the last of them are we getting one more access to this
area restricted unseal the door all right all right or i'm in the retirement center welcome
to the halcyon holdings corporation early retirement center you the lucky few have been
selected to spend the rest of your days living the highlight in your own private district in
bizantium no when you arrive you'll be whisked away to your very own luxury penthouse furnished
exclusively by 24 seven furnitures deluxe falsco wood collection very nice before beginning
your new life in bizantium our safety regulations require you to consent to the following you hear
and after referred to at you and hereafter referred to as the employee consent to the
rules and regulations of the halcyon holdings corporation early retirement center here and
after referred to as the center the employee confirms that they have read and understood
the rules of the center as written in article 3 section 5 clause 24 of the early retirement welcome
packet the employee also confirms that they received this packet en route to the center
in the unlikely event of injury death of the loss of personal items the employee assumes
all liability for the incident just skip to the bottom i just end usual license agreement i yes
i agree you just made the first step on the greatest journey of your life now please proceed
to the elevator some assembly required 24 seven furniture is not responsible for any injury
psychological damage for divorce litigations that occur during the assembly process after you get
we're all retiring the three of us are retiring together so the audio
bones what
this is not retiring well it is literally i guess this is not part of the brochure okay
yeah 500 500 oops don't die
i think we may have been deceived yes they lied to us chairman rockwell must go
robo phobia i'm okay i'll take it i'm just afraid of everything range attacks detection radius
plus 20 damage just just many of you are affected by a harmful combat effect no no no
let's see headshots deal 25 percent of their damage to enemies that's kind of cool i guess
when you use the inhaler any down companions are revived 15 minute cooldown that's too much
your range attacks reduce the target's armor rating by one point per hit
oh that's pretty good i'll take it all right i've investigated it turns out they're killing
everybody down here what fucking absolute twist uh disable auto mix disabled unseal the hatch
that robo phobia is constantly there because of max or sam oh i think we're gonna have to
rip his battery out you did good sam every sam unit comes lean mean and ready to clean
this unit is unable to process customer please repeat the command go back to the ship sam you're
scaring me all right what do i need to do go this way ah no match up with that watch out for that
rat excuse me give me aggro i can't believe we i can't believe i broke holy fuck i died instantly
what was that because of the robot that shot me oh i'm still wearing this shit
get me back my msi stuff let's move didn't i disable all the drones i'm gonna see a lot of
sad faces that i just tried to do that don't worry i didn't all right where you at
all right this way i think maintenance tunnels prosperity plaza
all right hold on let me use the workbench and do some tinkering uh the shotgun to be better
handgun handgun do again 312 dps i'm running out of money though so easy
uh nothing really needs to be repaired i guess what about my shirts good okay all right now
whore tents oh right right that's the person that turned into i made it oh it's this lady i'm okay
remember it's the lady i did what you wanted oh there that's one right there can't you just see
the stench of impropriety radiating off of him what you're talking to me like that i've we already
had a discussion about this shit i'm getting a certain thrill out of our little arrangement
if this goes well perhaps i'll start hiring wandering delinquents to handle all of my affairs
it is going well i hope the retirement district is a paradise you should see for yourself it's
awesome in there this pools and spas i knew it i just knew it what a disaster did you get a good
look around what was it like an endless extravagant garden there were even signs that said no for all
looking it was just one giant party they had a vodka fountain everything is gold everything's
made out of gold toothbrushes why that is positively gaudy i must have one yeah it was really cool i
can't believe they kept this from us from me the nerve the audacity here take your payment
i have to fetch my things i don't care what i have to do they'll give me luxury or give me death
preparing body dye for use all right have fun it's a paradise you're gonna love it
see you on the other side follow i can't that's not in this game that's uh that's complaint
complaint against game you can't follow anybody all right now we can go back to phineas we've got
the stuff jerry there's a robot following you monkey s what no way for sore ocular processors
captain or rather your head you have a message from adjutant sophia akande who's that no one
looks quite the same in person as they do in my reports and my reports of you have been
exceptionally thorough you've had quite a career oh let's skip you have something i want
i'd like to negotiate uh i'm listening phineas wells is wanted by the board i want to convince
you to turn him in to us okay and what exactly he has a little laughing vandalism illegal
experiment i could go on he was made to me wells is a dangerous man you're going to endanger
everyone in health yarn he's an obsessive psychopath he stole a bunch of chemicals
so now you're in contact with wells i want you to send us a tracing signal from his communication
terminal cut her off aida thanks can you believe the nerve on that psychopath you know i can still
hear you right adjutant akande's call has been terminated will there be anything else captain
uh let's get the fuck out of trace that call and send a virus to your computer please
if you don't mind my saying captain minister clark is lucky to have you on his side
don't go rogue on me now i can't i'm afraid of sam all right what densest are we bringing
i need sam i don't need sam your entire ship is a robot i've got chemicals i've got chemicals
doctor i've got chemicals i'm bringing them to you i've got them here they are
install them breathe them experiment on them hey good forget about the chemicals for a second
the colonies on the verge of collapse i found your chemicals in the ministry the board was
testing them on human subjects uh i had to let the test subjects die but i brought back
all the chemicals i put them out of their misery here's your canister of chemicals by the way
these are both awful um you've brought me enough chemicals to get started at least
but all of them i'm just sorry they came at the cost of human life to accomplish
um something about repeatedly melting frozen people there are a lot of big words you know
how food goes stale if you freeze it too much like that but with people dumb science 40 uh the
colonies on the verge of collapse the board's been trying to cover it up i know i'm suspect
what do we do the board's mismanagement put our colony on the road to collapse if we don't put
a stop to them some of colonists are going to die what do we what do we do it gets worse the
chairman's planning on freezing every worker in halcyon it's pretty fucked up
yep and the chairman's plan to save all of us yeah i always knew halcyon was heading
toward this cause for let's just let's go to chili's and order everything off the menu might as well
then i'll stop it the board's going to kill them all we need to think about this there has to be
something we can do that's it we just give up all the trouble went through for another
this colony's a mess i'll be glad to put it behind me as soon as i get a chance whoa
we got to be something we can do let's go cut them off we need to get to those colonists
would have been a lot easier if you just set up your lab next to the hope
yeah i like it just wait until you hear the details i haven't been this energized since
the time i injected myself with raw cap and all if we skip the entire third act of the game
and that's going to work and get to the yelling us in the process i thought interest system
micro jumps were prohibited for a reason experimental methods for killing noxious
life forms are not covered under this unit's limited liability agreement
well said whatever you are hey you'll need to switch auxiliary power using the unreliable
then head to the bridge i can't wait for the germa rumble 2019 or 20
when it's the dentist versus somebody else in the tag match interesting i think let's do it
i know you're wondering why i'm doing all this the people on the hope are the answer to the
cost problems hope is carrying some of humanity okay by the way why are you hiding behind bullet
proof glass it took me this long what being frozen into your brain that is bullshit that's
why i don't desire to end up like that's an absolute that's regardless it's quite comfortable
you know i have my beans have my caffeinoids plenty of toilet paper all right level 20 i
thought this was a big brain oh what's wrong with me all right i'm standing next to something i'm
terrified of 12 13 to 9 26 okay you gotta go you gotta go you're out of here i'm sorry i need a new
dentist let's just make it work let's get to like a hundred like 80 reduce damage from area
thickened plasma more carrying capacity this one's not terrible more damage with low health that's
pretty good yeah i'll do it and you show time damage plus 25 increases the damage dealt by
this companion after performing show time yeah sam it's been fun see you later goodbye you can
stay on the ship and there's a pig over here oh wow it's an omega pig i don't think those things
existed all right let's go let's let's do it let's actually do this let's let's do this
let's go for it keep sam no sam scares me hope talking i hope dr wells has not
dragged you into one of his irrational schemes again my diagnosis of his mental stability is
not flattering you want to be ceo hope let's go to the hope
we have arrived at the hope i need you to reroute power from our ship to the hopes auxiliary
generator you'll have to connect me to the hopes comm system so i can convince her central computer
to enable the skip drive we're gonna get a robot fight an ai fight what's gonna happen if i skip
the hope your calculations are even slightly off you could crash the entire colony ship into terra
two for the sun oh good thing i'm great at math i know all the best numbers
i must recommend you leave the calculations up to me captain there's so many numbers so
many big numbers you have the best numbers in brackets trump
all right that's all for now well talk to that computer and let us know how it goes
i like your special move breathe down my neck why don't you okay hope power hope comes
packs yeah power is now being ruled from the docking bay patch ada into the hopes communication
system status power cool maintenance looks good hibernation storage seems all right logs cool
ship puts me on edge captain you know what you're doing i don't who are you i hear someone snuck
into the repository who the hell is this all right coms oh we have to talk to oh quincy duncan you
know when they posted us here i told him there wasn't any point nobody would be so stupid as
to fly to the ass end of the colony for this derelict shows how much i know you've got about
five seconds to tell me what you're doing here before i make you take a walk outside
uh i was sent to repair the reactor so it doesn't explode and take out the colony
they sent me to extract a few samples from your uh frozen cargo it's gross
an engineer life explode holy shit all right you'll want a uniform so my staff doesn't shoot you on
they're dangerous it makes a board and trigger happy we've got a few extra in the old badge
station to my right good luck thank you to your right to my right right okay well that looks
did i tell you everything uh all right this whole starving of that thing isn't all that
cracked up to be on the upside the bathroom is the cleanest they've ever been since we left port
oh all right do i have a do i have one you just need the id card oh all right let's break some
of this shit down all right i'm gonna sell your robes no i don't anti riot gear i mean it's cool
but i don't need two of them i put guns a lot of just 350 that's not man it's terrible now that's
pretty cool i'm gonna give that to the priest stun baton ultra i gotta give some better weapons
because the things that they have kind of suck yeah all right here i need a
you what do you have you good with melee no you're the melee here and take this instead
take the flamethrower let's go no that doesn't make any sense for you that's out of character
for you you don't have two handed guns keep the tactical shotgun you use the flamethrower
where'd it go and the stun baton now we're ready let's do uh harmful status effects all right
thank you so why is this some kind of weird disguised costume thing when the guy just told
me hey you're a new recruit why do i have this costume i'm supposed to be here what what i'm
supposed to be here you get tired of patrolling just go rough somebody up that's bad advice
guys excuse me i'm almost out of juice out of juice i can't lie to a robot robot communications
wait wait it wants to talk to me it wanted it said it wanted to talk to me it said it wanted to talk
there was a hey i have to ask you a question it said like hey i have to ask you talking
i took too long what oh i i i no i didn't say i i i i said i i i
can you hear me captain i have successfully integrated myself into the hopes con systems
and i'm attempting to establish contact with the hopes more primitive processor now would you
like me to play a mood suitable music selection while you travel to the bridge oh sorry file not
found i'm currently trying to not get spotted by these monsters i need some i need okay i need to
talk to somebody i need somebody to see me that's not a robot well that was a good little skip
wait can i is this correct is taking me home i think so oh there we go have a nice day
okay that's the hopes computer up ahead i'll admit i am curious to wake him i hope you guys
work it out patch ada through i am speaking to you through the hopes computer system
it's a rather cramped feeling but it'll do i'm ready to skip hope tell me am i really doing
the right thing i don't want no i'm ready to skip hope are you sure that is extremely dangerous
skipping the hope will void the warranty on the skip drive and also potentially kill an entire
planet how is my humor now captain improved skip jump starting the skip drive destination set to
the rings of terra 2 jumping destination okay do it if we're meant to make it we will no use worrying
otherwise doing it i mean affirmative skipping the hope in three two one ada does your captain
seriously intend to do a micro jump in system with engines that haven't been powered in 70 years
on a derelict ship that's what my captain intends yes but that is a gross misuse of the skip drive
the zero point drives corp and i will not be held responsible for any damage incurred during
transport and this will cause extreme damage yes i am aware of that you should not be doing
this the humans will die thank you hope it looks like all systems are go captain i would advise
you to hold on to something what when you hold on to something all right bring them home
home why is it pointing at the sun into the sun
it made it we are still alive and have successfully skipped into terra 2's orbit
i reported as much to vinius wells but he has not responded perhaps you should check in on him
i will we made it all right everyone's alive look okay good let's do a little bit of
let's get handguns to 80 debuffed enemy critical chance minus 20 percent and let's put lie i have
108 lie now no one's gonna get anything by me nice work uh catch me being bad no not you
the puman so i could get my disguise back error crew data not found identify yourself
i was in one of the pods i just woke up if you're experiencing errors just take you to a mechanical
engineer this statement is false paradox protection protocols have prevented me from
registering your stated identification please we can't lie to robots mechanical engineer they
don't know what it is everything i say is false error paradox prevention has temporarily disabled
this unit's auditory processing thank you for your cooperation you're welcome back to the lab
can i teleport no nope i killed him there's no you don't kill a robot they just unplug
this is the wrong fucking area excuse me excuse me excuse me excuse me
excuse me i don't recognize you are you new here on your own business what's your problem
you relax i'm not looking for a fight
all right here we go all right all right all right all right all right all right okay
just get out of here how do i get back in my ship there's a tiny little bridge uh what is
colder than cold freon captain i am receiving a transmission from dr wells captain i shall now
play the transmission before you get the bad thing oh they found me somehow they're about
you got that glass from getting me and there isn't enough time to explain everything and very
important you need to rest the board all their lackeys they're all a bunch of swine do you hear
me they're fucking corporate swine you fucking pigs i'll take you all out with me i'll never
it would seem the recording captured some rather dire events i presume you want to dock at the
orbital lab to check on your associate as soon as possible how can i be of assistance
uh can you make cereal or something i haven't eaten in 12 days sandwich a ham or anything
i have lots of minutes many minutes unlimited minutes perhaps providing an adequate power
source i can function indefinitely cool uh tell me about the captain tell me tell me this i put
my feet up on the chair and fold them tell me what about that captain i require a captain to pilot
the ship without an identified captain or crew i serve no purpose as you may be aware captain alex
hawthorne was a smuggler of some repute i failed to predict the likely outcome of his reckless
behavioral patterns i should have predicted that outlaw in our travels together alex liked to
pass time by as he called it tinkering to improve my design okay i'm done i guess we'll go check on
phineas phineas i'm coming to save you he's arrived in phineas's orbital lab all right
let me just take care of business again and we're gonna bring the dream team even if i'm scared
did they get them no alchemy books they left the pig um they can't get in how can they know this
as per official arrest protocol outlined in defense logistic incarceration document
the individual who's been detained at this location must appear in an official halcyon court
at the appointed date and time with this paperwork and failure to appear at the appointed date and
time with this paperwork will result in additional late fees please know that this is the only copy
of this receipt that you'll receive you know it's your responsibility to have it with you when you
repair for your resurrection yeah can i be his lawyer max what they wanted to talk talk about
i can't wait to go on the epic rescue mission check your armor it's all good it's good all
right what did you want here they come you don't okay you don't want to talk
fucking dying instantly okay what the hell is this stupid robot next to me
you made your bed now you have to sleep in it fine why was there only one bullet in this gun
what's he doing holy shit oh god oh god oh god sam all right if i'm standing far away from
me he doesn't affect me oh shit oh jeez oh shit oh jeez rick why are you saying that and why am i
repeating it poster whose poster is this all right let's get in there obscure body in the sk system
did you leave a video recording for me publishing last will and testament please
present login hack it if you're seeing this screen i phineas v wells have been peculiarly
kidnapped and very probably incarcerated by the perfidious and cowardly government
of halsey khan in the prison fortress of tartarus if i have not already been executed for charges
leveled against me i hope the person reading this terminal will find a way to finish my work or
rescue me preferably the latter this screen constitutes my last will and testament i commend
my body and my belongings to the icy depths of the ether if this is junko i've prepared an emergency
camp package located in the hidden panel i locked the panel from my terminal and claim its contents
immediately you're supposed to burp must delete entries from terminal memory no telling whom i'll
be looking what's this one say exposition exposition i've got my notes with me i have
my equipment and now i have this lab it's time i return to work only the hopes colonists can
forgive me for what i've done they're the only people who can set things right and i'm going
to find a way to revive them no matter how long i have to stay hiding they say i'm a murderer
and they're right i am i regret what i've done but i'm not about to turn myself into the board
i'm not going to go begging the board for forgiveness i always suspected this would happen
the board finally discovered what i'd done and sent their head hunters to track me down but
they'll never find me onto the subject number 13 can still hear the screaming trouble sleeping
trouble concentrating psychological toll significant statistically insignificant if i
experimented on the subject every month i would not make a dent in the hopes population in a
lifetime he was my 12th subject to die i don't know how much longer i can keep doing this strictly
speaking i do know the hope has hundreds of thousands of colonists i've only experimented
on 12 how many more experiments must i do before i revive a single subject 110 100 500 113 seconds
of screaming this subject was stronger than the others but in the end his body failed to survive
the revival process thanks a lot doctor secret panel nav key ivan slept once tartarus now let's
go get the professor new weapon fins force long gun energy tinker it replace this is it a science
weapon cool that's how does it do time to tinker it's pretty neat tinker armor please read important
yeah actually you're right didn't i request no more fertilizer shipments be brought on board
siri unplug yourself all right tinker first of all let's tinker this
i can't what i can't be tinkered well we're gonna tinker this 46 armor we'll do it one more time
48 armor 36 armor let's get it up again here we go 41 armor good tinkered can anything else be
tinkered based based what are you doing prepare everything might as well this is the final battle
the game i'm preparing all my stuff who keeps ordering these captain as it appears we may
soon be embarking for a maximum security prison planet i believe the crew would like to speak
with you too as you humans put it what was some people have concerns who has concerns
what a meeting of the round table of the dentist exactly keen on busting into a prison but riddling
board stooges with bullets does sound like a ride and a half to extract the scientist you will need
to infiltrate the labyrinth but that course of action is likely to be quite dangerous captain
it's because he took off your dentist outfit what's so bad about the labyrinth we can't abandon
phineas we have to free him if we have any hope of saving the colony great figures i've got to be
the one to save the day again look at it as saving the day look at it as securing your investment
phineas owes you big time i'm sure the outlaw phineas will appreciate you saving his day as
it were captain if you really need to do this you should see to your final affairs that close out
any unfinished business once you sneak into tartarus you may be there a while or permanently
we're doing it everybody strap in everybody strap in if we don't make it at least it'll be a great
story outstanding never thought i'd volunteer to break into a prison seems like your tendency
towards risky behavior is rubbing off on me captain command you're a good friend not recognize
sorry we never found your french book waiting for me all right nothing else in here okay
all right let's go we want a speech don't fuck it up don't fuck it up don't fuck it up don't
fuck it up are we clear good 10 10 10 10 10 10 60 good you can't take those chairs either
those are mine and the couch oh at least two or three of you are gonna die and that thing's
already dead it's not even real good luck message for junko no messages nobody ever fucking sends me
emails hey be ready for anything i forget where my chair is on to tartarus you're about to install
the labyrinth on tartarus and determine the fate of the house here on colony if there's anything
you want to do before enter the prison do it now this is it this is the end of the game if you end
the game now you're not gonna be able to find the uh max's book bye sure i am pleased to inform you
that we have arrived at the labyrinth please be advised that the punishment for trespassing is
execution all right please be advised that electrical storms on the surface of tartarus
make departure impossible at this time ellie you have to walk off the ship first
resident count is as follows 3071 resident deaths including but not limited to executions
are as follows 1684 resident escapes are as follows zero the interior make it one chili
take a scarf with you captain make it one ask that you leave your captain's id with me
in the event that you do not return and another captain will come nice try nice try understood if
you die or are incarcerated for life i can generate a new id for the next captain i would prefer you
return though oh speak of the devil captain i am receiving a transmission from the prison's talking
authority let's talk shit attention unauthorized spacecraft this is a maximum security installation
your presence here is an explicit violation of udl corporate policy all right you are hereby
confined to your docking platform until a ticket detailing your crimes have been filed and
notarized at which point your vessel will be seized and you will be executed by you well uh
how long would that take i wager it'll take a bit longer than it takes you to lose your patience
and storm out of your ship looking to get shot to be honest that'd make my job a lot easier you
come out you shoot you full of holes and then everyone goes about their day worry free except
you you'll be dead okay true uh fine uh execute the chairman's eyebrow stylist over a lost
biometric id that'll end pretty well wait you're the stylist uh thank the law you're here everyone
knows how particular the chairman is about his eyebrows here take my biometric id instead
anyway tartar stalking authority signing up hang on another ship just pulled into your dock
wait is that from the ground breaker what uh pay no mind to that just have a pleasant day
biometric id received transferring data to external cartridge how can i be of assistance
uh goodbye have a nice life okay all right we haven't used ellie in a while bye sam
sam only why would i ever do that all right you two i mean you're you're only here because
i'm scared of the robot but i have a lot of faith in you you're a good dentist so are you
elevator no i'm i'm allowed to be here i'm the stylist i'm just a stylist
just a stylist coming through all right are you walking
i let them die no i have a very specific mission i'm supposed to be doing
yeah it is a little too late you want to go back there's a war going on outside
you don't even have a fucking costume anymore well now you do all right coming in no
oh i have to go up it's all right i can get caught once nice look at that that wasn't so hard
hey final battle might as well get some final stuff how much money do i have
oh what's this cotton candy outfit no no not worth it let's go i have 71 heels i don't think i need
any more of this well let's save it in here restricted access transition to the pit what
kind of former dentist will wear cotton candy outfit i don't know like a child dentist
wait restart it no just run imagine not having a hundred lie talk to me talk to me
i was hired to test your security procedures congratulations you did it oh that's great thank
you sir you're welcome thank you yes sir bye didn't we say we were gonna like fight our way through
here i haven't raised a finger we're going out it's gonna be so dangerous guns blazing let's go
for it no i'm just this is just walking to where i need to go pit exit uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh
uh-oh is it enough it's enough uh-oh i have to go up oh shit is there any drugs i can take
to uh to make it so i can hold it something about you doesn't look right i know i haven't
been feeling well yeah you're not contagious are you hey keep your distance i don't want to get sick
do not disturb when lights are on open the door there well look who it is i'll be dead
you should have just killed him i was prepping the studio for our announcement and here you
are as a bonus ah and the wayward doctor are you about done with your escalates i'm still
disguised as the stylist lifting after all these days i'm more interested in breaking them wouldn't
mind taking a swing at yours and you know most people once they're out of prison don't seem keen
on returning oh i would go anywhere to see you fall sir when you go off and get yourself shot
try to avoid taking one to the face i'll want it recognizable to show to my citizens
uh chairman rockwell i presume my word you correctly identified the most recognizable
man in the colony remarkable i just want to make sure because when they find your teeth lying around
they'll be able to identify you then again he's an insane person thankfully he's our insane person
now a proper company man i'll see if he's please phoenix would rather die than cooperate yes he is
an extraordinarily obstinate fellow isn't he he isn't working for us per se semantics he'll come
around but that's between us as far as my adoring citizens will know we've turned a dangerous
crackpot into a working-class man it's a miracle is this the i feel like i haven't had enough time to
care that this guy's a villain it was just like this guy's chairman rockwell and here's a video
and i'll hate this guy it was like it was like 30 minutes ago all right um that's a lie it's pr
it's for the best really believe me the good people of Byzantium don't want to know what
goes on here i know halcyon's in rough shape but riots are the last thing anybody needs right now
another thing captain have you at any point why we're tight not fucking up our entire society
i believe we could ask you the same i'm making actual progress towards stabilization and recovery
you're just getting in the way you'd rather you prefer to keep writing this down as far
i can fix this place i can do it if i and my people can write it out in luxury and happiness
yes yes i would i don't know if you've noticed captain but halcyon's pretty much a lost cause
oh well the problem is i've already rallied all of Byzantium against you
they're outside waiting and they're angry you you have is that what you were doing at the ministry
i'm not an unreasonable man if you manage to storm the castle as it were and make it out of here
with phineas alive i can't exactly afford more havoc than you've already caused fine if you survive
you'll need someone to sell the rest of the board on your plan right because it'll be me
uh you're damn right right you just wait here for my orders hey and tell your tell your dog to stop
that was easy just stay there phineas shoot him no no no not yet not yet wait patience
one of your runs he won't
wait that's the person i hung up on captain you have an uncanny i hung up on this lady
you've disrupted the balance of power you've upset the natural order of things you've introduced
uncertainty and there is nothing i despise more than uncertainty
it's over sophia stand down we are liberating halcyon and there's not a damn thing you can do
to stop us wow when you put it that way i sound pretty awesome typical running your mouth in the
middle of a crisis it's almost as if you delighted chaos my report said you were simple constant
i simply never imagined you'd be stupid enough to throw the entire system
into chaos i should have dealt with you a long time ago you were always too dangerous to leave
unchecked okay i got a colony safe stop you're making me blush uh can we hurry this up i've got
an entire colony to save leaving you alive was my greatest mistake but it is a mistake i intend
to correct i have dr wells in my custody i don't care kill him once i've secured his cooperation
i can move forward with the program i can repair the damage you've done i can set things right
i don't whatever don't you don't understand finish is my friend i'm not living without him
don't test me sophia it's bad for your health i don't enjoy the thought of killing you there's
been enough violence already uh don't test me sophia it's bad for your health i'm aware of
your propensity for violence halcyon is a bloodier place because of you i wish you'd simply cooperated
with me you're the finest marksman in halcyon you could have been my gun okay um let's talk
fair enough i'm giving you exactly one chance to parlay with me
uh-huh
what dumb intimidate 80 heavy weapons 50 two-handed melee 80 uh you do not want to party with me it's
gonna be a big bloody mess okay charm i don't want to fight you sophia you're one of the only
rational people left anyone with eyes can see that you're talented captain i only wish you used your
talents for good yeah you wander the system doing as you please answering to no one
your mere existence throws halcyon into chaos i simply can't have that uh halcyon is changing
and there's nothing you can do to stop it's time to let go i'm not throwing halcyon into chaos the
board's doing that all by themselves the board is the only power left in halcyon we're the only
ones keeping this colony from dissolving into ruin you had so much potential i would have put
your talents to good use i would have made you wealthy beyond belief was this the matrix
okay great cool story agent smith uh yeah that ship's been skipped i still can't believe you
skipped the hope to terror too what an absolutely reckless thing to do you put the future of this
entire colony in jeopardy all right should i do like on my phone's running out of battery
i gotta go i tried to recruit you but you threw your lot in with that she keeps going i don't
even know who this is am i supposed to know who this is oh you could no funny you should say that
because the chairman was just telling me this is all your fault i don't have a hundred lie no
no ruined ruined ruined the ultimate lie the ultimate lie your plan's never gonna work
i'm quite aware of your brazen act of corporate vandalism by the way those test subjects you killed
reset the game what was last time i saved it my scientists assure me they can recover the daddy
reload i know but i have you what did i do it temporarily delaying are we where was it oh it
was not without not that far 15 9 this one here yeah i'm going for 100 i mean i did all points
in the why i have to all right lie wizzie was a lying suit i know there's a lying suit
dialogue skills plus five character skills lie 108 108 let's go
all right i sound pretty awesome typical my i should have dealt with you all right but first of
all i should have dealt with you long ago i could have you could have been my hired gun you we could
have done so many things you should know who i am i you should know from maybe the first few hours
of the game i could have been a character i don't who the fuck is this i hung up on you maybe 40
minutes ago in the game these last two major antagonist characters that they've introduced
i don't even know who these people are i met them like an hour ago this is did i fuck it up
what did i skip all right i got a colony save i have dr well right uh let's talk about this
fair enough i don't want to fight you you're one of the only rational people left anyone with eyes
can see that you're you wander the system i do um i'm not throwing alice on the chaos the boards
doing that all by themselves the board you had so much potential okay uh yeah that ship's been
skipped i still can't believe you skipped the hope to terror too i know you were always well here's
the thing funny you should say that because the chairman was just telling me that this is all your
fault rockwell said that chairman rockwell that's absurd you're lying this is another one of your
tricks i've been the chairman's most reliable associate good we got we got that info at the
end of the game uh sophie's been overstepping her bounds his words not mine i've already recruited
the chairman to my side he's done working with you you let the situation get out of hand rockwell
once you've gone that's ridiculous halcyon is collapsing the labyrinth is riding you're
running wild through the colony and i let the situation get out of hand i have given
that's what he said nothing less than a lifetime of loyal honorable service and this is how he
repays me by leaving me twisting in the wind everyone's disposable to the board sophie
even you enough i'm not going to stand here bickering with you i was expecting the chairman's
support but i'll have to do without he also said i dare you to come trying to shoot me on the program
yet you've caused some complications but i can improvise i can fix this he said i haven't lost
control of the lab i bet she can't open the door and fire within a second operational i can still
put a stop to you no
i'm sorry i was taking over a security system in the process i'm not a hacker i can't get
even i can't get to 80 hack i can't get to 80 hack i don't have it no i can't
game sucks i can't do it i haven't lost control elaborate our security uh i destroyed your
experiments in the ministry your plan's never gonna work yes i'm quite aware of your brazen
act of corporate vandalism by the way those test subjects you killed they died in agony
my scientists assure me they can recover the data you've destroyed you've succeeded in temporarily
delaying our research nothing more phineas tells me your scientists are hopelessly lost all your
research is wrong your scientists are lying to you their research is critically flawed your
scientists are lying i wrecked that data that experiment was badly engineered i'm gonna talk
about lies we're gonna keep the lies going your scientists are lying to you their research is
critically flawed i mean it's the research isn't it was terrible it was awful that isn't true
it can't be you're trying to manipulate me that experiment was absolutely essential to the program
my scientists assured me they were close to a breakthrough sure you're not surrounded by
liars gave me their word uh you took the word of a bunch of corporate lab coats and people say
i'm slow i don't know what pains me more realizing that i've been lied to or hearing the truth from
an idiot like you we're going to have to start all over again all that research all those
experiments you've sent us back decades i don't see any reason to continue arguing with you
i know when i'm beaten the only thing left to do she's surrendering
congratulations captain you've outplayed me i accept your terms and we return dr wells to your care
thank you hurry up and leave before i thank you i'm glad we could settle this without violence drop
the honorable adversary act and fuck off already the fate of the colony is in your hands now
i bid you farewell captain thank you appreciate it let's go get the key wait are you in that office
hold on were you talking to me from over there very cool any other people i can lie to
wait is it wrong my gear oh okay keep it on i might need to lie i might have to continue lying
oh that was cool hey vinius i'm so glad to see you how did we get you out of there
come on out you don't know how glad i am to see you you must have said something to get under
akande's skin she's gone and i don't think she's coming back and you you lunatic you broke into
the board's own fortress just to rescue one doddering old man you are absolutely out of your
mind and i can't begin to thank you enough i mean thank the people that just believe everything
that anyone tells them there is no perception checks or lie checks you just just tell people
whatever they want to you just have to everyone's so gullible i could tell everybody in this game
that the sky was not blue that it was green and they wouldn't even look up to confirm it they
would just go green you say wow that's interesting really green damn i thought it was blue anyways
here's the key card uh oh yeah the board never stood a chance against me you know i wouldn't
let anything happen to you vinius do you have any idea how much trouble i went to save you what
break into the most heavily guarded facility in the most hostile world in halcyon no i have
absolutely no idea how you did it you're a goddamn miracle worker you've broken the board's
stranglehold on this colony and you saved my life but there's still so much we have yet to
accomplish you and i are going to have to work harder than ever to save halcyon i'm afraid the
situation is far worse than any of us ever anticipated uh i was just about to pop open
some drinks to celebrate i would like nothing more than to celebrate this victory but we have
a serious problem on our hands earth has gone you literally walked through everything received a
single message in three years there's been no communication no signals nothing two years ago
the earth's directorate's frigate disappeared on their way back to earth we don't know what they
discovered when they arrived or if they arrived at all they haven't exactly been hands-on around
here anyway so there's one less rubber stamp to worry about earth is humanity's home planet
the psychological effects of losing our original home will be devastating
i got a master liar now this that's it i'm done there is no plan just random
chaos you're experiencing a crisis of faith preacher don't worry that just means you're
paying attention we're in serious trouble my friend do you know what this means for halcyon
we can't rely on earth for support anymore we've been cut loose we're entirely on our own
we have a lot of work ahead of us we better get started yes we do you've done a marvelous thing
you've succeeded where anyone else would have failed including me we must begin the revival
process immediately starting with the hopes of brightest minds and then we're going to fix this
damn colony one problem at a time wait what do you mean starting we're going to need a leader
and i can't imagine a better person for the job than you what do you say old friend will you help
us well you want to be ceo i've got plans with the chairman in my pocket no one's going to know i'm
running the colony i'm going to run this colony myself i've already convinced the chairman to take
my side you can count on me i'll help you revive the other colonists i'm going to do what i've
always done whatever i want all the time huh oh sorry i wasn't listening i was thinking
about getting some ice cream i see well you've certainly earned a treat for yourself
i'll just uh get on with reviving the other colonists and saving halcyon then
okay enjoy your uh creamed ice or whatever you call it chocolate the osi teaches that everything
in the universe happens according to the grand plan but the stranger that arrived in halcyon
was an unplanned variable from the moment he landed in emerald vale his actions altered the
course of history the events on tartarus brought about the end of the board's authority
but the board's mistakes would haunt the colony for decades to come the damage they left behind
would require the work of a generation to repair dr finneas wells began reviving a handful of the
hopes colonists engineers scientists technicians and intellectuals they were among the brightest
minds the earth had ever sent out into the stars the hope scientists and engineers woke up in a
colony descending headlong into total collapse with no way to return to earth they had no choice
but to band together and devote themselves to the cause of saving halcyon did we do it the people
of halcyon were nothing if not hardy in the absence of the board's authority many of the
colony settlements and why are we getting a ps4 dashboard add-on for the end of the game was
especially hard in the years to come some towns dissolved by attrition and starvation
but most of them found a way to carry on in the years to come halcyon was forced to reckon with
its newfound freedom the board was gone and for better or worse the colony was responsible for
its own destiny left unchecked the war on monarch consumed both msi and the iconoclasts
and when the sulfur clouds settled only stragglers from both factions remained
some found their way to who is that person who is that person and some lived their final years
fighting for food in the wilderness in the end only the beasts remained made mcdevitt replaced
reed tobson as the leader of edgewater she and her followers transformed edgewater in their image
anyone was pressured into leaving town and those who stayed behind are they omitting stuff from
history i murdered them transform the old cannery into a new garden the nearby edgewater cemetery
provided a convenient source of fertilizer it was said that the first corpse that fed her garden
belonged to reed tobson under the leadership of junley tennyson this is what it is corporate
influence the ship's mechanical stability gave junley the time to educate a promising
generation re writing the history schooled in her family so on it's the ultimate line the future of
the groundbreaker books i'm just this is more line of the hope and the abandonment of the lifetime
employment program forced byzantium to come to terms with some uncomfortable realities about the
state of halcyon while byzantines were reluctant to surrender the luxuries they'd grown accustomed to
the board's diminished authority gave them little choice in the matter no pepe hands nearly everyone
had to learn to make do with land oh not pepe hands uh no is that pepe hands even had to get
jobs it was a dark time indeed we savored her adventures on the unreliable once they were done
she returned to life as usual running missions of dubious legality shunning respectable work
and living life to the fullest wait we don't we don't talk anymore
but she was always bad okay after all he'd seen and heard adventuring with you
the vicar maximilian de soto renounced his faith and joined the effort to rebuild the colony
ironically he finally found the joy that had eluded him over the course of his life
and realized that perhaps he was always meant to you made him give up god laborer after all
he quickly dismissed the idea he ruined his life he left the crew of the unreliable little was
hurt from her again she exchanged occasional messages with ada but they were light on details
and grew increasingly infrequent months later her name appeared on the manifest of a research
vessel that vanished during an unexpected solar storm as hard as she tried to drink them away
eventually overcame her traveling with a crew served as a that was everybody's favorite character
i oh you found my favorite character i made her leave within 20 minutes and now she's dead most
comfortable the deep end of a bottle and the far end of a trail few have seen her since the travelers
often swear they hear her and her machine gun in the night screaming swears and spitting bullets
the sam unit that accompanied you spread awareness of the product line superior sanitation and
maintenance capabilities across what was left of the colony this led to a boost sam's doing okay
did you know that sam units are the longest lasting toughest acting cleaning solution in alcyon
minister clark was released from house arrest and his contact with you gave him a sense of renewed
purpose and figure once it became clear that no help would be coming from earth he threw his
considerable efforts and talents into helping house yon manage the crisis would just get like
this epilogue of every person we've ever come across sofia akande was the true power behind
chairman rockwell however after the riots on tartarus she was never again seen in the colony
various theories circulated after her fate some believe she boarded an interstellar ship
capable of journeying to a distant colony others believe she died trying to escape tartarus
some few suggest she fled to monarch where she continued to live among a small band of loyalists
and then there's me there is another fear the narrator of this story that sophia's encounter
and here's uh it's me talking deliberately retreated from public view but continued
supporting the colony in secret when dr wells began reviving the hopes colonists he found
himself with a sudden windfall of additional supplies and resources courtesy of an anonymous
donor if world knew who it's bugleberry never chairman rockwell also for the changes in house
to come whenever you needed strings pulled or a voice to sell a policy change rockwell was only
too happy to oblige they should have killed him as for dr phineas wells he spent his remaining
years in his orbital lab he did by the failures of his past um he was determined to make things
right by building toward what happens if you kill everybody do you even get an end of the game
engineers than he first expected thanks to the additional batch of chemicals you stole from the
ministry wells never forgot about the human lives that were lost in acquiring these chemicals does
it just get to the end here it just goes the end despite limited resources over half the hopes
colonists were successfully revived even after wells passed away the hopes scientists and
engineers worked night and day to pull halcyon from the brink of collapse their efforts continued
to this day which may be reason enough for optimism dr wells laid the groundwork for
the project to save the colony but he would never live to see the fruits of his labor
he passed away a few years later his work was carried on by the scientists and engineers he
revived life will never be the same in halcyon it is widely agreed that the colony has a chance
of stabilizing within a generation owing to the hard work and determination of the surviving
colonists recovery is a distant goal and the path is long and uncertain but the people of halcyon
carry on determined as ever and what about you the unplanned variable in the history of what happened
to me you brought an end to the chaos on trotter and left dr wells to save halcyon on his own
you had more pressing matters to attend to as you tasted your first scoop of risos partially
emulsified semi-frozen milk like dessert you realized something all your troubles all your
adventures all your struggles and choices they had all led to this single moment and it was all
worth it there's a nice touch i like that what happened to earth and no one knows what the
future has in store for halcyon all we know for certain is this the name of the unreliable and
that of its intrepid captain will remain the subject of countless stories for years to come
no now it's the end that moral of story oh why be violent when you just lie
and make everybody believe things that aren't true and save the world ice cream game give final
score now um i feel like all right the game was fun i thought it was an interesting game i thought
it was a fun game i do i think it was good but the that main campaign how many main story missions
even were there like eight i don't they weren't more than like seven or eight main story missions
in the game maybe ten five and the fact that the the the main sort of antagonist of the entire
video game they just sort of appear and almost like pretend like you should know who they are
one of which you only get to see on screen twice you could have gone on a date with pivardi
oh that's too bad there's a 12 minute speed run if you go evil and corporate you meet them earlier
wasn't i corporate i wasn't i doing stuff for corporate including the optional quest he didn't
really miss much 10 to everybody msi is not part of the board all right all right i'm sure there's
plenty of stuff that i didn't do i did two runs of the game and it's barely a difference and there's
like three board quests but even still though i feel like them if you if you just oh i'm gonna
do the main i didn't i didn't i felt like i dilly dally a lot was this three i was streaming two
hours before the internet went down so let's say let's say just under six hours today and then
seven six or seven hours yesterday and then four so like 16 17 hours in the game 15 hours in game
now i guess that's still that's still pretty good if for but i still i feel like i did other stuff
too i wasn't just doing story missions 15 to 25 is the average yeah took me about 30 hours to do
everything okay i did skip an optional planet yeah that's probably true but it's hard to place it
it was it was like a it was like a seven three seven two something like that it got maybe point
two point three base points there because the ice cream ending it was good i i look i wouldn't have
played it and stream the whole thing if i didn't think it was any fun maybe like a c like a seven
seven one there you go i wasn't a fan of the ending but i was a liar so like i like lied
to myself about of you know in the first place i said the same thing yesterday too it's it was
i had an enjoyable experience in the video game and not every video game has to be the best game
you ever played so there's that too i lie to myself every day would it have been as funny if
you didn't go down the liar route maybe not but you know how i mean everybody that plays this game
is gonna play it a little differently new vegas now or whoa i've ruined new vegas for myself i
can't play it i was being chased by like a hundred easy peets i would i had the time gun
i can't play new vegas again i can't do it i stepped way out of i i like pulled myself out
of the universe and just made it a shit show but new vegas is overrated i didn't i didn't say that
i thought it was good for the two about full streams i played it until i cheated this is where
it went very very very wrong there was a point in new vegas when i couldn't open the door i
remember explicitly where it was it was in that bar with the um there was a show going on behind
the door and i didn't feel like going to get the key so i just no clip through the door
and that was it it was over over at that point because i and then now you've ruined everything
and you can do that everywhere and then i but it don't matter anyways thank you for watching
that's going to be the end of the stream well i know it looks like it's been a three and a
half hour stream but it's actually been about six because of uh the internet crashing halfway through
but thanks for watching i'll see you guys in like three or four days probably on
either monday or tuesday and we're probably going to just start halo because that's when it comes
out right i have those of you that don't know i have a procedure coming up here i have to do
another endoscopy and it's gonna put me on drugs it's gonna fuck me up for a day or two and i have
to fast the night before so there's gonna be like two or three days when i'm just gonna kind of be
out of it so i have to do that hope you had a happy thanksgiving everybody that celebrates it
i will see you guys at the latest probably tuesday either monday or tuesday is when you'll
probably see me depends on how i feel after everything's done he's kind of being drugged
see you soon we'll do the bits we'll hang out for a little bit and sorry about the whole thing
crashing earlier it was very strange it's like the internet went down but it didn't it was very
weird but yeah see you soon let's transition over here maybe it was a twitch ingest problem
maybe that's very possible this is still broken it always is yeah it don't matter it seems to reset
itself after about two or three weeks it then decides to pull from a stream from two weeks ago
don't ask me why hey shitty viewbot thanks for the 500 bits i was just wondering if you
ever played any of the serious sam games you seem to have a lot of fun with dusk and the two games
seem quite similar i had a vision a few years ago where there's a weird dream that i had when
me and star played it the whole thing so i made a video on it i've had this strange dream about it
something about that we were getting chased by crabs and stuff it was really really it was
fun though i remember playing the whole thing was fun but um yeah i thought about it serious sam is
interesting serious sam is a game that i always have glossed over i don't know why just because
it seems too chaotic but it's not like i'm against ever playing it 20 to 30 uploads in the future
uh it has come across my desk a few times and i just go maybe uh thank you dark soul for the 250
here's my money no jokes this time since you seem to hate them and your own content these bits are
exclusively for auto someone who actually appreciates me but actually happy thanksgiving
streamer give the boy some turkey treats also in honor of thanksgiving epstein didn't kill himself
and the nfl is rigged uh dash your uncle okay quick cut his mic
all right all right appreciate it happy thanksgiving thank you thank you gm egon for
the 500 bits you want wacky talk about the star wars holiday special i've never seen that you know
i feel like it's something i should have seen i've heard it's wild thank you for the 500 bits
gm appreciate it hey piss juggin thanks for the 300 bits thank you for streaming i remember
watching your uploads come out when oh watching your uploads come out when it looks like they
kind of got cut off thank you though appreciate it thanks for watching hey sad vega thanks for the
250 speaking of collecting bits happy thanksgiving happy thanksgiving hope we had a good one hey
apple shift thanks for the 250 hey since it's thanksgiving i want to let you know how thankful
i am for you and this community you're the most wonderful inspiring and dedicated streamer on
twitch damn that's that's a lot and you came into my life at what feels like exactly the right time
becoming friends with all the incredible people in the discord has been an absolute blast too i'm
genuinely happy in life right now and you're the best person i could ever have to look up to
when things get rough love you have a great thanksgiving i'm i'm really happy that you can
find friends and people to hang out with people that you can talk to and play games with and just
hang out in a call with that's um that's awesome and if it has anything to do with me then that's
i'm glad that that's sort of a catalyst there thank you so much for the 250 bits and for
sticking around hope you had a great thanksgiving thank you apple shift thank you the plushie for
the 400 bits hey germa i may not be here when the stream ends but i want to thank you and chat for
their kind words the other night i had a good time on your discord the last night and i'm going
to try to see a therapist soon that's very good news solid solid solid solid stuff i wish you the
best and again i will say do not be afraid of going to therapy do not be afraid of somebody
trying to help you i really appreciate it thanks for the 400 bits good luck to you hey gnarly
thanks for the 250 happy thanksgiving germa turkey i'm extremely thankful for all the
outstanding content you've consistently put out over the years as your career as an internet
comedian superstar and millionaire thank you appreciate that thanks for the 250 bits uh sign
up with facebook thanks for the 250 uh hey germa why is it that you don't that you have donations
disabled and only bits turned on you'll get the full money from cash donations unlike bits where
it splits with twitch i'm sure some people would prefer to donate cash also like that you'd be one
step closer to becoming bill germates a long time ago i decided against having something like a
paypal setup because paypal is sort of weird and they will i remember hearing horror stories of
people sending a bunch of money and then they can charge it back and if you've already transferred
that money or accepted it or spent it or something then it's like wait you have to give that money
back and it's like wait what and it goes into like an appeal process i don't know people that still
do it and well just don't touch the money for 90 days and it's like well okay well just let it sit
should just have like an a big open pit of a paypal account where i just don't touch it ever and then
i look at it every like four months to see what's in there so it's just something if i was ever
going to do anything like that i don't i just don't think i would just it's it's kind of too
much for me to have to think about spoken like a true crypto backer you just said a contradiction
what was it what did i not convey the thought did i go off what did i do i said i've charged back
and people sending money and then like four months later they can take it back it's interesting stuff
right that's why that's why i don't do it if i ever did that i wouldn't oh right but
that's me mid-thought changing gears and saying i'm not gonna do it
there was talk a long time ago of a patreon but a patreon is just subs but on a different website
you know hey sign up for my patreon hey you you subscribe but there's a different website where
you can subscribe again it just didn't feel right it felt sort of like didn't feel didn't click
but you'll get more money yeah but i would rather take a sponsorship or something than
try to double dip you guys you know what i mean like hey give me five dollars a month on twitch
all right cool thanks a lot hey you know i got a patreon five dollars a month over there too
like but you all right i guess but you already you already are doing that just make it as a
tip jar maybe i just have no goals or reward tiers or anything i guess maybe it would just be there
it's are a tip jar yeah i know but i'm just saying having bits and subs and then having a patreon is
like you're asking the same people that are potentially giving money already to do it again
which i would rather instead of tapping into you guys again for a separate website to pay money
to i would rather just i would do a sponsorship before that he hates taking our money pepe hands
you need at least 10 different sources of revenue no i don't need 10 sources of revenue
but yeah i guess that's a long answer to why i don't have a donation set up i don't know that's
kind of the thought process but thank you for the 250 sign up with facebook i appreciate it
c4g thanks for the 250 rpg ayaya clap cute chat rise up rpg ayaya clap
thank you thank you trampston for the 500 bits love you on your stream germ germ if this screen
weren't between the two of us i would pop through and kiss you on the forehead thanks for the 500
bits uh i'm glad that's not possible because not only that would be uh that would be a little
strange but also that would mean that people could reach through and strangle me
so i'm i'm glad that's not a capable technology at the moment thanks for the 500 bits let's get
the credits rolling move over to the other screen oops sorry i bumped you thanks everybody for
subbing the credits uh unfortunately have been killed because of the disconnect that i had like
two hours three hours ago so this is going nice and slow this time slow credits pepe hands
wait this is old trotter was there yesterday is this old it can't be scroll it faster scroll
it faster hey that's me that's you that's you read them i can't read them because
if i read them then it's not fair to the people that got deleted two hours ago and they're gonna
be like well hey all right i'll i'll do i'll do two thank you zombie slapper two thank you
ampere mari two that's it
yeah sorry everybody who subs the first few hours got cut off i don't know what the
fuck happened it makes no sense but you do what you got to do we have a few more bits to do
we have convo breaker thanks to the 250 if anyone does not believe in the power of germa one guy
it's just because you haven't had a moment yet i've had more one guy moments than i could type
here before the character limit mostly because of my four years of watching new sub badges when
and these bits are a small tribute for those i'll always cherish how me mentioning your
companion looking like a dentist cause you to four hours later google dentists take the
hypocrite chronic oath to stay in character and any others to come never underestimate the power
of the one guy it is immensely powerful it's insanely powerful i wish i was the one guy
pepe hands you are now i was about to mod that person that would be bad so i deleted it
i modded you in spirit in my mind guys all it takes is to slash mod and then all the sudden
that person just has to like copy and paste a bunch of commands they might have saved
and delete everything i've ever worked on they could like delete every nightbot command they
get to lead every vod i don't know i'm scared i almost had so much power you did for a few
seconds so close so close but thank you convo breaker appreciate it thank you clowers clowers
b for the 250 bits i had a dream about you a couple days ago it was just you streaming
something and at some point you lost your dog and then you banned me why does everyone else
get cool germa dreams and you ban me please unban me but what happened to my dog did i think that
you took my dog give my dog back and maybe you'll get unbanned ban him again but in real life guys
where's my dog where the where the where's auto what the fuck happened where's my dog
well i had something really important i was about to do like i'm gonna ban the
ban uh clowers joke but um if you ban somebody doesn't like remove a bunch of stuff from what
they may have been done on this channel well it'll like it'll like fuck a bunch of stuff up right
i feel like i don't want to do that i don't want to like delete i just like swallowed hard
oh no i'm not gonna risk it but anyways pretend i banned you flowers that's a weird dream
hey bobo dorago thanks for the 500 bits hey germa love the streams the first stream i've ever
donated to and watched i just hit 3k subs on my youtube where i upload old music and advice for
playing the youtube game interested to hear what people like when they listen to my music
unfortunately my advice for the youtube game is um i actually don't really i actually don't really
like youtube i'm like a i'm like a youtube i'm an anti youtube but that was back when i was on youtube
is it is it anti tuber i actually cannot give advice about youtube for one reason because when
i was active on youtube was four plus five maybe years ago so the advice that i would give somebody
is like five year old advice it's like watching uh patch notes from a game that you currently play
when the game was in beta three years ago so i feel like some of the stuff i would say might
not be accurate anymore but uh listen to my music here was here you go if you want to listen to
music take a look at that all right all right i'm gonna get i'm gonna give you i'll give you three
seconds ready see if we can get anything out of three seconds here here we go ready wait there's
a phone ring what is it hello all right let's skip over here what's it what's in the middle
is that you it's kind of low-key smacks well uh anyways no he said it was old music oh right
this is not music okay all right all right all right i get it i get it i get it i get it i get it
i get it anyways bobo i wish you luck on youtube it's a different beast than it was five years ago
but thanks for uh honored that you would come and watch the stream and ever consider donating or
watching i wish you luck is my youtube copa compliant i have no idea is it rats look at
that rat there's a rat in the chat that's a cute rat you could be fined i we are i know we already
went over we already talked about this we talked about it hey c4g thanks for the 250 um u gene
posted under the bit limit i'm paying their bit text so you have to read their message
all right you've paid the entry fee but anyways all right uh u gene jerma thanks for all the good
streams remember coming back home from middle school watching tf2 videos to now about to
graduate college even though your career peaked at shb i've been watching you all the way don't
really know what i'm going to do after college here's my first donation before i go out into
the real world and become homeless thanks for all the good streams jerma heart i don't think i
don't believe i peaked at shb but about to graduate college you gotta you you close in
a book you're about to open a new one and here's the best part the best part about graduating
college is you've been reading books that other people have written after college you get to
write your own i hope it's a good one thank you hey and finally we got jack the mac for the 500
bits hey jerma thanks for playing dusk last week love that game it deserves the exposing you gave
it the game's fantastic uh i can't wait to play amid evil by the same publisher looks just as
interesting should be cool what have happened to that book jerma said he was going to write
books are hard to write i gave up after about 17 pages i think yeah i i copy and pasted random
blurbs i was just copying pasting random pages like two years ago somebody in here definitely
has some of them i just was pasting them into this chat but happy thanksgiving hope you had
a good one thanks everybody again for your support uh wish me luck i've got a endoscopy
i've got an upper gi stomach an esophagal endoscopy coming up and uh gotta do it right
i'll see you guys again i will keep you updated expect to see me somewhere around monday or
tuesday and if it's monday we'll do something interesting and if it's on tuesday we're going
to start probably halo thanks a lot guys i'll keep you up to date take care have a great weekend
much love to you all have a great