Let's go ahead and refresh it all and just see what, you know, what servers are available right now to me to play in Team Fortress 2.
300, 400, 500, keep coming, come on, come on, big money, come on, 700, come on, big money here, we got big money, 800, 900, we're up to over a thousand servers, you know, just stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, listen, listen, stop.
How many people are playing on TC Hydro right now? In over 1200 servers, there's only six human beings, but that just ain't gonna cut it. All right, Charlie, boot it up, turn it on, boot up the time machine, we're going back, there it is, we're going back to 2007. Star, are you coming with me? Let's go.
Oh, don't throw up, oh, don't throw up.
Did we just go back in time?
We did. Are you okay? You feeling all right?
I didn't think that was gonna work. Yeah, no, that was great.
Watch your step out of the time machine, it's really important that you do that, so do you have any idea where we are right now?
I don't know when we are.
We could have gone back in any point in history, we came back to TC Hydro, Team Fortress 2.
I'm going back to see the dinosaurs, this is stupid.
No, what do you mean, you can't go, no, no, no, no, no, that's my time machine!
Hey!
He actually used it.
I'm stuck on Hydro forever.
I don't even know if this is a good spot for this or not.
I'm sure we'll find out in the 7 minutes and 35 seconds that we're not going to be playing on this map.
Or this part of this map, or this round, or this mode, whatever you want to call it, this quadrant of Hydro.
Spy capping, I remember spy caps on Hydro were insane.
If a spy was back here right now and I didn't have this, he could just stand on this and he probably would win.
But that ain't gonna happen, because I have a big sentry.
See? Bang.
Orick XL, you got it.
Now you could be, no, you're not a spy.
I remember people go through this choke here, and that's all I remember.
I don't remember much.
It's been so long since the time machine was destroyed.
I've been on it probably for 20 years.
It's all becoming a blur.
Do they have an engineer too?
I don't know, actually, you know what?
I remember this, I remember, it's all coming back to me.
It's all coming back to me.
I'm gonna have a sentry gun right here, and it's gonna make everybody's lives better.
That would be heavy, that would be a lot of people.
I just, please, just, I don't know where to go.
I'm not sure, just repair it and just stand here.
I have one revenge crit, I gotta make this one count.
You know what, I could probably build a dispenser, which I will right here.
Get out of here, get.
Yeah, I could have sworn you were a spy, but you're not.
I don't like the way this place looks either.
I feel like I'm in a cave.
I mean, technically we are in a cave, but look at this.
I don't know, I don't like it.
It hurts my eyes.
Wow.
That's one way to do it.
Okay.
I guess we're doing okay.
Watch the stairs, watch the stairs.
I've got six kills of this thing right now.
I'm like on a total, total tear.
I can't believe this is still going.
Hydro is not supposed to last this long.
Oh, oh, oh, we're gonna win, we're gonna win.
You know what, let's do it.
With all my crits.
Let's make this happen.
Come on, come on, cap it, cap it.
Yeah.
Hydro, where you get 13 points, six points, and three points, and you win the game.
Did I just really get somebody?
Look at this room.
This hallway is just stuffed full of people.
I didn't kill him.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Get off this point.
Geez.
All right, well, I'm sticking around here.
I don't want just some random dude to walk right in and just instantly win the game.
That does not bode well.
We got, there's an engineer over here now.
I think we should be okay.
The question is, can we, hey, hey, come here.
What?
Where did he go?
Did he drop down?
I'm confused.
I'm dropping down, screw it.
What just happened?
165, that did 165 damage?
I jumped off.
That was like a 10-foot drop.
That's bullshit.
For this experiment to work, we've got to win three times.
Did once and do it again.
Ooh, gotcha.
This is going to be a second win.
All right, this is win number two.
And I don't even need to make an edit, I don't think, because that was like two seconds.
So we can just keep talking about, like, I don't know, the weather.
So it's kind of sunny out right now, overcast right now.
It ain't bad.
It ain't very good either.
Well, I know how to play territory control.
Don't worry.
I've played it before, Valve.
Let's do it again.
In the same, like, two minutes, let's get the third victory on Hydro.
And then I can go eat, like, a banana because I had just bought a bunch of bananas.
So, like, why not, right?
Why wouldn't you eat a bunch of bananas if you bought?
Why there's this many people in this one tunnel?
This is like, we're going to win.
This is it.
Yeah, this is a game where I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything.
Game over.
Game over four points.
Dude, what?
Let's do it again.
Third time's a charm.
Let's go.
No, no edits.
We're not doing any editing right now.
I want to see for myself if it's possible to get the trifecta on Hydro in less than,
like, four or five minutes.
Because if it is, wait a minute, no, don't let this guy get by.
He can't break up the trifecta.
Oh, he really is.
What is he?
What?
What is happening?
Where is this point?
How did we just win the game?
It's just chaos.
Hydro.
Look at this whole team.
There's no rhyme or reason to anything that's happening right now.
Things are just happening.
And we're going to win.
Yeah.
Congratulations, Red Team.
You did it.
You won.