Hey, what's going on everybody? Jerma here with an update video.
I felt the need to make this video because of various developments going on in my channel in my life.
So we're going to talk. I don't have any gameplay. I haven't recorded much gameplay since like four or five months ago.
So in the background of this video is probably just going to be Spider-Man. You cool with that?
You don't want Spider-Man. Okay, but how about Spider-Man 2? Yeah, I knew I'd get you with Spider-Man 2.
So if you want to listen, you go ahead. And if you don't, then you've probably already left.
And I don't know why I'm even addressing that person because they've been gone for probably the last 10 to 15 seconds.
So I will address the elephant in the room, which is my uploads over the last couple of months.
I'm sure you're well aware there's only been like three uploads to this channel in two months.
And that's something that I'm not particularly happy about.
I obviously want to make as many videos, make as many videos that I'm proud of that I want you guys to watch.
Try to get as much videos and content up as possible. But sometimes, sometimes you need to collect yourself,
take a break, and reiterate inside your head why you do these things, why you make these videos,
what you're doing it for, who you're doing it for, and are you still interested.
And that's a very important point that I want to make. Very, very first off, before we talk about anything else,
I have to stay interested. We could talk about money and power and the fame and the fans and
how fuh-wow. Kiss my hand. Now kneel. I don't, no, I just, I need to stay interested. I have to be
completely and totally into the thing that I'm currently working on. I've never been able to just
force myself to upload something. Even back when I was uploading a shitload of videos years ago,
I was totally fucking into it. I wanted, I was so into making those videos every day because I was
currently so into the subject matter. And lately, I've been into certain subject matters that take
way more time to come up with and way more time to produce, which we can segue into talking about
the next subject I want to bring up. And it's a huge video that I've been working on. I've wanted
to make this video for about a year and it's currently taking up a bunch of my mental energy
and spare time and money and effort is gonna be huge. And it's gonna come out this summer.
I don't want to talk about what it is. I'm sure people can piece together the stupid fucking things
I've said on live streams to be able to piece together what it is. And I've told some people
what it is. If I've told you, if you're one of the people I've told, just keep zipping, you know
what I mean? Just keep it up. You're a secret keeper now. You've been elevated to the status
of secret keeper. That doesn't happen very often, especially in my circle of acolytes that I have
here. So if I've told you, just you know what to do. So stay tuned for that. It's coming. You'll see
it when you see it and I really hope you guys enjoy it because it is a legit just like love
letter to you guys. And without getting overly sappy or emotional in this video, it's for you.
This video is for you. I've had this idea that I thought people would really, really be into
and it's just a total concentration of all the stupid shit that's been going on on this channel
for five years. And I hope you guys really enjoy it when you see it. And that's pretty much all I
got to say about that subject. We're going to move on to the next one, which is streaming,
which I got to be careful of because every single time I talk about streaming in a video,
I curse myself and I don't stream for like three months. So let's hope that doesn't happen right
now because I've been streaming a lot lately. These last like four months, I've been going
a couple of times a week, sometimes more than that. Sometimes like four, five, six, seven,
eight hour streams. I streamed all of Dark Souls 3. I streamed a bunch of Stardew Valley. I did
Doom a couple of days ago. I've been streaming Overwatch as shit load. I've been on there a lot
and it's something that I'm having a ton of fun doing. So if you still have not followed my Twitch
and you're into that and you like streaming, then come on over. And if you're not, if you really just
hate live streaming, you don't like watching live streams, then there is a little bit of good
news here for you too, because all the streams that I do, at least the major ones that have
substantial amount of content in them will be broken up and they will be uploaded as highlights
to YouTube. Now I don't know if that's going to be this channel or if I'd make a separate channel
entirely for stream content. I don't know, but I don't like the idea of putting whole streams up
on YouTube because they are currently on Twitch right now. You can watch entire VODs on Twitch
right now. So I don't want to do that. I'd rather have, oh, you played through Dark Souls 3. Here's
like two or three videos condensed of all like the best moments from when you were streaming.
That's what I'm into. I'm just not sure exactly when it will happen, but I would assume in the
next couple of months here is when it would start to be a thing. And finally, we're going to talk
about my book. That's right. You didn't think you were going to ever hear that shit again,
did you? About my book that I'm writing. If you have no idea what I'm talking about,
if you're fairly new to the channel or if you're an old subscriber that forgot because it's been
so damn long, I wanted to try to make a choose your own adventure book, write it and come up
with some stupid ideas, put it in like a medieval fantasy world and you get to pick different things
to do. And it was going to be free. I was never going to charge for it. I was going to just release
it because I'm using the Inkle writer to write it. And there's been progress. I actually started
writing again. I stopped and I started and I stopped and I started and now I'm finally
writing again. And it's become kind of like therapy to me. You know, whatever I feel,
I fucking today sucks. You know what, I'm just gonna sit down and I'm going to write like two
chapters and I don't know. We'll see what happens. I have no idea if this is ever going to get
finished. Another like six to 12 months might go by and I might just throw it up onto Twitter
and have everybody just enjoy the fucking mess that it's probably going to be.
So that's the update on that. And that really wraps it up. That's all I really wanted to talk
about today. Just want to make sure you guys know I'm still around. I'm still kicking. I still get
a bunch of shit up my sleeve, but a magician never reveals his secrets except to like a few people,
except maybe like 30 people that I've already told the secret to. So he does reveal his secrets only
due to a very small amount of people. Anyways guys, thanks so much for watching. I really
appreciate it. Have a good rest of your day. Have a good rest of your morning, night, evening,
whatever the hell you're watching this video. And I'll talk to you guys soon. So take care everybody
and goodbye.