Bada! Hey guys, you can probably tell by the title. Labo VR.
Change the title? What do you mean? Cardboard VR? What's wrong with that?
Is Cardboard VR not a good title? No, not really. It's not. Why? Does it have to be funny?
Set your expectations real low, guys. This is a Labo stream. It's too funny. I don't know. How
about, like, how else would you describe what we're doing? This is Labo VR. It's Cardboard VR.
I'm to the point. Every time Jerma says Labo, drink. Labo, Labo, Labo, Labo, Labo, Labo, Labo,
Labo, Labo, Labo, Labo, Labo, Labo. Hope it's water. But there's nothing wrong with the title.
All right, we're keeping it. It's staying the way it is. Anyways, so we've got to talk about
Labo VR in particular, but I've got to, first of all, this is a special occasion.
We only do Labo VR. Well, we never do Labo VR. We've never done Labo VR. We only do Labo once.
Labo! Hey! We only do Labo, like, once a year. Three times a year. So I've got the finest
fucking grocery store wine you could possibly find. That actually looks kind of good.
Let's, I, I couldn't really, this is hard to get this open. So let's go ahead,
diaper bulge. Get out of here. We're going to do a little bit of a, I'm going to pop it,
and we're going to say, start the Labo! You ready? Start the Labo! That was the same audio
clip. Anyways, where's my glass? Right there. Let's see. This is, this is not going to be
good. No, I can't say shit like that. If I say shit like that, then I'm like, I don't
want to slander a company. It's probably good. Okay. Glass, hint of old Thai dishwasher soap,
hard water, and sediment. Oh, that sounds good. Okay, but I probably shouldn't do this
over the Labo. Where should I do this? This is dangerous. Did you hear that? It made the
pouring sound and nothing even came out. Listen to this. I can't even show you. Do you hear
that? Let it aerate. That's too, don't do a heavy pour. There you go. This is called
a copper thief. This was selected by the seller master select. It's probably going to be good.
All right, let me just move my diaper out of the way. I had to wear a diaper for this
stream just because I could just shit and piss in here. It's going to be a while.
You're also probably noticing, excuse me, Jeremy, what's going on with these? Are these
new? What is this? This doesn't look like yours. Well, I think my switch might be permanently dead.
This is italics's switch. So I didn't, I haven't turned on the switch in a long time.
It's been like at least like two or three months, three months. It hasn't even been
plugged in. It won't turn on. I think the lithium battery in it is permanently dead.
This wasn't $60 by the way. I'm moving this like over here. So now you fucking sickos can like
talk shit about my life. How did you break it? I didn't break it. It just, it won't turn on.
I can't, it won't charge. I can't even get it to the screen like the, hey, it's charging
screen to pop up. Whatever. Let's try this. What is in here? There's like pieces of wood in
here. Did I fuck this up already? That's sweet. There's some sweetness here. It looks
like a Jolly Rancher. What's this one called? This is a, okay, this is a bourbon red wine.
Bourbon red wine. Does that mean this is extra? All right, I gotta be careful. I need a,
whatever. This is a fuck you table. Who cares? Welcome to, this is Nintendo Labo if you don't
know. We're going to do the VR kit. The weird thing about the VR kit is the VR kit
for some reason decided to release in like three different packages. So this is the
Blaster and the headset. They sold out of the regular one. So I had to, I went around
looking all over the place for where I could get the other kits. This thing right here,
this like big camera elephant trunk, this shit's going to take about four hours to
build. This is the longest build in Labo history. This is going to take a long time.
So I'm actually kind of glad I only have the two here because it's going to be like a six
hour build just for these two. Plus I've already wasted like 12 minutes. So, you know,
that's what I do. I'll be ready for a long stream. And by the way, only drink alcohol
responsibly and only if it's legal in your city. You know, drink responsibly. Only
drink when you're going to build a Labo in the comfort of your home with wine. Don't do
it ever, ever again. All right, let's go. Let me get it on the screen. There it is.
You probably remember this setup here. It's going to take a week. No, it's not going to
take a week. What else we got? Get that out of here. It looks like I have a wicked
fat stomach. Do I? No, this ain't moving from here. This is like staying right fucking
here. I'm not taking this anywhere else. All right, so let's go. We're going to build
the headset first. We should have that good to go. I am ready. We're going to make the,
I think we're going to make the goggles first. No, I don't, do we have to practice?
I already know how to do this. Is this, okay, what a waste of paper. They put this in every
single Labo. It's this one right here. This is like the little french fry cup holder thing.
I don't need this right now. Move that out of the way. Actually, I don't need this whole
thing. Let's, okay, let's, let's go ahead and just do it. I know how to do this shit.
That's not my first ever time. All right, yeah, there it is. I, just to give you a rundown how
this works, you get a cardboard cut out here and you flip it over and it's grooves. And what
you do is you fold the grooves and you turn it into a little device. Put the wine on the
desk. It's going to be fine because I'm, this whole thing is going on the ground. I'm putting
on fucking pants. I'm going to go get like just jogging pants and put them on.
There's no way this strange happening like this. All right, that looks good over there.
You guys got me so fucking self-conscious every day. I can't wear, like I cannot wear these
pants. You guys are all immature. Grow up a little bit. All right, here we go. All right,
so we got this piece here. I can't even like see. Like this, I already know how to do,
I got to get a trash bag in here. It's going to be a long night. I already know how to do
this. I've done it like six times already. Don't grow up too much or you'll wind up like
Jerma985. Yeah, don't grow up too much. I can't wait to, I got a plan, by the way,
to how to get you, that's right, you sitting there right now. You're going to get to see
Nintendo Labo for yourself. Oh my god, it almost just happened within five minutes.
Okay, I'll listen to that guy. So it folds like this and then like that. Tab goes in here,
as you can see. Got the Nintendo Labo side. By the way, just want to make this real clear,
I am the only motherfucker on this whole website. On the whole website, and it slides in like that,
as you can see. I'm pretty much being nervous. I'm the only fucking person on the whole website
that does this. You're not going to find this anywhere else. You will never find somebody,
dude, what you see here building a Labo on the whole website. Find me another streamer.
Hasn't never happened. I'm the Labo guy. That's like the Jerma the Labo guy 985.
I can't wait till the Nintendo invites me to like the next Labo premiere event,
because I'm the only fucking person that's made any content of this goddamn game.
Oh, we're here at the Nintendo Labo event here with the exclusive streamers and YouTubers
that are really, really into the game and series. Look who's coming down the aisle.
Who's coming out of the limo? Oh, it's just Jerma985. He's the only fucking person.
I should just get on stage and do a fucking speech. He's coming down the aisle. That's a grocery
store. That's what the event is. It's not even like a cool theater. We're like the mayonnaise aisle.
All right, here we go. Don't swear. Stop swearing. I know I can rotate the camera
around with a little tool here. I never thought this was ever going to happen.
But this is actual, this is actual stomach sitting on table. That's not like clothes.
I don't, this is why I don't fucking ever turn on a camera. All right, I know what I'm doing.
Let's go. You tilt. You can zoom in by holding. Yeah, you go like this. I've got the boomer belly.
Reset the camera by pressing X. I've got a little toy. Can you see how good,
is it showing up well? Because this stream's about to go off the fucking rails. So
just wait till you get to play VR though. We're going to share it.
That, this camera right here is going in the headset. I was going to do two,
but it was impossible. There's no way it was going to fit in there.
Can you turn the music up a little louder? You want the music louder? The music sucks.
No, it doesn't. All right, that's, I already did this. Let's just skip it.
But these are cool. These are really cool. It takes a while to build.
You can get your friends over, grab a bottle of wine and do it. Do it. I just thought
about something right there. I'm going to go get into that. But we'll do that on the first
wine break. Just thought about it. You can just see the cogs turning in my brain.
They were just spinning. Box wine. This is actually bottle wine tonight, not box wine.
Write it down. I won't, no, I will not forget. Don't worry. Okay. Onto the real thing. Let's
build the headset. Oh, switch it. We're good. All right. So we're going to do the
pedal. What do you mean pedal? What? No, no, no, no, no, this is wrong. Hold on. I'll fix
this. Always keep a backup switch. Uh, yeah, it was in the other switch. That's right. This
like rich and I have to do the whole thing again. God damn it. They looked at how,
look, give me a break. You see how easy this is to fucking fuck this up. They're,
they're like this big. They're this big. Hold on. You can't read a microscope to read
the text on here. I'm not building that thing again. I already did it.
For a second, I thought they put it the wrong thing in the box. I was like, this is
no fucking way that somebody would do that. Right? There's no way. All right. Okay.
Everybody can relax. I'm ready. Okay. Your controllers have to be updated. All right.
Let's go. Should I not hold it? Is it like radiation coming in here? That like kind of
freaks me out sometimes. Is it like electromagnetic fields like going, I feel like it's going to
interfere if I pick it up. You're going to get super powers if you just hold on to it.
Well, we'll start drinking. Oh, oh, oh, I can't fucking do that. These are not mine.
I just saw haha. You got like, you got like a hundred more of those to do it tonight.
Just going to tell you this is a fucking Nintendo labo stream. I guarantee you if
you've somebody keeps track of that, there'll be at least fucking each each one of you
will do that like fucking 30 times. Lick it. Why would this is not mine? I don't
lick things that are not mine. You're using up the supply that you get the idea.
You can tell me like cringy. I fucking dare you. What do you have? I would love to have
that one, Nintendo, but you only made like a certain amount of them and you can't buy
them anywhere. They were so scared that people didn't want to spend $80 on the whole
thing that they made half of those and half of these. I don't have this one. I have this
one. Lick the cartridge. It's not a rat tail. It's my hair coming down. Look,
restrict the use of VR mode for children six and under. VR mode is only suitable for
players age seven and above. Kids, please check with an adult. Do you want to allow
the use of VR mode? Six and under. All right, you're two. You can adjust your
VR mode settings here at any time. I don't have it yet. I need to make the VR headset.
No, I already did it. Isn't there a skip? Welcome to Nintendo Labo. Here, we're going
to show you how to make the fucking pencil holder. All right, I already did it. Just
skip. Wait, wait, what was that? What's that? What's that thing? What's the guy?
There's more? Oh shit, they never used A before completely. I know. I can't play
completely. Do this again. Put them wrong. Didn't lick the cartridge. I'm not going to
lick that cartridge. Guys, this thing said it was going to take like five hours to build it,
and it's been 20 fucking minutes and I've done the wrong cartridge. I'm going to be here all
night. Lick the cartridge. Why would you ever, what world would you want to live on to do that
about licking the cartridge? You, okay, you're doing this wrong. I really hate to
blow this up here, but I've had like three sips of wine and you're already asking me to
do weird fucked up shit. I know now that like future drunk Jeremy is not going to do that.
You've ruined it. You could have done that like in two hours and I would have done it.
Now I know. I mean, that's your fault, not mine. He's not going to do it. I already know.
I can hear. My internal monologue right now is locked in that I'm not going to lick that
cartridge. It's locked in and then nothing that can be done is not going to change. It's
not going to happen. It's already locked in. I can't believe I can't do all the other ones.
All right. This is going to take 30 to 60 minutes in Jeremy stream times. That's like two hours.
It's not going to take 30 minutes. We're going to make the actual goggles that go on your face.
Wait, is it actual glass? You actually put like a piece of glass in there.
Making the Toy-Con VR goggles. Four steps you need to complete. This is really actually
cool. VR lenses, VR goggles, the safety cap and then prepare to play. We don't need this anymore.
It's getting recycled. Don't worry. Everyone's like, oh, you can break it. It's getting
recycled. Don't worry. All right. So we need the VR lenses. Dip it in the wine. No, thanks.
The VR lenses are inside this box, but hold on a second. Don't go opening this box yet.
There are some warnings first. There's a snake in here. That's the warning. Oh,
Nintendo. You got me. Wait, what is the warning? Warning. Never use the VR lenses to look at the
sun or any other bright lights. You could damage your eyes. Should I try it? It's pretty
bright out right there. No, I'm not damaging my eyes for the sake of fucking comedy. No way.
Never place the VR lenses in direct sunlight or near a light source. Concentrated light can
burn nearby objects. What are they talking about? If these lenses are facing a certain
way, I can burn my house down? All right. What about warning three? No. All right. So let
me see. These are dangerous apparently. Don't look directly at the sun. All right. Look at
this. You got, I don't know. I know we're not doing this yet, but just look at this.
Look at this image on the left here. That looks like a superpower. That like looks cool
enough to, you know what I mean? That looks like somebody's shooting fire out of their eyes.
Is that really possible? All right. Well, there they are. Is that the only thing that's in
there? There's something else in here. I have to test it. Maybe. Maybe, but no, it's, it's,
the sun's gone. This, it's, it's not that, no, I don't have, I don't have a direct sunlight here.
Try to like do it like over here and like beam over here. It's too bad it's not like
noon. I don't think this is not for anything. All right. So what do we need? We need a sheet
A. I'm going to move this out of the way now. There's nothing else in the box. I'm
going to put it back in here though just to keep it safe because it's dangerous.
I remember the sun. No, I mean the sun's not at its peak right now. It is currently, it's 4 30,
4 30 p.m. Pacific daylight time. So it means the sun is no longer, it's going down. The sun
doesn't hit this side anyways. All right. Here's A. A. No, not that one. It's another, it's,
it's A2. So it's this one. All right. I'm going to move this shit out of the way.
Get the blind out of here before I cause a fucking huge problem. Lick the cardboard. You guys,
I ain't doing any of that shit. So here is the main piece here. So we're going to move
this big piece here. This big one, the yellow one. Punch it out. I know you guys, I know
you guys missed those satisfying noises like this one. I know you guys missed those satisfying
noises. All right. It's a great big yellow one and then I'm assuming we're just going to
punch it around other pieces of the sheet later. Okay. Don't forget, if you have any trouble,
you can use the back button. Yep. All right. These goggles will be your window into a whole
new world. They're pretty important. So let's make sure to make them right. Don't screw it
up. Be careful not to mix up the front and the back. Pay attention to the screen so that
you always have the correct side up like that. That's correct. No mistakes allowed. I don't
make mistakes when I play this. Make sure you have plenty of space when working on big
pieces. It might help to put away any pieces you don't need for now. Yeah, I'm good.
I got this. I got this completely. All right. Flip it over. Before we start folding,
take a good look at where the fold lines are. Right. Okay. They're all over the place here.
Yeah. When making fold lines, try to crease the whole length firmly with both hands. I know.
This is our first fold. Okay. Both hands. Crease it right here. Ready? First fold of the
evening. Hey, I want to, nevermind. That's good. That's creased. I didn't even do the
right one. I didn't even do the right one. Not paying attention. It's this one.
Already did it wrong. You already did the wrong fold. Don't make any mistakes, kids.
Just make a mistake on the first fold. Looks good. Good job. Yeah. That's nice and creased.
Now for the two sides. Both these come up. I think all of them. I'm just going to do
them all this way. I'm going to punch out this shit too. All right. Nice and tight.
I got to fucking don't do that. I'm going to make, every time I start to make a room of mess,
it just stays a mess forever. And I always talk about how I'm going to clean it and I never,
ever do. Ever. What do you mean ruin it? What did I do? What are you talking about?
I had to punch the holes out. What do you mean ruin it? The long use ball. Okay. That
one and then the, yeah, right here. I didn't, how did I fuck it up? What are you talking
about? How is it fucked up? I didn't do anything wrong. These both fold in and then the tabs go.
And then I believe this is going to, ooh, this is where it gets tricky. Oh, ruined. Oh,
it's ruining it. Looks good. This looks good too. This fucking shiatsu. So that, then these tabs
go down like that. Push that out. Destroying it. You guys have never built a fucking labo
before. You have no idea. How many of you have built a labo before? Show of hands. None of you.
You know how they say, oh man, yeah, I, streamer, influencer. Yeah, I played labo and I,
I mean, like a lot of people really thought it was cool and they bought it. Like a bunch of
you guys bought it. I don't think any of you bought it. I've done this like fucking five
times. You probably, maybe three of you have bought one. Like it doesn't do anything.
Paid off. Wait, did I not do this one? These tabs fold, right? Am I doing the folds wrong? I
better not be. Did I ever broke it? It's over. All right. If one piece breaks, I quit.
These come up. Those ones fold over. Now we have to get the glass in here. Okay.
So then that comes over here. Get that out of direct sunlight. Don't touch that.
Here we go again. I need to know. I need to know. I'm going to look at a light
just quickly. Are you in there, lenses? Come on out. Sup. Hi there. We're the VR lenses. Good to
meet you. Sorry for all the warnings. Please don't peel off the film on the lenses.
Sorry for all the warnings. You are real. Try to avoid touching the round lenses themselves.
They need to be nice and clean. I think I already touched them a bunch. Okay. Behold
the VR lenses. Time to attach these guys to the big piece we creased before.
All right. Hold on. Where did they go? So don't, but don't take this off. All right. So don't
peel that off. So this is going over here. Bring it over to the side with the tabs we let standing
up and slot it in from below. What? Like this? Okay. So those tabs are up, right? I did that,
right? I'm not touching the lenses. I have not touched the lenses one time. Now let's make
a quick check. Does everything look the same on the screen? Yeah. Yeah. It does. I'm gonna
have to lick those lenses clean. Remove. Oh God. Remove these two pieces from sheet B.
Already going to B. Which ones? The two canisters? Lick them. You guys are fucked.
All right. Take out the middle. Let's punch them in your view so you can see how cool
it looks. All right. Good. So these are both, these are identical. So then these go on
sides like this. Hey, we want action too. Use these on the round holes as guides
here to line everything up perfectly. The black side should be facing up like this. Okay.
The stream's over. Oh, because I ripped a little bit. It doesn't matter. You're not
going to fucking see this. It's going to be on my head. I'm going to let they fold.
Oh fuck. Get out the bag with the special parts. Are we going to rubber band this? No.
Here's the special bag. Don't look. Don't look this directly in the sun.
Do not put this up to your eye. It'll fucking burn your house down. Don't do it.
All right. Two of the gray washers. There's a lot of gray washes in here. Just two of them.
There's a bag within a bag. Only Nintendo. And Lego. And every other company that makes
the small, loseable parts. Okay. Two washers. Got them. Now what? I gotta put the seat
down. This is killing me. I'm already sweating. It's fucking hot. I'm going to go like turn the AC
on. All right. Two of the gray washers. Punch it through here. Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait.
One after the slip the holes in the pieces of the sticky Audi bits. Wait.
Slip the holes in the pieces over the sticky Audi bits on the sides of the VR lenses.
Like this. Okay. And then a washer over it. This is where the washer come in. Here goes
nothing. The washer should snap on like this. Like that. I'm not touching the lens. Don't worry.
Don't freak out. I'm not touching the lens. God damn it. Get on there. All right. I did
touch the lens this time. I'm touching all over the lens. I swear to God. I can't.
Oh no. Oh my God. Why is this so fucking hard to do? That's the right side.
You don't understand. It's not working. Oh, they really went down in quality, didn't they?
Says the vehicle. I don't understand. Guys, it's supposed to just snap on. It's supposed to snap
on. It's not on. It's not on. I'm not too weak. It's just, it's not cut. I got it. It's
not cut right. It's not cut right. I got a defect. You want me to prove that? Look at that.
You want to prove my defect? Look at, look at, look at the defect that I have.
I am defective, as you can see. It's warped. Same thing on the other side. Great. Go back.
I did it. No, I didn't do it wrong any time. No, that's correct. Same thing on the other side.
And that snaps in. So he's going to lock it in. See if it's as difficult to do this one.
This one doesn't look warped. Done. In one, in one second. This one not warped.
Let's make sure it's on there. Good. Not even warped. All right, so that's in there now. That's
done. I've got like sediment on my face. What are we doing down here? All right. Looks good.
We're going to fold it over. The VR lenses are fully attached. This piece is taking up a lot
of space. Let's fold it up a bit to be more compact. So this comes up. So we go like that
and then like this. And that comes down here like that. Okay, we're making a McDonald's
Happy Meal. Tuck the cardboard underneath the plastic right here. You'll need to do
this again later, so remember it well. Like that. Okay, it's in. And with that,
the VR lenses are ready. They are? Phew, that was quite the complex piece to start with,
but we're not done yet. Maybe we ought to take a quick break. You got it. So how does this go?
Like this? All right, so that's that. Let's go two out of four. Windrate. Yeah, I gotta windrate
real quick. All right, so if I can move this out of the way. Let's get this in a spot
where I know where it is. Right over here. I was gonna throw that, but that would be
better to do. All right, so let's get B, sheet B again. And we do the big piece.
Whole thing. Can you get into my car? I don't know what that means. All right,
is this the only one we need? Just B. This is gonna be a pretty complex shape,
apparently. So I gotta punch out a lot of this crap. Hold on. So this is nothing. This is
just a big three. Three. And then the middle stays in. Now this stays in. This pops out.
He said ear. Oh, sorry. My eyes aren't that good. It's hard for me to see all the way over
there. Here comes the counting joke. We all think it's so funny to count. One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve. It's my favorite. I love it.
So we've got this is good. Everything's done. Okay, this will form the slot into
which we insert the console itself. Lay it out printed side up and look at these fold lines
in the middle. I see them. So this goes across this. Is this is this foldable? This
doesn't look like it folds. I guess it does. Okay, then is volume too low? Yeah,
that's better, right? Is that like a little better? No, not really. It's fine. I'll turn
it down later. Don't worry. I'll panic go back and forth, lowering and increasing the volume over
the next four hours. All right, then this one comes up this way. This is a tricky one.
This is tricky, guys. All right, so that's done. And that's done. So we got these two
folded up. We should do these flaps at the ends too. Both flaps? Yeah. You're in the
midst of dealing with finals. Well, good luck. Hopefully you ace them. Hopefully you get
at least a B minus. These come up? Yeah, the whole thing does. My eyes are getting so bad.
Hope these tabs go up. Of course they do. Two? That should be it. Now we're going to use the
sponge stickers from the bag. Sponge stickers? Ah, this thing here. I dropped something.
That's the core. Fuck, there's wine on it. Oh, I can't like get over there. Hold on.
There's no way to get this reliably without causing a problem. There's three different
problems here. There's like my ass in this camera. There's like fall over table.
Okay. Why do you wear short shorts? These are not short shorts. They're regular shorts.
I'm just sitting down like a normal human. They're just shorts and I'm sitting. Sorry,
I don't have like shorts that go down to my ankles. A bunch of fucking prankers
pranking me all the time. All right, that is what I need. So then I get to tear these off.
These stickers are going to stop the console from slipping around. It doesn't matter if they're
a little wonky. Put all these on here. There are eight spots to place the stickers and they're
very, they're helpfully numbered. Pay close attention to the markers as we place them.
So just put smoothing the piece out to make sure it's nice and flat will help the
stickers sit properly. Right? Well, you just made me fold the whole fucking thing. So
that's not going to happen. First up are the smaller stickers. There's smaller ones.
Start with the spot. Oh, I can't see. So I have to tear this off. Do what? Is it tear
off nice and clean? It does. Okay. All right. So we just align these up. So it goes like
that, like this. Oh, I'm going to fuck this whole thing up. So it goes like halfway on.
All right. Here we go. Can't screw it up. I only got one. There are no extras in here.
It's like this. Right? Right? Yeah. That looks good. Yeah. Now that's, that's perfectly fine.
That's perfect. You couldn't ask for a better, but the sticky stuff on the edge of that,
though. Okay. Yeah. So you're going to fold it over. Fold over the sticky sides like that.
I was going to say that wouldn't make any sense. Yeah. They were kidding when they
said this is going to take a while. That's going to do that with, I'm assuming one, two, three,
four. Let's just see. One, two, three, right? Three and four together here. Okay. So one,
two, three, four. Let's just get this done nice and quick. Not too quick though,
because I don't want to ruin it. Somebody's gave community subs like an hour ago.
Uh, Dr. Steen. Thanks for the five community subs. 20 minutes ago. It's hard for me to see.
Oh God. Good DZ. No. Those are from last night. No, they're not. That's like 18 minutes ago.
I've been streaming for like, I've been streaming for like 30 minutes. I can't wait
till you guys get to see this. We're going to experience this together. It's going to be so
much fucking fun. I cannot wait. I didn't even sleep last night because I knew how much fun
this is going to be. It's like Christmas. You're waiting for Santa. You're waiting for Santa.
Santa's not here yet, but he will be, he will be in like six hours. I can't get this off.
I can't get this one off. I probably looked like so ugly right there. All right. So I'm
doing this right, right? So this goes here and this hit, wait, but has it fold over?
Or it just doesn't? Huh? How is this? Oh, holy shit. I almost just messed it up.
I was going to put it over here. It's supposed to go like there. I almost just blew that.
That would have been really bad. It's Nintendo Labo. So guys, I gotta tell you something.
I went back to the dentist, right? I had another dentist appointment today. I was there
earlier and you have no fucking idea how fucked up this was. So I'm in the chair,
right? I don't want to mess this up. Where does this one go? No, it's not that. Put it over here.
They both go side by side. Three, four. Yep. Okay. Three. And let's get this other one. Four.
Then these, these pieces of, these ones are bigger somehow. Oh, 15 turtles. They make
these things so hard to fucking remove. I think that looks good, right? Both these fold over,
I hope. All right. Then what do I do with the big ones? So these are longer and they go
just across the whole thing. All right. What are you saying? Seinfeld? What was the dentist
story? Oh, you can't believe it. So how about the chair? No, that's a joke because I've had,
I've had three dentist stories in the last two weeks. Tell the rest of the dentist story.
So how about the dentist? All right. That's correct, right? Yeah. Too long one. Then here
and here. How the fuck did that go? I have no idea. And? No, there is no and. I've already
told it. I told it two days ago. The joke is I have a third dentist story. But you know,
that's, that's just the punch line. There is no punch line. Oh, here's another dentist story
incoming. There is no punch line. I wasn't even making a joke. I was making a reference
to me having problems with the dentist every day. I need closure. There is, why do you need
closure on a non-existent story that didn't happen? All right. Speed it up. These go
across here and then here. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Yes. I've got bad teeth.
What did you say? Have you seen these? I can bite. I can take a Jolly Rancher guys and
go like this and I can bite right through it. I was that guy in middle school and high school
that had the fucking steel teeth. You guys remember now and laters? I used to just put
them in and just stop chewing and people would fucking gasp and freak out and like my teeth are
gonna get ripped out. Nope. We'll be done with the tedious part here in a second.
That explains a lot actually. Does it though? What does that explain?
I'm, I feel like that doesn't explain a whole lot. I feel like there's way more to
that story. Where's the other one? I'm missing one. Where'd it go? Where's eight? Where did
eight go? Check the table crease? No. Where is it? One, two, three, four, five. Check the
VOD. No. There's one more. What the fuck did I do with it? Christ. I bent it too.
They look exactly the same. Give me a break. All right. Now I have to like move this back
because the table is now out of the view. I need to go back here. There we go. No,
I'll get a little closer to you guys. Hey. He doesn't know. I don't know very much. You're
right. See you have this, you have this like periscope right now. You can like see everything.
You can like zoom in and be like, what's that stain? I don't know there's a stain on my
shirt. I have no idea. Did I eat like a hot dog with mustard on it earlier? Yes, I did.
I don't know. I may have dropped something. I don't care. I don't know. All right. So now
these turn over and fold in. All right. We can finally be done with this tedious sticker game.
That and then like this. Come on. All right. Done. Finally. That took a million years.
The whole thing's done. Fold it over. So is a hot dog a sandwich? No, I would call it a sub.
I mean a sub would. Is a sub a sandwich? Sub sandwich, right? I guess it is a sandwich.
But a lot of people tell you it's not a sandwich, that it's a hoagie or it's a grinder.
It's not a sandwich. It's a hoagie. It's a grinder, right? Hot dog is not. Well, hot dog is.
It is. What happens here now? Well, I played Zelda VR. Well, this is not my switch. So I
don't. My switch is dead. Like permanently dead. Unless I did something wrong, which I
know I didn't. All right. So this folds all the way over and then attaches together like this.
I'm assuming that the arrows line up and line up the markings and push it in firmly.
Once it slides in like this, how the fuck does that go in? I guess like that.
Are taco sandwiches? I mean they could be. If you want to break it down by it just it's
very definition. That one's in. All right. That's good. So that's done. Is everything
lined up perfectly like this? Make sure your piece matches up. Yeah, I think so. Right.
What do you guys think? Yeah. Yeah, it is. Flour tortilla. Flour. I mean, I don't know.
I'm not going to. I'm not going to get in a fight over this. So give the slot a check
from the side too. If it looks a little at all wonky, just straighten it up. I mean,
it's a little wonky. A little bit. This looks like I'm about to put a hard drive in here.
Here's my new keyless hard drive bay. Toolless hard drive. All right. This is wonky, but it'll
do. Does it really matter? I got a fucking Vive set up. Do you think I'd give a shit about
this being wonky by like 5%? I got a Vive right here. All right. That's good. Stand it
back up. And with that, how does this connect to here? Let's see if your console slot does
its job. Now is also a good time to straighten your slot out if it's gotten crooked at all.
So I have to slide that into here and make sure it fits. Ow. And it does. That fits pretty
good. Snug. Fits in there. So it can come out nice and easy too. That's a perfect fit.
Nice. Let's stick that back in. All right. It should come back on the screen here in a second.
All right. Let's go. Not on my screen though. Shit's too loud. That's better. All right. So
that works. Now, where do I put this from here? This is just porn music. This is not porn
music. What are you talking about? This is like arcade claw machine music. This is not
pornography music. This is the song you hear playing over and over again inside of every
Dave and Buster's you've ever been inside ever in your life. But that's not true. They play
like, they play the hits. They play the hits. I'm wrong. I'm sorry. All right. What
are you B? Yeah. What the fuck are you watching? What are you talking about?
That's porn music. What does this one do? Dude, I'm starting to feel like a little
drunk right now. Maybe I should like lick something that's a small cartridge related
thing. Oh, that'd be like fucking funny. All right. So let's go. What's this piece for?
Your nose, of course. Leave the printed side facing up as you crease these fools.
Okay. All right. Crease this up there. Any other piece? I wish I had a nose.
So this is going to like slip on like this. I think my nose is too big for this.
Yeah. I've got like a schnoz. So I don't know if this is going to work.
We'll see. We will find out very shortly. So that goes up like this. Okay. Look,
you want to see how disgusting of a human I really am? I just like put this on my
nose for a second. Who's that? Who's that villain? There's a villain. There's a bad guy
in like comic books that's always covered in like grease. What's his name? There's like a
greasy villain. I don't know. The Silver Surfer? The Silver Surfer is like kind of just covered
in oil, right? Yeah, I would be the Silver Surfer. He's fucking cool too, man. He like
skis around and blows up planets, right? That's like his MO, right? That's what he does.
No, no, no. That's Iceman. What does the Silver Surfer do? What is the Silver Surfer? What's
the difference between Silver Surfer and Iceman? They're the same. I don't, I can't. If you
had like a crime lineup and you told me to pick out the Silver Surfer and you had Iceman,
you had Flame Guy and you had like Colossus, I don't know if I'd be able to pick him out.
It would be hard. Iceman, I mean, what? He's like chrome. Yeah. What does he do?
He's silver and he surfs. Isn't he a fantastic four villain? No wonder those movies have been
so bad. What a cursed franchise. Wait, okay. What the hell's going on? It goes this way
and then you do it the other way. So it's that and then that side. Yep. Fantastic four.
We got, okay, what is this? Let's get the smooths. No more stickers. I don't want to
put more stickers on here. We only need one sticker for now. Thank God. Was this,
is this to like determine where you are in the room? Wait, don't do this yet.
First fold the piece firmly in half like that. So that's that. This,
they're, yes, they are lined up perfectly. This part needs to be neatly lined up. It's easy
to get it wrong. Be careful. That's in there. That's perfect. Now using the star symbol as a
guide, apply the first half of the sticker and then it wraps around. You kind of like
an adhesive tape. All right, I guess, is that what this is for? To be adhesive tape?
These are thin too. Oh boy, this is really thin. Make sure you guys can see.
Fuck. Damn it. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Got it. And then fold it over the other side.
No air bubbles. Good. Yeah, so it is just like adhesive tape. Everybody calm down. Stream
over, folks. Time to go home. What? Why are you going home? Don't go home. We've got,
we've got a whole bottle of wine here. Are you going to go home? No, you stay
or go to a different channel that you enjoy. See you later. Don't leave me. Don't leave me here.
If you leave, I'm just a guy folding cardboard drinking wine. You can't leave.
Don't leave me here. I'm just like a sicko if you all leave. All right, flip the piece
over and show it on screen and lift this part up. Okay. Like the second you guys all leave,
I just become the weirdo. What'd you do on a Saturday night? I just drank and played with
a kid's cardboard toy for six hours. Oh, you didn't like, you did? Yeah. Yeah. Don't
you have a girlfriend? Yeah. Where was she? I don't know. You know, I can't, no, this
can't be like that. All right. So we just slide this into here. This is kind of an
awkward way to do that. That looks good. Check the closet. No, I already did that before the
stream starts. She's not in there. Stand it straight. Time to stand the whole piece up
nice and sprayed. That's the way. Okay. So it does stand on its own. I'm gonna get it straight
like this. There you go. Okay. The nose piece is complete. So how does my nose go in here?
Like this? This hurts. I'm just a rooster. I guess it's supposed to be like that. The
bridge of my nose is so fucked up. Those are gonna be painful. All right. Fit the nose into
the main lens frame. Open up the top and lay it out flat. All right. We gotta do some surgery
here. Excuse me. Make sure you get that line over there. I don't want that to go down.
So then this, how does this open? So this goes like this. So you pop it out here
and then lay it out like that. Now move the nose piece into position, into position,
into position, into position. Why was I saying that so weird? Like that. Oh, there's a little
slot there. But now for this part, it'll be easiest if you hold the lens piece as shown.
Yeah. Slide the red tab with the smooth sticker right into the slot in between the lenses.
Let's check from the other side too. Just look firmly inserted. So it just goes in here.
That goes like this. And that's it. It's in. That's in. No, it's not. Fuck. How do I keep
it in there? Let's check from the other side too. Just look for, it's not firmly inserted.
Show auto. No, no. I'm building a VR headset. No, we're not going to show auto. No auto.
I'm not showing auto. Show auto. Yeah. Where are we going to put him? Where's he going to go?
There's no room for him in here. No, I'm not showing. I'm not. All right. I'll show auto in
like two hours. Okay. How does this go in? Let's add the console slot. So this is, it
goes like this and then spins this way. Just like that. Down here. This is ridiculous.
How am I going to see this? It's two little feet should slide neatly into place in here.
Is this the wrong way? All right. It's two little feet are in there now. In. Come on,
get in there. Is it in? It's two little feet go in and then now lift the middle flap and
join it to this slot at the top of the nose piece. It might be tough, but push it all the
way in. Okay. So is this even in there? So this, I can't even tell if it's even in.
I think it is. All right. So then this piece comes up. I didn't fold this fucking piece. I
didn't fold this piece backwards. Why didn't somebody tell me I didn't do that? Nobody
told me I didn't fold it. Is it in? Oh, okay. Now it's in. Is that good? Oh,
no. God damn it. The whole thing came apart. A bunch of trained engineers to put this shit
together with one hand. Get back in there. And this feet go in there. All right. All
right. All right. All right. All right. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
It's in. It's in. Done. That's it. That's it. And hey, Otto can fix it. Otto's not coming up
here. Can you see the little, can you see the console slots, little feet poking out the side?
Yes. Yes, I can. Yes. See? And on the other side. Yes, I can see the little thing popping
out. Oh, and the bottom of the slot is still properly connected, right? Always best to make
sure. Yeah. Yeah. Yes. Great. Then let's finish this thing up. First, roll the lens piece over
onto its front. Okay. If it lines up perfectly with this fold here, the next part should be
a piece of cake. It does. I would call that, I would call that perfect. If I were going to
get a ruler out here. Lift up the great big top flap and tuck it under the plastic here
like we did before. Okay. So then tuck that in like that. So that's in and secure. Now
secure the sides. So slide it down and tab it. Do the same thing on the other side, right?
This happened here. Tab it. All right. Same thing on this side. Slide it in. Get that
tab in there. Beautiful. Accomplishments. We're making them. We're making them.
Now before we make sure that the whole flap is still neatly tucked into place.
It is. That's, that's good to go. Close that other side. And are these corners tucked into
place too? Yes. Yes, they are. Is this slot still a neat rectangle? Yeah. I think so.
Now stand up our goggles. Here's a little tip you want to remember.
Why is there water on this? It's not okay. Freaked out. Master hand. What is it? Do you
see this symbol on the top right? Yes. Try giving it a little tap. Okay. Is this supposed
to do something? I don't think that does anything. I think, I think I'm just doing
that for no reason. The VR goggles are complete. You guys get, you guys get the
fuck in there. Hope you know that. We're going to, you're getting the fuck in here.
You can experience VR for the first time. That's the bulk of the work done. Nice job. All
I need to know is build an important little accessory, which is what? Three to four. You
mean three more pieces. Make it a safety cap. Oh great. Do I need this? What if I just don't
build this? Who cares? Remove this one piece from A. Like what if I just don't give a shit
about safety right here? Just that one? That's it? That's it, right? Punch this out.
Safety cap. I wonder what this is for. I wonder. That's that. Punch this shit out.
Push this side. These are both out, right? Yep. All right. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good.
It's going to be a hell of a vacuum job in here later. All right. That's good. Move
this out of the way. I don't think I need these anymore, but I'll put it here and
definitely need this. Don't want to lose this one. I am stuffing my legs underneath this
table right now because I have to put this all the way down. I need a different chair.
I need a specific Nintendo Labo seat. Put on real pants. These are J. Crew shorts. They're
very nice and they were extraordinarily expensive. They were more than like 80 bucks.
These are fantastic pants. They can do anything. They can go anywhere.
You can wear these wherever the fuck you want. It's all made up. None of that was real.
God, these are fucking Walmart. They were on the clearance rack for like four bucks.
All right. Let's go. J. Crew CEO in the chat. I'm getting wine, love. That's how you know
it's really starting to kick off here. All right. Time to put together the safety cap.
This accessory will make sure the console doesn't fall out while you're in the...
Okay. I wasn't going to make this. Oh yeah. Who cares your shit? I don't need
a safety cap. I thought it meant like my safety. All right. Rich streamer.
Like that. I'm going to take this outside and just try to like
burn something. I'm going to like burn some grass. Just like I'm going to take
one blade of grass to see what I can do. Don't do that at home. Don't do that because
I said to do it. Fold this. Do I have to start putting a disclaimer on every stream
that says just don't listen to a word I say. Jerma lied about Ace Attorney. Thank you for
the 10 community subs. Jerma lied about Ace Attorney. That's 10 subs. Thank you so much
for the 10 subs. I didn't lie about Ace Attorney. I told you the truth actually.
I told you the truth about Ace Attorney. How is that a lie? I said that's not a lie. Oh my
God. Somebody asked me about what happened to Ace Attorney and I very truthfully, very
transparently told them and everybody like three times. Ace Attorney is not I don't even
know why am I explaining this a third time. Ace Attorney is a series that I did not think
I thought it was a different kind of game. And I said I was going to play it off stream
and see if I wanted to stream it and then we'll see. But I kind of hung it up a
little bit though. It's not happening. So that's not lying. That's me telling the
truth. That's just the truth. That's me telling you a truthful statement. A lie would be I'm going
to play Ace Attorney tomorrow and I don't play Ace Attorney at all. And you say where's Ace
Attorney? And I go I didn't say I was going to play Ace Attorney. That's a lie. The text
game Resident Sleeper. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what I'm doing. Guys,
I don't know what I'm doing any day. Okay. If you think I got a plan. I plan out very
specific stream. But like drink wine and play Labo. Kind of just happened like six days ago.
It's like oh yeah let's just do that. We'll do that on like fucking Saturday. I don't even
think I got a plan. The dunk tank is a plan. That's going to happen. That takes a while.
Day-to-day basis. I don't even know what fucking I'm eating for breakfast.
All right. All these are done. And then we're going to fold the whole thing up.
So like this. Connect this and this. Weird man. This is weird. Really. Don't embarrass
me here. Come on. Get in there. Don't embarrass me. Don't embarrass me please.
Come on. They make fun of me every time I stream. Don't let them make fun of this.
Come on. Jerma you're bad at that game. Jerma you suck. I died again. Come on. Don't let
them do this. Come on. Come on. They make fun of me every time I play a game. Not this
time. Thank god. Pointing and laughing at you this time. That's not what you said.
Pointing and laughing at you this time. I don't know where that came from. This time.
All right. Safety cap's done. Let's practice putting on the safety cap.
So the safety cap just slides down on top of here. Like that. All right. My mom has
a shirt like that. Okay. What? Anything else? Is there anything else I need to know?
My mom has a shirt like that. Okay. It's a purple shirt. The whole website you're on
right now is a purple t-shirt. Okay. Don't think it. Don't be fooled. It looks great.
Take the safety cap off. And put it over there for now. Okay. Looks good.
When you're playing with the VR goggles alone, always make sure to put the safety cap on.
Okay. Goggles and safety cap are ready. There's one more. What's the last piece here?
We're going to add the console and the Joy-Con. Oh, this is where we're going to get to play.
Oh my god. I'm fucking, I cannot wait. You won't be able to use TV mode for this part.
Take the console out of the dock. All right. Hold on. This cannot be played in TV mode.
Let me experience it first. Hold on. So you, I'm going to do it first and then you guys
can do it after. This is going to be fucking awesome. How do you capture without the dock?
I point it into the lens over there and I walk around with you guys. That's hot.
That's the only way. All right. Let me, hold on. I got to put the screen on so I don't
fucking embarrass myself somehow. All right. Hold on. Is that here? Okay. All right. So
without further ado. Never mind. All right. So then how does this work?
So now make sure you have the both Joy-Cons. Sorry. Hold on. I'll get this back on here.
Camera. Okay. Sorry. Just wanted to make sure nobody could say anything bad about me.
All right. So here I have the left and the right controller. Let's turn the volume up
so you can at least hear it. Maybe it's just a song. So who cares? All right.
I think I have to attach these. The time has come to remove the final seal. Done, done,
done. Oh, I'm taking up. I'm taking this off. Okay. Go ahead. Peel off the film.
Yeah. Wow. Whoa. That's weird. That's really weird. That's strange. I can't even describe
what that looks like. All right. That's off. I'll let you guys see it in a minute.
It's my turn with the VR. Okay. Let's fill in on how to hold the VR goggles while using them.
Always grip them firmly with both hands like this and of course you'll want to make sure
you're holding them the right way. Okay. Finally let's practice looking through the
VR goggles. I don't need to practice that. Okay. Let's slip it in there. Let's try it.
Come on. And with that we can finally say the VR goggles are ready to roll. Let's go.
Whole new virtual world awaits. All right. Let's get it in there. I get to do it first.
Okay. Here we go. Wow. That's so cool. All right. Hold on. Let me move this.
I gotta pick something. Hold on. I gotta pick. This actually hurts my head.
All right. What do you guys think? Dinosaur Safari sounds fucking awesome to me.
There's Mario Brothers. Mario Paint. I think Dinosaur Safari. Put on the safety. All right.
Safety goggles are on. Dinosaur Adventure. Okay. Are you guys good? I'm going to do it first.
What the fuck? Holy shit. What the fuck? That's a T-Rex. Oh my god.
That's a doctor. Oh my god. This is more realistic than Vive. Whoa. Oh my god. He's
right here. He's literally right in front of me. Hey. You guys gotta see this shit. Seriously.
Wow. No, no, no, no, no. Drive. Drive the car. Drive, drive, drive.
Drive the car. Drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive. He's behind us.
Whoa. Holy fuck. Now this is Stegosaurus. Stegosaurus and then the T-Rex. This is
called Fight of the Century. Jesus. He's so cute. Who's that? It's hard to tell. I can't see.
There we go. No, no. I was blurred out for a little bit.
All right. How about that? I had to quit on. I got disconnected. Oh, wait. Oh, what's this one?
This is called Dino Adventure. They have like at least two or three dinosaur related games.
This is so cool. This is a good person here. Oh, I can see it. It's up there.
That's a Pterodactyl. Oh my god. The Pterodactyl is huge. Who's that? Oh, it's a Triceratops.
I didn't know they eat it. I didn't know they eat plants. Holy fuck. That's amazing.
I thought that they ate meat. You guys getting this? Watch the turtle.
I'm not going to. I'm not going to put on like the turtles having sex. I mean, I was going to
fucking be in there and watch like the turtles having sex thing. But like, come on. I'd like to
keep my Twitch TV channel. All right. So here's the real question though. Don't make me. Hold on.
What is it? What's it called? What is it actually called? It's called like life,
life source or something. Life scenes. What was the actual name of the television show?
I'm not going to type into Google turtle sex. Are you out of your mind? This might be worth
doing it. I need to like be able to hear it. In nature, it's rare to form such a life long.
What's this called? This is called nature. Oh, a nature documentary.
List of circling. Oh, turtles. Before she accepts his advances.
Oh, wow. Is there a whale over there? Can you guys see the fishes?
Their first breath together is the beginning of several hours of mating.
Several hours. Oh, well, I don't have to hold on as tight as he can
to keep her all to himself. Interesting. Unfortunately, they have company.
What's that? Another male. What's another thing he can to separate the pair and mate
with the female himself. There he goes. He's he's coming up to the behind the other guy.
What? That's the soft vulnerable parts.
He's punching him in the head. He's like punching him in the face over and over again.
Out of his rival.
Wait, what? What's going on over here? The female is struggling now with the extra weight on her
back. She will need to surface to take a breath. There's a turtle over here. There's
two more turtles that way. Another male. He's over here. What's he doing?
This is fucking crazy. More competition. What? There's like three. Whoa. And here's another.
All right, I don't want to. I want to get out. I want to get back to Super Mario Brothers.
Out. I want to get out. I want to get out. I don't want to see this anymore. This is like
three that fight each other. Now the female has they're like fighting each other locked on
her back and it's twice as hard for her. Now we're done with that bit. It's over. He wasn't
wearing the safety cap. I'm just imagining like if somebody was actually in VR and like just
watching that. It's like I say that. I say that. But aren't there like specific VR apps
where you just like watch people? Like oh I'm just gonna sit here and just like stare at
people. That's so weird. Like I don't know. Like I can't. VR porn. No man like that's too
fucking much. I don't know. That's too weird for me. And I'll tell you a couple of reasons why.
Listen to me. This is important. Story time. This is not a story. This is not like it
really happened. But just listen. If you're 18 plus conversation coming up here. Okay so
if you're not like you're not of the age fucking 18 then close. Just get out of here.
Leave. Just leave. Come back in like 20 minutes. If you have a VR helmet on your head and you're
going to watch pornography and you're going to have the VR helmet headphones and your hands
out here with like the controllers and you're gonna be like you know you'd better be alone
in the fucking house. Better be. You better live alone or you better be certain that your
roommates or your parents are not going to come home. That scares the absolute shit out of me.
And I mean I don't I haven't done that in VR. I haven't. All right let's move on from that.
That's too scary. What if like you're just sitting there enjoying adult material and you're
locked. I've been locked in. I've had people come in this room and I didn't even know they
were here. Imagine how fucking awful that would be and the embarrassment that would entail.
If you did not know somebody opened the door and there is no like whoa hey man knock once knock
for once in your life. No no no no no you're just immersed. You don't even know that they're
there. They could walk in and you're just whoa. Okay I would never in a million years
in a million fucking years. Never. If you're gonna do that and you're gonna enjoy adult
material and you're like you know an adult you're an adult. Before you before you start
just go peek outside and make sure there's no cars in the driveway. Please for your own sake.
I'm just saying. Anyways let's see what's in here. I don't think I was supposed to put it
in yet. And I don't know have like a security camera pointed at that because okay if you're
if you're in if you're doing something in particular that certain thing in particular
we're not going to name anything. This could be anything. If you're in the headset you're
in VR you're fucking sitting in your chair. I don't even know where the hell you'd be.
You need to be you need to be able to get out quick. How do you why does that even exist?
How is that even possible? You get you gotta have if you're gonna do that not only check
that there's no cars in the driveway you're gonna get a nest cam and every like six minutes
like have it pointed at the driveway like okay nobody here no okay you can't lock your door
either because if you lock your door people are gonna be like what's he doing what are they
doing in there? You lock your door it's even worse. Why did that bring it into the bathroom?
Hey what are you doing man? You're bringing your whole computer into the bathroom.
Yeah yeah yeah. But why is that? I didn't do my taxes yet. I'm gonna do my test
and I'm gonna be in there for like two hours. Oh you do your taxes in the bathroom? Yeah
yeah I do my taxes in the bathroom and now I'm gonna take a shower too. I'm gonna
I'm gonna be in the shower too. Jesus Christ look at this. I used to do that. Guys okay not not
just no no no anytime I wanted to hide something in the I was doing in the bathroom I would turn
the shower on and turn on the like the water too for like 10 but no no listen listen listen
it was only for like no no no not wasting water listen to me I would turn it on so
people thought I was going in the shower but I was really I was going to the bathroom I was like
actually going to the bathroom and people I don't know I don't know but it's like when you know
just start dating Kim you know you don't want Kim to know that you're in there going to
the bathroom I'm like taking a shit so like I'm just going to the shower and then you
would go to the bathroom as fast as you can like in eight seconds and then like turn the
shower off oh you guys gotta see this let me do it first for real this works weirdly enough
line up the cursor and tap I wish you get you know we're gonna do this together
it's not fair come here it's not fair you guys should be able to do it too
I may as well just put on it's something else okay it's nothing you can't even see there's
no way you'll see all right might as well just put on like I'm watching like a fucking
tv show in here or something all right I'm gonna give you guys something to listen to
while I play this for like two minutes and more turtles not doing that again
there there you go you don't know what I'm doing in here I'm in the bathroom oh this
is crazy move the person using the joycon with the joycon what don't fall off
he's like just a little guy all right you can do get those coins or get those bricks
wait he can shoot too that's so cool this is really cool wow you guys gotta see this shit
hold on I can turn the brightness down just wait all right I'm out of the bathroom
you I will let you see this if it's the last thing I do take the switch out of the case
yeah but that it doesn't need to be in here it really doesn't have to be in there you can just
okay but the what about the experience oh it's pretty good porn music right
look at that hair all right I'm gonna drop the brightness so you can see what the
fuck is going on god damn it oh why can't I open it okay here we go always a little guy
there you look see you guys are doing it well that's all I can really do for you
put out your knock you ever think to knock let's build a blaster what's this look at how there's
so many games to play why can I not mirror this how would you ever why would I ever do this on
stream we're gonna build the blaster and we're gonna um talk about life I don't know
there's so many things that looks at somebody that's cool I can't mirror this though
all right we're gonna do blaster get back in there
wait wait wait what if we just play them I don't maybe maybe don't need to have them on VR
whoa no this is a spoiler this is spoilers I don't see this I doubt this is a spoiler I
don't see any of this I don't stop stop stop stop stop stop I don't see it stop
you can paint it okay be out no I'm looking right at the fucking sun with these on
arts and crafts vr this is the blaster blaster how do I select the goddamn blaster
I want to select the goddamn blaster okay thank you blaster this one's gonna take
like four hours it's gonna be a long stream welcome to the rest of your life but this thing
actually goes like that's cool with rubber bands and stuff I'm excited now don't look
outside with this on what are you a dumbass what if we like pop this up and they put the
camera over the window and they go like would that be funny all right let's make a blaster
that's what you're here for toy con blaster kit look at all this did you ever apologize
to the taco bell worker that you made cry does that mean I made a taco bell worker cry
when how I don't know what you gotta work early oh good night Kim yeah Kim's gotta get
up really early so we got a quiet time good night Kim sweet dreams girl um I have no idea
what you're talking about and I don't remember making anybody cry so that might be a lie
do you ever lied about my VR do you ever lied about age attorney do you ever lied about
playing jammin max yes yes you do do you ever lied about this what about you what did you
lie about how many times have you lied to me there's a lot here okay the core is first
one of the five making the core I'm a dummy thick I don't know what that means all right
I mean the bag's over here I got that all right we need sheet a and these four pieces from
a let me get these out real quick oops do I need that none of them came out I don't know
this is just no it's not broken look it's got the lines on it that means it's not necessary
for a second I thought my mic was gone I was like what I remember gonna lick the cartridge
nope not gonna happen link back to this clip I haven't I got like one and a half glasses
of wine guys this I come on I'm not gonna get shitfaced I'm just gonna fucking enjoy my
wine and build my toy this is a brandy wine this is a bourbon wine it's good stuff
good old grocery store wine drink water I've had plenty of water today and when I take my
first break in like I don't know a little bit I'm gonna have some water I drink responsibly
come on we joke around a lot but I do I drink water I drink plenty of fluids
that's not gonna be good I'd like to be careful about that it's time to be serious you're not
fucking comedian be serious all right so this comes out all the pieces huh so this is just
this is just recycling right right in the recycling bin
good go what am I I'm just like moving my hands around lick it oh yeah okay I'll ban
anybody that says that for at least I'm not kidding six days on the moon or on Mars which
is how long I don't know like fucking an hour punched out let's punch this out how you guys
doing you guys doing good you guys having a good time how's life how's life treating you
guys I'm not gonna lick it stop calling me a coward having a good time good you're having
a good day I'll be having a fucking great day this is gonna take a long time I'm already seeing
how this is gonna be a problem no it's not I got plenty of wine all right let's go don't
forget if you have any trouble you can use the back button uh-huh uh-huh yeah are you
ready to build the sleek toy con blaster first we'll be putting together all important
inside parts grab this piece from the ones you just removed it's got a controller
mark on it the core you guys are curious so then yeah you don't have to tell me every time
I know how to do this stop telling me how to do it not bad okay so this folds up let's get
creasing we'll start with these two fold lines on the front side of the piece give the one
close to you a good bopping yep these two come up and flip it around well those are hard
these are really really tight not bad could be better did we get community subs trin trin art
trin art just gave 10 community subs thank you yourself some trin art thank you trin art
look at his look at this dick hiding posture no it's called table hiding dick posture okay
you guys need to relax it's always gonna be about like a dick all right got a lot of
folds so then wait this has to go back and around the other side too
wait what why is mine not the same color oh no it's all right the whole thing goes across
is he okay it's the same thing i'm fine is he okay i see that okay often when i look over
the chat i'll look over and somebody be like no is he okay yeah i'm doing great are you
doing all right dude is he all right is he okay yeah i think one time you almost
puked on stream i was worried no that was a fake you're talking about this
that's what you're talking about that's exactly what you're referring to i know that because
i did that like two weeks ago i just wanted to make sure i could prove that that was not real
see hey is he okay all right i need to pay attention stop talking about my
penis and puking you have anything else to talk about leave me alone this comes across like this
that's tricky that's a really weird fold but no thank you so much uh to turn off for the
10 community subs always appreciated thank you so much that's incredibly generous of you
and then fold fold fold just fold them all i got it i got it the doorknob is shaking
what you're gonna be fine don't worry look you got me here to protect you
somebody burst through that door and they got the hands like this easy
he's out he's done that's it he's done all right let's go let's fold this one over that
one's done okay and then the whole thing has to come over right like this and then it's up
like that this comes up the whole thing yeah okay and this piece comes down like this into here
that right did that right yeah okay and then flip the whole thing over and then this comes up
so elaborate down and in and this is the core this is the core of gun piece
so that's in and that looks good let's that looks perfect right the holder for the joycon
r is done work with this piece next it'll be the blaster make satisfying sounds pretty
wanted that as well wear pants next time you know you can't tell me what i can and cannot do
if i want to wear bike shorts no like i don't think i can do that yeah you see lots of
creases everywhere the whole thing right stop flexing i'm not flexing on camera i did it
once for a lol moment okay it's literally every single crease start at the top here
damn people are laughing i don't know why but they are laughing oh there you go there's like
there's like haha number 40 not very many more to get to 100 come on guys we can do it if we
put our power together we can do that right every little tab looks good i got them all
okay put all that boop into good use and start building fold piece up long thin box
so this comes up this i'm assuming wraps all the way around yeah uh yeah it comes across and
this probably goes down into here damn it it's tight fold this in and then that piece slides
over okay next part it just makes a little cylinder okay that's easy enough there there
you go now where does that go just get a job at a box factory and stream it that's not
the same i keep pulling the table further and further in here and it's going to be out a box
what does it what does that mean box factory two full lines crease both the lines and then
it's going to come okay up one two all right and this goes like that the tabs on each end of
the cookie will fit nicely into the slots fold the cookie up like so what the cookie
all right so this goes in like that it's the same on both sides right stick it in both tabs in
that's it on that side clicked beautiful jerma give us your end game review we don't talk about
that here no if you talk about any game you ban like literally and i don't want i'm not
fucking around here like you put like end game shit you're gone you're gone like permagon
don't fuck around that's not a joke don't fuck around there mods get the full power here that's
where to go don't fuck around you don't know who's seen it or not don't do that don't you
know you gotta wait at least like six months don't do it i'm not kidding don't do it i'm
that's not a joke i know we talk about joke bans but that's not a joke ban that's a real
one don't do it you'll regret it in like fucking 30 minutes you'll go fuck i'm like
perma band from his channel don't do it don't do it all right uh but now we're gonna talk about
we'll talk about like like six months all right here we go tons more fold lines don't do it
you can regret it trust me the movie is fun and good good wait i'm skipping too much all
right what's going on here fold all these lines there are a lot a little tab there
little tab there it's fun just to do this it's it's relaxing it really just is
little cardboard tabs and shit it's it's fun to do this don't you think you're doing a mom voice
it's fun to do this isn't it it is that's good fun it's relaxing it
yeah that whatever mom trying to convince her children to play a safe fun video game
mom voice jesus god there's no tabs there i think i got them all i did i did all right what's next
the whole thing folds up whole thing folds up and over like that yeah like a little sandwich
and then this holds like wrong side wait what like that folds down tab goes in
i don't know if you do your homework maybe you can play with some nintendo labo
okay i got a call from your teacher today and they said that you threw an orange
today in class man is this fun gonna go ahead and tell me why you threw an orange in your
class it's fun to click these together don't you think you could be doing it right now okay
then time for some aerobics wait what this one's down down and then in you guys are fucked touch
each tuck each leg down and inside the box they should be pressed flat against the sides
all the way in you guys are fucking crazy he's fucked no you're fucked you're fucked
tonight you're fucked not me tonight all right so then we've got this little piece here
these two all right so like this like that yeah so if it's just in one more check before
we combine the bits do the printed markings on yours match the one on screen yes so put it down
oh that's a satisfying fit is it don't tell me that is it wow it is that's very satisfying
actually look at that it's like an ice cream sandwich nice okay cool so we have that core
piece built it looks so snug and cozy in there i wish there was room for me too god i wish i was
in there ta-da this bit's done now but there's still a long long way to go we haven't even
finished step one that's all we've gotten done we made like a we made like a spore car with
feet we made a hippopotamus all right well thanks for coming on guys i'll see uh see
you next week i'm gonna take a week off this is just that's too much i gotta take a week off
all right uh b and c five pieces from b and c looks good right b and c so it's the whole
thing took all the pieces out of b he's wasted i i am not not even close not even close
maybe i should put drunk labo in stream time no give me maybe not give me that
crit uh let's go here i'm wine mom no you have no fucking idea god some of you guys are
fucking out of control like out of control i don't know what to do with you some of you
some of you are out of control what am i i don't know what to do with you angry labo
stream what are you talking about i'm wicked wicked happy all right there's the big one
that just gonna sit here i gotta get both of these two out too one two okay looks good
that one is out of here and which one's on this one this one this one time i mean time
i hope not that would be bad put that away for now all right we got these pieces here
what is it what is this piece gonna be what am i building this is going to be a gigantic
rocket launcher and it started with this this is the piece you start with and this turns into a
like actual blaster cannon so that's cool i'm looking forward to how we can turn this into
that step by step right so we got this piece starting here increasing all these fold lines
with the printed side up check the screen closely don't screw it up okay dad so every
single line is coming up this way every single one i won't mess it up don't worry 50 minutes
until auto why are you counting for that it's one of when i go and break again oh
you want it auto waiting room you'll get it why is he he's gonna come in here and look at
the camera for a second and then leave he's probably in bed with kim right now
baby he's probably sleeping so i can't do that no no auto auto no not getting auto
no he's probably just like lying down with kim no sorry guys no auto that's just the way it's
going to be i don't make the rules i just follow them i mean i i make the rules actually
and then i follow the rules that i put in place for me to follow them so that that's a
rule i made a long time ago that if auto was asleep i'm not going to wake him to get him
on stream he doesn't want to be on camera he's a fragile boy he doesn't he doesn't want to be on
camera what's wrong with you guys what the fuck how do i delete somebody else's message
all right looks good folded oh somebody's gave bits uh trinat gave one thousand three
hundred thirty four bits pinwheel kills germa in end game thanks for the uh 13 bucks cheers
to that more of this dumb shit i'm just gonna hire somebody to do this for me
i'm gonna pay somebody 50 dollars an hour to do this part all right if you like stickers then
i've got good news for you we will need eight of these 50 wow 50 eight of these
i can't even count that high oh fuck this sucks right this is this is where it takes
hey you know the three or four hours to build it this is where it comes from
comes from this tedious shit so that goes over here on the actual crease too
so i'm putting i'm putting them on the creases wait till you guys see this shit that i'm capable
of i fucked it up but let me out of context that sounds really stupid i forgot that it's
not even in the room right now wait till you see what i could do just wait till you guys see
what i'm capable of i forgot in my brain i have knowledge here that you don't have
and you won't have it for about maybe like another 30 but wait till you fucking see what
i'm capable of come on it's a little crooked but it's okay actual anime character you have
no idea ever since i was a kid people underestimated me all right what i don't need
this one oh god damn it what i thought it said i needed eight stickers god they underestimated me
what it said i needed eight what the fuck man really we got big bits 15 dollars from spoons
for self-defense thank you i can't read for that far away thanks for the 15 bucks
jerma can you pretend to be elmo thanos for the rest of the stream
uh reality is often mr noodle reality is often disappointing mr noodle that's all you get
that's how you do that voice clip it leave it there don't clip it so this rolls back that's
weird how that rolls back do it again do it again so this goes like this and this
back like back bending its spine backwards but i didn't even fold this one how you
supposed to do that oh okay so now what like this what a psycho what a psycho check the bits
i'd see them wait what did actually did actual big bits come in why would you start crying all
right right here right in the middle two slots and the big slot let's see if i can get it in
got it got it big bits now i'm getting oh look i'm getting jaded wow what a surprise
okay then flip it over like this get the slots sticking out here can you guys see is this a
good camera angle do you want to change it you want to go in deeper how does it look is
it good you need the camera like over here brighter it's good yes okay yes they are in the
right spot so these two little sticks here he's doing this again welcome to the stream how are
you good to see you again hope you're having a good day welcome back thanks for asking you
you know what thanks for coming out how many people are here 8 000 holy fuck thanks guys
holy shit thank you that's a lot of fucking people top five and twitch nice yeah i don't
know what to say that's a lot that means a lot thank you for the huge people there
all right flip both sisters over and fold them in half what labo this is the vr labo the
virtual reality labo take one sister and line her up just like on screen she'll slide in
here to keep the tabs in place this right right here that feels nice and snug i see big
bits a lot of money a lot like too much money all right so hold on uh juno upsetto gave 50
dollars 50 bucks 5 000 bits thank you juno upsetto and they say imagine not donating
real big bits bwl well imagine giving anything at all that's remarkable to me so thank you
uh thank you for the 5 000 bits and the 50 dollars uh freudian weapon gave 50 dollars
right after that your vocal range never ceases to impress me also when it comes to wine what
is your recommendation also thanks for streaming tonight you're my heart you're welcome you're
welcome thank you thank you for the 50 dollars you do have a nice elbow yeah i do have a nice
elbow don't i how do you take bits back you can't no no refunds zero refunds i got range
absolutely no refunds zero refunds okay i gotta stop that because that's like mean and annoying
yeah oh these all fold up and around them some of these tabs sticks through right
okay yep look at how this is turning out to be something really really weird look at this
that's weird huh that's wild that's weird weird stuff weird wild stuff okay this goes
this goes down okay so then what how does it slips in so this is kind of needs to be bent
a little more because this goes in here like that and then these tabs come out and go in
in this
right am i doing that right oh shit this is gonna be oh okay so what is the tab that i
fucked it up i didn't stick that tab in i'm so angry right now you can't even begin to
understand my rage what's the point of even having the tabs on here i don't get it maybe
one day i will he's mad because bad say it again mad because bad mad because bad
and then this part flips over this way this tab goes down and the koala bear comes forth
no shit all right so then this comes over here this goes up like that and through here
this controller mark should be up it is and then this will slide all the way in
ready insert the holder as far as it will go
oh shit no no it's tearing uh that's in that's in look at that look at all these pieces
coming together this is gonna be a rocket launcher eventually eat the labo what if i
just fucking started tearing the thing apart what a waste and these ears fold in and this
thing all the whole thing goes down here's fold in and this whole thing goes down here
like that holy shit that's cool nice you'll want to do an important check here if you
pull on the end of the holder does it move a little bit without coming free
it does should that not be happening what the fuck no kind of right no it is here we go
just a gentle tug don't tug too hard or the holder might pull free why is it doing that
i mean it's it's not even in there secure i'm look at how gently i'm doing this guys
that's all right it's fine put the stopper into the little gap you can see around the
bottom of the holder it's going to go on the l mark okay let's look at some folds here
fold in half and then fold this one over and the tab beautiful little thing folds in half
get this little guy here doesn't have opposable thumbs yes i do i'm a human ah this i see this
keeps it in place here wait what so this this is the right way right all the way all the way
that's in there that's in there correctly and the other side too right oh this folds down
and into the little tab this thing is intricate for being looks pretty good did i get black
box for this i did not i've got a copper and tea it's different red blend it's still red blend
i don't know it's the first thing i saw at the grocery store whatever same thing on the other
side yeah here comes a spill joke no i can't do that here i can't do that don't even make
that a joke because i don't know that can't be a reality sorry guys no funny jokes to
spill everywhere he got wine all over his room nope sorry no can't do that vr wine spill please
why do you want that that bad that's in and then ruin toy no i'm not gonna why would
i do that these things are expensive so there you go starting the cannon here this is like
the guts what's that what am i making it's a gigantic rocket launcher it's a big blaster
almost like a big tf2 rocket launcher it looks really cool all right so that's done can i do an
american accent i like them i'm gonna respond to that all right so this is c so it's this
piece here yeah he said tf2 i'm not nevermind all right that's the one piece we need to
finish the core of the rocket launcher my legs are so tired right now because they've been
bent like this because i have to do it to make sure like the crotch cam isn't complete and total
view every second all right let me punch these up put the plastic bag back i don't have any
plastic bags right here so this these this actually stays in here i don't want to take
that out i don't care anymore fuck it who gives a shit you can make your little jokes
you can make your jokes that's fine all right uh you'll need a sheet of smooth
okay i got the smooth stickers i got one here auto is streaming tf2 right now
wow he's dog i think that's kind of impossible but it's cool all right so we need two on those
wrap this around and then around here cool thank god i was able to use this one for
something same thing on the other side grand theft auto little auto he's so cute he's my
special little boy he's my little son same thing on the other side i did it he actually has to go
into the vet he needs to get a shot okay more stickers on this side two more right so this
is long ways don't let me mess this up i will i will screw this up so instead of this way
we go this way and then hold it over okay so across the whole thing come on i need to prove
why i'm the number one nintendo labo streamer looks good same thing this is gonna use another
sticker to cover the last the sticker will overlap a bit with the net one next to it that's fine
all right good thing i read that i would have been freaking out about that he's the only one
oh come on where's my where's my recognition from nintendo where's my award where's my award
i am responsible for at least three sales of the nintendo labo my mother watched the
treatment she bought one one of the mods bought one they thought it was cool and i think one or
two other people bought one i'm responsible for three or four sales where's my award where's my
red carpet event all right now these all have to fold even with the tabs on okay it's
gonna be hard with the tape jesus i feel like it's gonna break this guy lied about
auto i did not lie about auto auto is just fine see him some other time he's doing just fine
i still have 24 minutes i got plenty of time i got plenty of time time but time is a curious
thing sorry it's power never mind even the little ones in the little frayed ones all right
but let me ask you this right so like uh you know i'm an influencer you know i'm a dot com
millennial influencer how many of you guys be honest with me here if you don't what am i
what am i doing what the fuck are you doing dumb stupid idiot no one should listen to a
goddamn thing i ever say so i'm an influencer you know i tell you things and you and you
listen to me um has anybody bought a labo because they've watched it on stream that's a
lot of nose but what if i ever what okay so if somebody comes up with hey man like we want
to sponsor your channel any analytics you can give us yeah yeah i'm mr nintendo labo
i haven't sold any copies i sold three copies of the nintendo labo
really yeah yeah yeah like four oh okay how many viewers do you have i don't know like
four thousand we'll call you back we'll call you back man thanks thanks for calling okay
all right what's next i bought wine i sell more bottles of wine than i do the video game
all right rubber bands small we need one of the smaller ones oh viewers are dropping fast
it's all right it's always yeah having a lot of viewers is cool
but it's all right you know it's not about the viewers not how many viewers you have
it's about how many units you can push a nintendo labo and then tell somebody that comes
you at like a twitch party how many units you sold and then maybe they'll give you like like
30 grand to do it again that's you know that's what matters so this goes in here all the way
will that fit in there got a box of wine cooking wine sponsorship no no one ever
sponsored me it just doesn't happen no one ever sponsored me i'm too much of a rebel
is a rubber band safely in the notches it should look yeah it is it is right yeah that's
in there uh it's time to attach the piece the rest of the core i'm no sir like i'll be real i'm
one of those people that will accept like i never have but if i accept a sponsorship let's
say it's for like a certain drink for like a wine company or something oh you should get
sponsored by a wine company oh that'd be funny but i'm the type of fucking asshole like
weirdo where if i will take a sip of it and go oh that's gross and just be kidding around
and then they'll cut the contract of half so i did this never gonna happen i turn the
core piece over so let me make sure both pieces facing the same direction okay like this
somebody say same yeah same oh they said save okay why am i holding the joy con
because i have to fast forward this is intricate i have to go forward that goes all the way in
here like this that like a little ship kind of lift the cover piece up and slide it on
check that your work to make sure everything lines up like it should i mean that's what's
snapping into place though that's kind of just sitting here is it supposed to just sit there
this doesn't feel like it's all this is not right why is this just flopping around
like it maybe it's just supposed to be like that yes and then the sides go in
okay put it around like that i'm gonna put the brightness up a little bit you guys can't see
i'm gonna put the brightness up that's better it's getting a little darker better you guys
can like actually see better right actually yeah i mean just like make it a little bit brighter so
you can see what's going on all right so what's next the rubber band now has to come up remove
your makeup all right now that's it make sure the rubber band doesn't hasn't come out from
the under the tabs no it's still there still in there right that's it there's the core the
whole core is done why does this feel frame rating on the other camera what is up with
this bullshit this is frame rating for what better that's better worse that's better is it
washed out how bright is this this is as bright as it can go watch out that's bright right
that looks good i think that's good you got to see my knee oh heavens to betsy we saw his knee
all right now this can go in here we're getting the scan lines though what the
fuck cameras suck all right that's gonna have to do one last check let's try inserting the
joy con that's the one with the plus button yeah i know what it is so this goes in here like
that like that so that goes in and this is going to be a little like right something like that
right why did somebody give me a minus two i just made a sound it doesn't well i'm not
making a joke everything doesn't be a joke i can't get it out now what is it what does
it say in the instructions about not being able to remove it from the thing i actually
i really can't get this out no what the fuck come on i can't get it out it's in there for good
cut it out i'm not gonna cut it out i just i don't know why it's in there so tight
they usually don't come out like this it's not this hard to get them out this is so
deeply in there it's unbelievable you can hear that right like that shouldn't be doing that
i seriously don't get it i don't know what it's stuck on jesus don't break it all right
that's it that's it i did it there's a tab on the bottom like that reference to the taco
belt thing you said that you got a big order and it was completely wrong you complained
and the manager just broke down crying what the hell are you talking about this didn't happen
this did this is something that you made this up what are you what they got my order wrong
and i complained and the manager cried that is a made-up story this did not happen
that was my cousin well you can tell your cousin i'm sorry to hear that but it wasn't me
all right now i'm making the actual rocket launcher 2
i can probably move this core out of the way let's check this and let's do a wine check
here i didn't do anything this is d d is right here throw it you guys want yeah it's so so
i don't know what it is with the twitch audience right but like oh yeah hey break it
like shatter the glass break the wine no one in twitch chat ever says hey read a book
hey dude like relax and breathe deeply because everyone wants you to break something
they want you to smash up your house so we need both pieces drink some what i'm i'll be
good don't worry i'm taking my first break in like now and like right now soon what did you
do torti just gave 20 community subs 20 20 community subs from torti that's a lot uh thank
you for the 20 community subs that's a fucking shit low subs thank you for the incredibly
generous contribution thank you torti 30 there we go all right um someone give me a sub and
i'll high five myself what do you mean stop it's it's cardboard stop dude be careful with that
it's like oh it's like a quarter of an ounce you might get oh hey wait wait dude be careful
you might get wind in your face you might get like some wind in your face prepared for that
is he okay is he okay you okay man you've never been better uh wait wait that's don't
follow these until you know what you have to do don't be an idiot don't be an imbecile
okay so these tabs so we're gonna start with this one facing this way so these tabs pull out
and all the way back it's kind of weird how they do that though this camera does look like
you guys have chlorine eyes i hate it that's a lot of money uh hold on a hundred bucks
10 000 bits from Magellan 36 100 hundred they say hey man this is the last money to my
name i'll be moving back in with my parents starting next week i've been up and down the
road looking for re-employment but my name's now been tarnished for beyond repair taco bell
was my one true go at life and you've ruined it more than you could ever know thanks asshole
signed you know fucking who next time somebody asks for extra diavolo sauce put it in the
bag or there'll be a complaint that is issued to the manager on duty just want to be clear about
that you know i'm not trying to be mean or anything just trying to be like like completely
real about it you know you're scary oh all right what am i doing here flip it like that
with the tabs bent why are you linking a clip that says auto in two hours he's like sleeping
i'm not going to get auto ladies and gentlemen i proudly present something i worked on a long time
something that nobody thought i could ever do something that people thought i would was
impossible for me to do on my own i made all of king's fucking landing oh yeah these are
all individually crafted pieces that's the red cape take a look this took like 17 hours to
make this is an incredible piece what happened to the tower what happened uh what happened to
the other tower there's another there's one here and there's one there it's not there
kim's gonna kill me hey where's auto i didn't go get i went to go get king's landing
all right what where are we switches you go yeah my switch is going to sleep
we're doing just fine how many hours in are we been three and a half hours holy fuck
it's a long time what are you gonna do this all right no slow down i don't want to drink
that much i don't want to drink that much be responsible okay auto is in bed he is not going
to be awoken to be exploited in front of twitch chat but i do have to do this though because
fucking god damn pants motherfucker i can't wear belts they make me want to puke all right hold
on belts just like feel this i was like squeezing my hips i don't like it i got
arthritis in my spine i can't wear them why does it still look like this there we go that's much
better jesus all right finally finally all right what are we doing next auto plus king's landing
it's gonna fall on me let's go tenfold you guys can ride all you want i'm not going to
go wake my dog up and put him in front of a camera that would be a bad pet owner he's to be
relaxed and hanging out and doing what he wants to do i'm not going to force him to do something
i'm not going to just pick him up and stuff him in a camera pick him up and stuff him in the
camera no not gonna happen sorry good owner no i'm not gonna why would i do that he's just
relaxing why would i want to just go disrupt his day he's just being a dog somewhere you
know no get up and i want you to come out for content get over here quick
oh he's fine just look up a picture of just type in auto germa and you'll get a good picture
you know what he looks like same thing with the other one right i'm assuming
pull the whole thing in half maybe looks like this is coming across all the way around
that goes into there that go get midas i'm not going to take my roommate's dog out of his
room to show on camera you guys have lost your minds there it is arrows pointing the right
way take a moment to check that none of the teeth have gotten folded it doesn't look like
it right teeth look like they're straight up now we're going to work with this pot what are
we doing with this pot already got it in the right spot and though i don't spin it
i'm gonna smash this whole desk i almost just did no dog on stream we need a dog
you don't need a dog you're fine listen you don't need a dog you don't know what
responsibility wise it's really hard work you gotta feed it you're gonna take it outside you
have to take care of it you don't know what it's worth you don't know what it's like
minus 100 bits that actually looks kind of funny all right uh crease crease crease crease
crease of all am i a dog no i would have been like a bee or something in a past life
i would have been like a honeybee like an ant dude in my past life i was definitely a
cheetah no you weren't you were probably like a bug statistically speaking you were a bug
i think in my past life i was probably a cat or a wolf no no you're a beetle or one of the
one of the five trillion different ant colonies in the world let's just be realistic about it
right all right this closes i'm assuming right i mean it's not cool to think about that
it's really cool to be a jaguar you weren't a jaguar in your past life unless you hit
the lottery there we go this folds into here so this goes up like that make sure they're
facing the right direction pay careful attention to these semi-circles these semi okay so yeah i
got it the right way right yeah that's correct so face it this way and then stick it through
here i'm assuming through here let me see if i'm right no i'm not right through the middle
weirdly enough this just goes in the middle like this that dude what dude all the way
insert the hexagon into the opening like this it might be a tight fit i mean it's not even going
in it's not going in what do i do i don't know i don't know what to do it's not going in what
do i do seriously man like just get in there i mean it's kind of in there kind of not really
though it's like all fucked up is that what it's supposed to look like no it goes all
the way in what this is a really tight fit i'm gonna feel like i'm gonna break it
all the way huh the teeth i did it it's i mean it's there it's all the way through oh
uh-oh that's not good that really isn't good am i going to actually break a labo for the
first time i'm supposed to be a labo streamer no it's okay not great but not okay that's
okay all right close it up that and then this comes across and in close it close it
close it same thing on this side this is the i guess this is the first part of the cannon
dude i'm gonna display this this is going right next to king's landing
as you didn't think i fucking was capable of doing that sponsored labo streamer nope
nintendo's gonna sponsor this channel drinking alcohol on stream they wouldn't want this they
wouldn't allow that it would be a huge problem that's good i think that's the whole thing
right and then the tab goes down and sticks in the corner here it's a little notch there
it's in there now okay it's in now what the last thing to do for this piece is to talk the
flap the little tooth should slot right into the opening okay there's no there's not
any music what did i do he already did i miss big bits where i didn't there's no big bits
what are you talking about germa stocks are soaring i'd i'd get in if i were you all right
remove these three sheets c and e i heard analysts were talking about this stream in particular
was going to be the most booming streams of 2019 and 2020 there's a twitch.tv analyst told
me that well it didn't tell me that i saw it e and c so this huge piece is coming out
let's see let's see one of these old ones here this one here insider trading
and analysts told me that they said new stream is pretty cool i was like nice thanks for that
man dude how many people even own germa such a such a hidden gem and then you wake up tomorrow
when it's fucking down 85 percent you were like but but you like drank on stream and
i talked a bunch of shit about nintendo and talked about how unsponsorable he is
and bad of a streamer he is oh fuck oh no how did i not see this coming and then i like
i think make my way over to the bank and take out the fucking atm deposit you know what i'm
saying is done what i lose that popped up big you're actually in a huge downward trend
right now in your stocks i just took a week off though does that matter what doesn't matter
whatever dow stocks twitch stocks who cares twitch stocks your stocks are down i mean are
they though so i put a call option out on tesla a few weeks ago sure about that are
you sure about that i'm talking about my stocks stop flexing i did not do that i'm just pretending
to call options on tesla lol i know you say that now but if you had done that a week ago
talking stocks here you know i know what i know about stocks investment advice from twitch chat
didn't somebody have a twitch account with twitch chat like told them what to buy for
stocks and all that that's so funny that's such a fun idea so we got this sounds like an easy
way to lose money i don't know i don't know how well or how bad that uh channel's account
did i know that they he was doing it somebody was doing it it's a really fun idea really cool
piece of content all right um so what we got punch it all up a full okay i need a big space
show auto labo is a resident sleeper every labo that comes out i have to do
i signed a contract with myself no one else was involved labo streamer i fucking hear it in my
sleep that's a fold all so this has to be like this all right i gotta get this out of the way
germa is his own demon lick the cartridge oh man that sounds kind of fun i've had a few
drinks man that sounds like a fun idea maybe i'll do it he's not gonna do it
let's fold this tab out do it do it link what do you mean link tab up
this one how many more of this one too so many creases and folds and doodads and
noodles and qrst uv this two fold lines here is there no it's not oh there is shit
what a fucking disaster you know i woke up the next day and i was so embarrassed i was like
what the fuck happened i knew what happened but i'm never gonna live that one down
it's impossible i need this back here top five streams if you say so
so this one goes across between the holes down here right yeah two holes
i think i don't know i don't know i don't know i hope it's right
it's kind of a weird place for a sticker to five streams
to top up i missed it somebody said the top five streams that was the wrong place no it wasn't
no that's correct is it yeah no it is that's right so only one
i just got here and you're already drunk i i am i'm not but thanks for asking okay uh
firmly with both hands all right the whole thing has to come up in half
somebody said kappa you never see kappa anymore this is a tough one kappa really fell out of favor
didn't it people now do like omega lol no people don't do it anymore 100 000 bits damn
thanks man it's a lot that pulls the crease there omega b w l b w l jerma how do i get
into voice acting really simple learn how to say w that's it w no no no no no no no excuse me
w w no no no no no try it again w w w w w w w try it come on you'll get it that's good
you did that ww joke a long time ago no i did w i did w w is w it's three syllables
in the va voice acting world that was drunk god damn it that was like drunk repeat just rewind
that and listen to that sick that's like dr steve brule there's i in the voice acting world
got him well i'm just gonna do them all just do them all right that one is gonna be hard
okay do them all create some all this is like a thick piece of fucking paper
your steve brule is just john wane is it w w w it's me john wane no it's not john wane talk
like that's not what are you talking about john wane john wane no i can't do a john wane
i tried all right so let's keep going bale grim uh john wade's an interesting impression
because if you can't do john wane you just sound awful trying to do john wane
and if you can do john wane you sound great there's really no in between
you sound terrible and really bad and not good at all if you try to do it if you can do it
you sound great what's the worst possible voice you can do like most grating i don't know i
don't think i have anything like that i'm gonna get this last one i mean maybe like
air coming out of a horn maybe like an air horn that is barely running out of air
might be close that's that's as close as i could probably get something like that probably
kim is sleeping okay no more of that uh shit all right i'm being quiet this is look at how
hard this one is look at this do you understand how fucking impossible this one is look at this
shit how are you supposed to do this wow god damn doesn't want to do it that wine's not
going to spill i got a good eye on it god damn all right that's all of them right one two three
four yep so this is going to be the uh the blaster portion right take care of these triangle
teeth huh fold them up so tiny can we get a sweat check yeah what's that oh we're good
we're we are completely clean didn't expect that did you you did not expect that neither did i
all right now this is it's down here so this piece goes where the hell does this go
many important bits come together to make a space station after all this is a gun flip it over
fold it all up every little crease okay i got it we got bits what are you talking about
what's that he got you again well it's really easy to get you it's not that difficult to
get you he's hungry for bits wait bitch see a bit how much how many this one's actually
not that bad i didn't like it at first it's too fruity it was like really sweet and sugary but
it's it's growing on me a little bit this is uh cooper cooper and thief for those of you
that want to pretend this is a sponsored stream go ahead and pretend i did all that
oh shit uh we need eyelet we need one of these and one of the washers washer and
eye something that's going to go through there oh shit do you see the tracks go this way
and then oh shit that and then this on top of that like this snap that piece on ready to go
sit in there kind of all right snapped in like that step three is fold the whole thing over
weird okay so this what is this for oh must be an ammo box of course i have no idea what that
is how do you skip forward to its completion well it's pretty easy you go to bed so go
to sleep right now when you wake up in the morning come back to germany85twitch.tv
and open this content and skip forward like four and a half hours from right now you just have to
go to sleep and then just and wake up you'll be able to get it that's the only way minus 120
thousand bits for being a poop with head thanks all right that was fast now it's time for this
piece why does this fit my face so perfectly this was made for my chin and face to go in
is my chin really that skinny what well so let's fold everything from this side up
someone measure it measure my chin what is that going to do here come all the follow lines do it
all okay this one a compact chin kind of have a big chin it's skinny but it's long
i've got a long skinny chin it's all right though i don't that don't mind it i think it was okay
you know as long as you're okay with the way you look who gives a fuck what anybody else has
to say you know what i mean all right folded everybody says you are handsome though who
cares what everybody has to say you know what i mean like people people can be mean and
oh you're handsome people can be cruel you look great today yeah you know don't worry
what will people have to say about you you know it's not a big deal where's this going
again flipping around what i keep flipping it around oh oh shit this is going to go over here
huh where line up the control panel what what in the name of god is this doing i need two
grommets i'm not sure if this stream sucks or not it sucks pretty bad if you're new to
the channel we do every labo every single one every labo is done on this stream so if you don't
like it there's a door right there you probably have one too that means everybody leave no that
means if you like it stay if you don't then i'll see you soon you don't have to love the
labo streams i do and that's all that matters right it's not like that jerma i'm outside
well what are you doing still on twitch oh shit he's hemorrhaging viewers who cares
i built a bird house to less people that won't give us a shit all right let's go grommet i'm
doing it wrong oh fuck i thought somebody was just back seating me like bad oh oh shit i
actually did fuck it up i'm not sure if this stream sucks or not thanks for the confidence
boost damn it i need a coin to get in here ow i actually did lick it fuck i didn't mean to
i was pretending to lick it jesus christ man this stream sucks hey don't say that about my stream
i work real hard on these where did it go it's right there no don't yes i'm wearing two
different socks and you have to fucking deal with it all right work real hard on this shit
all right what do i need to do so it goes underneath it goes like under here this
lines up like that okay all right then it goes through thanks for catching that by the way
somebody caught that i would have been miserable if i didn't know look we do whatever on this
string look have you figured that out yet some of you some of you long-time subscribers
are still like wait what's he doing today we do whatever though we want come on man
does this go on here it does we want auto all right i'll give you auto at some point in the
near future oh god we're getting real intricate here okay so then this moves here and then
this comes over now what does this go this all right that's really weird remember the
corbit it actually goes inside the lss2 go ahead and get it ready check the direction
of the eyelet house if the side where you insert the tab is on the inside then you're all good to
go it is slide the core along until it comes to rest against the eyelet's house what the fuck
okay so like this what's a bourbon wine i have no idea kind of tastes good though the rubber
band hasn't been come loose check quickly to make sure and fix it no it's not oh dear we
have to fold the whole thing around this like a sandwich i don't look like a piece of sushi
roll up the sides around the whole thing this goodness this goes under here and go like that
i'm not supposed to close this up like this there it is there it is there it is there it
will go back this comes up first slide it there this comes up all the way like that
and then this side comes up here which leaves this here like that okay and this closes down
there oh my god all right so how do i connect this together hold them in one place until we
can secure them see this little flap over here flap yeah fold it up it'll help keep everything in
place for now really well i just hold it that really did work okay it actually worked
and then the rubber band comes up and goes over and around the whole thing
that's it this up and around i think that's good looks like it's all right i don't know
yeah no it's in there and then we fold this shit up we'll fold up the control pan on x
first raise up the skinny arms my god this is elaborate and then bring them connect the arms
by sliding the notch so i'm connecting these like that yeah once that's done lift up the sides
this holy shit this is crazy it comes up and this folds down and this comes across here
this is looking like a rocket launcher that's for sure so we have to do more building on
that then that's over here get this where does this go rubber band should be on the
other side of the tab isn't it though looks like it is that's not on the other side looks like
it is that's in the right spot right this thing looks cool yeah lavos are cool they really are
tabs here it's cool to see it come together regardless of how the game is it's cool to
make a little device that's cool to make a king's landing it's in front it goes in the front
all right i got it i got it thank you everybody for giving me the tips that i need that's in the
front that's good to go right in front so then what does this do it's probably this next bit
might surprise you lift up the whole thing and align it like so was the arrow arrow
and it goes in the mark on the end should be the line it is like that and then it goes down
all the way in god come on come on and oh i see look at that here's the tube this is cool
nice all right let's stick it up here these tabs go back inside weirdly enough they kind
of fold back in on themselves this is one and the other one's on this other side
i can't really get it though there we go done cool now what pull it to the right when you
let go does it snap back into place that's pretty cool so it's like total shock huh
how they think of this shit i have no idea the lss is ready for launch all right next part
well that's the second step complete the front of the toy is now all done why not take a break
i don't think i need a break making the clacker so we need c and f c and f where's the home
stretch maybe like another hour and a half maybe like another two hours we need this thing in
the middle what is a clacker what does that mean clacker let's see do an auto break no
we're good we're good we're good i want to get this done because once this is done and i play with
it for five seconds we'll just hang out in the chat for a little while another glass of wine
we'll go on our merry way you know all right looks good i'm going to move this out of the
way because i don't think i need it right this second all right a little spaceship here
let's punch out the necessary things needs to be like that hang out jupiter yeah we'll just
hang out for a while because i don't have the other they don't sell them together they're all
sold out i went to gamestop i went to best buy target like i went everywhere nobody has this
shit you have to buy this on the nintendo official website shop it's not on amazon
either you can't get the whole kit on amazon right now it's all uh locked out you could
spend like 110 bucks to get it from some third party but i apparently bought it too late
but i should end up doing that take that sheet of marker stickers this thing okay
bend the sheet no i can see it i can see it just fine so the stickers on this part of the
sheet it's the right in the middle all right i see you can't see but i can that's all the
matters is that i can see so right here i'm trying to see so hard it's the wrong piece
i can't see help i'm gonna do some punching you know i need i need like a little pen to just go
like it's so much easier than my finger it's a little too late now though use your teeth no
i can't bite into this shit it'd be bad news come here come here okay so now right here
needs to be this big sticker right here the big one large one the biggest one on the sheet
don't pull them all off that goes right on top of it like this right oh no come on it sticks so
much good good i was going to lick the cartridge yet yeah i did against my better judgment yes i
did i fold it all it was on accident though to be fair fold it okay every little piece
needs to be turned oh nintendo fold fold fold it crease it again crease fold fold fold fold go
go go how did you look at accidentally with prior judgment because i pretended to lick it
but i went too far i pretended to lick it for the joke and my tongue touched it
unfortunately it's the truth it went too far not good with depth perception have you seen me
slap myself in the face before i have done that this folds in these ones go out
out and out and these come in all the way does it push it does it do the whole thing
like this i think so lick the table no i'm sorry that's not gonna happen that actually
will not happen there's like jokey lick the cartridge and then there is embarrassing
i'm embarrassed for you you're looking at the table like you're i don't this is i don't
want to be here anymore and then i lose 500 people there's a difference there really is i
close it up same deal fold this piece up like that so many jupiters there's a lot of jupes
some pretty good jupes tonight from what i've seen they've been pretty good
do these go in too hold on flaps go in yeah supposed to do in in stick there we go so
what what i don't know what i'm making here a clacker i don't know what a clacker is
is it going to be like a probably snap it all in can you see the marker sticker through
the windows in the hand they look like robot eyes and the opening below is the mouth
i think you can see them i can can you good only boomers know what a clacker is
i'm not even i'm a late i'm a late millennial an early millennial not even a boomer i never
understood that joke okay more more stickers one two these go where right here right on the
dot i'm not even 38 i turned 39 in fucking september come on guys i turned 37 in august
okay there we go uh tiny fold lines on each of the robot feet fold them back i did that
right right you sound like you were raised in the 30s what are you talking about like
the way that i talk fold them off you sound like you were raised in the sound like you
were raised in the 30s i don't think i talk like this possible but i don't think i do
everybody born in the 30s talk like this lots of inflection sort of a weird fake british
accent but it's not really british it was american 1930s american what even was that
accent it was like we're still british but we're not quite british anymore transatlantic
right it's true inflation hit accents hard all right let's get this part done
whoa all right so these like that wow so how did they have to combine them together
that was a stuffy nose okay so i have to combine these little hands together
wow okay then these fold in to make a little right they don't stay down though the next part
requires some gymnastics take the top of the robot head all the way over and then stick it
down through here that's pretty cool that's exactly what i just did another one of these
it goes right in the front right across the whole uh star more wine relax what are you
drinking those of you that have 21 or in your jurisdiction that you're allowed during
what are you drinking water soda beer cider lemonade absent absent i saw an absent
all right you're ready to fucking go and now i know why you're watching this stream
holy shit man i'm freaking out this guy's making a giant blaster and cardboard i can't
even take it i'm fucking losing my mind so they this just goes right here that so then
we're done with these for now what did you miss dude you missed so much shit you have no idea
i showed a dog i showed auto yep so this goes what is it what the hell is it doing
so i had it right i think of this like that okay can i borrow your car i'm low on gas
no dude get out of here take a lift stick those in tab in tab in tab in tab in
it's gonna connect them this looks cool it's like a little it's a little spaceship don't take
a lift at eight though what do you mean don't take a lift at eighth though i don't know what
does that mean don't take a lift at eight why not what does that mean don't take a lift
at eighth eight get the get take a lift oh shit what does this go well and there it is
right this is a strike oh what do you mean a strike where like everywhere don't take a
car on the lift um don't take a lift on the eighth here oh it's the actual company
i thought you meant there was like a big strike going on somewhere like don't take a
car it's gonna be crazy going through i didn't know that all right well don't take don't take
lift on the end i thought that was like a big like protest or a big strike or something and
be careful and out of what city that's why i was like what are you talking about
he's a fucking boomer i'm not a boomer all right whoa whoa wait wait we're gonna put
this device into this hold on this is gonna be cool this is like three hours of work i can't
wait to fucking just smash it and rip it in half and laugh in the camera okay so this
goes like this line the clacker up like on screen then into the tube it goes like this
am i doing this right am i doing this right huh like that right yeah i am okay so they go how
far down does it go line the clacker yeah the clackers lined up it's the clackers lined up
with the arrows oh i dropped it hey there we go it's supposed to go down there all right
make sure the clacker ended up in the same place as the one on the screen it did now we've got to
secure the clacker next we'll be opening up some tabs on the clacker and make sure that it
doesn't move around hold it down from above where's the clacker the clacker is right here
okay opening up some tabs on the clacker huh open up this tab this one here and then what
oh fuck i need a rubber small so that's out small rubber band dude okay so this is like 40 bucks
i would pay imagine like a five thousand dollar labo and you can make up a real house
or like an airplane like a two scale backyard airplane it would be like four grand that'd be
fucking cool i would do a full backyard airplane labo i would hire five people
all right what do i do this goes on here let's stick it out said make sure it doesn't move
but it kind of is where does it go from there wait wait wait wait hold on wait wait wait
you gotta i gotta put it through and then close it this is fucking nuts what this is
fucking insanity insanity i don't this is not this doesn't feel secure in now what oh dear
god now i have to go over here and across through here i feel like it's not gonna work
i guess it did i guess that's right right and then put this down which i mean that's as far
down as it can go have i ever told you the definition of insanity fuck right fuck right
okay yeah that looks right do the same thing on the other side okay
small rubber band what's the best far cry game i want it on a scale of one to five
three now two now one now i don't think so blood dragon no i don't know about that
none of them yeah yeah i think so i'm kidding relax relax it's a joke this is a comedy stream i'm a
comedy streamer says it in my description go look at it go look at my channel description right
now what does it say youtuber for five years decided to do the twitch thing as well hope you
like it it says it right there and i'm a fucking comedian and channel all right so that's
done too it's in both that's it right is a minus two and a plus two still legal
yeah that means it was zero you can't give me fucking minus two on that one that's my own
that's my own channel what the fuck are you a cop i can't reach it i can't reach like how do
i reach the wine from here i don't want to stand up my bum is sore i don't it'll hurt even
more you even do that when you sit up and it's like oh i wish i had fucking jedi powers all right
get a gamer chair what a waste of money no thanks i'm not gonna get a gamer chair
why would you ever get a gamer chair i mean if you have one and you like it cool
but the chair is a chair they're just chairs it's a chair you sit in a chair i could bring a
folding metal chair out here and be fine i would play a game and be fine
nah dude you need to spend like uh 200 bucks on one of these chairs
just lie on the ground what just lie on your back on the fucking ground and play your game
sit on your couch no i don't want to sit in like the backseat of a toyota camry to play
all my video games i'll get a goddamn chair from staples for 40 bucks i mean this chair
was 400 but you get the idea well what's the next step so look it's a default fucking chair look
look at my chair okay this is my chair it's i'm kidding this was this was like
not that much money it was this was more expensive than all the gamer chairs
but it's better in every way i got lumbar support i feel good when i sit in here
default skin chair oh i don't want the fucking thing up here when you sit in those gamer chairs
you're like oh wait what's it say hey we've been moving an ad all stream get one of these guys
oh my back hey what's going on mate yeah we're just chilling up playing some uh playing some
fortnight oh i don't i don't i don't i kind of don't i don't understand why my by my
spine hurts every day i mean yeah no it's going good no i love this chair got him got
him hold on i need to take a break oh fuck ow you just complained about your butt hurting
yeah because do you see what i'm dealing with here look at this i'm hiding my penis
because people are out of control i have to like sit under here i have to sit like
under the table these people are like did he stand up i gotta be like under the table
no wonder my ass hurts i'm not sitting in the chair if i was sitting in the chair i
wouldn't be like stuffed under the table like this the tape guys the table i'm i look at this
do you understand i'm wearing the table right now that's how this works this is me wearing
this thing this is how i have to sit because we've got a bunch of fucking jokesters
i'm like the fat kid in a disney cartoon ah no it's time for lunch bell rings
what are we doing that was a chicken little tear joke i'm just saying i've got to be like
i've got to hide i have to hide my body chicken little get out of town i went oh
oh yeah excuse me oh that actually kind of made like a loud noise my monitor my monitor
just like changed to colors for like two seconds it was like i could see the the crystal plasma
i think it's all right but that went out hard it was like boom make sure you remind me that
there's a there is a rubber band on the floor does that one remember buy a new table why would
i buy a new table this is a fuck you table we already went over this you see how dirty
and shitty this table is i will never get rid of my fuck you table i can eat on here
i can fucking pick it up i can stick on it i can punch things it's on the floor i know
how much wine did he have not that not kim i'm not that much not really not that much
i'm making i'm making a reference to the fact that look i'll show you can see how much i'm
drinking it's over there i can't read you but i i not that much i people are just people are
just being funny and making funny references and jokes i mean i broke i did not break the
castle what the fuck guys what the fuck are you doing i thought we were cool i thought we were
cool just like snitching immediately within two seconds i thought we were fucking cool
all right so the next part is yep oh this is the actual headset does this go like on here
eventually is this gonna like stick on here because i have to like go like this right
how does this work that's not how it works right it's gonna be like this
how is this gonna work that's like looking for a headset from this far away all right f
i need only a couple pieces just a couple little ones right this one here and this one here
what is he not wearing pants look it's a pair of shorts it's a pair of fucking shorts
that have a zipper on them relax look is he not wearing pants what are you talking about
why would i not wear pants you know i'm gonna you want to get banned on twitch i'm not gonna
wear pants this time bye i'll be gone forever let's get this in the way uh four fold lines so
right here salmon or pizza for dinner oh flies not down relax salmon or pizza oh boy
probably oh it's tough somebody put a straw pole in chat and tell me what it is put the
salmon on the pizza and disgusting all right so that's folded somebody i see a straw pole
right now let's see what you guys got what does it want me to do so this folds in
and then folds together like i think i'm fucking this up no no folds in and together
slow down slow down you're not cool that doesn't make you look cool makes you look
annoying what does this go i'm just so happy i'm so happy that like everyone watching this
stream right now that knows about like the rumors you're never gonna be a rumor you're not
you just i'm so happy that this was a 36 3700 people here none of you are gonna be rumors
none of you because you're gonna be like oh that sucks that person sucks okay where does
this go and right in here right it's a weird place this is the crosshair make sure it's
the right way up like that stick it right in the middle there kind of moving around
that i mean that's in there doesn't feel that secure but it's in there i guess i drive i drive
it an n7 with a loud rotary engine do you drive down the same street every single day
like 20 times a day going as fast as you can on that road it's like a that's like
probably like a 40 that's probably like a 35 mile per hour road you're going like 55 every
day do you do that you don't do that i know you don't don't you don't do that
you why would you do that you wouldn't you you wouldn't you wouldn't do that
think of the children look at the kids you drive by that fast going like 55 and a 30
look at the children for god's sakes do you hear them laughing they're over there playing
you're gonna go 55 and a 30 you see that you hear the ball like like a little ball
being bounced you look over you see the playing basketball in the driveway you're gonna go 55
and a 30 unbelievable set up a camera and speed check them just go sit up there but then i'm
like the i'm like the fucking nosy nancy that's up there with the radar gun i got you
motherfucker i'll be all like on the corner like they'll drive by me that was 50 what
i'm gonna do and now i'm gonna call the police
yes police yes it's me nancy yes they drove by very fast did you get their license plate no
okay so you'll patrol good a lot uh where was that piece i didn't have an actual phone in my
hand there was no phone in my hand to do the prop uh you know it's i'm an actor okay i can
take it fold it up in half like that looks like you're having salmon pizza for dinner no all
right let's go with salmon salmon yeah oh yeah salmon oh yeah oh yeah salmon yeah what do we say
to salmon you know filthy rich streamers salmon is like four dollars all right okay all the way
up in here oh man this thing is so sick i can't wait to like hold on let me like oh man pretty
good where's it going straight up and what are they i don't know what's that attaching
the clacker is attached band for tos hey listen up it's illegal in las vegas i'm not
gonna do any hand motions but okay there's gonna be a bunch of hand motions all right stop doing
fucking hand motions chairs are uncomfortable he's on beat he's on beat fuck he's on beat yep
yeah how much money did i get for this not enough not enough oh oh uh four to five
i'm almost done making the grip oh we're gonna get a grip only two more steps all right let's
get this so what is the clacker can i am i gonna fuck this up if i
yeah i said i wasn't gonna do hand motions but i can't help it we need uh gnh how long has
this been five hours you shit me that's a long fucking time for one blaster all right
this piece here take a sip i've taken plenty of sips uh the whole thing right yeah those you
guys the other guys get it the more that i drink the less likely there's a stream tomorrow
every like sip increases like the time forward for when the stream starts tomorrow afternoon
oh the sudden now everybody wants me to slow down now you said salmon now i want salmon pizza
i would eat salmon pizza right now and i would be i would pretend to love it
the manager would come over how was uh how was everything tonight oh it's fantastic why do we
do that by the way what's wrong with people there's too much sauce on this no it's i mean it's
okay i think they add too much sauce and the noodles are underdone no i'm not sure if i
really like it that's okay oh how's everything doing oh oh oh it's fantastic i love it
fantastic why don't why don't you tell them how's your burger oh it's really like overdone
it's like i wanted medium but they get it's like well done the lettuce is like really
wilty and gross oh oh ma'am how's your burger oh fantastic thank you no the burger sucks
tell them why do we do that what's wrong with us i can still hear him are you still going
car like the person in that car somebody said that you're that guy in that car
yeah yeah yeah what do you do oh yeah
yeah yeah okay
he's still going go get forza and fucking leave us alone like what are you what are you doing
oh shit a red light's coming up oh fuck it's okay it's all right i can only do that for like
12 seconds okay okay wow wow what a rush wow fucking like what else what are the pieces
do i need what was that that was being arrested that shit happens like fucking 25 times a day
why don't you think like okay eating the same food every day you get all it gets old imagine if
you had like a hot dog every single day you're not going to be as excited for hot dogs anymore
if you eat 50 hot dogs in a week the 51st hot dog is like i don't i don't know if i
want to eat a hot dog right now how many times you have to speed down the same road
before it's like oh this is kind of fucking dumb like this is i just every day i just like 10 times
a day i guess i'm gonna do it again at the 11th time it's always the same road i wonder if they
do it in other places too you know what i mean let me see let me look at a map oh my god let's
get like google maps out that's not a bad one to vroom on all right what about down the street
over here let's go like a few more like kicks to the left that i like that that's a
good vroomer road go take a bath go like soak for a while you need it i just picture and i know
i'm making up a character that doesn't exist but i picture a person just like drinking something
like an energy drink or or like a or eating something out of the hand like a fucking burger
or something and they speed and they just like throw the trash out the fucking window
i feel i feel like they're illiterate too not just a vroomer i feel like you also
like throwing like styrofoam out the window like you got like a burger box and it's it's the worst
possible thing to throw in a fucking window styrofoam just like i don't care i don't care
i don't you know oh yeah i just trying to build a children's toy here who cares
oh is that glass yeah
yeah
get a fucking life anyways uh we're we're okay these stickers what does this one got
building building uh you're interrupting my building children's toys i still gotta stand
get a vr helmet and fucking get in a car game right in the middle get a life says the guy
playing with cardboard i'm not affecting anybody else my okay you could good point maybe but if my
listen that doesn't make that's bullshit you know why if i opened up my window and leaned
out the window and was screaming about every build i was doing hey so now hey now i'm taking
the cardboard and i'm turning it upside down i'm plugging in the next piece
and now i'm taking the next piece that's the difference i'm not doing that right oh how about
yelling out this window just in case anybody was wondering it's a cool rocket blaster it's
a rocket launcher so i would accept i would hope somebody would look up and be like will
you shut the fuck up huh what yeah you're being really fucking loud and like annoying
everybody in like the whole neighborhood really preposterous kim is not asleep she's
downstairs yeah who would have thought who would have thought that like being wicked fucking loud
without your window screaming at us i know the window is open and i'm leaning outside to get
some fresh air while i scream yeah you that that's it you just described exactly why we're
annoyed by it fuck you boomer and then they keep going anyways let's keep going let's keep building
our children's story but we're not bothering anybody else it was a long rumor rant but you
knew it was coming eventually it's only sometimes you can get groomed on stream before you fucking
get annoyed by it i added in like littering and breaking glass it doesn't matter it doesn't
matter be kind to each other okay that's the moral of the story be fucking nice to each
other don't be like a rumor being a rumor means you're like a bad person apparently
all right i feel like my hair just stood on end i'm gonna go to a goddamn town hall meeting
it's like a las vegas town hall i'm ready to do something about these fucking rumors
god damn it i am a fucking old person now aren't i anybody that threatens to go to
town hall is definitely over the age of 50 all right the whole thing every fold every line you
got it i hear it in my sleep as for god and sometimes it's not even a rumor and i think it
is and i'm prepared for it and i get ready for it i hear like no okay no that was just
somebody like starting their car because they're going to work i think we're all
folded it's just a fan all right a fan you're just scared of getting a job
what the fuck are you on about all right next jerma doesn't have fans i do at least 100
connect that bottom part oh this is a weird piece okay like that how long was that
rumor part of the stream i can't tell i can't see from here hefty amount like 20 minutes
ah i'm sorry spent longer time one more dumb shit it's okay as long as it wasn't like 40
it's an interesting looking piece this folds all the way and really really i don't believe
you i don't wait what hold this down this comes down and then this comes up roll it over
jesus all right this these two come down i'm getting sleepy stop being so boring
i was just screaming for like 10 straight minutes i was just i was just making loud
fucking noises for like 15 straight minutes i was screaming and yelling loud equals funny
no i wasn't trying to be funny i was trying to make a point it's all right i can't win
can't win what's next loud equals i'm right got it no that was the culmination of like six
months of being roomed on and off stream no loud doesn't equal right loud is not funny
damn it don't think of me like that actually think of everyone what is this what this is
a tight piece what are the squares on my door uh they are noise dampening devices
it is noise foam makes it so there's no echo in the room as you notice when i go like hey hey
hey hey hey uh there's no echo there's a bunch of panels over here there's a couple of bass
traps in the corners a couple of bass traps in the what's gonna say sink closet it dampens
the sound in the room so without a bunch of furniture you cannot have a bunch of echo
don't resident sleeper come on it's what it's it's easy nine ten eleven it's like 12 a.m of
course you're gonna resident sleeper it's time for bed in like 10 minutes but i'm not
stopping the stream that's it right looks good that little piece here all right next is this big
one got a tab here i'm going to bed in a few yeah do you think you know do do whatever you
want do do you think hope you have a good rest have a great sleep hope you have the best
dreams possible define good have a good i don't know have a good restful six to eight
hours of sleep i'll give a good restful like eight hours of sleep you wake up refreshed and
ready to take on the world you know unless you've been drinking wine all night in that case and
sleep in a little hold all this stuff 13 hours maybe you've been up to 13 hours or
it's not that long tell a bedtime story um i don't really have a bedtime story you're
better off just kind of making one up yourself 13 hours stream i don't that's not gonna happen
this has been about five hours feels a lot shorter than that this will be uh like seven
six to eight i'm not doing a 13 hour stream all right that's all folded good to go all right
now what what do i do with this read the whole rat movie script i i made it i don't need
to read it i already know all the lines okay this whole thing rolls up on this side thing rolls
over that and then it comes across the whole thing it snaps in give us a good night kiss
um how about a good night soft dude you know hey good night soft dude it's good
close it now if you take it off you go to bed and we'll see you again soon
thanks for coming up blaster is nearing completion it's pretty interesting it's got like a little
in the middle so that's cool and this tab folds out and what does the tab do
hidden opening and stick it in it's that simple apparently all right then this piece
which is right and left it's got a couple of lines here to fold lick us or you'll never
see us again that's not true you tell me if i don't lick the camera then you guys won't come
back i have trouble believing that so all right let's put it all together
ooh yellow two of them these are thicker than the other ones getting almost to the end of
the grommets so we're combining these two so this is r and r each bit has a hole in it
and we want to line those up first make sure that the r mark on each piece is facing
upward so all it is now r and r right so r and r like that i think i don't know
that i mean that's correct and then the yellow grommet goes in the middle here
through all of it or just through the middle there which one so right okay through the
middle this and then stick this on here click all right same thing in the other one
whoa shit all right wait so then this then what okay another snap what there already is
a snap on it am i doing this wrong there's already a snap on it this seems like it's
not supposed to be the way i guess it is because then this washer comes on
that's on there right did it too early i think i got it i think that's it right
snap too early snap too early that looks like it's on wait i need to get that off
you snapped too early damn it this is on there so deep too look at how bad that is
that's on there so deep i'm never going to get that off oh it's going to take
oh it's going to be impossible no way oh this is so bad i fucked this up so bad huh
buy a new one that's not going to work come on do it get off there i know you can come on
it's on this so good it's going to take i need a good coin or something i'm not
no no that's that's not a good idea got it ah come on oh get off it won't get off
it won't come off oh shit got it okay same thing on the other side um something i'm gonna close it
do i look skinnier than normal i don't fucking hard to do he's big chunky what's that pizza
what up whatever there's pizza somewhere right done finally man i just fucked that up my
fingers hurt uh look a bit like more than something you can hold it does there's a hair
stuck in here push the button try pushing the button the hook like bit should lift up
does looks pretty good okay this this piece is up next it's fancy armor what did i do with that
piece where's that did i take that piece out where is this i didn't take that piece out
is it this one no it's not that one where the hell is it it's right here come here it's
that one right there okay so it's this bit i guess i never took it out
okay that's it right just this piece i think so pretty sure we're almost done
we're getting there please feed me i'm starving i have no ability to do that almost almost
feed us ads no you look it's getting late it's like 12 30 eastern we gotta finish this
all right we need the sticker sheet again these last two right on both uh dots right right here
right on top and same thing carve the uh mark no bedtime stories just type in like scary
stories into your google search you'll find something interesting i guarantee it
i don't want any fucking ads you bastards the normal stream is already just a long what
that's like the normal stream is just a long ad this is not an ad an ad no if it were an ad
they would have sponsored the labo in the title with that we're getting real close to
be able to go fold lines you got it all of them i'm gonna go swimming really bad like right now
oh well i'll take a bath is he drunk um not as much as i was during the br street i'm like a
solid six at 10 right now for uh inebriation i would say did it all come on okay this is
important so this goes here like that and this folds up like this i guess do you see a semi
circle yes i do but dude is like what the hell are you talking about oh that was a hiccup so
you're going to insert the grip now wait wait wait wait wait wait go back this just comes up
and then this goes in here like that in all the way so it's in all the way
all the way up to the this little slot here and it pushes down well you're fucking going
too fast that goes down here into these slots but they don't really stand that well
the whole back comes up over the whole thing and this comes down down down down
into the slot here as well like that i'm a goddamn genius fold them over here on this
side i'm assuming right okay is the door actually moving no the door is not moving
put that side too all right rub a band i know where it is right here so now what do i do with
this so this latch comes up here it's gonna be hard to get okay then rub a band over it
close it again strange okay then what is this attached to that's in there the rope
band is going to stretch all the way over the hook and the rest of these notches down
here what um they're in that's in there under the circle yeah say hello to the grip
power it up for him it'll help support the rest of the toy con all right almost done
whoa that was a lot that was a lot okay f and i last two sheets all of them no no not all
this is gigantic i think that's it right uh i still have these spongy pieces here
because i was there there's only two pieces left in this one right here
the not even not this piece yet really okay you're getting close google labo blaster you
are the first image result that's bullshit i mean there's no god damn it it's the same clothes
and the same i wear that shirt like four times a week the same hair oh i'll do the i'll do that
pose before the three minutes don't worry how did i get so far away okay uh home stretch almost
done but i can't see the twitch chat so now i'll get this out of the way for now i got
that this piece is the one we need first um how many folds the whole thing all right okay
don't go so fast on me here i got a band juke somebody got banned well maybe think twice
before you say something crazy that's done then this folds in half here like that yeah
yep yep yep yep same deal we got a little uh little waterfall maker
this goes in here now which one there's two slots which one i don't know which one i have
no idea top tabs i think we're in what are those what are the two tabs for see these little
tabs here they should slot into the openings too you can do them at once or one by one
those are not going in i think we're good they're not in though see what i'm saying they like keep
popping out that's as good as it's gonna get my god you're still building this i mean it's a
four-hour project this takes four hours this is not like 10 minutes you see like i'm not
gonna do it yet because i don't want to fucking break it but six hours and four we've been oh
fuck we've been alive for five hours and 20 minutes no hey this is a four this is a four
hour project the goggles were a one hour project we're only 20 minutes behind schedule and i've
been doing a bunch of dumb shit food is ready bye this is not going to work
hey like a full dinner this is like beautiful okay this is fucking amazing salmon couscous
tomatoes and asparagus hey we're gonna go to labo fuck the labo how hot this is fucking 10 out of
10 let's take a look at that salmon oh it's covered in like sauce you didn't oh you didn't
think there's gonna be sauce on this salmon this is this is like looks amazing but i can
assure you we don't eat this thing every day all right let's go okay stop stop stop stop
ah shit all right hold on i'll be right back i'm still here still here right back i'm not
gonna put sauce on the labo this is just too good i can't just not eat it this is like
unbelievable almost done see you in two minutes almost done all right let's go oh that was so
good five star restaurant quality food still a lot left in here all right thank you for your
patience i appreciate it it was she was making food and it was just done and it looked i had
to eat it i had to it was no getting around that one all right so god damn it i got like
fucking salmon oil salmon grease all over this sorry it's just one piece so we're at left side
oh this looks bad uh let's just punch him out don't forget to hydrate no i did i had a glass
of water downstairs do not worry about me i've got a glass of water i've been drinking
water all night that was so good though holy shit i'm so satisfied all right let's fold
we're almost done we're getting close to the end you could say i was there the whole time and
all i got was this lousy stream shit i do have to fold these home stretch only one more part
we're so close to you not being able to enjoy the virtual reality portion of the stream
that's okay though it's all right still the journey is what mattered not the
friends along the way it was the journey there no no was the friends along the way not whatever
it was you know how that goes more pieces there's only one no there's no more there's
like three or four more pieces left and that's it can you wash your hands what no no this is
from this is from when it first came in the room i that's not from right now that's from my
panic realizing how good it looked it's kind of greasy but whatever i never said it wasn't
going to be not greasy i just told you it was going to be done all right what does this do
now am i a good cook no kim is kim is a great cook i am not i just enjoy her wonderful
fucking food that she makes all the time so i am spoiled in that regard for sure she makes great
food what am i doing with this oh god now what how does this go in attaching these two big bits
might be tricky take a good look and make sure everything's facing the same way right down
here okay folds down the whole way oh god that's in there we're down is this piece folded up
okay then where do i go with this hold on this right i think so slide the jaw into place
right through the middle that's in this through and stick it in to keep it secure
good finally time to attach the grip to the rest of the toy cone this all folds out
hold this whole thing out okay this too and then this fucking thing comes in like this
slide the bottom of the grip between the bits of the tube we just opened up
see ah see the angled slots on either side of the hook part of the grip
lower them right down over the sticky outy bits on the tube oh jesus so this goes through
here okay it's in all the way down right yeah it's all the way down
fold this all up stick it in stick it in where oh right here wait what okay that's in
fold this over itself and then attach am i gonna stream in the retirement home
no i'm just gonna retire i'm just i'm just gonna retire you know just be at the blackjack
table all day doing like fucking 50 cent minimums for the rest of my life when i'm like 80 there we
go that's in stream it no i wouldn't have streamed that zoop zoop turn the whole thing around so
that this faces you like this see these tiny tabs flashing next we'll be bringing the top
one down right over the bottom one
okay like that is the tap boy wait all the full lines carefully and slop a little tab into place
that's as good as i'm gonna get it right it should look like this
it does not look like that now it does that's in same thing on the other side
all right get it in there it's in we're so close to being done
another piece from h what is gonna be left after there's only like two pieces left stop
okay fold it all up two three four five six seven eight nine ten awesome all right it's all
folded up now what do we what do we do with it the whole thing turns around
show auto eating no what why would i do that okay so then this part goes over here
so these tabs go in the slot up here facing this way right yeah that's as good as i'm gonna
get it i think that's in down this oh shit that's cool okay then they all uh tab in right
all of them tap in actually these ones get in there this should this is really turning into
like a bazooka this is actually really cool big cardboard bazooka then folds up down
this goes down as well same thing on the other side and we're done just gonna add one more
piece i need a bazooka on stream all right cool it's attached that's attached
then this thing comes up we need two more of these fuck okay one two there's only one
more washer in here that means we're getting close so we start this way by pushing through
uh that's it do we don't close that up okay prefer beef or pork hot dogs depends on the day
could go either way now lift up the big flop and then tuck it away where it belongs in there
wait where nice oh it's done it's almost done i can't wait it is almost i'm looking right at
you i don't know why all right this last remove these three pieces f and h that is it for this
this one's done empty done out what is the last little slide here okay this one's done
there are still a couple of pieces left for the real last little bit okay throw them away who
cares put the piece over it's a microphone stand no it's a a blaster it's a big blaster
two folds i think that's it just two so what does this stick on so this is the holder for
the joycon that's it all right lots of folds that's what you came here for that's why
you're here to watch a guy fold cardboard that's exactly what you're getting no ifs ands or what's
here you're just getting a guy fucking folding cardboard and drinking wine while he does it
that's pretty much all that's here a couple of rumors you know only a few rumors that's it
though it's gonna fold all together and we're gonna stick this up um yep wait a second okay
this is on the right side right right side with the little bumper there stick it on
attach it and then go all the way around and attach the other one
yes okay so here's this side it's correct what does it look wrong is this wrong
no is it i don't think so it's wrong is it wait is it wrong it's wrong are you sure
no it's not it's right what no this is this is right right right no i was right what the hell
making me second guess myself all right all right all right i got it i got it i got it it's
all right don't worry what the hell i thought you guys were fucking with me i was like no don't
do it you're doing it wrong don't don't don't i was like yeah whatever fuck you everyone
just fucking with me that's him that's good so that's where the headset sits so you really
do put your face in the fucking elephant trunk where does that go pop the gear over the grommet
for what left side it's strange for what kind of doesn't doesn't fit over there okay so it
just sits there come on get on there you're killing me line this up with a hole my god
this is elaborate no it's good for children's developing brains shit damn it i really
how many times did i do this today get off before i break it come on what happened where did it go
this i don't i have no idea where it is got it got it now this goes on here right let me just
see him do it first before i fucking do anything stupid yes you motherfucker no no no it's this
first then this then this then this okay finally jesus got it done let's get shimmied in here
now what through there and then all the way down and that's in and then close it up
both sides and there so this is like a little antenna is that could that be everything or try
to contain your excitement while we do some important checks is the hold of the joy con
only rotation should only rotate in 90 degrees 90 degrees that's it no more than that got it
a few more hand checks now hold the grip with the wish every hand is more comfortable and then
cock it right pull the sticky outy bit back to your click then push the button that's how
you fire the blaster what button what are you kidding what i don't know how this is working
wow that's actually really cool damn well all right yeah what what is this sorcery that i agree
that's fucking insane uh if you build everything properly the clicker should make a nice noise
it does could it be that is the blaster done no not quite just a bit more you can finally
play with the blaster that might be a good tactic a good glass of wine all right one more
stuff this is it guys i'm done it's over i'm gonna play i'm gonna tell you how fun it is
uh-oh guys i'm sorry that's it it's time for you to be turned off okay get the joy con
left and right ready there's a song you've been listening to the whole time so joy con
r goes in the front holy shit okay so it goes in here it's in there now what the bump on the
back of the what should rest nicely in the opening it does joy con left goes in here
just kind of slides in this part that's in now i mean the goggles right let's do a quick
check from this side can you see the bump on the back of the controller poking through here
poking for where i can see it yeah i can see the green now open the cover so that can we can
insert the vr goggles oh oh fuck i need these okay then this go is oh this is going to be like
a submarine what you actually have to do this this is ridiculous okay so that's in what about
the safety thing raise the cover to hold the vr goggles okay so go like this so that's in
no i don't take it out that's it i did it now i'm gonna play while you guys just watch
me look like a dickhead on camera how do i do this wait doesn't this insert the
console into the goggles how what oh shit hold on this is gonna go in here i don't even care
like this i spent five hours six hours making this i'm gonna get the fruits of my labor right
now it's in it's locked in here we go attach the vr goggles and the joy con they're in there
push the button to start what button what the fuck this is crazy looking downtown defense
guys if i could only describe to you how cool this was wow this bullet drop too
uh this has to be like 480p there's no way this is more than 720 this is like 520p
it's i can't even see what's going on and it hurts my face i did it yeah the resolution
is very low this is pretty cool though if i was eight if i mean if i was like 18 if i was
like 28 this is still cool like i made this this koopas koopa troopas
i wonder if i can just put this on the screen can you hear the sounds
i mean it's cool defeat all enemies within one minute you got it i think i did a pretty good
job his his little knees this is cool take regular breaks yeah hey don't tell me what
to do nintendo look at how cool that looks you're in it dude you're in it right now you're in it
wow it's your turn i can't i don't there's no way for me i can't i can't do that
i'll show you i'll show you relax relax okay okay sure you have blaster in the middle
and you shoot shoot shoot it's great it's not that great it's kind of great
we aim around kind of dumb actually
this thing is awesome this is cool i love this thing the fact that it makes the actual
shooting sounds i don't put it back in i wonder can you see this if i put it back in here
i don't think you can no this little gun though is this is awesome i'm gonna hold on
well there you go there's uh six hours of making a labo it's only like uh one two am
there you go the finest build you could ever see the craftsmanship was there it's too bad i
couldn't mirror it so you guys could see what the hell i was doing you forgot the pose
there wrong one what are you talking about
kid cartridge what are you talking about the pose oh oh all right
i thought you guys were talking about do like a cool you got a missile launcher pose
oh fuck all right how is it like this i gotta get the whole thing
okay ready like that show the mouth how is it i can't show the mouth is that good all right
you're done you're done all right boom i don't have the other ones looks like a smelling
device i gotta find it i don't know where the tnt is what's going on the camera right okay let
me move this give me one second i'm gonna move this out of the way i wasn't lying up two
different socks on who cares all right give me one let me one second no leg day i haven't
been in the gym in like fucking two years what are you talking about show auto auto no no no auto
all right let's hang out i wish i could show you more labo but that's uh that's really all there
is hair is a little screwed up but it could be worse if you google image uh child eating
salmon dinner you're the first result if only that were the case if only all right let's move
some of this out of the way we'll hang out we'll do the bits close this out that was really
fun though that was cool i just can't really show you how cool it is unless you were here
and your head was inside the headset this this has to go over here all right there we go let's
take up the whole space can i scream i don't want to scream really loud no thanks i don't
think i'm gonna do that what happens if the rubber band snaps in the blaster gonna have to
make a new one gonna have to get it i gotta buy another one i found your old demo reel you
still looking for a job no not anymore all right let's get the bits um that took us about
six and a half hours or should we just relax for a little bit wine cam there's still plenty
left that didn't go too crazy yeah bits and rely yeah we'll just hang out with him with like
we can put like 45 more minutes seven hours eight hours no no geoguessor everyone just
kind of chill but uh we'll go for the bits why not we're just hanging out here i'm gonna
change to irl if you watched that uh travesty of a stream of building a labo thanks for watching
we're gonna just chill for like an hour into irl just chatting i guess right uh i gotta change
the title to uh wine hangout how's that sound that sounds pretty good all right uh the
lighting seems weird in here doesn't it don't you think what are my plans for the future i
don't have any plans i don't have very many plans color correct it let's actually go into
it and just move it around why can i not i there it is jesus auto fucking white balances on get
out of here whoa oh no no no no no no no no not okay that looks better not by very much
but it does let's put the contrast up i gotta make this smaller it looks better uh this
needs to be lowered a lot hey look it's my room that's a wide angle of the room too
sweat check empty completely fine it's been six almost six and a half hours we're good to go
let's lower this a little uh whatever i don't fucking i really don't care ah who cares
whatever i'll just sit up what shade of lipstick is this this is uh called midnight red see all
right let's go back into the bits i hope you had fun i did it was blessed as always
using playing the labo it's a lot of fun is this a logitech c920 it is and that's a c922
so the plan is to stream tomorrow let's hope i get up yeah we're good i'm not chugging wine
what are you talking about all right yeah this thing's been a bit it's it's look at it it's
a pretty big bottle there's probably like one more glass in here just about he thought about it
for a second ditch the glass you don't have to pretend why would i drink it out of the bottle
it's got an air raid all right so six and a half hours ago we had don't stop streaming
until the bottle's done then i'll see you on fucking like monday or tuesday i'll see you on
like tuesday if that's the case uh what dreams uh dreams i come back next week i have i've been
i've been trying to work on it have you done the dreams tutorials that's the answer there
that's your answer dream seems a lot like labo it is in a way i look drunk how do i like
improve my image all right there we go no that looks worse you just look greasy i've been
sitting for like six and a half hours no i gotta go like this let's tell it there we go
hey we got good lighting now all right let's uh let's go through the bits
answer your questions we had five dollars from mr comcast earlier this afternoon check the
closet there's nobody in there there's nobody in that closet i can assure you there's nobody
in there i promise you no one's in that closet what is this okay i just opened up the
a tab of that kid the labo blaster and i thought it was me it's not it's not this nobody
in the fucking closet it's just trash there's nothing in there see there's nobody in there
anyways uh thank you to mr comcast for the five dollars hey germa john comcast here just let
you know that i broke my arm while trying to climb over the fence to your back garden
so now i have to wear a comcast haha just a little humor for you there anyway just stopping
by to let you know that we hair comcast are getting together a pro fortnight team to boost
our sales and we'd love to have you on it we know how much you love getting that victory
royale and also how much you love being mean to kids call us we're waiting i'm not i'm not
mean to kids i'm not i am not mean to kids kids are great what uh thank you mr
comcast with five dollars thank you schwarz schwarz ed for the four dollars they say l
l isn't like a loss like i lost something thank you for the four dollars regardless mr uh schwarz
mr schwart you asked for it all night there you see there's the dog where's dato see you guys
woke him up to do this shit no he was already awake there you go there's dato
hello look at how tired he is okay put him to bed where he belongs in bed he's he's like
shedding okay good night dato i'll see you soon he's just like that dog dog you're like babies
you know what i mean just like that was kim yeah he's too perfect for this world he is
fancy he's so good he really is he's like the best dog ever he is eight he is eight
years old he's fantastic i love him imitative baby being picked up i just did uh but we had
uh two dollars and 50 cents from devakitty hey jerry remember your old ass stream where
you were playing layers of fear and you should totally play an actual scary game
and he plans to play amnesia another really spooky but good mod for it's called amnesia
white knight anybody hope you enjoyed labo wine boy wine boy um the last horror game we did
was dread halls and i can't really say that i have plans to do anything else they just kind
of happen they just kind of happen i don't plan it if i feel like playing a horror game then
we'll play a horror game right i don't have like a plan to do it you know there's no real
plans layers of fear 2 is yeah when is that coming out when's layers of fear 2 is that
like a thing the shrek game i can't wait to play shrek 2 uh but thank you devakitty
mr comcast is back again with five more dollars uh hey jerma john comcast here again
just letting you know that we sadly had to disband our pro fortnight team due to us
being banned from every major esports event so anyway we noticed that you had a fuck load
of wine so since you're drunk now is probably the best time to ask will you be
coming to my 450th birthday party if you're wondering how old i am or how i'm so old
because every evil corporation ceo is immortal you make me die uh we need a clown to perform
you'd be perfect okay all right and that's you got you got to the point there uh i'm
gonna have to respectfully decline your uh offer to come be a clown thank you though
appreciate it clown makeup tutorial i thought i don't have a clown makeup tutorial for you
just put makeup all over your face and go like this with red and then do like orange here
and then laugh and scream at people but thank you mr comcast thank you jess you got it for
the 250 germ finally finished that painting thanks for being such an inspiration on more
ways than one jerma heart let's see let's take a look this is fucking awesome hold on where
did it go viva las vegas baby let's put it on screen this is from jess you got it the next
big stream will be soon this is a high resolution that elvis the real elvis
this is awesome thank you so much this is fucking amazing viva las vegas baby great job
great fucking job thank you so much that was from uh wow nice album cover
it's it just looks great it just looks great that's all there is to it
uh that's from jess you got it thank you that was great it looked fantastic the lights and the
the lighting work and the color work somebody said the cape looked amazing yeah there's some
talented motherfuckers here i don't mean that term like that like oh motherfuckers
huh what oh it can't be it can't be the end of the wine took a week to finish it
and i just i've been drinking for like six hours i'm not even sweating either this is
like a non-sweat wine this is a big deal this is actually a big fucking deal i am not sweating
at all i'm going to remember this brand isn't this is a no sweat brand uh but thank you jess
you got it thank you for that amazing painting picture looks great uh deadly sp thanks for
five dollars when the next labo comes out you should stream it in a vineyard in nappa valley
just 12 hours of you getting shit faced with an endless supply of fancy red
and overpriced cardboard in sully california sully and shut shelly california the original
thing i thought would be funny was to do this on a mountain to stream the labo vr on a mountain
and just try to build it but the wind made that impossible there's no way i wouldn't be
able to do it in the pre-stream chat like two weeks ago we talked about me doing a
labo on a mountain no it was impossible it's it's too windy it would never fucking work
unfortunately although there are some like calm places imagine just like
let me do this piece now it's six hours of that it would take like two days i can't wait
to get in that dunk tank it's gonna be fucking so much fun you guys have no idea how much how
much i'm looking forward to that stream it's gonna be fucking so fun camping stream no no i
don't camp i suck at it hey sayus or souse thanks for the ten dollars souse this will be the first
and last time i donate i appreciate you so much thank you well thanks for the fucking ten bucks
thanks for the incredibly generous fucking donation ten dollars is more than enough money i could
ever assume anyone would ever give somebody on the internet so thank you i really appreciate
that much love to you thanks for the ten bucks keldos thanks for the 350 germ boy just
wanted to say that you always make my boring and sad days a bit better you're the only one
that can make me laugh with your stupid jokes and boomer ramblings and for that i thank you
very very much germa one guy germa heart ps uh you stink please wash no i don't think so
not today not today not to put both arms i'll show you both we're good we are so good right
uh but keldos i'm fucking happy that you can hang out here i i'm shocked all the time that people
will think it's fun to watch some dickhead drink wine for six hours and play with a kid's
cardboard toy we go back and forth we have fun i'm just glad that you enjoyed it's a blast
for me so i hope you have fun too i am so happy that you have fun and we both have fun
at the same time if it wasn't fun i wouldn't be doing it let's just put it that way for
real thank you thank you keldos now we had five community subs from dr stein thank you
dr stein again for your five community subs if it's not fun why bother thank you that's
exactly why if i'm not having a good time then what am i gonna pretend to have a good time
that's not gonna happen maybe like pretend to have a good time for six hours what like
that's not gonna happen uh rare pepe body lotion thank you rare pepe body lotion for
the 10 bucks what happened when you went to the dentist today he replaced them all all these
see all new all the way back he's got all new teeth i just had him i had him pull out that
he pulled him out and put him back in but thank you rare pepe body lotion that's an
interesting name rare pepe body lotion what's this remember dentist is fucking in my mouth
like dentist is in my mouth doing these things remember dentist is fucking
that if you weren't there at the very very end of the last stream uh two days ago i thought
this i didn't i forgot to turn the stream off and i was watching the same clip like four five
six times in a row just needed just needed to know just needed to know uh but kimchi w thanks
for the events uh this week your streams have been my lifesaver after smoking the devil's lettuce
almost every day for the past six years come to the realization that i was addicted now i'm on
my fourth day clean your streams have really helped distract me and keep me laughing ps
kind of get some germa hearts in chat for support yeah i mean if whatever road that you
decide to take you just take care of yourself you know uh good that you kind of saw that you
had an issue there and you made some steps to correct it that's all you can do it's just a
series of trying to figure out what you can do and trying to do it that's really that's pretty
much life man i'm really really happy that you can kind of make those steps to go in the
direction that you think is the right direction so good luck to you much luck to you hang in
there keep going i'm happy to be somebody that you can watch and laugh to and this community
of hilarious fucking people figure out what you need to do and do it germa 985 that's i mean
that's not a quote that's just if you can figure out what you need to do to make your
life better then do it just do it that's the best uh advice that anybody could ever give
do and do it everyone you heard the man do it no but it's it's true everybody has
their own path everybody has their own stuff that they're working on that they're doing
and not two two no two people are the same so it's hard to you know everyone's so different
yesterday you said tomorrow so just do it wow what a statement no but yeah that's really it's
everybody's got their own shit to deal with everybody's got their own path find yours
now you can go off that shit what am i fighting joel it's already done say something how can
you say something so brave be careful you might punch yourself oh what is it oh what
no what the fuck mosquitoes up tonight what's going on here uh but hey uh zack or zake
thank you zacky or zacky zake z-a-k-k-e for the five bucks hey germy cheers from finland
hello from uh america i was once on a cruise ship to sweden i took a huge shit
in my cabin bathroom but the toilet didn't flush after multiple tries i didn't know what to do so
i found a cleaning lady she didn't speak any finnish or english so i took her to the bathroom
i pointed at it and said look in swedish and pressed the toilet button the toilet flushed
perfectly did this really happen that's oh that's a copy pasta i don't know shit guys i
don't i really don't i don't know any of these i don't have time to fucking know every meme
uh thank you zake for the five dollars though germa lied about ace attorney he didn't lie he
told the truth he tried to be as transparent as he could with talking about how he wasn't
sure if he wanted to play the game at all and it wasn't for him uh he didn't lie about it
though he did tell you he wasn't maybe not gonna play it though hey mr squishy thanks
for the 250 kim wants to know if you want pizza and if you took the extension cord
yeah put the camera in uh thank you mr squishy i'll take salmon salmon sounds pretty good tonight
that was fucking amazing uh swiggity swanky thanks for the 250 may the fourth be with you
by the way nice bulge hey thanks is it the may fourth it is may fourth i'm getting i'm
going i'm getting off the internet you guys thought i was streaming tomorrow i'm not i'm
not gonna be on anywhere near the internet on may 4th it's too late too maybe too late for
you not too late for me it's may 5th tomorrow yeah i know lore what do you mean i don't know
what day it is wait it's may 4th right now it's cinco de mayo tomorrow what i'm getting off i'm
not going out of the internet i'm not fucking going anywhere i'm blocking myself in my i'm
going to sleep all day tomorrow cinco de mayo no way i ain't going anywhere uh but thank you
swiggity swanky for the may the fourth be with you i was gonna get a full darth vader
oh it's my darth vader t-shirt what am i stupid hey me flebel thanks for the three bucks this
dinosaur joke is hilarious no way what's the opposite of hilarious all right terrible this
joke is terrible was it you didn't like the dinosaur vr thing it wasn't you didn't think that
was funny no we loved it the shower one was the best i didn't even think about that i'm just
like watching someone in the shower uh we liked the turtle part no that's good it's fine whatever
uh what's the opposite of hilarious i don't even know what the sounds were playing
i i typed in dinosaur t-rex sounds and press enter and then open the first one and then put
the goggles up i had no idea what the fuck was happening uh swiggity swanky thanks to
250 i'm still backed up on vods in the first live stream i decided to catch and you're
watching turtle porn and giving chat the adult talk i gave the adult talk when oh the point
yeah but that's that's real though that's real life uh thank you swiggity swanky though
thank you trin art for the tons of community subs haunting gave five community subs don't
want to miss that future gamer gave 250 just made this video let's take a look this is
called germa shows us vr i feel like this is gonna be pretty funny let's get to something
stream you know we're gonna do this together it's not fair come here it's not fair you guys
should be able to do it too really top 100 funniest fails ever gamers are idiots top 100
fails ever ever uh thank you future gamer for the 250 in that video uh thank you too thank you
again for the 13 bucks pinwheel kills germa and endgame we had a lot of money come in right
there we had 50 50 bucks from juno upsetto 50 from ferodian weapon 15 from spoons for
self-defense uh weird whisk card thanks with three dollars in the middle of all that
no messages thank you that's thank you we also had 250 from strawberry pulp germa they are
coming for me and i can't stop them all i want is to see auto before they get me please
this is my last request they are they you saw them you saw auto auto is there torah t20 community
substance for torah t20 community substance it's a lot thank you so much torah we had
100 bucks from magellan seven dollars eight dollars from dr steen twice in a row uh yank
out your hair and make a clone that's not how that works you need blood and uh drink
some grape juice this is grape juice it's just been it just sits in a barrel for like 16 years
fermented grape juice that's right uh but dr steen that was like 15 16 dollars from dr steen
afro ninja thanks for the five dollars hard days but you make it funnier at least
hope you get through whatever's going on thank you for the five dollars and i wish
you the best thank you afro ninja c4g thanks for the 250 how come you never do the
germa shuffle anymore that used to be your signature dance move seems like you forgot about it what is
that what's what's the germa shuffle am i stuck here jeez i'm gonna go forward the fortnight
this thing that's not mine that's like that's backpack kid the germa shuffle i don't know what
that is i'm scooting in the chair is the germa shuffle your alzheimer's has progressed
pretty rapidly uh thank you freudian weapon for the 15 dollars freudian weapon the spontaneity of
these streams is something i find so appealing like what will he stream next helifino every
stream is another pleasant surprise well uh i don't know either so we're both in that boat
together it's a surprise for me too every day oh right there's nothing in here but thank
you for the 15 bucks bad planning no it's not bad bad planning no i just don't do the same thing
every day now that's it for that bottle but we do what we do when we do when we do it
i have a blast every time did he drink the whole bottle yeah he did uh yes he did what a
drunk it's been seven hours you guys how many okay hold on a second it's just wine it's
i'm not drinking like fucking vodka out of the bottle it's wine seven 50 milliliters
over the course of seven hours that one bottle of wine in seven hours that's the serving size
my mom can handle wine but moms can handle wine better than you i don't give a shit about
your mom's alcohol tolerance i don't care for all i know your mother i don't know what i
don't know who your mother is rude i was just told that mom's drink i'm just defending myself
i'm not trying to be rude i'm just defending i'm pulling the captain america shield up and
going my mom's better than this streamer no not drinking wine maybe they are what's the
percentage it's uh wine is not that high it's 16 16 alcohol by volume it is copper and thief
red blend it's good i'm a dog mom that counts i'm you get i'm not okay i was not the vr stream
made me three times more drunk i'm all right right now i mean i am i'm i'm a little drunk
right now but i'm not it's not terrible i'm not like putting twitch stocks on the stream
you understand this is like a different kind of drunk i'm not like doing back flips over
here what was i drinking that night what was that what was i drinking that night it was
wine but what kind of wine it's a crack wine i don't know it was it was definitely like crack
wine i was fucking crazy that night uh but professor dante thanks for the five dollars
professor dante they say meep professor dante thank you dante for the five dollars and ten
cents freudian weapon thanks with 250 on top of all the other money you've given not to
be that guy but salmon on pizza sounds pretty good uh fish can be not i mean people
octopus on pizza all the time so is an octopus number one pizza topping in japan i i'm pretty
sure that's a fact no yeah it is octopus on pizza is the number one topping of pizza in japan
too expensive yeah it would probably be a pretty big it would be expensive wouldn't
the japanese put mayo on their pizza i've had mayo on pizza before i've had a blt pizza
they're fucking amazing mayo people people like it's so mad if you like mayonnaise like
who cares mayo with turkey mayo with fucking tuna fish mayo with egg salad really mayo with
tuna with tuna salad you don't like that how could you egg salad is gross ban that guy for
life i'll do it okay got it hey uh what freige thanks for the five bucks five dollars what
freige streamer claims racing cars all day is boring while folding cardboard for six hours
i don't fold cardboard every day all day every single day hearts for my boy auto is so cute
right now hearts for my boy is what kim just said he really is so cute hearts for my boy
why do i do this you notice i do that often i go like oh let me tell you what is that what
is this let me i do that all the time i'm not italian i'm like irish and polish well i don't
what does this mean i'm not italian lore you guys knew that already i'm not italian
i'm not italian no i'm not italian what what he everyone's like oh yeah yeah yeah you're
italian okay yeah i'm not lying lying about what about being irish and polish
that's like that that's like 10 10 elbertsons up the line you know what i'm saying i'm not
slavic polish you have the vodka resistance passive that makes you immune to vodka you
can drink a whole bottle take an ancestry test get the fuck out of here that wine looks
disgusting what why it's the it's the fucking dishwasher that's what you're saying i don't want
to do it no i'm not doing that my mother's side is i don't even you don't need to know
any of this shit i'm a goddamn elbertson that's all you need to know you don't need
anything else i'm irish and polish and that's it let's burn my eyes does wine burn your eyes
this must be bad wine elbertson i know my lore anyways put add it to the fucking wiki
irish and polish that's not a joke uh genie boy thanks for the three bucks hey jeremy you're
going to go through many changes in my life now that i'm at my final stages of college
it's been overwhelming and stressful i want to thank you for all although i want to thank
you all the way from chile for remaining as my constant and reliable source of joy and
entertainment during these bittersweet moments thank you uh college is tough once you get out
you look sweaty how about now i got like i'm one of the size cock-eyed don't fucking bring
that up ever again i just brought it up talking to myself um but for real you um congratulations
college is fucking hard college is that's an accomplishment hopefully you can figure out
something to do afterwards all of them from chile uh thanks for being here congratulations
on getting through uh the final stage of college stick with it be careful the last few months can
be hard you got all kinds of shit to do so what did what did kim say what did kim say what did
kim say let's go to school wait wait my man's so handsome i was gonna wink but i think i
might be too drunk to wink let's try you think so i got it i still got it i'm fucking
30 it's free and i still got it i still got it okay i'll be 45 and then i'll go down
but uh thank you uh genie boy uh oh i'm gonna fuck this one up this is a lot of money too
phylactery phylac to phylactery lich gave 50 bucks eat more food i like it eat more salmon
i like it ah shit was that like a fetish thing that's why i turned the camera off
just give me 50 dollars everything can be a fetish but come on let me look let's get
my defense here let me give you some defense eat more food i like it eat more salmon fetish
bucks are huge you can make some serious money do i do i just have to eat salmon on stream
if i just ate food on stream is that like what would happen is that it salmon fetish
no there's no way maybe he wanted you to be healthy yeah that's probably it you guys have
been you guys get your mind in the gutter why do you have braided hair i'm leaving it
i ain't gonna fix it fuck that it just it just happened i don't know how i have no idea i
don't i don't know why that happened but anyways thank you uh phila phil phil phylactery lich for
the 50 bucks and the food comment thank you that's a lot of fucking money would i ever
return to overwatch probably not the big multiplayer competitive kind of games i just i don't do
them anymore i just can't i don't have the time to do it anymore i don't have the i just
can't do it i really can't it's a lot it's a big time sink to really get into again
no i can't do it but i hope it's i hope it's still fun i do hey mr squishy thanks for the 250
figured you'd like to know i finished my bottle of absinthe great stream fuck you finished a
bottle of absinthe before i got through a bottle of red blend oh that's relaxing as fuck
save that one put it in there hey but no but you finished the whole bottle of absinthe
did you do the thing where you like put like the sugar cube and you melt the sugar cube
out of the spoon and put it in the absinthe dig shot that's too much work for me just give me
the fucking red blend and we'll be on well we'll be on our way drunk man no you messed up the
hair i what am i why is it like four different pieces of hair here wait a minute this is
important it's like five people's hair right that's weird i that's that's like 10 people's
hair remember hey remember this i'm not going to do it it's too ugly the peasant hair
like i could be like right now ready wait wait let's get a better one ready like okay
peasant hair that doesn't look that bad from over here it does you look terrifying i know
uh deleted laughing my ass off thanks for the five dollars hey germa great to see you so
successful in a platform that rewards you for your creativity keep shredding those records
my dude much love thanks that's thank you any milestone for viewers or subscribers it's
fucking i can't believe it thank you i just hope that the people that are here
if you stumble on the stream you can relax and have a good time it could be a thousand it
could be five thousand it could be ten thousand i just want us all to have a good time that's
it good cool thanks germa
relax do a cooking stream yeah maybe one day i'll do a cooking stream and i'll do my famous
salmon you saw a way better version of it like fucking didn't work uh but thank you
voyeuristic vol for the five dollars you ever consider the possibility that you're actually
a failed prototype for a human labo imprinted with false memories i think it realistically
explains your labo obsession it's an existential exercise i just think it's it's just so stupid
that i know that nobody else does so i so i do it cam will do it with me yeah that'll be fun
why does this guy sound like he's about to cry me i think i think i'm gonna cry
but like right now what do you mean right like right right the second what are you
talking about me are they talking about me are you talking about me you fuckers ate all the
pasta in the fridge and i only had one serving hey i had a little bit of the pasta it was good
hey dr stein again dr stein 15 dollars hey germa today me and my girlfriend of three
years went through a nasty breakup and i'm the most depressed i've ever been in my entire life
i don't know what to do going forward and your stream was so helpful today i can't thank you
enough for your hilarity and humor really helped me out that's that's rough that's tough
because that's a long time but it obviously was not meant to be right i'm really sorry to
hear that hopefully you're both okay hopefully you're doing all right just give yourself some
time give yourself some time three years is a long time but depending on i don't know how old
you are or what your stage of life is right now but um just keep pegging away because
you here's the one thing that people don't really talk about with that kind of scenario
is three years and and you got a breakup but what happens if it was five or six or seven
or eight you know what i mean so you know you you you date somebody you spend time with them
and then you know if it didn't work out it didn't work out i wish you the best hopefully
you can find it again of course right don't feel too bad don't feel too down it's going
to be it's going to be hard for a little while but just stay on track and uh let life play out
right darryl is best when he's drunk because he isn't himself i i act like this all the time
what um you guys act like i'm fucking destroyed what i can't i have a few drinks and all of
a sudden it's like ah you know he's like a real person now yeah what what how red's the
tongue let's see it's like purple you sound like you're gonna cry that's not fucking true
germa unplugged no i like i understand let me like let me let me give you a little bit of
rebuttal though it's 11 15 pacific it's like 2 a.m eastern we've had some drinks the stream
is over you know we've basically been hanging out it obviously this you know this is still
like 2000 there's still a lot of people here but you know we you know we just the the broadcast
has ended we're just hanging out now we do this frequently so you know this is the i i get real
sometimes at the end of these streams and we're just chilling and doing whatever it's not
you know what is this we business there's 2000 fucking people here there's 2000 people
there's 2000 people here it's a way it's a it's always a way it's always a way he's high he went
up an octave that's how you know he gets serious he went up an octave it gets serious when it
goes up an octave i'm not gonna why would i cry on stream right now uh niall aureon thanks
with three bucks so is germa con gonna be a thing uh it's very possible it's very very
possible i wouldn't call it germa con though i'd call it like i rent out space for like
four hours and if you're around you can come i don't i wouldn't call it anything but yeah uh
kane kane 5707 gave 10 community subs uh about 40 minutes ago thank you kane really appreciate
that thank you for the immense community subs jexpo can you try to do a flip yeah sure
okay same joke as the last time exact same no literally no difference at all can you put both
earphones in oh i don't think i can no i can't hey ghost twink thanks for the five dollars
best stream i've seen in a while thanks germa thank you that was good hold on that's pretty
good that's my catchphrase now better not be uh thank you for the five dollars though that's
a polite way of saying your last one hasn't been so great what were the last two what sam and max
was fucking blast and then what was right before that what was right what was the last
stream what was before that dream dreams was fucking dreams was a lot of fun mordhau you
didn't like what mordhau dreams sam and max that was those are those are great streams
mordhau sucked why mordhau sucked why what because i was just playing dreams was a lot of
fun it was one guy i've had fun like it doesn't matter like look all right listen it i i just
not every stream has to be like no never mind never but we don't have to go it not every stream
has to be like the green screen kind of caliber of stuff you know the sam and max was fun we
just chilled and we played a game for like six hours it's just fun to do that you know
you know nobody's expecting i know i know i'm just kidding around ever since oh crashing here
ever since germa quit the vr scene it's been downhill i didn't quit vr how high can i go
lower your fucking i'm tell lower your volume i'm serious i'm not kidding did i break the
internet i think i just like fucked up the internet i dropped like a thousand frames right
there i told you to lower your volume i did just say that what the fuck i just i just said
it i said lower your volume please i'm gonna my stream was lagging when you said lower your
volume all right hold on i'll try again i'm gonna load up i'm done doing this that's it
that's all you get i'm done bingo sunshine thanks for the 250 who got you who you got
in the nl germa who you got in the nl in the national league lowest note
my girlfriend's not gonna sleep in the same bed with me tonight
it's the couch it's the couch for us what do you mean us like all right yeah let's go i'm
gonna take the stream down to the couch you're gonna watch me sleep okay what a fucking weird
i would never let anybody watch me sleep ever if i okay listen who knows what kind of
fucking weird shit you might say in your sleep like kiss kiss me kiss me kiss me kiss me
imagine if i if i did that i wouldn't have i'd have no explanation for it
oh yeah i love kool-aid kool-aid yummy kool-aid poor kool-aid in my cup please
kool-aid kool-aid in my cup yum you'd be terrified you'd be fucking terrifying no
all right we're almost done uh thank you calm brad kurticus screw that smoke it to enhance the
stream bingo sun but wait wait bingo sunshine what does that even mean who do you have in the
who do you got in the nl like national league like baseball what do you mean nl who you got
in the nl i watch you oh god he does talk in his sleep sometimes all right well uh what
about the okay kim can corroborate this story listen to this shit one time so listen this is a
big deal uh one time get this out of my ear so one time i was asleep and those people that
have slept in had a kind of weird dreams before you can maybe relate to this so i
had a dream where i was lying in my bed and it was very normal i just was in my bed
looking at the ceiling and the door is there the bed is here there's a bureau over there
okay whatever i'm not awake and i know i'm i'm dreaming and it's weird and i'm like what the
fuck this something's weird here i'm definitely this is real but it's not real i'm asleep
okay so kim is next to me in bed and i look over and i feel no no no no and you know when
you're dreaming and you panic because you know you're in a dream and it's really real but
you're not lucid i've lucid dreamed a few times before but i can't i've never been able to do
for like at least a few years so i'm sitting there going i'm dreaming i'm dreaming fuck i
gotta wake up this is terrifying this is i'm panicking i'm panicking okay wake up please wake
up wake up wake up wake the fuck up wake up and i woke up and i'm in bed okay what's this
where am i okay no no no just in bed there's the door there's the bureau there's kim i'm still
dreaming no this is not real i'm still in a dream this is fucked up this i'm not i'm not
awake i wasn't awake i was still dreaming so i'm lying there again second this is waking up
i thought i woke the fuck up i'm still in the dream this time i start to hear a weird
noise coming from the door it's like i'm like fuck no i just want to get up i just want to go
i gotta stream in like fucking two hours so i fucking please wake up wake up wake up wake
the fuck up okay i'm awake door get up i get the fuck out of bed get me the fuck out of
here okay what's over here there's a light let me uh i i just have to make sure i'm awake
flick the light switch up and down guess what when you're in a dream light switches do not
work you want to test if you're dreaming flick a light switch if it doesn't work you're dreaming
so i flick the light switch like three times and the light doesn't turn on so i'm just like
i'm fucking stuck here forever and i'm like i went back down i went to go lie down
and i fucking please just fucking wake up god and i wake up again and i'm not awake yet
but only this time by the way this was like 40 minutes in my brain not like 10 seconds so i
wake up i'm like no this is not right again i look over kim looks at me and she's looking
over like this staring at my eyes and i'm just like that's not the fucking real kim
that's not kim i know it's not kim and she's like what's wrong she had a real dick real
fucked up demon voice and she got up and she was like like towards me and i was like oh shit
like i grabbed her by like the head and she's sitting there going like
like fucking snakes coming out of like all over her face and shit was fucking horrifying
and i'm grabbing her by the neck like trying to like strangle and i'm like no
this can't be real and i'm trying to move her over and finally kim in real life woke me up
in real life and i'm just like like i could pull that out of the fucking matrix
and she was like you all right you okay and i'm just like yeah i'm fine i'm fine what's
wrong what do you mean what's wrong you don't want anyone to even know that you're fucking
dreaming and being like a psycho so i'm like yeah it's just like i'm fucking tired you know
it's like tired what's wrong what's the matter and she said she said you were lying there
on your back and you were going like this that exact fucking noise just like
and that's why she woke me up yeah mouth closed too mouth closed high pitch just
exactly like that he's being brit yes this is real this is real this is not made up
oh it's terrifying i thought i was never gonna get out and i thought i was stuck there forever
she saved your life i i know right what if like i didn't have like a girlfriend
what if i was stuck there forever what if i never got out of the dream world that would have been
dead i woke up like five times oh i had such a bad headache i felt like shit that day man just
lying there just like silent just like she said no emotion you were just lying there doing that
something fucking wrong with me what was i dreaming about all that shit that i at that
moment i was like strangling her because she was a demon remember she was like
what's wrong and i was like that's a demon that's not even kim that's a fucking demon
you okay dude
uh thank you jack for the 250 wait till you see this shit
oh i look like 60 oh my god the same picture
here you go here's a link is that funny why is my posture like that i don't know because i'm
fucking 60 why can i not paste this oh yeah yeah that's fucking hilarious thank you
thank you jack thank you jack for the 250 and that image jerma lied about fruity loops
thanks for the 250 hey jerma didn't watch the stream because it was boring
come on uh hope you had a good star wars nerd consumerism day
i had fun all right it doesn't matter you said that an hour ago how long were you here for
you probably watched the whole damn thing hey sorry didn't watch the stream i mean i've been
here for like four and a half hours though thank you jerma lied about fruity loops hey
john horns thanks for the 250 hey jerma finally got a big boy job so it's hard to catch you
anyway i'm drunk off my ass on borg which is half vodka half water and meo energy give it a try
i love the v-neck take half vodka half meo water i like v-necks
v-neck i know that person really that person got it john horns gets it v-necks
accentuates your fucking clavicle and it shows off your fucking dimple here your neck dimple
it's a good look i can pull it off i can pull off a v-neck i've got the fucking neck dimple
and the clavicle to fucking go for it v-necks are for lizard people watch his eyes watch his
eyes watch his eyes if they move really fast back and forth he's a fucking lizard watch his
eyes slow it down somebody slow it down he might be he might be slow it down what if his
eyes turn green for a second hey effectator effected a resident editor thanks for the 250
i finally committed to teaching myself how to program this game idea vet for a long time
if i complete it in the next six years will you play it on stream and tear it to fucking shreds
probably yeah yeah i mean i don't know why not if you've done in six years i mean whatever
i'll be fucking 40 hey deleted laughing my ass off hopefully this is funny and no one has done
it before this is called sell out germa sell out germa is this video's title let's take
a look at it see how it is i'm ready i'm ready i'm ready for me money thank you the five dollars
deleted laughing my ass up thank you so much and did we sub in the last two minutes
hey wonder bread thanks for the ten dollars thanks for all the laughs and always great
content first vid i watched was grab that auto loved him ever since thank you that was a
lot of fun to make it was we did the the christmas thing on stream the gra the not the
grandpa the christmas uh stuff please tell me about twitch prime oh okay i don't know
if you know this or not but um god uh you know yeah there's a service if you have amazon
you can link up your twitch and you can subscribe to see you know it doesn't cost
you anything thank you though wonder bread for real that means a lot thanks for the 10 bucks
and but that's a that's a long time grab that auto has a special place in my heart so
uh thank you to squamst for the squimps for the five dollars germa when you have nice hair
can we call you perma yeah like right now say no so i feel better about myself uh jacoby
thanks for the four dollars bleed purple dab you stink oh sure thing let's pretend i did
thanks for the four dollars uh grapple mace thanks for the 250 nice ringlet bangs
i don't have bangs ringlet bangs oh you ruined your hair before you read the bits
now that's not good that doesn't look good at all how did you get your hair like that
i was born i was born do you guys find it hard to wink with both any you know your
right or left eye like ready what looked more natural left or right i need to know
this one looks better yeah it's almost like i can feel my face pulling over here when i
wink with my right eye like what are you what are you doing you sneaking in here
why are you sneaking in here why do you have like a ripped up shirt on this is yours when
did i rip the shirt that bad oh shit it's a demon i'm gonna have to get rid of her
you're not gonna there's nothing in there is this a dream ah shit she might not be real
stop i woke her up that probably it's okay when you're on the couch tonight
i can was i when i was better that one which one i'd sleep on the couch i'm gonna go like
in the bed like that i'm gonna go put both legs out too i'm gonna t pose in bed
hey cosmic moses thanks for the five dollars jeremy didn't mention this because i didn't want
to make you in chat sad but i thought you should know my precious doggo venus passed away
i showed him on stream before she was at 18 i've been miserable for weeks but you've been
cheering me up i upload some photos of her let's take a look show them if you want sorry
for this giant message no no no no problem at all i'm really sorry to hear that no what a cute
little doggo 18 that's a long life that's a long life well she looks very very loved
i'll link the album here for anybody that wants to see she looks very loved
rest in peace enjoy the years that you had with her because she looks fucking she's beautiful
18 is legendary yeah that's very that's a very very long life
my last dog that i had before auto went to 17 so at that point it's that's a real legit family
member it is i'm really sorry to hear that rest in peace to venus thank you for even
sharing at all with that with all that so thank you cosmic moses
beautiful dog only a few more we got bingo sunshine for 250 wrong answer but while you
tried to do a backflip and it was a good ass stream ghost twink is rude stop snapping your
fingers okay good night jerma love you geez man that was loud why will you just
read the bits i'm trying to give you more money what's going on here
that's that i i did that correct right i just that's right isn't it i'm not like insane
right the salmon fetish guy oh he was drunk all right all right i see thank you bingo
sunshine for the 250 the ball of koala thanks to five dollars kim check she just came in the
room so you very clearly saw her go out that door don't need to check when she's already gone
dr stein thanks for the five dollars the same exact thing happened to me i woke up like four
times or more and it kept being a dream but i kept changing fucking locations it was awful
yeah when you try to wake up from a dream and you wake up in another dream
your panic meter goes to a thousand and then when you finally do wake up it's like you ran
like four marathons you feel like crap did you cry to the movie click i've never seen that
when we start to finish i just remember when he's like punching the shit out of david has
it off his face i don't remember anything else and then he just goes wow i got a headache
that's the only thing i remember let's get the credits rolling what do you say they're
gonna be over my face has this been in the background this whole time why did everybody
say anything why did anybody say anything here come the new subs and the resubs thank you everybody
much love to you here they go the labo vr kit it was kind of nice actually this thing is
actually really cool this whole thing was built with cardboard that's i mean that's
remarkable this is really cool it just is come to my house and fight me why would i want to fight
you i would be like hey man like relax uh we did have a couple more clue the sniper 250 from clue
the sniper thanks a lot clue sniper man bear pig gave five dollars is that vegas meetup
still gonna happen i'd almost definitely come out for that sounds like a fun time instead
of like a pax east or like a pax prime or an e3 i'll probably just end up going out there
and see if i can get that actually to work am i gonna go to evo i will probably go to evo
because it's in vegas so why wouldn't i right it's kind of it's like fucking right down the
street go to evo like that shit is right down the street so why would i not go it would be
kind of it would be stupid if i didn't because it's really interesting stuff but we
got uh man bear pig thank you for that uh niall orion thank you no meme but how do
you feel about pet rats rats are incredibly intelligent loving very very awesome animals
like rats are highly intelligent adorable fun cuddly loving the creatures yeah i love rats
garfield the bunday killer haven't seen you in a while hi garfield garfield the bunday killer
250 i was thinking about tf2 again germa it's a crying shame what valves do into that game
the last good thing added was naming the scout after you uh i don't know if that's real though
i mean i think that's that might just be just be a coincidence if it's not then like i said
i've made a statement about it before that's incredibly fucking wonderful that i could even
imagine anyone would ever do that it's probably just a coincidence but that community is
unfucking believable so uh but what are you gonna say the last good thing added was
naming the scout after you i know everyone compares you to the scout but what class is
your favorite in terms of personality regardless of gameplay the spy i got tf2 after seeing your
fat guy enji vid it's the first vid i saw of yours garf's been a fan for over four years
you want to be in shrek 2 garf got hired for independent retailing of shrek 2 phil is in it
phil lord is in it garf goo i don't think i want to be in shrek 2 uh the spy is my
favorite character in that game just personality wise i think he's really fun and interesting
and who who couldn't love the heavy the heavy is just a lovable amazing character so uh but
yeah i mean that tf2 is would i be sitting here right now talking to you guys if i didn't play
team fortress and make all those videos no probably not so team fortress was a very real
start of everything i was doing so i i mean i played that game for years it was one of
it was like the biggest part of it was a huge part of my life so i owe a lot to that community
i know i owe a lot to team fortress and valve for even making the game in the first place so
i owe a lot to that community they propped me up really fucking high they did so i have
nothing but love for that community at all nothing at all but love and finally we have
through multi trip gave five dollars i can't go to germa con can you come to mecon instead
can you go to mecon i don't know i don't know what mecon is what is mecon
it's me it's just mecon it's me call it jexpo no it's just a hangout it would just be a
night if you were around that would be it germa and friends yeah just whoever it is
11 50 is 12 o'clock almost eight hours here i don't know this is going to be a longer one
garfield the monday killer 250 no i wasn't joking the guy who made 21 jump street is in the new
shrek 2 reboot wait what do you mean shrek 2 reboot what do you mean what happened to
the shrek 1 reboot okay let me get this straight you're gonna go fight a dragon
and rescue a princess just so far card will give you back a swamp which you only don't
have because you filled it full of freaks in the first place is that about right you know
what maybe there's a good reason donkey shouldn't talk i don't get it shrek why don't you just
pull some of that ogre stuff on him you know throttle him lay siege to his fortress grind
his bones to make your bread you know the whole ogre trip oh and know what maybe i could
have a decapitated entire village but what's going on here we got over 200 people to remake
shrek what this is an hour and 30 minute video their heads on a plate got a knife cut open
their spleen and drink their fluids cool you handle the dragon i'll handle the stairs
i'll find those stairs i'll whip their butt too that's right take it off okay easy
as you command your it's like fucking a ton of different videos i'm gonna have to watch
this whole thing not tonight um that's really interesting though but hey juno upset oh six
dollars and 96 cents thanks for all you do jerma thanks for all you do you just gave me
seven dollars that's a lot that's it a lot that's a lot of money to give somebody that
you watch on the internet thank you thanks for all you do you guys do a lot and with
that i will see you guys what time is it i'm supposed to stream tomorrow oops what is it
midnight all right here's the deal i'm gonna fucking go to bed and if i get up we're gonna
go tomorrow tomorrow is supposed to be sam and max episode six season one and then season two
episode one maybe episode two if i don't get up to stream then we're gonna go then we're
probably gonna go either monday tuesday wednesday or he's gonna justify his absence now yeah i mean
i'll see you guys on fucking monday i did the whole bottle holy shit just keep the clip that
clip it somebody clip it no if i'm for some reason i'm not around i will um i will be around
on monday or tuesday probably monday monday late afternoon or tomorrow or tuesday wednesday
let me wait wait wait i have a colon what's my colonoscopy not to get real here but
when is my colonoscopy let's see sunday monday tuesday wednesday thursday friday
oh shit it's right it's tomorrow no um today's may may fourth fifth monday the sixth seven
eight nine ten all right so listen hear me out hear me out for we'll go like four five
days next week what a red mess that colonoscopy would be i'm thinking i'm thinking right
maybe tuesday wednesday thursday friday and sunday that's probably a good idea because
i got a lot of things i want to do that's filthy it's just like oh what did you do
last night i don't know just dragon plate labo yeah because i've got shit to do on monday
all right here you go ready bingo listen listen up we're not done streaming by the way you
think i'm gonna leave are you fucking kidding me i'm not done so plan four because i've had some
shit to drink and i have shit to do on monday the seventh the eighth the ninth and tenth
and the 12th we'll go five days next this coming week here so we'll go back we'll come
back on tuesday tuesday wednesday thursday friday sunday we will finish sam and max
big hands you think i got big hands you said that about this week well we did we did yeah but i
didn't think i was gonna drink this much we did what would we do monday tuesday wednesday
saturday monday tuesday so tuesday wednesday thursday friday you look like you lost weight
i don't think i did did i probably feel the best all right well i'll let you know i'll let
you know we'll go at least four or five days this week if there's nothing tomorrow if for
some reason i can't fucking go tomorrow which i mean i will see i'll be around i'll let you know
i'll be in the chat and we'll go from there so if there's nothing tomorrow then we'll do like
tuesday to friday i'm just gonna leave it at that because i really don't know how i'm gonna
feel tomorrow maybe i'll feel fine and if i feel fine then we'll just fucking go tomorrow
whatever but i will see wait we had a couple more bits come in thanks to the five dollars
very professional scheduling jeremiah i don't have a schedule it says no schedule right in
the front page um we'll see we'll see if i wake up fine tomorrow then we'll just go tomorrow
if not then we'll go on monday or tuesday or something we'll figure it out we'll go
another four or five days we've got plenty of shit to do we got we got stuff to do
but see you later guys i'll put the uh these just check the sauce check it tomorrow
much love to you and i'll see you soon regardless have a great rest of your night
i'll see you guys soon where is my outro i don't have no idea there it is germa lied about
stream legends he did not because he's gonna do it right now so yeah just keep an eye on the
sus tomorrow afternoon you'll have a good idea what's going on at the very latest i will see
you on tuesday at the very earliest i'll see you tomorrow we'll figure it out whatever
fucking let's go let's figure it out where's um extensions there we go i had a lot of fun
i love these fucking streams i love we just kind of can hang out and just stick around
eight fucking hours of just hanging out and dicking around it's great you guys are fucking
awesome it's just so fun and comfy it just is i really fucking mean that stream legends
let's get it out here there you go there's your present take care of yourselves much love
i'll see you real soon regardless if it's tomorrow or tuesday see you soon take care guys and goodbye