Okay, I apologize about that. That was weird. So what's going on guys? Hopefully you're having a
Fantastic Saturday, or if it's Sunday where you are too. I gotta shout this out. I gotta say hey everybody come hang out
Hey, but streaming on twitch.tv T. Oh, we're gonna play CSGO. The best game mode is in CSGO right now
Gun game the real gun game the fun one the one where it's instant respawn. You run around like crazy
Steam community body 15 minutes. Yeah
Uh-huh. Okey-dokey. I almost forgot Twitter
Well, let's get a server going so people can play while I finish this up
How about how about King of the Hill Badlands? All right, you guys ready for the IP? Oh one second
No, not even on 14. Hold on. Let me press play. I have to like give the IP to burger boy
Because he got really mad at me last time. I didn't give it to him
So here we go ready nope, oh you're gonna get you're not gonna make it
I'm about to paste it people probably reading it right now going in wait. Did you already paste it? No
It's just sitting on the screen right now people will be able that there's already people in there. Oh, sorry. I was tweaking them
All right, you ready?
How about we're in five seconds?
What were you doing? Were you like all like toilet? I was getting off modern warfare 3
I'm about to hit this this button. I'm about to hit the button
63 dot 146 dot 183 dot 46 colon two seven zero two five
You better hurry up. All right, I wasn't even ready
Join the I'm joining off of you. Oh, you better hurry up then. Oh steamy D. We're good. I'm in here
I gotta like I don't even put it on. Yeah, I told you to like go because I thought I could like remember the number
It didn't work. No, I can remember the number. I can remember that 12-digit number. No
Hl2 dot exe troll what's gonna happen there? It's not real. It is real
It's always real now when it's loading the game. Have I seen the hung?
I've not seen the hunger games. Is it any good? And if the answer is yes, I would probably see it
It's about as good as the TV show community as good as it gets
That was a I was a good movie with Jack Nicholson. Oh, there's burger boy the insensitive one
I
Sensitive one
Burger Boy the insensitive one areas because we all know that he's a real insensitive bastard. You've seen it five times
Oh, it's gonna be bad. Do you think different happen that fifth time? Ouch different anything?
Do you do? Oh, they're speaking of Twitter. Well, where's my like hold on?
I gotta like say to my Twitter followers. No, hold on. Just tick. Oh, yeah
Hey, just just take a look. It's for those of you wondering. I'll bring up my my backpack so you can look at it
Oh burger boy
There's this page one so you can go over page one while I do Twitter and then I'll do page two in a second
I got backstabbed don't get backstabbed. All righty. All right, we go to page two page two
That's the page two even though you can't see. Oh, it's show. Oh, yeah. Sorry. Sorry
So I go back to page one so you can see the colors and this whole thing is being given away
So hopefully you're one of the winners. Oh, no page two. I got a lot of strangers a lot of strangers page three
Hey, you're heck you're heck. Yeah
Page four. I love how burger boys using the
Logger now and you're gonna have to deal with it now, aren't you? No, I don't know. He's on my team
Oh, I'm like medic on him one more page after this. Does any of them stick you to the wall?
I don't think it does. I think only the is my character was like standing up after I get killed and then page six
There you go. This is probably like the best page with all of my actual hats that I like love
And all the strangers are of course are over here and you get the idea. Do you do you do?
All right, let's do it. Let's do a high five and let's get this wrong
Yeah, I items that I cannot give away. I've not I won't be able to get away
So I can't give away the cheaters lament. I can't give away. I think there's a couple other things
You can't give either. There's like two or three items. I know for sure. I cannot give I'll be ginger
Let's turn this down. It's just a tick just a tick. Well, where's my Gerardi? I don't have the Gerardi. Oh
Shrek. Oh
Okay, not again. Oh
Watch it watch it watch it around this corner here mini century. Get out of here. Oh, how did I not get him?
You a spy you kind of acted like one. Oh look MLC stealth just killed stealth
When do I think I'll hit 25,000
Probably a couple weeks, maybe maybe a week. I don't know. It's gonna happen sooner rather than later
I probably will say that I don't know though. I have no idea follow me Jack
Oh you ran into it whoo-hoo-hoo. That was pretty nice, but don't say so myself. I just got like fished
I got fish killed. I'm screaming. This is boo. This is boo man 61 and MLC stealth boo and stealth. Hello
Hello, but those of you wondering I was kicked by console. That's not cool. You got kicked
No, no, no, like someone's saying they were kicked like for what what'd you do? Nothing problem. That's about your B
It's it's changing. Love it. Yeah, it sounded like you were talking to your like dog. Like what did you do?
What did you do auto?
Nucleus, huh? Nucleus
Nucleus
Nucleus direct it. I'll try it and the conqueror. Why am I using that the contrar?
It's CH. It's like church. Do you know how to pronounce things snipers? I'm scared
Oh, do you remember yesterday? I was saying about how hard is the headshot soldiers that there's like four soldiers on the other side
I just can't headshot one
Actually, I recognize that beard any day. Come here German. Well, what's that?
Nevermind boo. Why you know post-modern warfare 3 that's what she said
Oh, it's cuz I really don't like the game anymore
I might not be totally dumb and I'm weighing it about in my head because I've got some old recorded gameplay
I just never used I might make a few more bids out of it pyro direct hit. Oh
Come on, come on come out of that watch out for the crits people everywhere like all over it
No, no soldier, I'm gonna go I'm gonna go pyro with this setup cuz I like it
No, no, let's go. Oh, no, come here do it again. No, I missed it. I missed it. I missed it. Oh, no
No, I gotta turn the volume up a little bit. Can you guys can you guys hear the uh in-game volume?
Okay, where's it too low? Let me know. Oh, no, I can't we have to play speaking of playing
I gotta start like actually playing. Oh
No, I missed. Oh, no
Get him off the point. Oh, no, the only one on here. I'm screwed. We're gonna get it. That's a spy
Well, I'll hear a joke. Yeah, tell me a joke. Let's hear it. Give me all you got with jokes
I love jokes. No, I missed time that badly. Oh
Oh
You son of a bitch you rat bastard, so what way what was the joke? I'm waiting. It's probably tight
No, it's probably a joke. Oh, no, I just missed I gotta step my game up a little bit here
I'm like one in twenty five thousand. Oh, no, like I wrote stealth just like you do stuff. Mm-hmm
Then he backstab me. Oh, how did I not get him? Oh, get me out of there. I'm dead
Oh, there's no way I could have survived that can't be pyro right now. That was a lucky headshot. Holy shit
I'm going demo. I'm going demo demo man. Hey, what makes you a good demo man?
Um, a lot of things if you are good with shooting your pills, I can drink from a frying pan
What makes me a good demo man, oh he just felt
How do I not get him with that how do I not get I want to be your discussion it with you now would I
No, we need a medic. We all we do have a medic. We need more than one medic
You have two medics. I think we do. I had showing one of them
Once I just walked right off the map. Hey, there's a big hole in the middle of this map
If you didn't notice and I'm still as a joke is your mama's so fat
Everyone at the movie theaters thinks she's I can't really yet burger boys coming for me. Hey, it seems
Your mama's so fat at the movie theater. She sat next to everyone sick
I got one for you. Your mom is so stupid
She made me cookies and was a wicked nice woman and was awesome to be around at all times. There you go
Oh
All right. I got one too. All right. What is it? Why did the
King and Queen get a divorce? No, why because they had a bad night?
Yeah, suck both versions of the like word night. All right, boo. You're gonna do one now. Well, I've got to do a joke
That's why I work good Lord
You'll have to give me a few minutes then. Oh, come on. You have to like make it your own
No, the pressures are no, I've got to be honest man. I've got to deliver. Yeah. Yeah, get out of town
Big joke. Yeah. Good luck. Oh my god. No, I don't want that
No, get on the point. Yeah, I can't I can't keep my head over there. I'm just trying to log stuff in there. Come on
No, no, no
So boo, how about that joke? I can't I'm sniping him in my element
Sniper was walking down the street one day was he singing to a diddy diddy dum dee dee dee
Yeah, so he was singing that song and all of a sudden a bus came and just smashed into him
Oh, and that's the punchline. They will live happily ever after
I just got the like event for Germans and he made cycle path. Oh, really?
It's just starting
That was happens like much later than it should yeah, I sometimes said it to do that
Because when I usually when I'm when I first put the announcement out
I'm just kind of sitting there doing like nothing and shouting things out
So people probably just like what the hell is he doing 15 minutes in is pretty much when everything really gets going
I guess you stream get priority as well for the for the game, which is fair enough
Let's do one more round in here and then we're gonna go to
Different
I literally just tried holding down shift to sprint. Yeah, I've been doing that since I've been playing battle. Oh, look at how the jokes
Oh, did I save your life just barely? I think who just wait. Okay. I'm so confused right now
I just saw a stealth die in front of me by MLC still
Bye behind me, but I don't care. I'm too fast for hey, who's the real one? Oh my god. I can't hit the soldier
I'm so scared. Oh my god. Thank you for saving my life
Can I play Saxton Hale? I we tried doing that a while ago. It didn't really work out so well, though
It's we do prop hunt
Well, only because I was the only person that could get into the server and we were just spending a whole lot of time
Just watching spectating and it was kind of boring. So at least for a stream. It was kind of boring
I'd want to do that for like a video get get a bunch of people in there and make some like fun video
And I'm going to die get me out of here. They're way too many people there to be fighting right now
Come on
That other stealth guys being is like
360 I have to help it's it just the end for me might as well just do this. Oh my god. Oh my god
But I don't kill by a fit. I was you
Oh
Son of a bitch
I was in the spawn door and he shot me right in the back
Like I was like I was right like in the door and I got hit right in the back. Yeah
The red team it was a revolver too. He's not dead. We got a lot of scouts. I just heard it
I just heard him. I just heard him the soldier behind this bastard. I feel like playing pyro. I'm starting to like him more now
I was never good at pyro before
You know, I've learned to really like playing pyro playing pyro is like a ton of fun for me and I never used yeah
I I never used to like him because I always wanted to use the flare gun and when I found another pyro eyes
It's impossible
Yeah, the flare gun pretty much reinvented pyro for me like it became so much fun
What are my views on meet the pyro? I think it's gonna be epic judging by the last two
We've gotten meet the medic and meet the spy. They've been unbelievable
So one can only hope it's got to be something just as good if not better than meet the spy and meet the medic
What are they? What are those like a 2d animation thing? Yeah, that'd be interesting. It'd be interesting. It'd be cool
No, no, like it looked like it sucks
What if meet the pyro sucked? I would be disappointed. I shouldn't have shot him. Why'd I do that?
Well, at least you got my back. Anyways, I'm getting destroyed
Passage meet the pyro was like stick figures and like the music was a MIDI file like
What if what if the pyro was a stick figure Wow, you just blew my mind right there what?
You just totally blew like he takes off his his mask and it's literally just a stick figure
It's like a broom like in Family Guy
Yeah, they're probably not gonna take his mask off I bet you hit the hill take his mask off
You're saying why are you saying well hurt him or her the pyro will probably take off the mask right when the ending happens
Like oh, here I go. Like you're it
It'll probably be something like that. What if it'll be Gabe Newell's troll face? What if it was just Gabe Newell's face?
It's just Gabe Newell's face is him like he made the character like after himself
I cannot hit this scout to save my life. Can't hit anybody to save my life for real. Jeez
I mean all jokes aside the pyro is clearly just gonna be Zoe
Clearly stick the scout and if I'm gonna go with the if I should stop do I have a strange stuff?
I don't we'll go with the whole set. How do you stop a gay bed easy?
You press the gay bet gay Ben gay bet in addition. I'll save you. Oh
Help me. Oh boo with the pistol. Nice
Somebody can somebody can find an empty
Randomizer server we need we need an empty randomizer server not a full one not one
That's like an arena a real good like instant respawn randomizer server with nobody in it then we can hop into it
No, I'm not doing with that. It's going to lose to be destroying me all game
So that so that is a
Quest for the germa group to find that randomizer server
How many how many
Germa points do they get for completing that quest? I said 15 German points. I know that's you
You got Optimus Prime with you
Come on now. He's gonna headshot me. I know he is he always does
Can I like vote Optimus Prime like Best Buy in the in the world like Best Buy in team fortress
Can I like can I like safely say that right now? I like really think I can he's in part of part of that
But like electric bugalow bungalow get with electric
espionage
Oh my god, why am I not hitting anybody with this? Let's get in here and then do it. That was so lucky stuff
I'm gonna die. Oh
This is a brass piece. What are you doing? Oh, did I get lucky? I did not sorry. I'm sorry
I'll get on that get on it. Somebody get on it. Somebody just sneeze on it
No, no, I refuse to die. I refuse jump it jump it jump of the pit quick
Alright, so that that is a we got a randomized server right there empty if that is the game
Oh, that was so close. Let's go find out. I need to go to
Add a server. Let's see if this one has like no people in it. Alright, so here we go
This is the server that we're going into right now. You ready guys. Yes
207.188.214.12
colon two eight zero one six go go go go go
Attempt in one five idiot. How dare I assume so randomizes like heavies with spy knives
Yeah, this is like this is like total nonsense. Oh, it's in it's on nucleus
There you go drop to the slot reservation what?
Oh
Okay, so slot reservation well
Well, my first one was a medic with the machina girati and
Disciplinary action. I should have got in there first before sending it. Oh damn it. All right. What was the second one?
I don't know. I gotta get in there first
See if this one was existing we're gonna have to change. This is no way I'll get in there now
Server let's try it again this one. Okay. There we go. All right
So I'm I'm gonna go I'm gonna put a new IP into the chat. So when you get a chance
Everybody go to this server and I'm gonna tell you guys ready two or five dot two three four dot one five two
Dot eighty five colon two seven zero fifteen head in there now. Let me know when you're connecting
and
There you go. That's the one we're playing on right now
The other one filled up too quickly and has a lot of slot reservations. All right, there we go
Thank you Ari or Zeus whoever it is and doesn't really matter whatever you pick what okay, this is like the oddest thing ever
I'm holding the am I the heavy or this on the sniper? What in God's name? I'm holding the enforcer
It's totally broken apart and I just I can't even if we have to see this. I can't even explain it
No, I got the sticky chopper. I've never had oh nice the golden wrench. Oh my god
The the hand models of me sometimes they're fine
Sometimes they're just totally broken because I'm a soldier and I have medic gloves with my syringe gun
Then I pull out a weird-looking winger and he has normal hands
Dude, I'm holding this wrench like a gun and it's like I'm not even touching it. It's like floating in my hand
Who has the century this guy spy with a degreaser?
It's floating around like a clown. That is an oxymoron right there spy with a flamethrower
Oh, I am like the child was found missing
They're like hello
What the hell is this? This is the force of nature. I
Can I can't even do it? I can't even taunt all right the force of nature the pistol and
The Clyde and more crits god. This is I can't even play my head hurts by looking at this
ugliest thing
That guy's still standing there all I can see what I'm so confused this guy's just
Oh look at this like a sniper with the Liberty launcher the chocolate and the the fan of war all right Liberty launches sniper
This could be interesting and I zoom in every funny good
Hold on this guy has it that guy just had the Natasha as a sniper and he was holding it like a sniper rifle shooting
Oh my gosh
I'm using the
Overdose and if you like reload and shoot at the same time you can just keep shooting forever
I was like yeah, like it instantly reloads it all right. Oh wait. No it doesn't actually like shoot
Look at this like pump action like freak out gun. I'm using what else do I have on the pistol?
That's boring and what what the hell is this?
What the hell is this? Why am I like a monster?
What I wish you could have just seen that I had huge like brown
Monster hands
It was the engineer who are you playing? What are you doing? I'm a spy with the Ollipool caber
I was like sasquatch right there a poco fists is that is that like a fake thing what?
Say wait just soldier soldier spy turn on but when I say soldier spy I mean like soldier with a with a knife
Soldier spy so they've added new crazy funny items huh right engineer with the oh the criticola and the all this is gonna be good
Oh, that's awesome. I hope I can stay alive
Because this is a great setup is it a soldier of the criticola soldier with a rocket launcher. Oh my
Rocket launcher criticola like are you are you shooting me? Oh, no come on
He's come on what I didn't even get to use that awesome setup. I just had that pains me
It's it's thereby not a does it not have like king of the hill cuz it this would be great for king in the hill
I don't think so all right ubersaw frontier justice in Geront
Fantastic that has a medigun as a pyro. I'm a medic Tommy slav it looks so like out of place
Oh, okay, that's it. Did I kill him I got so the a poco fists are the regular fists
But they give people when you crit them. I don't think I was hurting anyone. I was shooting them. It wasn't doing damage
Numbers weren't popping up above their head god. This this like makes me so happy like this mode doesn't doesn't just make you like so hell
Look at this this guy's like wearing wearing the intelligence like mary poppins like what the hell are you doing?
He's bouncing it on his head all right syringe gun and the wrench again, and I built you can't build buildings
I forgot well. Well. This is a bloot sauger. I'm dying right now. Are you serious? No?
I'm literally dying right now because I'm happy blue. It's gonna kill me
Oh
So the blue saga was literally killing oh that was ball, okay?
I need German. I need you to tell me what I have all right. We're actually I'm standing outside the spawn door
I just I have no idea what says you have the direct hit the crits Creek and
Also, Chris Creek. Yeah, you have the crits crazy. Let's see what this looks like from my point of view
This is retarded. I just saw like two seconds all right. I got the fist. I don't even have a secondary
Okay, I don't have a secondary apparently. It's probably the razorback so razorback fists of steel wait. What's fish cake?
It's like a reskin of the chocolate. Yeah, this is so why does this look so perfect with the sniper? Oh come?
We just got crits too. We got crits. I'm a spy knife read the top of the screen. What's at the top of the screen?
Oh, oh god. I am so stupid wow wow wow you uh wow look at how stupid
I am it says what you have right there, but that wasn't like right when you spawn it tells you what you have
Oh my god. This is not there. I'm using like a regular pyro set right now
I literally have the like a normal active. What do I for a melee golden wrench?
I'm a dimmer man with the enforcer and the guns like broken apart and floating well. I got it
I got a golden wrench somebody. I don't know. I'm trying to reflect Rockets
I don't know what he has called the wrench they turn to a gold statue. Don't know yeah, they do I've never seen
Yeah, everyone's like he's like he's a different class and I was standing in the same spot. Oh this person's awesome
Why do they keep like capturing the flag so quickly? That's like the kill
Kretsna, oh, that's too funny. I don't know. I don't think I could play this mode a
Thousand times and I would probably laugh just as hard every single time. It's just this medic is holding this enforcer light like a
like a
Gang member like sideways. I want I want everyone to see just how I picked that up look at this
Like oh yeah, let me just spin this giant axe in my hand. It's like a hundred and eighty pounds
Let me just hold it with one hand. It's not even doing any swing animation
There's no swing animation with that. This is so odd my brain like cannot handle how this looks
It actually looks like kind of normal to be honest
I feel like that's the way like a shotgun would act in somebody's hands like no one
I'm gonna lot of kills with this enforcer. Oh, let me just one second guys
Let me spin up my like 200 pound axe in one hand. Let me go cool
Look at look at all useful. This is gonna be come on. I gotta kill him with it
Now who keep well, that was weird. No swing animation. You can't tell I got burger boy the insensitive one
Burger boy, you can't call for medic man. Nobody has it
It could be like a heavy with the damn crits critical the many gun engineer with the Natasha the winger and the atomizer
Can I double can I triple jump? I can double jump. I can double jump as the engineer
Probably the atomizer. Yeah, I have the atomizer with the ng. I can double jump and I can build building. That's a spy
You I get the cool setup and I die instantly this happens every single day. I turn the corner
Oh, that was the spy. So I was going invisible behind people my force of nature
Invisible that's crazy term a singer song. That's somebody just said
Come on winger. Oh, let me look. Let me hold. Let me let me just
like a little
No words can describe that. I can't even make a joke. It's too stupid. Oh god. That's a dead
That's a dying battle right there. I have the revolver
My spy has three hands because I'm holding killing gloves a box and I pull up my cello
Scout with a minigun everyone run for your life
Teagle challenges me to a duel. Yeah, I wonder how mad burger boy is right now
I bet you burger boy is screaming at his computer screen. I healed for a hundred points as a sniper
X-tank, wait, am I holding this backwards? All right. Look at how I'm holding this
I could really hurt myself with this thing fish cake. Oh, it still works
I will let me launch your fish cake and the backwards extinguisher. Hmm. Yeah, make sure don't drop it on your face
I have two shotguns scout a gun of family business. I have the syringe gun of the heavy
I don't like this what just even killed me what what I am confused. That was weird
We do do do do do bring up. Oh, that's my favorite dubstep song. How'd you know? I was doing the heavy minigun noise
Charge and charge can I charge as a sniper? I can't oh, I can't charge. Damn it. What?
Okay, so I'm I'm a spy and all I have is the tribal and shit. I don't have any other item
Can you cloak? Yeah, I wish I could charge and charge right there. That would have been hilarious
I just spawned and for some reason I spawned with like 350 health overheal. Yeah
I think I think some of the people do something. I think everyone does be honest. I'm spawning over heels
I have a rocket jumper
I guess no, maybe not everybody bootlegger Razorback. Okay, this is actually a pretty good setup. I know I can't charge
Oh, this sucks. Never mind guys. That's the worst set up ever. I got a razor back though. I can't be back
I had Girardi rocket jumper and
Equalizer I can't
I'm a spy with a tribal men's ship and that is literally a if you shoot me a duel I'll do you I'll do anybody
Why not? Absolutely dead ringer heavy vote for the next map. Let's go to
Bad water bad water sounds fun. Alright, so I have I'm a soldier with a big earner and the enforcer
Don't work the taunt. I can't do the taunt. Damn it. Taunt doesn't work with this thing. What the hell better off?
Yes, I was scotch resistance. I have no idea how this works
Okay, right. Look at that's just pointing straight down into the ground. That's so funny
Oh, this thing's great for people to jump in
I don't think I've even seen the guy I'm dueling one time
Oh my god, that guy's got so many people that Natasha. All right
this will be the last round of the randomizer and then we'll go to one more random server and
Oh my god, I'm a medic with the Natasha and a different screen. Well, what do I have for mail?
I didn't even read it. Oh the wrench. Oh, you thought the medic was just gonna be healing didn't you? Oh my god
This is so OP. Now. I just switch over get some heels around a little bit
I'm a spy running around with heavy fists punching people
Well, I got you. I got your king Dedede. Oh
Come on, give me those crits. Come on. Come on. Where is somebody? Oh, this is so insane
Medic with a god damn mini gun. Are you serious? And I'm healing people with the crits for you
This is ridiculous and I can upgrade and repair buildings
Wait, what's the big kill? It's a reskin of the revolver. I have a revolver and I have a pistol
I don't even know what he has. What does he have? Let's get the Scottish resistance. Somebody do something
Well, what that last like two seconds?
I had this thing called a jar of ants is that just I thought it was dry
But when I threw it at people they would like taking damage. I never seen that pool. That's weird
I get that is healed a thousand points as a pyro. I was I don't think it was that even a pyro
That was weird. Did you did it? Did you did it?
So because I'm a spy I have a wrench and I can't I can either disguise but I can't build anything
All right shotgun short-circuit. What what is going on? I'm so confused. This is how he's holding the shotgun. Hold on
Hi
So this is that's the reserve. Oh, I have the knife too
Okay, I was holding the shotgun down like a minigun and it was like shaking. I couldn't even like tell where I was shooting
All right. So after this we're gonna go to a no, I'm getting the worst things ever
Yeah, I got a great one last time the medic medic set up. All right, so bonk it
Oh, this is gonna be great bonk a tongue punch. Does it do anything? Am I am I'm invincible, right? Yeah, I am sick
I'm getting I'm getting all these pistols. What what?
Buffalo steak sandwich to again mini crits and you take mini crits, but you can't use anything but melee that was weird
I'm the no swing animation throws me off cuz I'm just like standing there. I'm like am I even swinging people
Oh, it's tied up now. Oh, we don't make it. Wait a minute. How does the widow maker even work?
How would the widow maker work? Am I this is infinite ammo? Well, how's this gonna work?
I think I just haven't fitted ammo. Oh, no, I can't lose this. No shit. No
I really think I just had it fitted in with that thing
We're getting my spawn trapped now the front two justice had ten shots and I'm confusing. Oh, man
Oh, yeah, I still have metal like yeah. Yeah, I just can't see it. That's still funny. All right
We're gonna go one more a random just normal server to play and then we're gonna hop in a CS go
Let's do let's find another good server. Sure. Let's try and get a
32 person here we go. Oh, let's go back and turbine
No, no, no, no go to dust bowl. That's 30. That's got 32 right now. Yeah, we're gonna do it
There are 32 people can play in this. So this would be the last shebang
I gotta give it to burger boy first. Hold on burger boy will like flip out if I don't and
then ready 96
36 2 7 0 1 5 and join and that's the server guys
Good old dust ball good old-fashioned dust ball. Oh, it's not randomized
No, this is just a regular. Okay. Oh, yes dust ball my favorite
I like dust ball people don't like it, but I like it. I like it after that brass beast game yesterday
So my buddy, I'm from Providence. So cool, dude. Good old Rhode Island. I'll go blue. Why not mission begins
In 50 seconds, that's what I just said Hobo King. Yeah, I will absolutely do jailbreak
Oh, I have while there's people here
I need I need to mention this there is going to be no stream next weekend
Because I'm gonna be a Paxi's Paxi's live stream
Well, I bring your computer with you bring everything down that would not that would not happen
I'm going to know stream next week. I just want to be very clear
But the good part is I'm gonna get plenty of cool videos at packs and there'll be plenty of cool stuff to see from that
So do not worry. So what do you actually do it packs? Cuz I know nothing about game conventions. You just play new games
Um, it's pretty much a good giant
It's just a convention where pretty much every developer you can think of is gonna have like an alpha build or a beta build of their
Game there and you can kind of they have like playable demos
They have like trailers that you've never before seen stuff and it's just a great place to hang out
There's like a bunch of like free play rooms
They have like a hundred Xboxes a hundred like ps3 is like like a hundred
PCs all lined up you just to go in and play with like people that are in the room. Well, it's it's really interesting
So, what sort of games can you go and check out or any you're looking forward to checking out?
I don't know man. Not nothing really. I'm trying to think if there's anything I in particular would like to
Well, too. Yeah, put what you do portal to last year
I went last year the line for portal to was like an hour and a half long to play the demo and like to see
Like the trailer and stuff
It was like this enclosed off boxed off room and you couldn't you couldn't get you you couldn't even see what was in there
It was like a closed off like box and they could line went into the box
So it was pretty nuts. Do I live near the West End? I do not I do not live in the city
I am just outside of the city. Oh a lot of peeps up here. We got a double of a right there. That's spy
Watch yourself. That's me. That's not me. Or is it Twilight Zone? I just got freaked out right there. Oh god. Oh
Spam out the door. Oh my god. Is that is that what I think it is? Is that burger boy? It is that's not spy
Do it go
I'm kind of doing something. Oh
appearance parents from
MLC dad
MLC pop illness see pops MLC pops. Yankees are better than the Red Sox. Oh
Could you say such a thing? Oh
I just got destroyed right there. Okay. Oh, no, this is spy. We gotta get around. I'm going around they're taking over, huh?
They're up like the top. Oh
Nice reflect. You know what? I'm gonna go medic. We need another one
We need another medic. Oh auto calm inbound. Yeah, why not in my next vlog auto?
We'll do like a gameplay commentary. Oh, let me get that
Oh, no, you heard it here first auto was gonna do a gameplay commentary of when I do my next blog
Oh god, that's not safe. Oh
We got stopped. No, we're about to have no stay alive. Where is he? Where is he? Where is I'm trying?
There's like too many people in the way. All right. What do you say man? Let's do it
Crits everywhere
Chris Chris Chris. Yeah, that's my dog people like who is auto. That's my that's my dog. That's my good old dog
No, no
I'm doing something. Oh MLC mom. Do they have YouTube channels? Yeah, they do. They're doing minecraft, aren't they? Wow, you just saved my life
No, I didn't. Sort of
Auto auto the dog. Auto. Scout on the point. I'm trying to find him. I'm trying to find my dog. Auto. Did he just run in here?
Okay, I think my dog just ran in here. I heard that her like the ching-ching. I'm like looking at the screen
I'm not even looking down. I'm trying to like clap and get him to come over here. No, he's not even in here
I'm like going insane. Look at all these people that need healing. No, that was lucky. I don't think he's dead though. Oh
All right new course of action, I'm just charging up my uber and then we're going in do I know any Irish
I I do not know any Irish Palestinian. Oh, I know Irish people, but I don't know the language
Who do you know any Irish? I mean even though you're not that's a spike. Get out of my face
I can't even speak Welsh, which is like my own my own city's language
Wait, that has a language. Wait, that has yeah. That's really what? Welsh, yeah
That's like no belly. No belly anyone speaks it in this country though. That's crazy. I don't know
They had like an actual like I thought they just spoke English. Don't open that door burger boys out there
Oh, it would be bad. It'd be bad if burger boy got in here. I'll close that door. Do not let burger boy in here
It just moved
And open it now. No, don't open it. What are you talking about? I love how we just got this guy here like holding this
Like all right. What are we?
Doing here? Oh turn around. Oh geez. No, no, who opens? Oh my god. They came from behind actually
That's dad. My god. I'm gonna puke. I'm going spy. I'm gonna go. Oh
The original sounds so cool. If I was gonna play Highland or what would I play for a class?
Probably engineer. I'm like most comfortable playing engineer. I knew you were fake. I could smell ya get off the elevator
Oh, I was waiting for him to try and stairs to have me and I got killed either engineer or maybe pyro
Just because pyro is I could probably do what we needed to be done. Hey, I'm pyro. He's not dead. There's no way he's dead
No, man. No, here comes the chase
Didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't wrestle mania 28
I got people that are at wrestle mania 28 friends of mine that are there right now and
One they haven't even done it on scene or the rock. I used to be big into wrestling man
I used to love it not so much anymore though. Oh my god. Hey, what's up, everybody?
I'm just gonna like stuff myself into your face. Oh, no
Hey, but remember that Simon Stone cold stunned the entire McMahon family. Actually I do I'll link that and then the rock rock bottomed
Oh my god, thank you. I'm just being an idiot right now. Oh, they're way too. I can't play spy
It's not possible right now playing heavy. I'm not gonna get me
Got a beer be in like 10 seconds BR BB check duck or this or not. What this I'll do more minecraft
I mean we were trying to the latest minecraft thing that me left her in italics did
We were having a lot of server problems
It would be crashing all the time and I don't know we might try and do something else at some point just cuz it was
Me is that another spy? I think so. Oh, come on. We can do this. Oh, no, we can't eat the sandwich
It's the only thing you can do. No
Where's my dog? Oh, I'm gonna get him in here. Oh, you're gonna do like a face cam video auto face cam
Let's see if I can do it. He's not gonna come in here. He's like no way. I'm back. They're all I hope mr
And or mom on Papa's stuff or something. Nice. Nice. I'm gonna take the brass beast off for this one
What do I think do you tell me what's the worst game ever? Hmm? Oh, I don't know
What's the worst game ever played?
The lens that's a tough one. No, it's definitely not not borderlands not for me
I don't know why I'm such a thing against borderlands. I just you've made you bought it like come on
Oh
My I just heard a spy swear to God I did. Yeah, I knew I did I knew I did I heard him
But I got killed anyways, wait, there's seven spies. Oh my good God
Oh, there's another one
worst game
Recently the worst game I played I can't think of one. I heard that mermaid that
Darksiders is it or something like that dark side. We just law we got destroyed. This is something about this
I don't know a new game that came out which is kind of like
It was like an indie game. I like Nova did a playthrough on it
I know it's called I am alive. No get him off. Oh
All right. This would be the last round that was too quick last round before we go to CS
Go counter-strike go go go and what's go stand for? Oh, just go
Ghost kind of strike like move like move go forward like go. I have to appear offline
Mm-hmm. Oh my dad can't start up with you. Yeah, just when we get into a CS go to top office. That's totally cool
It's totally bad. How do I do this?
What am I doing? No, actually I'll stay online to be honest. I'll do that after me when we switch
All right, if we get rolled again, there's not this is not good news. Yeah, get your crits Creek on the pyro now for this
But oh, yeah
You'll be able to see that video soon on booman 61
You actually will
Come to you soon on the new team fortress to exclusive channel
I wish now
Let's do it. Oh
That's a spy holy mine, oh my god
Why did I jump down?
That's bulls crazy. It's like no respawns to like no respawn delay. We're getting absolutely destroyed right now
Oh, yeah, he's still alive. That's by is still alive. All right fall back fall back. Watch your backs too for that spy
No, he got behind it. He got there. Go go go go go go. He's gonna kind of spike out gonna spike it
Thank you very much. You are the man. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
This way
All right, keep the defense keep up the defense. Oh watch them watch the spike app watch this bike app
If I could be any class in TF2, I definitely would be the spy
You just go invisible and not die in real life. Yeah, you can just never die
I go ahead good shooting the shooting the face. I don't like let you step on a candle or something. I'm fortunate like that
Like oh, yeah, you can go ahead and put like three bullets in my head and I'll just deadbringer
Oh
That Joe was a spy. That'd be really weird. Think about that in real life with the dead ringer, right?
Let's say let's say you I you had a gun and I had the dead ringer and you shot me and I had Degrin dead
Ring around so it would drop like a dummy like body of me
But I would still be alive and I what if I like appeared again, would it be the same body?
What if you disguised as burger boy, then you went to burger boys house me like hey burger boy. Oh
I just talked to burger boys like parents. Oh, hey. Hey, what's going on? Mr. And Mrs. Burger boy
All right block that spy. He's gonna try and get him behind us Crono careful. Whoa, what's up? Turn on girl, huh?
I turned I turned around to fight the first spy and I got backstabbed by another spy that came behind me
Oh teams a spy by in the base red spy in the base pie in the base. That's right
No, it's not get her to that spy. That's his bike. No, it's not. I am so conscious right now
I'm like freaking out credit to run away. Oh you bastard. He's still alive
We need some we need some serious spray action going on over here. Oh
No, run run run run run away run away from that drive the sandwich. Where's my sandwich? Somebody eat it?
Just bumped into a spy. I knew it. I knew it. Oh, no kill the medic. Oh my god
No, I don't have my sandwich. I don't have my sandwich yet. Hold on fall back fall back. Don't die. No eat it. There we go
Ah, this is gonna be a losing battle if I don't do this. Oh
I got backstabbed. Oh
Yeah, at least we're holding them, right?
Is there a spy right here? What's going on there? That was like a freakout session. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go
Oh, no, run run run
Pyro. Oh, no, she probably stops the piping. There's two spies behind us right now
I he's day's gonna be right here in two seconds every time
Barely
You know, I was actually something you guys talking about team fortress in the chat the classic version, you know what? Oh
You good. Come on kill the whole team. Oh my god. I have a critscree. Oh my goodness. That's by still minus
This could be really bad. Oh, I knew it
I was thinking about doing a team fortress one video team fortress classic video
I think it'd be funny showing like what it looks like then and what it looks like now. Oh
There's another heavy right there, too. No, do it. I'm struggling. You just did a oh
Get bad. Oh my god, they're gonna spy cap us somebody come back there
the grenades and team fortress one was ridiculous, I you could never go back and play that and
Really seriously play it. It's just ridiculous. No, we're about to lose. We are
No, I forgot you can't do that anymore shit
Oh, you can't I just threw the sandwich down for myself. I was like, oh, I got more ammo sure
Team fortress to with grenades would be well put it like this imagine everybody on the team is a demo man and has their
Own loadouts
We got to get up in that room. They're all up in that room. Well, this is good
This is a low round. Oh
Yes, this is this is we're putting up a defense right now. Oh, oh my it's you again
Oh, hit it hit it the critscree get it. Good. Oh
How is he not dead my god? Oh
No, yeah, that's what we get. That's where it ends
Good medic good medic is good. Oh nice count Dracula voice. Oh, yeah, that's right count Dracula
They have a boy. Oh, they're trying to build up over here. Oh, it's bad news bad news bears
Nacho back up. I want to get killed. Oh
Oh, it's interesting. I actually like I'll just like a movie
German what movie bad news bears?
I
Was like a baseball player and they said hey any baseball player who like thinks they're an actor
Like come to this like open audition thing so I'd like try it didn't work
Because I was in drama and like middle school so I was like I'm a good actor you could have been a star dude
Who's constant back up back up back up. Whoa look what console just said whoo in the chat or in them
Somebody said oh, so you got a live streamer right now. Well, thanks for choosing the QQ buffet. Oh
You are very welcome. Oh, we're going in over coming in watch it watch it right when they turn it cool
Oh, oh well
Oh, no, so this is like a legit stalemate right now
I think because I want to get see it's going so we might have to like
16 on 16. Yeah, this is just a this is just a totally balanced game right now. No respawn delays on dustbowl
I'm gonna go we got a ton of engineers do which you know, I can't no no change which it either
Oh, I hear the fan. See your fan just turn on mine. I just heard
And I was probably yours. She probably was mine. You're right. No, it's fine mine
Oh my look at the three bags my god run run away
Run away after I think afterburn you could you could tweak afterburn a little bit make it a little more balanced
Maybe you'd make a shorter duration but more damage
So like instead of like 10 seconds or whatever it is make it like four or five seconds
But have it do more damage a little bit more damage. It's okay in its current form though
I think I don't think it's that it's not that bad. Oh my god. Oh
You got it. Hello. Hello, mr. Medic. How are you?
I
Like how he just stood there while like we put mines all over him
No backstab. I'm gonna go I'm going scalp at the end here. This is such a difficult game to win
Oh my god, but I don't think I've seen you once. No, I've been I keep getting killed by Jemma
Stop being so selfish. I want kills too. I just mean I got like I was like octo heavy for this like whole thing
Two or three medics on me not anymore though. I'm saying as to scoot. No
Imagine a team of 16 spies all just cloaked sneak on the point and at the same time all decloak and capture
I was gonna say imagine that and like they they just like pretend that they're the other team
Super spy check mode super spy check
Oh, it took me so long to get ahead of you. Oh man, dude, look at look at the
Metals, that's ridiculous. I feel I want to like switch to blue. I can't though
Oh my yeah, the domination like things nice headshot sick. Come on blue. Oh
stealth
Come on blue man 61
Ready to charge doctor. Oh, they got a big century back there now tables good turn right now
You guys got a good uber good like push coming tables
Um, not too sure about the uber is that uber charge, but are you sure about the push?
Confidence is growing slightly. I'm standing in the tunnel not taking damage
What about burger boy just stand here burger boy
I think it's nothing good about this team. Oh burger boy burger boy
There's nothing good. Yes stuff at last
There's nothing good about this team
Fire I wish I could hear that but I have my voice chat turned off
That would be funny to be able to watch that burger boy. There's nothing really upset
All right
So burger boy on a scale of 1 to 10
10 being like like you will like rip down your house like burn your house down and one being like
I guess I'm like kind of mad how like pissed off are you right now?
I bet you it's at least a seven or an eight. Oh, let's speak. Let's be quiet so we can hear his answer
I can't hear it. So it's you're gonna have to relay it to me
Actually, maybe he's not even listening to the stream. No, maybe he forgot. I was screaming. Oh, they got that. Where's that spies right there?
Oh my gosh
What do you say? What is that?
Is that what he thought damn it I wish I could have my I need to turn it on hold on
Oh my god. All right. All right, you can tell him to do it again burger boy. Do it again burger boy rage again
Is he gonna do it? Oh, no, he's not like actually bad. I wish I caught that on video. Oh, you're losing burger boy
It's over. Oh look at it. It's it's all over. Let's see what he says. Hold on. Here it comes
Oh, what do you say about that burger boy? And what cuz I want no I want him to like flip out. He's silent
Yeah, but I did he's still here. No, he's not yeah
Alright, I'm gonna transition to
CS go. Thanks for coming. No, you're not allowed to come. Yeah
All right, let me um, let me try and figure out how to do CS go could be sort of difficult
I'm gonna do windowed mode. It's gonna take maybe a few seconds. Give me a minute guys counter-strike global effects
All right screens gonna go black for 20 or 30 seconds
I'm still here. Don't worry. Oh, no black screen. Oh
What do we do? It's a black screen. Oh burger boy. You're listening right now after we play this for like 20 or 30 minutes
We're going to McDonald's. We're going to get double cheeseburgers. I hope you know that video settings
We are going to be playing in
windowed
1280 by 7
I think I'm gonna go and play Call of Duty 4 so I'll drop out the
Job out the chat, but I'll see I'll still listen to the stream. Okay, that's cool
Yeah, I can do I know what you're saying at all times stuff
If you're back later and happy days, but enjoy CS go
Thanks. Thanks for coming boo. Thank you. Bye. No, all righty
So we're gonna try and we're gonna play some CS go gonna play some gun game
And if you're more than if you have this you're more than welcome to try and join in off of me or if stealth is
appearing online him it's gonna be difficult
it's gonna be kind of difficult to get everyone in the game because it's um
Wait valve confirms that meet the pyro is already done and ready. Holy crap
That means we're gonna get it soon unless we don't unless it doesn't happen. Yeah, at least we don't get it
Someone like sneak like I would steal that if I like work for valve and put it on the internet
Yeah, you probably would get fired that would not be good
You guys can hardly they're they're quiet. Are they still quiet who they are like me. Apparently you guys are quiet
I don't know why I just try to turn you up. That's odd
Did you did you did it? So this is gun game?
This is like legit like gun game was it like that the whole time or was it like that?
Just for uh for when I changed over was it like that during tf2 as well. Oh
Get gun games
Also, they so they were both low really really low for the team the team borders or just at the end there
That's weird the whole time. No someone they were saying it's like the end of team for just to probably when I transitioned over
Oh, oh, yeah. So this is the gun game. This is my favorite thing about this game. I love gun game
I can't handle the kid
Thanks for the feedback guys. I appreciate it because I I try to it's hard to make it
Sometimes explet is weird and they just lower the volume of everybody
I don't know why but so thanks for uh, thanks for being here to be able to tell me what's going on
So if you don't know what this is every time you get a kill every single time you kill somebody you
Get you get a different gun and I think it's 26 or 27 kills
I don't know the nice healthy stuff is the worst counter-strike play ever. I must have to in general doon-doon-doon-doon-doon
No, it's fine. Oh, I'm not standing still don't look at me. That's off of his prime
Optimus Prime. Oh, he's dead. Oh, I'm gonna get behind. Oh damn it. This is still in beta
Yep
So as you see when I kill somebody else see if I can show you right when I kill somebody the instant I do it
I'm gonna switch a gun. It's gonna go to something else. This is the like shotgun type thing
Oh, I'd love to show them that example, too, but I can't get a kill to switch my gun
Hey, well, you're not really on the screen. I was just saying ah
Yeah, we're this is PC. I don't this is not really even getting developed right now for consoles
I think they're doing that later. Yeah, I think it's actually co-developed for car. I could be totally wrong
I'm not sure on that. Oh, well, that's that's how you miss three times point-blank
Well, that was the auto shotgun somebody's already reached knife level
So once you go through all the guns once you get like 27 kills
You you use a knife and you have to knife somebody and if you knife them the game's over and you win
Well, whatever team had the person knifing. Thanks
Come on, keep you going. Damn it. Ah, oh, that's game. Oh, so do you want ways MLC still?
At the bottom of the league of boards. Yeah, this is definitely the best mode in Counter-Strike
No, in my opinion it used to be a mod then they made it like an actual game mode. It's so fun
Hey, what do you mean go go see teeth? What up? What a delic?
Yeah, I mean the streams been going for like an hour and a half now
So if some of you guys got to go you got to go. Thanks for coming. Appreciate it
Oh, I love this map. I love this map. This is a map. Shibby was like losing his mind on
There's only two maps. Oh, I love this one. Oh, that's right. There's only two maps. What oh no bullets
Wait, didn't there used to be a map? There is where it's in the top left. What are you talking about?
Oh, cuz there's nothing up there for me. Oh
Well, you must have been glitching out. Oh, there it is. It just came out there dad
Oh, I got a headshot from across the map. Well, I'm gonna make a ton of vids and packs man
It's gonna mean me and taxis are gonna be best friends when it comes to videos. I'm in trouble. No
Running the bullets burger boy has a YouTube channel. He's his first video is gonna be going up and like probably like 15 months
Oh
Show yourself. I gotta get a good string together. Oh, come on. Damn
I hear these people in the chat saying like this game of sucks. No way
Let's get this is the most fun game mode on don't see us know what our teammates here Sam
Oh really that is goomba stomp that guy. I don't think I did. I mean we had that conversation last night
We were like, can you goomba stomp? What's going on here?
Cuz it said I like damage the teammate when I land on top of them. Oh my god
Can't believe it how many bullets does it take? Yeah, my favorite gun in CS
Go is probably the shotgun. He just regular shotgun. I love that thing. Oh, come on this thing
This is my favorite gun in CS right now. I love this thing. Unfortunately when I get one kill that it's going away
No, I'll see it's gone. I don't know how you get kills in this
No one dies when I shoot them is the auto shoddy P90 is awesome, too
Everything is pretty balanced in this game. There's way too many of them over there. No way I was gonna do that
I'm the worst counter-strike player. I literally don't think it's the worst one
You know, it's it's tough playing this game in a window. It is very hard to do this. My like my my hands look so tiny
It's like yeah, I'm little baby. I can't believe I didn't kill him. Do I like pretzels? I love pretzels rolled gold, baby
I'm doing absolutely terrible right now terrible. I wish I could full screen this
All right, X split make it so I can full screen my game first problem. There's no hats second problem
No hats third problem. No lasers
fourth problem
Oh my gosh, that killed me. I'm sorry. I got already on the line machine gun. I was doing pretty well last night
Oh, thank you. The game's already over. No, no, she's I'm yeah, that's Alex. I know just saying
Please the asses is over. He's in the yeah, what where is he? Why is he not a mod doesn't make any sense
We don't we don't trust him after I would have after what happened I'm gonna go tea go tea go terrace after I got into the
cookie jar
Okay, really? Oh, well, I'm a moron. No, I'm not shooting. I'm shooting my own teammates up
Oh, I thought I was gonna get him. I got it. I gotta get in tryhard mode now
I want to get a good game tryhard mode activate three and two. Let's go
I want to be at least one to two. I didn't kill him
Gotta get that gun game gotta get that gun game up. I didn't see that guy
I got it blended in with the background. Let's go. Let's go. Keep it moving. Keep it moving here. Keep it moving
Okay, I literally think I'm doing 99% damage to people and then other people are just taking the last shot
Well, LL Cool J in here. Let me see if I can speak up on it. We go. There we go
So that's what I'm talking about. Now we're now we're going now we're going strong do
Moving keep it moving here. Keep it moving. Oh
Eggs, I gotta try hard like an egg. How do you have 14 freaking points?
I went to try hard boy. Didn't I tell you I'm not messing around anymore. No more messing around dude sniper rifle
Let's get one. Hey shaboom. Where is it? 18 and 8? Come on
Give me like 10 more kills in a row, baby. Be careful with this light machine gun, dude
Oh, that was that wasn't killing. Ah
Come on. It's hard when you get to the pistols. It gets difficult. This is where it gets really difficult
It gets difficult when you're using any gun in this
Trying to pull up a headshot not gonna happen. Oh, come on now. Come on now. Oh
Oh, I had it. I had it. Come on. Let me win this round. No crap in my pants. No, this is not good
I gotta find a way around damn it. All right, I'm gonna someone over here
Oh, I can't believe I didn't hit in the face losing it now. I'm losing it
I had it had it for a little bit. No, I'm gonna lose it. I'm gonna lose it
I was so far ahead. I gotta kick off somebody. I'm going this way, man. There we go
Finally got out of that stupid pistol. Now. I got the dual Berettas dude. Oh this guy
I'm gonna make this guy's day bad this egg over here. Where would this egg go? He's had a clean shot on that egg
Oh my god, I can't believe I didn't do it. That was a lucky spawn. Did I get it again?
Yeah, I did it. Oh, yeah. I can't believe I won the game. That's the first time that's ever happened
This game's so hard. I just made them rage quit. Yeah, that's the first time I've ever done that
Wow, that was a I wish I was like I wish I was like recording that because it's probably not gonna happen again
Well, you kind of were recording that
I own Battlefield 3 so do not you don't don't please do not get Battlefield 3 for me
I appreciate the gesture though. Like thank you so much for even considering doing that, but I have Battlefield 3
Oh boo, did you see my I just won did you see it was for you? Yeah, but I'm I don't it's gonna be
360 I guess I could use it. I could use that. Oh you bastard Optimus Prime
Hey, what do you know? Optimus Prime has the knife in this game and he's wicked good with it
Coincidence I don't think so
Give me that headshot. Give me that headshot. Oh, no. Oh
All right. I'm I I quit the game you left
Optimus Prime spits in the hill. Oh, I guess he's wicked good counter-strike source. Did I say source?
I meant counter-strike go stealth can't take it. Oh
Jump down. I was doing alright in the beginning. I was doing alright
See if I can come back to life here what how does how does that make any sense?
How I killed that guy did I shoot him through the grate and how the hell did that happen?
Yeah, I'm not sure how much money it'll be I was assuming it won't be more than 50 bucks
It probably wouldn't be more than 40. I bet you it's I'm gonna say 30 bucks. That's my prediction again
I could be totally wrong really depends on what kind of strategy they want to go for
No, Steve stop killing people. I can't see what gun you have. Oh, this is gonna be tough sniper
I'm gonna have to like cool. I'm gonna have to like call of duty quickscope somebody. Oh
Where'd he go? Where'd he go? Where'd he go? How did I not hit him? There we go
LMG is that the real burger boy? You better believe it. You better believe Oh
Greg oh, that's a bot bot Greg. Come on. I'm at the crystal level. Well, this is a bot. Come on. This is a damn
Damn it 22 somebody's already at the knife level. It might end right now. That's over
It is over the TKO. I believe he's the one that got it. Good game. Oh
All right. I think I'm uh, I'm gonna hop out of CS go now just wanted to play I got that
I'm probably gonna use that gameplay. I might actually use that that one that I went ham on ham
I had like a ham sandwich a ham ham hamburger. Oh, you're still here me. I thought you like ran away
I'm still I thought I thought you I thought you were like sad that you like can't play CS go. I'm sad
I'm so bad. Yeah
Yeah, that's gonna wrap it up here guys
Thanks for coming everybody and see you guys next time. So by the way, I need to make sure you guys all you're not even do quop
No, you're right
What am I thinking my out of my mind quop gonna go black? Oh, he's gone
I thought you like I thought you legit rage, but I thought you like and Skype call and get me out of here. I
Really thought you did that. I was like, oh, he's got it. Go see you later
Scream region screen region. Let's go for five lives on co-op five lives on co-op. See if we can't do something cool
Here we go. Just get good enough at the game so we can hear the music in the background
That's never gonna happen
I will never get good enough at this game for that to not happen co-op looks like grandpa trying to walk when he has no
Crutches. Oh, but I almost did a legit back foot. That was sick. Oh good. Thanks for reminding me woodadelic
There is no stream next weekend. There will be no stream
I'm gonna be at Paxi's pretty much for the whole Friday Saturday Sunday
So there will be no stream next weekend
I will try and do a makeup stream in the middle of the week sometime
Probably I would say probably Thursday of that next week after that
So no stream next week and I am just sitting here idling like a car
I'm doing like the skip method the music just keeps coming in
I'm so bad at this. I can't even get the music to start playing do do do do do
All right, that's it I'm not gonna get better than that. So yeah, thanks everybody so much
I will see you guys all soon and take care everybody. Thanks for coming so much. See you later
Yeah, bye oh
And we what's not I'm like frozen. I think I'm frozen with the stream on oh
So, uh, hello, what's going on everybody? It's Jerma's frozen computer screen and