I don't know why he does that. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. Oh, we should we change the title.
All right, let's pick that movie. I'm so I'm actually excited for this. Pick that movie.
I'm back. I'm here. I'm right here. Oh, it's okay. Cool. Yeah, throw us in a just chatting.
All right. So can you pick the movie that fits each clue? Are you ready? 3000 people left.
I how dare they? All right. Play quiz. There's a timer. All right. You guys ready?
Just scroll down. All right. Here we go. Right. Let's go. Character all the way. May. I don't know.
Um, all the character in the movie all the way may meet the fuckers. This was set in Chicago.
As good as it gets. Nope. Lead plays multiple characters. Three minutes of AV. No, I don't know.
I haven't seen half of these movies. Emote only. I cheated. This is a this is a biopic. Uh,
I don't know. I haven't seen half of these movies. I know it's not this one. Touchables.
Thin blue line. Not gravity. Aviator. Okay. Based on a foreign film. It's probably clueless.
Um, I don't know. Four rounders? No. What? Main character is a novelist. As good as it gets.
Based on a Jane Austen novel. Gravity. I don't know. Features a real life NFL player. I mean,
that could that could be any of these. Somebody from the NFL like runs through a party and
ramps through a wall with his pads on or something, right? No. This is a sequel.
Meet the fuckers. Features Danny DeVito. Where is it? Uh, where is it? Where is it? Where is it?
Where is it? There it is. Poker. Rounders. Sandra Bullock. Gravity. It's a French film.
There's only like there's only three left. It was Animal House a French film? What? I don't know.
Documentary. This is okay. I got it. 73%. That's fine. This is fun. I like this. All right. All
right. Everybody calm down. I'm gonna do the next one. All right. Pick that movie too, right?
Okay. You got four minutes. Same deal. Three, two, one, go. Directed by Alfred Hitchcock. Francis
Ford Coppola. Um, I haven't seen any of these movies. I've seen like three. Francis Ford Coppola.
Francis Ford Coppola. Francis Ford Coppola. He didn't do Narnia. I don't know. I genuinely
don't know. Can I skip? Fuck. I was going to click that one. First film with Meryl Streep.
Probably one of these. Wait. Features an angel. I don't know. Oh, that is an angel. Involves a
bicycle race. Is there a bike race in Die Hard? Screenplay by John Hughes. This one. Set on an
island. This one. Fucking Alcatraz. Okay. I gotta slow down. Stephen King adaptation. Keith Richards
has a cameo. Oh, fuck this movie. I don't care. Features a real life ballet dancer. I don't know.
That's so specific. This is a silent film. Best picture winner. Philadelphia? Best original song.
Philadelphia? Real life father and son. Talking animals. Narnia. Guys, I don't watch movies.
I don't watch movies. Is there a third one? Pick that movie three. Let's go. Let's go like this.
I'll take up the whole screen. I'm ready. You can skip. Yeah, but I don't want to skip. Ow. Okay.
Famous line. Plastics. I know this. I know it. I know it. I know it. I know this one. Right here.
Dustin Hoffman character dies. Spoiler. Never seen one of these movies. I've not seen one of these
movies. I don't know. Features a rap star. I don't know. All right. Though that's that's
literally Charlie Chaplin. Features character who's deaf. I don't know. East of Eden? Stars Harvey
Keitel. First best picture ever. Okay. Charlie Chaplin. I don't know. Clint Eastwood directed this.
What did Clint Eastwood direct? Wait, Clint Eastwood. I don't know what this is. I'll do TV
shows. I'll be better. This is the last James Dean film. I thought that was James Dean. First
Spike Lee film without Spike Lee. With. All right. This one? First Academy Award for Meryl Streep.
Kramer. Features character that's blind. Start a fire. Right there. Okay. Kevin Kline film debut.
Right here. Oh, that's not. I don't know who that is. That is James Dean. That's. Oh, well what the
fuck? First Academy Award for Black Actress. I don't know. I don't know. This is a musical.
Got it. First. Yeah. Fuck this. First James Dean film. There. There he is. He wasn't on the cover
of any of these other movies. Features a rap star. Okay. I'm not good at movies. Did I do the
wrestling one? Why you. I'm getting bat chested but you guys don't understand. I told you I don't
know any of these. All right. Where is it up here? Wait. Hold on. I don't. I don't. Any spoilers for
any of this shit. Can you decipher the Marvel superheroes from these anagrams? Wait. This is
like the whole movie. I haven't seen this. There's gonna be a lot of spoilers here. How about popular
all time? Okay. Oldest to new. Can you. Okay. Let me. I think I can get this one. I think I can do
this one. Yep. I can definitely do this one. At least. At least I think I can do this one. Okay.
Can you pick the films of the MCU in order of release date? All right. Ant-Man. No. Avengers.
No. Captain America. No. Doctor Strange. No. It's gonna be Iron Man 1, I think. Or The Incredible
Hulk. Iron Man 1. Got it. Not Iron Man 2. After that, you've got The Incredible Hulk. Then after
that, you've got Iron Man 2. Then after that, you've got. No. Thor 1. Then Iron Man 3. Oops.
What was after Thor? What was after Thor? Captain America? Is Captain America? Whatever. Pixar. I
will not get Pixar movies. Disney. Literature. Star Wars movies. That's easy. U.S. States. All
right. Well, I fucked that one up. All right. Let me do something I'm good at. I'm doing the
wrestler's one. Do I have a link to the wrestler one? I think I do, right? Okay. WWE theme song
quiz. Let's do it. Do Jerma quizzes? No. I know all those. I'll get all those answers right. Okay.
So this looks insane. Is there a time limit? There's a 20 minute timer on this. All right.
Here we go. Do I have to write it? Do I have to type it in? Okay. Hold on. So let me go. So
can I press play? Wait. Is this cheating? Is this cheating? Oh fuck. What did I do? God damn it.
I'm an idiot. I fucked it up. Hold on. Refresh. Refresh. Refresh. The YouTube video fucked up.
Hold on. I don't care about it. The DMC is going to be. It's like 10 seconds. Okay. I'm ready. I'm
ready. I'm ready. So I have to hit play and then hit this at the same time. Ready? Three, two, one,
go. Let's see. It says it right there. It's literally right there. What? Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Wipe out on NBC. Undertaker. What the fuck is this? Oh, you've got it now.
Mr. Perfect. Nope. That's uh, that's Goldberg. Let's go. Let's go. I don't know. Test. No. Wrong.
I don't know. Come on, man. That glass break is all I needed to hear.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Keep going. Keep going.
No shit. I need. No, no, no. I know six wrestlers. I don't fucking know any of these. I have no idea.
I know this one. What? What? What? That's, that's Bailey, right? This is too new. This shit's too
new. This is, this is too new. This is, these are all people from like 2010 forward. Um.
Oh, it's John Cena. I don't know. These are all so new. It's not fair.
I don't know any of these fucking people. This is a live concert. This is literally,
somebody recorded this at a concert. He ain't even on, he ain't even on this list. Whatever.
I gave up. I actually gave up. I gave up. I don't know any of these. I don't know any of these.
I know like, it's like, it's wrestlers from like 2010 forward.
Do you remember? 2010 was 12 years ago. Wait, wrestlers by their 80s action figures. I actually
might do pretty well with this one. Hold on. I'll give this another minute. There's no way I don't
know some of these. All right. All right. There you go. Kurt Angle. Fuck. I came to play. I came to
play. Yup. I don't know. Is there a show all answers? Because I don't know any of these.
All right. Wrestlers by their action figures. Hit give up under the timer. Okay. I'm going to tell
you if I've ever seen this person wrestle before. Barely. No. No. Yes. Bare. Yes. Yes. No. No. Yes.
No. No. This, this era is right when I stopped watching. Right before. No. No. No. I, what,
I spelt it wrong. This era right here is when I stopped. Unbroken Matt Hardy. That's the difference.
What was the other, just the Hardy brothers? No. Yes. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No. Yes. No. No. Yes. No. No. No. No. Yes. No. No. No. No. No. No. I didn't, I've never seen
anyone wrestle before. Moment. Yeah. Mr. Kennedy, you're right. Mr. Kennedy, you're right. No,
Randy, it was before, right at, right, Randy Orton was when I stopped watching. That's,
I gave you like three eras that I stopped watching. All right. Give me something that I can do well.
What's under here? Disney. Anime. Songs. The Office. Anime. Which is my anime family? God,
no, I don't think so. I can, I don't think I can do it. What about popular? Anime by picture. Maybe
I could, I do the anime by picture one, you think? Maybe. Anime by opening. Anime by picture. Let's
see if I can get it. All right. I, if I don't get at least 50% on this one, then I'm, I'm handing
in my anime card. I don't deserve it. Here we go. I mean, that's literally Dragon Ball Z. Well,
whatever. That's one piece. Uh, Naruto. I don't fucking have any idea. I don't, I don't know.
Next. Um, wait, I know this one. Wait, it's not eating Yasha. Oh, fuck. I got that wrong.
I know this one. How do you spell? I don't know how you spell it. Samurai Champloo.
Full metal alchemist. I don't know. I have no idea. Uh, I don't know. Uh, I don't know. There it is.
You know, Yasha. Wait, I think I actually know this one. I think I know the name of this one.
I know the name of this one. I, I know the name. I don't know how it starts, but I know it's
something, something, something, something club. It's a, it's a, it's a club. It's a, it's a club
that people are in. It's a club, right? Can you give, can I get half points for this one? It's
like, look, every, we're in a club. I got half points for that one. Stop it. Stop. I know this.
Right? How do you spell this? How do you spell this? It's a Yu Yu Hakusho. How do you spell this?
I get half points for this. I just forgot what it was called. This is the one anime you know. Hit
give up under. I'm not giving up. I don't know. Is this, um, this is bleach. No, it isn't. Is it
bleach like the cleaner? I don't know. I don't know. Gundam. I'm going to take a wild guess here,
but I think it's correct. I know. Okay. How do you spell this? It's loop looping, right? There it
is. I think I, I think I know this one too. I think I know this one. This one's no, I am not confident
because it's going to be so wrong. And everyone's going to be thinking of an idiot. I'm going to
get it wrong feeling. I think I'm stupid. I'm going to type it anyways, because I don't care.
Oh, whatever. I don't know. I don't know, dude. Yugi Yugi. Oh, what is this? I don't know.
This is bow bow bow bow bow bow bow bow. I got it. Cowboy bebop. I don't know. Oh, come on, man.
I have no idea. I know this. I just can't get it out. I can't get it out. It won't come out.
Oh my God. I know it too. I can't get it out. It won't come out. This was a car with a fast car.
Speed racer. Speed racer. Got it. I was going to say Scooby Doo, but that's inaccurate. I don't know.
Swimming anime. I don't know. Speed racer. Is a speed racer again? Is this okay. Tell me if this
is a speed racer. Is this a speed racer? Is this like speed racer X or like speed racer.
Let's go or something. No. Trigun. I have no idea. Shit. Wait, this is called. This is called like
Enders. Enders. Enders game. Enders. What's this called? It's the anime. The anime. Oh my God. It's
Evangelion. How do you spell it? Evangelion. I don't know how you spell this. Evangelion.
Okay. What was I thinking of? Enders? I don't know. Mods. What was I thinking of?
Zone of the Enders. That's a Kojima game. Whatever. I know this, but I don't. It's like
Steam Boy or something, right? Is it fucking Astro Boy? Steam Boy? What is this? It's something
like that. Oh, I don't know. That's Hellsing. I know these. This is something I don't know.
I know this. Hey, can you tell, can you tell that I've watched Adult Swim before? Because it's the
only ones I get. Is this Pokemon? No, it's one of the other. It's one of the, it's another one.
No, I, I am not confident. Is it? Wait. Okay. Pokemon. Digimon. Yu-Gi-Oh. Things where you like
had monsters. It's Digimon, right? Yeah. Now there's Bleach. Again. But what is it? What is it?
What is it? I know this. It's Shin. Is it right? What is it? Do I have that right? It's like,
is it Shin Chan? Yeah. There he is. There's Astro Boy. Tennis anime? I know this one. It's the one
about the, the, the sword fighter that he fights a boss every episode and he beats the shit out of
them. This was One Punch Man before One Punch Man. What's this called? This, this was an unbeatable
swordsman and nobody could take him on. What was it called? It was called like, oh, I know what it
is. I've seen some of the episodes. Somebody would talk shit the whole episode and he would
do two slashes and they would just die. It starts with an R. Is it like R-I-R? Like a, it's an R.
Does it start with an R? I think it starts with an R. It's like, I can't get it. Give me, I get a
half point to that. Yeah. Let Chat Out. Let him out. I need some help. Yes. Okay. Ruruni Kenshin.
God damn it. I knew it. Now, what is this? You misspelled berserk? Wait, how? His B-E-R-S-E-R-K.
That's berserk. How did I spell it? No, actually, what did I, did I spell it fucking wrong?
This is Hunter x Hunter. I never would have gotten that. Wait, was I, I was saying berserk? It,
it's not like berserk. It's berserk. I thought it was like berserk. What is this one? What's this
one? This one's called Ninja Scroll. Okay. All right. This is cheating. So, I'm gonna, I'm gonna
hit give up. This is cheating. So, I got two that I wasn't supposed to have. So, I got, oh fuck.
Death Note. Where's the book? He doesn't take a bite out of an apple and it kills somebody.
Where's the, if the book was in frame, I would have got it. The apple had fucking nothing to
do with this show. It's just an, oh, he's got an apple in his hand. Where's the book? Grey Man.
Oran High School Host Club. Yeah, I never would have got that whole thing, but I told you it had
club in it. Yu Yu Hakusho, right, I told you. I spelled it wrong. Afro Samurai. How the fuck
did I not get this? Soul Eater. How did I not get this either? Tora Dora. I, no idea. Fruits Basket.
Vampire Hunter. Eureka Seven. Outlaw Star. Never heard of it. Code Geese. I think I maybe heard
of this. Full Metal Panic. Never heard of it. Samurai Seven. Never heard of it. Beyblade.
I was gonna write Digimon here, but I figured it was gonna be an embarrassment if I got it wrong.
Fist of the North Star. So that's not Berserk. You guys said I got, this is the typo. Space Pirate
Captain Harlock. Never would have got that. Zatch Bell. Tengen Topoguren Lagann. Free. Super
Dimensional Fortress Macross. Nope. Would not have gotten that. Would not have gotten that.
Would not have gotten this. So this was Berserk. I thought I got it wrong. I was like, how?
The sword. He has the sword in his hand. No. Gigantor. Angel Beats. Pocono. Prince of Tennis.
Science Ninja Team Gachaman. And Dr. Slump. Okay. That was fun. What else we got? Anime by a single
character. I kind of just did that, didn't I? Anime titles real or fake? So what, I have to say
this is a real or fake title? I'll try it. Okay. So I got five minutes. Yuri on Ice. Do I just type
fake? Fake. F. What? What's happening? Oh, I'm hitting too many buttons. Okay. Chicago, the child
of many wisdom. I'm going to say true. What do I do? Real. Okay. What? Log Horizon. Real. Monkey
Dojo Adventure. Real. Assassination Classroom. I know that one's real. The Last Potato. Fake.
Ghost in the Shell Standalone Complex. Solid State Society. Fake. Oh, I thought they made up that
part. Mobile Suit Gundam Unicorn. Fake. Okay. Death Billiards. Real. Yukiko and the Magic Clam. Real.
Turn left, turn right, go on. Fake. Problem children are coming from another world, aren't they?
Real. Fairy Sisters Hack and Slash. Real. Hayate the Combat Butler. Real. Gun Buster 2 is fake.
Five Centimeters Per School. Fake. Livestock Complacency. Fake. Sakano, How to Raise a Boring
Girlfriend Flat. I feel like there's like a translation issue. Behind the Silent Window.
Real. Batum. Real. Kiss Him, Not Me. Fake. The Scarlet Dancer. Real. Blade Dance of Elementalers.
Real. Naoko, Natsu, Nishi, and Me. Classroom Restaurant of Doom. Fake. I Can't Understand What
My Husband Is Saying. Real. Black River, Orange Sun. Real. Akihiko, Kiss Demon, Kill Demon. Real.
I mean, that's literally a coin flip anyways, unless you've ever heard of these. So I'll take
50%. Do Food? Food? You can do a random quiz. Alright, what about like, like, alright, Famous,
Musical, Broadway, Show, Quote, Comic Book? Do TV? Alright, Show. How about Popular All Time?
Okay. TV Title Fill in the Blank. We think your chances are not remote. Channel your focus,
use your television, and enjoy. TV Fill in the Blank. I'm gonna be so bad at this. It's gonna be
awful. Name that sitcom. I'll try it. It's gonna be terrible though. Four minutes? Okay, let's go.
Alright. The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air. The Multi-Million Dollar Man. Nope. The Six Million Dollar Man.
Melrose Place. The, I don't know, Monty Python's Flying Circus. One Tree Hill.
Lone Order Special Victims Unit. America's Next Top Model. Hi, I Met Your Mother. Father Knows
Best. Gilmore Girls. Party of Five. Sabrina, the Teenage Witch. Whose line is it anyways? Faulty,
I don't know, The Facts of Life. The Big Bang Theory. Malcolm in the Middle. Are You Afraid of
the Dark? These are pretty, these are kinda easy. These are easy. Sex and the City. Three's Company.
Two and a Half Men. I think that's Ugly Betty. Mission Impossible. Uh, the Press. Hot Off the
Press. Meet the Press. Charles in Charge. The Twilight Zone. Grey's Anatomy. Unsolved Mysteries.
Leave it to Beaver. King of the Hill. As the World Turns. Warrior Princess. Not. Rocko's Modern Life.
Okay, let's see what we got here. The Diaries. Faulty. What about, okay, leave it. Falcon Sons.
I give up. I'll take 80%. The Vampire Diaries. Diagnosis Murder. Faulty Towers. Designing Women.
The Rockford Files. The Grace American Hero. Falcon Crest and Knott's Landing. I did pretty good.
That's better than the average. TV Characters. So many characters. Game of Thrones characters.
I mean, that's so easy. That's so easy. Do the anime opening one? I won't get it. I'm supposed
to guess the show based on the opening? How would I ever do that? I don't know anything about these
shows. Um, was it on a TV show? The Ultimate Friends Quiz. I don't, I would never get a single
fucking one of these. Not one. Name that anime by opening. It's, alright, I'm gonna get this wrong.
Oh my god, dude, what the fuck is this? Really? I ain't gonna get any of these.
You know the ones I already know. Do a geography quiz? Yeah, we're moving on from this. I don't
know any of these. Okay, I'll humor you for five seconds. Okay. Well, that's Astro Boy. Speed Racer.
They go so quickly. Um, is this the same intro? Dragon Ball. Oh, that was fun. I'm not, I don't
know. Songs. Disney songs? Figure out the Disney lyrics. Ooh. Do Breaking Bad. I don't know. I
don't want to do Breaking Bad. Okay, you ready? Can you name the lyrics to the Disney song with
no hint? I don't get it. How does this work? What? You, you, wait, I have to get, um, what? This is
the whole song? You, you, you, you, you, you. Um, how do you not find it? Alright, let me think of
some Disney songs. I'm on my way. You can go the distance. No. Um, uh, you never had a friend like
me. Look, look at, look at this.
Beside me. Take a look at this trinket and funny. Me. Up on that, up on that beach. Up on that shore.
Up on that many people galore. Makes you kind of think. Up on the, wait, hold on, wait, wait,
wait. I got, I already know, I, I know the song. I know it. I already know the song. I know the
song. I just need another second. Um, what does he say? Under the, under the sea, under the sea,
buddy. It's the weather down by the, take it from me. What do they got? A lot of sand. What do they
got? What do they got? A lot, a lot of sand. We've got a hot crustacean band. Is it not the whole song?
It's like the fish.
Do, do, do the, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then.
Wait, this is, there's no way this is the whole song. Take it from me. It's better down where
it's wetter. Down where it's wetter. Take it from me. Up on the shore. They talk a lot of shit.
Back the fuck up. You're going to get hit. Um, up on the shore. They got a lot of sand, right?
Where's sand? We what the, what? We what the? That doesn't make any sense. Well, how am I,
what way am I reading this? The, the, the up. Which way does it go? Look at the we what the?
This is wrong. All day right up on the shore. They waste all day up on the shore. They up on
the shore. They eat all day up on the shore. They waste away up on the shore. They swim all day.
Up on the shore. They sleep all day up on the shore. They dance all day up on the shore. They,
what the fuck is this song? I've seen, is it resident sleepers because people want me to
say sleep or because you don't like this? I'm having trouble understanding. Rest all day up
on the shore. They dream all day up on the shore. They, wait, resident? Why would that be here?
Sleep up on the shore. They, who? I don't know this. You dream of under the sea. On the, under the
sea, under the sea, under the sea. Wait, do I have to write this that many times? No. Under the sea,
we the, we got the, let me see. Let me tell you what I've got so far. The, you dream up that.
Look at the, you on the, you what? You under the sea, under the sea. It's down where it's wetter.
Take it from me. Up on the shore. They, all day, they, they, the, we under the sea. Down all the,
the, they, the, on the, they, they, the, they, uh, day, the, on the, under the sea, under the sea.
Eat, we, what, the, under the sea. We, the, we got, the, we under the sea. Do I know any other
lyrics besides just like para, whatever they call nouns? What are they called? Conjunctions?
I, all I have is fucking conjunctions. The seaweed is always greener in somebody else's lake.
You dream about going up there, but that is a big mistake. Just look at the world around you right
here. I don't even know how the tune of this song is. The ocean floor, such wonderful things surround
you. What? I, I, give me the fucking tune. Under the sea, under the sea. Darling, it's better.
Down where it's wetter. Take it from me. Up on the shore. They work all day. Out in the sun,
they slave away. While we devoting full time to floating on, okay, now I get it. Do another one
that was good. How does it go? It's like, do, do, do, do. Is this illegal for me to sing this?
Ha ha! The seaweed is always greener in somebody else's lake. You dream about going
greener in somebody else's lake. You dream about going up there, but that is a big mistake.
I'm gonna get fucking sued. Might as well stop this now. I want to do another one. Can I do
another one? Do they have more than these? Oh, let me do the first one. I like this. This is cool.
All right, let's go. That's probably the only Disney song I know. Uh, my time. The, the, uh,
the, uh, uh. That's inaccurate. Find the, find the time. Find the power inside. In the, in your,
you find the, you find the right, you find the, what a wonderful phrase. In, uh, in the,
in that, of, and. These are the vowels. This is the Wheel of Fortune, that way you get these.
In that, and of, you find the, and the, uh, and you, uh, of, or, of, this, to, to, you find the,
and the, and the, and the, how many times do they say the and and in these songs? Fight for, for,
long time, long last, long last, fight for a long time, fight long roads. Why am I saying
where's long from? For, oh no, for a long time. For, uh, wait, what? For the, this, that. Think
of something else that's not one of those just filler words. People. Um, fish. Egg. Heart. Heart.
He, he, uh, he, uh, for, uh, before. Be. Best. Yes. No. Sure. Time. Dance. I. Let it go. Go. Hold it
back. I'm just thinking of other songs that where they say fucking words. I, what the fuck is this
song? I am dead serious right now. What song exists in this Disney cinematic universe?
In that be and of you find the, and the, uh, and you, and, uh, of, of, and that, that go, that go,
that go. What is this? Sleep. Stop doing resident sleepers. You're fucking with me. Afraid. Like,
I'm not afraid or something, right? Fear. Uh, will. Do. He, uh, will the, for, uh, of the.
Rest. Oh my God. Time to rest. That's the only time they say it? Fight. Assault.
Beginning. Die. Kid. While away. The hours. Conversing with the flowers. Consulting with
the rain. Da, da, da, da, da, da, da. If. This and that of the, and the time. You find the strength.
You find the. What the fuck is music? See. Eat. Oh, wait. Just think of other songs in Disney.
Here comes the baker with this tray of pastries with the sugar. What? What? That of sugar. The
go. The, the, that of, of, of sugar for a small price of sugar. The sugar will eat. You'll eat
sugar. Who the fuck is eating sugar in these movies? Why are they eating so much sugar?
Who's eating this much sugar? I don't understand why sugar pop up in half the song. Sweet. Savory.
Eat sugar. It's a, it's a spoonful of sugar. Helps the medicine go down. The medicine go down.
The medicine go down. Just a spoonful of sugar. Helps the medicine go down. In the most light
full way. Just a spoon full of sugar. The medicine go down. The medicine go down. The medicine go down.
Who else? Who knows any of the other lyrics to that song? No one in this chat knows a single
other lyric of this song in the most delightful way. Okay. That's it. The tang, the sweetness,
the whatever, you know, I got it in every. Can I get the instrumental for this one too? Let me
get the instrumental for this one. It's, I can, I don't, I don't remember there being other lyrics.
Okay. Every job that must just do the fun and snap the game of every task. This does not sound
like this song. It's because this part is spoken. It's not sang. Oh, okay. So here it comes. Here it
comes. Yeah. Yeah. Just a spoonful of sugar helps medicine go down. Just a spoonful of
go down. I'm doing it too fast. Just a spoonful of sugar. This is way too slow. Spoon full of sugar
helps the medicine. It's way faster than this. She is going lightning fast in the movie. All right.
Let me do the other one. I like these. These are actually fun. Oh my God. There's like a thousand
of these. All right. This one's quick. Here we go. Finding you and the finding you sleep, rest.
Oh, you're actually ready. Whatever. Okay. I'm having fun. Okay. Uh, the time time and time.
Oh, it's because you linked me a piano tutorial. That's why it was slower on purpose.
Finding make my of that time of um, can may I, can you, can we think of some, think of some,
think of some, think of some finding you can finding you can do anything. Finding you can,
can be feel like I long. Um, finding you, finding don't give me any hints. I don't want to see them.
You're clueless, clueless. What the world earth. Stop giving me hints. Planets circle sun, the sun,
the moon in the big blue house waiting to come and play jar. The moon, the sun and the sun shines
shining. Well, there's a lot missing over here. What is all this? Use time for and of this. Yo,
you scream, bought jar. I don't understand. I don't know what the jar thing is. Jar hold
circle football. What the fuck is your username? Um, mercury, Neptune, uh, Venus. Oh no. Did I,
my internet die? No, I'm here. Mercury, Neptune, major F. Wait, good picture. Um, I don't know.
Guys, I really don't know. This one's really hard. The sun finding you can the sun. Shit. Finding
you fire, flame, burn. What? No Disney song talks about burning shit. Let's go see the car. The,
I don't know. Tornado. Fuck. Muppets. Muppet. Kermit. I'm going to lose big time. I don't know.
Shit. I don't know. I actually don't know. Orc sun, sun, the sun, finding you can something you.
I give up. I have to. I give up. I give up. It's I give up. I can't do it. What tail as old as time
true as it can be beauty. And I just type the name of the movie. You know what I start doing
is type the names of the movies. All right. No, that one doesn't count. That doesn't count.
You. You. How are you? How are you? How you? No more. No more. No, I'm doing more. Please do
another type of quiz. I'm, I'm still streaming. Just relax. I'm having fun. You know, no one
fights like Gaston. No one know for the of you. Oh, relax. I'm fine. Your, your time as and uh,
too, too, too, too slippery for the time of for the time of your life for the know that for the time
of your for the of your how your time how will can't see see world show the world. I can show you the
world. Destiny sugar spoon dog cat. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. No, not. It's not time. Dorito chip snow
shake cheese Dorito. There's no I can show you the Dorito. That's not that the Doritos makes
no sense to me. Crunchy cheesy and wonder that's why you spamming Doritos. Triangle chips chip.
Wait, I got it. I didn't even need your help. Be our guest. Be our guest. Put our service to the
test. Put our it's not right. Put our service to the test. Um, I'm really starting to realize
just how many words I don't know. You know what I mean? There are lots of words that I just don't
have in the front of my head. I have a lot of four know the of your will a the of and and everything
else is kind of sprinkled in lightning lightning strike um zap cast try you must I can fire I come
on really strong strength let it I okay let it okay let it go let it fly let it go let it know
it for the I not this dot dot dot there what's the dot dot dot green green grass grow I'm never
going to get the Dorito thing for the castle ZZZ all right ban that guy for a day ban that
guy for a whole day ban that guy for a whole last day a whole last day stop you're distracting me
now I'm trying to focus man stop banning everybody for a whole day resident sleeper gets you timed
out for a whole day and I'm streaming tomorrow by the way you're gonna get tied up for a day
actually don't do it don't do it the half the chat won't be here tomorrow half of them won't
be here tomorrow and tomorrow's a sponsored stream so I don't want to no no no wait wait wait
wait I gotta rethink this no no no let me rethink this tomorrow's a sponsored stream I don't want
to like get rid of half the chat no unban everybody unban everybody all right I'm I'm I'm a little
gift present why can I not get any of these Santa Santa's not Disney bad good fight what the hell
else do they talk about in these songs for the rest of your life what something for the rest of
your life for the rest of your time for the rest of your for the rest of your life for the rest of
your what the fuck it no something for the rest of your cat world hard is this SpongeBob what do
you what do you what is that what's that email goodbye good burger what what are you what is
that says good good bar butter finger butter chocolate oh my god it means no worries for the
rest of your days I just forgot I forgot I was I was busy sitting here thinking of like a fucking
Cinderella or something or Aladdin I don't know I can't believe I didn't get one okay put an
emote only one more this is gonna be quick one I promise for the for the your your I'm so stupid
so what did the chip have to do with anything is it because they eat they're they're hungry
and they eat we should have put bugs everywhere you should have put bugs I would have got it if
you put a bunch of like tarantulas and bugs and grubs and stuff I would have got it you and your
for the rest of your days life of life of life of life that's the meaning of life mean meaning
you and your I mean the and your I mean the rest the of life your face your grow you grow you
to the to you it's happy birthday to you happy birthday to you and you know to you to you to you
to you to you what's all the to you to you of life to you didn't have life to you of life
to you all right mods give me the piano tutorial instrumental of this song without the lyrics and
I'm not gonna I'm literally gonna just click it and listen to it I'm not I'm I'm just gonna click
it I'm not gonna see it but do you even know I wonder if I can get it that way I won't look
I won't look does someone know it they don't know it does anybody know what at this point
shining a light light go let me you you got it okay I'm not gonna I don't I don't care I'm not
gonna look I'm gonna block it out all right yeah so you got it it's not there I think they're
conversing amongst themselves what the fuck is this do you know what this is don't look okay
I won't look I won't look I have to paste it over here though so I have to hold on
I'm not gonna look I have to paste it over here I'm not looking I probably swear to God
okay what is it I didn't I did not see it is it playing I fucking saw the link
is this the piano tutorial I know it now
necessities those simple bare necessities
but you rest of your life yeah whatever those simple bare one more I promise that's it
I swear to God I'll do one more and I promise I'll never do this ever again
I will never do this ever again I promise this one didn't count oh that was an ad before the video
that's this bitch it's piano tutorial video of course I'm gonna get a piano tutorial ad
all right so the embedding it in discord was better because when I clicked it it like opened
in another tab and it was like right there so I can I can block it in discord and I can click
it one more this is one more I swear to God I promise this is gonna be the last one I won't do
another one after this I swear I swear I promise I promise this is the final one I promise yeah
embedded in discord because um if I open the link it like right here and I'm a fucking squirrel and
I'll look at it I yeah yeah I should be showering instead of watching this do whatever you want
you look really yes today thank you okay um yes simple Gaston no okay let's do let's do the
vowels you and uh of the that this time there's always time all all of the time tail as old as
all of the time sorry just burped you probably all heard that maybe see should you go for it
I me my life stop putting the chip uh the fucking butterfinger finger all right I promise
is the last one I promise try to me I think me I think I to all the I want to subs already got it
how how does it make any sense I'll get a piano tutorial what how would you know that yep all
right let me see it I have no idea how you know this what how would you possibly know this at
this point okay I'm not gonna I can't I'm not gonna be able to see it I'll just see the big blob I'm
just gonna go like this okay I literally can't see anything I'm looking over in the discord chat I
can't see anything I'm deliberately making sure I can't fucking see what this is is it there yet
okay okay I kind of have to okay what is I didn't see it what this is the one I've been singing the
whole fucking time oh my god make a man no wait this is not the one I've been singing the whole
time what's the one that I've been singing the whole time have I been wait this is the one I've
been doing the whole time this is the easiest one somebody said Disney sucks what a great tune that
is though what uh it's the Hercules one I don't know my way I can go the distance show me that
one I want to do I want to do that one I want to do that one I want to do that one I can go the
distance yeah let me see that one let's see that one in fact it's definitely going to be this next
one right it's one of the most popular ones I'm just gonna type distance until I get it not that
one not that one come on it's gonna be one of those popular ones and feel like I belong
all right give up way I can go the distance I'll be there someday if I can be strong I know every
mile will be worth my while he would go most anywhere to feel like I
I cry every single fucking time that happens in that movie I cry every time I literally cry
every time oh my god yeah I do oh literally guys literally I literally cry I literally cry
by the way there are people just hitting like fucking home runs over here I just this has
been here the whole time it's just the same like I keep seeing guys like hit like fucking grand
slams that I get look they're just hitting bombs I'm interested in this now what a perfect fucking
song for this don't you think what's going on here this is oh this is cricket oh it's cricket I was
wondering I was like these guys are doing double crow hops at the mound oh holy shit well what is
this you know I feel like I would love cricket isn't cricket it's just like somebody hits the
ball and they just sprint around in like a circle you throw the ball as fucking hard as you can
and you have to hit the ball then run back and forth over and over again I feel like I would
probably like it but that's just been going on this whole time it's like the only thing I've
been seeing holy shit that what wow that's almost a strike okay um what the hell are we doing now
you know that intro video that plays at uh the thing that just loops in every hotel room
like I'm getting it's just like a big loop over and over again and you just like you never turn
it off okay that's better all right so now where are we going where are we going from here I've
had two in five nights at Freddy's I'll do another couple quizzes what about puzzle country trivia
logic puzzle why is the why are these the two most popular on the whole site Harry Potter and
country trivia like what's this one no I can't do that figure out the lyrics just so many lyrics
finish the Christmas song oh I like this one all right I got five minutes I'll get it have yourself
a merry little Christmas do you hear Rudolph the how much do I have to do red nose reindeer
how many do I have to do like how much is it red nosed reindeer it's the most wonderful time
of the year should we play Christmas some music I know I like song ones sorry oh this one sucks
never mind I don't do it anymore uh what's another good one Halloween Christmas holiday songs
thanksgiving which what should I do just pick up a popular one this quiz is does the quiz doesn't
suck I just like I don't want to think of Christmas right now it's too early don't it's
like Dasher what's going on over here I don't know people fucking hitting home runs I've just
been looking at this the whole day it's been like two at least two or three hours straight at this
um thank god I can cover that with a facecam um Dixon no wait there is a Dixon Donner Dasher
Dixon on on Dasher on Donner on I only have one minute Dasher Dancer Prancer Vixen dude comet's
a pretty sick name I don't know if it was a comet comet's probably a comet definitely has the best
magic out of the group I would say okay Dixon I don't know it's I was thinking of Vixen but
without the V countries of the world this is I'm gonna be embarrassed this is gonna be embarrassing
I don't know half of the world um honest to god I've already done this embarrassing thing before
but whatever enter a country um at um USA Canada okay um Spain Portugal Iceland Greenland
is it two words Greenland uh United Kingdom that's not a country uh Finland Sweden Norway
uh Mexico Australia that's Australia is there what is it what is that uh Japan um
Sweden Finland I don't I never know what to do when that happens can I be honest I never know
what to do because like I mute cut the cam I just I just run away and try to get away okay I only
have 13 minutes what how he's but you can't even type this many times in 13 minutes Ireland
I'm going up here France Germany uh Denmark uh what's that one up there uh Austria Italy
and speaking of EU I'll see you tomorrow at 11 a.m pacific time for an EU friendly stream
I'm gonna be playing power wash simulator and it's gonna be a sponsored stream for all you EU
crowd why don't you come on up I'll be there oh shit I have 12 minutes um Greece uh Poland uh
what's something I'm gonna I gotta go left to right what's above France France and then there's
something right there what is that not France too what is right above France Austria Germany
Denmark France Ireland UK uh what's what is um Italy Greece what's right there that I don't know
for some reason somebody's trying to give it to me bell diamond wink Belgium no Belgium is not
right what's right above France okay I'm right I'm running out of time let's I know like you know
China there's you know South Korea there's North Korea uh there is uh there's uh there's Russia
there is um uh it's India I'm I'm over here now there is I know this stand is right there
then there is what is I could just start writing countries somebody's saying cheese cheese cheese
what's the cheese for all right let me just Brazil's right there then you got uh Ecuador
then you've got um the domin Dominican Republic you've got no Peru Peru is right here then you've
got cheese what Wisconsin's not up here what's cheese buttery cheese butter cheese butter cheese
cheese cheese cheese there's a country known for cheese every country is known for cheese
there aren't very many countries on earth that don't have a cheese state every country on earth
has a cheese region that doesn't help me oh Swiss cheese but that's not above France
but what I what's above France there's a good sauce to put on think of a type of cheese you'll
get there I don't care I give up Luxembourg I thought that I thought some of these were cities
I thought this is some of these were cities I thought that Luxembourg was like a city
okay what are the quizzes can I do what time is it landmarks city state find the U.S. states
no outlines minefield what this is the one that I kept fucking up this is the one I've done I've
been here before I've done this before yeah I don't want to do this again I've actually been on this
website and did this one I'll try it one more time though Idaho West Virginia I literally clicked
there but that's fine Tennessee North Dakota literally clicked there but that's fine West
Virginia I literally just clicked there West Virginia come on come on I'm I'm literally right
there literally New Jersey's like it's so why did I think New Jersey was as small as a like a pin
prick Delaware okay guys if all the lights in my house were off I would still have trouble finding
where the fuck I was how many times have you been in okay the house that you've lived in
even if you've been there for a full decade it doesn't matter if you it doesn't matter you know
where the things are but you still have to go like this on the wall to where the light switch is okay
sorry that was bad you got to fill out the outside first it's the only way you can do it
oh you can skip that's right I forgot what oh that's Arizona it's gonna be so hard to click this dude
oh my god and I know where New York is I just clicked it I can I zoom in because
how am I supposed to click that reliably every time I have to slow down I'm trying to go too
fast and I keep just clicking out of the circle it's right there but I don't want to get it wrong
it's right here but I don't want to get it wrong that's it what I do oh Louisiana is the is the
boot what the fuck are you talking about I'm doing this one more time and I'm done like a quarter of
an inch off thank you I need more info first Mississippi is right here I think I don't know
I can't click this yet because it's gonna I know where it is but I can't click it same with this
one George is right here I'm not clicking it though Haya's right here I'm not I did click
it never mind I'm not clicking it what wait you you idiot it's Utah what are you doing that's
Utah I've clicked it 10 times already there's a little demon person just always 24 hours a day
he's right here he's like he's inside my brain and he's right there and he's and all he does all day
24 7 he just says the same sentence over and over again hurry up hurry up hurry up hurry up
hurry up hurry up hurry up hurry up hurry up and I'm just like I'm fucking I'm going fast
go as fast as I can I could be taking a bath and I'll hear hurry up hurry up come on hurry up
hurry up go quickly fast fast go fast hurry quickly quickly go fast hurry up no slow down
slow down thank you see he's like grabbing he's grabbing the muffs and he's like Michigan you know
what that is right there hurry up see and he fucked it up I got it man all right I'm done
I quit I'm done last one slow down I know where these all are I know where these all are see
right here Utah you know that Massachusetts Nevada Pennsylvania I know where these are
what did I crash what the hell was that I mean that's yeah I clicked it I clicked it do a food
quiz all right we got food quiz I mean I literally clicked inside of it I literally I know I clicked
inside of it okay um you're distinct refresh your page you'll be good all right so give me a food
one is there a food one on sparkle is it like a good food category or what yeah if you guys have
some suggestions put them in the send them mods you got some the food cube what's the food key the
food cube okay is that on here food cube just search for food that was so vague where are we
sending these to your hold on does it oh there's okay there it is food cubes can you name the food
items that have been cut into cubes I'll try all these are all sushi to me I don't know what any
of these are 12 minutes um I see a kiwi yeah um this meat beef do I have to be specific uh pork
that's pork right uh that's cabbage that's a green that's a green bean a green uh green pepper
that's not a green pepper what is that bell pepper oh it's jalapeno pomegranate okay salmon um this
is like a melon melon that's an orange it's like birch wood oh it's it's food not materials
uh that's corn that's cool looking that's uh dragon fruit cantaloupe yeah uh tofu or soy
no that's what I thought this was what is that oh that's a mushroom that looks like wow that looks
cool yep that's really cool looking tuna that's okay tuna was somewhere else coconut no somewhere
else that's some kind of cheese like cheddar is it cheddar or cheddar cheese uh that's pineapple
or that one is just kidding lettuce uh do we have to be more specific romaine romaine lettuce
this one right here looks like lettuce oh that's a banana oh what how is this not a banana where's
the actual banana where's the banana really so what the hell is that fucking bamboo freaking bamboo
sorry um that's watermelon this is i still have no idea what that is this is some kind of meat
nectarine no it's a peach it's not a peach either what is that sweet potato that's a sweet potato
could some of these be ice cream is that possible is it possible for these some of these be ice
cream looks like soap um starfruit no where's the starfruit i wish it would blink so i could see
tomato celery i'm guessing them correct but they're not the ones that i'm looking at i swear
this is lettuce this is romaine lettuce or butter lettuce or that has to be lettuce this what else
could that possibly be carrot yep there it is all right cool i got carrot i'm good beet that's
definitely a beet whoa there's a lot of beats here there's like five things on the board okay
cool onion green onion there's a regular onion i can't even do that sound if i wanted to that
just kind of happened i was so focused and just that just happened that's not that looks like
coconut doesn't it i would say that's coconut but i guess i'm wrong well these are definitely fish
so let's just say tuna salmon like bass right yep uh cod uh halibut uh haddock um
straw sable fish i didn't type that wait that's just that's another word for it okay what about
swordfish i feel like i think one of those is swordfish no what kind of meat is that it's not
pork chicken no chicken somewhere is chicken what meat is this like lamb no i don't know maybe that
is that fish that's probably fish right that's gotta be fish it has to be some kind of fish
where's the music that's a good idea you're right sorry about that yeah there should be music here
okay there's definitely cheeses here right let's just say like swiss cheese no no lettuce no oh
that's a mango okay i was gonna say mango or one of the other fruits like that oh lime huh i'm not
gonna get lime that's ridiculous then with lemons here too then so where's lemon yeah how did i pass
over lemon and lime that's like a pencil sharpener i'm kind of stumped how could you forget the
radish i don't know what meat this is it's not beef it's not wait it's turkey it's not turkey
shit okay never mind i'm wrong completely what is this rock this is just cave moss
has like these weird eggs in it pomegranate has the weird eggs what else has weird eggs in it see
this has weird eggs in it this has weird eggs in it this is some kind of cabbage oh shit i'm out
of time so what was it what what is endive endive endive what is that oh an apple okay
cauliflower what about this in purple broccoli weird leek heart of palm mackerel trout i was
gonna say trout potato broccoli it was broccoli you never see the inside of a piece of broccoli
though you just eat it but you don't see the inside of broccoli so that's where that one's
confusing purple potato yeah grapefruit wow i thought grapefruit was a fish wow pear zucchini
pumpkin ugh fucking gross all right um let's do another one how about one more yeah there are two
grapefruits there's two of a couple things there's two limes there's two apples there's two carrots i
think right what the fuck is wrong with you what he's a bit stupid three cauliflowers yeah
i thought this was a fish no i didn't think that a grapefruit was a fish i thought that that
minecraft block was a fish do you not know what an apple is if i don't really eat apples guys
i eat radishes i eat bananas i eat watermelon i eat dragon fruit i have onions i eat the
fucking washington mushrooms all right what about some related ones mcdonald's or burger king let's
fucking destroy this one quarter pound with cheese that's mcdonald's filet-o-fish mcdonald's
alaskan fish sandwich that's some weird shit that probably at burger king triple stacker burger
king southern style crispy chicken sandwich burger king you what onion rings burger king double
croissant which working tender grilled chicken sandwich breaking southern style chicken biscuit
i don't know breakfast burrito uh that's working chipotle barbecue snack wrap mcdonald's warm oreo
brownie sundae that sounds incredible wherever this is i'm going tonight just kidding grilled onion
cheddar burger berg memphis barbecue pulled pork sandwich uh the morningstar veggie burgers was i
believe really fruit and yogurt parfait that's mcdonald's whopper burger king bacon egg and
cheese bagel they don't they both have these premium bacon ranch salad with grilled chicken
as a burger king item that's burger king sweet potato fries burger king big mac mcdonald's
there's some weird limited time item and menu shit on here so sorry didn't get it all right
fast food restaurant hut can you pick the 25 highest selling quick serve restaurant chains
what what do you mean 20 oh i mean another 25 on this list okay uh it's definitely we're the ones
i just know i i'm out of time burger king uh chick-fil-a chipotle del taco is not right why
did i click that why would i ever click that dominoes dunkin donuts uh is no not firehouse
jack in the box kfc mcdonald's obviously pizza hut taco bell subway starbucks
wendy's all right this is where it gets hard some of these are just barely up there and if i
would take a guess i would say some it's probably arby's sonic highest selling highest selling five
guys nope but this is kind of not fair because i feel like these are just the restaurants with
the most amount of chains right so if that's the case then i'm gonna have to go with something like
this right papa john's little caesar's popeyes pandexpress the rest of these are not everywhere
probably this one yep probably dairy queen there's only a few more definitely not in and out
timmy's what tim tim hortons no i don't have any more guesses it's gonna be one of these sandwich
places like jimmy john's they're everywhere but but which one of these two guys named sandwich places
um it's not it's not in and out it can't be they're not they're in a very limited uh market
panera yeah did i run out of time i didn't run it oh did i got them all did i get them
i thought it was 25 wait what what happened oh i have no more guesses left okay well what i want
to know the answers all right it was jimmy john's uh water burger really and zaxby's were the other
ones okay water burger oh it showed you the answers oops fast food logos i mean this this is
children could get this right classic american food can you match the two parts to create an
american food classic yeah i can that's buffalo chicken excuse me what what candied bacon what
corn chicken fried cheese steak key lime pie buffalo where's the oh come on buffalo wings
okay candied uh candied sweet potatoes candied benedict eggs benedict hash browns
tuna casserole yeah i need to go right to left cheese steak sloppy cheese steak philly cheese
steak bob new england clam chowder hot dogs hot dog hot dog hot dog hot dog hot dog hot dog
hot dog pulled hot dog i don't know french fries sloppy joe oh sloppy joe sounds awesome right now
deep juice pizza pork pulled pork uh surf and turf red velvet cake oysters Rockefeller cranberry
salad cranberry sauce chicken fried steak corn on the cob corn dogs candied salad
cedar waldorf sweet potatoes no world off salad cedar plank salmon and candied sweet potatoes
i know my american food and it's good burger king death metal what is delicious foods a to z um
that's artichoke bacon coleslaw donut um what are those clams oh wait what are they oysters
what the what are those i've never seen those in the top right before in my whole life
okay whatever um aren't those things hush hush puppies right aren't those hush puppies um
what are those called those are called corn balls oh all right you hold on burger hamburger
ice cream um lasagna wait hold on is that kimchi oh god oh it's just i don't like that i hate it
it's just this like it's just red shell whole entire fucking animal i don't know i don't like
it i can't get over it i don't like it i can't even look at it it's fucking weird man it's just
weird to me it's where i want to cover that with a piece of paper my grandmother that's what ruined
everything we had the dinner table and it would be people everyone's eating and the thing some
people eat lobster like like they've never eaten food it's like in their whole life like some
people eat a lobster like it's literally the last thing they're ever going to eat in their entire
life and they like what's in here oh and it's just like god damn it what are you doing oh there's
some still in there and i just want i just i don't like it i don't like it i don't like it at all
and a lot of people that i have grew up around ate lobster like that i remember when i was younger
it'd be like oh you don't like lobster oh come on jeremy you got it's lobster you gotta like lobster
and i'd be like i don't really like lobster so i remember eating the little legs i'd be like
just the tiny little meat that was in the little legs i would try it i didn't like it just and i
that's it and that's how i i was like yeah see i ate lobster the i'll tell you the claw meat the
hinge and you wanted something you want to know how i know that i'm out of my god darn mind you
know how i know i'm out of my mind i love king crab legs i king crab legs are delicious to me
they're amazing i love king crab legs i love crab legs but eating like ripping this thing in half
and eating it's like fucking stomach i can't do it i'm on the clock it's all right i don't know
what it's called and i'm sorry if any of you are eating right now but let me just preface this by
saying i don't know what this is but it's gross there is a substance inside of a lobster and i'm
telling you right now this is kind of disgusting so mute i'm serious there is this stuff inside of a
lobster it's this weird like green shit yep it's the green shit i used to watch people eat that
and i would go what is that and why are you eating it i know that's the best part oh yeah i can't i
don't i'm sorry but i used to watch spoonfuls of that go into my grandmother's mouth like
what is she eating this is traumatized yeah man i can't eat lobster and but i can eat crab
that's the liver and pancreas okay i can look if you gave me a lobster roll and you said hey
here's a lobster roll it's got claw yeah it's got claw meat it's got tail meat and it's been chopped
up it's been washed we've been you know rinsed it whatever and it's cleaned it's been buttered
and here you go and it's chopped up and it's ready here you go i would i would eat it i'd be like
okay this is fine this is this is fine to me but the but the there's something about man going
like this and just yeah i can't do it scroll down i like okay claw meat i've i've eaten it i eat it
i've had it before but i don't know it freaks me out tearing apart an animal and eating its organs
like a slurpee yes i don't i do not like that i i'm not particularly into that yes how do you
feel about clams i feel the same way about oysters too like what the fuck man i know oh they're so
delicious but it's just the oh yeah yeah give me give me give me give me that knife yeah pry it
open and then and it's just like an old lady eating peaches i don't own no no you put that
in a chowder i'll eat a clam chowder but i'm not gonna i'm not gonna suck this thing up and
suck up all the shit that's in it i'm not gonna suck his whole body up you like clean it you know
take it out cut off the pieces that you need take the you know the part the parts that you know
are not gross to me because honestly i don't know what's in i don't know man it's weird to me
you just like chowder no i will eat clam chowder and i'll be like that was delicious that was very
good but i don't want to open the clam and drink all of its fluids and its body and inhale it and
swallow it as fast as i can i don't like to eat my food like taking shots of alcohol i just don't i
and maybe that makes me a weird guy and i've always oh hey hey hey just put some tabasco on it you'll
like it you like tabasco you should do it i like tabasco i don't like inhaling a whole animal in
one second i i don't like breathing in an entire animal and all of its fluids you ever done a raw
egg shot no you're showing free advertising for oranges what do you mean oranges what are you
talking about oh wait whatever that is you are a chicken you are a chicken no i'm just very
particular about food but i only like crab legs and i don't like to eat it that often do a lobster
review no because i don't want to that one okay why do you not eat lobster because there's only
one part of a lobster that i like and i'm not going to buy a lobster to just eat its palms
and not eat the rest of it lobsters number one are expensive and number two i'm not going to i'm not
going to buy and eat and and and eat this thing to eat 20 of its body i don't want to do that
when all the rest of it is edible and and you can eat it now if somebody has lobster or crab
or they're like hey look i've got a lobster would you like a claw serve it up put some
butter on it what about a whole chicken yeah i don't i mean i i can do that but i don't like
to do that either now that i think about it i think it's a little different though because
this thing i this is gonna be bad i know but a lobster no no yeah that's the difference this is
i it's you're losing followers no i'm not i'm almost at a goddamn million did you see that
this is 993 000 followers we're close to a million here and when i say we i mean i mean of
course me lobsters are functionally immortal well that's insane i can't why are we eating an
immortal being so we're trying to get their knowledge omega l l okay dude how do you feel
about shrimp they're also weird no i need this internet to work come on i need come on stop i
want the internet to work um i like fish but shellfish has just always been a little weird
big shrimps gonna take you down this was a four out of ten rant this is not a rant this is me
telling you how i feel about the food is it a rant or is it just me talking about how i eat
your opinion on greek food i love greek food mediterranean food is literally number one or
number two i'd say it's up there probably number two uh here's my tier list uh mexican's number one
after mexican you got mediterranean and italian that are kind of close and then everything else
what would you order at a greek restaurant um there's lots of things i would order at a greek
greek restaurant one of my favorite things in the world is just like a chicken shish kebab oh yeah
it's so good chicken oh my god chicken shawarma that's another one chicken pita pita wraps euros
oh my goodness with that tzatziki yeah thai food i love thai food a good uh a good pad thai is uh is
up there too with that peanut sauce forget about it grape leaves a good a good grape leaf see you
later what about indian food yeah butter chicken oh see ya some of those good curries oh hell yeah
i like a lot of different foods i just don't like a full like a lobster open it up and drink is the
the poop in his body i'm sorry i don't want to do that does that make me a little particular why
you always wait what do you say why do i always what why are you leaving with the food all the
time usually you can tell the stream is ending when we start talking about food because that
means i'm hungry because i probably haven't eaten in six to seven hours or so maybe eight hours
so it's it's time for me to eat that's how you can tell where hot dogs for you they're high but
they're not that high i'm one of those weird motherfuckers that i will always eat a hot dog
if it's available every time i don't know why if a hot dog is cooked it's available and it's on a
tray i will eat it and i mean even if there's other food items oh hey we've got this hey we've
got chicken salad we got chicken salad and there's also a uh we've got greek salad over here too
i know you really like um we have some some this quiche and i literally just said that because
right here and i couldn't think of another food but if there was a hot dog as well oh yeah we've
got quiche we've got lobster uh we've got hot dogs we've got uh pasta chicken broccoli alfredo
and hot dogs i'll always get one i will always make room for one hot dog and then i'll eat
everything eat the hot dog and i'll go up for seconds what do you think i'm getting for seconds
what am i getting up there for seconds if it's available that's right i will always eat double
portions of a hot dog barbecue we've got oh yeah we've got some uh cheeseburgers dogs uh maybe some
fish and grilled fish on the grill i'm always going to eat at least three hot dogs even if i
eat other stuff is this a quiz no this is the end of the stream what about corn dogs they're okay
i'd rather have it just a regular dog just one line of mustard on it and that's it nothing else
just one single line of mustard across nothing else and we're talking just straight up yellow
just french's mustard nothing fancy nothing fancy loaded chili dog i'll definitely eat it you know
it's as good uh one line of ketchup and then to make sure it doesn't fall off the hot dog
take tabasco so you take your toasted bun your hot dog bun open it up and then take tabasco
and put it inside the bun so it soaks into the bread and then put the hot dog on a drizzle of
ketchup and that's how that's it it's delicious green peppers on a hot dog i've never done that
before what's the worst ballpark food popcorn popcorn sucks why would you know popcorn sucks
i hate popcorn i love popcorn when i make it in my own house and sit on my couch i love it
popcorn as a going out food is awful it's awful movie theater nope you know what i do here's my
movie theater mcdonald's order a large coke that's it just a huge at least 32 ounce coca-cola and
make sure you piss before the movie because popcorn doesn't matter what size you get it always ends
up the same way you get it you put a bunch of butter all over it and oh wow movie theater
popcorn let's go your hands end up turning this weird greasy film and it gets all over your lips
you start to get this popcorn exhaustion where it starts to taste terrible after a while you've got
half a bag of popcorn that you're not going to eat that you haven't touched and you just it's
like just butter and oil and it's just like this greasy flavor it's just like i don't fucking want
to eat this anymore it's like popcorn exhaustion it happens and you end up just getting it stuck
in every single tooth you know i had a piece of popcorn stuck in the gum up here up underneath
my front tooth gum and it was there three or four days straight i had to go in there because i it
was either this or i had to go to the dentist it was slid in the gum so i had to really really
meticulously with a fingernail sit there for it but it felt probably like at least an hour just
get it get it get it no no it's still in there finding various tools and then finally like you
slide it down out of the gum it sucked now even with a toothpick it was hard i like popcorn it's
just i don't like eating it at um out at places because you always have that you always don't even
eat it it can really get bad that you have to go to the dentist and i contemplated it at least once
you know what i was talking to holly about uh the other day which she was she looked at me she was
like what happened to you what happened this is completely unrelated but i want to talk about it
so i i get i've had ingrown hairs that in my nose before so this is why guys don't don't pluck
your nose hairs don't do it if you want to trim your nose hairs you trim them to the line right
to the edge of where you're kind of where your nose right to the edge kind of here right trim
them to here don't go up there with a don't pluck them don't do stop please stop i'm about to tell
you a horrible story don't pluck your nose hairs don't do it just trim them to a point where they're
not visible but they're above the line that's it you don't have to do anything else proceed i'm just
telling i need to tell a story but look this stream is over i'll see you tomorrow if you're
gonna show up tomorrow we'll see you tomorrow morning 11 a.m pacific so i used to get up there
with one of those nose hair trimmers and right and those things yeah they get rid of the hair
and if you pluck it gets rid of the hair but on two separate occasions years apart i had an
ingrown hair in my nose in here this way so like it was in like it was like there like right here
and i'm not making this up this is for real some of you may have had this experience before it's
a horrible experience the nose hair that got ingrown started to be inflamed and it was painful
there eventually ended up being a big red painful bump on the outside of my nose and over a week or
two the nose hair that was inside my nose came out the front of my fucking nose this way this way and
eventually it was in the i'm in the mirror and it's like oh my god and i had to pull it out through
the front of my face two different times horrible experience i told you this is gonna be a gross
story i said be ready here comes a gross story this can't be true it is it's absolutely true
did it hurt yes it did the thing is when the hair finally like actually came out the other side
and again this happened two different times multiple years apart that didn't hurt it was
the whole process of the thing going in and through and just this oh this inflamed painful
part of your whole nose viewers dropping i told them to leave so don't pluck your nose hairs and
don't jam a machine up there no just be careful just even if you're going to use one of those
things that those are fine but just just only go like up right here just a little bit you don't
have to go far don't i know i trust me i know you'll look in the mirror and go fuck all right those
are fucked okay let me take care of those don't go that far please yeah and those nose hairs they
actually do quite a good thing for you somebody just said it those things actually you want you
want to have nose hairs they are a defense for you so stop ripping them out yeah trim them
all right i've been on this for way too long i'll see you guys tomorrow goodbye i'll see you later
i'm talking about nose hairs and like eating the poop out of a lobster i think it's time to go i'll
see you guys tomorrow at 11 a.m pacific sponsor stream we're going to be playing a power wash
simulator they're sponsoring a portion of the stream tomorrow it's not the only thing we're
doing but they got into contact and it was like hey let's do a sponsor stream i'm like all right
yeah i i like that game why not so i'm looking forward to it should be fun again if you didn't
catch the beginning of this stream i know i turned it off the internet problem was not why i turned
the stream off i turned the stream off because i my obs was messed up and i couldn't capture a window
so there are two different streams here both of them are like what two three hours long something
like that three hours long each but yeah baseball is now moved to august 19th august 19th if you
missed the beginning of the stream i had to move it i could have done it but the show would have
been worse that's really all you really need to know uh i don't want to have the show be bad well
not bad but not as good as it could be if i waited another 30 days there were some issues with a
couple of venues that were going to drastically change the show and i did not want to drastically
change the show so we're doing it in august august 19th but yeah uh i will see you guys
tomorrow morning have a great rest of your night thanks for watching thanks for sticking around
power wash simulator good night goodbye see you soon and you know call your mother come on