Mario Yahtzee Rematch. How do you spell yahtzee? Is it like- it's like ya- yahtzee? Yahtzee?
All right, I'm gonna do- Mario Yahtzee. Mario Yahtzee Rematch. All right, hey!
I know exactly where that is. I can get it right now. Isn't that interesting?
Mario Game Gallery. You didn't- you thought this was gonna take a while. Oh, BRB guys,
I gotta like set this shit up. Nope, nope, nope. Turn the PS4 off. Get this on the screen. Hey,
you thought it was gonna take more than five seconds. Welcome to Mario Yahtzee.
Wait, hold on. Best out of three. See if I can beat Mario again at his own game. Dude,
talk to Transformer after this. Uh, if we still have some time, I'll do it. Maybe we'll do that
tomorrow. That's something we could do tomorrow. All right, Yahtzee. No, no, no, no, Yahtzee. No,
no, I wanna play- what are you doing? All right, here we go. It's like I never left.
He's gonna get straight here. Gonna get a big straight. Don't you start it off with a big straight.
That's all right. Wait, he left? Did I fall asleep? Yeah, I mean, it's a- it's a generic
kind of open world kill zombies game. Not a whole lot of freedom with the car, not a whole lot of
freedom with the environments, but you know, it's still- it was all right. It was all right. Look,
okay, I didn't get like food poisoning from eating at that restaurant. I didn't really like eating
there, but I- I'm gonna be all right. Ooh, all right, so we got one, three, three. I'm thinking
we do one, two, three, four. Oh, let's- let's go for it. We need a two? No, we don't. We need a- no,
hold the threes. Don't be nice anymore. The days gone devs aren't here anymore. It's all right.
Let's just pick the one. Okay, it's my turn now. It's the best- it's the best out of three, guys.
We got plenty of opportunity. Oh god damn it. Full house and a small straight immediately.
Come on. I think I just take the small straight here. I mean, he- the- I- it's- I'm- that's what
I'm gonna do. I'm just taking the straight. 48 points to one. Go for the- yeah, go for the big one.
Three, four, five, let's go. Two, give me a two. It's not a two. I really enjoy playing with you.
Yo, go fish. Go back to days gone. You don't get to have it both ways, okay guys?
I ain't gonna get like bullied out of days gone to do the thing that everyone wanted to then be like
wait, wait, wait. Can you go back to days gone? That was fun. Play both at the same time. I can't
do that. Okay, so we're gonna go with fives here. We could do two, three, four, five. I mean, we
could go- we could try for a big straight. Just need a six or a one. Give it to me.
It's gonna have to be choice. Damn it. Choice or twos?
It's gonna have to be twos. Damn it. Damn it. It's all right. Oh, he- he can win one.
He won't win this though. But he has nothing on fives. I mean, this is not bad. This is not a
bad a thing. I just need to get- I gotta get some good sixes, fives, and fours, and I'll be good to
go. This is bad. Hold the three and roll everything else. It's just- it's bad. Bad. A full house though.
I mean, I- a full house with these is so bad. This is gonna be- how many points is that gonna be?
That's not- that's a waste. Yeah, I'm not gonna do that. I'm just gonna hold- I'm holding the three
and just roll it. Oh, come on. I wish I didn't do the aces before. No, I'm not gonna forfeit.
This is still a winnable game. I- I- all right. I- I'll take this terrible roll. It's fine.
It is still winnable. Look at all the options I have. What's he gonna- what's he gonna- four of
a kind. If he gets- this is gonna be hard to do if he gets this. Four of a kind is- will make this
very hard to win. Or he might just get a Yahtzee. Not the worst possible scenario. Why are you
giving this to me now? I just had to- I keep getting him the turn after the first- I mean,
go for a full house. Just try to get a four. This is the best I'm gonna get. Or roll the four. Or
go for four of a kind. I'm not gonna get it though. Try it. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Give me
the Yahtzee. And I'm back in the game. Do it. Back in the game. Back in it. Now we have a chance
to win. Although that kind of sucks that he got that. That actually- that really sucks.
Because now I have- I have to get a big straight. Or- I wonder if I hold the four.
Hold the four and try four to hold the six. Let's try fours. Four, four, four, four. I would have
got a six too. Shit. I might throw this on choice. This is dog shit. I might- I- 20, that's not bad.
This- these are both not good enough. I'm just gonna do choice. 20 points for choice. That's not
terrible. That's pretty good. As long as you- if you get more than 19 points. If you get 20 or more
for choice, that's fine. That's a good roll. Does he go- what is he going for? Four of a kind of ones?
Oh fuck you. I think this is unwinnable. This is a- it's gonna be close. I need a straight. I need a
big straight. Or you know what? I'll take a goddamn- what- okay hold on a minute here. What happens if
you get a Yahtzee again? Is it- is it just a four of a kind always? Or will I get more points? Like
I can get five fives, right? I'd- oh. Is it worth- is it worth doing the fives or is it worth taking
the four of a kind? It's the four of a kind definitely. Unless I get five here. Well,
four of a kind. Why don't- those go- the points went up. I went by- up by two points? Yeah.
What is Otto doing out there? I can hear Otto like-
Let's go for four of a kind. This is gonna be- if he gets it though,
um, after this game, um, he's just being like a weirdo out there. He's just going like, hey!
Mario's gonna put this on the aces line. That's fine. Okie dokie. Your move. My Mia. My Mia.
Hey, what's it take so long? My Mia. Yeah, he's just being like a little weirdo.
He's just like rolling around being like- okay. Mario, let's go. He did it on the- on the ones.
All right, so we can do fours or fives. Let's go with fours. No, full house is not. Let's go
just roll fours see if I can get some good ones. One, two, three, four. Ah, but one, two, three,
four. Everyone- it didn't- don't people get mad at me when I do this? Come on. This is the only way
I can win, right? Two. Is that a good game? That actually might be over. I even got a Yahtzee too
and he came with all one Yahtzee. That shouldn't even count. It should be like 25 points for that.
He's gonna get five. Four of a kind here. This game over.
I mean, I- if I get five sixes, maybe? Is this still possible? Or is this actually unwinnable?
It's definitely unwinnable. I'm gonna try it though. Well, I might as well just do the five first.
Roll for the straight. I- I- I can't. That's the best full house I'm gonna get. Wait! Wait! Don't!
Wait! He's playing Yahtzee again. It's fun. It is. He would have to get no more sixes. It's- I mean,
he might roll the- yeah. Just get one six. Just completely screw him over here. Okay.
Okay? The threes? Oh, all right. He just threw that one in the garbage. Why? Why? Five sixes
are straight. I- there's no fives or sixes here. Well, there's the fives. Here's the opportunity.
One, two, three, four. No. Just give me some more fives.
Hmm. Might as well go out with dignity, right?
Shut up! I'm just- I'm sorry. You sound so defeated.
I care more about Mario Yahtzee than I do about Days Gone. Oh, god damn it. This is over. So does
everybody else. Play it out. Sixes. We can't do a straight. I could have used
so long ago. Come on. Fill it up with sixes. At least give me something cool.
Unwinnable. Wait. Oh, 20- 30 points, right? Yeah. Unwinnable. Game over.
You never defeat Mario? I defeated him last time. I beat him at best two out of three.
Mario's gonna put this on the sixes line. I beat him at Go Fish. I beat him at Yahtzee.
He beat me in checkers. I'm not done. We're going again. I'm just gonna go for the straight.
Okay, give me- give me. That's it. I got it. I'm gonna really enjoy playing with you.
I got a better score this time. I win. How about another game with me?
Yeah. All right. That's- first game goes to Mario. Second game is gonna come back to the hometown,
to me. I'm playing on my home turf now. We're in a stadium with 40,000 people watching us play
Yahtzee. He's gonna start off strong here. Oh, fuck. This is bad. I think a little is a big one.
Little straight. All right, my turn. Yahtzee right off the bat. One,
two, three. I can get- I just needed two. I need a four. This is not gonna work. Let's just go with
the ones. It's all right. It's not a bad aces. Please use this emote. It feels useless.
Well, don't say that. What's he trying to do? Why is he holding the two ones?
Hmm. Mario's gonna put these on the aces line. Why wouldn't you just roll for the ones?
Your roll. Well, I already have the straight. Let's go for the big one. Five. Five. No.
It's my turn now. What can we expect as an eSports? The Mario eSports Yahtzee?
Don't do it. That's going on the aces line. Yeah. You're gonna take a shitty two.
It's your turn. Ooh. Okay. Now we've got an opportunity here. I'm going for straight up
sixes. Give me some sixes. Hmm. I can still do choice even if it's not good. Give me at least
one more. Come on. Six. All right. All right. So, all right. Hold on a second here though.
Do I take the full house with the one and the six or do I just take the sixes? Or do I take
it as a choice? Because that's like bad and good. Sixes. We might not get this again. Oh, brother.
We might not see that again. This guy stinks. That's gonna be the move that wins me the
championship. Just watch. Here comes the Yahtzee. Mario's gonna put these on the four of the kind
line. Your roll. That's all right. I'll take that. Tie game. Roll the fours or roll the, yeah. Yeah.
Roll the fours. I just, I mean, I could go for the, I could, I could do it. I could go for it.
I could go for it. I just need a five. Sometimes you gotta fucking do it.
Nineteen's not bad choice. It's fine. Twenty points is fine. Spirit broken. Oh, I'm good.
That's not even that good. Three is not even that good.
Big straight four of the kind. One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four, five. Give me a two.
Give me a two. Two. Yeah. Big hit. Big win. Big hand. It's my turn now. Big win. I just
pulled ahead by a lot here. On for the Yahtzee. Got it. Oh, fuck you. Mario's gonna put these
on the Yahtzee line. Oh, well. Unbelievable. Whatever. I can still win. Your move.
I have to get a Yahtzee. We gotta make it happen. We gotta go for big odds here. Big Vegas odds.
Come on. Give me at least another three. Give me four of a kind. Well, give me a Yahtzee right
here. Oh, well. I'm gonna really enjoy playing with you. You're gonna get a big straight.
Oh, no. He'll get such good points here. Let's see. No. Dates are going on the big straight
line. I have to get a Yahtzee. Your move. I have to get a Yahtzee. I have to. Come on. All right.
All right. All right. All right. Here we go. This is my chance. And then it's a game again.
We have a one in six chance to get this. It's very doable. It is. Four. That four of a kind is
better too. Four is a four of a kind. Probably four of a kind. I don't know because he's got that
two-point differential. I might not get another four of a kind. I might not get another four of a
kind. Oh, you're so good. What are you? Full house. That's not it. No, I don't. My god. Mario's gonna
put this on the full house line. Your roll. I could go for the four of a kind with the ones
or roll the five. No two? I don't even have a two. Do I just roll the two? Do I salvage this and roll
the two or do I keep the fives and try to port? Oh, I don't know. I might just roll the two.
I should have rolled the fucking two. He's gonna win again. No. Then we're gonna be tied up. I
won a series and then he won a series. We have to do another one. It wouldn't help. Eh.
Is this still winnable? If I get a Yahtzee, it may be. Oh, there are the twos. Two.
Oh, yeah. Here comes the Yahtzee. Yahtzee. Ready? Are you ready? Here it comes. The game's not even
fun. Oh, you're so good. I don't know why people play this. I got it. Go back to Days Gone. No,
we're done with that one. Let's see. Mario Yahtzee is the Days Gone of Yahtzee games.
Mario's gonna put this on the choice line. Yeah, we're getting destroyed. Okie dokie.
Your move. I mean, if I can get a four of a kind with sixes or I just need sixes all across the
board. That's not it. I gotta go for the Yahtzee. I have to go for the four of a kind. I have to go
for the four of a kind. I have to. If I do the six, then I have to try. That's the only way I'm
gonna be able to try to get a Yahtzee. But the sixes, well, it's not gonna happen. I'm so
unlucky. Look what happened. And now I have to take the dumb crappy six. Look what happened.
The game is unwinnable. If he gets another six, it's over. I mean, I think it already is unwinnable.
I think that puts it out of reach completely. Yeah, it's impossible. I would need four sixes
and then a Yahtzee, but I don't think that's even gonna do it. Holy shit. And when you pray,
you get it. You just, when you pray for it, sometimes it happens. Four of a kind with six.
Oh, come on. Do it. Just do it. Do it so I can win. Just do it so I can win. I'm not even gonna
give you a small victory here. Not even gonna give you a small victory. That's it. Here's fives.
Yeah. Oh, Mario rolled five of a kind. I'm gonna roll these ones again.
Well, he wins the series. That's two out of three. He wins. He wins the series. Mario's gonna put
these on the fives line. So this next series of games, this is the world championship coming up
here. It's the best of three series. I said three out of five. Well, I won two out of three last
time and this is two out of three here this time. None of this even matters.
Just give me the... It doesn't even matter. I lose. Like, who cares? Okay. Thank you so much.
Nice game. Hey, how about another game with me? Yeah, I'll do another one. Here we go. This is
the start of the new series. Game one of the world series and we're playing best of three.
Good luck. Yeah, I got crushed two times in a row.
You're addicted. Do you get addicted to this game? Do they have new versions of this? Actual...
This is definitely not an iPad. This is some shitty iPad game I can play.
I can't wait to get the Yahtzee for iPad and play it in bed.
That's a good four of a kind. 14 points? I wouldn't have done that.
Well, got the straight already. Go for the big one. Let's go. Damn it. Two. Ah.
You're playing at a huge table? No, we're playing... We're lying in the grass.
We're in Mario's backyard.
That's good. That's very good. Four.
Okay, I'm ready. One, two, three. I could go for the big again. I'm going for it.
Big straight. Give me a five. Come on. Ah, come on. Don't make me pick a shitty choice here. Do it.
Game one's in my pocket. It's already here. See, right now Mario is internally
infuriated by what just happened there. Ah, it feels great. Why can't I play? Why can't you
play this at the casino? Okay, somebody look it up. Are there any Yahtzee tables in Las Vegas?
Can I play Yahtzee at the casino? I got it. That's going on the little straight line. Your role.
There is no house edge. Yeah, but he got a small straight. There is Yahtzee in Las Vegas.
That's all I needed to hear. Okay, so we can do... Let's grab the sixes. Let's go for a big six.
I can't wait to play. Are you telling me there's really this Yahtzee in Vegas?
Holy shit, I'm doing it. Damn. Ah, choice. They get twice as many roles for house advantage.
Look at all the practice I'm getting. Yeah, playing against Mario. I've been in Vegas for about
like seven or so months. Seven and a half months, something like that.
Hmm. Mario's gonna put this on the full house. That's a hell of an advantage.
We get to roll twice. That's bullshit. I would never play that. I would rather eat my money than do
that. So what are we looking for here? We're looking for threes. Let's see if we can't pull
something out here with threes. I'm switching it to the ones. There you go. See, that's the kind
of play I would do at the table. And everyone would be like, a guy with a cigar in his mouth
would turn and be like, holy shit, this guy knows what he's doing. He gets it every time first.
This is the third game in a row he would get it. Thank God. Yeah, I am drinking pineapple juice.
How could you tell? Did anybody even say that? Did they make that up? Am I arguing in my own
head again? All right, let's get some fives. Or four of a kind would be great. Bingo. Yahtzee.
Do it. Do it. And win. Do it and win. Do it and win. Do it and win. Awww. Pineapple juice is
gonna melt your stomach. I'll be fine. I'll be all right. It's very pineapple-y. That's the best
four of a kind I'll ever get. Unless it was a six, but didn't have any sixes. Let us play with
smart click. Now that would take forever. Uh oh. This is bad.
What do you get for the- do you get 22 points? Mario only enjoys playing with you when he's
winning. Well, I can do fives. I can also try for the two- I could do full house, a terrible
full house, but it's still a full house. I'm doing it. Oh, that sucks. That's so bad. That's
terrible. 13 points? Why did I do this? That's so bad. No, I'm taking it.
If I got two fives there, that would've been so- that would've been worse than a full house there.
This is the part where the guy with the cigar puts it back in his mouth and shakes his head and looks
away. Yeah, I thought I could trust you, kid. That's when the guy grabs, he like smears his
hand on the table with the four grand and chips into his lap. I'm going to another fucking table.
This guy's an idiot. And then I have a conversation with the dealer. Oh yeah, I'm on like vacation
with me, my family. Mario, I'm trying to tell a joke.
Bingo. Bang. Ah, do it. It's a good move. It's my turn now. I really do have this in Vegas.
I'm going to go start smoking cigars and just sit there and play all day for like 25 cents a hand.
I'm going to roll these ones again.
Yahtzee again.
Mario's going to put this on the sixes line. Your roll. What's the matter? What? What do you need?
He's looking at me like, hey. He's like, don't smoke. Don't do that. Mama mia.
Otto. What's the matter? What do you need? He's just like kind of staring at me like, hey.
Do you need to go outside? You want to go outside? I think you might need to go out.
You need to go outside? Is that what your problem is? Is that your problem?
What's the emergency? Emergency. I have to go outside. Mario, deal with it. I'm talking to my
dog. Show us the dog. I can't. I'm dressed like an asshole. I can't. Let me, I got to take him out.
I think he must have gone outside. So give me, give me like a minute or two. I know I'm stopping
like I'm getting off the table mid game. Hold on. Yeah, I'll be back. Just like hold my place.
Hold my place. I'll be right back. He's so angry. All right, beer beat.
Take it so long. Hey, what's it take so long? Hey, what's it take so long?
Mama mia. Knock it off. Pizza. Pizza the heck out of me.
Mama mia. Hey, what's it take so long?
Who's there? Who? You're making me cuckoo crazy. Okay. Hi, Mario. This is scary. Well, I had an
extra pair of dice that was under my sleeve at Mario's casino. They dragged me. They got out of
the back. All right, here we go. What's happening in the background? You made this to like an hour
ago. Get back to. Yeah, that was from like an hour ago. All right, here we go. I'm back at the table.
Hi Mario. All right, here we go. I'm gonna win this one. Bingo. Three threes. Yeah, Otto had to pee.
He had to pee real bad actually. He was like oh god. He just peed for like 25
seconds. That was, now that's way too long. Maybe like four or five. It was definitely not 25
seconds. Into a bottle and he was in the passenger seat. Come on. Another three. It's all right.
Whatever. Why would you count? I'm just not going one, two, three, four. Wow, that's a long one.
Does he have a uh a win condition here? If I get. No, he does. Still a game. That's going on the
fours line. I can live with that. That's all right. Okey dokey. Your move. He's building his late game.
He's trying to. Too bad. This would have been an amazing full house. Sixes of five. They're
gonna do the sixes. Let's go for it. Do it. One more. Well, that's unfortunate. Oh brother.
It's okay though. Were you playing that back to work clip while you were away? Yeah. What's he
going for? He already has his sixes. What are you trying to do? These ones again. You trying to get
a yahtzee? Why would you go? I got it. What are you gonna put this on? Mario's gonna put this
on the deuces line. Why would you do that? Okey dokey. Your move. He just blew the whole game.
He actually, I think, just blew it. Oh all right. Well, whatever Mario. It's not my role. I'm not
gonna tell you how to do it. Way to go. It's my turn now. He has to get a straight or a yahtzee.
It's not gonna happen. These ones again. No, no. The game's over. This is game over. I'm gonna roll
these ones again. It's the hardest thing to get in the whole game. That's going on the big straight.
Holy shit. He got it. Oh that's bad. Oh no. Your role. Oh he didn't. Okay, I've, for a second,
I looked down and like scratched my nose and I heard, that's going on the big straight.
I was like, oh there, he got it. Uh fives. Let me put this game away.
So he can still win if he gets a yahtzee. He needs, no, he's gonna... don't get a yahtzee. That's not
good oh god don't get a six game over that was that was scary see if I can get
it I'll try Mario I'm trying to roll man no don't matter one more if I win the
next one then I win the championship against Mario and that's it Mario I'm
going for it you got to win two more I just have to win this one that's a
pretty strong start if he gets a full house here that's a strong 28 points
shit I get it let me answer with something big no that's not what I want
I don't want to do a full house with one in three he took off the weights I can't
restart holy shit these huge numbers he's going for straight glad he didn't
hold the sixes the fives cuz that would have been bad really not hard to get a
little straight that doesn't concern me that much I should still hmm fives or
should I go for two three should I go for the big one we'll just do the fives
it's too risky yeah it is too risky but I'm doing it anyways and go do not
answer with a big straight no don't do it don't get him one something bad
something terrible yes that is dog shit good two fives Mario is echoing he's
echoing what do you mean he's echoing I've also been my audio has been delayed
this whole time we can hear him through your mic oh it's because the game's
really loud I was delayed by about a full second so I was probably reacting a
second later than when things happen I know I get it let's go I get it Mario
you can hear through your dangling headphone that's so funny it really is
hanging down right here because my audio was delayed that's great let's go no
that's not good but it might be all I could get what do you think four and
three full house better opportunity later I'm gonna go for it or I could go
for the threes damn it yeah get a little straight two three four let's try to get
a little straight fuck it's such a ridiculous it's such a high chance to
get this to I need a two no I need a one or a five don't do this to me thank
God you got two dice
it's good he's got really his full house was awesome this four of a kind is
really good I need a good four of a kind or do I try to get the full house yeah
come on yahtzee yahtzee it's all right I don't know if I four of a kind that
though 13 points look at he's got so much I'm just gonna go with threes
big straight no one two three four oh he's got great rolls here he's had four
of a kind on his last three turns I think already got the straight this is
this is just out of the pocket straight to no it's not it is free um I do I do I
just hold the told the tooth is for a hold the two or just hold I don't really
want to hold the six hold the five and the six I mean what just try to get a
better choice trying a big choice yeah I see it yeah it's true oh that's what I
needed that's exactly what I needed full house sixes and fives I'll take it thank
you I felt good yeah hold the five that was I wasn't gonna do that I was gonna
hold the twos and try to get some you know trying to essentially throw the
hand away still either one of us can win not a bad choice still do fours that's
also not a bad choice I wonder if I just roll the three and do choice that's what
I'm gonna do or roll the fours or all the sixes yes no yes no no no yes no yes
no why just go before no no yes either hold the force of hold the sixes I
should have just held that thing that I was doing and everybody yelled at me
because that mad because bad mad because I'm gonna do what I want now if I have a
question I'm gonna ask it out loud and I'm gonna cover the screen and I'm not
gonna look what is that gonna be 21 if he wins by two points I'll be very upset
don't put the twos to not good at all I hate when you start with two or three
sixes don't get four sixes I need to get that he just has a good just he's got
great points not perfect points he's just got great points for everything
that imagine that was just six six six six well here's my opportunity my turn
come on don't I'm don't do it yes at least I matched them three three three
three I need a four of a kind and really anything at this point that's ballsy
you got fucking kidding me that's a going on the straight line really your
role give me a break that's as unbelievable I try to get four of a
kind with the sixes I think I do otherwise within what what's the other
plate in five I have to go for it oh it's what the sixes do it's with the
do nice he might just do that right now as well check and watch this here comes
to Fox not this time that may have just completely screwed any chance he had I
might win by two or three points right now I get I have to play smart here so
we're just gonna go fours I'm just going for the fours I'm gonna try to
get his minute just standard get good gameplay it's that's not good but it's
all right just whatever it is at least ten points whatever whatever just no
zeros and I went and hold the threes he's in trouble how is day lol how is
days gone I'll need to confirm no deny how days gone four of a kind let's go
for it oh no oh yes all right 180 he gets a
yahtzee he could win the game just no yahtzee no yahtzee no yahtzee no yahtzee
he's not gonna get it I beat him again I did it Mario done
Mario has been defeated I need fives and none of these are fives 220 take the
game and take the series there it is no I win Mario sorry
sayonara Mario you're done more more more go fish I'll do what I'll do
another okay here's what's gonna happen I'll do a go fish and then I will call
it for the night round to go fish and then I will see you guys tomorrow I'm
starting early tomorrow by the way I started a couple hours early today I'm
starting at least a couple hours early tomorrow too yeah just take all my cards
I'm a gay some go fishing okay so it's what do you want to do tomorrow I was
under the impression that days gone was gonna be a game people wanted to watch
but I thought I was gonna do that for like a couple days I don't think I am
what what's what do we do tomorrow give me Luigi's last guardian I streamed all
of the last guardian on stream tomorrow might just be like a weirdo spring yeah
tomorrow I'm gonna give you fair warning here tomorrow is gonna be like a fuck
face stream so every stream know what every stream what about that time that
I beat the last boss in Sakura that wasn't a fuck face stream that was like
I did it stream this is a fuck face stream no that's not true the first like
five hours of this stream was days gone we're dead zero hold on the first stream
that you saw was days gone for five hours so that was just I was just
dreaming that game you can't really plan but that's exactly what I just did for
tomorrow play Sam max and max gonna be this weekend we're gonna do MS DOS night
again and Sam and Max this weekend I wouldn't do that on the weekend you know
everyone's hanging out just chilling on the weekend I'm kicking his ass if you
care I know you got those now looks like it's time to go fishing again
yeah he can have it do you have any looks like it's time to go oh I also I'm
gonna get Bushido blade I'm gonna get Bushido blade one in two those are those
old-school one-hit-kill like sword game like samurai game right those games
apparently take an hour or two to beat the whole thing so we're gonna try to
do them both in the same night have you ever heard of dragons dogma I don't I
have never heard of it it's a fucking fun just don't look for that let me pull
the Mario look oh it's a boo it's gonna get the Luigi's play putt-putt I played
every putt-putt on screen at the same time like two years ago no he's gonna
ask for it I'm gonna get it I'm gonna get his whole stack what about the
hotline Miami to Shrek campaign really this I don't know tomorrow is just a
total fuckface stream I might happen I'm just gonna line up a bunch of random
shit maybe we'll just do it I don't know but that one had like there was like
pornography in that one go fish do you have any of your goombas looks like it's
time to go fishing again Sam and Max's this weekend yes it is for Mario say
your turn play the Jurassic Park game yo you gotta have a Yoshi at this point no
really one-to-one do you have any bigger boys please give me your possess do an
episode of Sam and Max tomorrow no cuz I don't want to do like two hours of Sam
and Max and then just do it that I'd rather do this weekend and then just do
an episode into episode season three you know cuz I'm obviously just gonna do
them all you still want to play go fish you still you didn't get that one how
fishing for Luigi's I keep picking Mario yeah cuz I keep thinking he's top deck
in Mario no I need those looks like it's time to go fishing again
you definitely have a Mario no your games with five-year-olds don't lose I'm
not gonna lose go fish no he's gonna top deck it right now no he's gonna top
deck it top deck Mario oh my god what the fuck is going on
here he's definitely got a fucking Mario no no I top deck top deck for me I don't
get to go again looks like it's time to go fishing again all right we thank
Yoshi's no no he's gonna win he's got five I need I need to give me all your
Yoshi's come here go fish what cards are do you have right now that's another
book for you a fishing for dick bombs looking for Luigi's looks like it's
time to go fishing again go fish now I'm gonna take them all here comes a
comeback it's time to come back give me a Yoshi don't ask for Yoshi don't ask
for Yoshi there's no way give me another Yoshi right now I was planning that the
whole time I was just working it I'm getting up from the table hey Mario's
game gallery that was fun now just no I can't I won't I can't I'll get like
upset that I lose to him in checkers so no I'm gonna beat him in everything else
I will actually like suck and click random places and checkers and lose and
be actually annoyed and everyone will be in the chat going like dude are you
serious like are you no you'd like to kidding around you like not play
checkers like you're not this stupid and I'll be like no I fuck god damn and I
can no I just beat him twice no I'm gonna exit the game he's not pretending
he's not Joe no I'm not I'm I have no confidence when it comes to a board like
a checkerboard anymore I lost all I would I'm like terrified to play it now
because I don't want to click somewhere wrong and be stupid but that's gonna
take us to the end so tomorrow we are gonna be starting I'm gonna edit the sus
command tomorrow we started around 1 30 this afternoon Pacific expect something
like that again expect something like a noon to 1 p.m. Pacific if you're
wondering why this is why are you starting in like 12 1 the last couple of
days it's because somebody is coming in to Vegas and I have to get them at the
airport so I wanted to make sure I could get a stream in me yeah that's right no
not mom no but I'm not like take it it's they're just kind of in town just kind
of passing through town so I'm just gonna hang out with them for like a day
or two so I've it'll be as if I really like never left I mean obviously I'd be
gone for like a day or two but so after tomorrow I will see you guys on the
weekend and we'll do Saturday and Sunday you hanging out with Penn and Teller I
mean they have a show here but no no tell us who it's a secret maybe you'll
see it's not even a secret maybe it's like just to keep an eye on like the
Twitter but as of like Thursday it'll probably do something maybe they'll be
like a tweet it's it it's an old friend hello old friend Joe Vinnie no no no no
it's stuff you don't have to guess who it is it's not like it's not even like a
big deal they're just coming to hang out for a day he's meeting Sam and Max yeah
like my two of my closest buddy no no no no it's not it all right just look
tomorrow we'll go from like noon like me I don't know maybe even noon to six
maybe noon to five five or six hours and then come back in the weekend and we'll
do MS DOS and Sam and Max tomorrow I have no idea what the hell we're doing
it's gonna be a magical mystery ride so I mean don't miss tomorrow's stream but
like if you do it is just a magical mystery ride stream so who has any idea
what you could be missing I don't know but I will see you tomorrow I'm not
gonna play GeoGuessr no we're gonna do something else maybe I'll take like like
the personality test tomorrow I don't know we're just gonna we're gonna wing
it completely subvert expectations yeah I well I don't really have anything planned
so we're just gonna dig around do the Hogwarts test I'll compile a few
interesting things and we'll see but uh let's do the bits thank you for hanging
out I did want to stream for at least six to seven hours like usual and here
we are let us rewind the clock back to six and a half hours ago to Atrolus
Atrix for the 250 they say yeah simulator it's a little skinnier than
a piano skinnier thank you for the 250 Keldos thanks for the 250 thanks Keldos
for the 250 bits they say thanks Keldos for the 250 bits they say thanks Keldos
for the 250 bits that is what they said thank you though thank you Keldos thank
you mr. Comcast for the $3 hey German John Comcast here just letting you know
that I tried giving you $5,000 but the internet kept crashing before I could
send the bits ah well in other news I started using tinder and got a match so
do you have any advice for an old boomer about what to talk about on first dates
except for my overflowing wealth and amazing internet services of course
thanks daddy oh by the way you should host another POG championship we need to
see more of that POG champ POG champ let's see it advice for dating just put
on Iron Chef that's the easy if you go on a date just watch Iron Chef I've
gone on that rant before but it's best did I did I say something about like
putting like an ice cream like ice cream side up today or that is that like then
did I am I making that up in my head I did say that right yeah I said I was
gonna put like an ice cream if my ass what no well up like some it was up
their ass whose ass was it I don't remember what that was what no I don't
remember it was something stupid it was a high fifth it was a hypothetical ice
cream up that's where we're gonna stop that one a lewd and crude thanks to the
five dollars you started the stream right in the middle of my brewing
session making a stout give me a name for it let's see here a stout um how
about Domino yeah Domino literally I'm sorry but like it's it's the first thing
I looked at Mario was pointing yeah he's pointing at it so no you should name
it um friend friend don't even get any of those things name it French French no
creativity streamer I don't know what about how do you name a beer just have
it be like a series of numbers and letters I'll just alphanumerical like a
two six BBB one five five five two it's the batch number and then underneath it
right the secret batch I would think that that was a pretty I would think
that was really cool if you handed me that bottle and I saw that label I'd be
like well this is fucking something this is something interesting here why like
that printed kind of stamped on alphanumerical label this is gonna be
something interesting going on here this is a secret stash it's the sacred the
secret batch Smotherham just gave $50 5,000 bits from Smotherham thank you so
much for the 50 bucks it was up Shrek's ass don't question me you said it well
you typed it I've read it we're both equally at fault here thank you for the
$50 though that's a lot of money thank you for real but uh lewd and crude hope
it tastes good hope it's a good stuff thank you though hey iPod thanks for the
$25 iPod Matt if you don't like the vibrations on your ps4 controller all you
need is a small flip philip screwdriver and some scissors unscrew the four
screws on the back of the controller and pull the front and back shell apart it
may feel like it'll break but it won't take the battery out of the basket and
unscrew it from the motherboard at the top of the controller there's a thin
cable plugged in unplug and tuck it back pull the plastic holding the
motherboard and there are two motors on the plastic with wires soldered on the
motherboard cut them and you will like the weight keep them there if not they're
taped to the plastic you have to use some force but they'll pop out if you do
put I'm not gonna I'm not gonna cut into my PlayStation 4 controller or you can
just turn the vibration off in your ps4 settings that's how that that was the
end of that by the way I didn't read the end I was sitting there going like
doesn't know there's no way anybody oh it does that those things will take $60
yeah you could also like drop it off your roof too and it would probably
mess with the vibration but thank you iPod Matt with $5 and the DIY tip hey
the Jack thanks for the 250 Jack you'll never hit me you'll never hit my tiny
head it's so tiny I've got a frickin such a tiny little head I do I'm not
afraid to admit that I know that to be a fact I know that be a fact thank you to
Son of Jenova for the 250 hi Jerma Jerma Hart this is my attempt at making a
Jerma blind emote I hope you like it I mean this is awesome this is great it's
a great rat emote but I think that I've got I've got something already that's
really good though make it available now I've got one that can be used for more
than one occasion it could be either and of course I'm talking about Jerma C
that could be more than one option there Jerma C if that's what it's gonna be
that is great though thank you for that get rid of Saturn I've never seen
anybody use it but that's I can't get rid of Saturn thank you Juno for the 250
her Colonel I'm trying to sneak around but I'm placed in a generic zombie game
and the sound of the rocks hitting the ground are alerting the Freakers thank
you one black for the 250 hey Jerma are you going to watch Microsoft e3
conference next month from software may show their next game really that's
pretty soon after the secure Oh but maybe thank you daddy for the $30 we
got some moonshine we got some Cheetos we got some tail come on out thank you
daddy thank you daddy Phil that's what I'm gonna call you from now on daddy
Phil daddy Phil daddy daddy Phil daddy daddy file how do I fucking make this
correct without having to say your whole damn name how about daddy dad daddy
feed daddy feel that's what I'm gonna call you just the first two but thank
you for 30 bucks Dr. Papa thanks for the 30 bucks thank you
bubble bass or bubble bass for the 10 bucks keep playing you coward I did I
played for a solid two or three hours after you wrote that I did I played for
about five hours I was having fun but I did see the end of the tunnel there that
I could see the light at the end of the tunnel it was gonna be just kind of more
of that more of that and more of that I played for like five hours and then we
played Mario gambling for like an hour and a half we don't have to be too harsh
on that game I mean it is like a generic I was very harsh on it everyone I
already was I can't backtrack that guy I said I said like things that I cannot
take back already you saw the light at the end of the tunnel they had to push a
pickup truck out of the way to get it that was good that was that was like
screenshot worthy good seriously that was unbelievable like I can I wish I
could I wish I could smell that comment you know I mean everybody would smell
like fucking like vanilla it like roses and shit but thank you thank you mr.
Attajan for the $5 germ is a crackhead streamer confirmed who sneezes stories
into people's heads I'm not a fucking crackhead I was hit in the face with a
shovel before though like right in the head I have I have taken a shovel to the
face the corner of a shovel went right into the corner of my eye like up in my
like forehead up on like the brow bone and I was like 12 oh I'll tell you what
happened now this is a very short story I was at my friend's house and we were
outside in the snow without context somebody beat me in the face of the
shovel right okay so let me give you context so I was at my friend's house
and we were outside playing in the snow it was snowing out we were probably like
12 13 years old and he had a little sister and his little sister was in the
front door of the house we were outside and he had a shovel and he's standing in
front of the front door maybe yeah maybe five to ten maybe ten feet away from the
front door and he was taking big huge and this is one of those plow shovels
the big heavy fucked up ones that you stick on the ground and walk and you
plow forward right so what he was doing is he was picking up the snow he flipped
it upside down it was picking snow up with the shovel portion and she was
opening the door and he was throwing snow at her to try to get into the house
and hit her with the snow so he's just shoveling throw she was opening through
a closing the door opening through a closing the door he was just trying to
throw snow into the house so I was on a sled just sitting behind him and I don't
know what I don't understand how this happened I really don't know it like my
memory doesn't form this for some reason but I was sitting down or like
sledding because he had a staircase a little staircase that was covered in
snow and I was like kind of going down it and like inching back because he was
maybe I don't know five feet in front of that so I like sled down it and like
shimmied my butt forward and I was getting way too close because he wasn't
paying attention to me so on his backswing he was getting close and I
guess just stupid 12 year old me did not understand but I just got too close and
on his big backswing to like throw the snow he hit me right in the fucking face
right in the eye and busted my forehead under pretty much right where my brow
bone meets my eye it was just like boom and my face just exploded with blood and
I had to get it like sutured up there's actually I mean maybe you can still see
it I actually have like a line in my eyebrow let's see if we could find it
together don't make fun of the shirt I know you already will so which I was it
was it right here right there I have like a hole in my eyebrow like right here
I didn't see that before did you now you do no you just could like see it by
nose damn it I see the hole that's down by your chin your career is over now we
saw your nose hairs fucking idiot what am I thinking I can't be trusted with a
camera a webcam I can't am I doing pants on yes thank God and I've got like
wicked long nails fucking hell this is why I can't do anything I saw some
flakes in there people can like screen cap and like zoom in and find like the
boogers in my nose I know I've already see these posts you don't think that
like scrolled by like the reddit before and seen like a picture of like inside
of my mouth and shit and like I need to I need to like trim my nose hairs I need
to do some like grooming I haven't done it why would I turn the camera on I gotta
get a haircut whatever just who cares why do you care because I I don't know I
just do I like this double you too self-conscious I'm just kidding half the
time don't worry I'm just kidding I'm kidding don't worry I really don't like
maybe like 30% of me is like oh shit I have long nose hairs today 70% of me is
like fuck it whatever he always cares don't listen to it looks like such a
psycho with this shirt on though but I like this shirt and it was washed it was
cleaned from the last time you saw it don't worry but anyways let's move on
almost done here we have five dollars from impressions 28 his five dollars off
a Visa gift card I don't know what to do with because you're a cool guy
germapop oh five dollars off of this I thought you meant like a coupon for five
dollars off a gift card well thank you for the five dollars appreciate the five
dollars from the Visa gift card hey the Jack thanks for the 250 Jeremy you need
to stop playing this you would banned by TOS because there's no gameplay and
you're not in creative hmm thank you Freudian weapon for the 250 if you're
making balloon animals on stream can I have a giraffe please I can only do
snakes and small dogs nothing else hey CAD thanks for the 250 what flavor was
the Gatorade before you ruined it with your piss always blue or purple any of
the hot colored Gatorade's by talking orange red any of the you know the sun
light spectrum any of the heat flavors they're all terrible red just tastes
like fucking old fruit punch orange tastes like battery acid it just acid
yellow yellow just tastes like sour patch kids that they grind it up and
added water to and then drained the water from the sour patch kids mixture
it's awful blue tastes fresh like the blue tastes like a nice fresh clean
laundry blueberry and purple is a nice deep deep grape medicine flavor because
all Gatorade's are disgusting they're all awful and then not you should never
drink them but you should drink instead is water with just a squeeze just a
squeeze lemon just squeeze it in there and add like two or three tablespoons of
salt and like some tomato juice and a celery stock and maybe some maybe some
maybe some like hot sauce to a little bit of vodka and have a goddamn party
that's a terrible Bloody Mary now I used to drink Gatorade all the time not
anymore though I used to be one of those dudes that just on his nightstand was a
32 ounce Powerade purple and I just slam it right before going to bed back
when yeah I mean if you okay if you like going to the gym and stuff but I used to
do it man I used to drink Powerade and Gatorade just as a drink just when I
wasn't working out you kind of get addicted to them yeah I would do it right
before bed too how do I still have teeth I don't know I really don't know because
these are made out of wood listen we're George Washington yeah something we
have in common but thank you to Jerma lied about where for the 350 Jerma
pissing into a bottle would be more interesting to be honest Jerma pissing
into a bottle on camera would get him banned from the platform forever and
then I would just retire I hope that would be it hey remember the guy that
retired by peeing into a bottle on stream so no you're probably not gonna
see that it wouldn't be banned those of you that like oh like oh you're gonna
get banned because of this no I would I would get retired because of that dude
you see Jerma like did a bunch of crazy shit he got like banned oh he got
retired he was retired he's retired now what happens after twitch do you go to
heaven this is just like I'm just in purgatory I don't even know it hey
Clawrcy thanks for the 250 no IQ I can't play three minutes of ads people will
leave Jerma IQ here's four plus hours of days gone yeah but days gone is a video
game ads are annoying breaks that you might see the same one about like
Gillette razors 30 times an ad is not the game an ad is not a stream it's an
annoying lapse in time and you can't compare three minutes of ads to four
hours of days gone you would rather watch no no no I you'd have to make that
a little bit harder it would be like 20 minutes of ads versus like would be
like the equivalent of four hours of days gone no it wouldn't no no no no no
that's wrong long story short whatever you're speaking for us I'm speaking for
me and you and you and you and you and you and you and you and you and it's
still like a thousand people here that are agreeing with me but thank you thank
you Jerma light about way for the 350 thank you mr. calm cast for the three
dollars and also thank you to clower see clowers v for the 250 no one is
agreeing with you yes they are I can just say they are and then in my twisted
narcissistic brain it's real somebody just said yeah yeah I agree I agree and
I can just twist it into my narcissistic such a sick fucking brain if the longest
I say it it's real sicko but thank you mr. Comcast for the three dollars hey
Jerma John Comcast here heard that you having internet problems yeah I mean
they were annoying for a little while yeah that sucks luckily for you we heard
Comcast are the best internet service I'm not actually I don't read I don't
read that like it's not true I would be happy to welcome you into welcoming into
our welcoming family for the price of your soul and dignity in other news have
you seen in my watch it must have fell off my arm when I tried crawling through
your window to get into your house it's worth five million dollars I really need
it back thanks cutie well my watch now finders keepers that is the law I just
have to wait when did you say this this is two hours ago finders keepers is you
have to wait like an hour and if nobody claims it in an hour it's yours didn't
we already talk about this if okay but like can we read I want to read I want
to revisit this for a second wait wait wait remember that if you find a
briefcase on the side of the road with a million dollars cash in it what do you
do do you turn it in what's the time frame where it's yours everybody thought
it was crazy when we were talking about this do you return like seven hundred
and ninety thousand dollars and say I found eight hundred thousand dollars in
cash on the side of the road you don't know what do you do yeah but how would
you return it I feel like people have this image in their brain of if you
walked into the like a police station with a million dollars in a briefcase
hey I found this and I'm returning it does is that I don't even know that
would be who do you call you have to like call somebody you call the ghost
busters anyone would claim it yeah that's what I mean you'd have a line out
the door of people telling it was theirs I don't know okay hey I found a
briefcase on the side of the road that had 250,000 dollars in it I'm not sure
what to do 500 grand goes to charity and you keep like 150 that you know right
without would that make sense it wouldn't be worth the trouble sit on it
for a year just in case someone comes looking for it and is ready to kill like
that you got like the secret briefcase from the movie that never happens how
come we never see that shit in the movies when they do the briefcase swap
there's a million dollars in cash in here we just change the briefcase and do
the exchange how come there's not some random dickhead that like thinks it's
their bag and they pick it up and then they just go home that's literally the
Oh that was in mr. bean literally the plot of a mr. bean episode what does he
do does he donate some to charity and keep a bunch and then like throw the
rest of the window I think sir I'll take $200 cash please oh does he talk like
that yes he does he talks like that don't get don't tell me that shit yes he
does be great English art scholar is here to speak for a few minutes not too
long doctor on the subject of our new purchase ladies and gentlemen of the
national yeah fuck he doesn't talk like that as I've learned by staying with my
best friend nobody no no this is this is bullshit because this is from his like
movie he had to talk in his movie he couldn't be Mario anymore in the TV
show mr. bean he would always just be like oh oh he'd be like yeah he did that
shit he didn't talk in the show in his movie he had to talk and there was just
a laugh track that played hey but thank you cad BTV but the 250 when can we
expect to see German 95 in Mario Yahtzee eSports you already saw it I already
took the championship thank you though hey Luden crew thanks for four dollars
and ten cents thank you Luden crew there's no message here but just four
dollars and ten cents thank you uh thank you Tibetan hover a craft for the three
dollars hey German if you're looking for things to try tomorrow you might
consider twitch sings if you're not familiar here's a video from my friend
doing it I know what it is I think I would embarrass myself though no I would
embarrass myself mmm sounds great sounds like fluff fun and you don't usually no
I'm usually fucking people go like sick dude what would you just say nice man I
agree with everything he said he's fucking so cool I didn't even think
about it like that that's really smart thing to say or do oh that's an
intuitive way to use that mechanic I mean that's what I hear so hey daddy oh
thanks for the one two three four five dollars here thank you
smother him gave the 50 bucks thank you huge huge five thousand bit donation
here talking about Shrek's ass thank you thank you absolutely not for the 15
dollars you were the third channel I ever subscribed to on YouTube seven
years ago I loved all your videos and was sad to see you disappear from the
main channel didn't realize you swapped to streaming it after I found your
second channel and I'm so glad I found you again because you always have
provided the most wholesome enjoyable content much love yeah I I love all the
time I spent on YouTube it was great it's some of the it's honestly some of
the most unbelievable years of my life I've ever had not to say that this is
not the same but I have a ton of incredible memories of making those
videos more than seven to eight years ago six years ago eight years ago five
years ago it was it meant everything to me it was my life it still kind of is
right the people remember you from the server still yeah but I if somebody's
been around for that long that's like an entire that's a major a whole portion of
your whole life if you have been watching this channel if you subscribe
that long ago and you watch the videos and that's a lot of time why do you
shit on your old videos no I I tease my own old videos I love every video I've
ever made I really do except for a couple of them there's at least like a
handful of low-effort videos that I kind of just threw out there that I'm
not happy with but for the most part like 99% of every upload I've ever put
on YouTube I thought it was a great I loved every second of it and then
twitch is kind of the you know been doing it for how many how when did I
start streaming actually streaming and I was a streamer a fake streamer back in
like 2012 I streamed on twitch I streamed on YouTube not all the time but
maybe like once a month once every few months I would stream no I never on
Justin TV did I maybe one or two maybe like once on Justin TV but this is
another like next step you know just continuing to do what I like to do I
know a lot of people are sad and you know I missed those those videos I wish
you would make them again yeah you know part of me says the same thing but it's
kind of it's it kind of it's kind of just did it I dumbed if I kind of done
with that this platform is kind of what I enjoy to do and there's things I want
to try with it which you've seen some of them already and what's next I don't know
I have no idea I could never answer that question but let us get the credits on
the screen of all the subs from tonight or today yeah it's only eight yeah we're
ending early I forgot it's been seven hours and yeah it feels weird that it's
like 830 usually it's like 10 or 11 interesting holy fuck there were a lot
of subs thank you guys this is a shitload you guys are awesome some of you guys
tell me that you've been watching for years and some of you guys have been
paying this channel money for years it all it all boggles my mind sometimes and
it like now so it's really easy just to kind of forget and just oh yeah we're
streaming today whatever that's true what am I gonna stream today this
community has been large and fun and interesting for a long time and I can't
believe still this many years later we still have a couple more bits to do yeah
thanks this is this is a lot of fucking fun I hope it still is for you and when
it's not like I've said in the past then I'm not I don't want to like put
pressure on it having to be you know if it's not fun anymore it's not worth
doing you could pay me a fucking million dollars about maybe like I don't know
wait a minute no I I I can't like pretend to like have fun not very many
people can I don't think but I'm just gonna keep doing it well it's still fun
and I still enjoy pretty much 99% of every stream is just fun to do and fun
to be around a community of people that also think things are fun that think the
thing I'm doing is fun that think the thing is cool that they're seeing or
that they're participating in what was the 1% skate tree and carousel and Mario
tennis that makes up like 1% or like point like 4% or something your
transparency and honesty vastly outweighs the parts of your stream I
dislike of which there are quite a few that's powerful we don't like the
streams well I I don't really have I don't really have an answer for that you
know if you if you think that a bunch of stuff on the stream is like not funny
or not fun that I all I can do is try right all I can do is like all I can do
is just put forth the thing that I think is gonna be fun and if it's not then if
you don't think so then I can't like change your mind you know and look I'm
not gonna be I'll be completely honest here there's there are sometimes what I
know it's something's not fun and I try to do some try to make it fun try to
change it a little bit try to change the subject try to move on from something
you know what I mean it's it's it's it's kind of like a the nature of live
broadcasting for more than you know six seven plus eight hours at a time I'm
always trying to make it fun and I can't convince somebody that what I'm doing is
like funny or interesting or cool for you or interest or fun for you if you
make that decision for yourself then I what am I gonna tell you that you're
wrong I can't I can't do that I'm forcing you to watch this no I'm not
trying to you know jump on a comment that somebody makes it but I am NOT like
upset by that most of the time because I know okay if I was watching somebody
and I didn't think they were interesting or I didn't like a lot of
things they were doing if that person were to tell me that what I thought was
wrong then I would say well you're not me you don't know that right not every
streamer is for everyone it's all good yeah that's all good that does it that's
cool you're taking it too seriously you're the only streamer I never miss a
stream for if I didn't like you I wouldn't spend so much time here well I
appreciate your honesty so thank you that's I hope I hope you enjoy the
streams when you do come every stream is for me no but just that's we've had kind
of you know not not streaming just Jeremy's talking right and I'm just
trying to make him fun that's all I can do if I fail I fail at least I'm trying
at least I'm trying while I'm here this used to be a days gone stream and not
every stream that look and then nothing not every stream am I like oh I gotta
make sure something fucking hilarious and crazy and fun and it's gotta be
funny fuck for the most part when we talk about that it's it's like a joke
what about that clown car stream you'll see that in a little bit and like less
than five years you'll see it within five years you couldn't care about days
gone but you liked that I was streaming it well thank you again like I said I
if somebody you know tell every people telling me how awesome the streams are
and how much fun they are and how happy they are being here it's it's great it
really is but that I don't also want to then I never want stuff like that to
inflate who I think I am or who I want to be right I don't want my ego or my
narcissism to like take over and it's like yeah I'm just perfect everyone's
fucking everyone's wrong when they say anything bad so sometimes people say
you're taking it you're taking yourself too seriously here you go no you take
you too self-conscious you too it's cuz I want to stay grounded on certain things
that's why we bully you no no that's not why that's why we bully you you're
grounded no but it's good I'm still having a fucking ton of fun I would not
be able to sit here for seven fucking hours six to eight hours every time if
I didn't think it was fun I wouldn't be able to sit here for 45 minutes if I
didn't think it was fun no we did now we're alive we're here but we're going
to two more or three more no you look up more than that we got on a little
tangent there hopefully we're still live yeah to 29,000 drop frames damn over
seven hours that's that is like just barely barely tolerable that's just at
the point where it's tolerable but really annoying I gotta get on top of
this and try to get this fixed but speaking of that hey mr. Comcast thanks
to the 250 so I took my five-year-old child Jeremy Elbertson to get an ice
pop of his favorite master of comedy German 985 when he got his ice pop he
started screaming at the other children about how he's going to crash the
ball coin market with his six stock trading skills sadly his ice pop melted
in his hand as he talked the result of the ice pop looked like what can only be
described as Jermis face being randomized too many times in the Dark
Souls character creator yeah I love that that's like my favorite emote can I just
tell you I love that emote I love I love it I think it's fun I want to eat it too
I want to eat that emote in particular but thank you mr. Comcast thank you
mostly lost for the 250 nice shirt and nose hairs just zoom in on them and get
it over with thank you though thank you Tibetan hovercraft again for the three
dolls have you ever considered listening to fire sign theater I've never heard of
them if not I highly recommend checking them out their comedy seems very in line
with your sense of humor that I've never heard of them before I do a little bit
of a YouTube search today after the stream see what they're all about but
thank you for the recommendation splarg gave five community subs earlier thank
you about 20 minutes ago thank you splarg appreciate that just a five sub
drop stealthily at the end of the stream thank you all new thanks for ten bucks
hey German I would take the effort to make a made-up story about how you did
some cruel and absolutely insane crime against humanity that you would then
deny above all else but we all know what happens to those who expose the truth
monkey yes monkey yes there we go that was better thank you all of you for the
ten dollars and your cryptic message here thank you thanks for the ten bucks
thousand bits from all of you 250 came in from germa lied about Taco Bell which
videos are your least favorite all the modern warfare 3 videos all of them
except for grandpa and there was like seven or eight of them hey devil kitty
thanks for the 250 term I love you streams you make anything worthwhile
watching I want to watch every stream but as is evident by what time it is for
me I have to stay up to like six in the morning to watch you since you started
like two for me germa Hart oh yeah that's it's always that it's always tough
and really whenever I start a stream there's always gonna be some group of
people that aren't able to do it if I start at 2 p.m. if I start at 4 p.m. or
11 a.m. there's always somewhere around the world that cannot watch but there
honestly is not much I can really do and like I really I wish that I could kind
of have my stream broadcast out at everyone's current time zone but if it's
one or two o'clock in the afternoon where I am where I live that's just I
can't like rotate the earth so I really realistically it's it is just the way it
is because some some places like 14 15 say like 17 hours ahead well like 14
hours ahead as a Brit ruining my sleep schedule and watching your stream is one
of my guilty pleasures whenever I have time off University I'm glad that
you've chosen my stream to just chill and watch whenever you can if you want
to you know it's and that's another kind of thing about live broadcasting of the
seven eight hours of stream it goes through the whole day if it's 1 p.m. and
I start and I stop it you know 9 p.m. it goes through a whole day a whole period
when if you catch you don't have to catch the whole thing if you catch a
couple hours or something and then that's fine and I'm not it's hard to
like sit here a movie that you go to the theater for the longest ones ever in
history are three hours like 35 minutes like the extended edition of Lord of the
Rings is like three to four hours that's like watching two back-to-back extended
Lord of the Rings movies no it's how long is the extended Lord of the Rings
the average Marvel movie is four hours no it's not four hours and I got it I
got it right it's like about four hours but my point is is that it it's a long
time it's a lot of time so don't don't feel bad if you can't catch streams or
if you catch a little bit of odds or if you check it out on the second channel
I mean obviously I love when people are here but live obviously but it's a it's
a long time I can't expect anybody to be able to book their entire day and watch
the stream and if you do then I hope you fucking like the whole thing and hope
you have a lot of fun it's a long time I only love the people that are here live
that could not be further from the truth but almost at the end here and then I
will see you guys tomorrow early afternoon thank you to German light
about Taco Bell again for 260 what flavor is German pop it is the side of
the freezer scrapings with a hint of vanilla and lemon and if you put it up
and you smell it if you get it close to your face and you smell it smells like
windshield washer fluid that freon vanilla smell I'll take two please I
would eat it it's gonna be alright won't kill you thank you hike zero for the
250 they say here you go okay here you oh my god what fucked up like British
Saturday morning cartoon is this I feel like I'm gonna fly by in a Monty Python
movie and scream at somebody but that's gonna be it I'll see you guys tomorrow
somewhere around like 12 to 1 p.m. maybe around like 12 to 2 I will set the sus
accordingly later tonight but somewhere around like that 12 to 2 p.m. Pacific
we'll see you we come up with tomorrow should be some fun take care everybody
see you soon have a great rest of your night ta-ta stream legends that's right
forgot let's do it you guys ready you want your loot here come three two one
legendaries all around to like maybe two of you take care guys season