I'm back. I'm here. I made it. The internet works. Stream is bopping. I can feel the energy.
It's time for the movies. I've been waiting for this like three days. The internet has been fixed.
I've been assured of that. We've done a lot of testing. Almost no drop frames in the last
probably 12 to 15 hours. That's pretty good. That's the green light. Now if we get a red light here,
then that's, I mean, that's not fair. But you kind of have to do what you do.
Are you talking to me? Yeah. But anyways, this room has been set up for the last three days to do this.
And I've been really excited to do this because this game looks really fun.
Looks like a good time. Get this out of the way. So everything gets zapped on like a monthly basis
here. And it's very frustrating. Can I just say? I mean, you guys know this. But I'm ready.
I'm not going to wait anymore. This is ready to go. Want me to prove it? Take a look at this shit.
All right. We're going to test. We're going to make sure it's synced up correctly. Yes,
I'm wearing a wire. I'm sure you've been aware of that. And it's frame ready or what?
Okay. I'm in my workout gear. That's an Xbox live vision camera. They don't make these anymore. You
have to buy them from third party sellers. I bought two of them just in case the price goes up.
And of course, I've got my cocktail table over here.
Currently doing a Bay Breeze. If you don't know what that is. Look it up. It's tasty. Metal straw.
Yeah. It's better that way. It's colder. See? What is this? You'll find out. You'll find out
real soon. All right. So let's just do it. Let me get, let me get locked in. You can't even
hear the music is fucking awesome. There. Now you can hear it. We've got to sync this up. Make
sure. Can you see my mouth move when my mouth moves? One, two, three, four. Hey, we got a green
screen back here. Let's add some footage right now. Here we go. I'm in a car now. Take that one,
put it somewhere. I don't know. How about this one? He's riding a horse. Use it. Use any of this.
Who cares? That's two extra bonus clips that you didn't have before. All right. What do you say?
The sink is off. Ready? Here we go. Did you hear that? Hey, hey, it's off. What? How off is it?
All right. Can you hear my voice first or hear my voice later?
And this is very important. My audio is early. You hear it. You hear them. Okay. Hold on. Wait,
wait, wait. So if I'm early, shit. Hold on. If I'm early, how about up? Ready? Oh, hold up. Ready?
How was that? Better? Let's try. Good. To the music, to the beat. It's got to be to the beat.
It's important. Yeah. All right. Good. Let's go. Is it in focus? This is on the Xbox 360,
by the way. They don't make these anymore. They don't even make Xboxes anymore.
Are we in focus? Yes. Is the lighting okay in here? Check the light meter to be sure.
It's a little out of the green. Now it's still in the green. That's all right. It's okay.
Now let's position the camera. Make sure everyone can fit themselves into the
outline without appearing too small or too big. If you find that anyone is too short or too tall
to fit in, tilt the camera up or down and try again. Welcome to the cut out studio. This is
why we separate your image from the background. Select start. Great. Please move out of the picture
while we scan the background. Please hold on. Cut out complete. Now get back in front of the
camera. Try playing around with the cut out style to see the best results. That's so bad.
Can you see yourself clearly in front of the background? What do you guys think? Four? I
think four looks good. Four has a little bit of haze on it though. One is bad. Two is worse. Three
is okay. Four is haze. I don't know if I like four. Which one? You tell me, right?
Shit! This is two. This is three. Who is three? I'll give you a lefty. No, it's okay.
We need to be trained at a very young age to use both of our hands and arms. Because seriously,
take a look at this. Ready? I'm going to show you. Ready? Watch this. Boom! You're gone. Right?
Have you come from over here? Have you come from that one? You're gonna laugh. I can't defend
off an attacker that way. Why can nobody use... We need to be taught at a young age to use both
of our hands. I can't... Throwing a ball like this is like... Throwing a ball like this, I can fucking...
I can go 100. All right. Two looks good. I'm already winded. This might be a quick one.
I've been waiting fucking three days to do this and I'm already like,
oh, I threw four punches. It's time to go home. All right. No, no, no. Two is fine.
One's actually not that bad either. I'll go two. Two is fine.
How many actors are there? Choose the correct number. I could do this one, but not yet.
Step into one of the four outlines for your picture. This will decide which role you play
in the movie. No, no, no, no. I want a new picture. Step into one of the four outlines
for your picture. This will decide which role you play in the movie. That's scary. Oh, I know.
Step into one of the four outlines for your picture. This will decide which role you play
in the movie. Why am I so scary looking? I just ripped out the fucking cord. I don't care.
Hold on. I have to connect my fucking wire. Player one, get your butt on the set.
This is me? Dodge the arms and strike the targets. Yeah, I tested this one. Pretend you're in a dojo
preparing for a big fight. Avoid the arms of the training dummy and hit the targets to score.
Anytime you look at somebody from the side, it's just like, oh.
Action. You fight like a master. That's smart. Right on target. You're getting the beating.
What a what? What's happening in the corner? What's that? That showed the dummy.
That's gonna hurt tomorrow. Take that, dummy. Always use the paw. Ouch. I bet you won't.
Always use the paw. That one was angry. Right here. Ouch. That's smart. They look like Nick
Arcade. Revenge. Crushing blow. Got it. You just beat the heck out of Bruce Lee there.
That wasn't bad. Player one, come to the set, please. I broke the fucking audio. And now
it's your time to shine. What do I do? Just follow my instructions and act like a star.
Okay. Give me your most evil laugh. When? Now? Action.
Come on. That was fantastic. Oh, okay. Got it. You were a star. That's it. All right. Let's go.
Star. I look like a fucking character from The Office. I'm doing like a look in the camera.
Can you believe what Steve Carell just said? Player one, you need it on set.
What's next? Throw the log as far. All right. I can move my right hand. Throw the log.
Make like you're at the Highland Games in the Kavatoss event. Throw that pesky log as far as you
can. Action. Was that 650? That wasn't bad. That's kind of far. Again. 200. Wait, I gotta be like in
it's kind of quick. Good throwing. That log sure won't bother us again.
I thought it was going to be like a situation where you just have to get the thing, the pixel
to touch quick. Player one, get yourself to the set. Don't worry. That's me. I know where
I'm supposed to be right here. And now it's your time to shine. Just follow my instructions
and act like you're a star. Show me fury. And action. Keep it up.
That was fantastic. You were a star. All right. I'm good. Imagine like looking into my window right
now. What am I practicing for? What is that person doing? Because there is no logical explanation
as to why somebody would be standing in their room doing this. I'm like hacking myself up for
what? Like a conference? Look at how red my face is. I didn't realize how hot it was going to be in
here. What am I? Okay. Pretend like you are a treasure hunter. Pull on the rope before the
time runs out to get the treasure. I'm like as red as the snow. I'm not, am I? Action. What?
I'm not very good at this, am I? Holy shit, I'm turning like green. I'm not this red.
Am I this red? What's happening? I'm like, I swear to God, this is like, this is like bizarre.
It's the camera. I'm turning into a Willy Wonka character. I have a sunburn.
Oh. What the fuck? No, no. I got to like, it's 110 degrees in Vegas right now. What the fuck
was I thinking? Get the ball in the hole three times. Hey, let me do this like, this is like,
oh, I got to shoot the basket. I'm not really, I'm not this red. Look and see, I'm not that red.
Where's the basket? Where's the ball? What? I don't know. Oh, that was close, but no cigar.
Oh, okay. Got it. Two. Only one more left. Shit. You can do better than that. Get in there.
Come on, sink the ball into the hole. We have a winner, ladies and gentlemen. By the way,
at the end of this, it cuts up a trailer. That's wonderful. With like three other random actors
that aren't in this house. That's a wrap. That's a wrap. Let's see. Are you ready? I'm ready.
Play every character. That's, that's kind of the idea. I have like four costumes here.
It's gonna be fucking impossible. I'm going to be like purple at the end of this.
Everyone's super. Every superhero's super. But some are more super than others.
Go on. And where there are heroes, there are villains, battles, adventure, breathtaking effects.
Not a silly costume in sight. Why am I in the Bowser plane? Ever wanted to wear your underpants
over your trousers? Rippling muscles. Astounding abilities. Fiercer than a ranting mom.
More courageous than a hungry mouse. Faster than waiting for a bus.
So when you're feeling low, remember everyone's super.
No, I don't want to replay that. Why do they have to be red? Oh, okay. No, I don't. Would
you like to save your movie? No. Why would I want to save this fucking movie? That was awful.
Save it. Who cares? Who cares?
That was a test. I was testing the program for that one to make sure it worked.
I would just. J1. Who cares who? Nah, you guys ain't ever gonna see who cares what.
That's for me. That's a private showing only. That's only for me. I think I'm pretty sure I
was naked. Here's the thing, guys. I cannot be 100% certain that I am not 100% underwear
naked in that video. I don't know. I can't turn that on. I was testing it just to test the lighting
in the room. This was two or three days ago. That may as well be three years ago. This takes a long
time. Damn. He's testing the lighting in the room. What breed of dog is Otto? He's a dachshund,
actually. Remind me never to save a movie ever again. What do the aliens in the teen sci-fi flick
the faculty need most for survival? I was gonna say sugar. Which ape leads the first
ape rebellion and conquest of the planet of the apes? I don't know. Caesar. In The Princess
Bride, what word does Miracle Max hate to hear? Yeah. From 1996, Romeo and Juliet took a year
off from Yale to film Terminator 3. Claire Danes, that's the one. 2008's The Dark Knight is a sequel
to which film? Batman Again. I got it. I told you. I know what I'm doing. I know my movie trivia.
Mary-Kate and Ashley Olsen act together in this 2004 film. Freaky Friday. No, no, no, no, no.
Jennifer Lopez and Woody Allen provided voices for what animated insect film? Beam Movie.
Let's never do that again. Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the You're in the Movies Awards.
Awards? Yeah. And now the moment you've all been waiting for. Nobody's seen the movie yet. The
nominees for best actor are. Nominee one. Nominee two. Random dropper's license image two.
Nominee three. Nominee four. But of course, there can only be one winner. And the You're in
the Movies Award for best actor goes to. Yes. Please take to the podium to accept this prestigious
award. Perhaps you'd like to say a few words. Thank you. Thank you so much, everybody. I'm
glad everybody liked the trailer. The movie ain't out yet. You have to go see it still.
But I really appreciate the support nonetheless. Make sure to go see it next year when it comes out.
Have a great evening. Make sure to tweet at tip your waiters and waitresses. And I'm out.
Guns cold blooded. A spillage in a lab transformed a lizard into a monster,
causing panic and havoc. Let's check our equipment is working correctly.
Is the picture in focus? Is the lighting okay in here? Check the light meter to be sure.
There's 110 degrees in Vegas right now. This sun is just beaming in here. This fucking shitty
webcam from like 1998. This beaming sun. That's why I'm like turning red.
Can't hear me. I'm saying that it's be the sun is beaming in here.
I'm gonna turn the music down. Thanks for the reminder. All right, light looks fine.
Now let's position the camera. Make sure everyone can fit. I'm not going down that line
without appearing too small. People will do like a thing. Oh, look at the thing on the ground.
It's six feet tall. Therefore he's triangulated. He's fine too. I've seen that fucking joke a
thousand times. It's not going to be an original joke. Welcome to the cut out studio. This is where
we separate your image. Great. Please move out of the picture while we scan the background.
Please hold on. Cut out complete. Now get back in front of the camera. That was scary because I
have a big shadow on my face. And I've got a real angular face. Like every single like you could
you could like get shade over here in my like angular fucking face. You know what I'm saying?
Two, uh, two is fine, right? Yeah. It's going to change a little bit as the light changes.
No, that's good. That's fine. How many actors are there? Choose the correct number. All right,
here's where I'm going to, I'm going to add an actor. I'm going to add an actor.
Step into one of the scientists and civilian. This will decide which role you play in the movie.
That person, I love how he's two. No, I'm going to start with two.
Step into one of the four outlines for your picture. This will decide which role you play
in the movie. That's two. That's how I know that's two. No, no, no. I want a civilian.
in the movie. All right, let's go. Scientists, civilian. So I got to remember that because I
got, I've got some, I got some wardrobe changes like a big girl on the fly. I'm happy with those.
Who's up first? So we've got me. We've got another actor. So that bathrobe guy is going to be a
player too. Why don't I even have this in my hand? Go into the obstacles and hit the jumps
in a car. Drive your scooter through town, dodge the obstacles, but hit the ramps to score.
Okay. I shouldn't have wore the red shirt. People would not even be commenting on my life.
I can't even see that far. Is that a jump? I should be reacting, shouldn't I? All right.
Like, whoops, whoops, whoops.
Ghost rides it over the finish line. What a fucking probe. Player two to the set.
Pretend that you're surrounded by hornets. Swat those suckers before they sting you.
Action. Get these things away from me.
Sayonara, Stripey. Take them down.
These fuckers, they sting. One to swat. You sure can swat. All right. Play one.
Who's turn? Oh, I'm competing against myself. How is that any better? Players one and two.
What? What do you mean two? Both of us? That means I have to be like, what? This is
called, this is both of us. Let's all do the conga. Hit the drums as fast as you can to make
the monkey dance faster. Shit. Okay. I thought we were going to be, see, okay, there we go.
It's two of, it's both of us. And action. Dance monkey boy. Get that monkey go.
What happens if there's four people on the screen? Player one, get your butt on the set.
Okay, I'm ready. It's me. It's time to put you in the spotlight. There's no scoring.
Just follow my instructions and show me your acting talent. What is with that? There's like a spot
on, wipe it off. Action. Wipe that shit off. Come on. Show me what you got. This is not how
people walk. Right. Now try this. Do it again. As confused as you can. And action. More feeling.
Put more feeling into it. Let's do another. Give me a look of absolute terror. Go this way.
Nailed it. I look like I'm fucking 15 years older in that middle picture.
Player two didn't even get to do anything. How am I still losing to the guy in the bathrobe
when he didn't even do anything? Fuck that guy. That guy sucks. What did you say to me?
Start the water from rising. Shut the valve as if your life depended on it. I have to do his face.
You didn't even mess up your hair. I did though. I did.
Shut up. Fuck. It's me. It's me. I gotta do a better job to get the wasps.
I gotta do better than me. It's gotta be slow. Slow and flick the fingers.
This is embarrassing. Hold on. I gotta make this less embarrassing.
You didn't get stung at all. Player two, I need you on set please. When I put on this other thing
on the ground here, you guys have no idea. This is going to get impossible. I need a personal
assistant. It's time for your starring moment. Follow my instruction and act your heart out.
Act like you're a nervous wreck. Action. Nearly there. Now try this. What? Run on the spot as if
you're being chased. And action. Keep rolling baby. Fuck. One more. Shiver uncontrollably like
you're freezing. That was really good. Amazing. That was really good. It was. I don't want to,
you know, toot my second horn here, but it was pretty good. Just wait till I get my third and
fourth horn in here. Player one, come to the set please. Player one, it's me. Great job. No,
you good job. Good job. Good job. Now it's my turn. Pick the clothes that matter. What?
The costumes are all dirty. Pick the outfit that matches the hat and give them a good scrub.
Scrub the clothes? Why? I need like a lower body. Pick the what? Fuck. That's good. Now give it a
good wash. Come on. Are you sure that was right? Give it a wash anyway. You only got one. Oh,
no. Right. Right. Okay. Add the outfit to the hat. Okay. I fucked it up. Not that one. That one.
Scrub it up and see what happens. Wait. This is, this is. Okay. So now I didn't even see the hat.
Come on. Are you sure that was right? I didn't see the hat. Give it a wash anyway. I didn't.
Sorry. Second me will get this. You're supposed to match the outfit to the hat. To the hat. Okay.
I can do it now. Ready? All right. It's just a regular hat. Now it's this hat. It's not the
clown hat. That's not the clown. That's not a regulation clown hat. Oh. Fuck that part.
How? How is that not good? How can you even determine that?
All right. I gotta nail this. Get the ball in the hole three times.
Oh, this is the, this is this thing again. Okay. It's all the fun.
Got it. Print. Ship it. Get yourself to the set. Holy shit. There's even more.
We need to do a few retakes. Just follow my instructions and show me your acting talent.
Retakes. How fucking you lean? Pretty far. And action. Get up. That was fantastic. You were a star.
That's fucking stupid. You take those green grass. Perfect. Let's go to the movies.
Here we go. Got it. Wait five minutes for it to load.
Is there any mature ones? It was a day like any other day.
Until a terrible accident. Created a horrifying atomic monster. Cold blooded. Watch in terror
as the radioactive mastodon wreaks havoc. Created by nature. Twisted by science.
No weapons of warfare known to man can harm it. Can anything stop this leviathan?
Can mankind use science to fight nature with nature? Feel your blood run cold. Cold blooded.
Terrible. That was awful. That was really, really awful. Truly awful.
Best part is when he pushed me. They didn't even use the lean. What was the point of the lean?
That very beginning. Why do I feel like I'm watching green screen movie night footage?
That's like what this is. Except it's happening in real time. What do you mean don't save? Oh
right. Because of the... It takes like 10 minutes. All right. I'm gonna get these. I'll get these. I'll
get these. Come on. Play as all four characters? I will. I gotta ease into it though. There's like
25 movies to do. In what... Hold on. What movie spy has lost his identity? Faced a
supremacy in the 2007 issue Ultimatum? I haven't seen any of those. Boba Fett wears the armor of
what type of warrior? A space trooper. A storm trooper. Oh boy. What do the animated films
Corpse Bride and Curse of the Web Rabbit share? Tim Burton. Wait, did the bull stop? Stop motion.
Oh never mind. In Sleepless in Seattle Sam and Annie meet at what famous landmark?
Starbucks. King Kong was also remade in 1976. What was the name of Jessica Lange's character?
Jessica. Bill Murray portrays a network television executive in what 1988 Christmas comedy based on
A Christmas Carol? I was just gonna say it. Scrooge. Brad Pitt and James Gandolfini both
appeared in which movie written by Quentin Tarantino? Saw IV? A teen thriller
disturbing mirror is the plot of what Alfred Hitchcock classic? Attack of the Birds. In which
southern state did Renee Zellweger spend her youth and earn her bachelor's degree? Mississippi.
I'm 0 for 10. In the line of the witch in the wardrobe... I didn't get a chance to even do that
one. Got it. Oh who wins the award? This is important. Who was better me or me? Welcome
to the You're in the Movies Awards. Who did a better job? Me or me? And now the
moments you've all been waiting for. Just went like a four me's in here. Nominees for best actor are
nominee one, nominee two, nominee three,
nominee four. I'm gonna say uh, I'm gonna say me, me one. Me one. And the You're in the Movies Award
not bathrobe actor goes to... Not bathrobe. Fuck. Please take to the podium to accept this
prestigious award. Perhaps you'd like to say a few words. What can I say? What can I say?
I was cloned off of this guy right here, up there. Yep. And they gave me two extra...
I'm not good. I'm not good in front of people. I'm not good in front of people.
Thank you. It's been me all fucking time. It's been me. Like a crow's feet? How can I see that
on like a 144p camera? Fuck I do. I really do. Stop clapping at that. You maniacs. How do I get
this out of... How do I leave? Oh. Should we throw in a third actor? This one's called made of men.
Let's go. Me, me, me and me. Two friends break free to find they've been subjected to a cloning
experiment. What happens if it's just me? Okay, what happens if it's just me? Let's check our
equipment is working correctly. If it's just me, then who is the... What happened? Is the lighting
okay in here? Check the light meter to be sure. The lighting's fine. I bought this. This is a
Phillips Hue, sits on the table, coffee table, dumb fucking pretend ball light. I got this like
two years ago. Just about like a year ago maybe. I've not used it once. This is the only time I've
ever turned it on because I don't know what to do with it. So I'm going to add some light here.
The bar went down. What do I do with this though? I can make it a different color too. I wish I could
show you. Put it on the bright side. Is that going to help? Does it help me? What's this thing? What
does it mean for? Why did I buy that? It was like 70 bucks. Now let's position the camera. Make sure
everyone can fit themselves into the outline. I felt like, ooh, to be sitting on the coffee table
and I can make it like a nice warm hue. If you find that anyone is too short or too tall to fit in.
I've never used that light once.
Hopefully they get my fucking... I need to get like a light pin.
I need like red pins.
With the cutout style to see the best results. Can you see yourself clearly in front of the
background movie? Four, four, four, four, four, four, four, four, four, four, four, four, four,
four, four, four. Four? But that's a little... Can you like see the outline though? I don't like
being able to see the outline. It's just like pretend. Four is bad luck. Better than two. What about
three? All right, I'm just gonna sit right here and I'm not gonna move from like here. Ready?
One looks all right. One looks okay. Three's too wiggly. And four has like a big halo around it.
One's okay. My arms are fucked. I'll try four for one of these. I mean, I'm gonna be like blowing,
but whatever. Is it worth it? No, I ain't doing it. I'm doing three. We're sticking with three.
One.
How many actors are there? Choose the correct number. Step into one of the four outlines for
your picture. This will decide which role you play in the movie. If the picture is okay, press A to
continue. That's like, this is just emo slots. Oh, she's like, a Terma Wild one. Wait, yeah.
Oh, look, a Terma Wild one. Terma Wild two. Terma Wild three. Terma Wild four.
I don't even know who's gonna be who. Who's gonna be who? That's so stupid. All right,
this is gonna be fucking impossible. This is gonna be really, really hard. Bear with me here. It
might look a little shit. Player one. Okay, I got my other costumes are here. That one's there.
What? I need to get different pants on. Let's get the tornado.
Run as fast as you can to get away. This is on camera forever. This is this is for us.
It's gating on you. I played a bad wind, but this is ridiculous. Oh, we are just too wild and
crazy, guys. That's what I'm doing. Fucking Steve Martin. Player three, I need you on set, please.
Oh, God. You're at the fun fair. Press the buttons to launch the rockets and sink the boats.
Action. Look, look, look. This is the face for this one. You took him down to Davy Jones' locker.
You got one. Great shot. Bullseye, you hit him amidst ships. Look, look, look.
I don't want to do this anymore. I want to do something else. I don't want to be this
anymore. I only need like 10 seconds. A minute. You took him down to Davy Jones' locker.
Great shooting. Those boats. Is it four or two? Four? Is it four? Player four, get your butt on
the set. It's time to work your mind. Memorize the symbol on the stone block, then point to the
right scroll. And action. Now concentrate. Clear your mind. Use the power of your mind.
I'm like naked. Great. You are a memory star. Type one. I need new hair. Remember the symbol.
What symbol? Memorize what you see. I don't know. Oh, it's that one. Wrong.
You need more training. There's just a naked guy on this. There's a naked guy with holes in his
stomach. All right, four. We can't do four. Four's not going to work. Who's next? I'm going to keep
throwing my ankles. Player two, you need it on set. It's time to act like a clown with a bungee run.
Now run as far as you can before the power of the bungee drags you back.
I gotta like move this thing. What? Why is it all fucked up? Action. Get those arms moving to gain
speed. That was some bungee. You did it. There's a blind spot just taking over the whole thing.
I'm going to have to move this. We're going to have to redo it. It's time to put you
in the spotlight. Just follow my instructions and show me your acting talent.
Slap your fist and look mean. Action. That's it. Ow. More. Show me your best muscle pose.
Should I put the suit back on? Action. Keep it going. Let's do another. Walk on the spot and action.
That's it. Keep it going. I have no room to do that. Oh look at the one on the right.
Look at the one on the right. It's like my head's at like a fucking 45 degree angle.
Oh god. Who was it? Who was it? Player who? I don't remember who it was. Player three?
Walk on the spot. Action. Why do we keep looking over here and doing that like? Turn to the camera
and look shocked. And action. Nearly there. Let's do another. Stroke your chin like you're deep in
thought. Action. That's it. That was fantastic. You were a star. This is like I'm on some shitty
modeling site and these are my headshots. That's just round one. It's like yeah what do you have
for a portfolio? I have these three Polaroids. Please use me in your car commercial.
Oh fuck. Okay well I gotta combine them. I'm like a shitty Goro. Let's see who can get the uh the
hula hoop going fastest. Action. Work the hula baby. Work it. You're in the groove now.
I'm wearing the other guy's skin. I fucking killed this guy and like I'm wearing his skin.
That's not, that shouldn't be in the movie. Don't put that in the movie.
What the fuck. Player two come to the set please. Is that I don't know is player two just regular
me? I don't know. Player two is the bathroom right? Shake the maracas to make the monkey dance.
The more you shake the more you score. Robe yeah. This guy with the blanket on. And action.
What are they? Faster faster. Shake rattle and I'll just shake it. Faster faster. He's just warming up.
Look at him go. I'm not doing this on the fucking camera. It's really crazy behind me.
Shaking all over. Make score. Yes we do. Player one come to the set please.
I'm gonna fucking die. All right maybe I shouldn't do four people.
Run as fast as you can to escape the bowl. Run as fast as you can. Reach the gate to escape
the charging bowl. Action. Get those arms moving to gain speed.
Hey hey it's me. Are you videotaping this? Cool. Maybe you should call the police.
Now that's one of those scenarios where I wish I could do that again. Because doing that again I
would do like a uh it would be that's like the typical like that was on Nickelodeon like Nick
Jr like fucking 10 years ago. Well this looks crazy. You know what else is crazy kids?
Rugrats. All right what am I doing? Crack your knuckles like a hoodlum.
Keep it up. I want you to scream. And action. Keep it up. Keep it up. No scream like scared.
Ah it's all backwards. This is going back. I was wondering why do I have like four arms this way.
I have fucking. Look at this. That's not how it looks. Keep it going.
You brought the house down. Beautiful. Why is the third one always the worst?
Player two get yourself to the set. Yeah we ain't doing four again. This was a mistake.
I'm doing two at the most. And now it's your time to shine.
There's no scoring. Just follow my instructions and act like a star.
Shake your fist. Action. More feeling. Put more feeling into it. I said I wasn't gonna do that.
Right. Here comes another. I said I wasn't gonna do that. I'm not supposed to do that.
Keep your arms by your side and snore. Action. Don't stop now.
You brought the house down. Beautiful.
Just awake. I gotta keep going now. This is gonna take like fucking two hours to finish this one.
Can I like fix this shit? Wait wait wait. Before we go any further. I'm gonna like
recalibrate this thing. How do I do that? Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. All right. All
right. All right. Finally. I can see myself. There we go. All right. Whose turn is it?
Oh it's just me and me. Pretend like your treasure hunters. Pull on the rope to lift the treasure
from the deep. Whoever does it fastest wins. Action. No it's mine. No it's mine. No it's mine.
You didn't get the treasure. Time to walk the plank. I don't know how this is gonna play.
This is why I gotta do one or two. Player three get yourself to the set. Oh don't look at my
midriff. Watch the cups carefully. Oh by the way I'm wearing a fucking wire. If anybody says
anything fucking illegally you're caught. What? What is it? We're letting pee? Action. Round and
round they go. Okay. Which cup? Whatever. Round and round. I didn't even pay attention.
There's a 30% chance that I get this right. Got it. You found it. There's no pulling the
wool over your eyes. My modeling career is really gonna take off after this. I'm doing different
costume changes. I didn't pay attention but I know which one it is. I didn't even look. I know which
one it is. It's the one right in the middle. I know it's that one. You need to shape up buddy.
Okay this is around my ankles right now and I really thought my pants were done.
My pants may as well be down. Player four you need it on set. I had like a split second like
holy shit don't even tell me my fucking pants are down. Run on the spot to power the light bulbs.
Guys I ain't doing this again. Action. I got a broke ass arm. I got it by a fucking bus.
Who's the fat naked guy? They should use you to power the country. I'm just a chicken. Yeah
I'm a fucking turkey. Player two. Come on. Finish this. I need to take a drink break. It's time for
your starring moment. Follow my instruction. My starring moment? Act your heart out.
Slap your fist and look mean. Action. Keep rolling baby. Hey stay there. Walk on the spot. Action.
Show me what you got. They loved you baby. Player one. This better be a good movie.
Now it's your time to shine. There's no scoring. Just follow my instructions and act like a star.
I'm not doing that. Whatever that is I'm not doing it. And struggle like you're tied up.
Action. Don't stop now. Hey here comes another surprise. Present. Action.
Oh. Keep your arms by your side and snore. And action. Keep rolling baby.
What a pro. The one in the middle is Toddler that shit his pants. Player three. It's your time to
shine. There's no scoring. Just follow my instructions and act like a star. Too late.
Try to raise one of your eyebrows. Step closer and crouch down if you need to.
Action. Keep it up. I can't do that. And another. Give me your most shocked expression.
Action. Come on. Pretty good. Brought the house down. Beautiful.
I'm not going to do that. I'm not going to do like the YouTube thumbnail thing. Maybe I will. I will
for the next one. Whatever it is I don't care. I'm just doing a YouTube thumbnail. On set now please.
All right I'll do the YouTube thumbnail please. You ready?
Scoop mud onto your opponent. Mud fight. Splash your opponent with mud till you can't see them
anymore. Wait I have to splash myself in the face with mud. I thought this was all over me but no
that's just I'm just half a person. You did it. He's as happy as a pig in. Shit. Say it. I was
supposed to go. You didn't even see it. Player two. On the set please. This trailer is going to be
dog shit. It's marathon time. I don't know. Run the distance as fast as you can but beware of
overheating. Pace yourself and grab the bottles to cool off. Grab the bottles. Action. Son. This is
a marathon. A sprint. Pace yourself. Pace. Like you've just eaten a curry. For some race. You
thought of going pro. God damn it. Player one. Get your butt on the set. Shit's here forever man.
Can never get rid of these. Shake the maracas to make the monkey dance. The more you shake the more
you score. Oh by the way uh I bought like 38 Kinect games. Action. Okay but where's the diaper?
Diaper check. He's just warming up. I'm gonna go sideways. No how do I do this without doing
that? I don't know. I'm gonna punch him. He was born to be a dancer.
Shaking all over. Great score. This movie's gonna be good. Wait that was the wrong person.
That was the wrong person. That was the wrong person. Player four. I need you on set please.
Yeah let me put this up. I am putting the fat suit on again. This is the only one you're gonna get
unless I do the fat suit the whole time. It's your time to shine. All right this is acting.
Follow my instructions and act like a star. Like we're snuggie. Run on the spot as fast as you can.
And action. Come on show me what you got. I have to hold up my like loose skin. Let's try. Oh that's
disgusting. This is gross and I'm not even trying to make it gross. Action. That's it.
You loved ya baby. Player one get yourself to the set. Not the top rope. It's time for
your starring moment. Follow my instruction and act your heart out. And yeah that's right. Open
your mouth and say ah. Me? I did it. Step towards the camera. I lost over 145 pounds.
Look at me here. Oh I had to. Hear that applause. What a moment. Player two I need you on set please.
I don't care. I'm not putting it on. All I had to do was. It's time to put you in the spotlight.
Just follow my instructions and show me your acting talent. Okay. Wobble like you're in an earthquake.
You got it. Action. Keep it going. And another. That's getting the academy award.
I just hurt my neck. Keep your arms by your side and struggle like you're tied up. And action.
That's it. Keep it going. Surprised. Action. A feeling. Put more feeling into it.
Burger. Wait I didn't do the like. Fuck I keep trying to show you what I'm talking about.
And it keeps cutting me off. Actually I'm kind of glad it is because I don't want to do that face.
Here we go. Me. Me. And me. Today is a day you'll never forget. Why am I so bad? Somewhere.
Somewhere. At some point in time. In a secret location.
The boundaries of science are being stretched beyond breaking point.
Through the miracle of science you could find yourself becoming more. Much more.
What's wrong with me? Loads more. And then some. So when you're in a pickle there's only one person
you can count on. You and you and you. Did the software screw up and shape me?
Oh Jesus. I need to see that again. Let's replay. I just need to know. It did like the mapping
software. I don't know. Everybody just has the fadsuit on. I couldn't have made that any better.
We cannot afford to make another four player one that took a half an hour. I know right?
Me. Me. And me. Today is a day you'll never forget. Somewhere. At some point in time.
In a secret location. The boundaries of science are being stretched beyond breaking point.
Through the miracle of science you could find yourself becoming more. That's pressing the button.
Much more. Loads more. And then some. So when you're in a pickle there's only one person you
can count on. You and you and you. My god. No I don't want to replay that. I guess I'll save it.
Me. All right let's do some trivia. What mythical creature was central to the film The Secret of
Rowan Einish? Loch Ness Monster. I have no idea. Pretty woman Julie Roberts whoops it up at the
Polar Grounds and a nod to which of the love story. Um I don't know. What kingdom does Shrek's
nemesis Lord Focklod rule? Uh the legendary swamp. I don't know. I don't know any of these.
In superhero movie Tracy Morgan spooks what superhero team leader? I never saw it. What
famed actress was a regular on Knott's Landing? No idea. This real life model for Q shares the
same last name as his fictional counterpart. I don't know. The movie titled Dazed and Confused
comes from a song by what rock band? Um Led Zeppelin. I haven't seen very many movies.
What 1992 movie is a prequel to a series created by David Lynch? Um I don't know. In Say Anything
what song is playing on the boombox Lloyd is holding in Diane's driveway? I don't know any
of these. What movie was set on the last day of school in May 1976? Grease?
Grease is like in the 40s. Grease is seriously like 19 fucking like 52. Who wins the award?
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the You're in the Movies Awards and now the moment you've all
been waiting for. The nominees for best actor are. I'm gonna say uh. Nominee one.
It's gonna get the whole thing. Nominee two. Come on fill up the whole square.
Nominee three. Nominee four. But of course there can only be one winner and the You're in the
Movies Award for best actor goes to. The award? Please take to the podium to accept this prestigious
award. Perhaps you'd like to say a few words. It's me okay. Arm. What arm? Arm? What about it?
Uh thank you for the award. I appreciate it. There were some other great candidates up here
but I'm really happy to see that. Ah yes I'm waving to you in the top right. I'm really happy
to see that that I'm the candidate that you choose to represent you in this latest election.
I'm not doing for everything. I can't do for it. Scared witness. What's private money? Murder at
the mansion. A practical joker is mysteriously murdered in the slapstick whodunit. Let's check
our equipment is working correctly. Is the picture in focus? Yes it is. Is the lighting
okay in here? Check the light meter to be sure. Now let's position the camera. Make sure everyone
can fit themselves into the outline without appearing too small or too big. If you find that
anyone is too short or too tall to fit in tilt the camera up or down and try again. Welcome to
the cut out studio. This is where we separate your image from the background. Select start cut out
studio to continue. Great please move out of the picture while we scan the background. Please hold
on. Cut out complete. Now get back in front of the camera. Try playing around with the cut out style
to see the best results. Can you see yourself clearly in front of the background movie?
How many actors are there? Choose the correct number. Not four. Two. Not four. I can't do four
of them. It took like 40 minutes. Step into one of the four outlines for your picture. This will
decide which role you play in the movie. Murder suspect. Murder suspect. But I think I want
prankster though. Don't you guys think prankster? Hold on. Step into one of the four outlines for
your picture. This will decide which role you play in the movie. What a shitty superhero mask.
Player one you need it on set. I want I'm gonna do the hat and the white scarf. I've done this like
already. Let's do this one again. It's all the fun of the fair. Throw the ball in the hole three times
to win a prize. Action! Come on. Think the ball into the hole. Hey let's do this one again. Hey
hey let's do this one again. Hey hey hey they took that one. You can do better than that.
Only one more left. Oh that was close but no cigar. You can do better than that.
You didn't get enough. I did get enough. I got three. That's enough. That's enough. All right uh
I should have got a wig. I should have got a wig. I think Kim has some wigs. Player two
to the set. Although that I will sweat through that and I will ruin her wig. It'll be horrible.
It's time to act like a clown with a bungee run. Well that's easy. Run as far as you can before the
power of the bungee drags you back. And action! Get those arms moving to gain speed. That was
some bungee. You did it. She has like all kinds of wigs and stuff. Player one on the set please.
That's me. It's time to put you in the spotlight. There's no scoring. Just follow my instructions
and show me your acting talent. Slap your thigh and laugh. Action! Nearly there.
Yeah! Hey stay there. Imagine you're celebrating a big win. A big win? Action!
Keep rolling baby. Yeah! Hear that applause? What a moment. Oh I'm not supposed to be on camera.
Players one and two on set now please. Sure. Drill down as quick as you can.
It's digging time. See who can do it the quickest. Shake the jackhammer handles as hard as you can to
drill. Action! Keep it up. Don't stop now. Come on. It's hard to hold this here the whole time. You
didn't dig far enough. Look at all those zits. No there's not. That's like a mole or something.
That looks ridiculous. Player one get your butt on the set. No that's like lighting. And now
it's your time to shine. No those aren't zits. Just follow my instructions and act like a star.
Give me your most evil laugh. Action! Keep it up. They loved you baby. I'm not doing that on camera.
Player two come to the set please. I'm not doing that. And now it's your time to shine.
Just follow my instructions and act like a star. Give me a stern frown. And action! Come on. Come
on. Can you get it? You were amazing. What a pro. That looks like it's photoshopped on my head.
This game. This is gonna be fucked. Yeah. No it isn't. Players one and two on set now please.
They're all fucked. Let's all do the conga. Hit the drums as fast as you can to make your monkey
dance faster. You got one of some funny about this uh this Xbox live vision camera. This is one of
the only games that actually uses it. I'll give you your hand too. I'll help you. Don't worry.
Dance monkey dance. Look at that monkey go. Yeah but they made this thing just for this stupid
toy and I'm gonna take it apart and see what's in it. Player one come to the set please.
I want to know what's in there. It's time to put you in the spotlight. There's no scoring. Just
follow my instructions and show me your acting talent. No. Laugh like a hyena. What about the
jester hat? Okay. Okay let's go again. Open your arms wide and welcome. Action. That's it. Keep it
going. Let's do another. Rest your head on the table. Action.
Show me what you got. Hear that applause. What a moment. Did I get it? Did I line it up? What a
gamer. I lined it up right? Her picture is empty. Player one you need it on set.
Dance to the music. Uh okay. Dance to the music and match each pose. When the music stops
get into the outline and remember hold still while you're posing. Pose. Hold still pose. And action.
Hold that pose. Let's dance. Move a muscle. Let's dance. Let the music play. Freeze. Let's dance.
You were born to be a dancer. You won't take no for an answer. That's how I dance. Player two
on set. Oh that's me I'm playing too. Pretend you're in a dojo preparing for a big fight.
Avoid the arms of the training dummy and hit the targets to score. I could actually put it on for
this. Action. Revenge. Dump. Dump. Dummy. What a crushing blow. Ouch that's smarts. Bullseye.
Take that dummy head. That showed the dummy. You fight good. That's gonna hurt. I clearly did not
get it by any of those. Right on target. Ash. I hit by a dummy. That was awful. I couldn't decide who
was more wooden. You were the dummy. Shut up. I gotta do like a big Dracula cape next time. That's
a wrap. Here we go. Let's go to the movies. Here we go. That was way too much. All right I'm gonna
drink this one slow. Dial M for a menu. Today's meal is murder. There's plenty to eat
when murder's on the menu. Murder at the mansion. Everyone has a motive.
It's coming. Everyone has a secret. Everyone is a suspect. Am I gonna kill this guy?
Who has the last laugh when a joke goes too far?
But who is to blame? Who is guilty of murder at the mansion?
So bad. Dude the freeze frame. Because I don't know. I must have done it wrong.
Let's see it one more time. That was when I like smashed my head on the table. That's so fucking
stupid. At least it didn't make me fucking 12 sizes bigger than I am. I think I'm just
doing fat suit next time. All right cheese. Dial M for a menu. Today's meal is murder.
There's plenty to eat when murder's on the menu. Murder at the mansion. Everyone has a motive.
Everyone has a secret. Everyone is a suspect. What was the dancing? Who has the last laugh
when a joke goes too far? But who is to blame? Who is guilty of murder at the mansion? It's the
guy in the red shirt. He's attacked and he's hurt everybody. It was me. I did it all. What do you
mean who did it? I was on camera four times hurting people. All right here comes the trivia.
In Pan's Labyrinth what type of preacher does the title refer to?
Pan? Russell Crowe is a man of many talents. For what rock band does he sing, lead, play guitar,
and write lyrics? In Bubba Hotep and Elderly Elvis in what person battles a monster terrorizing the
nursing home where they live? I should know this. I've seen this movie. Right. Damn it. I've seen
this movie. Todd and Copper were the two main characters in one animated film. Um I don't...
Fox in the Hump? Mark Ruffalo actor in Collateral also starred in what romantic comedy? Now you see
me? According to Love Story, love means never having to say I love you. This British hunk has
played Bruce Wayne Van Helsing. Frank Potente exploded onto the screen in this cult hit.
You've got veils about two people who meet on what online service? America Online.
Why did the lead characters go to the island of Kong? Research. The film production company
Egg Pictures was created by which flight plan actress? JetBlue? Delta. Ah shit. Right.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Your England Movies Awards.
Here are the nominees for best actor in a party game where you drink wine.
Before you, three of your co-workers drink a bottle of wine and you thought it was a good idea
to put this on TV. That's a zit. No they're not. I don't look like that.
I swear to god I don't look like that. I swear to god that's not what my face looks like.
Of course, there can only be one winner and the Your in the Movies Award for best actor goes to
please take to the podium to accept this prestigious award. Perhaps you'd like to say a few words.
Where are these zits? Oh fuck I'm still on camera. All right. Oh thank you thank you thank you thank
you. Wait I gotta get a good one. Okay hold on. Can I? Thank you. Bookers just shot out of my
nose and nothing I can do about it. Thank god it's only 140 feet. Thank you everybody for the
opportunity to holy shit. Nothing I can do about that. It was 140 feet you didn't even see it.
Holy fuck. I'm so glad this camera sucked.
Thank you. Okay. Ah whatever. What are they doing over there? That was it happened so fast
that you may not have been able to see it. I can see it on no I don't even know where it is.
It was disgusting. With even like a 360p camera that is like that is career ruining.
That is career ruining. Thank god it's a shitty fucking cell phone camera.
All right what we got? Let's check our equipment is working correctly. Is the picture in focus?
We have to do the romance one. Is the lighting okay in here? Check the light meter to be sure.
Now let's position the camera. Make sure everyone can fit themselves into the outline without
appearing too small or too big. If you find that anyone is too short or too tall to fit in,
tilt the camera up or down. Welcome to the cut out studio. Great please move out of the picture
while we scan the background. Please hold on. Cut out complete. Now get back in front of the
camera. Try playing around with the cut out style to see the best results. Can you see yourself
clearly in front of the background movie? How many actors are there? Choose the correct number.
Step into one of the four outlines for your picture. This will decide which role you play
in the movie. If the picture is okay, press A to continue. Otherwise, retake.
That's this. I said to drink this one slow right? Play one get yourself to the set.
I'm surprised I've been able to do it for this long and not fucking pass out.
Oh. Beat the drums to make the boat go faster. It's a tropical storm.
Run away. Beat the drums as fast as you can to make your boat move faster.
Action. Keep going. Left, right, left, right. You pushed it to the limit. Great score.
7,500 points being no points. All right here we go. What's next two or four or three or one?
Players two and three. On set now please. Two and three? No this is the mud one.
This doesn't matter. Mud fight. Splash your opponent with mud till you can't see them anymore.
Action. Keep splashing. You did it. He's as happy as a pig.
Who's Jerma's sexy friend? Player four to the set. Oh it's the fat guy. Everybody laugh out loud at
the fat guy. Oh sorry hold on let me get my fat fucking suit on. It's time to act like a clown
with a bungee run. Now run as far as you can before the power of the bungee drags you back.
Action. Get those arms moving to gain speed. That was some bungee. You did it. Naked. Naked. Naked.
Player one I need you on set please. And now it's your time to shine. There's no scoring.
Just follow my instructions and act like a star. Look as embarrassed as you can. Action.
Don't stop now. Stay on set. Cry your eyes out. I can do this. I'm really gonna cry. And action.
That's it. You were amazing. What a pro. The one on the right is a flash at me right in the face.
Get your butt on the set. Can you stand together there? Turn your flash off in a movie theater.
Yes I'll take a few photos. It's time to put you in the spotlight. Who is this player? Just follow
my instructions and show me your acting talent. Who is this? Who is this? What character is this?
Imagine you're celebrating a big win. Action. Yeah. Keep it up. Right here comes another.
Shake your head and wag your finger. Action. Keep it going. That was fantastic. You were a star.
Players three and four on set now please. I'm just gonna put the bat suit on. I don't care.
See who can get the hula hoop moving fastest. The faster it goes the more you score.
And action.
Come on work with me here. Move those hips people.
Move those hips people.
Player one to the set. Dance to the music. All right come on. I'm gonna do like a
burn baby burn. It's time to stretch your funky stuff. Dance to the music and match the position
of the hands to pose. Like that one? The Fortnite one? What's it it goes like this? Action. It goes
like this. What's the Fortnite one? I don't know how to do it. Can you feel it? Let the music take over.
Work that booty. Work that booty. Funky. That was some performance. Great with a capital
ending. You can't dance on camera unless you know what you're doing.
Because that ends up in a fucking folder. Play it too. Get yourself to the set.
The costumes are all dirty. Pick the outfit that matches the hat and give them a good scrub.
This one sucks. Action. That's good. Now give it a good wash. This. Great. That one. Don't forget to
wash it. You're forever making bubbles. Try the costume on.
All right pirate hat. I wonder if it's gonna be that one. That's good. Now give it a good wash.
Great. Don't forget to wash it. Try it on for size. Funky. Finally. That's good. Now give it a good
wash. You did real good. The costume crisis is over. Two has real boring stuff so far. How's
this romance? Player three you need it on set. What is romantic about this? Like doing the washing
clothes. It's time for your starring moment. Follow my instruction and act your heart out.
I want to see your angriest face. Step closer and crouch down if you need to.
Action. That's it. Keep it going. You brought the house down. Beautiful. I can't believe I have to
sell the farm. I don't want to sell the farm. We have to do something. I don't want to sell it.
It's time for your starring moment. There's no scoring. Follow my instruction and act your
heart out. Three, four, two, one. Which one? Point at the camera and laugh. And action.
More feeling. Put more feeling into it. Stay on set. Dance a jig. What the fuck am I doing?
Action. Come on. Come on. Great. Stay there. Imagine you're celebrating a big win. Action.
Keep it up. Keep it up. You were amazing. What a pro. I hope these don't automatically get
posted online. It was one. Fuck. Player two. On the set, please. This is what I can't do.
Oh, no. I lost my wire. It's supposed to be in my underwear. It's supposed to go like up.
Not my underwear, but it's supposed to go through me. Now, you must have seen this before.
Watch the cups carefully. Then point at the cup that you think contains the P. Action.
Round and round they go. Okay. Which cup? That one. You found it. There's no pulling the
wool over your eyes. Round and round they go. Okay. Which cup? You found it. There's no pulling the
wool over your eyes. Round and round they go. Okay. Which cup? You got all three. There are
no flies on you. Oh, it's a green Cheeto. Player three. Get your butt on the set. What a romance.
Oh, shut the valve. I can't wait to see how romantic this is. Start the water from rising.
Shut the valve as if your life depended on it. It's backwards. Action. Turn the wheel.
Faster. Faster. Hey, hi there. You stopped the water. It didn't even mess up your hair.
Players one and four. On set now, please. One and four. Well, it's gonna have to be me like this.
Oh, bro. Pretend like your treasure hunters. Pull on the rope to lift the treasure from the deep.
Whoever does it fastest wins. And action. Booty. It sure was an annoying look.
I'm starting to pull up this hot, sweaty fucking lard thing. Player two, I need you on set, please.
It's time to put you in the spotlight. There's no scoring. Just follow my instructions and show
me your acting talent. Act grumpy and let out a big, long sigh. Action. Keep it up. Let's do
another. Pretend to push something out of the way. And action. That's it. Hear that applause?
What a moment. Player one on the set, please. I'm not a psycho. I just pretend to be one on TV.
It's time to put you in the spotlight. Just follow my instructions and show me your acting
talent. Give the frog a loving stare. The frog? Action. Come on. Show me what you got.
What the hell? Good. And another. Point straight ahead of you as if you've just seen something
shocking. Action. The heck happened over there? Holy shit. They loved ya, baby.
I'm giant right now. Stop looking at the camera.
The camera. The number one rule of all of acting. Player three, come to the set, please.
Now clear your mind. Focus your energies. Chop the blocks until they break. Where's the hat?
Where's the hat? Where's the hat? Where's the hat? Where's the hat? Where's the hat? Where's the hat?
Action. Cracked it. Actor smash. Cracked. You've broken. Corn holy. Bye bye rock. You smashed it.
Another rock bites the dust. Smash that stone. Actor smash.
You broke the rock. Boom. You cracked it. Bye bye rock.
Broke it. That was awesome. Ever thought of making statues for a living?
Players one and two. On set now, please. It's just me. I don't care. Am I drinking?
It's marathon time. Run the distance as fast as you can.
I'm not drinking fucking vomit. Action.
Slow down or you'll burn out. I know you got what it takes.
I need to go to the sprint. This is a marathon, not a sprint. Pace yourself.
We have a blowout, ladies and gentlemen. That was some race. You thought of going pro?
This does look like you. It really does. You're right. It looks like somebody pooped in there.
Player four. On the set, please. That's disgusting.
I'm going to get ice and get home. Play who? Four?
Dance to the music and match each pose. When the music stops, get into the outline and remember,
hold still while you're posing. And action. Move a muscle.
Let's dance. Freeze. Let's dance. Hold that pose. Let's dance.
Stop dancing. You were born to be a dancer. You won't take no for an answer.
This stream is fucking vomit right now. Don't look at my stomach. Player three. To the set.
And now it's your time to shine. Just follow my instructions and act like a star. Pose like a
hero. Action. Nearly there. You brought the house down. Beautiful. Player one. I need you on set,
please. Real heroic. Fucking costume changes. And now it's your time to shine. There's no scoring.
Just follow my instructions and act like a star. Blow me a big kiss. Oh, I don't want to because
people are going to keep this from me. Action. Keep rolling, baby. And another. Look up to the sky
as if you've just seen a flying pig. Action. Don't stop now. They loved you, baby. That's a wrap,
folks. Here we go. After this one, I'm going to get ice. Sir Arthur Conan Doyle,
which man investigated a photo of fairies in film fairies. True story vomit. What is Biff?
Looking for love is a tricky business. Having a best friend can make it harder. A little romance.
Excitement and security is what we're all looking for.
It's fucking huge. It doesn't work out. We try again.
And again. But sometimes the right one for you is closer than you think.
Watch close to your heart because love is never far away.
When he opens the door and he's naked, he's just naked. I need to see it again.
I'm going to be quiet for this one. I'm going to try. The whole dancing thing still makes no
sense to me. That's like a full two minutes of acting. All right.
Okay.
Looking for love is a tricky business. Having a best friend can make it harder. A little romance.
Excitement and security is what we're all looking for.
And if it doesn't work out, try again and again. But sometimes the right one for you
is closer than you think. Watch close to your heart because love is never far away.
Oh my god. I kind of have to. That was fucking ridiculous.
He's still at large. Why the hell keep getting arrested? The bar is closing on him.
Oh my goodness. I got to go get ice, man. I got to fucking take a break after this one.
That was fucking so stupid. What website was that? And the fact that there's a scene
with just two fat Fatsuit people at a club or something. What?
It doesn't make any sense. Did I fuck something up? I think I screwed something up.
It was the same person. I'm just going to call it love story. God damn, that was fucking fun.
At the very end, with pushing the cake, there's no context to any of this shit.
All right. I'll be right back while this saves. I'm going to grab some ice.
I'm going to grab some water and I'll be right back.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the You're in the Movies Awards.
And now the moment you've all been waiting for. The nominees for best actor are.
See, I had to blow my nose after that.
Nominee one.
Oh shit. Who's best actor?
Nominee three.
Nominee four.
But of course, there can only be one winner.
And the You're in the Movies Award for best actor goes to.
Please take to the podium to accept this prestigious award.
Perhaps you'd like to say a few words.
Really fucking excited and happy about the last production.
So much that I decided, yeah, I decided to do my favorite drink.
Cranberry juice, vodka, and vomit.
The Bay Breeze. Look it up. Fuck the Academy.
Drunk yet? No.
Scared witness.
Oh, we drop frames.
All right, let's get back to it.
That's really awesome.
All right, I'm going to turn it down so we can get back to normal.
Okay, scared witness.
Private one.
Let's check our equipment.
I'm going to move the shit back to where it was.
Oh my God, why is the fucking grease grate fell on him?
Okay, is it in focus?
I don't know.
Lighting is okay.
All right, I'm going for it.
I'm going for four again.
Now get back in front of the camera.
Try playing around with the cutout style to see the best results.
Can you see yourself clearly in front of the background movie?
This one looks a little worse.
Recalibrate it.
That's all right. That's enough.
Two always seems to work.
How many actors are there?
There are four actors. I'm doing it again.
What other thing can I fucking put in here?
Which role you play in the movie?
Did I get it?
If the picture is okay, press A to continue.
Otherwise, retake.
It's like that you're on a Disney ride and no.
Step into one of the four outlines for your picture.
I have to be my team.
This will decide which role you play in the movie.
Just do it. Do it.
If the picture is okay, press A to continue.
Wasted enough damn time.
Player one, come to the set please.
Okay, I need to get ready to get into this stuff.
So I get this the bat suit.
I need to like have a costume.
All right.
Oh, this is all fucked up.
It's not manned.
Drive your scooter through town.
Dodge the obstacles but hit the ramps to score.
Okay, I got my cap suit. Ready?
You got a license for that thing.
This.
I can paint work.
You said we have a plane.
It's stunt man.
They're going to use a clip of this for five seconds.
Have you got a license for that thing?
Just go.
They're going to use a second of this.
They're going to use a second of this footage.
Why? I don't even want to do it.
I'm standing up on it.
Can I do one knee?
Hurry up. I'm trying.
I'm trying to get out there as fast as I can.
Player two to the set.
All right. I finally have this on the right way.
The bat suit's been on backwards the whole time.
Okay, wise guy.
You think you're tough?
Walk the mean streets of the city and whack those gangsters.
But mind you don't hit the broads.
Whack the gangsters.
And action.
What did she ever do to you, bully?
Don't hit that dames.
You whacked him.
But mind you don't hit the dames.
Oops. I don't knock the green screen over.
Go. That's bad for business.
You took him down.
You busted my boards here.
You whacked him.
But mind you don't hit the dames.
You sure know how to treat a lady.
I did it.
I gotta recalibrate because I punched the box man.
Players three and four.
On set now, please.
Wait.
Oh god damn it.
Don't knock it over.
Better?
Better.
A little, a little bit better.
Yeah, that's fine.
All right, continue.
This is the mug one again.
Three and four.
Just put the f**king hat on.
Splash your opponent with mud till you can't see them anymore.
Action.
You did it.
He's as happy as a pig in...
Player one, you need it on set.
And now it's your time to shine.
And act like a star.
Try to raise one of your eyes.
I can't.
I'm just gonna scream.
Step closer to the camera.
Feeling, feeling into it.
Stare at the wasp.
Step closer and crouch down if you need to.
And action.
Keep rolling baby.
My eyes are crossing.
Ooh.
We're old man.
Player two, come to the set please.
Player two, f**king New York.
It's time to put you in the spotlight.
There's no scoring.
Just follow my instructions and show me your acting talent.
Cry your eyes out.
Action.
That's it.
Keep it going.
Stay on set.
Stand like you're the king of the world.
Action.
Nearly there.
That was like a ooh.
It's kind of hard for me to get up out of bed.
That's not like I'm powerful.
That's the my I gotta do that otherwise I'll fall.
Forward didn't do so hot.
On the set please.
You got it.
Freestyle dance.
I don't want to I'm gonna do something else.
Burn baby burn.
It's time to stretch your funky stuff.
Dance to the music and match the position of the hands to pose.
And action.
That was me falling down by the way if you're curious.
Remember I've got this fast f**k underneath me.
You understand?
Look this fat f**king thing is underneath me.
I'm gonna fall.
I want to jump so you can see what's here.
You need it on set.
Why does it cut me off every time?
I ripped it.
Uh oh not good.
How it's like backwards.
I'm rolling it up.
I've had three times and measured those muscles.
Action.
And attempt left.
It's walloping time.
Who sure pack a punch.
Players one and two on set now please.
See who can get the hula hoop moving faster.
The faster it goes the more you score.
And action.
Those hips baby.
Work those hips.
You're in the groove now.
Oh he got through it.
Player three you need it on set.
Can I get somebody to do a compilation?
It's time for your starring moment.
Of every costume change just cut together faster.
Show me a big cheesy grin.
Action.
Come on.
You brought the house down beautiful.
Player four to the set.
I wish they would do one two three four.
It just dude can I get all my scenes done as play one?
It's time for your starring moment.
Follow my instruction and act your heart out.
Beg for mercy.
Action.
Keep it up.
Please.
Come on.
Here comes another.
Give me the coolest look you've got.
Keep it up.
Is it?
What a throw.
I'm not taking off the suit.
Keep it on.
Here we go.
The drums that are never used in any scenario.
Let's all do the conga.
Hit the drums as fast as you can to make your monkey dance faster.
And action.
That was an achievement.
I did that so fast.
Punch the targets.
I love punching this one.
It's time for some training.
Punch the targets until they disappear.
The more you beat, the more you score.
Remember, if you don't beat the target, you won't score any points.
Action.
Smash.
Look like a million dollars, baby.
He's on the ropes, all right.
Come on.
Smash, bang, wallop.
Jab, jab, jab.
We have a world champion.
Player three, get yourself to the set.
Let's see how strong you really are.
Hit the pad three times and make the bell ring.
The harder you whack it, the more you score.
I like this.
I don't want to rip it.
Action.
Take this with you.
Psycho.
Player two, you need it on set.
And now it's your time to shine.
There's no scoring.
Just follow my instructions and act like a star.
Yeah.
Show me a big cheesy grin.
And action.
Keep it going.
They love you, baby.
I did the same fucking face for the other one.
Player three, I need you on set.
Can you keep the player two on set for more than a second?
Why can't I just do all my scenes first?
It's time for your starring moment.
Smile in the camera, I guarantee it.
And act your heart out.
Do a big grin.
Give Frog a loving stare.
Action.
That's it.
Kiss the frog.
Kiss?
And action.
Come on.
Show me what you got.
Great.
Stay there.
Did I get it?
Like a hyena.
Action.
You think you're going to be in my town?
Ah.
Player four, get your butt on the set.
And baby bun, it's time to stretch your funky stuff.
Dance to the music and match the position of the hands to pose.
Jared Leto is just a hyper ultra slowed down SpongeBob.
It's just SpongeBob at like 0.2% speed.
Oh my god.
Nobody wants to be filmed doing this.
Dance to the music.
Shake your body down.
That was some performance.
Great with a capital groove in.
You chose this.
I didn't, I, my, come on.
We're almost done?
Oh, run the marathon.
Here, do you remember this one?
It's marathon time.
Run the distance as fast as you can.
But beware of overheating.
Pace yourself and grab the bottles to cool more.
Action, ladies and gentlemen.
Cool and refreshing.
Look at that steam.
Try slowing down to cool more.
I'm going to catch up to you motherfucker.
Oh shit.
I got to get him.
No.
That was some.
On the set, please.
I'm going to get my robe.
No, not the top rope.
Dodge the obstacles.
No, another fucking tricycle.
Drive your scooter through town.
Dodge the obstacles, but hit the ramps to score.
And action.
Turn.
Go.
Gas.
Come on.
Wee.
That's gotta.
You said we have lift off.
I'm the paint work.
Have you got a license for that thing?
I'll just walk it.
I'll walk it.
I'm sorry.
I'll just walk it.
I didn't mean to do that.
This is the worst one.
Next time, I think we'll use it.
See what you guys are writing over here.
Come to the set, please.
It's time to put you in the spotlight.
There's no scoring.
Just follow my instructions and show me your acting talent.
Kiss the frog.
Kiss my stomach.
Like a hyena.
Jesus.
You made it a play.
Get your butt on the set.
We just need a few retakes.
Retakes?
That wasn't good enough.
Act your heart out.
How far can you lean?
You don't want to like pop it?
Or what?
Pop it?
Keep it going.
You brought the house down.
Pretty good.
Beautiful.
Player two, I need you on set, please.
They do this to make it so the person has to sit on the couch for that long.
Follow my instructions and act like a star.
How far can you lean?
Pop it again.
Action.
Come on.
Fantastic.
You were a star.
That wasn't even a reshoot.
That was a new shoot.
What do you mean reshoot?
That's a wrap.
That's it?
Let's go to the movies.
Here we go.
Private Eye.
It was a quiet day for crime.
Then bad news walked in.
Everyone wants to play the field.
And no one wants to get caught.
Love can make us do terrible things.
Diabolical dancing.
Sensational scandal.
Most people want one of two things.
Love or money.
Some want both.
Before you act on your suspicions,
get yourself some proof.
Get yourself a private eye.
That was terrible.
I couldn't even follow half of that.
Like the kissing under the gut.
Let's might as well do it twice.
I don't understand the line-up part.
It was just all one person.
Private Eye.
It was a quiet day for crime.
Then bad news walked in.
Everyone wants to play the field.
And no one wants to get caught.
Love can make us do terrible things.
Diabolical dancing.
Sensational scandal.
Most people want one of two things.
Love or money.
Some want both.
Before you act on your suspicions,
get yourself some proof.
Get yourself a private eye.
The double pop is the best part of that.
Oh man, that was probably the worst one so far.
Get yourself some proof.
That like lifted up the stomach and walking forward.
Oh man, just name it trash.
Mark Wahlberg received critical fame for his role as Dirk Diggler in this movie.
Interesting.
What or who inspired the character of Chewbacca?
George Lucas' dog.
Got it.
Ghostbuster Peter Benkman claimed to have what college credentials?
Psychology.
Psychologist.
Thank you.
In what city does the multi-culture Thanksgiving comedy What's Cookin' take place?
I don't know.
Los Angeles.
Never Say Never Again with Sean Connery was a remake of what?
1965 James Bond flick that also starred Connery.
Say it twice.
I don't know.
Air Bud.
What does the captain say is the problem in the prison drama Cool Hand Luke?
Which Shakespearean play and movie features fairy
royalty in the mischievous satyr Puck?
The Tempest.
I literally just pulled a random Shakespeare play out of my mind.
What film do Owen Wilson and Jennifer Lopez battle animals in the jungle?
Jumanji.
I don't know.
Mission Impossible.
Top Gun.
What Disney character portrayed Jacob Marley in Vicky's Christmas Carol?
Goofy.
I got that one.
What creature did Andy Zah was going to do it?
I have some knowledge somewhere up there.
I've got a little bit of knowledge.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the You're in the Movies Awards.
And now the moment you've all been waiting for.
The nominees for best actor are.
I wish I could take individual pictures.
Nominee one.
Nominee two.
Nominee three.
Nominee four.
One day it'll make a puzzle.
But of course, there can only be one winner.
And the You're in the Movies Award for best actor goes to.
Shoulder.
Please take to the podium to accept this prestigious award.
Some actors do it for the money.
Some actors do it for the fame.
I do it because I love it.
I care so much about it.
And I'm going to continue to do this.
Nobody's going to cheer for this.
Why are you not cheering?
Nobody cheers.
I'm all washed up.
There's blood in there.
All right.
Oh, what do we get?
I think we need, I mean, I really, really want like ninja school.
Ghost team.
Look at this.
This steal the day.
There's so many.
I'm doing one actor.
I want to unlock some shit.
Is the picture in focus?
Yeah, I don't have the script.
Look, look, look now.
Look now.
Hold on.
The music is too loud.
I know.
I agree.
LBRB LBRBY.
Don't lie to me.
Okay.
LBRB LBRBY.
That was a lie.
That was just a straight up lie.
All right.
Prehistoric power.
Four adventures go in search of a forgotten world and get more than they bargained for.
I'm going to do this one quick.
Just one actor.
Just me.
Is the lighting okay?
Now let's position the camera.
Just me.
Welcome to the cut out.
Great.
Please move out of the picture while we scan the background.
Please hold on.
Cut out complete.
Now get back in front of the camera.
Try playing around with the cut out style to see the best results.
Can you see yourself clearly in front of the background movie?
Yes.
How many actors are there?
Choose the correct number.
Option screen?
Options.
Well, let me just do this quick quick.
Explore, explore, expedition later.
Step into one of the four outlines for your picture.
This will decide which road you play in the movie.
Oh, that's gross.
It's small.
All right.
I'm just going to fuck up this whole production.
I don't care.
Let's see how much I can fuck this whole production up.
Run as fast as you can.
Reach the gate to escape the charging bull.
I'm just going straight up who gives a shit.
You know what I mean?
Action.
He sure got a mean look about him, don't he?
Yee-haw.
Stay back.
His arms moving to gain speed.
He sure got a mean look about him, don't he?
Oh, we dropped some fucking frames.
Great work, Slim.
You rule the rodeo.
I was going to have a drink in my hand the whole time.
I think that's a fun concept.
Player one, get yourself to the set.
The FPS is so good.
It's time for your starring moment.
Follow my instruction and act your heart out.
Stroke your chin like you're deep in thought.
And action.
Keep it up.
Let's try one more.
Point at the camera and laugh.
Action.
It was fantastic.
You were a star.
Now it's time to really fuck it all up.
Watch this shit.
Player one, to the set.
For your mind.
It's time to work your mind.
Memorize the symbol on the stone block.
Then point to the right scroll.
What am I doing?
And action.
Remember the symbol.
Look at those fucking sweaty pit stains.
You'll grasp at shadows.
Now concentrate.
Concentrate, young apprentice.
It's 110 degrees in Vegas.
Give me a break.
Wrong.
You need more training.
Got the right one.
Read the symbol well.
Clear your mind.
Use the power of your mind.
That was not good.
Place that in your mind.
Perfect.
You are a being of light.
I'm gonna laugh my ass off if this turns out to be a good movie.
What am I doing?
I'm trying to skip fast.
Player one, I need you on set, please.
I don't want to do that one, I want to stop.
All right, here we go.
It's time for your starring moment.
Follow my instruction and act your heart out.
I want you to sneeze.
All right, I can do this good.
Action.
That's it.
Keep it going.
Hear that?
What a moment.
It's right in your fucking eyes.
Player one, on the set, please.
Do my famous life is pain monologue.
Well, there's no audio.
What is this?
Imagine the biggest noise you can.
Play the instruments to make a racket.
The faster you go, the more you score.
Action.
Bang the congas.
Hit the tambourine.
Stroke the child.
There's a gong.
I did it twice.
Shake that maraca.
Crash that zimbo.
That was great.
You sure can make a racket.
Thank you.
Those are perfect teeth, though.
They really are.
They're nice.
All right, last one.
Player one, come to the set, please.
I can open up all the...
I'm going to try that.
Cup and the pea.
Oh, this thing again.
Now, you must have seen this before.
Watch the cups carefully.
Then point at the cup.
I've done this like 10 times.
You can't just take one of these
that I've already done like a hundred times.
Hmm, which one is it?
Which cup?
Which ones are going into?
Round and round they go.
Okay, which cup?
You took your eye off the cup.
Round and round they go.
Okay.
Which cup?
You found it.
There's no pulling the wool over your eyes.
Round and round they go.
Okay, which cup?
You've got your wits about you.
Boomers don't have fun.
Fucking boomers.
Always ruining our 2003 webcam video games.
That's a wrap.
All right, here we go.
Let's see how shitty this one is.
Which is me.
And then I'm going to unlock all of them.
It started with a meeting of great minds.
And a plan to travel to a lost world.
Journey to a land never beheld by man,
woman, nor child.
Discover sights and sounds no human has ever seen before.
Prehistoric paradise.
Marvel at the mammoth monstrosities.
Ground-breaking discoveries.
I just kicked it out of the room.
Terrifying monsters.
Older than your dreams.
Scarier than your nightmares.
A daring rescue mission.
Be prepared to witness the spectacle that is prehistoric paradise.
God damn it.
With the drink being eaten,
and then with the drink inside.
Oh, that was dog shit.
But let's do it again, why not?
I have to do it twice.
Drinking every photo.
What a joke.
I don't have any more juice left.
I can't even, speaking of drinks.
Why am I hands in the air for the meeting shot?
Because I sat there for like, with the drink.
It started with a meeting of great minds.
It actually goes, I can't.
And a plan to travel to a lost world.
Journey to a land never beheld by man, woman, nor child.
Discover sights and sounds no human has ever seen before.
Prehistoric paradise.
Marvel at the mammoth monstrosities.
Ground-breaking discoveries.
Enormous eggs.
Terrifying monsters.
Older than your dreams, scarier than your nightmares.
A daring rescue mission.
Be prepared to witness the spectacle that is prehistoric paradise.
I fucking love it.
Uh, no, I don't want to replay it.
Of course I want to save that movie.
We'll watch them all once through.
I will mute my mic.
So you don't hear me like.
At the end of this frame.
Dino.
Don't mute.
Oh, okay.
Well, just a half for, you know, for editing and stuff.
You need to direct his commentary.
What can I give you there?
Katie Holmes tries to reconnect with her estranged family
by hosting Thanksgiving in what film?
Uh, I don't know.
Oops.
Shrek's line, that'll do, donkey.
That'll do is inspired by what film?
Uh, Bape.
Yes, I knew it.
I told you.
What does Bill Murray do for a living in the film Scrooged?
Uh, he's an accountant.
What 1944 Judy Garland film features the song
Have Yourself a Merry Merry Christmas?
It's not The Wizard of Oz.
What actor surprises the Ann Darrow role?
I don't know.
Director Doug Liman helped popularize a Los Angeles subculture in this film.
Um, I was gonna say, I was gonna say like hippies.
Bryce, the dog, oh, this is what has started to, I'm like, um, I don't know.
In 2001, what song does the computer howl sing as it is being shut down?
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you.
Um, The Aristocrats.
The Aristocats.
Name the settlement where Luke and Ben first meet Han Solo.
Um, District Nine.
I don't know.
Sir Arthur Conan Doyle is which man of his part, uh, true story.
King Kong battles what animals on Skull Island?
Godzilla.
Well, I don't know shit, apparently.
Apparently, German just don't know shit.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Your in the Movies Awards.
And now, the ones you've all been waiting for.
I'll check the sheets, don't worry.
Nominees for best actor are...
Nominee one.
Nominee two.
I'd better win.
And now...
Nominee four.
Oh, wait a minute.
I don't know.
One of these are all me.
But of course, there can only be one of the Your in the Movies...
Those two.
...actor goes to...
Yay!
Please stand up to the podium and give yourself a prestigious award.
Perhaps you'd like to say a few words?
I got something to say.
Hey, all of you are so smart and so awesome.
You're all good.
Don't let go.
Okay, I'm gonna...
I need some more juice.
What are the cheats?
Ooh, more films.
You're in the movies, cheats.
Do you guys want me to just start cheating?
What do you think I am?
Some kind of fucking non-video gamer?
What do they do?
Unlock all trailers and directors mode.
Enter these commands simultaneously.
Option screen.
Unlock all features within the game.
So hit them...
Hold them all at the same time.
LBRB, LBRBY.
In the options menu?
This is the options screen.
LBRB, LBRBY.
Did it work?
LBRB, LBR...
How do I hit LBRB twice?
What, like...
Hold...
Hold them.
Why does it just not say LBRBY?
LBRB, LBRBY.
What?
Hold them twice.
That's bumper trigger...
That's LLT is trigger.
Trigger it, hold all of them.
What?
What does this do?
I can make my own movie...
Welcome to directing.
You can create your own movie.
Record footage, change shots and record your own audio?
I want a new script.
Uh, whoops-a-daisy.
Just found probably the fucking best.
How do I record audio though?
I don't have a way to record it on the Xbox.
Movie viewer, shots and audio.
Okay.
Viewing control.
Press down on the D-pad to move to shots section.
Arrange and edit your shots.
Use the left and right of the D-pad to select a shot.
Press Y to add a new shot.
Delete the shot or press X to record footage.
Keep an eye on the shot meter when adding shots.
It shows how close you are to the maximum movie size.
When it's almost full, you may need to delete shots before you can add more.
Press down on the D-pad and go to the audio channel.
Fuck.
I don't have a way to record audio.
Select a soundtrack and record audio.
Press A to record audio.
Shots section.
You're not ready to direct a movie.
What do you need when you finish?
Use the director to save your correction.
Set the script lets you make your movie by playing the game.
Set the movie lets you watch and upload it in the movie theater.
You need further help?
Okay.
Add a shot.
Oh no.
Oh god no.
This is too much to do.
Fuck.
What is this?
People on fire?
I gotta unlock the other films.
Yeah, that's right.
Uh, this is from the first one.
Is it ghosts?
I don't even see this stuff.
I need to, I want to do these ones.
I want to do the one where you're a ghost.
Okay, hold on.
No!
Do the movies first?
Yeah, I feel like that's a, hold on.
Record actors.
Action three, actor three, action one.
Let's go.
Be in the car.
Okay.
All right, that seems all right.
Review that.
Okay, that makes sense.
Looks good.
Done.
Is that in there?
Okay.
Uh, let's record this, uh, record this actor.
Should I?
I'm not gonna dance in the shower.
Okay.
Fuck, I'm just, actor one.
There we go.
I can control myself.
What the hell am I supposed to do here?
Is this YMCA?
Young man, don't you need to feel down?
I say young man.
Okay, what else you got?
Come on, give it to me.
Throw it at me, anything.
Um, I don't know, okay.
And then, record actors.
One of the ghosts.
Let's watch it.
Movie done.
Audio.
Choose soundtrack.
I have no way to record audio.
I don't have one of those.
I bought this thing secondhand.
All right, let's walk, let's go.
Am I controlling the wizard?
I'm just dead.
Okay, nice.
Well, this one sucks.
All right, I want to, I want to listen to the,
I want to unlock more movies.
Fuck that one.
That one was terrible.
Do I have any kind of USB headset?
I don't.
I don't have any USB headset at all.
All right, let me see.
Hold on, make it a movie.
Do I have access to the other ones?
I do.
It worked.
It actually did work.
No, it didn't.
Deity for a day.
Super funk.
Music things.
Vampire villas.
This one.
Let's check our equipment is working.
I need, I gotta get more.
I gotta get more ice.
I'll be right back.
Ice.
It's been three and a half hours.
It seems like one.
Yeah, it kind of is going by, isn't it?
Time flies when you have fun doing it.
I'm on my camera right now.
Okay.
You started three.
I had three and a half hours ago, yeah?
All right.
I'm just going to make a quick Bae Breeze.
We'll get started again.
It's cranberry juice.
You want to know if you're of the age of 30 and you can drink.
Shot of vodka.
Half cranberry juice.
Little more than half.
I fucked it up.
Half pineapple juice.
It's a Bae Breeze.
I ruined it.
How about vodka cranberries?
Yes, I know.
I know the hair just came down to the perfect spot.
Vodka cranberry, vodka pineapple are two timeless drinks.
This is a Bae Breeze.
You've never had a fucking Bae Breeze before?
Okay.
I don't know.
I just took a shower like three hours ago.
I don't know why it's in here.
Man, that got collected.
Okay.
Anyways, picture isn't focused.
Yes, it is.
Is the lighting okay in here?
Check the light meter to be sure.
Now, let's position the camera.
Make sure everyone can fit themselves into the outline.
He's drunk at five o'clock.
These are Bae Breezes.
They're not, like, I'm not drinking them.
They're straight vodka.
It's like a half a shot.
It's like I can drink like 10 of these and sing.
I could sing the entire alphabet.
Welcome to the Cutout Studio.
This is where we separate your image from the background.
Select Start Cutout Studio to continue.
You would sing.
I tell you, I'm not drunk at all.
I'll sing to prove it.
Like, okay, weirdo.
You know that thing that people do when they're shit-faced
at a bar at a karaoke night?
Hold on.
Now, get back in front of the camera.
Try playing around with the cutout style.
Breeze always works the best.
Can you see yourself clearly in front of the background movie?
Two seems to work out.
I don't like the haze from Four.
Your core gets everything.
I'll just bring it in.
Breeze, all right.
The problem is like the sun is starting to set.
It's a chip.
Welcome to the Cutout Studio.
This is where we separate your image from the background.
Select Start Cutout Studio to continue.
Do it again.
Please move out of the picture while we scan the background.
Please, hold on.
Cutout, now get back in front of the camera.
Try playing around with the cutout style to see the better.
It's better, all right.
Oh.
Choose the correct number.
Step into one of the four outlines for your picture.
This will decide which role you play in the movie.
To the set.
Hey, it's five o'clock Pacific.
That means it's like 10 o'clock where you are.
What time is it?
Howdy, Sheriff.
This is a holdup.
Dodge the junk and punch the desperadoes.
But these never show up anywhere.
These never show up anywhere.
The punches don't do anything.
Action.
That showed him, Sheriff.
Come back and see me sometime.
Oh, I'm supposed to grab that.
Ah, my arm.
My fucking broke my fucking wrist.
You want to try dodging?
What did she ever do to you, bully?
That was a close one.
This is our showdown.
Nope.
One for the county jail.
Don't hit the dames.
Fuck at it.
Players two and three.
Oh shit, I forgot about costumes.
Two and three?
These were all fucked up.
It doesn't matter.
It's a holdup thing.
Tend like your treasure hunters.
Pull on the rope to lift the treasure from the deep.
Whoever does it fastest wins.
Action.
Booty.
I gotta get in this.
Player four, get yourself to the set.
Not good.
This is a mess.
Play the instruments.
Imagine the biggest noise you can.
Play the instruments to make a racket.
The faster you go, the more you score.
Action.
Crash that cymbal.
There's a gong.
Shake that maraca.
Bang the congas.
Hit the tambourine.
Poke the child.
That was great.
You sure can make a racket.
Player one, I need you on set, please.
It's time for your starring moment.
There's no scoring.
Follow my instruction and act your heart out.
Vampires, right?
Imagine you're looking down a well.
Action.
More feeling into it.
Stay on set.
Surprise.
And action.
Keep rolling, baby.
That wasn't surprised.
That was just weird.
They loved you, baby.
Player two.
I'm doing a vampire.
It's time for your starring moment.
Follow my instruction and act your heart out.
Act like you're a nervous wreck.
Action.
Don't stop now.
Great.
Stay there.
Walk on the spot.
Action.
Keep it up.
And another.
Another one?
Go crazy with panic.
Action.
Come on.
Show me what you got.
That was just like...
I don't know what that was.
That was just like the...
Oh my god.
Player three.
You need it on set.
That was fucking terrible.
Ow!
My arm.
And now it's your time to shine.
That was like I've been into a fucking pizza that was too long.
Just follow my instructions and act like a star.
That was over acting for my friends.
Act like a ghost.
A ghost.
Action.
Keep it up.
Stay on set.
Lift your hands and scream.
Boo.
Action.
Poor feeling into it.
Hear that applause?
What a moment.
Players two and four.
On set now please.
I can't get out of character.
I'm stuck in this one.
Let's all do the conga.
Hit the drums as fast as you can to make your monkey dance faster.
I did this already.
I did this jump.
Action.
Ow.
On the set please.
That's great.
Knock on the door, dodge the junk.
Imagine you're waking up the sheriff.
Knock on the door, but be ready to dodge the junk.
And catch the gold.
Action.
I'm going to tuck these in.
Hold on.
I'm going to like Steve Urkel this shit for the next one.
Ouch.
Gotta move quicker next time.
Already?
Player three, get yourself to the set.
I should have done this for this character in the first one.
Now you must have seen this before.
Watch the cups carefully.
Then point at the cup that you think contains the pea.
Action.
Round and round they go.
Okay.
Which cup?
You found it.
There's no pulling the wool over your eyes.
This is a fucking great old man.
Round and round they go.
This is the guy at the poker table from like fucking three weekends ago.
Which cup?
Who took your eye off the cup?
I do like this though.
I do actually really like this one.
I got point eight seconds.
Round and round they go.
Okay.
Which cup?
You've got your wits about you.
I'm afraid to pull these all the way up
because I feel like you'll be able to see my like fucking thighs.
Player four, I need you on set please.
Let's do our own movie.
Look at all that stuff you got there.
Look at all those.
What's that?
Cranberry?
It's time for your starring moment.
There's no scoring.
Follow my instruction and act your heart out.
Look the floor.
Act like a zombie.
Action.
That's it.
Lift your hands and scream boo.
Action.
Keep it going.
Wait.
Pretend you're a vampire.
Action.
That's it.
Keep it going.
You brought the house down.
I was kind of trying to break out.
Like I'm in the thing's stomach and ripping the fuck up.
Why am I destroying this fat suit?
Do you think I'm ever going to use this again for any reason?
And now it's your time to shine.
Just follow my instructions and act like a star.
Oh inside of Humpty Dumpty was another Humpty Dumpty.
Who is this?
Put your hands together in glee.
Who is it?
And action.
Let's try one more.
Wake up and scream.
Action.
They loved you baby.
Has he gone insane?
How about a good time playing?
Play one, right?
This hurts.
It's a tornado.
Run as fast as you can to get away.
It's gaining on you.
Oh my god.
Quite a bad wind but this is...
This is fucking real.
This is fucking really happening.
Runner, you made it to the game.
Player four to the set.
And baby bun, it's time to stretch your funky stuff.
Dance to the music and match the position of the hands to pose.
Action.
Work that booty, work that booty.
What a soul.
Get into the groove.
You are the greatest dancer.
Let your feet do the talking.
Dance to the music.
That was some performance.
Stop this.
God damn it.
Greatest with a capital grooving.
Player one, get your butt on the set.
I know.
I said that earlier in the stream.
All this shit is fucking on camera, bro.
What am I gonna do?
Delate the vlog?
You are a treasure hunter.
Pull on the rope before the time runs out to get the treasure.
You better get it.
Action.
Hey.
You didn't get the treasure.
Time to walk the plank.
Maybe the crazy frog kid.
When he was like going like this and then he goes like this.
You have to like, come on.
You cut me off every time you do something funny.
Player three to the set.
I'm gonna do the crazy frog kid.
You'll see.
At least 10 of you will know what the fuck I'm talking about.
It's halfway through the crazy frog video.
The enemy is about to attack.
He does this.
Wave your arms to clear the smoke so you can see them coming.
It's like We're ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
and he goes...
Okay it's the best part of the whole video.
That video has like 600 million views because of that part
Player Four, on the set please.
And now it's your time to shine.
Just follow my instructions and act like a star.
Act like a ghost...
And, action.
Don't stop now
And another rub your belly. Oh I can do that
Action more feeling play walk on the spot action
Keep rolling, baby
You were amazing. What a pro
Player one get yourself to the set
It's time to put you in the spotlight just follow my instructions and show me your acting talent
Give me your most shocked expression
Keep it going hear that applause
Who's the best me me me or me
Bathrobe German's doing pretty well players one and two on set now, please
Fucking god
It's marathons time run the distance as fast as you can but beware of overheating
pace yourself and grab the bottles to cool more and
Action I know you can do it. It's like an oasis
Yeah, and an energy drink a bad race. You must have worked up a sweat
players three and four on set now, please I
Feel like a fucking two-year-old like I need like a four-year-old. I didn't go to the bathroom
It's digging time. See you who can do it the quickest shake the camera handles as hard as you can to drill
Action
Player one again
It's like the longest one so far and now it's your time to shine
There's no scoring just follow my instructions and act like a star
Creep on the spot like a burglar action. That's it
Keep it going
Don't go away
Run on the spot and act scared
action
Thing keep it up. Love ya, baby
Play it to get yourself to the set. I had to throw a scooby-doo in there. Sorry
Screw screw you and now it's your time to shine. There's no scoring. Just follow my instructions and act like a star
Give me your most shocked expression
and
action
Come on. Show me what you got right now. Try this
Look really really worried
Step closer to the camera
Action. Hey, get up. Keep it up. You brought the house down
Beautiful. That's a big goal. Let's go to the movies
Stand six inches tall
Orlando Bloom it was supposed to be the trip of a lifetime
It turned into a holiday from hell
Gaze and horror
upon the bizarre creatures of the night
This is the vacation to end all vacations
You won't be able to leave
Anyone hear you scream?
There's loads of excitement, but be sure not to lose your head
Have your friends for dinner
literally
So what's going on there?
Sucked out of you. It's time for a vampiric vacation
What was the crying
70 on Rotten Tomatoes more like 32. I was supposed to be shocked at eating my friend
I seem very happy about it. It was supposed to be
the trip of a lifetime
It turned into a holiday from hell
Gaze and horror
upon the bizarre creatures of the night
That doesn't even look like me
The guy that writes not me that somebody else says the vacation to end or vacations
You won't be able to leave
Will anyone hear you scream?
There's loads of excitement
But be sure not to lose your head
Have your friends for dinner
literally
So if you feel the life being sucked out of you
It's time for a vampiric vacation
All right
Let's do another one
I'm gonna do I'm gonna do a few more. I'm getting like fucking tired
Say vampire
What I mean avatar? What's wrong with the avatar? No, we're not done yet
I'm gonna do at least a couple more put Cheeto in one
Alright, I'll try it. Oh shit. Okay, I gotta get answer these questions
How did Han Solo acquire the Millennium Falcon he stole it
Jamie Foxx Michael Mann and Jada Pinkett Smith
Work together on what film?
What are the four friends sharing the movie Dreamcatcher?
They're all they're all aliens. Oh and Luke Wilson portrayed this famous duo and around the world in 80 days
Lewis and Clark, what are the two young lovers attend school in the tragic love story? That is a
Daniel Daniel Radcliffe Daniel Craig. I'm kidding
Which actor is hidden behind the hideously scarred face of the twisted mason verger?
I wonder how many guys would get some of these in the movie of the same name. What is Solaris?
Some what dinosaur what city did the dinosaurs attack in the lost world? I have no idea
New York no in Dirty Dancing Johnny Castle says nobody puts baby
in the corner
Yeah, Jamie Lee Curtis and her mother Janet Lay appeared in how many films together six?
Would have been great if I got that one
Batman begins scream right at David at Goyer has scripted the adventures of what other comic book hero?
Which early 007 spoof featured David Niven as the aging?
Why are you leaving us hanging like that? Who the fuck is ladies and gentlemen?
Movies awards and now the moment you've all been waiting for
the nominees for best actor are
Nominee one
Nominee two
Nominee three
Fill the board. That's it
Nominee four
but of course there can only be one winner and
The you're in the movies award for best actor goes to
maroon
Beach, please take to the podium to accept this prestigious award
Perhaps you'd like to say a few words
You know what I mean? Thank you. Thank you so much everybody. Thank you
Let's check our equipment is working. Correct. Is the lighting okay in here check the light meter to be sure
Now let's position the camera make sure everyone
Welcome to the cutout studio. This is where we separate your image
From the background select start cutout studio to continue
Great, please move out of the picture while we scan the background
Please hold on
Cut out complete now get back in front of the camera
Try playing around with the cutout style to see the best results
Can you see yourself clearly in front of the background movie?
How many actors are there choose the correct number
Step into one of the four outlines for your picture. This will decide which role you play in the movie
Don't was in my eyes. Okay, Chris a to continue
otherwise
retake
Player one on the set, please
Contender punch the targets
It's time for some training punch the targets until they disappear the more you beat the more you score
Remember if you don't beat the target you won't score any points
action
They don't hit back. So let them have it
You missed one up that work rate hit him with the rope it dope smash bang wallop
smack
Keep on your toes
Get stuck in
You don't know what is keeping them up
He's on the ropes all right
That was
Amazing those bags won't be back around for a while
I'm so that's so much easier than putting on another fucking costume layer to to this already player to that's fine with me
Drive your scooter through town dodge the obstacles, but hit the ramps to score
This one is the worst. I really hate this one
Action this one's just not fun
Don't ever use this
Dude
It's just here
I'm the paintwork. Have you got a license for that thing? I do
You said we have liftoff still technically the bicycles here don't need a license
With a little practice you could be a great. That was a lot of fun. Glad I did that whole pocket thing
That's not going to be in the movie at all
Player three get your butt on the set
We're gonna combine two costumes here
Pretend you're in a dojo preparing for a big fight
avoid the arms of the training dummy and hit the targets to score and
Action right on target
God I'm too wide run home to your mummy dummy
You're getting a beating
Do you know kung fu?
now that must have point a
lot
That's gonna hurt tomorrow
You're supposed to dodge
You're getting a beating bulls-eye take that dummy head
That's here. Yeah, that's that dummy
Nice here. I'll catch my
Dumb dummy that was awful. I couldn't decide who was more wouldn't you want a dummy?
Player four get yourself to the set play for
Run as fast as you can meets the gate to escape the charging bull
action
He sure I got a mean look about him. Don't
Speed
Ha
He sure I got a mean look about him. Don't he?
Great work slim you roll the rodeo
Player one oh shit
And now it's your time to shine just follow my instructions and act like a star
Run on the spot as fast as you can
action
That's it. You were amazing. What a pro
Player two come to the set, please
It's time for your starring moment. There's no scoring follow my instruction and
Act your heart out
Slap your fist and look mean
Action it up. Keep it up
Stay on set
Look as confused as you can
action
I don't know what's going here
Here comes another strut funkily on the spot and action
You can't keep rolling, baby
That way that she's a stick you were a star
She does not agree on the set, please double the double the TF double the TF
Double the TF. Oh, you are a moment follow my instruction
Act your heart out. Who's three? Who's three?
Imagine you're looking down a well
action
more feeling
Put more feeling into it. Hey stay there
Walk on the spot like an evil villain
And action
Keep it up. They loved you, baby
Like the inside of a trash can I think that has nothing to do with me because I'm a clean person
I think that's just dirty like that's just dirty laundry
Hi, a boy get your butt on the set was player
Player three was the bad one. Oh, that's okay
Start the water from rising shut the valve as if your life depended on it
action
Turn the wheel
That's the faster
Hold up so you don't see me naked back here. Oh, hold on. Hold on a second
Just wait a minute. I don't know what time just hold up. I'll be right there
I need a sign for the delivery. Okay, just hold on just stay there. I
Jesus what the fuck am I doing?
Player one you need it on set
Pretend that you're surrounded by hornets swat those suckers before they sting you action
You were born to swat
Oh
Sayonara stripey
Take him down
You got one
Take that you picnic spoiling feed
Well done. You sure can swat
Play it too. You need it on set
Can I get it? Can I get away with wearing this?
Okay, can I get away with wearing this out it was like this
It's time to act like a clown with a bungee run now run as far as you can before the power of the bungee drags
you back
action
Get those arms moving to gain speed
You do you but I say wow, that was some bungee you did it
Player three come to the set, please
It's diggin time
shake the jack hammer handles it as hard as you can to drill and
Action keep it up
Don't
Excellent you turn the lights out
Game complete
Player four come to the set, please play for was
Who the fuck was played before and now it's your time to shine
Just follow my instructions and act like a star. No, it's me. It's this again
Roll your arms and look as angry as you can
action
Oh
Okay, let's go again
Strut funkily on the spot
Action. Come on. Show me what you got
They loved your baby
Player one get your shit
It's time to put you in the spotlight
There's no scoring just follow my instructions and show me your acting talent
wave your arms and scream like you need help and
And action
Come on
Come on. Let's try one more
Stroke your chin like you're deep in thought
Action. Hey one more pose like a hero
action
Keep it going
That was fantastic
You were a star
Player two, I need you on set, please
It's time
Just follow my instructions and show me your acting talent rub your hands together in glee
action
Don't stop now
Go away walk on the spot and
action
more feeling
Put more feeling into it here that applause
What a moment
Don't you know if you do nerd neck far enough you can do full of momentum like an octopus
Player three you need it on set bat fat and hat, right?
Don't run. It's the defense run on the spot. How are the lightbulbs only running apparently weird?
action red like the wind
Keep on running and sparky fun. They should use you to power the country. It was still going
Why is two and four on set now, please?
clear the air
Just get the smoke out of here. I got
Imagine the room is filled with smoke wave your arms to clear the air before your opponent
Action
More clear the air you truly are a master
Player one. I need you on set, please
It's diggin time
Shake the jackhammer handles as hard as you can to drill
Action don't stop now
That's it. Keep it going
You didn't dig far enough
Player three get your butt on the set. We're gonna run again. I
Don't want to run with the fucking fat suit on again. I know yeah, it's your time to shine
There's no scoring just follow my instructions and act like a star crack your knuckles like a hoodlum
Action it up. Keep it up right now. Try this
Look as confused as you can
action
Nearly there. Let's do another
strut funkily on the spot and
Action
Keep it up
You brought the house down
beautiful
Player four you need it on set
I'm coming
No, I'm coming. There we go. It's time to put you in the spotlight
Just follow my instructions and show me your acting talent
Give me your most evil laugh
action
Fucking bad
Yeah, you can tell him right now to see your eyebrows and look from side to side
action
Keep it going. That was fantastic. You were a star
My four and a half hours. We can't fucking believe it
It's time for your starring moment. There's no scoring follow my instruction and act your heart out
Give me your most shocked expression easy
Action
Keep rolling, baby
Right. Here comes another
Mop your brow and look exhausted
action
Come on. Show me what you got. They loved you, baby
That could be a pretty good puppeteer. I think oh
Cheeto is so talented player to go set please last scenes here. I have no idea
It's diggin time
Shake the jackhammer handles as hard as you can to drill
and action
That's it. Keep it going
Keep it up. I don't want to move my hands like this anymore
You didn't dig far enough
This is unbelievable player one come to the set, please
Run run as fast as you can reach the gate to escape the charging bull
He sure I got a mean look about him don't eat get those arms moving to gain speed
I thought I was gonna have to do the little leg you roll the rodeo. Damn it
What running is that a three on the set, please? There's gonna be a lot of chase scenes in this movie
Right. See look at this
Run for your life. It's it's a tornado run as fast as you can to get away
action
15 seconds on you
Quite a bad wind, but this is ridiculous
What a runner just get you may be gay
Player four come to the set, please
This has been like 25 scenes
Dance to the music is a bank robber a bank robber dance on baby burn
It's time to stretch out as a bank robber dance to the music and match the position of the hands to pose
action
Work that booty work that booty
Let the music take over. Can you feel it?
Gotta take it higher
Let your feet do the talking
That was some performance
with a capital
I'm not gonna yeah
That thing that people want me to do player one to the set. I
Can't crack close. I didn't do it. I can't book. It's time to put you in the spotlight
There's no scoring. Just follow my instructions and show me yeah, I can tell and
swim to the surface
Action hey and another walk on the spot looking around you action
That's it. Keep it going
one more
wave your arms in complete panic and
Action
That's it. You brought the house down
Beautiful
Is it time?
Ready
Here we go fix the green screen. I'll do it after yeah the running movie wouldn't be surprised
scared witness
What there are no perfect crimes
This
Danger lurks around every corner
It's a deadly game
When you are running for your life
Hiding a secret that nobody broke
Chased
Hunted
Excitement lies dead ahead
Jeopardy awaits
impending peril
Where would you go if you?
Over there. Yes, you
were scared witness
Best part about that movie was the guy eating the stuff out of his arm. They use it like four times
God all right one more. Oh
I want to count how many times the guy eats stuff and pukes all right
scared witness
There are no perfect crimes
This
Danger lurks around every corner
It's a deadly game
When you are running for your life
Hiding a secret that nobody knows
chased
hunted
Excitement lies dead ahead
Jeopardy awaits
impending peril
Where would you go if you?
Over there. Yes, you
were scared witness
Was there a sleeping clip I don't remember the sleeping clip
Looking down the well right that's right. I forgot about that
Okay, here we go
I
Don't know fixed it. I'm gonna. I will I will don't worry
I'm gonna fix it. I'm gonna recalibrate the whole thing all right for this next this next one. I'm gonna get really close
It's just gonna be close up of my face for every scene and whatever the other actors do
That's fine. Don't look at the camera so much well
I have to look at the screen because it's like hey punch this thing and I obviously have to look to see where it is
Yeah, I'm gonna. Yeah, I'm gonna sit in my chair
Should I just read I'm just gonna read like the manual from this game
Who told Scarlett O'Hara that she should be pissed off in by somebody who knows how I don't know what movie that is
We fixed the green screen
Should be better. I'll do a little lighting check. Oh a new image. I gotta see what it is link location
Is it is it nerd neck is that what this is that movie sucked?
Yeah
That is quite the nerd neck
All right, I'm gonna try to get this caps so I can sit here and read them
I'm gonna get full body me reading
Should I do it? I feel like I want to do four, but just sit here as me every time
We'll do not just one
They take a long time. Oh with the awards thing. I wonder if she doesn't
Ladies and gentlemen
Welcome to the you're in the movies awards and now the moment you've all been waiting for
nominees for best actor are
nominee one
nominee two
nominee three
nominee four
But of course there can only be one the you're in the movies award for best actor goes to
Yeah
me
Please take to the podium to accept this prestigious award. Perhaps you'd like to say a few words
Not really
Goodbye
It's rigged. Well, I mean, it's like a it's like a three and a four chance that I'm gonna win
I'm three out of four of those actors. All right, let's see two ghosts do the best to scare up a couple moving into their home
or spiders from
No, I got that never mind
I
Kim just buck dialed me I can hear like people talking in the background
All right. We're good
All right. Oh, so let's do
super fun
Gaty for a day. Let's check. Our equipment is working correctly. Is the picture in focus?
It's important. It's the lighting. Okay in here check the light meter to be sure
It's good as it's gonna get
Now let's position the camera make sure everyone can fit themselves into the outline without appearing
Welcome to the cutout studio
Great, please move out of the picture while we scan the background
Please hold on out
Complete now get back in front of the camera try playing around with the cutout style to see the best results
Can you see yourself clearly in front of the background movie?
again
Welcome to the cutout studio. This is where we separate your image from the background
Select start cutout studio to continue
Great, please move out of the picture while we scan the background
Please hold on
Cut out
Complete now get back in front of the camera try playing around with the cutout style to see the best results
Can you see yourself clearly in front of the background movie?
Fuck welcome to the cutout studio. This is where we separate your image
Great, please move out of the picture while we scan the background
Please hold on
Cut out
Now get back in front of the camera good try playing around with the cutout style to see the best results
Can you see yourself clearly in front?
How many actors are they just me who's the correct number?
Step into one of the four outlines for your picture. This will decide
Cast away, I guess
See you guys like fucking ten minutes
Why you want you need it on sec pretend that you're surrounded by hornets
Swat those suckers before they sting you
Take them down. That's smart
Wankin will win any beauty pageants after that performance
Player one get yourself to the set. It's time for your starring moment
There's no scoring follow my instruction and act your heart out
Act like you're pushing the shopping troll and action
Keep it going. Hey stay there
surprise
Action, that's it. Keep it going
Stay on set
Look like you're a nervous wreck
action
Nearly there. You were amazing. No good. No good. No good. No good
It's too late. It's too late
What does an experiment go wipe the film clean we need to clean up wipe the dirt from the reels
Action there's more good to clean snap to it
Hi there. Hello. It's me. Yeah, just your neighborhood deity big deal
Clean snap to it
Like those I'm seeing this through
This film is way too dirty. You should have cleaned it some more
Look at spots pissing me off player one come to the set, please
It's time for your starring moment follow my instruction and act your heart out walk on the spot
action
Come on
Let's do another
Turn to the camera and look shot. I can do this one. I'm feeling
But more feeling into it. Okay, we're amazing. What a pro stock photos
Is the book backwards? No
The book is not upside down and baby burn
It's time to stretch your funky stuff dance to the music and match the position of the hands to pose
It's like shit
Get out of here get out of here son. I got a knock
Was an interesting dance style
Looked like you were dancing to your own beat
Player one to the set it's time for your starring moment follow my instruction and act your heart out
Put your hands in the air and look scared
action
Keep it up. Don't go away
look glum and
action
Don't stop now
Hear that applause
What a moment that's actually person sitting on the toilet. I feel like I make that face every day
God oh
Player one get yourself to the set
fucking close
Pace yourself and grab the bottles to cool the wall
Action. I know you got what it takes
Like you've just eaten a curry
This is a marathon not a sprint pace yourself
It was some race you thought of going bro
Player one on the set or how much more is there?
We've got to do some retakes. Just follow my instructions and show me your skills
Act like you're swatting a fly
action
Keep rolling, baby
Come on. It was fantastic
You were a star
God that's a wrap. All right
Let's let's see how fucking awful this was
One of the game controlled characters is gonna win the award. I doubt that
deity for a day
Feeling washed up. I've got you beat
Seeing things again
Why not get away?
lose yourself in
paradise
meet new friends
dance with the natives
eat fantastic feasts and
If you ever get homesick
A warm welcome awaits you
deity for a day
Will you ever tire of being admired?
I was underneath the I was sunk in there. I was deep in that shit
Oh my god
I'm swatting the flies. It's just like that's
deity for a day
feeling washed up
Life got you beat
seeing things again
Why not get away?
lose yourself
in paradise
Shitting on the beach
meet new friends
dance with the natives
eat fantastic feasts
And if you ever get homesick
A warm welcome awaits you
deity for a day
Will you ever tire of being admired?
No, I don't want to replay that one
How many movies are there so far
Really one two three four five six seven eight nine. We've done ten
ten of these
Holy shit
Uh, yeah, we'll watch them all
I'll do one more. I'll do one more. I'm starting to run out of steam here
We'll do one more good one
We'll call it 11 movies and then we'll watch them all start to finish
You look dead
It's a lot of moving around
It's like doing vr
It is vr. You looked at a book for 30 minutes. Yeah intensely
Intensely i'm gonna watch out i'm gonna get me liquids on though. Oh, I gotta do these uh trivia questions. What am I doing?
What city does king kong wreck have it on new york?
What country does maria come from and maria full of grace?
Uh italy bernard frazier starred in the film versions of george of the jungle and one of the tv show
He was in yeah, that's right. He was in wg, right?
Post cuts from the edges based on life and what famous mother and daughter
Michael douglas played a down on his luck professor in which 2000 movie
um
I don't know that either
No, not ant man
What is the battle on skull island lizards?
huge ones huge lizards
I told you that's correct
In moulin rouge, what was christian and satine's sacred song used to express a love for each other?
uh lady marmalade
Earbud
All right. What's the last one? We're gonna do
Ladies and gentlemen, is there a christmas welcome to the you're in the movies awards
Spiders, okay
I will do every actor in the spiders movies you've all been waiting for
The nominees for best actor are
Nominee one
Nominee two
Nominee that's a good movie poster image though. Look at that top left
If you clean that up nominee four, that'd be a great movie poster
There's no one of course. There can only be one winner
And the you're in the movies award for best actor goes to
Please take to the podium to accept this prestigious award. Perhaps you'd like to say a few words
All right spiders four actors
I'm going all out for this
spiders from space
Let's check our equipment is working correctly is the picture info
Is the lighting okay?
Now let's position the camera make sure everyone can
Welcome to the cut out studio
great
Please move out of the picture while we scan the background overact the shit out of this please hold on
Overact
Cut out complete
Now get back in front of the camera
Try playing around with the cutout style to see the best results
Can you see yourself clearly in front of the background movie?
Anything after this i'm going to do i'm going to do the bits after this
We're going to want to go through probably take us to like five and a half six hours
And then after that the bits will be probably half an hour
So
All right
I think it's the light. It's not a light in the room right now. How many actors are there choose the floor?
Step into one of the four outlines for your picture. This will decide which role you play in the movie
It doesn't matter just get them all
If the picture is okay press a to continue
Let's do it
Spider is in my attic. Whatever the hell this is called player one. I need you on set, please
All right, no, no more fat suit
Fat the fat suit's done. I can't do it. I can't put it on anymore
I'm playing one though. I know that
It's time to act like a clown with a bungee run
Now run as far as you can before the power of the bungee drags you back
Action get those arms moving to gain speed
That was some bungee you did it. All right, it's gonna be person with half me
And then person with the rope
No more fat player two to the set
It's time for some training punch the targets until they disappear the more you beat the more you score
Remember if you if you don't beat the target you won't score any points
Action shit, it's so fucked up. He's getting too dark
Smash you look like a like a like a million dollars, baby
Get stuck in
He's on the ropes. All right
What a hit
Fists of fury
I've beaten up the arrow 25 times today
Champion did I just get out of bed?
Yeah
And it was chilly
Players three and four on set now, please
I'm just gonna hold it up
See who can get the hula hoop. No, that doesn't look right the faster it goes. I gotta go. I gotta go for it
half
You can't just knock it and action
Work the hula baby work it
Keep it up keep it up
What's this even for this is not for anything
And we have these and gentlemen player one to the set
It's time for your starring moment. No scoring follow my instruction and act your heart out
Imagine you're looking down a well
Action. Hey, let's go another all in the cup all of it act surprise 100% of it
and action
Keep it up easy
What a pro
Go in animal
Play it too. Get yourself to the set
Run the marathon run run run run. It's
Running distance as fast as you can beware of overheating pace yourself and grab the bottles to cool off
That's so bad the dark the darkness is destroying this
I'm gonna wait till the 20 seconds is up
winner
Keep it up
Player three get yourself to the set. Can you hump them?
All right, get it right
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Am I am I outlined here?
That's so weird. Look at that
They actually caught me me as an outline
That's weird
All right, at least like I can see the bottom
Yeah, this is gonna have to be the last one just because i'm the daylights burnt here
Still fucked up down here. Unfortunately. Oh well better than what it was before
What is it about? What is this here? What's going on here? Start the water from rising shut the valve as if your life depended on it
action
Turn the wheel faster faster
You stop the water it didn't even mess up your hair
Player four on the set, please
Step on up, please
Stupid running the fat suit. I always pick the wrong run on the spot to power the light bulbs
and action
Keep on running
Oh shit red like the wind and spiky fun. They should use you to power the country
I don't have any audio anymore
Player one come to the set, please
I got it hit man
Who is this me? Okay wise guy you think you're tough
Walk the mean streets of the city and whack those gangsters, but mind you don't hit the broads
Action start walking
You're busting my boards here
What did she ever do to you bully?
What's a girl gotta do to get noticed
What a hit
You whacked him, but mind you don't hit the things
You took him down
You're busting my boards here
You missed him
Shave the pounce you let him go
That's bad for business
Come back and see me sometime
God was gonna strangle somebody player two come to the set, please
I can't I broke my audio jack. It's I can't hear a damn thing
Seriously, I can't hear anything
And now it's your time to shine
Just follow my instructions and act like a star
Imagine you're looking down a well
action
Don't stop now
And another point at the camera and look stern
And action
Keep it up
Don't go away
I didn't I mean I gotta slap your fist and look mean
action
Keep it going
They loved you, baby
Like look at number two like whoops
I'm too tall. I actually kind of man
He's still playing this is the last one on set now, please
three and four
Mud fight splash your opponent with mud till you can't see them anymore
Anyone for mud pie
Can you tell I gave up can you tell I gave up it's pretty obvious
I'm exhausted. I did all my energy running four hours a player one on the set, please
Who it keeps cutting out because I broke this stupid fucking jack
I don't know who this is supposed to be
Who quick run for your life. Oh, it's a tornado run as fast as you can to get away one
And action
See i'm going all out
That's all I need. I already captured it. Keep moving. The twist is gonna get you
You're not in new mexico anymore
Quick check
Player two you need it
The sweetest shit this shit
Just putting my house through like this. The editor is angry. He started throwing things around
Catch the golden film reels and dodge the junk
Action, oh, you're supposed to dodge the junk
Great catch more reels to keep scoring
That's just great
Keep it up
One of the people in the house is really wonka
Oh charlie, it's okay
What do we share all of us? So seven of us are gonna share the same fucking thing
It's a fool by the way, there's no way this would work in real life
You managed to catch all of the reels you might just have saved this movie
Player four get yourself to the set
All right all out for this one no matter what it is. It's time for your starring moment
I will follow my instruction and act your heart out
Keep your arms by your side and struggle like you're tied up
action
Come on
Don't go away
All up go all out act like like you're a nervous wreck
and action
Keep rolling, baby
You brought the house down beautiful
Delete the bod player one get your butt on the set
It's time for your starring moment follow my instruction and act your heart out
Shave your eyes from the sun
action
That's it
Right. Here comes another
Strike your best kung fu pose
action
That's it. Keep it going
You were amazing
What a pro. Oh my god
Cap that one
Cap that one zoom in and then stretch it up
All right, final stretch coming up player two get your butt on the set
Okay, wise guy you think you're tough walk the mean streets of the city and whack those gangsters
But mind you don't hit the broads
Action start walking
You're busting my boards here
Come back and see me sometime
What's a girl gotta do to get noticed
Hit you took him down
You sure know how to treat a lady
You let him go
That's bad for business
You whacked him but mind you don't hit the things
You took him down
Missed him
That was okay. You could do with a bit more gangster training
Let's go
Player three. I need you on set please player three has done almost nothing
This is the weird hat and smoking jacket player three. They've done anything
And it's almost close to zero
Run as fast as you can reach the gate to escape the charging bull
Action get those arms moving to gain speed. Ouch. He nearly knocked you into texas
This here bull can rage
Ouch, he nearly knocked you into texas
Is this your first rodeo partner?
He's going all out for this one
Player one you need it on set
I kind of like that though. I just can't stand there sternly
Catch the golden film reels and dodge the junk
The editor is angry. He started throwing things around
I can do this
and action
I'm not gonna hit once
Great catch more reels to keep scoring
Ouch, you're supposed to dodge the junk
That was both keep it up
That's gonna fucking be weird
Watch yourself catch the real so we're gonna lose my movie
Please be careful. I don't think the insurance covers this
Oh, what a safe pair of hands you got
You that was pretty good
You saved most of the movie we can get the rest with
Stock footage and body doubles. That's what i'm doing. I'm just giving you stock footage. What's all this?
Player four. Player four
Here we go
Oh, this is gonna be a good one
Let's all do the conga hit the drums as fast as you can to make your monkey dance faster
action
Dance monkey dance
Monkey go?
Skate boogaloo
I that's never gonna come up
That's just in my mouth bro
Player two. I need you on set, please
It's time to put you in the spotlight
Just follow my instructions and show me your acting talent. Oh, what are they doing? No, it was that this was this was a guy
And scream like you need help
action
You brought the house down beautiful
Player three to the set
It's time to put you in the spotlight
There's no scoring just follow my instructions and show me your acting
Look up to the sky as if you've just seen a flying pig
action
Come on. Show me what you got
You brought the house down beautiful
Player one get yourself to the set. Oh my god. There's a lot
Oh, don't break the phillips you that was seven dollars
It's time to put you in the spotlight
There's no scoring just follow my instructions and show me your acting talent
Give me your most shocked expression
action
Now try this
Wave your arms and scream like you need help
and action
Nearly there
They loved your baby yellow teeth
What well done people that's it. That's the final one. All right, get me out of this suit
Here's the last one of the night
spiders from space
No one could have dreamt
Such an eerie event could occur
here
On our own planet earth
But they came
They fed
They spun their meticulous webs
For your lives
They're freakish they're brutish
They're certainly parachute they're spiders from space
Where was the eating thing
Do you get that you could tell like where these are going?
They it started like the first like seven were like wow i'm like really into it and like these last ones have been
Just so phoned in the last two especially
They didn't even use the footage of me eating all the fucking stuffing
All right, we're gonna watch them all i'm gonna save it
Maybe when they're saved they won't lag
Oh my goodness, that was fucking fun
That was absolutely worth playing that was worth buying a 360 and xbox live vision camera
so
The best part about having a 360 still
After this because I bought up at this game. I bought a connect and I bought about 30 to 40 games
There's gonna be
a week
Maybe two weeks worth of connect games
I got
So many
Oh, yeah, I got connect star wars. Absolutely
Every connect game you can think of that you think is worth playing
I I have it restart the console. Yeah, i'll do that too
I'm gonna red ring this xbox
Did I get twister? Yes, I did
No connect games are worth playing
That's true. Well, some of them are
I think there's at least a handful that might be worth playing
Star wars connect dancing
I don't think I have that one
Connectable connectimals. Yes, I have that too
That's the only good one
So we will go through i'm gonna assume that I wanted a whole stream for this game because obviously
I felt like there was a lot to explore when there was
I do have rise of nightmares. I also have hunt
Yeah, I got them all
All right, let's take let's i'm gonna restart the 360
Should have about 11 or 12 to watch start to finish
Here we go
Oh
I am
Tired
I didn't think this game was going to take it out of me that much
But it did I think it was the changing clothes like every 15 seconds ladies and gentlemen
Welcome to the you're in the movies awards
And now the moment you've all been waiting for
The nominees for best actor are
Nominee one
Nominee two arm base arm and arm
Nominee three
Is the constant standing?
No, I think it was not many four. There's probably a combination of everything
But of course there can only be one winner
And the you're in the movies award for best actor goes to
Please take to the podium to accept this prestigious award
Perhaps you'd like to say a few words
I'm so tired. I am trashed right now. Not even alcohol. I'm just saying
Oh, how many different do you think? I feel like I want to do these
That's some of the point. There's like six or seven more that I think I'm gonna do
Steal the day some of these look funny, but uh, let's go to
movie theater
Watch a movie. I'm gonna restart the
console
This thing is on fire
Wow
This thing is burning up
Whoa easy, what the fuck are you doing?
It just spit the disc at me. I didn't do anything. I would say this is probably like 250 degrees
If I were to take a guess
Inside of here if I touched inside of here, I would burn my hand out to go to the hospital if I put my finger
Inside of this unit
Okay restarting
And here we go. I wonder what the bottom of this feels like
xbox sucks
Yeah, and so earlier today it was it was over probably 100 105 here in vegas. So
Probably not the best environment for an old 360, but this is one of the newer models. This is one of the slim ones
They can handle it, right?
Okay, here we go
All right, the slim models had overheating problems
Uh-oh
How bad come to you're in the movies the game that makes you
All right, we're gonna watch him start to finish
All right, we're gonna do who this is who cares
No, no, no, no, no, I might be in I'm no we're gonna do who cares too
You ready?
Who cares?
Everyone's super
every superhero super
But some are more super than others
And where there are heroes
There are villains
battles adventure
Breathtaking effects
Not a silly costume in sight
Ever wanted to wear your underpants over your trousers?
rippling muscles
Astounding abilities
fiercer than a ranting mom
More courageous than a hungry mouse
Faster than waiting for a bus
So when you're feeling low remember
Everyone's super
Well, that was the first one and it was dog shit
Here's who cares three. I don't remember which one this one was
It was a day like any other day
until a terrible accident
Created a horrifying atomic monster
cold-blooded
Watch in terror as the radioactive mastodon wreaks havoc
Trying to dodge the laser
Created by nature
twisted by science
No weapons of warfare known to man can harm it
Can anything stop this leviathan?
Can mankind use science?
to fight nature with nature
Feel your blood run cold
cold-blooded
Okay, that one actually sucked
That was just stupid
The lizard was the best character in that whole trailer. It wasn't me
Here's me me and me
me
Me and me
Today is a day you'll never forget
somewhere
at some point in time
in a secret location
the boundaries of science
of being stretched
beyond breaking point
Through the miracle of science
You could find yourself
Becoming more
Much more
loads more
And then some
So when you're in a pickle
There's only one person you can count on
you
and you
The thing the algorithm making everybody fat is just fucking too funny
Oh, man
Here comes the murder mansion
dial m for a menu
Today's meal is murder
There's plenty to eat
When murders on the menu
Murder at the mansion
Everyone has a motive
Everyone has a secret
Everyone is a suspect
Who has the last laugh
When a joke goes too far
But who is to blame?
Who is guilty of?
Murder at the mansion
No, I would not like to see it again
This one I think is my favorite. I think love story is my favorite. There's so much going on in this one
I love all of them equally but I think this one might be the best one just because it's a fucking all over the place
Looking for love
Is a tricky business
Having a best friend
Can make it harder and
Excitement
And security
Is what we're all looking for
And if it doesn't work out we try again
And again
But sometimes
The right one for you
Is closer than you think
Watch close to your heart
Because love is never far away
That's my favorite I love that one
Uh, I just the best part is the the picture the naked fat guy, right? That's your picture
That's what you have for a photo and then you show up naked too
At the front door and it's like that. Oh my god. Wow, you're so so dashing
This is the private eye one. I think this one was pretty good, too
private eye
It was a quiet day for crime
Then bad news walked in layers
to that
Everyone wants to play the field
And no one wants to get caught
Love can make us do terrible things
diabolical dancing
Sensational scandal
Most people want one of two things
love
or money
some
want both
Before you act on your suspicions
Get yourself some proof
Get yourself
a private eye
Okay, so the first my favorite part is the first scene
The private eye is sitting there and the door open he's crying
Before somebody like a customer comes in and he has to shape up real quick
Normal I can see that again
Private eye
It was a quiet day for crime
Then bad news walked in
Everyone wants to play the field
Is that person crying?
And no one wants to get caught
Love can make us do terrible things
Diabolical dancing
Sensational scandal
Most people want one of two things love or money
Some want both
Before you act on your suspicions
Get yourself some proof
Get yourself
a private eye
I mean, that's kind of bad like back to back. These are like just
I think I can't pick one. I can't pick which one's better
I think it's probably love story though
Let me see it again. Let me see it one more time and then we'll move on
Looking for love is a tricky business having a best friend
Can make it harder
a little romance
Excitement
and security
Is what we're all looking for
And if it doesn't work out we try again
and again
But sometimes the right one for you
Is closer than you think
Watch close to your heart
Because love is never far away
It's like a computer put it together. It's not even it's it's like just
Stock put it in a computer
God a computer did put it together. Yeah, that's true
But this this is the dinosaur one these these next three are fucking horrible, but we're gonna watch them. Anyways
It's yeah, it's like talk to transformer
It started with a meeting of great minds
And a plan to travel to a lost world
Journey to a land never be held by man woman nor child
Discover sights and sounds no human has ever seen before
Prehistoric paradise
Marvel at the mammoth monstrosities
Groundbreaking discoveries
Enormous eggs
Terrifying monsters
Older than your dreams
scarier than your nightmares a
Daring rescue mission
Be prepared to witness the spectacle that is
Prehistoric paradise
It's like your actor was so bad that they just got like drunk on set every day
And they didn't even do their lines
So you had to piece something together. What you you you already were halfway through making the whole movie
Vampire, I don't remember vampire. I don't even remember this one
Oh, yeah, the scooby doo who run this one is the most coherent. I think it was supposed to be
the trip of a lifetime
It turned into a holiday from hell
Gaze and horror upon the bizarre creatures of the night
This is the vacation
to end
all vacations
You won't be able
To leave will anyone hear you scream?
There's loads of excitement
But be sure
Not to lose your head
Your friends for dinner literally
So
If you feel the life being sucked out of you
It's time for a vampiric
vacation
I like I like this one, but I like one part there's only one part of like when they're at the dinner table
and
The robe robe guy has like a wine glass in his hand and he's just like
Overanimated and over enunciating that's what we'll see one more time
It was supposed to be
The trip of a lifetime
It turned into a holiday from hell
What's the dinner?
Gaze and horror upon the bizarre creatures of the night
This is the vacation
to end
all vacations
You won't be able to leave
Will anyone hear you scream?
There's loads of excitement
What a lovely game but be sure not to lose your head
Have your friends for dinner literally and that's what I tried to rip through it didn't work
So
If you feel the life being sucked out of you
It's time for a vampiric
vacation
All right, oh yeah, yeah, I
Uh witnesses, oh, this is the one with this one with shito
This oh, this one's the eating. This is the eating. Oh, I love this one. This one actually might be my favorite
It's it's tough because it's so fucking scared witness
There are no perfect crimes
And when you're the only witness
Danger lurks around every corner
It's a deadly game
When you for your life hiding a secret that nobody knows
chased
hunted
Excitement lies dead ahead
Jeopardy awaits
Impending peril
Would you go?
if you
Over there. Yes, you
Were scared witness
And then I did an even better one in this next one when I stuffed the whole thing in my mouth
And they didn't even use it. They didn't even use any of it
deity
Oh, right the book one
Deity for a day feeling washed up life got you beat
Seeing things again
Why not get away?
yourself
in paradise
Meet new friends
dance with the natives
eat fantastic feasts
And if you ever get homesick
A warm welcome awaits you
deity for a day
Will you ever tire of being admired? This is that was this is the one that it was just I was done
I was done. I was didn't want dumb was done doing this
God
When did that even happen no one could have dreamt such an eerie event could occur
here
on our own planet earth
But they came
They fed
They spun their meticulous webs
Run for your lives
They're freakish
They're brutish
They're certainly her suit
They're spiders from space
Oh, who cares one
I think it's just it's just the superhero one, but I might be naked. Let me see
These superheroes super
But some are more naked good others
And where there are heroes
There are villains. I don't think i'm gonna end this for more than a second
That I I tested it. I think i'm going to eventually
breathtaking effects
Not a silly costume in sight
Ever wanted to wear your underpants over your trousers
Rippling muscles
I just need testing
fiercer than a ranting mom
I told you I was going to make work out here hungry mouse
faster than waiting for a bus
So when you're feeling low
remember
Everyone's super
From yesterday. Um, i'm sorry. No what you're looking at here is you're looking at something I did
Uh to at least two days ago
Yes, so this was the 17th
so this was
Like two or three days ago. Yeah
I told you I was in it. What am I gonna this shirt was clean. Am I gonna wash the shirt?
I put it up for five seconds
I put this shirt on did the test and was like i'm ready to stream and I couldn't scream
So that I just took off the shirt and it went back to bed. I didn't go to bed
But I I like I don't know what I did something
The shirt's a little dirty. It's dirty now. Oh, absolutely
You better believe it
Just upload it
Uh, well, that was fucking really really fun. That was really fun
Uh, yeah, i'm still on camera. All right
Oh, I I put the shirt on for literally 20 minutes
No, I wasn't throwing up a high batted smell that was the robe
That was that was the robe
Look at how dark it is in here now
It was this that's what you were smelling and that's what I was smelling but that's what I was relaying to you
E that's the e3 striat. That is the e3 striat bro
Oh man, does everybody have the the boogers coming out of my nose?
I kind of want to see it. Let me turn this down
Does anybody have like the snot coming out of my nose?
Right there
Is that it? Is that actually it?
I want to see if this actually happens. Can you actually see this?
I look tired
I don't think you can see it
No, thank god. This camera is like 140p
Perfect. You can't see shit
Look at that forehead shine. Well, I mean i've been running around in a circle in my room for six hours. Well five and a half
All right. I'm gonna call it here
Thank you for joining me. Um, that was you're in the movies
That was a lot of fun
That was way more fun than I really thought about I just I I saw it and I had to get it head play
Hope you had fun
so what we're going to do now is
We're going to do the bits
But we're going to start with the bits that I missed a couple days ago through three days ago
So we're going to just going to chill
Uh, and we're going to go through them
Just going to relax and play
nothing
Maybe I should just stay on camera
I don't know if I know that xbox is going to like fucking explode. I'm going to turn it off
I feel like this thing is gonna burn out
Uh, can I just like go like this?
nice face cam
Hold on. You can hear the xbox dying. You probably can
I just want like the square
What if I don't move?
Uh is it i'm just gonna have to go like this
Hey, there you go
Now we'll just hang out and do the other go to the other screen. Is the picture in focus? I mean sure it is
I guess I can just hit back right? Yeah
All right, if you're gonna take off, we'll see uh, we'll see you tomorrow
I have no idea what's going on tomorrow. I know there's some stuff that is possible
I wonder if star's computer works
Star's computer was all screwed up or something his power supply was fucked up
There are
There are like 30 dead pixels on this webcam
Oh my god, I burnt it out
One two, three, four
Five six seven eight nine ten you can find like oh ryan's belt in this thing
Five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen
Wow
That's unbelievable. This thing really is a piece of shit, isn't it?
Whatever not like i'm gonna use it ever again unless I play this but I do have a second one because I bought two accidentally
How much was the xbox camera it here's what I didn't know
Uh, you're in the movies comes with one of those
I did not know that
So I bought one of those separately and it's sealed in a clamshell box
Uh, I didn't know you got one when you bought it. So
It didn't say that on the list
Unfortunately, so I have a second fresh one. Maybe i'll plug the fresh one in in like six months. We'll do it again
Sell it on ebay
No, I want to keep it. I want to keep it forever
All right, let's do the bits. Let's uh actually get this
Open so these are from a few days ago. We're gonna do we're gonna go through them very quickly
At least quick enough where we can head to the other ones too because I don't want to be too late tonight
Because this is a good place to kind of stop and this is what I want to have happen in the future as well
those of you that have been around
Uh just hanging out for the last
Maybe a couple weeks or so once or twice. I have talked about
Bits on the beach. Oh, yeah, I guess I could just do this couldn't I?
Oh, watch this ready. We'll just have like some random shit in the background
Ready? Watch this
Zits on the beach
That's one there's one it's hot in here
All right
Uh, let's get to the bits from a few days ago
Watch out for that monkey behind me. Where is he?
Oh, that's a lion
It was a monkey. Okay. So from a few days ago
I'm gonna put these over here actually so I can see them better
We had a new piece of artwork from yenwen
Which I want to show on screen because it was insane. It was
Yenwen's artwork is more detailed than my own face
Let me get it here
Take a look at this
You've seen it. Yeah, it's ridiculous. It's it's I there's more detail than my actual face
It's the chin one. Yeah, look at this
This shit is so fucking funny. Yeah, nice pick. I'm getting it. I'm getting I'm getting I'm getting I'm getting I'm getting I'm getting
I'm gonna VPN
The VPN I use takes like an extra five to ten seconds to open like any websites
All right, here we go. Why am I in a VPN?
Because my internet sucks
And routing traffic somewhere else actually helps with my packet loss because my internet's a piece of shit
But look at that
That's from a few days ago
I have to shave too
Look at what like two days does
Make it an emote. You look like night crawler
night crawler
like
Jake jillin hall nightcrawler or like go through walls nightcrawler
Now that's amazing
both
But thank you yen wen for that. It's fucking fantastic
It's a jim carrey william depot. I'm like losing my face here
Slowly, it's deciding it doesn't like where I am
Uh, but no, that's insanely talented
there's so many artworks that
yen wen has done that are just ridiculous
And there's also a couple of clown car emotes
I might as well put this one on screen because it's fucking funny
Please shave take a break and break in a hot bath. You look stressed and not well. I'm all right
I'm fine. What's what are you talking about? I'm all right
I mean, I i'm i'm i'm i'm 33
This is what you look like when you're 33
I'm a 23 and i'm 33. This is just what you look like this
I'm doing just fine
And i've been jumping around in my room
They're telling you to take a shower. I'm going to i'm going to you better believe it when this is done
Uh, but let's put this on the screen
Come on, get over there
He keeps up with the roller coaster pretty well
I gotta like put the new shit that lord out did on this stream. I've been so busy. I haven't been able to do it
It's really good
Yeah, there's like two or three things that he that he's done that i've done
And I just haven't put them on because I decided to haven't had I just have been too busy to like put it all up
And set it all up
I've had it for like at least a couple weeks
I'm still I keep disappearing
But thank you. Yeah, when there's a fucking fantastic as always
We also had 250 from for real though
Jeremy i've been watching the vod for your majesty majesty stream and enjoying it
Uh, I thought you might suggest the dungeon keeper series and war for the overworld
Uh dungeon keeper is um
Didn't they remake dungeon keeper but it was a terrible game. Didn't they like redo it and people hated it?
Because it wasn't like true to the old games or something
Yeah, the remake sucks
That's too bad
But probably not probably not dungeon keeper
unless it was something that
I unless i've ran out of more stuff like because I have a lot of stuff that's coming that I want to do
It was a microtransaction nightmare
That's unfortunate
But thank you for real though
Uh, thank you squalled easy for the three bucks. Hey germy the other day
I donated two dollars to italics and he made fun of me for being poor
Will you cheer me up by saying the funny word which one?
Got lots of funny words
Which funny word?
I said I said that s word like 10 times today
I think you heard it
theater
Fucking lion behind me
Uh gondor land. Thanks for the 250
You say you'll stream anything recommended
But i've been recommending bookworm adventures for two years and recommendations channel lying streamer. I didn't say i'd play
I I didn't say i'd play anything recommended. What would you get that from?
I i'll stream anything that you tell me to stream. That's not gonna happen
Bookworm adventures is they can't even purchase it anymore. That shit doesn't even exist anymore. You can't buy it anywhere
You have to like download it for you get it from like amazon. Everything's been asking it sent to you in the mail
I never said I I
The recommendation channel is if a recommendation is not a streamer you're gonna play this
That's not a recommendation. That's a demand
Hey, you know what? I what the heck i've been recommending demands to you streamer on demand
I
Don't even like talk about thanks for the 250 this documented evidence that marijuana is good for the human body
This is a 34 year old stoner that plays video games for money
This documented fucking medical evidence that marijuana is like does good things for you if you have different like conditions. I didn't
That's true. That is a true statement
Marijuana has medicinal benefits that have been studied by the medical doctor field and you know it you know it
I'm not saying like I smoke weed fucking every second of your life
No, but if you like
You know, whatever sometimes if you feel like it
Thank you. Chris buck 365 appreciate it
Five bucks
No message just five bucks sawdust bunny seven dollars and 20 cents. Thanks for the seven dollars and 20 cents. Appreciate it
No message
whole of one zombie. Thanks for the 250
Really enjoyed the germa sad story video and I think it's amazing
You've created an atmosphere for creative minded people to riff off of your content
That includes the discord art section. It's a great thing
No, it is a great thing. I bumped you. I bumped you right here because i'm like i'm like i'm talking with my hands
I need to like
Sit up or something
There now i'm like you can actually see my face
Forget about down here
uh, but
yeah, I
If anybody takes anything on this channel and makes it into something fun
Something interesting something like transforms it into something else
That's really really fun to see
Change the cutout style
That's making it worse
uh, it's really fun to see people do things to everything that happens on this channel if somebody pulls out a
A clip or something that we did that was fun or something or that they thought was fun or funny and they turn into something else
It's really interesting to see it
But no, I I agree
I agree
Uh, thank you. I don't even like taco bell for the next 250 two dollars 50 cents germ
I'm sorry to be a negative nancy, but I gotta point out you got all mad when we said peepee poo poo
But then you talked about your girlfriend pooping on you. I did not talk about my I talked about my girlfriend shitting her pants
in bed
I didn't talk about my girlfriend shitting on me. I talked about my girlfriend shitting her pants in bed
Didn't happen, but it was an interesting story. You got to look back. You got to find it
It was from two to three days ago. You'll see it. It's it's a it's a funny. It's actually a very funny story
I thought it was hilarious
It's a very very funny story like really big misunderstanding and really funny
A hole of one zombie. Thanks for the 250 in case you ever considered expanding your merchandise
I'm an ideas man
ideas, man
What is it merchandise is weird for me? I I I
I probably
Well, I I can tell you i'm probably not gonna do that. I'm not gonna do this
It's I mean, it's is that even my face?
Let me see if this is even my face is it
Uh, yeah, I can I can tell you i'm probably not going to use this
But I really appreciate it
Thank you. That was um
This is help
Uh, that was hole of one zombie
Podcast listener. Thanks for the 10 bucks. Uh, no message. Just a couple of emotes. It's germa
rat germa heart germa rat 10 bucks
Thank you
I really am slowly just fading out into nothing. I gotta like move over here
But thank you for the ten dollars podcast listener
Uh sawdust bunnies. Thanks for the 250. Sorry for calling you a boomer
I completely forgot just how off the fucking rails I was three days ago
I was all over the place three days ago, wasn't I?
Did I get mad that people were calling me a boomer?
Uh stefunkey chicken. Thanks for the three bucks. Please look up germa scares room full of children on youtube. It would be it would be
Remotivate me
What is this?
Oh, yeah, here's the next one
Vroom has to be in a clown car
These emotes are yeah, they are
I'll put these on screen
Let's put them on here
So you can see
You have a lot of different examples, too
Well, would you you would you would you use that would you use that would you use that emote?
Maybe we'll see maybe we'll see what we can do here
Fucking cat. I think I have to get off this. It's freaking me out. Yeah, that's I did it again and i'm so sorry
I
I am so fucking sorry that I did that like twice in 15 minutes
I'm gets because i'm way too close. I'm closer than I usually am
Uh, but thank you fat boisiant fat bossiant for the five bucks
Just want to say I love your content and it has provided my life with more enjoyment that I could have ever had
As i'm debating
Phoning nine nine nine have so much chest pain, but I should get through it
Nine nine nine
Hopefully you're all right
Is that is that is that an equivalent for something like nine one one?
Well, hopefully you're all right. Hopefully you took care of it
Uh fat boss and hopefully you're all right
That's the uk. Okay. Well
Yeah, if you're here now, I mean this was three days ago
Take care of yourself. That's that it's kind of scary
Hopefully you uh, you're all right
It's zero. Is it zero zero zero in australia?
You can you hear this xbox?
It's going crazy
Uh, thank you to core monster for the five dollars. I spent way too much time on this
How can I save things and I can't find them afterwards i'm so stupid
Yeah, it's right there
Is it not what do I do with it?
There okay, that is not a car driving by that is the xbox
No, is it wait, is that nightcrawler?
Or is that uh, who is that?
Thank you
Nightcrawler
Uh, that was core monster. Thank you core monster. Let me fix the hair a little
That's what i'm looking completely fucked up
Uh, thank you though core monster
Good shit good shit
Dubski dude, thanks for the 250. Hey germa, you should seriously consider playing dark wood
It's one of the best horror games on steam
On steam really and it's sitting at a 93 with steam reviews
I promise you it'll make for a perfect scare saturday stream
Normally, I don't give people money just to recommend a game but dark wood is that good
Okay, also chat will love watching you shit your pants
Is it good?
How good is it?
It's good
You're doing everyone a disservice by not playing dark wood. Really?
Is it top down? Is that a top down game?
It is okay. I have seen i've seen this. I might even own this
I don't think of I think it was one of those things where I just bought it one day or like a steam sale or something
maybe
Uh, do you still use your instagram? I don't have an instagram
If you are looking at a germa 985 instagram account, it is not real. It is not a real account
I do not have one
I have a twitter and I have a facebook that i've never used
I don't have any of the social media accounts
Wait, what is this germa psycho? Why is it like why is it blood on my chin?
Facebook sucks. I haven't used it. I have i've made one
Almost 10 years ago and I have used it maybe three or four times
Yeah, all right. Let's meet a fat suit. I I know I just did it. I just was doing that for like the last six hours
What's your email germa 95 germa 95 germa 95 germa 95 at germa 95 dot germa 95
I'm holding a fish in my facebook profile. I'm not I don't have a facebook
I don't have I don't use the germa 95 facebook doesn't I don't do anything
I don't have a fucking facebook. I don't have like a fish profile. Whatever you're talking about
Can you repeat that? Yeah, I'll get you one more time
Rejection hotline at rejection hotlines.com
Should I make this an emote? All right. I gotta let me go through the bits
Let me go through the bits
I kept thinking about yeah, uh dead pixels. What are you talking about? Somebody's saying this dead pixels. What's what do you another arm?
checking monitor man
Your monitor seems like it might be fucked
I remember
I got a dead pixel and I bought a new computer. This is
It was a laptop. This is probably like 12 years ago or so probably 12 or 15 years ago
I got a new laptop
and there's a dead pixel on the monitor in the laptop and I
Fucking could not stand it. I lost my mind
I did a thing where you you heat up a little like washcloth with like hot water
And then you take the hot damp pad and you like massage
I gave this thing eight like four hour massage trying to massage out this dead pixel
It didn't work
Just like pushing and massaging and they say tap
You see I sat there tapping on this dead pixel for hours
It didn't do anything and it drove me nuts
Has that ever worked for anybody by the way has like tapping the dead pixel article that you get from on the internet
That's that one person tells you to do it
Has that ever worked for anybody?
No, no, no, no. No. Yeah
Why would that work? I guess it's you you it gets the electricity to get stick in there and
Get in there and
Move it around and the crystal. I don't know. I have no idea
Should I try to fix these?
Are those dead pixels here or those like dead pixels on on more of them appeared?
Is that the 360?
How many are there?
Shit, there's way more than I thought
Yes, I'll maybe take a look at the top left
That's venus up there
God
Oh fuck. Well, I may have just made it worse
It's broken
Hey, i'm just kidding now we're in focus
Okay
Uh, where were we?
I forget right here
Oh dark wood, right? All right. Maybe i'll maybe i'll try it
I don't know. I have to look into it. I have to see that because I don't
That's it on my fucking hand
What is that?
Like that's a pimple on my hand. That's not a
That's a pimple on my hand. Can you get those?
That's not a wart
It's I think it's irritation
That's not that's not a word. Look at I think I have a zit on my hand
Oh, you know what it is. It's from resting my finger here and getting that indentation
It's not a liver spot
I'm not that old
Uh, thank you to
A uh, I know princess of misery for the five dollars. I drew this for you dad. I hope you're proud of me
P.s. I hope they cast you as the green goblin in the new spider-man franchise
Yeah, i'm like jacked
I could be a fucking green goblin. I swear too much though. Let's put this a lot of artwork
You guys are really killing it with the artwork here
Let's get it on. Uh, this is me
This is like what I actually look like with no shirt on
So you just had to call me short
It's pretty accurate to how big I am
At least in the chest area
This is not safe for work
What?
It's fat
No, I got those broad shoulders
That's what my mother told me at least
But thank you, uh princess of misery. That was very very very very good shit
All the artwork has been stellar
So, thank you an anonymous cheerer. Thanks for the 250
Uh, that's it. Just 250
Clueless sniper. Thanks for the 250 the germ of that face you made inspired me to make this
I feel like i've seen this character somewhere, right?
spider-man
Oh, that's the green goblin. I'm fucking stupid
Not bad. I don't think I could do it. Not bad
Uh, but no, thank you for that. Are you actually a boomer? No, i'm 33. I'm still a millennial. I'm just like you
I'm just like you i'm 33. I was born in 85. I'm a millennial
I'm not a boomer a boomer would be I would be gen
X or something
If I was like 83 or 82 or something
I am a millennial
Just like you
Or some of you guys are zoomers
Jen jex
Okay, uh, we were at uh, that was clueless sniper. Thank you clueless sniper for that artwork
Clueless sniper again for 250. I think this is a double message here
it is
Uh, but thank you for the goblin the green goblin. Thanks for the five dollars a few days ago
Errorless thanks for the 250 streamer rages at in-game character
Was it playing three days ago? Oh
metal wolf chaos
I beat that game
I forgot about that. It's kind of a blur
Uh, but thank you errorless for the 250
All right, this is right when I was in the middle of just being very upset at everything in the world, right
Man boy 777. Thanks for the 250. Hey germa. I've been wondering how can I be more like you?
I've been cursed with incredibly thick hair
And i'm really getting tired of it. How did you get your hair so thin?
Uh errorless. Thanks for the 250 again. Is he still doing his old hat charade?
old hat charade
What do you mean old hat? What were we talking about? What hat charade? I don't
I'm not sure
I don't know
You look nice today
Do you drink milk ice? Please answer. It's very important. No, I don't drink milk over ice
I don't drink milk anymore
I can't my stomach can't handle it
My intestines can't handle it
But thank you pin for the 250
Pin says hey germa. I just got my acceptance letter for by you
Hell, yeah
The whole process has been a surreal experience and I've spent most of this week figuring out
How i'm going to live now that i'm moving away from all my friends and family
It's crazy to think that in the middle in middle school. You're originally just some funny tf2 youtube guy
I enjoyed watching and now that's evolved into becoming one of the most consistent parts of my life
And there's a part two
Uh worse of all congrats. That's fucking awesome
Uh, they say knowing that at least one part of my life is going to stay consistent in these
Turmulous times
Uh brings me a bit of comfort plan on catching you strange whenever I can in between my civil engineering classes
Hope nothing but the best comes your way pal
Same to you
Good luck
You're gonna do just fine
Um happy anytime somebody says that they're pursuing something that they want to do
Good luck to you
BYU
That's yeah university
Um, i'm uh, what byu does have a six story underground library. Holy shit. That's a lot
That's a big library
Yeah
He did the joke he did the joke can you say joey, uh,
stinks like cheese
I just did
just shave the
Shave the first part in the last part off of that and you can
That's not yeah, I died that that is a german na5 stream reference and I don't want to be used in your
In your insulting manner for whoever you're saying that about
Joey smells just fine from what i've been told for I don't know. Yeah, I don't know. I have no idea
He could he maybe he doesn't I don't know. I have no idea. I don't know. I'm not there
I'm not there. So I can't tell you that if he does or he doesn't
I don't think probably doesn't
Moving on. Oh, are you going to up dog university?
What's up dog anyways
Just joke
No, they'll be doing that
Now I think they like came up with that in the fucking egyptian times
Uh dead medic. Thanks for the 15 bucks dead medic. Thank you playing but thank you
Thank you for playing this awful game. So I never have to I did say that it sucked didn't I?
I was like, can I say this? Can I say this?
this game sucks
I always hate saying stuff like that
because
People like that people like shit and you don't want to
You don't want to like just be like, oh, hey the thing you did that game sucks
It's like if you if you'll enjoy it, then i'm glad you do
You know, I I hate to like be that guy
does it mean like you when it boils up to that like up to your eyeballs and you're just like
What is it? What is it? What does it got on IGN? Anyway, I hate to be that guy, but it sucks
Hey, if I didn't enjoy it, I wouldn't have played it for 12 hours. Let's put it that way
I got enjoyment out of it. However, I did
Uh, but thank you dead medic
Uh, we also had
The jack for 250. Thanks for the denmark time zone stream
Yeah for sure
All right, because I went to like 12 one o'clock in the morning. I think all right. Well, welcome to denmark
greetings to denmark
Not yet, but in like a few hours
Uh, thank you also to c4g for the 250. I just logged into wow and it's free t-shirt day in there
But it ends in like 10 minutes and I can't find the shirts
What are you talking about?
is
I don't know what that means
There's free t-shirt day
they don't give
t-shirts away in world of warcraft
Oh what you don't mean in real life you mean in the game they were giving away tabards
I see. All right
That's gonna be fun. I'll be playing that
Maybe not even on stream because I don't know if i'll be able to
I'm gonna break one of those servers
Hey guys, i'm playing under
shadow more
I'm streaming it
Oh, what's what's that behind me?
What's that? Oh, is that a stampede of like 600 fucking people?
Not gonna be I wanted to do that. I wanted to do that initially, but they're not gonna have enough servers to do that
There are actual stream servers if you still trigger really
only 600
How do they all right? Let me ask you this. I I don't know much about
Warcraft streamers or warcraft players or anything. I really don't but I know that there are warcraft streamers that have thousands and thousands of viewers
How do they not break the servers?
Yeah mutton street people that have like two three four five thousand more viewers than I do
How do you not like flood a thousand two thousand people somewhere and just crush it?
Do you just kind of hide where you play?
Do you just try to go to like a low population server?
because they did that thing with um
That like instancing servers together, right?
But
I have this weird fear that if I ever wanted to stream that game if there was only like 10 to 20 servers in wild classic
and a ton of people were streaming it and
50 to 100 000 people and even not just people that are playing with like the streamers
But just people that are trying to load into the game just because they want to play wild classic
I think they severely underestimate how many people want to play that game
Severely more people want to play wild classic they want to play real actual current. Wow
How many people are still subbed to wow but a couple million?
One two three million something like that. Maybe a little bit more
I would assume at least a couple million people are going to want to do that
Aren't they like three or four hundred regular servers?
Two to three million. Yeah
any more servers
uh, but thank you
Thank you mega big gargantuan for the four dollars first try after loadout swap, that's true. I do remember that specifically
Uh, thank you. Nile orian for the six dollars. Wait, you need money
In the game. I'll start with in-game currency
How was my day weekend? It was a little stressful. I'm not gonna lie because the internet
I was supposed to stream the last two days in a row
But just couldn't because the internet was broken. It seems to be back to normal
So I kind of had a stressful weekend
I'm not gonna lie. Just got a sec. I have we got a stress pimple
Uh, but almost done with from a few days ago and then we're gonna move on to the bits from today
Shouldn't take as much longer
Uh back in thanks for the 250 great 11 plus hour stream much boomer meltdowns. Holy moly. I'm tired of the mess
Much love to you germa and chat. Love y'all
Thanks for sticking around for that the whole thing if you were there for the whole thing. That was a long stream
Future gamer. Thanks for the 250
Uh, here's my burger edit. This is so gross
I'm hungry too. You just made me hungry
Well, I mean this doesn't make me hungry
But you said burger and now I want one of those and how it's still early. It's only like 8 30
This is what happens. This is what
I lost my train of thought but over the next couple months
I'm gonna start pulling streams back
permanently
To this time that I started today
I'm gonna start streams at about 1 to 2 pm pacific maybe somewhere around 12 and 2
I'm pulling back to the streams permanently a couple hours
All right. Now get this off the screen
people are eating spaghetti for god's sake
so
2 pm pacific is probably going to be when most of them start
and the reason why
Is i've started to realize something
I've been streaming longer than ever before yeah this last year i've been live
for at least
like
Five and a half to eight hours six to seven six to eight hours almost every single stream
And what ends up happening is once you start a stream at three or four o'clock pacific
Four five six seven eight nine ten eleven pacific twelve pacific even we try we we trickle in
It that's three a.m. Eastern that's like six five six seven a.m.
uh europe
So i've been streaming for longer therefore. I don't want to keep
Half the world awake if they want to stick around and watch a stream
So pulling the streams back to like 1 2 pm pacific
Allows streams to stop before it gets to be more than 11 or 12 o'clock eastern
Eastern
I used to do that shit
Back in massachusetts. I would stream till
You know i'd start at seven o'clock. I used to start at 7 pm eastern time and that was late
Thinking about that now that was that's a night time
Seven eight nine ten eleven twelve one two
I don't really want to do that anymore
He thinks he's keeping people awake. Well i'm not keeping people awake
I just there i've gotten a lot of feedback about how
Oh, I really wish I could stick around but it's four o'clock in the morning eastern it's like oh, yeah
I guess it is
I'm i'm like in one of those really early time zones
so
It'll be something i'll trickle in. I mean this stream started at like 130
You can expect that same kind of window
Like one to two like 12 to one one to two something like that
So I like clam chowder. Yeah, it's good
Take out the clams
Add some potatoes and some corn and you got me you got me there. I'm not a big fan of clams
Fried clams are all right, but uh claims kind of freaked me out
I'm more of a corn. I'm more of i'm a fish chowder person. I like fish chowder
I don't really like clams though
but anyways
Uh marvosh mcgally. Thanks for the 250
It's always fascinating leaving the stream at 1 a.m and finding you still streaming at 9 a.m
After waking up. Hope you enjoyed this weird game. Good night
Good night again, and that takes us to today
So why don't we open that up now?
earlier today
We're gonna go back to earlier here. We are we had
Three dollars from stefunky chicken today
Look up germa scares a room full of children on youtube
What is this? Is it do I really need to look this up?
again
Germa scares a room full of children
Well, I I don't I can't see it
Where where is it?
on youtube
Somebody already has it. Is that it right there?
Germa scares a room full of children
My computer's under my desk. So I have to I had to plug my headphones in
All right, germa scares a room full of children
What where
What I what happened?
Hold on a second
Why did you do jojo poses because I didn't know what they were
I had request. I had a list
One about that green screen stream. There were
hundreds
hundreds of requests
Hundreds of them and I had on a list and it was jojo poses and I didn't know what the fuck they were
I just like okay
I guess I had to get uh chat had to help me
They had to I had to find like youtube videos to see what they even were
I don't know what a jojo pose was
And I did all of them all of them. I think I didn't I think there was two that I didn't do
I'm the jojo pose green screen guy now. I've never I have not even seen a second of that show
I couldn't if you okay if you lined up and in the lineup
All the characters from that show I wouldn't be able to tell you which one of them was jojo
That's how completely ignorant I am to this whole thing
I don't know which one of them would be the man. I don't know who it is. But anyways, that was uh,
That was a stefunky chicken. I watched it. It was a little it was a little strange
Jeff gave five community subs. We had five from jeff
earlier
Beginning of the stream. I kind of was over there and not
Paying attention. I didn't have like stream labs really in my view
But thanks with the five community subs also, holy there was a lot of money earlier that I just did not see
a lot
Uh, first of all fiti gave
fiti gave
64 dollars
They say don't mind me getting my next bit badge
Holy shit. Jeremiah
Wait, hold on. Wait, wait
Holy fucking shit. You fucking suck at this dude, man. You're so bad at this game. I didn't even know it was possible
Just kidding. I love you
Uh, it was 64 from fiti. That's a shitload of money. Thank you
and then
That's a lot
And then right after that ape 808 gave 50 bucks that you ape money for you
That's a shitload of money. That's I didn't even see these
Bala koala gave 50 as well play the test germa son. I did
I ended up doing it. That was 150 in the first
10 minutes of the stream. Thank you. The three of you for your huge amount of money. Sorry. I missed it
I just was kind of back there so I couldn't really see anything
You're a big guy. Thanks
I like when people say that
Makes me feel happy
Uh, so, uh, thank you guys
For you for you money for you. Yeah, what's what's the four? Yeah, I know it's for me
For you. Yes
Yes, I know
I
It's a meme. Oh, okay
Well, thank you
Uh, thank you to the three of you
We also had three dolls from tar alecran for the three bucks germa for the love of god
Please get a haircut my mom walked into my room and I legitimately got embarrassed because of how greasy you look great stream
Otherwise, by the way, i'm not gonna
Is what are you? This is like this is fine. What's wrong? You guys act like I fucking just crawled out of a dumpster
Yeah, just so I just like got this liquid in my hair
Am I gonna stream tomorrow? Yeah, i'm gonna try to get a hold of star and see if he wants to do terraria tomorrow
He was having computer problems though. I'll find that out tomorrow afternoon or later tonight
Uh, but thank you, uh tar alecran and
I look I look fine
Thank you though
We had uh, also, I know princess of misery from a few days ago, but also today
Thanks for the the five dollars
Five dollars
This money is for auto. He is a good boy in case my last bit message you got lost in the matrix
Here's the drawing. I wanted you to see
I think we got we I think we caught this is the one. Yeah, this is the jacked
Uh shirtless germa
It was very very very good
That's exactly what it looked like
And they also say can you adopt me by the way i'm 21, but I hope that's not an issue. I love you dad
Uh, I I don't think that's I don't think that's possible. I can't take on any children
I have trouble tying my own shoes. I don't think I could ever take care of another person
21 year olds could be useful
Well, that I get you that that was that that's like a boomer thing to say I didn't say it
Oh, wow, get rid of my son gets to be
16 so you can roll the fucking lawn
That's a boomer comment there and you guys call me the boomer
Am I gonna do a meet and greet one day? I do them all the time
I don't really
I'm not like a meat. I'm not a meet and greet kind of person though
I don't know. I just never really have been
What's my mouth?
I during like packs and places like twitchcon or any of those convention type places
I'll usually tweet something. Hey, i'm gonna be standing here for the next
Hour if you want to say hello come say hello
I don't think i'm ever gonna have one of those scenarios where i'm standing at a booth
And there's a line of people to say hello and shake my hand I don't want to do that not into that
Feels weird for me at least for me. I that this is a personal thing
I I have more
fun
Knowing that we're all here together collectively
And if I do a meet and greet
Everyone's just hanging out. We're sitting around. We're talking about stuff
I'm not really into the whole
How are you? Good to see you. Have a nice day. Hey, how are you? Good to see you stay in school
Hey, what's that? Oh, I like that pin stay in school. Eat your vegetables. Goodbye. See you later back to the next person
It's I don't I don't like it
and that's not to say there's anything there's nothing wrong with that it just personally it just
It just feels weird for me. It does
It's nothing like that. I know but i'm just saying i'm a weirdo. I'm a weird fucking person
i'm a strange person and I think
Lightning bolts just go off in my brain every second. That's the awkward talk you have with your uncle
Stay in school
How is it nothing like that? It is like that
I guess it depends on who it is, right?
Ever considered going to do a small convention having a panel where you just fool around for 30 minutes?
I've thought about it
But anytime I go to a convention
I I sort of I turn into a little bit of a recluse
I don't really read I just kind of like poke around and look at stuff and okay
Hmm
Call of duty looks all right
There's a new uh new barrel feed look at I don't I don't hey look at me
It's me turbo dot at five. Welcome to the channel. I don't I just kind of do my own thing
some people really love to go to conventions and
Turn it on
And here we go. I'm fucking here and i'm ready
I like to dial it down almost to zero when i'm just walking around a convention
Go undercover
No, but people I've had people grab me before
You know, oh, hey, I I think I know who you are and i'm like, oh, yeah
Oh, it's interesting and we just kind of hang out and talk for a minute. That's it. I'm into that
But I don't think i'm not sure I didn't want to do unless it was something I had complete in total 100 control over
I'm, not sure I'd want to do a panel
Where hey coming?
Hey, what next? What do you want to ask me? I bet you know, you know, it's weirdly enough
You don't want santa when he's the mall santa
And like people come up and they they talk to the mall santa
Like oh, what do you want for christmas?
Well, uh, I want you know, I just I just
It freaks me out a little
Because I don't think I have very many answers for like a panel
He's comparing himself to god
No, i'm comparing myself to a mall santa
That is um, I think that's a little far off than what you are describing
Oh, he's comparing himself to god
The guy with the fake beard
That's not even the real santa
no, but
to put the to long story short
i'd rather just have it be a
Interpersonal thing and not a setup thing that people have to wait in line for or
I mean, it's not
I should do a mall santa stream this year
No
Just be a mall santa
I don't know. I don't know if i'd want to do that. I don't like that
Clean your webcam. Oh, sorry. Sorry
Better. Sorry about that
Oh, we're doing bits right forgot
Uh, but that would thank you. Uh princess of misery for the five dollars. Thank you so much
Thank you
espada escalado for the 250 the plaid chad
I think that was a reference to one of the
Videos on demand that we consumed on this stream
Brush your teeth your breath smells it definitely what's going on my neck. Oh, it's just red from the the gloss from in here
Uh
the plaid chad, I don't
I don't know what the plaid chad is
plaid chad
Thank you though espada escalado. Thank you snoozing copter for the 250. Can we watch this?
Uh depends on what this is
Voice actor from banjo kazooie gives you a city tour
Wait, wait a minute. What is going on here? Where my son? Why can I not hear this?
Uh
Voice
If you want if you want to watch it
Here, I hope I I can't get it out. It's this thing sucks. I broke it earlier
All right. Let's let's put it on. I will give this like 25 seconds before I fucking don't use it anymore
So this is banjo voice actor from banjo takes you on a city tour
Of real city tour
Mine's not working. Am I still live?
What the hell? Uh, okay. Here we go
E
Is
That's good that looks really good
What's going on is the video frozen
I can't take it
Is
That was him
All right
Okay, what just happened?
That was a jacobin
Jacobin for the hundred dollars one hundred dollars
That's right hundred I don't know how this works, but here you go
Uh, you just bought a hundred dollars worth of
In twitch currency and you gave it to me. It was a hundred of them actually was ten thousand of them and that makes a hundred dollars
uh, thank you, uh jacobin for the
the test
You tested with a hundred
I probably I probably may have tested with a dollar first, but I got it and that's a fucking huge amount of money
Thank you so much
That's a lot of money
Thank you jacobin
oops
a dollar
But I you know, that's all I will keep that money. I'll use it get that knee out of here
Where were we before though?
How's the xbox?
sucks
What was on there fucking halo?
It's actually a fucking beloved franchise
Uh, thank you too. That was snoozing copter for that
Video, uh, thank you for that
liam
death axe
Thank you for the eleven dollars
liam death axe
Really appreciate it. They say you love your streams dude. They make me happy. I'm glad they do
Makes me happy to know that you're happy because that means you're having fun and that means we're all having fun here
And i'm gonna get a haircut because that one person said that it didn't look good
I don't know what that has that has nothing to do with what you just said
Thank you though
Thank you, uh grow lith for the five dollars
Growlithe this stream is the best birthday present I could have asked for thanks jeremy happy birthday
Hope you had a good one. Hope you're still celebrating depending on what time it is where you are
Happy birthday growlithe
I hope i'm saying your name right
But thank you though. Seriously
Gnarly thanks for the 250 germa wild one germa wild two germa wild three germa wild four
You got the whole sleeve in there the whole thing you got the whole like
Arm what was it arm and a face right it was like this
like this
I don't remember
You got the whole thing
uh also, thank you to
Non-descript civilian for the five bucks. Hey stir a great stream today. Hope you and germa stream sometime soon again
Maybe tomorrow if he's around shade your hair bald. I would look so awful
you know those people that
People that have like me like my like me
If I was bald I would look
That just wouldn't look right
I'm not gonna do it. I would look really really weird bald but completely bald
I would look like
Like british and not I wouldn't look I wouldn't look british. I'd look british, you know, I would look british
If I was bald head a bald fucking head
We'll see
Implying that british people are ugly
No, what i'm just saying like I would be one of those like movie british
like action movie british
not like
romantic comedy british
EU isn't awake. That's true
But thank you to uh, nondescript appreciate it
Uh star i'll talk to him tomorrow. See what he's doing. You might see terraria tomorrow because we did miss it from this past weekend
And I do want to complete the game
Meme machine, thanks for the three bucks. I fucking love germa. No, I kind of looked over there. Thanks. Let me get you right in the eyes
Link link link link link link link link. Look at the link. Look at the link. Who's talking to me?
Who's coming into my room?
Who?
No, that that that that's why I was saying to be careful. That's why I was saying to be careful
It just like it struck me. It struck me right in the back of the head
it was like
No, she was gonna come in with the dog, but like I this was in the way and it was fucking dangerous
Where's auto? He peeked in you saw him. You didn't see him in the corner
I'm more dangerous
What is going on here?
Why is everybody linking? What is this gif?
Holy shit
I think I have to do this
Oh god
What would I what would this even be wild? I don't even know what I would do with this
You can't even see
that's
Bottom one
What even is that's not even an image that's it's the hand
I would have to clean it up a little
There's another one
What what are these all these links?
I I've seen the bald one before yeah, I know i've seen it
What is what is what? Okay. Hold on a minute. First of all, let me I'm not going to click a link. That's
catbox.mo
What is that link?
Is that is that am I going to click this one?
It's safe. It's fine. It's safe catbox.mo
That's a fucking they're gonna they're gonna like grab my they're gonna get my like box
What is it?
Don't click it. It's fine. It's a popular uploading site
I don't know these things. Are my teeth fucking yellow?
Okay
That's so like it it's so fucked up that we can do that
Oh, okay. It's it. I I just got electrocuted
That was 50 bucks
By phylactery lich. Hey german today was a great stream was just wondering if you could explain how to give bits
I'd like to donate maybe next time try it with 50 cents
All right next time
Thank you for the 50 dollars phylactery lich you've given way more money than that, you know what you're doing
Uh, that's a lot. Thank you
You've given a fucking lot
I've said it before I'll say it again. Make sure you're taking care of yourself first
That's most important
50 bits not 50 dollars
5,000 bits actually
Thank you though for real
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you all of you
We've got a little bit more. We've got a few more to do
We've got tingy for 250 germ boy. This message is for chat. Make sure they listen
Hey guys, we need to cancel the carnival stream germ is going to die if he does it. Here's germ approving it. What?
the end user license agreement
Invite everybody that ever wants to go to the public it's free all the rides are free and then at exactly like 4 pm sharp
Right. Oh, yeah, there's rides and shit and at 4 pm sharp exactly
They're gonna put me into a giant fucking slingshot and slingshot my casket in the fucking atlantic ocean
Uh, that's I that's not gonna happen on the 21st
That's not gonna happen. I'm gonna be just fine. There's gonna be plenty of safety involved
Uh, but I appreciate that. Don't worry. I appreciate the concern, but i'm just fine
I'm gonna be just fine
Thank you tingy for the 250
Invader z thanks for the 250 just letting you know that you're my favorite streamer
I always look forward to seeing your content invade this for you. Oh, this is cute. Oh, we gotta put this on
Come on. Wait. No shit. I flipped it. Okay. I gotta flip it. I gotta flip it
wrong way
oops
Flip it
Flip it again
There we go. Okay. Hey, yeah. Hey, man
Hey
Is that night crawler?
No, thank you
Holy shit another 50 fucking dollars came in 50 dollars and 15 cents from if I liked your lich
that's
but that was
A piece of artwork from invader z. Thank you for that. Appreciate that and then if I liked your lich again
Just dumping more money out here
Hey, so I figured out how to give bits, but uh, how do I send a message?
I would love for you to read what I type. Uh, thanks for owning that fat suit
Well, thanks for paying for that fat suit like four times
Uh, thank you if I liked your lich for the hundred and fifteen hundred and a hundred dollars and fifteen cents
That's a lot of fucking money. You're spoiling me at this point. Thank you
Really really appreciate that
We are getting
Close to the end. I know this was a lot. This was a longer bit session
because I
That those the bits earlier for from almost a 12 hour stream that it got
Cut short because I was so tired and I just had to go to bed. I was I was barely functioning at the end of that stream
So we're uh, we're getting to the end here
Uh, thank you peanut gangster for the five dollars jerma. How's it been buddy? You're the best. It's been pretty good
today
Covered with let's see how many more dead pixels. I think we've gained a few
Some of those over in the right. I don't think we're there before
I think some of those are new god. Damn it. That's the second time i've done that
Like not that I care but seriously
It's gonna happen again
Flurry fuck did I actually break it?
No, I think it's it's fine
Uh, thank you though. That was uh, that was peanut gangster. I'm doing just fine. I'm doing good
I've been good today. It was a that was a really fun stream today. I enjoyed it immensely
Also, uh swim k thanks for the five dollars. Hey streamer made an animation about you
Not sure if you've seen it, but thanks for being a great dude
Uh, let's see
I've not seen this yet
You guys have a lot of good shit to last few days a lot of insane artwork a lot of animated videos and shit
What do I got? Uh, jerma985
All right, let's put this on screen
Let's get it on screen. Let's take a look
So what do I got? Uh jerma985 is a is a jeremy985. What's what's his name on twitch?
Yeah. Yeah. No, you had it right bit
You watched that guy
Yeah, I mean I checked his stream out every now and then like sometimes he's playing something cool or he's doing something
I'm like, oh, yeah, i'm like a fan
Oh nearly what's he doing now? Like you never heard of him before
No, never I did but what is it? Yeah, i'll check him out. Yeah right now. He's uh, he this is a cute little bird house
Don't you think so?
No, I just saw what he was doing
Uh, no, you know, man, uh, you know, let's uh, you want to like get in the lobby and like play overwatch or something, man
No, no, i'm gonna check this guy out. You're like a fan of him. Yeah. I want to see what he's doing
Yeah, no, but no, but like we should like go. I I I gotta go though like uh, hey
Do you want a free steam game? Yeah, dude free steam game. What are you talking about?
Yeah, uh, just pick a game that you want and just like don't open that page
I don't even fucking remember doing that. I remember I remember painting the bird house, but i'm making the noise
one one person said paint a bird house and it
Just kind of decided to do it favorite bands girls in my favorite band. I don't really listen to that that much anymore, but
They were my favorite
They still are I don't know why they wouldn't be still
But that was awesome. Thank you
Sometimes I forget the things that I say and do on this stream all the time
That was one of those cases
but that was from
Uh swim k. Thank you swim k for the five dollars as well
It was really really good
Uh stinky beaver. Thanks for the five dollars. I have been watching for a long time. You're the funniest boomer
I know. Hey, thank you. Yes, I try
Sometimes you swing and miss sometimes you swing and you hit a ground ball. That's a double play
And it ends the fucking inning
Uh, thank you though. Thank you to stiff funky chicken for the three bucks. Oh, I missed big bits. All right
Oh shit, they're rolling in so fast
Okay, that was a hundred and fifty dollars
from
Jacob in 13 150 bucks
Are you shitting me?
That's a lot of fucking money. That's a hundred and fifty dollars and they say I figured it out
Uh, I think you figured it out and you emptied 150 fucking dollars in one go here
Oh shit
I will try to put that to good use. Thank you so much for the 150 bucks
And on top of the other what the other the other two three hundred bucks
Figured it out. That's a lot of money
Thanks
Thank you. You're scamming tech illiterate people
Wait, you have to press the button twice. Oh, no
Yeah, are you like sure you guys sure you could do this? Like I do you like billionaires?
That's a 250 dollar
Drop from phylitary lich. That's 350 dollars today
Holy shit
Who's my debit card is spilling everywhere. Oh, no, someone catch my money. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it
uh
Monetarily sometimes when stuff I don't even know what to say. That's this is an extreme amount of money that i'm being given
and
There's nothing I could even say to show my thanks besides just say thank you for the fucking huge huge huge support
to this channel
uh
Like I said before I hopefully can put it to good use
Thank you guys
And let's not skip over the other people here
as well
we had
on top of those
Those dump trucks full of money
We also had 250 from deus morta
Hey, buddy, here's a rough proof of concept for an emote great stream tonight. I'm excited for that carnival stream
It'd be cool if you went to evo some year
Or a meetup that week and I was gonna go to evo this year
It just didn't work out
It's not kind of too much going on
I will I mean there's no reason why
I would not be there
Something like next year this one
This is just an extended version of like this
that one
Should I just fill up four slots with this and just say who gives a shit?
I have so many emotes slots that i'm just not using
Yeah, this is just not kind of a kind of a different version of that one
Where'd it go? I love how I wrote this. That's so funny
Yeah, look at this. It's like oh I I did this
I hate my computer
I'm i'm gonna i'm going back i'm going back to like fucking imac from 1995
Here we go. The arm
The arm is like green
That's
It's from the green screen
I feel like there's a curtain behind me that i'm like and here's the next part of the show
Thank you, though
I'll probably add some stuff
Why not? I might as well
Back to it though
We had that was from day's mortay
Pigeon. Thank you pigeon for the 250
Jerma will twitchcon still be happening and how will that work?
It will be my first time seeing you and I don't know how it would work. I'm looking forward to meeting you
And then they say not like this
Hey, man, i'm looking forward to meeting you. Oh, I don't hey, I can't wait to meet you. No, not like this. I
Fuck that guy
I can't wait to meet you not like this
No, um, if you're at twitchcon i'll be there probably friday and saturday. I got a lot of stuff going on
So that last weekend before that is the carnival stream
So i'm going to be pretty tired pretty busy
It's going to be kind of insane
so i'm going to be
Probably a little bit out of it
I will be there on friday and saturday, but probably not i'm not sure how much i'm going to spend on the convention floor
I think I will probably end up
Maybe a few hours at a time on the convention floor
I'll be like, hey, i'm
In front of the smite booth or whatever does that game still exist?
I think it does
But that's how you'd be able to find me. Just keep an eye on my twitter
I'll say something about where I am
And if you see me then pull me aside and say hello by all means
Uh, but thank you pigeon. Thank you pretender for the 250 your hair is amazing. Please keep it
I'm going to i'm going to and then we had garfield the monday killer
250 I swear I gave you like eight birthday bits and came
Out of garfograph retirement for them
Well garf is here. Let me tell you about garf's future endeavors. It wasn't announced officially, but my pal grant and I are producing an animated remake
Here's a sneaky garf a garf peak a peak garf. Here it is
an animated remake of garfield
A remake of garfield
No, this is this is like sonic the hedgehog
That's startling me now
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. That was another
Fucking huge amount of money
Let me go here first. Hold on
This is the remake
Is it tails in sonic?
That was garfield the monday killer
They say
Here's a sneak peek
Of the remake animated remake and then garfield also says
Okay, germ, uh, that's also for 250. I thought the links would just take you to videos, but they're files
Here's more short clip files to the files i'm producing live action segments are allowed and we're still recruiting team members
So germa is always welcome
A friend of garf is a friend always wait what what?
Hold on first of all
uh
Jacobin gave that to 250 if I lacto regula gave 250 and then jacobin gave 250 150 dollars
250 250 not two dollars and 50 cents
I'm gonna be honest. I had to message my bank and say yes
These transactions were me
It when your bank is starting to be like, uh, sir
Are you sure you want to donate five a hundred dollars to an online internet clown?
Yes, uh confirmed
Uh, that's 500 bucks and I don't even know to say that's fucking insane
You've got to be shitting me guys like what the fuck is happening right now
a phylactery lich another
dollars
They figured it out and I guess they're just they're still going
My bank is also upset that I spend so much money on twitch fight me
Holy shit guys
Do you understand that that was that's more than a thousand dollars between these two people?
um
That's a holy shit
I'm speechless. I don't even know what to say. I don't even know what to say about that. That's
Unbelievable. That's insane
Thank you for the fucking
Just just just money
just like
A shuffleboard that you just went
with hundreds on it
I feel like I just
I put down like 100 bucks on the roulette table and then he's like, oh you hit it. There you go
Damn
Thank you guys. Seriously
That means a lot. I hope you think it's worth it. I hope you can afford that
If please please only give to this channel, here's like where here's like money to this channel, right?
Like if you subscribe to the channel
Then thank you for subscribing and like five dollars a month. Thank you
But if you're if you're giving tons of money to this channel, we're talking about like here's like the scale
Here's the tiers of money, right?
I'm some I gotta put me somewhere like down here
Right. Take care of you. Make sure that's happening. And if it is then it is and I just want to make it really clear though
so
Take care of yourself. Take care of your friends your family your life your expenses your entertainment yourself
And then whatever else you have left over. That's
I will take it if you give it to me, you know what I mean?
Because sometimes people come in with a lot of money and I just
It's an incredibly like humbling experience to me
And I it's it's a lot
Terma wants it all
Whatever you got after that
you know
Myself right up here. It's like by like a peter by like a charleston shoe
And eat that and then and then and then me of course
Says the guy who only reads above the doll of bits. Yeah, but that's because
I mean look at how long the end of this stream has been
You know, the channel has grown a lot
since a year or two ago
the
It I was actually thinking about this the other day
And this is kind of the I guess we can kind of go over this
is
Once that's when the channel grows
I obviously want to be able to still interact with people and if people are donating at the end of the streams
We'll go over them, but there is a very very real
um
Scenario there are real scenarios that have to be we have to know that they exist
If the channel continues to grow, you know, the average viewership has grown by 60 or 50 or 60 percent in a year
What happens if that happens again? It might I don't know I might drop to zero. I don't know
but
I I always have to be looking at it because I don't want to have a scenario where
The end of the stream ends up being as long as the entire actual broadcast portion of the stream
I don't know. I have no idea what's going to happen
but
We always have to be kind of
Evaluating how that's doing and how that is
But I never want something like this to really disappear
but anyways
It's the end of the bits voice
I back before I even turned it on back before I I was actually I struggled with even turning on subs
And key and like I didn't want donations
I'd never turned on I never had paypal or anything like that donations. I didn't have it
I kind of I was kind of reluctant to actually have the bits and have the subs
But then it's also another scenario of it. Do you want to do twitch?
Full-time do you want to stream three or four times a week?
20 30 hours a week on twitch
Just read during a stream. I want I absolutely refuse
The reason why I refuse to do this because I think it ruins the broadcast
I think it
Uh, it takes away from what we're what we're doing here
I don't like to read anything during a stream unless of course it's something like the like this huge amount of money that's coming in
now
I find
We I have a goal here right like today
Uh, I have a goal that I want to just focus on doing this. I want to have fun. I want to
Be able to have all of my attention be on the thing that i'm currently streaming
And it's not that I don't want to
Say to those people that sub during the stream or say to people that give a hundred fucking dollars right now
We're stopping because that's a lot of money
Whoa, whoa the two you just too many too many subs just went on
Too many that was a lot that was that was 69 subs
Almost fucking 70 subs
Holy shit phylactery
That's a lot. That's that's too many subs
You should have seen
This dashboard over here. It almost broke
Holy shit
and not only that
but also
Vilemi gave a hundred bucks. This is just the money stream right now
Thank you. Vilemi. Hey jerma speaking of a thousand dollars. I'll earn my hundred thousand bit badge with this one
I'm sure you know what I want by now
Love you. Jeremy. Keep doing what you're doing and you'll go far
Where you want one of these?
Hundreds of dollars and hundreds of dollars in subs
He's gonna dive in his pile of bits in his vault
No, actually that money is going to go directly to
Uh, it's gonna go directly to the carnival
So, thank you
Or a casino. Yeah, I what I could I could double it. I could double it right now
I'll just go to the roulette table put fifteen hundred dollars on red
I got the shirt on
I would not I would never do that
ever
Never my good luck charm, but thank you phylactery. Thank you. Vilemi
you guys are just
Absolutely, just spoiling me just rotten
Thank you
I hope I can use the money that you're giving me for things that
Can come back into the channel that maybe you think are fun
Thank you
treat yourself
To a McChicken later on but uh Cosmic Moses. Thanks for the five dollars, Jeremy
I missed the last few streams because I've been in the hospital
with
Necrotizing fasciitis or fasciltis
I'm not sure what that is, but hopefully you're all right
I'm back home, but that aging video with the up music made me sad like actually sad
Uh, hopefully you're hopefully you hopefully you're good
I'm not sure what that did that exact
illness is
But no, don't worry about me that aging video. It's just it's just it was just a little joke
You know, but for you
hopefully, um
Hopefully you get you can get that squared away. I'm not sure what that uh entails but
Uh much love to you. Hopefully that
You got the right doctors on the case there
Keep your head up. That's right
Hey, I gave 10 bits and my badge didn't update I feel robbed
Is it decayed? Is there a badge for 10?
My mouth is covered
Oh
Because I keep dropping this thing into the ground
By the way, this really does look like you're looking
Through to my stream through a dirty bathroom mirror
Uh, but thank you Cosmic Moses
Uh get well soon
Thank you so much for the five dollars
Fus ro boto. Thanks for the 10 bucks. Hey, there was a glitch in the bit system
So don't believe the amount that it says there is this is 100 million bits
Uh, that would be a lot. That would be at least that would be at least 200 dollars. I can't do the math in my head quickly
That's Italy. That's like 50 100 dollars or something. It's a lot
Thanks for the 10 bucks though. Fus ro boto
Peanut gangster. Thanks for 250. You think at this point your viewers have covered the cost of the next germa rumble live action
um
One at a time, you know one by one
I have to one thing that I do have to be careful of is
Because I am financing all these things by myself
I'm not getting any
Money from any other entity, right? It's just like the money that I get from twitch
Is this money that i'm using right? But I do have to be careful and I don't really ever want
any um
Outside sponsorships i've talked about it before with people at twitch and people that are involved in this particular project
It's it kind of it muddies it a little
What about fruit?
I lost that sponsorship
I hate I hate a bag of combos on camera and they ditched me
Like what ate a bag of combos? Yeah, they'll 645 calories a bag and then made it a processed fake cheese
What's the problem?
Whatever get a basket robin sponsorship. No, how much money did I get from the door cube?
Uh, I hadn't I had an affiliate code with door cube and it was used three times
so I made um
14 cents
nine cents after taxes
Hey pigeon. Thanks for the 250 because I had to donate for you to answer it
Oh, I see. I see. I see that's what they're not like this before. Okay
I'll be a twitch con though
You'll see me. You will see me at twitchcon
Gonder lane. Thanks for the 250. Will you ever come back to the east coast? We miss you cox is no good
So come back to your comfy boston basement where you grew famous
Well, um fiber is being laid all over vegas right now
So I will have fiber over the next I will be on a fiber optic network
in
Three four months maybe it depends either late 2019 or early 2020
I will have a one thousand one thousand symmetrical fiber line
before
My 35th birthday way before that like six months tops
And the thing with fiber is it's not coax
So all this bullshit all these problems that all these awful internet issues
Do not exist on fiber
There is no
Oh somebody turned on their microwave and kicked everybody off the network
Somebody had an unscrewed cable coax that there's no noise ingress like that with fiber
So
And I say that now but it's gonna be a thousand upload. I have 30 up right now. It's going to be one
Thousand through a fiber optic line
It would be I would just be cursed. It would be me
The problem would be me at that point if I cannot have a stable connection with fiber
A thousand fucking upload then it's me
It has to be
When's the carnival stream september 21st?
Somewhere in the early afternoon eastern time, but no I have no plans on moving back to the east coast
I'll be on the west coast for at least
Whether it's somewhere in vegas
over the night over the years or
I don't know. I want to be on the west coast
I'll be in vegas for a while though. That's for certain
That random guy cursed me. Yeah, I didn't buy the I gotta buy that fiber curse removal. You're right
fiber
We also had
All that money came in the 69 subs from phylactery
three dollars from cyan tf2
Holy shit. This man gave 500 bits. That's insane
If you decide to give me a cent
Then it's as appreciated as anything else
If you decide to give this channel any money
It's not just a thousand dollars of somebody donating
Or supporting subs too, there's a lot of consistent subs on this channel more than I ever could have possibly imagined
so it's not just
The people dropping the 500 bucks as much as that's amazing and insane for me
It's not just that so don't feel like oh shit. I only gave three dollars today. Fuck
No, that's I don't that I do not feel that that's I do not feel that way
Okay
There's no cent equivalent of a bit. I think it's 25 cents minimum, right?
Has to prevent people from just doing one cent spam with the thing
Right, so you could just have the chat be filled with the symbol
And speaking of subs, there's another five from kazi
Kazi 101 five community subs. Thank you. Kazi five more subs from the subway
No, for real. You guys are too good
You guys are too good to me
Just glad you still think that it's fun to be in the channel and i'm glad you still this many years later
I've been doing this for a long time
A lot of times when people do this kind of shit for a long fucking time
You know, wow, it's
Hey, here we go. What? Well, I started youtube um eight plus years ago. Whoa, this is a roller coaster
This is so cool
Five years six years. Oh, okay. I have seven years. Uh
This is you I you guys are still fucking doing this you guys are still going
and I don't know I i'm
Shocked that i've still been able to do this
It's been a long fucking time
So take things like the carnival stream
As my way of the kind of saying thank you and hopefully then we can make have a fun time. It doesn't matter
If that stream
Is oh how much was that stream expensive who gives a shit?
Who gives a shit?
You know what I mean?
It's it's worth doing
I mean that
He's getting better with age
We'll see
But we're reaching the end here
we had a phylactery lich gave five dollars
and they say
Seriously, I give all these bits and subs because you're my primary entertainment
And I never want to stop watching your funny ass streams involved 69 subs was for the meme
But next time i'll do 420 not tonight though because we're about to leave
sub
I think that's we're not doing that tonight though. Hold on to that one
Because that's fucking like thousands of dollars
Thank you, though. I really appreciate that. I'm humbled to be your primary entertainment
That would like kill the chat it would be like
It would just be flying by
But thank you
I really appreciate it
Pigeon, thank you for the 250 and the 250 right on top of it. How the hell do you how the hell do you do your budget?
thankfully
Uh, there's other people involved that can help with that if you talk about the carnival thing
I have things that I specifically want
That there are two companies involved. So I have told that we on paper and I spent we I spent a long time
On this remember I told you i've been dialing streams back
My streams have been
Instead of three or four times a week. It's like two or three times a week now
And I obviously want to stay by the book twitch actually keeps a really good track of what's coming out and coming in
So it's not just oh i have to go through this and see if they they keep it a pretty good track of it. So
That voice thing. Yeah, that's
That's old news
And it's fucking still sounds good
It still sounds fucking just as good as it did when I made it fucking 12 15 years ago
Yeah, it was like that's like more than 10 15 years old
And I still got it
Was that before I played tf2? That was that was like before I went to college
That was a long time ago
Why does the profile say that you're a teenager adult male senior male and old male? No, that's like what i'm capable of
That's what i'm capable of
That's what i'm capable of that's what i'm capable of
That is what i'm capable of and if you don't think that that was every entire spectrum of age
It was anyways guys
That's all the voices. He has that's not true. I got like second. I have like at least five or six of us
I got at least 10 voices 12
Uh, that's going to be the time here
I did not expect this to be an eight-hour stream, but it is
We've done some long ones recently. This is another long one. I'm going to see what star is up to tomorrow
And maybe there'll be terraria tomorrow if his computer is working. That was a problem before
I'm gonna go take a shower. I'm gonna get some food and i'm gonna get some rest
Thank you everybody. Thank you for fucking joining me. Hope you enjoyed this stream. I had a blast playing
It was definitely worth playing for sure
Right at the very end. Oh, I could do the outro screen. Come on
Uh dia beats. Thanks for the three dollars germa
Thanks for all the content you provide over the years
I feel like I can speak with the whole chat here when I say you've done wonders through this site
Sorry for the internet problems that really sucks. Nonetheless, we'll be here through it all
Thank you the internet is just in the united states
Unfortunately, you kind of just throw dice in the air if you're going to have a good stable upload connection
That's just the way it works. It's like that everywhere
Some people don't have a problem at all. Some people have more problems than they can
Deal with and it sucks
Because having unstable internet, it's one thing dropping like a thousand two thousand frames of stream is pretty normal
But thank you
And finally garfy the monday killer germ the worm. You didn't click on garf's links. Oh shit in the other right?
Yeah, you already did
Garf doesn't come around out of retirement very often
Uh garf made a more palatable trailer exclusive to you
All right
The film allows live action bits and we'd love to have you on board the crew since you're recruiting since we're recruiting youtubers
Consider this a pitch to you in a trailer for the audience
Here we go
It's a trailer
Are you like a clown costume?
Worry about it. He was here last night. He forced me to put on these clothes and then flew away without saying anything
I'm fine. It's fine
I'm fine
It's funny
It's over
That was pretty great. Actually
Thank you garfield
Uh, good luck to you
If I have time, maybe I would throw in a few lines or something
The only problem is i'm not going to have very much time until after september
Because of these a couple of streams, especially the carnival
Looked really interesting though
Pigeon thanks for the 250
Derma, I keep fucking up my bits
I keep fucking up my bits
uh
Ha lulu drew this
Another fucking awesome piece of artwork
This is awesome
Oh, no, he said the f-word. Oh, no, he said the f-word
Look at those eyes
I feel like I could swim in those eyes. They're like pools
shiny glistening eyes
Thank you. Uh, ha lulu and thank you pigeon for bringing it to my attention
This is great
Complimenting yourself
No, i'm complimenting a picture
That was drone of myself
Uh, it's not me. That's that's a that's a picture that was drone of me
Nice work for real
That's my time
I will see you guys all tomorrow
Whatever it is we do we do
I have not decided yet. There are plenty of options
Have a fantastic rest of your night. It's still fairly early for some of us
Take care. See you tomorrow
And I forgot the fucking credits. No, I didn't
Here we go. Here they come
It's gonna be a lot considering the 100 plus community subs that came through here. Oh, man
Where do you recommend games? Uh, go to the discord. There's a channel in the discord that is for recommendations specifically
I check it probably once a week
This is potentially hundreds of subs here
Read them out loud. I can't there's too many
But where do we demand games?
Uh to to my face and then i'll tell you I don't I I don't get demanded I get recommended
Play battle for bikini bottom when it gets a remaster. They're remastering that game
Avery dropped dead. Thanks for the five dollars. Hey, I also fucked up my bits
Please say hi to me and look at my cute dog dog's name is wheezy
Beagle let's take a look at this cute dog on stream. Thank you for the five dollars though. Avery
Is it uh, is it beagle? Yeah
Look at this dog. I want to put it behind the credits
Look at this dog
Sleepy dog. I have to do that voice whenever I see a dog. It's important
He's got a special plank
No, thank you
Dog looks comfy
I do cutesy. I think you have to do a cutesy voice at an animal
It could be a dog. It could be a squirrel. I do that shit to lizards
Thank you the sandwich
for one for 250
Hey, uh
Germ hey germanium here's some bits just to fill the air while the credits roll. Hey, thank you
The sandwich for one for you 250
Hey, thanks. Hey, thanks
Birds, I want a bird
I want one of those big ass birds, but they're really loud. Aren't they? I wouldn't be able to stream
If I had a huge bird back here, wouldn't it just be like?
All day
That's a vulture. Well, you know what I mean?
All right guys
Take care. See you tomorrow
Probably going to be starting at the normal time tomorrow somewhere around three and four pm pacific
Take care. See you soon