All right, so let me... yeah, we can hop in Red Dead. We'll jump in Red Dead for like an hour or two,
so I can kind of prepare myself for tomorrow.
Tomorrow being the multiplayer that I'm going to try. It seems any fun. Red Dead 2
incoming. What do you mean incoming? Red Dead 2, here it comes! Red Ted 2, Red Ted...
Red... why can I not say words? I need to like eat something. Holy shit. If you stuck around
just for... I was gonna say insane aquarium. For... I really do need to like eat something,
holy shit. I'm like floating by right now for some reason. If you're there for Zoo Tycoon 2,
thanks for coming out. Hopefully you stop by tomorrow when we play Red Dead online.
I'll see you soon. If not, when... I'll see you whenever you come back.
Make the entire map of Red Dead 2 in Zoo Tycoon. Well that is... that is just... that just ain't
gonna happen. Let me boot up my PlayStation 4 here. Shouldn't take me more than a minute
or so to get this ready. Red Dead Redemption. Jesus, what a lazy guy.
Do you know how long it takes to do stuff like that? It would take me like a year to do
that. Let me get this going. Yeah, we'll go... we'll try to get like another couple story missions
done just so I can kind of familiarize myself with it again. Am I gonna do any conventions
this year? Oh, no. Not for the... you mean 2019? Yeah, but I'm... what? What is this?
Why is this here? What's this for? I just turned on the PlayStation and this is what was
here. I don't know why. Is this the last thing that you saw from two nights ago? Play it.
I just put it on Red Dead. One more match. Just make Red Dead characters.
That's gonna take me like seven hours. I kind of want to... no, I'm not gonna make
Red Dead characters. I'm gonna press the wrong button. No, no, no. It's gonna take... wait,
like, I... let's play... we're gonna play Red Dead. Don't worry. You'll see this again sooner
than you did the last time. One match. Maybe I might... okay, we'll end on one match. How's that
sound? I do want to get some Red Dead in though. Yeah. We'll do that. Okay. Because
that's gonna take me to make characters now that's up here. Organize community rumbles.
Um, the reason why I don't really do them that often is because it kind of loses its...
the reason why it's so special to me and to the community in general is because I put a
shitload of time into making a ton of characters and the kinds of... there needs to be enough...
Can I just play it now? No. There needs to be enough time as to pass for there to be new
characters to make. Because sure, I could just make a bunch of people from before, from older
games and throw them in or older rumbles, but I like the idea of each one having a
significant amount of people that were, you know, new ideas, new characters, new interesting
things over the course of six to 12 months. And eventually transitioning away from the video
game. Because as a lot of you guys know, I desperately want to make another live one,
and but this time actually do it live. I've hinted at it, talked about it a little bit.
Like do a live rumble, like for real, like an actual live German Rumble 2 live
stream. Live CGI rumble? No, it would be... the resources that are available
on this side of the country, it wouldn't be that hard of a thing to do.
All right, what was the last thing I did? I don't know if it's been so long.
Who's gonna be on the... he's gonna be at that rumble? I mean that's... I'm not gonna...
why would I tell you that? I can't like tell you all the secrets,
you keep on... am I gonna tell you every single secret?
All right, let's open up the map and see where the hell we are. So I gotta go...
here's Micah, which I've not done. Still have not completed that mission,
and I don't think I'm gonna. This is where we left off.
Oh, should I just do it? No, I don't want to do that.
Let's go... is there stagecoach over here? Trapper post office stagecoach.
Let's ride the stagecoach, Bill. Yeah, this is single player.
I don't have access to the multiplayer until tomorrow,
so I just wanted to familiarize myself with the game again,
because then tomorrow I'm gonna stream the multiplayer.
Is it familiar yet? You could say that, yeah.
It only took 10 seconds to get there, so now we could go across this way.
My horse is in desperate need of yummy cakes.
All right, let's go. The story gets real good, it's worth finishing.
Yeah, that's what I've heard. I think when we stopped that was 40-50% of the way done.
Is that just about the 40% mark? You gonna finish LA?
Nah, I'm not gonna finish LA Noir. We talked about LA Noir, but it's not.
LA Noir is a really, really great game, but I could...
Did I do that? I didn't do that, did I? I didn't do anything.
What did I do? I didn't do anything. Do you want to overwrite the data?
I guess. Is that horse better than this horse?
Wait, what? Well, this is a good horse, apparently.
I mean, that is... It's not stealing if the guy's dead.
In the Wild West, that is. You gonna let me on?
Yeah, this is gonna work. It's also a murderer, where the horse is a murderer.
I'm not a murderer. Not yet, at least. Not now.
You're gonna let me... Okay.
I kind of need to take this horse somewhere, though, don't I?
Follow me. Is there a stable here?
Because if there is, then I could at least stable this one.
Hey there, mister. Can you only have four?
I think you can only have three or four horses here. Something like that.
This thing is fast. All right, cool.
Uh, how much money do I have? Because I can pay my bounty.
But is there a stable? What did I just do?
What did I do? Oh, I ran a guy over!
I ran that guy over! What?
Oh, come on. No, no! Get away from me!
I forgot how to fucking melee fight.
Don't always check your blind spots. I just slid into that dude.
He slid into that guy's DMs.
I'm gonna pay the bounty.
I don't even know what happened. That guy was like a squirrel.
I road killed a guy and I didn't even know he was there.
Was he sleeping on the ground? Look at that.
That's what every criminal says.
Well, I'm not a criminal. I was in the wrong place at the wrong time.
I wasn't even going that fast either.
All right, here we go. I'm gonna go pay the bounty.
I'm gonna go take care of everything. Go to the story mission.
Cool. Would you like you to stable this horse?
There we go. All right, I gotta name it.
So I got horsebag sonic, whisper thunder, and then...
Actually, this horse is way better. This horse is fucking 10 times better.
All right. Who am I taking out?
This is... No, actually, I want to...
Give me a whisper.
Wow. Name him skateboard. For what?
Is that a lot?
All right, let's do services.
Horse care package.
Name him something. Epic gamer. What do I mean?
All right, let's pay the bounty. Take the stagecoach.
And to get the absolute hell out of here.
How many bits do you have to spend to name him skateboard?
Get out of my fucking way.
Everyone just gets in my way.
No, I'm about...
How do I say please take me and take me to the jail?
Where's the please take me to jail?
That guy just spun around in a circle on the bridge.
Look, I'm here. I'm ready to take everything.
I'll be held accountable for all of it.
Did I just die? What?
No, okay. I was gonna say how the fuck.
I thought he instantly killed me.
So did I pay? You don't lose anything by going to jail, do you?
Does that not include my bounty? Did my bounty paid?
My guns are gone or not?
No, I'm good. I got all my weapons.
Springfield rifle. Bolt action rifle.
Yeah, please don't scare me like that.
If I run another person over.
All right, I need to go to the stagecoach.
Stagecoach, let's go.
And then I need to go from here to here.
So we gotta go to Rhodes.
Rhodes Ranch.
I probably could... I need to turn it up a little bit.
There we are.
That probably sounds a little better.
So don't steal it.
I haven't played the game in like almost two weeks.
So I'm sorry. I like bumped into a guy.
I bumped into another guy.
For the love of God, just go there yourself.
Where's the fence?
He's up here.
Is there another wagon fence?
This is so far away.
This is so fucking far away.
You just spend the whole time breaking laws.
I need to wait till this is gone.
What the hell was that?
Coyotes?
Going after a rabbit?
Yeah, that is what it is.
No, what if I bring this back?
I'm gonna bring this back to the guy that I just took it from.
I found it.
Look, it's right here.
I just wanted to say good morning.
All right.
Your stagecoach is back.
Let's go ahead and take a ride.
Rhodes Ranch.
See, where's the...
I crashed into a tree joke.
There... I didn't...
There is no crash into tree joke.
I already fell down a cliff.
Does that count?
I'm not sure.
All right, let's do it.
Time for a mission.
It only took us 25 minutes.
A little less than that.
Not very much.
Talk to Bill.
Come on, that's classic.
I didn't do it this time.
The horse did.
Cartoon Jerma crashes into a tree.
Well, it's a really good thing somebody said that.
Thank you for saying that because
my microphone was not correctly synced up.
Now it is.
It was almost a full millisecond behind.
Or ahead, actually.
How's it now? Let's see.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Should be good.
What is that guy?
I couldn't watch with the delay.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't realize it.
We just came from a PC game, so...
For my capture card, it's a 650 millisecond delay.
So I have to offset the mic, so...
Sorry about that.
Hey, Bill!
What can I do for you?
What is it?
We got something cooking.
You might be interested in.
Am I gonna like the sound of this?
Been cooking since Horseshoe.
But you went and kicked up all that commotion in Valentine.
Now we was preparing to rob the bank there
until you got involved in all that nonsense and...
I don't know.
I just feel like it's unfinished business.
That wasn't my fault.
It was just one of them things.
How come every time I get in trouble,
I'm called a fool and an idiot?
But when you get in trouble,
oh, it's just one of them things.
It's a good point, Arthur.
A very good point.
Well, what do y'all want me to do?
Hit the goddamn bank with us.
I love my Nerf bullet.
My backup Nerf bullets.
You really think it's worth going back there?
Four of us can hit the bank easy.
Did I make that joke two weeks ago?
I might have.
We linger.
Did I say that two weeks ago?
Just local boys get rounded up and pressed into action.
Two weeks ago.
If we go in quick and quiet,
we can hit it just fine.
If there's four of us, I mean.
Y'all think it's worth the risk.
It's a bank, Arthur.
So is the take good, according to the fella I met?
Yes.
It's the end of the stock sales.
Plenty of money and plenty of people milling about.
OK, I suppose we're taking a look at least.
I'm going to be performing.
I better go get old material as usual.
OK, so Bill, this better be good.
It is good.
We put a lot of research into this one.
I hope so, Mr. Morgan.
Her stress?
That man.
The daughter?
Thomas Downs?
Apparently, he's dead.
Dead?
Remember my clothes.
Oh, he didn't seem very well.
His wife.
I believe he has a wife and child.
We all change?
She will assume the debt, of course.
Of course.
Then you can head up there and collect.
We lent them a lot of money.
OK.
Gentlemen, let's go rob ourselves a bank.
What's the plan there?
I remember my clothes.
We're going to send Karen on in ahead as a distraction.
Then we're just going to rush on in afterwards.
Just a small bank in a little town.
Nothing that big in way of security.
We just need to bring you along as an insurance policy.
He's read the evidential to a sequel.
It is a prequel.
You ever see Star Wars the Phantom Menace?
It's like that.
There's only one difference though.
It does not take place in Star Wars.
Tell me again about this big can't go wrong family horse.
Oh, it can go wrong.
Anything can.
Once the shooting starts.
Well, that's reassuring.
Like I said, we'll see how it looks.
If we can get in all right, we'll send this Jones into the bank.
Yep.
They won't recognize her.
I'll show you boys how it's done.
What are you thinking this time?
I don't know.
That wasn't even my fault.
Fellers always like a lost little girl.
But nobody plays a drunken harlot boy like me.
It should work.
Once he's got them distracted, we'll move in.
When I was scouting the place the other day.
There was only a couple of guards.
We deal with them and any customers who are feeling brave.
And you always fancy yourself as the Bolt Man, right Arthur?
It was inconsiderate.
It was rude.
I see why you brought me.
It was untrue.
Hey, I'm more than willing.
It was very rude.
Best I do it.
Oh, and did Doug tell you I've also been cooking up some deals with them gray boys?
What?
No.
Banned that guy.
Nobody gets banned for making a reference to Star Wars.
I'm out there putting in the work same as you.
I've been drinking with them a couple of times now.
Let's turn and run me off the road.
It seems you're looking for some extra security.
Yeah, I'm sure they are.
Could be something in it for us.
Well, just be smart about it.
Got a lot of irons in that fire right now.
You mean Star Trek?
Yes.
I know, Morgan.
Well, Star Trek.
Can't believe if you got me going back to Valentine.
Don't tell me it ain't hurt you leaving that bank behind.
What do I think about sand?
Not really.
Work in town and not hit the bank?
The desert?
The beach?
That's counter empathetic.
I guess we went a bit beyond working it.
We shot the place to hell.
You did, Morgan.
Not me.
I played it cool up there.
A couple of punch-ups.
Dealt with some old Driscolls.
What do I think about sands from Undertale?
Like I said, you mess up.
It's just one of them things.
I mean, it's a character in the game.
Well, Bill, I don't know what to tell you.
Surprised you ain't already ripped me about that dynamite yet.
This is a pretty great loading screen.
Yeah, it is.
One mistake.
And I'll never live it down.
That looks really, really cool.
Look at that.
What do you think?
Pet on the back?
It's beautiful.
A medal?
Just know, I got the lead on this one.
We'll see about that once things get going.
Not paying attention is a bingo for me.
So, thinking this through?
Are you paying attention?
You rob Cornwall's train?
Or shoot a heap of his men in Valentine?
I'm his stage coach.
This is just dawning on you now.
And now, we're going back to the one place he knew where to find us.
That's the genius of it.
Folk never look at what's right under their nose.
I know what's going to happen here.
I ain't sure that's always true.
What's happened to you?
You're getting real nervy in your old age.
Last few weeks happened.
Forget about Cornwall.
Forget about Bill.
He can't have many men left at this point.
Got a bit hairy in that barn.
But we all walked away fine from that.
You don't walk away much.
If four of us could deal with them in Valentine.
And four of us could deal with them after the coach robbery.
I ain't too worried.
If you say so.
Quit messing with the cord.
Running into a rough patch here for some reason.
Don't celebrate too early.
Yeah, I don't really.
This music is very appropriate for the tension.
Maybe if your camera was off it would work a little more smoothly.
I don't have my camera.
What do you mean camera?
Up the contrast a little bit.
I don't think the stream is going to die.
I think we may have just hit a little bit of a rough patch.
Famous, famous last words.
How come they're not talking anymore?
Next frame please.
Gentlemen, here we are.
Okay, get ready.
All right, you ready?
Let's do it.
I am prepared.
Okay, go to work.
Of course.
All right, keep it cool and follow me, fellas.
Powerpoint Red Dead.
Oh, we're good, we're good, we're good.
We never decided.
Is it lost little girl you want or the drunk in Harlem?
I think the drunk in Harlem.
Of course, you know I like the Harlem.
You're the only one.
No, it must have been the green screen man.
You're a bunch of filthy sinners and the heartbreakers.
Now where is he?
That's pretty good.
He's pretty good.
Good luck, gentlemen.
We got this.
I've never seen anyone not pick the Harlem.
I know.
I'm 100% certain that every stream you've ever seen do this.
It was okay.
We're going.
Huh, hold on.
Wait till she's gone real dead.
Until he lands.
Okay.
Am I ready to burst through here?
There we go.
Nobody move.
Get on the ground.
Good.
Nice toss.
Elizabeth.
Ammo.
Open that vault right now.
Open it.
Is he pretending?
I'm just fucking with his concentration.
I'm making him start over again.
He's got it, right?
Open the safe.
Am I actually resetting him?
That was...
I didn't do that.
He did.
All right.
Here we go.
I'm in.
Someone come make sure the chute behaves himself in here.
What do we need?
What are we looking for?
Open the lock boxes now.
Wait, if he doesn't know, we can't hold this against him.
This guy's been hitting the head so many times he's gonna forget who he is.
Crack them or blow them.
Keep an eye out.
I'll be as quick as I can.
Crack?
Crack the safes.
Yeah, I think I should be able to crack these.
Why did I do that?
I should have blown one.
But you better be quick.
I should have blown him up.
I should have blown the...
Oh, no.
I should have blown him up.
I almost got one.
I almost have one.
Okay, I got one.
Only five more to go.
That's so much money.
Okay, hold on.
I gotta actually pay attention.
Come on.
Find it, Arthur.
That was quick.
That was three grand.
How much is in this one?
Three grand in every one of them?
Four thousand.
Holy shit.
I had it.
I'm trying to go too fast.
You motherfucker open.
Right here, right here, right here, right here, right here.
Right here.
Come on.
I only have two more to get.
I got the first one quick.
Here it comes.
Come on.
Right here.
I went through the whole thing.
Fuck.
Two.
Here's three.
Right here.
I just had it.
It was 60.
Was it 60?
Yep.
Blow up the last two.
No, I got it.
I got it.
I don't need to explode anything.
I just missed it.
It was right there.
It's right here.
Right here.
Got it.
Told you.
Got them all.
That's it, right?
Is it as simple as it seems?
Fairly.
Fairly simple.
How are we doing on frames?
Did you kill the bank teller?
You did.
You got hit in the head one too many times.
You didn't have anything on him either.
I bet you shouldn't have hit him three or four times.
Frames are good.
Yeah.
I think we just ran into a rough patch.
I don't think it's an actual issue.
Speaking very, very cautiously on that.
But are we just calmly walking out of here?
Someone's robbed the bank.
All right, we've got to go.
Lawmen.
My horse just got shot.
That's not good.
Dead or alive.
Out, out, out.
Let's go.
Everybody has to live.
I'm going to take a different weapon out here.
Yeah, repeater.
Maybe I won't need to shoot anybody.
It might be a good idea to get out of here.
Pretty swell, actually.
That's pretty great.
Maybe I'll have to get out though.
Because I don't want to go too far ahead of everybody.
I forgot how to use that on.
I forgot how it worked.
I had to hit R1.
Remember now.
I can't wait to play this online.
This is probably something fun.
Has anybody watched any of the online?
How does it...
Is it fun or is it dumb?
Good shot.
I hope I can get it.
It looks okay from what's there now.
It actually has a story.
That's cool.
It still is the beta.
That's...
Yeah, that's great.
Very interested in how it's doing right now.
Because GTA Online was cool, but...
Thanks.
I think we lost him.
Thank you, gentlemen.
I'm so glad that didn't happen.
Because I would have had to do the whole thing over again.
And I would have been really upset.
I would have gone...
What? Oh, no!
I had to do the whole thing again?
What the fuck?
Do you know what?
I was just messing around.
Holy shit.
It's taking this guy two weeks to get through chapter two.
I haven't played it.
I haven't really put any time into it.
I've been too busy with other stuff.
Too many other things going on.
Ride to the ranch.
It's still in Anor Londo, I see.
God, I miss that game.
I miss souls.
I really do.
Sekiro is going to be so much fun.
It looks great.
Have I played Bloodborne before?
You are referencing probably my favorite single player video game ever made.
Did somebody say Bloodborne?
Oh, now you're going to get him started.
Now he's not going to stop talking about it.
Here we go.
Now it starts.
He's not going to stop.
Yeah, I have not beaten it on stream.
That is true.
But I'm excited for a lot of things, actually.
Like I told you guys earlier in the stream,
I want pretty much every other weekend or so,
or once a month,
to not only do new games that are coming out,
but more stuff that you've never seen before.
From me, at least.
There's another thing coming up at the end of December.
That should be a lot of fun.
Tons of games coming out at the beginning of the year.
I'm fucking, it's going to be a lot of fun.
I can't wait.
Hey, my fault about the way the world is.
He didn't have a choice.
You're playing the Lego games?
He was good and he did good.
There wasn't no choice in that.
And you was good as killed him yourself.
And don't kid yourself.
You had a choice.
You speak as if killing were something I cared about.
You ever wonder about eternity?
You should.
I hope it's hot and terrible, Mrs. Downs.
Otherwise, I'll feel I've been sold a false bill of goods.
Now, please give me that money.
Stop hogging the internet.
Well, we just dropped like two or three thousand frames five minutes ago.
So I'm not sure why we're having internet issues at the moment.
Well, maybe when your mother's finished mourning your father,
I'll keep her in black on your behalf.
You think on that point.
Well, maybe you shall, sir.
And maybe other events will transpire.
You best stick to them books because mark my words on this.
Vengeance is an idiot's game.
Ah, Mrs. Downs, thank you for your punctuality.
It's next to godliness, isn't it?
That's clean.
Lego Island.
I'll have to take your word on that.
Good day.
Yeah, I told you I was going to play Lego Island.
I was going to build a computer to play Lego Island.
I got a Raspberry Pi that you can't even install it on there.
I was going to just build a fucking computer.
You don't like my Arthur?
I think I just put random clothes on him.
Christmas dinner cooking stream.
Uh, no.
Ten.
Did I just get three grand?
Holy shit.
The camp just took ten thousand dollars from that.
I've been donating hundreds of dollars a week to the camp.
About you playing that zoo game.
I was.
And then after like four hours or so, it was.
We kind of saw the things that we wanted to see.
So I have to go do Mike and now, don't I?
I actually have to do this.
All right, let me see.
I think I have all the upgrades though, don't I?
I'm 95% certain that I have the upgrades.
Everyone's calling my name.
I'm busy.
I got places to be, man.
I'm going to eat some food.
This is a sexy Santa cosplay.
I didn't say that.
Somebody, I didn't say that.
Somebody said that.
Somebody else said that.
I was just responding to somebody in chat.
How are we all doing?
No, I don't play dominoes.
I don't know how to play dominoes.
So let's do some cleaning here.
Shave my face.
Maybe.
Just a little.
Maybe just a tad.
No, no, no.
Just give him a long chin.
No, I want to keep the whole thing.
How do I grow more hair?
Is there a way?
Is there a way for me just to have the beard go all the way to 10?
Hair tonic?
Just drink hair tonic?
No, you put hair tonic on.
You don't consume it.
Take some ammo.
You drink, yeah, I drink the tonic.
It stops you from getting hairy insides.
I've been doing it so wrong this whole time.
All right.
Micah, are you the last mission?
No, you know what?
No, fuck Micah.
Let's go do the other side mission thing.
Let's do it.
Let's go do this.
Where is it on the map here?
What the hell is it?
Was it even on the map?
Maybe it wasn't.
And I can donate this.
I thought I had another mission to do.
I guess not.
I'll do it.
How long is the stream going to be?
Uh, maybe like another...
I'll do like one more mission and then we'll probably call it a night.
I'm going to start fairly early, I think, tomorrow.
Because I want to get started with the online.
WWE, yeah, we'll do one match.
We'll do one match.
Dad lied to us.
No, I told you I'm going to do one.
I'll do one match.
Upgrade?
I have all the upgrades already.
Unless they changed.
Let me take a look.
Make Arthur Morgan in WWE.
Yeah, I usually kill old dress schools too.
We ain't in the revenge business.
It don't keep you fed.
Just watch me.
Buy the mech suit upgrade.
$32 returned.
All right, let's take a look at the ledger.
I don't know if I...
Yeah, I can restock.
I'll restock.
Why not?
Uh, bought everything else.
Buy that.
I bought everything else.
I have the boat too.
I really needed that, didn't I?
Upgrade everything?
I already did.
Did you buy fast travel?
Uh, I think I do because I upgraded his tent, right?
Shave his head.
All right, let's go.
I'm gonna go do the mica mission
because it's there and I have to do it at some point.
Might as well just get it done.
We'll do the mica mission and then we'll do a...
We'll do a match.
We'll do another, like, backstage brawl in WWE.
I'm thinking about who I'd want to be.
Fast travel.
Do I have to go to his tent to fast travel?
What?
I didn't even pay attention to how to do that
because I didn't want to use it originally, so...
Let's see, where am I going here?
We're going to...
Strawberry.
It's behind his tent.
Okay.
Well, where the hell is Dutch's...
This is the new area we've moved away, so...
Is it behind my tent or is it behind Dutch's tent?
In my tent.
Hmm, on the side?
It's the map on the side.
It's shaving kit, clothing change, fast travel.
There it is.
Well, apparently not anymore.
There we go.
All right, strawberry.
Does this cost money?
No, it doesn't.
That's cool.
Goodbye.
That just costed me some sweet vista views.
Favorite member of Dutch's gang.
Uh, Jose is cool.
Fast travel, more like...
You know what I'm saying?
All right, Micah, let's go.
Don't make me regret this.
Every time you do a mission with Micah,
you get a $300 bounty somewhere.
That's why I've avoided it for so long.
I don't want to go do a bunch of shit and
get in a lot of trouble and have to pay somebody $300.
It's like down here.
Oh, there he is.
Arthur, what the fuck was that?
All right, I need to refill one of these cubes.
Have another one.
All right, see?
Everything's fine.
All right, Micah, what do you want?
What do you need?
What do you want me to do?
Let us begin.
Hey, Arthur.
Good to see you.
Why, you want rescuing again, do you?
No.
Why, is Arthur apologizing to the horse for feeding it to you?
I think he's apologizing for running the horse off the cliff and killing it.
Like you going off scouting and handing up in jail?
Dutch said you was a big shadow cast by a tiny tree.
I don't even know what that means.
I thought you was a tough boy.
Not one of those gentlemen trying to protect his riding clothes.
I just know whenever things get real,
you turn yellow and lose your head.
Yellow?
Sure seems that way.
So I guess you won't be riding with me to rob the banking coach.
I heard one of the old Driscoll boys yapping about it while I was inside.
You and me?
Do robbery?
That's what I said, didn't I?
Am I a tough boy?
No.
I'm a solid boy.
Come on.
Robbing another bank.
Can't exactly stay in town now, can I?
Like I told you, I ain't going back to Dutch
without a peace offering.
So what's the deal with this coach?
What do you mean?
Comes through about this time every day.
Like I said, if we were robbing a bank,
we'd be really far away from it right now.
How many men?
Guns.
Right.
I've been serious.
You'll be fine.
Banks been hiring every trigger man they can get of late.
The meaner, the better.
I'm afraid too much.
Compact and solid.
Forgive me if I ain't wholly faithful in something an old Driscoll told you.
When you was half drunk in a jail cell.
No, I'm not dense.
He kept yapping about it, saying how they've been hitting it on the regular.
That's a good lead in my book.
It is a bank.
Damn old Trisculls are everywhere.
We're going to ride to a bank?
These bastards got ahold of most of Big Valley.
Heard they took over some big ranch north of here.
I'm going to play Just Cause 4 when it comes out.
How the hell do you know how many end up down here anyway?
I never played Just Cause 3.
Do you know how it is?
Do you lose sense?
No, did I?
Drink there?
I think I played, maybe I did play Just Cause 3 for like a day on the multiplayer.
Nothing that needs to concern you.
I always pay my share.
It concerns me when you put us in danger and we don't realize till it's too late.
Like that move you pulled at Strawberry.
Just dance.
Just for your precious guns.
No, you'll never see a Just Dance stream for me.
You need to roll a little looser, Morgan.
Looser?
I've seen you come full on more than once now.
The only way you'd ever get a Just Dance stream for me?
Is if I hired like 30 dancers to dance behind me while we were all in the same costumes.
Do it.
Do it one day.
Just do it now.
Be right back.
See you guys in like 15 minutes.
Here's the spot.
Hold up on the bridge.
You got it.
Should be from over there.
Doesn't Micah look like he's wearing a rubber mask and over the rubber mask?
Fake hair.
Fake mustache, fake beard, fake hair.
Let's go.
There's that music.
Attack the guards and stop the stagecoach.
Bingo.
Oh, did I get them all?
Just leave one guy left, right?
More.
See you later.
Oh, sedazy.
Got him.
I shot him right in the tailbone.
Are you playing Red Dead Online?
You'll see it tomorrow.
I feel like it's gonna be wild.
Wait, I don't get to drive?
I gotta keep the horses with us.
Come on, horse.
Let's go.
Hat in the wagon.
Yeah, the hat's fine.
Maybe it'll fall off.
Take the hat.
I'll get the hat.
It's too tense.
I can't stand it.
What if the hat falls?
I'm gonna get that hat.
No, the mission's gonna fail.
The mission's gonna fail.
I don't want to sit through that.
I don't want to hear him talk.
I hate this character.
Forget about the hat.
It's gone.
Forever.
Garbage stream.
He lost the hat on purpose.
How much did you pay for Red Dead?
I did the wrong thing.
I paid the middle of the road
special edition, which is
you just get a cool horse.
You don't get to participate
in the beta that happened today.
Well, I will tomorrow.
But I bought the one
that you shouldn't have bought.
Where's the QTE?
When is movie night?
Movie night is Sunday.
This weekend.
There we go.
Watch this.
One, two, three.
Activate!
Oh, I didn't have enough deadeye.
Oh my god.
That's a mistake.
I need deadeye.
Let's bring Tom.
No, that's not the guy.
Banjo-Kazooie music.
Why is that making me laugh so much?
When is movie night happening?
Give it a...
Oh, Sunday.
This Sunday.
It's Sunday night.
Did I...
Did I not?
Maybe I didn't finish my sentence.
All right.
Okay.
Well, we got more.
People are here.
So, how many...
Is it deadeye or not?
Um, no idea.
Dark Souls are the light, though.
Tom.
What day of the week is Sunday?
It's the one that comes after Saturday and before Monday.
Sunday p.m.
Yeah, Sunday raspberry p.m.
Got it!
Do online?
I can't do online.
I did not buy the Ultimate Edition.
I have to wait till tomorrow.
So, I'm just kind of getting familiar with the video game again.
So, then I'm prepared tomorrow and I know what I'm doing.
And like I said.
Fucking mask.
Rubber mask.
With a goddamn fake mustache on it.
I'll pull that off sooner or later, Micah.
We'll see who you really are.
Six hundred bucks.
Three hundred.
That's pretty good.
Three hundred and thirty dollars.
Ultimate Edition.
No, the only Ultimate Edition I bought was Zoo Tycoon 2.
All right.
Well, there you go.
Hey, there you go.
Where...
I think I was gonna go like this.
And it was with the money, too.
What do you mean the money?
I was trying to...
I'm trying to launch myself.
I'm trying to do a springboard.
Shoot out of the cannon into the water and move.
It's not gonna happen, is it?
If it was online, you'd get four dollars and four cents.
You need to be going faster, though.
All right.
So, I'm good with...
Did you just shoot me off?
You have mere seconds to live.
Whoa.
Crazy Red Dead 2 moments.
Okay.
So, we're gonna not all save here.
So, we're good.
Let's go do Adam Sandler versus Adam Sandler in a backstage brawl.
That's not what I'm doing, by the way.
So many games tonight.
Yeah, I'm just kind of dicking around.
I was hoping I could play the online.
That was the plan that I found out
that I wasn't gonna be able to play it.
So, just hanging out tonight.
And we're gonna be going tomorrow, too.
So, don't worry.
I had fun tonight, though.
Zoo Tycoon was really interesting for the first like, you know, three or four hours.
So, let's get this changed.
We don't really...
I don't even really change the title.
I don't think...
Wait, what?
Wait a minute.
What the fuck is happening?
I have this on PC.
That's why it's like that.
Why do I have this on PS4?
What happened?
What?
Oh, fuck.
Okay, I know what happened.
I bought the game twice.
Like, between...
From probably a while ago.
When did I buy this?
How long?
Am I crazy?
That's why there was a random...
That was gonna be Beanbag Sonic from whenever the fuck I started it.
I must have gone...
Oh, wait, there's a PC version.
Fuck, isn't there?
And I bought...
Yeah.
Well, okay.
All right.
I bought it twice.
Now, let's open the real one.
The one that has the fucking 40 characters on it.
I can't believe I didn't like...
It did not deserve to be bought twice.
I was just...
My brain just did not comprehend what was just going on right there.
Yeah.
So, like six...
Yeah, like probably seven days ago.
Eight days ago.
I bought it on PS4 because I didn't think it was on PC.
And then I realized it was on PC.
I started making somebody.
Yeah, I'll take off the delay thing.
You don't remember eight days ago?
Well, no, I do.
I remember buying it, but I don't remember when.
The timeline is not in my brain
because I spent so much time in the PC one.
This guy buys games and forgets.
I forgot to like fucking...
I don't think you can...
You can't even refund a game on PS4, can you?
If you download it digitally?
All right, let's open up the real one.
Here it is.
I was wondering why that was fucking stupid.
All right.
Here it comes.
And I...
And this one was like 50% off on Steam.
That's the worst part.
And I just hurt myself in my ears.
I'm really sorry that happened, everybody.
The outro is playing.
Hey, look, that guy's dabbing.
Okay, let's go to play here.
Here you go.
Let's do backstage brawl.
Here's the match we're going to do.
Really, game?
You can't...
No duplicates.
I got an idea.
How about we do...
Oh, that's right.
I forgot we made him too.
All right, let's do...
Let's do the two actors.
Oh, no.
Willem Dafoe versus the Nintendo Labo.
Sounds right to me.
Let's do it.
He's really good.
He is.
Not even going to wait.
Spun him around.
I've yet...
Where's the punch?
Talking shit in his face.
At least it's even.
The Labo is just a Minecraft character.
Kick his ass, Dafoe.
Everybody ends it instantly.
I would laugh by myself.
But I've been Red Dead.
The stream is pretty much over.
I'm just doing this for fun.
Dude, even me versus the Labo.
Come on, bend him.
Fold him.
This is how I treat my Labo creations.
I mean, not completely...
Not completely untrue.
You can't lift him.
The stock sound effects really are so stupid.
So how does this end?
I'm thinking Labo is going to go through a table.
Going to the locker room.
Don't just fight out here next to the sound equipment.
They keep doing the throw him into the wall thing.
There we go.
Into the locker room.
Make something happen here.
Jesus.
That could end really quickly.
I love how that's just a big giant...
He's going to kill him.
There's just a cartoon trash can in here.
Get back in there.
His head's too big.
His head is too big.
Just let him go.
That's it?
You just let him go.
He picked him up and dropped him.
That's going to be it.
That was fucking stupid.
No, I don't want to...
If I'm going to do wrestling stuff,
I want it to be something that I think about
and well thought out.
Not just random matches.
Maybe someday.
Create Super Sandler.
No, no, no, no, no.
Not tonight.
I might increase the frequency that we do stuff like this,
but not so much where it happens all the time.
But anyways, that's going to be it for tonight.
Thank you for sticking around.
A little bit of a just chill stream.
We...
Something in my throat.
Played a couple of games.
Thanks for joining me.
And we'll do the bits
and we'll do the credits at the end.
See you guys tomorrow for Red Dead Multiplayer.
I'm not going to start as late as I did today.
I will be starting at probably...
An hour or two before.
So somewhere around...
Probably like five or six Eastern.
I'd like to start.
I'm not going to finish the main story in Red Dead tomorrow.
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe if Multiplayer...
Do Multiplayer for a few hours.
See how it goes.
If I'm still having fun,
maybe I'll just transition
and just keep going in Red Dead.
I don't know.
We'll see.
Did you miss the green screen movie night?
You did not.
That is Sunday.
Sunday night.
So with that, let's go back.
Just about six hours ago now.
It's really a six hour stream.
I thought it was a little shorter than that,
but I guess not.
So starting here with Peter.
Thank you, Peter, for the $3.33.
Cool guy.
Thank you, Peter.
Do test.
Thanks for the $1.
Parts.
Appreciate it.
Nostalgic Nerd.
Thanks for the 10 bucks.
Hey, Durban, wanted to sincerely thank you
for all the hard and amazing work you do on these streams.
You helped me get through some rough times in high school
and the death of my great uncle.
I can never fully repay you for what you've done
for me, but this is a start.
Thanks, fellow New Englander.
Thank you, Nostalgic Nerd.
Yeah, the music is not on.
That's correct.
I'm sorry to hear about your loss.
There is no repaying me,
so don't worry about that.
Thank you for the $10 regardless,
but you don't have to pay me money
because you think that you owe it.
You don't.
So thank you, though.
And fellow New Englander.
Yeah, New England's great.
I'm in Las Vegas at the moment, though.
Not sure where I'll be in the next couple of years.
I don't know.
Depends on how much I like it here.
I'm up in the air right now,
but thank you, Nostalgic Nerd, for the $10
and that wonderful message.
Thank you.
Thank you, Spartanese, for the $1.
Thank you, Enamelint.
Enamelint for the $10.
Thanks to the stream, German.
It's been a rough day,
but your streams never fail to cheer me up.
Cheer my heart.
Thank you so much, Enamelint.
Thank you for the $10.
Sorry to hear about your days
and how it's been going so well.
Hopefully tomorrow's better.
Thank you.
Kumutosen.
Thanks for the $10, Kumutosen.
10 bucks.
$10 three times in a row here, guys.
Thank you.
Hey, German, it's my birthday today.
Thank you for all the laughs.
I've been incredibly depressed
for the past while,
and your videos and streams
have helped cheer me up.
There's a small token of my appreciation.
Keep up the good work.
You're really doing a lot of good.
Well, happy birthday.
Hopefully it's still your birthday
because that was a while ago,
and if it's past your birthday,
happy second birthday,
which is tomorrow,
which is today for you, potentially,
depending on where you are in the world.
But thank you so much.
Happy birthday.
Sorry to hear about
that you've been feeling bad.
If you're having fun,
that makes me happy.
So thank you.
It's a double birthday.
Thank you, Spartanis, again for the $1.
Spartanis again.
Spartanis gave one, two, three, four, five.
Five dollars here.
We're almost six dollars here.
No message, just dropping bits.
Thank you.
Dog memes.
Thanks for the $10.
Hey, German, memes aside,
I've been watching you since the TF2 days.
Six years later,
and you're still going strong.
Here's some money.
Spend it on whatever you want.
Thanks for being a cool guy.
Thank you.
Thank you for being nice enough to
pay money to somebody on the internet.
You know what I mean?
All of you.
Six years ago.
That's so long.
Can you imagine?
Fast forward like a few years.
Like, oh yeah, I've been watching you
for 10 years.
Oh, 10 years ago when I started.
Who knows?
I can't even fathom saying those words.
Because right now it's about six and a half to seven.
Yeah.
Another few years,
and it's going to be a decade.
That's crazy.
At that point,
that's a significant portion of my entire life.
Will have been doing this.
On YouTube, on Twitch,
or wherever and whatever I end up doing.
We'll see.
I don't give myself a time limit,
but I don't give myself a
amount of time that I have to do it.
It's not like, oh yeah,
well, you know, in 20 years
when I'm still streaming on German 985 Twitch.
I don't know.
It's very significant already, though.
It's true.
But thank you, Dom.
Dog memes.
Appreciate it.
Gentle ghosts.
Thanks for the five dollars.
Hey, German, my friend Warren,
who is also a big fan of yours,
is turning 18 this week.
I was wondering if you could wish him a happy birthday.
You've been watching your content with me
for the past few years,
and I'm sure you'll mean a lot to him.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Happy birthday, Warren.
18.
Significant milestone.
That's the, you're an adult.
Except I didn't really become an adult
until I was probably like 26.
So sing him the rat song.
A lot of birthdays, huh?
This week?
Today?
Tomorrow?
Thank you, gentle ghosts.
And again, happy birthday to Warren.
Thanks for watching.
You guys rock.
Thank you.
Dr. Clay, thanks for the one dollar.
I was rewatching you play Mario Tennis
and you mentioned a music stream.
Has that been canceled?
Looking forward to the green screen.
Movie night.
I'm currently working on a submission.
Hopefully it will be done in time.
Take care.
I haven't, like, I don't cancel.
Ideas.
It took a long time.
Think about this, right?
The detective stream.
The green screen stream.
Think of how long it took to actually get that done.
So it's not like it ever goes away completely.
That green screen stream was mentioned
more than three or four months ago.
And then, you know, when they happen, they happen.
Kind of have to be in the right mindset.
Time has to be right.
I have to get the right resources ready
and try to get it done, you know?
The detective stream was also,
that took a while to do as well.
God, I want to do that again.
But, like, more elaborate.
I have no idea.
I got to think of some stupid ideas for that one.
But thank you, Dr. Clay.
No, nothing is ever, ever canceled.
They just get moved around.
Hey, DivUSP.
I'm just kidding.
Thank you, Divus, for the three dollars.
DivusP for the three bucks.
Appreciate it.
No message.
Thank you for the three dollars.
Fisherman friend zone.
Thanks for the one dollar.
My first experience.
My first Jerma experience was in the video
Ruiner of Fun, a.k.a.
Jerma's Mad Part 1.
I've been a fan ever since.
Also, can you do the Neelix voice, please?
Why?
I just can't believe.
I'm dressing up as Neelix for Halloween next year.
And everyone's going to hate my guts.
Hey, Elizabeth.
Thanks for the one dollar.
Show this on stream.
Well, first of all, let me see what it is.
Wait, what?
Don't get into that shit.
Don't do that shit.
What?
What's wrong with that?
Go to bed.
Yeah, like go to bed.
Like you don't have to do anything crazy.
Streamer promoting the use of drugs.
No, I didn't.
I said, if you want to do that,
if you want to do that,
then this is what I wouldn't be doing that.
And I would never condone.
Actually, I would.
I don't smoke marijuana,
but I don't smoke weed or anything.
But I do recognize its benefits.
You probably think I'm just,
oh, he's probably like high every stream.
Did you hear what he said?
What the fuck?
She's definitely high.
Really?
You ever like see somebody high on fucking marijuana before?
They don't talk about like,
they don't talk about like their,
like their dreams.
Yeah, they do.
They don't talk about like checking asses.
Point stands.
They don't talk about Garfield.
Yes, they do.
Doesn't matter.
If whatever you're doing is legal,
and you're all right,
and you're safe,
and you're being responsible,
whatever.
Think I got a problem with it?
But thank you, Elizabeth, for the $1.
Thank you, sly161 for the $1.
Hey, Jerma, I'm in the middle of class.
Can you please pause the stream for two hours?
I can't do that.
Thank you, Yeetee, in Yeetee,
tweet in Deetee for the $2.
Thank you.
Uh, is it cut tag or Q cut tag?
Thanks for the $4.
How'd, how do you donate?
You figured it out, I think.
Looks like you got it.
Thank you for the $4.
Appreciate it.
Uh, Dorosophilia, thanks for the $1.
Hey, man, I couldn't find the donate button.
This streamer doesn't have any on-screen text
or information in the stream title
telling me how to donate.
So I didn't know what else to do.
Pretty unprofessional, if you ask me.
Would you kindly pass along my money to him?
Yeah, sure.
Oh, that's from what it was, okay.
Thank you, Dorosophilia.
Thank you, uh, thank you, Dylan C for $3.
Thank you for $5.
I've been a fan of yours since the seventh grade.
Your YouTube videos and streams
always give me a good laugh.
They have also helped me through rough times
such as stressful days at college
for after I run a,
after there was a fire call to the fire department.
I volunteer.
Uh, I know it's not much,
but thanks for the fun times.
Or after I run a nasty fire call.
I see.
It's not much,
but thank you for all the fun times.
Don't worry about it.
Thank you for the $5.
Doesn't matter if you give $1, $5, $10.
Don't ever, ever feel like it's something
that you need to be sorry about.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
I'm only going to give you $5.
It's not much.
Yes, it is.
It is.
Just the fact that you decided to
in the first place.
Don't worry.
I don't want anyone to ever have to apologize
for giving me your money.
You know what I'm saying?
Thank you for even considering.
Much love to you.
Thanks for the $5.
Super seal.
Thanks for the $1.
There's an image.
Let's see what it is.
It is of, uh, what the fuck?
Well, that's not terrifying at all.
Thank you.
Super seal for the ice cream.
I guess.
Thank you.
Frody and weapon.
Thanks for the $1.
No message.
Thank you.
Palette of produce.
Thanks for the $15.
No message from Palette here,
but thank you so much.
For you 15 bucks.
That's a new emote.
Oh, God.
Extra cheesy.
Thanks for the $1.
Why are the beavers living in raw sewage?
No, that was a habitat that was
created with craft and care.
And I made sure to make it as comfortable as I could.
They had, they had a good life.
Snooze and copter.
Thanks for the $1.
It is a, I've actually seen a couple pieces of art for this.
This is awesome.
Thank you, snoozing copter.
Super Jax and the blue screen of death.
That's great.
Snooze and copter says for another dollar here.
Whoops.
I didn't attach a message.
It's all good, man.
Yeah, I've seen a couple pieces of art.
The rumble a couple nights ago.
It's great.
I love it.
Thank you.
Extra cheesy.
Thanks for the $1.
Beaver.
No, there was, there was, the beaver habitat
was a well taken care of.
Established zoologist.
They were auto-emote incoming.
The beavers were taken care of just fine.
And there, there was no issues.
There were no problems.
Appreciate the a dollar.
Appreciate the a dollar though.
That was really, really, really worded.
But thanks.
Dr. Froman.
Thanks for the $1.
Thanks for being an awesome streamer.
Looking forward to the movie night.
Me too.
It's coming up really quick.
Again, I got to reiterate this.
Make sure that if you have a submission,
you get it in by Thursday at midnight.
That is not even, that's two days from now.
Thursday at midnight.
And then make sure it is a YouTube link.
Check the rules and the pinned message there.
And follow them all.
Because if you do not follow those rules,
then your submission is not going to be
put in or considered.
Please follow the rules.
Thank you.
Asian Turtle.
Thanks for the $1.
I made this while I was waiting
for the stream to start.
And while you spent the next hour
building an enclosure for your beavers.
From the...
Oh man.
They bought a zoo.
Thank you for the $1.
Major Bluetooth.
Thanks for the $5.
Hey Jerma.
Really enjoyed the latest installment
into the rumble cannon.
And wanted to leave a cheer in its honor.
Brought the great laugh.
Since the rumble did not have a U.S. president,
I took your advice and imagined
the green screen to be William H. Taft.
Our 27th.
What a treat it was for our first U.S. president.
To get our first U.S. president victory
after such an epic struggle.
And then watch him honor his own legacy
by getting stuck on the rope.
Also juicy.
Thank you Major Bluetooth for the $5.
For that juicy five bucks.
Juicy fruit.
But yeah, it could have been anybody.
That's why he's too powerful.
He will never return.
Until I do a champion's brawl.
Which you could probably imagine what that means.
Swiggity dank.
Thanks for the $20.
Hey Jerma just got out of the hospital
from getting surgery on my nuts.
It doesn't feel too great as you can imagine.
But I'm all right.
And this stream is helping me keep my mind off of it.
Thanks man.
Um, yeah, I'm sorry to hear that.
Dude, hope you're okay.
Thanks for the $20.
Hopefully you recover quickly
and hopefully it's nothing serious.
Take care of yourself.
Thanks for the $20.
Hey dragon breath, thanks for the $1.
Hey Jerma, in case you haven't seen,
Joel addressed that thing about the dog smell question
that happened during the Labo stream.
You should listen to this with chat for a few minutes.
This is a VOD link.
It's fucking dog smell.
Hey, thanks a lot.
By the way, by the way,
that's a rare kind of anecdote here.
Now, I don't know if this is the right place
to talk about this.
But I know that Jerma hosted me.
Oh, he didn't host me.
He was doing like a little joke on stream.
And I want to say I was,
I was being a bit of an asshole,
a no fun asshole because like.
Wait, what?
No, he wasn't, was he?
I don't remember that.
No, that didn't.
Here's the, here's the deal.
What happened last Gregory horror show stream.
Jerma was going around and I don't fully like
get the, the, the brunt of this joke, right?
But he was going around and he was like
having a little bit of fun, right?
And, uh, he was, he was having fun with,
uh, all these streamers, right?
And then, uh, somebody suggested
he should like do the thing for me.
And it was like some, some sort of like weird
raid question about dogs or something like that.
And he did it to several people,
but when it came to me, I was like,
like technical issues at the same time.
And I was like getting back and forth
support from chat or something like that.
I can't fully remember what happened,
but, uh, and in the midst of this,
a bunch of like Jerma viewers bled onto
my stream and started asking questions.
And I kind of was like a bit of an asshole about it.
I started saying like,
hey, I really appreciate you guys like Beeman,
but like I'm trying to figure shit out here.
And Jerma felt so fucking bad.
I did.
I really did.
For like a good solid hour.
Basically saying, hey guys, like be chill.
And like, I really did feel so bad for like
not playing along.
Just to like make sure here,
like I have no absolute, no bad fucking
blog between Jerma and I is a super cool guy.
And I got to say this too,
the fact that he apologized and he was like,
guys, just chill out that that shows respect.
And, uh, I'm fine with playing along with stuff like that,
but just the fact that he did apologize for it,
because there's a lot of people that are like,
they don't give a shit what their audience does
or this chat does.
And the fact that he stepped out of the way
to like kind of not police his chat,
but you say, you know, calm down, you know,
I appreciate that, you know,
so, uh, you know, call me, call me,
Jerma, we can get into all kinds of weird,
uh, stinky role play if you want.
Nah, that's all good.
He's a good dude.
I wasn't under the impression that there was any
problem at all.
I just want to, you know, I mean,
because sometimes the people,
I was kind of losing my mind on stream
and we were going like, he's right.
We were bouncing around to different places
and critical started throwing cards at me
and ran into italics's stream and, you know,
we were just having fun and, uh,
but I think if you like trying to get shit done,
if you have something going on
and you're trying to figure out something
and all of a sudden it's like,
you kind of like what the hell
he's supposed to do it at that point, right?
But no, there's, it's all good.
He's a great dude.
Drunk Labo stream like strikes again.
You drank 400 glasses of wine.
Hey, but anyways, uh, yeah, that's that.
And, uh, did I, yeah, extra cheesy gave $13
to ask about my favorite animal.
And I said, I wanted a laptop or something.
I don't remember, but thank you so much.
Extra cheesy for the 13 bucks.
Armadillo was the correct answer,
but thank you.
Extra cheesy again came in with $3
on your next German craft playthrough.
You need to make a creeper zoo.
Thank you.
Thank you, Dr. Garbage and friends
for the $1.
Hey Jeremy, you should play the
re-release Spyro and ruin my childhood.
I don't want to ruin your child.
What's wrong with it?
Is the new Spyro not good?
I heard, I thought it was good,
but thank you.
Thank you, uh, 9e for the $1.
Name the restrooms after chat.
Smelly boy, thanks for $1.
Please say zoo-we-mama three times fast.
I bet you can't.
I'm not going to do that.
Hold on.
I'm mute my microphone for a second.
I don't get it.
I don't understand.
This is, this is a meme.
Don't worry.
Okay, fine.
We don't do memes here.
Hey Garfield, the Monday killer.
Thanks for the $1.
Ho, ho, ho.
It's almost that time of year again.
Wonder what you want for Christmas.
I can't finish a movie.
I can't finish a movie in for the stream.
The movie stream since I got finals soon,
but the German cinematic universe
has not yet halted production.
Odie, watch what you're doing.
That boom mic cost a whole $30.
What a crazy dog.
I bet Otto doesn't do stuff like that.
Don't drop that.
You're fired.
Congratulations on another awesome Germania.
You always put so much work.
Did you just drop it, Odie?
Thank you for the $1 Garfield.
Appreciate it.
Barfield.
I'm going to, you know,
your name now is Barfield.
Barfield.
I just quantum died.
I'm going to remember Barfield.
Barfield is going to have like
puke on his face and be green.
All right, quantum dead.
Thank you, Garfield, for the $1.
Hey, Pilot Guy.
Thank you, Pilot Guy, for the $20, Pilot Guy.
Hey, German, just want to say thank you
for all the laughs through my times of stress.
You've always been here and helped me smile.
Thank you.
Thank you, Pilot Guy, for your $20
and for being here.
More importantly, thank you so much.
Bake Me Home, thanks for $13.
It's a good thing you're streaming
because I dread to live in a world
where you actually ran an amusement park.
German land.
It's a good thing it's just a stream.
I think I would do a pretty good job.
You laugh now.
But thank you.
Thank you, Bake Me Home.
Thank you, Pilot Guy.
$20, $13.
Flabjack, thanks for the $2, Flabjack.
When are you going to give us comedy lessons?
I'm looking forward to that stream,
funny streamer.
Comedy lessons.
I don't know.
When is that going to happen?
Who knows?
Thank you.
Thank you, Bunny Butt, for the $1, $2, $3, $4, $5 here.
Bunny Butt.
How does one go about making stupid camera jokes?
I'm hoping for advice from my own streams.
Stupid camera jokes.
How many bits do I have to spend to name him Skateboard?
Well, I didn't make him have any name.
But stupid camera jokes.
I don't...
Get a camera and do the default Fortnite dance in front of it.
And then have a green screen behind you
and like key yourself into like a genie bottle or something.
And then when the person rubs you out of the bottle,
of the bottle, of the bottle, of the genie bottle,
when you come out of the genie bottle,
you can like give them like a hundred,
never mind, moving on, a hundred wee bucks.
Not wee, like Nintendo wee.
Vee bucks.
That threw me off so bad because of the stupid shit that I just said.
But thank you, Bunny Butt.
Sorry, I didn't name him Skateboard.
Severian, the great.
Thanks for your $11, Severian.
Thank you so much.
No message.
Just $11 fucking dollars.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Hater the Tater for the $5.
Actually, more like $11 here from Hater the Tater.
Jar Jar with fun size is Jerjer.
Jerjer.
That gets an e-heave from me.
Also, stream is now middle-aged, rocky, and unstable,
but still going like Jerma.
You're not middle-aged until you're like 45 or 50 years old.
I'm fine.
I'm doing just good enough.
Thank you for your $11.
Appreciate it.
That gets a little bit of an e-heave from me.
You know what I'm saying?
Mostly lost.
Thanks for the $2 here.
I liked Just Cause 3 a lot.
I think it would be a great game to play.
Jerma game.
Yeah, I mean, I'm going to give it a try.
Just Cause 4 comes out in like 6.
EDF 5 comes out in less than a week and a half.
Oh, shit.
Wow, I forgot about that.
Earth Defense Force 5 comes out on PlayStation 4.
December 10th?
December 11th?
Well, you bet your ass you know what we're doing
on the 10th, 11th, and 12th.
It's going to be that.
But thank you.
Again, mostly lost.
And it's got the right balance of fun,
gameplay, and mechanics with a laughably bad story.
That's Just Cause 3.
I remember Star made a video on Just Cause 3.
Looked pretty ridiculous.
So definitely kind of up my alley.
Sputa.
Thanks for the $1.
I'm sorry I can only go for small bits this time.
But considering you get so many bit messages,
I'm sure it gets difficult to remember them all.
But do you ever think back to messages from long ago,
rather as a pick-me-up or just in general?
Um, stuff sticks with me.
It does.
It can be, like you said, it can be very difficult though.
Trying to bring back the memories of donation messages
or bit messages.
And I try my best to keep, you know,
as many as I can fit up there.
But that's, it gets hard.
It's just that I never want to be one of those people
that's just like, thanks for the dollar.
Thanks for five bucks.
Bye bye.
Thank you.
Thank bye.
Thanks for the money.
But it is a challenge.
Do you talk to yourself while playing games offline too?
Yes, I do.
Like the one where I made you cry.
Yeah, I mean, you guys, it's,
I don't just take it lightly, you know?
Some of you guys have given a lot of fucking money.
A lot of money, a lot of time,
a lot of your free time.
And there are lots of, here's the thing, right?
The reason why I want to care so much about this
and take it as, try as hard as I can on certain scenarios
and try to come up with things to do
is because there are so many other avenues
for you to use your free time.
Thousands of people, hundreds of shows,
thousands and thousands of avenues for entertainment.
It means an absolute metric shitload
that out of all the possible places, you're here.
So I have to take it fucking seriously
because that's a huge, huge, huge thing.
And I'm going to do it for as long as I can,
as long as I'm having fun
and can keep coming up with stuff I'd like to do.
I don't want to get to that position where it's like,
I'm just doing it just to do it because I,
because I'm going to because that's what I do
and I'm just going to do it.
No, I don't want to do that.
Until 40, when I can't say swears anymore.
That's, yeah.
It's true, you can't, but thank you.
Thank you, Sputa.
Thank you, Pancakes for the $1.
Just want to say you smell like a shoe.
I really appreciate all your content.
Keep it up.
Let me see.
Now that's Dove Men Plus Care.
Fucking Walmart brand.
Thank you, Pancakes.
Thank you, Twitchy Pyro for the $1.
Jerma, thanks for providing a good laugh
while I try to figure out
how to get out of this walk-in oven.
I'll keep at it.
Try banging on the door and saying, hey,
somebody will go up the fuck and open it probably.
Thank you.
Thank you, DubskiDude for the $1.
Hey, Jerma, I've been a fan of your content
since kindergarten how time flies.
I'm already a great grandfather and on my deathbed.
I remember the smoke signal streams
you used to do with the pilgrims.
Good times, man.
And let's not forget how you goofed
on the Mesopotamians.
Their civilization wasn't the same after that one.
Can't wait for another 6.7 million years
of quality streams.
Keep it up, you timeless streamer boy.
Thank you, DubskiDude.
Thank you for the $1.
And we're going for another 7 million years.
They're going to figure it out.
They'll figure out like robotics
and I'll be able to put like an implant in my chest.
Thank you, SpicyMexicanTaco for the $1.
Thank you, $5.
Dr. Clay for the $1.
Just want to say I hate the menu in WWE2K19.
It's just white background with gray text
that says the menu selection.
The UI literally looks like a placeholder.
I know.
Oh, yeah, I know.
All the menus in these WWE games lately.
Just awful.
Even the character creator,
there's a menu for a menu inside of a menu to get to,
okay, you want to change somebody's hair.
Click on, okay, you got to go to body,
a lot of appearance, facial appearances,
and then the hair and then it's just,
there's like four menus.
There's so many menus that just stacked
on top of each other.
I would really much rather,
and I don't know why they don't do this.
I don't understand.
Wrestling is not like baseball or football or...
Don't worry.
Sheamus is still going to exist in 2020.
You know what I mean?
They're turning it into this roster update
where they add a handful of features.
It's not like, oh, every single year,
hundreds and hundreds of people change teams.
And you could argue that that could just be done
with something as simple as a patch, right?
Wrestling isn't real, so...
Well, I mean, there's the aspect of like
the fantasy kind of fiction aspect to it, yeah.
But I don't know why they have to come up
with one every single year.
It doesn't need to happen.
That didn't happen before.
That's a fairly recent thing,
the last probably 10 years.
A wrestling game would come out
when a wrestling game decided it was going to come out.
And turning the WWE franchise
into a Madden-like simulation sports game
that has to come out on a yearly schedule
is, in my opinion, is killing the whole thing.
It's killing the whole franchise.
And I would not be somebody that's...
My opinion is that's not an unpopular opinion.
All of these games over the last five, six, or seven years
is at least the last six.
With the exception of maybe one or two of them
have been pretty, I would say, very mediocre ratings and reviews.
Just like, eh, it's not special.
It's just bad and it's not very good.
It's... I don't understand.
After 2006 is when they started doing it every year,
but those early ones were still good.
So you don't know what happened.
Well, what happened is THQ was liquidated
and 2K ended up taking on the franchise.
And they turned it into the NBA, you know, NBA 2K,
WWE 2K, and, you know,
they had the teams at 2K that do sports
start to contribute to the games that, you know,
they took on the license from the WWE.
That's kind of what happened.
To be honest, like, for real, THQ may be one of the...
People, like, talked about it for a little while,
but you don't even realize just how...
That's like a pretty devastating loss to gaming.
There were some really great fucking titles
that were underneath THQ.
You can think about, oh, yeah, THQ got, like,
wiped out and liquidated and gone.
Oh, wow, that sucks.
Oh, that's too bad.
But then you realize, like,
the rippling effects that that has.
They made some pretty great games,
or at least they had enough to do with them.
But I could sit here and be sad about...
And I don't know.
Maybe I am one of those people
that's speaking from a small audience.
You know what I mean?
Because I don't know.
The reasons why I like the WWE games
is because I like to make stuff.
I like to make scenarios.
And, oh, remember in WWE 2K14,
you could actually put your characters
into, like, cutscenes?
That shit was fucking awesome.
There was like 40 or 50 different scenarios
you could put the characters in
to play out on screen.
Just to use that game, I can't,
because it just does not hold up well at all.
That game is only for PlayStation 3.
And it takes, like, 15 seconds sometimes.
20, 30 seconds.
Once you have an elaborate character designed,
it can take...
It's just so long.
It's so slow.
The menus are slow.
The creation is so slow.
It's just very outdated.
So it would take, essentially,
probably two or three times
the amount of time to make a character
than use the current-gen version.
And maybe it would be worth it,
but I don't know.
I just wish that they would...
I mean, who knows?
I don't know what the data is,
what they have,
or what people want out of a wrestling game.
But I like the crazy league aspect of it,
where people get to make their own leagues
and make their own interesting storylines.
And that's what I did
when I was 14, 15, 16.
We would make entire...
Me and my friends would just sit there
and just make whole scenarios.
Make whole leagues.
We used to make our dads,
and our dads would fight each other in the ring.
And it was like all storylines
attached to each other's dads.
That's what I want.
I could care less if...
Oh, you know,
the Hulk Hogan's in this one.
That's cool.
Okay.
I can make Hulk Hogan.
I can just make him.
But I'll get off that rant.
Dad voice.
But anyways, let's wrap it up here.
Mandragor root.
Thanks for the $1.
Mazekit, thanks for the $1.
Is the new home treating you well?
Yeah.
I'd say settling in pretty nicely.
Las Vegas is an awesome place.
There's tons to do, tons to see.
So yeah, I'm loving it.
For sure.
Thank you, Burger B for the $5.
Me and a few of the Discord boys
have been trying to find the most effective way
to thaw bread.
What are your thoughts?
Keep it real.
How to thaw bread.
How frozen is it?
Is it like rock solid
or is it just slightly crystalline on the inside?
It's like an ice cube.
Well, you could.
I mean, you could just sit on it for a little while.
Just take it out.
Just sit on it like a penguin.
But make sure you have like jeans on
so it doesn't like get too cold.
My best thought was to light it on fire in a toilet.
Now that is a terrible idea.
No, put it in the microwave on thaw.
Every microwave has a thaw setting.
You just have to look at the manual.
Look at the instructional manual of your microwave
and it'll be a thaw setting.
Thaw it maybe a minute or two.
Check it.
Is it spongy?
No, put it back in the other thaw setting.
Why would you sit naked on bread?
I didn't say that.
That's why I said wear a pair of jeans.
Microwaving bread sounds like the saddest thing in the world.
There's no reason to do that.
If you get a piece of bread.
Oh, I'm gonna make like a sandwich.
Just stick it in there and just put for 30 seconds.
That'd be awful.
It would turn into shit.
It would be so sloppy.
It would just pull apart.
Set it to defrost.
Yeah.
Am I gonna play Kingdom Hearts 3 when it comes out?
I don't know.
Probably not on stream.
I don't think so.
I feel like there's really only one way.
Here's how I decide if it's something I want to stream.
When there's really only one way to complete and play through a game,
I'm not like that interested in streaming it.
And I say that for one reason because
I don't know if you watch a Kingdom Hearts stream that's,
you know, pointed every direction.
If you're, oh, I'm in the Kingdom Hearts 3 directory.
Okay.
All of us here are doing the same thing.
We're seeing the same cutscenes.
We're seeing the same story.
And I got the same keyblade.
There's not very much difference between them.
You want to reenact Kingdom Hearts on stream.
I can't do that either.
I don't know the script.
But that's just not, I don't,
that's how I determine if it's something I want to stream.
How different is my experience going to be from the person
that's potentially right next to me?
Is there enough there that makes it fun enough, different enough?
I'm sure it's going to be a great game.
I don't know.
But with that, thank you, Elizabeth, for the $1.
Germa Defoe.
And here come the credits.
Thank you for joining me on this just hang out,
relaxed, chill stream.
I had a good time.
You know, I was like really chill tonight.
Don't you think?
Don't you think so?
You guys, were you guys relaxed?
Making like dinosaurs and shit, walking around.
Yeah. Yeah.
Should check out Zoo Tycoon 1.
Actually, that's what I'm going to do when the stream turns off.
But thank you to all the subs, everyone that just came in.
New subs, old subs.
There are a lot of you now.
There are a lot of subs.
Chat keeps trying to make you cry,
but maybe you should make chat cry.
No, why would I want to do that?
I don't want to do that.
Possibility of a game show week?
Well, let's see what I haven't played.
You broke your nail.
That's not good.
Grump broke a nail.
Which one?
Germa May Cry.
Good night, pal.
I'll sub when I can.
I've been a ghost viewer for a while until I finally made my account today.
So good to interact with chat.
Well, welcome to chat.
And there's another one that just came in.
14 months there.
A hand nail.
There's one of them on the hands.
Now you got to go to the nail blacksmith.
You put your finger out and he just takes a hammer and he's just
Welcome to my Twitch chat room.
So I will see you guys tomorrow.
Red Dead Online.
Let's see if it's any good.
Otherwise, we're going to transition to like
me fucking raiding cereal boxes.
Yee-haw.
Play Jackbox with us?
Oh yeah, that's true.
All right, here's the thing.
If Red Dead Online is just like, oh, okay.
I'm like riding around and running into trees.
The random guy threw a grenade at me and it's that for like three hours or something.
We'll play Jackbox tomorrow.
That would be fun.
Yeah, why the fuck not?
Let's do it.
Or if Red Dead is good, then hold on to that.
We'll probably do that on Friday.
Yeah, fuck yeah.
Let's do that.
Let's do that like in the next couple of days.
Yeah, yeah.
No, fuck yeah.
Yeah, fuck yeah.
All right, guys.
Take care.
See you tomorrow.
Get some sleep.
Talk to you soon.
Ta-ta for now.