Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm gonna be playing as the Soldier with the Direct Hit.
And before I get into any of the topics and any of the discussions of this video, I do want to talk about the Direct Hit a little bit.
I want to talk about how it's sort of rotted in my backpack and I neglected it for so long and how I'm so sorry.
Direct Hit will be friends. You'll be my best friend from now on.
So, getting a little bit weird in the first 15 seconds of this commentary already, but you know, let's just keep going.
So the Direct Hit, guys, is a phenomenal item. I think I've only talked about this maybe once or twice in the entirety of this channel.
But if you have aim, if you can really lead targets and you know how to land shots in this game, you can destroy people with the Direct Hit.
Especially buildings. It takes two rockets to take out a level 3 sentry gun that has not been repaired.
And because the rockets come out so damn fast, half of the engineers in the world are not gonna be able to react in time to repair their stuff.
So Direct Hit, I'd say, is number two in taking out sentry guns.
Now that might sound a little bit crazy, but Demoman Stickies, of course, we all know is number one.
And Heavies, I guess you could say would be number two, but I don't think so.
Heavies need to be really close to do any real significant damage to a sentry gun, whereas a soldier or a Demoman can be across the entire freaking map.
And it's actually ridiculous at some points when you use the Direct Hit to kill a sentry.
You sit 50,000 feet away and shoot two little damn rockets and the thing explodes. It's almost unfair.
Now one thing that can be said about using the Direct Hit, and I do understand the argument against using the Direct Hit against sentry guns,
is the no splash damage or no splash radius. Well, it has a splash radius, but not that big.
And as we all know, to take out a sentry gun as a soldier, regular default, whether you're using default, Liberty Launcher, Black Box, it doesn't matter.
You shoot the ground around where the sentry is, hopefully killing the engineer and blowing up the dispenser and the building surrounding it.
You can take everything out with a few rockets, but the Direct Hit doesn't have that.
You have to catch people off guard, because if you do not catch an engineer off guard,
he can sit there and just whack at the sentry while you're trying to take it out and you will never kill him.
But, and this is a very big but, bigger than the biggest but you've ever seen on a big fat lady or something.
What? Bigger? What? I lost my train of thought because I'm trying to be stupid.
But anyways, when you shoot a level three sentry with the Direct Hit, after the first rocket lands,
if you immediately shoot another one, it is going to take less than one second for that sentry to go down.
And in the world of Team Fortress 2, that is absolutely insane, because this game is so chaotic as it is.
As an engineer, it makes me feel bad, because the engineer is my main, as a lot of you guys know that.
That sucks. That's horrible.
Less than one second is not even enough time for me to turn around and look at my dispenser.
Like, oh, let me see. What's that over there? Dispenser. What? My sentry's dead.
That's how crazy that is. It's less than one sec. I believe it's seven tenths of a second after impact of the first rocket before the sentry goes down.
And guys, my burps last longer than seven tenths of a second. I mean, that is just a ridiculous number to think about.
But we are going to change gears here a little bit, guys. I want to bring up something that's not really related to this gameplay at all.
It's about a poll I want you guys to take.
In the description of this video, it's going to take you to a polling site.
And on me and my polls, right, I do this quite frequently, but still, I do want to gauge your guys' opinions on the direction of the channel.
Because there are a lot of games that are currently out that are coming out this November and December, this holiday season.
And I want to know what you guys want to see. There's a lot of stuff. Hitman Absolution.
There's already, like, the Warcraft expansion. There's Guild Wars 2. There's a lot of things that I would like to do.
But I just don't know what I want to do. It's kind of... I'm in that mode right now where I'm always going to have Team Fortress.
Team Fortress 2 will always be here because I love the game and I'm always going to make content for it.
But what else is there? I mean, besides GTA V, there's so many things coming out in the next four to six months that there is a lot of opportunity for new content.
And you know me. I love variety. I'm all about the variety, guys.
So in the description, if you could please, if at least, like, 60 to 70% of you guys click that poll and go and vote on this.
This would really mean a lot to me. And it would be great for you guys, too, because then you guys can sort of pick the content for the future of this channel.
Which I like to involve you guys as much as I can.
So thank you in advance for doing that, guys. And in the comments section of this video, leave me your top three most anticipated games of this holiday season.
Because there are a lot of them. And I'm curious to know.
So leave that in the comments section. And that is going to wrap up the video.
So I'll see you guys all soon. And of course, take care, everybody.