I'm playing crocodile man. Alright, that's fine. You can be crocodile man.
Whoever has the biggest mouth for eating birds with. Alright, let's go, go, go, go, go.
Here we go. Alright, this is where we start. I'm not giving you any time. I don't know any
buttons, but I'm not giving you time. So am I like coming to punch you in the face?
Yeah, no, no, no, no. The ball. It's only the ball. Alright, oh, okay. So it's like
dodgeball. Is that how this works? Kind of, maybe. I don't know. This is like New Age
Pong. This seriously is New Pong. This is sick. I don't know. Wait, wait, wait. Okay,
I can do an eat move. I can do an eater. Yeah, you can like gently tap it and then
you launch it up. It's volleyball pong and it goes faster every time. Okay, I'm
going to beat you now. Yeah! Jesus! We just ponged the shit out of each other.
Alright, it's time for you to get PONGED by Mist. Oh, easy, easy. Okay, okay, this might be
too much for my brain. Oh, fucking come on. That was not fair. I was not, I wasn't, why
was it right? Oh, you're going to do the jump threat. I don't know what I'm doing. Alright,
it's X. Do you have an Xbox controller? I do. It's X. You can hold it to do like a
charge attack, I guess. I guess. Okay, I've got it. Do you understand? Yes. And there's also
special moves. Don't you know how to do special moves? I get it, I get it. The ball is your
color now, so if it hits me, then... At least we had a volley going. At least. It's your color,
so you can hit it. No, it was purple. Nobody's... No, it starts off as the losing persons. Oh,
it does? Easy. Yes, yes. Yeah, so you have three HP left. What are the special moves?
Oh, and I can break dance. I think you hold down the button, you press the button. Yeah,
I mean, but I think there's other special moves you can do too, maybe. Other? All I can do is
like do some like dances and stuff. Okay, well maybe we should have looked. Yes, that was not
my plan at all, but it worked. Oh, come on. Noob. I even said damn it. Oh, you want to see this
pretty... Oh, what's he going to do? What's he going to do? What's going to happen here? What's
going to happen? I didn't know who won that one. All right, it's two. It's two. We both have two HP.
Oh, you ducked. Excellent work. No, I want to go down. I want it to go like... How did we get it
to go nuts before? You have to jump and hit it. I'm going to win. No, you're not. Yes, I am. I
don't think you're already... This one! Okay, this is where we really need to step up the game here.
I'm pretty sure I can like charge it maybe after I hit it for like a... Come on. Yes! I did the...
I won. I won. I get 100 bucks. I won. I won. I get 100 bucks. I won. Wait, you get XP? You
level up in this game? Maybe you can like... Do you unlock abilities? Okay, okay. All right,
so no mercy. This is the no mercy round. I paused the game accidentally, but it actually helped me
out. No! It didn't help anyone out. That's one. That's one. You little frog piece of dookie.
Somebody's getting a little upset about this. Oh! Super! Super! Good luck. Good luck. Good luck.
Fuck you! How are you ever supposed to do that? Shit. Take that. That was a quick move. They call
it volleyball. They call that the quick move. Do they? Something tells me that's not what they
call that in volleyball, but it's okay. I'm not sure how much volleyball you know. Oh, what? Get
out of my... Get out of my house. Get out of my house. I almost forget my accident. Get out of my
house. Get out of my house. See you later. Man, it's so funny. It's getting destroyed. Hey,
you said no mercy. I did. How did you get up that high? I don't know. Maybe it's like a move my guy
has. Yeah, it's a move to die. Okay. All right. You thought you had it. You thought you had it.
Get out of my house. Hey, get ready. Oh, be careful with this. Be careful with this. No,
I was swinging at you. The ball went through me. It was very bizarre. It was bizarre, wasn't it?
Come on. I faked you out. You see, you thought I was going to hit it, but then I missed. I was
just going for the alley-oop. What is your special move? We saw mine. Mine's like insane.
Oh, God. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I'm trying to like hit it again. Oh, here you go.
I don't know how to get up that high to even get it. Can you... Oh, I jumped. Can you... Maybe my...
Oh, you can double jump. I can't double jump. Yeah, that's the thing your character can do,
not mine. I hit that. I hit that. No, I hit you and it canceled out your swing. Well, you know what?
I don't even care. I don't even care. I don't even care. Try to get it. How did you come back?
You're not coming back. You're not going to come back and win this. No, you're not going to use
your double jump and like double jump all over me. What? I thought I had way more time. It didn't go
all the way to the edge. Redo, rematch, triple match. Let's go. Let's go. This is like a dirty
pool. You don't like the dirty pool level? It's kind of cool, I guess.
You're really good with the alligator. I wasn't really... Hold on. I was just trying to figure out
one very... Come on. You read right through that. So is this the perfect that I'm going for?
You're not going to get a perfect. I can guarantee you that. See? Curl up in a ball. He can't see you.
All right. No. Get over here. You did that by accident. You didn't even know. No, I was trying
to hit you out. I knew you were going for a jump because you always do the jumps.
I always do do the jumps. You got to jump in. You don't have good anti-airs.
I thought you were going to hit it right back, but you didn't. Nope. No, I'm meta gaming.
All right. Fine. Get meta gamed. All right. I'm obviously not going to do that again.
He hit it underneath you this time. Whoa. You hit that from behind you because you have a tail.
I did a tail whip. Oh, doing the tail whip. Oh, you want to do a tail whip again?
You know what? Every time you jump into it and I keep thinking you're hitting it
like this. Yeah. Oh, like this. Oh, I did not think you were going to get that. I was putting
my controller down and about to start the ship talking. How do you get those every time?
I'm a sly alligator. I almost just lost right there.
Oh, now it is one and one. Who is going to end this epic battle of epic proportions?
What is happening? What just happened? That was the scariest thing I've ever done.
I didn't even think you hit it. Like this game's fun.