I want to know how bad this microphone is.
Am I coming out like one side of your ear?
It sounds great. Well, it's about to sound probably way worse.
You got atmosphere.
That's what you got with me.
You know, I was going to do like this.
Camera's not working.
Uh, there is no camera.
I'm in my living room right now.
Like, oh, green screen stream.
I painted my living room wall green.
I hope it looks alright.
Yeah, it's like I painted it like it's like a it's like a green slash blue.
It might not work.
So by the way, how are we doing?
Let's get it started right now.
That's a lot of space.
I haven't even done anything yet.
We just started.
I got a big living room, guys.
You understand?
I got props over here.
I got there's a lot of shit I have here.
I'm going to take this slow because I need to make sure
that I took a long time trying to get this correct.
I might need a little more light this way.
I'm saying like here, maybe a little bit like right.
Let me see.
Is anybody else here with me?
No, let me do this.
Take the mic with me.
I can't take the mic with me.
That's not going to work.
All right, let me make sure that this is correct.
All right, let me just let me turn this up a little so we can see.
What if I do this?
That makes it a little better, right?
That actually looks all right.
And we're in 60 FPS.
The 60 FPS, right?
That's what this thing is, right?
Can you see?
You can see all the frames, right?
That's yeah, 720p.
Yeah, to get to do 60, I have to do 720.
So this is 720p 60 from motion.
I can do 1080p 30, but I don't think it'll look as good
because I was doing it and I was moving around.
It was like you couldn't even it was hard to tell what I was even doing.
Try 1080.
Hold on.
You guys tell me, okay?
You tell me if 1080 looks better because I tried them both.
So this is 1080 30.
Let me move that.
I'll do some karate chops.
Don't worry.
Now, so this is 1080.
This is 1080 30.
So you see what I'm saying?
It's like bring it back.
Wait, wait, hold on a second.
Hold on.
Hold on a second.
This is this is 1080 30.
What would you rather have?
Higher quality image or faster karate chops?
Do you see what I'm saying?
60 fps versus disgusting 30 fps.
Well, we can do both.
We can do both.
Let me just make sure we got hold on.
Let me get this.
One second.
Hold on.
1080.
I'll give you 1080 like roundhouse kick and you see the differences, okay?
Well, you do think I could do roundhouse kicks.
Oh, wow.
I didn't know German could do roundhouse kicks, huh?
All right, now let's take a look at that.
It's 60.
You tell me which one you want more.
Here we go.
60 fps.
Okay, there we go.
All right, here's 60.
Ready?
I'll give you a roundhouse kick at 60.
60 or 1080.
You want better quality or you want...
Wait, it's blurry.
Maybe I hold on a second here.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, hold on a second, guys.
Oh, whoops.
Okay.
60 fps is nice, but doesn't look good.
All right, we'll do 1080 for a while.
Here's 1080.
Can I like force it to 60?
I don't think I can.
But I don't think I could even...
That 1080 60 would be bad.
I can't stream from here on 1080 60.
This wouldn't work.
Hey, let me...
Hold on a second.
Everybody stay where you are, okay?
I'm gonna...
I don't think I can stream it at like 6,000 or 7,000 from here.
I'm at 5,000 up.
I might be able to get away with 6,000 or 7,000.
I don't know.
Maybe not.
That's gonna be tricky.
I think this is good.
There is glare up here, though.
Over there.
There's glare right here.
All right.
Is it better?
I mean, it's...
This one needs to be dropping.
Uh-huh.
It's a process.
How's that?
Better?
I should say it's a lot better than mine.
But the bat...
I need to turn this one back on.
This one, not this one.
Okay.
This one is good.
This one is also all right.
Change shirt?
I got plenty of shirts.
All right.
I'm ready.
So I have...
Take a look.
You wanna see?
You wanna see what we're working with today?
I have about 100 actions.
Oops.
So I think this is as good as we're gonna get it.
Maybe a little bit hot.
No, that's all right.
It's a big living room.
Yeah, I got a 6,900 square foot house.
All right.
I really wish I could get rid of that.
I don't think I can get rid of that.
I don't think that'll be a problem keying it, though.
Let me try this one thing.
That makes that brighter.
Okay.
I'm gonna keep it like this.
But give me one second where I find where these are.
I don't know where they are.
Shit.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, here we go.
Almost.
There's a little bit of glare on the sides here.
Am I making...
I'm casting shadows though.
It's perfect.
Okay.
Shadow.
All right.
So how we're gonna start this is...
I might as well just start.
Video editors can easily handle this.
Well, then I'm getting rid of the shadow.
Oh, you get...
You want the...
Go back?
Oh, God.
All right.
Fine.
Okay.
You good?
We cool with this?
Go back.
All right.
Here we go.
So the first thing that I want to do...
Let me make sure you can be seen here.
So I got a lot of space here, right?
As you can see.
I'm gonna do standing, walking, running.
I'm gonna do it all in the same...
How's that?
Give us a tour.
All right.
I think we're good.
So here's what you're gonna get.
Ready?
Begin!
Watch.
Okay.
There you...
That's standing.
Okay.
We got...
You got like a couple of angles, a couple of close-ups, right?
We're gonna move on.
You need more?
Okay.
I'll give you another one.
Here.
We're just getting through the general motions, you know?
So here's another like standing.
Just like kind of doing whatever.
Good day.
You're my guy, right?
All right.
Now we're gonna do...
Louder.
I know...
Guys, you have to understand.
There are like a hundred of these.
I'm just getting the good ones.
They're not the good ones.
I'm just getting like the easy ones.
Can you mic up?
I don't have like a lav mic.
I'll be louder.
Don't worry.
T-pose is on the list.
Okay.
Here we go.
You ready?
This is walking now.
Walking.
Some more...
I'll get some more walks for you.
I'll get you some walking in place.
Get some more walks here so it's a little bit hot.
A little bit more faster.
Close the camera.
What the fuck?
Now when he's running, it's like a break.
Faster?
He's coming.
Oh boy.
All right.
What else we got?
And that's it.
See you tomorrow.
All right.
I didn't bring any...
I brought coffee.
That's gonna drive me up.
I need to go drink my water from this toilet sink.
I'm gonna go drink water out of the toilet.
All right.
Hold on.
Here we go.
Next up is dashing, dodging, and crouching.
Crouching.
Walk in.
Wait.
Autofocus turned on.
Should've.
Stepping off screen.
Yeah.
I have to.
Autofocus shouldn't be on.
I just recalibrated.
All right.
Here we go.
Next.
I'm gonna like tire myself out right now.
Punch.
Being punched.
Kick.
Being kicked.
Being hit with objects.
Fuck me.
I gotta change my clothes soon here.
All right.
Let's do it.
I'm doing like all the Mortal Kombat moves.
Get the fuck out of here.
Yep.
I don't want to fight you.
I don't want to.
I don't want to fight you, man.
I don't...
I didn't want to knock you out, but I didn't.
Oh, did you think I was going to catch it?
That's it.
Broken bones.
And the ground.
How are you going to use that?
My shoelace came untied.
All right.
Kicks.
Oh, I just ripped my pants.
My pants almost just ripped in half.
Holy shit.
Oh, yeah?
That's two backhands.
Ooh, two.
I'm supposed to be doing kicks.
We'll do one of these.
Try again.
Fuck you.
All right.
I got to get hit.
Face.
Each arm.
Each leg.
Why do I keep the puke?
The shoe.
My shoe's untied.
God damn it.
I have to puke every time.
All right, we're done.
You.
It's time for you to pay.
You're going down.
The bigger they are, the harder they fall.
What is that?
All right.
Give me, let me get a toilet water break.
I'll be right back.
I haven't even gotten to the props yet, guys.
There's a bag of props over here.
There's a bag of props right there.
All right.
So that settles that.
Please do a fat roll.
We'll get to that in a second.
Hold on.
All right.
So climbing.
I'm going to climb.
Climb.
Let's climb.
Made it to the top.
That's not going to work.
I can't do it.
Okay.
That doesn't even work.
All right, here we go.
All right.
Just a little.
Because here is a flat surface right here, man.
I'm doing this the wrong way.
I have to do it this way.
This does that.
This is what is here.
It's me.
I'm in front of a screen.
What the fuck am I doing?
That's better.
Why am I on this?
Just go like this.
Why am I doing the struggling to get over a cliff?
I don't know why I'm into that right now.
That's you up there.
Hey.
Can you throw me down a life raft or something?
No life raft.
Don't worry.
I'll get it.
My fucking pants just fell down.
Hey, can you give me a hand down here?
That's like a 400 foot jump.
I guess I'll give it a try.
No, no.
Don't worry about me.
Two.
Three.
No, I'm good, man.
I'm good.
Idiot.
All right.
Cam back down.
Yeah, I'll get it.
All right.
Now, now we're going to do facial reactions.
Cam down.
Oh, no, I will.
I will.
I got to get these, though.
It's like, right, right.
It's good, right?
Say it again.
Come on.
These are close-ups.
So you can get my facial reactions.
Come on, right?
Please.
It's my birthday today.
Thanks, everybody.
No, that's supposed to be a surprise birthday party.
Come on.
I mean, why is it so dark in here?
Honey?
Oh, it's my birthday.
The doorknob is up at his chest.
Can I just put it right here?
Right on the chin.
Right there.
Ooh.
Ear lawsuit inbound.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Throw some punches the other way.
So you think about this brain screen, right?
Get close, like here.
I need to, like, blow it out.
It's designed for me to be, like, standing here.
But, dude, I didn't release full-body stuff.
Maybe I'll blow it out and get some more.
Do some more screaming.
Too much head room.
Ah, I mean, but that's all I got for the green on the bottom, though.
I mean, in the editing program, right, you'll just take it.
You'll just take this side and this side and just get it from here, you know?
So hopefully this is not going to be too much of a blowout.
I don't think it will be.
But I'll do some more of this stuff with the back blown out.
So there is no shadow at all.
Anyways, let's get going.
I hope you brought green clothes.
Well, I guess, here, hold on.
I can do this.
Let me test something here.
Because I have, like, a tester.
Let's see how it works.
Okay, let me just get it on here.
Because this will be able to give us a good indication of how this is going to play out.
Let me loop it.
Then you tell me.
Okay, let's get a green key on here.
And make sure I have it on there correctly.
Green!
Why is this not doing it?
Okay, let's take a look.
Ah, the beach!
It's like, it's a little watery here.
It's a little too watery.
He's giant.
Well, also, keep in mind, this is like, just, this is like the, I just have this through OBS.
You know what I mean?
So let me see if I do this.
This is just like the default settings through OBS.
You know what I'm saying?
If I mess with the settings a little bit.
I'm transparent!
Let me see.
I mean, with playing around the settings, whoever is, you know, going to be using it,
I think it'll be all right.
Yeah!
Okay, so I'm going to turn this off.
Don't worry, I'm getting in a full suit in doing a weather report, guys.
Don't worry.
We just, we've only been live for 40 minutes.
I got like, I got like another hour and a half worth of stuff to do.
I just, I'm just doing the basics.
It's nine more hours.
I don't know about that.
All right, so here you go.
So now, I gotta get chased.
And then I have to chase someone.
So that looks all right.
So here's the chase sequence.
So I'm going to be going from this way to that way.
So I have to chase, and then I have to chase somebody else.
Get back here!
You get back here!
Come here, you bastard!
Get the fuck out of the way!
Get out of the way, you fucking idiot!
Hey, come here!
Get back!
I don't know where to go.
I need, give me that!
Okay.
Get over here!
Get out of the fucking way!
What?
I'm in the middle of a chase, that's all I hear.
That's all I hear.
Shut up.
Shut up!
Hey, get in your car.
Hey, hey!
Get back here!
All right, now I gotta get chased.
Oh, Jesus!
Oh, no!
Please!
Oh, my God!
Right in my head!
Toilet water.
Be right back.
Jesus, running in place is so much fucking harder
than just running in general.
Getting winded after light exercise.
No, it's the running in place.
All right.
Now I gotta walk backwards, terrified of something.
Don't worry, I'm going to do death animations.
Don't worry.
We need some up close stuff, too.
Like, chasing.
Like, so you can get from like here,
from like, you know, from here up.
Oh, not hungry.
What the fuck?
Really?
Dude, really?
Really, Scoob?
Okay.
Away from something.
Yes.
Just trying to go to the bathroom.
Easy.
You got something to say?
Oh, look at me!
Look at me!
Stop running.
All right, I mean.
Isn't that just wonderful?
Oh, look at me!
Fucking idiot.
I'm the man.
Oh!
Hey, fellas!
He thinks he's dumb!
Look at me!
Was the girl the best?
Hey, look at me!
Ah, yeah, that's right!
I don't know why I'm doing that.
Stop.
Stop doing this.
All right, ready?
Next!
Oh, god.
This is where we're going to get weird.
There's your T-pose.
Let's get a close-up a little bit closer.
You're like, look at me!
Loser.
All sides.
Fucking really?
All angles!
I feel like I'm at the tailor.
Good.
Scanning.
Character select screen.
Face scan.
Oh, my fucking god.
Hold on.
Give me a second.
I'll spin around.
What the hell is the editor?
There it is.
Look at me.
So.
Yeah, it's really cool.
I sat in the chair and they did it.
They scanned me.
And they always have this fucking weird face too.
Too fast?
Well, the autofocus.
Fucking autofocus.
Stop autofocusing.
All right, I'm done.
It gets smaller.
God.
All right.
Do a close-up.
Look at me.
I can't just do it.
What was it like?
This and then like this.
I don't remember what it was.
What did I do?
I don't know what I did.
I think it was like that and like that.
So you'd be like, huh.
You sure are talking a lot.
Oh, look at me.
No, I didn't do it right.
Oh, yeah.
Interesting thought process.
Wait, look at me.
Look at me.
That's what you sound like.
Why do I have to hit someone?
Why do I have to like slap somebody?
Okay, this is where it gets real.
I see him down there.
Roger that.
Taking target out.
And then like you've got like missiles coming at it.
But hold on.
I didn't fit it.
So now you're going to take it from here.
This guy's 33.
Hand was outside.
I can't balance for that long.
Why would I be flying like that?
I got to get these done because it's going to fucking hurt.
Time for a different shirt.
Toilet water.
Oh, by the way, Germania 2018 is next weekend.
Oh, what a drop.
He dropped it.
All right, how are we doing?
We're doing all right.
Okay, now I have to do a cliche superhero landing with a pose and a smirk.
This is going to take me a few times.
I don't like it.
What is this?
Find the center.
Bitch, that's two.
I can't do it.
I hate it.
You're expecting someone else.
I killed like 10 birds coming down.
I'm expecting someone else.
I didn't do it.
Somehow I like punched the ground.
I actually did do the landing there.
Why are you winding up your other hand?
Wrong hand.
Hold on.
So I went down with this.
All right, where's my phone?
I gotta see what the next thing is.
I haven't even gotten to the props.
Okay, point around in amazement, horror, and excitement.
Wow, you see?
I read about that.
Nice.
Look at that one.
Hey, mom.
Mom, I see it.
Yeah.
Wow.
Is it right there or is it over here?
I can't tell.
Now, this is show business.
Yeah, now that's show business.
I'm doing right now.
Spider-Man sweat mark.
Where?
Point in more directions.
Okay.
I don't know.
Don't step in that.
I don't know what kind of step on that.
Buy a belt.
I got too fat.
Now we have to do horror.
What?
What is that?
What is this thing right here?
What?
What the fuck is that?
What is that?
What is that thing?
What?
What the fuck is that?
What's that?
What's that one?
They're everywhere.
Stay on.
Hold on.
That right there.
That's why.
That's the reason right there.
I'm like lost.
The follower button.
Hey, man.
Welcome to the stream.
My name's Jerma.
Nice to meet you.
Right there.
Bingo.
That's the follow button.
If you click that,
every so often you're getting notified that I'm streaming.
And I do lots of fun things on this stream like
playing Hitman.
We played that last night.
That's right there.
Holy shit.
Look at that hair.
Right here, right?
Hey, let me do you a favor.
So you made it to the YouTube homepage.
How are you?
My name's Frank.
I'm your digital guy.
As you see here,
here's your viewing screen.
This screen right here is going to show you
some of your favorite videos
from Gangnam style
all the way to your grandma's outer fishing trip.
This is right here.
This is your space.
Down here, you've got the like button.
If you like a piece of content,
go ahead and press it.
If you don't like a piece of content,
ooh, thumbs down.
That's over there too.
On this side,
they're both going to keep up with me here.
Here's the subscribe button.
And if you like a content enough to want to subscribe
and potentially lose their videos on your feed
because we don't do that anymore,
you have to click a bell.
The bell's over here by the way.
Click that bell right there.
And then click another couple of buttons.
And then maybe you'll be able to see the content
you subscribe to.
This is your space.
This is it right here.
That was passive aggressive.
Oh, I almost forgot to mention.
That's me Frank again from Nvidia.
Hey, I almost forgot to mention.
Hey, it's me again.
The YouTube guy.
This is your space.
We talked about your space.
Well, better get out of the way.
I'm in front of your video right now.
Hey, pause it though.
This space right here is your fuck.
Hey, it's me again.
The YouTube guy that's in the corner of your videos
that comes up and gives you digital help.
I better get out of your space.
Here we go.
Now I'm here.
Fucking God damn it.
I have something very specific I want to say.
Hey, it's me.
The YouTube paperclip guy from Microsoft.
Except I'm another digital representation of hell.
Whoa, I'm in your space right now.
Whoopsie, I'm over here.
So if you want to monetize on YouTube,
click up there.
That button over there.
That's going to bring down a drop down
to click on the monetize button.
Whoa, but be careful.
We pay demonetize your entire channel
because nobody works here.
We just kind of put bots up that catch random shit.
And you might be caught in the crossfire.
But this is your space right here.
Oh, we've ruined entire channels
because we demonetized the entire channel.
Don't worry about that.
This is what you need to be concerned with right here.
I'll be going this way now.
So passive aggressive.
That wasn't even part of the show.
Oh, I got to do this one too.
By the way, disclaimer.
Hey, it's me again.
Disclaimer, I am in no way a YouTube
or any of its practices or its headquarters.
I'm just your friendly neighborhood
paperclip digital help guide guy.
There we go.
See, there you go.
Edit it out quick.
See, you can't edit it out because I just said it.
Rerecord the audio.
All right, I will mic a lot of these.
Don't worry.
We're blurry on the left side.
Like over here.
We're good.
All right.
All right, I got to.
Oh, this one's going to suck.
I have to fall and do this.
Do that right.
That's bloating to it.
Now, whatever.
That's not that high, right?
It's not about that high up.
I'm probably like 150,000 feet.
That's not going to, it's going to, right?
Let's roll.
The ground is coming real fast.
Holy shit, it worked.
I feel fine.
Side view is necessary.
This is your space.
Why do people do this?
There's no reason to do what I'm doing, right?
If you were falling,
you would be going like this.
You would just be like.
Why do we, why, what is this?
This is like I'm an actor.
Brain scrape, right?
My underwear.
Shit, it's all right.
Okay, what's next?
Something move.
Okay, there we go.
This got like knocked over.
For some reason that got like tilted.
Don't ask me why, but it did.
Weirdly enough, fall towards the camera.
I mean like, oh, I know what you mean.
Like go into the camera.
Here we go again.
Oh, no, no.
Why would I be looking at you?
Oh, shit.
Was I doing my ABCs?
Why would you do that before you died?
Follow you back to it.
Take care.
Okay, I gotta line this up.
Look at my back sweat.
I got like fucking 4,000 pounds of lights on me.
Okay, this one's gonna be good.
I like this one.
I can't, I can't get up.
I can't get up.
I think it's fucking too heavy.
If I go down, maybe though.
Oh, what a day's work.
Invest in a belt.
I had a lot of other things to think about
than putting a belt on today.
It's all right, I'm about to get in pajamas anyways.
All right, I might as well do this.
This is like one of the most requested things
that everyone wanted me to do.
So I'm gonna get them like here.
We'll start, we'll start here.
Okay, so ready?
No doubt.
Huh?
What?
Oh, no, my magical powers.
Earth.
Earth is on fire.
What?
No.
I just shit my pants.
I can't do it anymore.
Take the shirt off.
I can't take the shirt off.
Now I'm gonna do like various spells.
Fucking God damn it.
What the fuck was that?
Someone's gonna make me a Mugen character.
Jesus Christ, okay.
All right, we're almost done with the actions here.
I don't know, I don't know about this one,
but this one would do.
Just let that here, it's still good.
What?
Really?
No way.
No, that's all right.
Nice.
Wait, what happened?
No, but we're still live.
I dropped some frames.
What was the last thing I did?
Should still be good.
Okay, did you see the last thing I did?
No, I dropped like 10 frames, that's fine.
All right, so here's this one that people have been asking for.
Fix the framing?
No, what do you mean fix the framing?
It's gotta be cropped anyways.
It has to be pulled back and forth.
That's gonna stay there.
Please dab?
I vetoed dabbing, so I'm definitely not gonna dab.
This needs to be like over here.
Why is this doing this?
Come on, man.
Give me a break.
Too small?
I mean, I could move it forward.
Maybe that'll help a little up there.
That should be good.
Yeah, that's good.
All right, so what's next?
It's on a slant.
It just looks like that because this thing,
it's actually really annoying actually.
Hold on.
Why the fuck is this doing this?
I wish it wouldn't do that.
Move the tripod a little.
It's the tripod.
I had it before.
This needs to come up a little bit like this.
How the fuck does that make any sense?
It makes no sense because the tripod says it's level.
I think maybe it's the way it's painted
because it looks like it's a little bit of an edge
over here that goes a little further in
or further out.
How's that?
Yeah, I think it just looks like that
because the way that the ground is over here.
All right, let's go.
Uh, so slowly peek into frame.
How am I going to do this?
This is going to be fucking hard.
I'm going to get hurt doing this one,
so I hope you're ready to see me
get like actually fucking injured.
Shut up.
Belly.
We saw his belly.
I'm sorry that I have to do this.
That was that was one of the most requested things.
All right, act like I'm shaking hands with somebody.
I don't know why.
And then swimming.
And then it's time to move on to the actual like breathing.
Good to see you, man.
So that's a nice firm handshake.
Okay.
You let go.
Thanks, man.
That's a good handshake you got there.
Hey.
Hey, it's been so long.
Hey, how are you?
Come on.
Yes.
Good to see you.
Put it there.
That's it.
No, it's good to see you, Mike.
Hey.
Hey, put it there.
All right, good to see you.
I'll give these.
We'll do it from here.
Hey.
Yeah, I'd love to shake your hand.
Fuck yeah.
Fuck yeah, man.
So you still doing that thing?
You still in school?
You know, let's do the other one too.
All right.
Hey.
Hey, it's Tim.
Oh, my God.
It's good to see you.
Thanks, man.
Yeah, it's great to see you again.
Tim?
Tim Davidson.
What?
Hey, man.
How are you?
No shit.
I got two of my own.
What's this?
That's just my new car.
It's beauty, isn't she?
I souped her up too.
V6 engine.
What do you got back there?
Not as good as mine, but still worth having in your garage.
Anyway, it's great.
That's great that you're doing so well.
Yeah, I know you gotta go.
I just caught you.
Let me get back.
Let me get into this little thing over here.
You know what I mean?
Good to see you again.
Yeah.
Take care of yourself, Tim.
See you later, man.
I do have a wheel.
It's a horse.
There's some serious hydraulics in that car.
Oh!
What the fuck?
Okay.
That was me getting on a horse.
I was me on a horse.
I was on a horse.
That's a horse.
That's me on a horse, and that's the thing that you hold.
Delete the stream.
Delete the whole stream.
Delete's over.
Delete it.
Delete the stream.
Delete.
Don't.
Nobody.
Idiots.
Nobody use that.
You'll be in big trouble.
What an old joke.
Puppet stream.
I don't even have a sock on.
Well, I just, whatever.
All right, we're almost done with the actions.
I have to swim now.
Can't you just, like, fuck, can't you just do swimming and...
Can't swimming and flying be the same thing?
Well, I guess I was fucking screaming, so that doesn't work.
This is, this is flying.
I'm just flying again.
I trust you.
How was that?
He can't swim.
How does he not know how to swim?
Just wait, wait, hold on.
There's more to that.
That was swimming.
I'm done with swimming.
Swimming's done.
He says, this is a huge great screen.
Contemplating life choices.
All right, here we go.
So here's where we're going to do some reactions.
We're like just about, we're pretty much more than halfway done.
Well, actually, there's a lot of, oh my God, there's so much shit.
We're like 30, 40% of the way done.
All right, here we go.
This is what, this is what you waited for.
So we got all the actions out of the way.
Now, here we go.
This is what you wanted.
Now, this is by far, this is the best part right here.
This is my favorite part.
This is the best part.
Stop talking.
Nice.
This is terrible.
Absolutely terrible.
Nothing about this is good.
Not one thing.
God, I hate this.
I hate this.
This is terrible.
What a gamer.
What a god of a gamer.
Seriously.
This is the thing I'm talking about right here.
I've told you guys this before.
Absolute perfection.
No ifs, ands, or buts.
This right here is absolute perfection.
What a gamer.
Hold on, hold on.
Wow, wow.
This is what it looks like up close.
From back there, it could have been anything.
This is perfect.
It's exactly what I was talking about.
Turn it up.
Are you in charge of this?
Get to shut this off.
Shut them all off.
Turn your lights in your house off too.
You really fucking watching this shit?
Oh, please.
Oh my god.
Fucking god.
Terrible.
Yeah.
Yes.
That's it.
Okay, so.
Hold on, I'm going to do this one.
Whoa.
So this is the virtual world of the world.
Cut.
So this is the virtual world.
Why can't I say that?
Virtual world.
Whoa.
So this is the virtual world.
It's amazing.
Fascinating.
All right.
Now how am I going to do this?
I have to get like shot at.
Time.
Close.
I want to keep the actions in the same close though
because if people are going to be cutting between stuff
then they kind of need continuity.
So let me get through like the most of the actions.
You got me.
All right, I'm not doing you got me anymore.
What am I?
What?
What a way to die.
Am I giving birth?
I have to make the noise, man.
All right, here we go.
It's almost time to bring out the props.
All right, so here we go.
Hold on, give me one second.
Camera's too high.
All right, so where is...
I don't know why this looks so off.
Sorry, I just minimized my action list here.
Okay, so now I need to frantically run around
as if the building is on fire.
Oh no.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, oh, it's everywhere.
Let me fix this shit.
This next one is sleep and be startled by something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm up.
Five more minutes.
Okay, I'll do it five more minutes.
Why am I making like jeans and...
I gotta go like that pajamas.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Costume change.
My starboard is pajamas.
No, no, you do it.
You do it.
I'm sleeping.
Yeah.
Okay, mom.
Five more minutes, mom.
Mom!
Hey, mom.
Can I have a glass of water?
No!
I'm getting the fuck off.
I have like a fucking tantrum.
I'm not having a tantrum on the ground over there at 33.
Ow!
No, did I just fuck this up?
No, we're good.
All right, so now I need my phone back.
Where the fuck is that?
Right here.
I have like a fucking tantrum.
Uh, so now we're gonna deal with the weather in my pajamas.
Okay, here we go.
Like outside with like no shoes on.
Let's get close.
All right, here we go.
Fighting game moves?
Don't worry, I'm gonna do it.
Brain.
Why would you put your hands up?
Out of the brain in your pajamas.
All right, so now I got this one.
If I don't move, it won't see me.
Costume change.
Still in PJs.
Oh, this one's gonna be good.
This one's gonna be good.
God damn it.
Transitioning into...
Oh, shit.
Stinging my blood.
Honey detected.
Nice costume change.
I walked off the green screen.
Fuck.
All right, you ready?
Are you ready for me to do prop-related material?
Here we go.
I'm gonna look like such a fucking idiot.
I have three pairs of pants on.
I have literally three...
I have jeans, pajamas, and now suit pants on.
Hope of that.
I'm gonna look like such a drunk.
Like my tie's gonna be undone.
I'm gonna be like a drunk guy at a wedding.
With like socks.
Just imagine I just like, I drank like fucking a pint of vodka.
I don't fucking care about this tie.
I got a t-shirt on.
All right.
Looking good.
Chip's got a fucking clip on.
I gotta keep it like that though.
That's so fucking funny.
Is either of these zipped up?
That's right, Diane.
As you can tell, there's a cold front coming down through California here over Mississippi.
That's gonna be about 45 degrees cooler than you typically would have out there in the Midwest.
Put the next slide up, please.
That's correct, Diane.
So as you see here, Massachusetts has got a little bit of a hot front coming in.
Pretty easy what you're looking at here.
Halloween weekend's gonna be a little bit tough for you there.
Make sure you bundle up.
Make sure you get a lot of hats on.
So next weekend, we've got two, that's right, two...
Oh my, did the stream die?
Are we good?
Are we still fine?
Good.
That's right, Diane.
It's gonna be a cold one this weekend.
As you can see here, we've got some low pressure coming up through the mountains here,
going all the way down over southern New Hampshire.
That's right, it's gonna make its way down here across the Nile River there.
And then it's gonna wrap back around and come back towards Massachusetts,
which then, unfortunately, your Saturday football game's gonna get potentially rained out.
As you see, two, that's right, two cold fronts coming from here and from here.
And it's gonna be a breezy one.
They're gonna collide together and they may be a gosh darn tornado.
So you better bundle up out there and make sure you have anti-tornado clothing on
and anti-tornado hats because they might blow away.
Diane?
I'm not so sure about that one.
It's gonna be a hot one, that's right.
It's gonna be a hot one out there, Diane.
As you can see, look at how big that sun is.
Look at how big that is.
I don't even need to tell you temperature numbers.
That's just a big old sun, ain't it there?
And it's gonna be shining across the entire U.S. of A, that's right.
Sun here, sunshine over here, and even sunshine down here,
where you don't typically get it, if you know what I'm saying.
So, bundle up out there.
It's gonna be a cold one.
Every day's a cold one with the sun out there.
And Diane, go fuck yourself!
Wow!
You know, typically I bring you the weather on a daily basis at 6 a.m.,
6 a.m. in the morning with Diane, Carol, and Rick.
But today, I want to show you something different.
Besides the fact that, first, be aware,
we are gonna have some snow over here in the Colorado Rockies,
coming through here, down into the southern part of Colorado.
But, forget that.
I want to show you something that I care about.
Something that I want to show.
That I haven't been having, I had no opportunity to do it until now.
That's me on my fishing trip.
That's me and my son.
I just wanted to show.
There we are.
And back to the weather.
We do have, like I said, some cold from who cares about this.
America, go out and live your lives.
Don't worry about the weather.
You just go outside and sniff.
You'll be just fine.
It's gonna be cold some days.
It's gonna be hot some days.
It's just, just go out there.
Go out there and live.
Diane, why is the tie three-fourths the size?
All right, so now, here's another one.
I have to get the tie off for this one.
Here's the last one.
We'll do one more weather.
Hey, it's me.
That's right, Diane.
We got the wacky weather report coming up.
That was my note.
So as you see here, it's gonna be, wow,
it's gonna be breezy tomorrow night.
So make sure you stay indoors.
60 mile per hour gusts.
Be careful out there.
Whoa, easy.
Next up, oh, of course, gotta tell you,
the local pumpkin festival is gonna be canceled
because, oh no, it's raining outside.
Back to you, Diane.
Diane, will you marry me?
That was just Jim Carrey.
He looks like he wears...
That's right.
Here's the weather.
Yeah, the roads are gonna be slick.
Especially on that road there, that one over here.
I think this is gonna be at least two or three.
I don't know.
Just look.
This is, I think, two or three different weathers
that are gonna come together
and find a dual weather scenario.
No, I don't care.
Just job.
I went out last night and I got destroyed.
All right, here we go.
Now I have to accept an award.
No tie for this one.
Nice.
Right, thank you.
Well, thanks everybody.
I just wanna say, being the number one streamer on Twitch,
it was a dream come true.
No, I never thought I would be here.
I never thought I would get to the stage in my life
where I was the number one most viewed,
number one most subscribed, number one most watched.
We're bigger than ESPN now.
So, I mean, right, yep.
That's a fan.
That's a fan up there, guys.
So, it's ridiculous that now
I'm able to buy Disney,
which I never thought I'd be able to do.
I swear to God, I'm gonna make the incredible stream.
Yep.
So, thank you everybody so much for all that you've done.
We made it.
We did it.
Well, oh, I did.
I did.
But, yeah.
Yeah, thank you.
I'll see you all, hey, Tuesdays and Thursdays and Fridays.
What's that?
Yeah, okay.
No, yeah, well, I'm not gonna play Minecraft.
Thanks for the enthusiasm.
I will see you guys real soon, Tuesday, Thursday, Friday.
Much love to you.
Thank you for this award.
Thank you for this.
You guys are amazing.
Thank you.
All right, one more of these.
Got it.
Yes.
All right.
Wow.
Whoa.
I never thought that I would be winning this award.
Unbelievable.
Let me just say,
from the bottom of my heart, thank you for all of your support
and for all of your wonderful contributions.
I must say, it's been quite a year.
Quite a year, in fact, that I've got two more games to announce.
That's right.
Two more games.
With the most ingenuity and the highest caliber of skill
that any of our developers have ever done,
it is my pleasure to announce our latest title.
Never before has there ever been quite a scenario like this one.
Diablo Immortal is nothing to do with me.
I'm not gonna make a Blizzard reference because I have nothing to do.
I have a different game to show you.
Here it is.
I can't go down that road.
That's right.
Hey.
Are there any gamers in here?
Of course there is.
Got quite a lineup this year.
Last year we saw some of the best games highly reviewed
that we've ever had as a company here.
We have you all to thank.
Our average Metacritic score reached over 58.
And I find it completely necessary to now show you, the fans,
a brand new experience that you won't have anywhere else.
We're talking about complete open world, complete open environment,
and complete and total control over your surroundings.
Yeah.
You knew it was coming.
But were you ready for this?
I present to you, made with me and my wife and our three kids,
World Zone.
There we go.
Okay.
World Zone is a PVP-inspired top-down FPS hyphen strategy game.
Here's some gameplay footage of it now.
You'll get this in your hands as soon as Monday.
Monday.
Like I'm talking about tomorrow.
You understand?
You're going to get this game on Monday.
Monday.
This Monday.
And that's my time.
Get your hands on it Monday.
Have a great rest of your conference.
Tell them about the shoes.
Whatever.
No, I'm not redoing it with shoes on.
All right.
Now I'm going to bring in a couple of props.
This is a baseball.
I'm soxing this one too.
There it goes.
Here's what I have to say about this.
See this bullshit?
Get out of here.
No, no, no, no.
Turn it up.
I saved the world right here.
I just saved the world.
Don't destroy the green screen.
All right, hold on.
This was an incredibly highly requested thing.
And I don't know why, but you'll see.
He's getting into it.
Open it up.
Nobody asked for that.
That was like one of the top requested things.
I'm not putting the suit on and doing that.
This one was highly requested too.
Here, let me get it.
That's a little too high.
Is your ladder this?
Somebody monitor the driving.
Here's the lab boat wheel.
God.
Every various driving sequences.
Do it over the shoulder.
I mean like this.
Jesus.
Yeah.
Taking you guys on the scenic route.
Hey.
Careful.
Whoa.
Hey kids, you want to sing a car song?
I don't either.
Hey.
Dave, right?
Welcome to Lyft.
So you're from here?
Yeah.
I grew up here.
I know all the secrets.
Don't like turn off your GPS.
I know where I'm going.
What's that?
Yeah.
No, I've been driving for like probably a couple of years now on Lyft.
Right.
Yeah.
Yeah, well I moved.
I moved here when I was probably 19 or so.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Sorry.
Yeah.
It's a great place.
You'll probably like it.
He's off-roading.
He talked two months.
Do one facing you now.
How would that make any sense?
Hey.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've lived around here.
I've lived here for about 10 years.
Can you not do that?
Can you relax back there, please?
This is what you're doing is incredibly distracting.
That's all.
I'll get you out of the car if you don't.
Jesus.
Did you see that?
Why am I going back and forth like this?
No, I'm good.
I'm good.
Oh, shit.
No, I'm not.
Holy shit.
Look at you.
Like, look at.
Why?
That's creepy.
I just did the dinosaur thing.
Which I can't delete that now.
You want me to go like this?
Hey, how are you?
How you doing?
How are things?
Just don't talk.
What?
Why am I doing that?
All right, I'm done.
All right.
Let me get a water.
We're getting to the end here.
There's still like maybe five or 10 things left to do.
Oh, hold on.
Somebody wanted this real bad.
I need the soup.
The James Bond thing.
Everybody has socks on at this stage apparently.
I need shoes.
All right, hold on.
But I got to.
I have to like make it.
I have to.
I'm like going over right now.
I got to make like I got to text somebody.
Give me one second.
Let me write like BRB on the screen.
We got like maybe five or 10 things left to do.
Shoeless.
Here, hold on.
Give me like a few minutes.
I'll be right back.
I need text on here.
Where the no, I'm not putting the dinosaur thing on ever again.
You got your one like what a fucking joke.
That was so bad.
Like I am I am embarrassed.
I bought that shit.
You know what I mean?
I'll be right back.
I'm not back yet, by the way.
I just wanted to make sure I made this really, really clear.
So I've I've been drinking water out of the sink this whole time.
Like literally like drinking like toilet, like the water in the toilet.
They have like a they have like a water thing here.
Like in like in the other room.
Okay.
Somebody said weird flex, but okay.
What a weird flex.
All right.
So let's do what is I don't know what that means.
Stop.
Do some flexes.
Well, I got to put on my shoes again.
These suit pants aren't in the box.
Is this a good James Bond hat?
No, it's like an old grandma gardening hat.
What did I put?
Why do I have this?
It's perfect.
It's the undertaker.
I don't know what my other shoe is.
Do you see my shoe?
I I I did.
I actually I don't know where it is.
I have no idea what my other shoe is.
Please pretend to be a grandma gardening in a suit.
Oh, there's like so many other things people requested.
I this I got.
I laugh because these these fell out of the bag.
Shitty boss from like an anime.
I'm like the one henchman that the guy goes through before he goes to the real bad guy.
Coffee space Spider-Man.
Think of blood-borne enemy.
Oh shit, zombies, zombies.
No, forget about the zombies.
You got it.
Here we go.
Let's have this.
Oh, did I get him?
I know I got him.
Sure.
Oh, new shirt going on.
I'm going to regret this.
All right.
So you guys tell me, you think I'm going to regret this more than I regret already
the dinosaur?
Oh, it was a clean bar.
Delete that one, too.
I want you to delete that whole thing.
That's got to be the biggest.
That's going to be the biggest bane I've ever seen.
Good thing I got this.
Sell that to a merchant.
Do you think I'll be able to get it with this?
I'll try just barely.
One more.
All right.
Nice.
Throw it.
You guys mind if I mine here?
Not a big deal, dude.
I mean, this is my house.
And it's much better than yours.
Well, I do get a pretty sweet house.
Way better than your Minecraft house, dude.
What's that?
Oh, you like!
You like what I have here, don't you?
Yeah.
Well, how do you think I made it?
You're in my garage.
Is he taking requests?
Yes.
When I'm done with all the ones that I want to do, he'll take requests.
Oh my god, this looks like shit.
And don't forget about me, the newest turtle, Socrates.
I may be small, but I sure got lots of power.
With my trusty curved blade, I slash those putties like nobody's business.
Check me out.
You'll see a little bit of footage right here.
That's right, Donatello.
And we should all eat our vegetables.
Like, ah!
That's right, Donatello.
And another thing.
Eat your vegetables and fruits, too.
They make you grow up big and strong like us turtles.
Like me, Leonardo.
Just stuff like that.
When you're older.
Not a great example.
There's too many of them.
Princess Bride?
God damn it.
I did the same thing I just did again.
Here's the only difference.
I can't wear this.
I look like a fucking idiot.
This is made for a kid.
This is supposed to be down here.
This is made for like a fucking seven year old.
I'm in like an X-wing.
Fighter One, what's your status?
That's right, let's take it to them hot guys.
Come on.
Watch your six.
Ah, I can't see him.
I can't get him.
I can't see him.
That is a negative here, man.
Hey, maybe you can get us a few rounds when we're done with this.
You know what I'm saying?
Watch out.
TIE fighters.
TIE fighters coming in.
Left side.
Right side.
Got him.
Watch your tail there.
I'm right behind you.
Yeah!
I'm going down.
No, I'm going down.
This is Fighter One.
I'm going down.
Fighter One going down.
Mayday!
No, I'm going to need it here.
This is the strangest plan I think I've ever been to.
Don't start with me here.
I am a pilot, but I'm also a Jedi too.
Can you hit that shit?
I can't take this.
Why would I take it serious?
I'm trying to close it.
It won't close.
Man, I already broke it.
Ah!
I don't think I can do it.
Let's try this again.
Really.
I just have to let you know.
You strike me down now, and I will become so much stronger than you.
I'll be at least a full tier up on a fighting game list than you.
And that was just me showing off.
It's time for the real fight.
Easy for you to say.
You're an evil Sith, but not me.
I'm a Jedi.
Oh!
Please don't kill me.
Please.
I'll be a Sith.
I will join the Sith right now.
I'll just join the Sith.
I pledge allegiance to be a Sith for the United States of America.
And to not the Republic, but to the Imperial for which you stand, the employer of the Empire,
one nation under, Dark Vader.
Ah!
Two more Star Wars.
Why is he spending so much time on Star Wars?
Even the darkest Star Wars fantasies.
How could you possibly make this into a clip?
I'm just acting out a fake scene that doesn't exist.
I just made up a scene that is not a scene in any movie.
Good luck.
I'll just do like standard lightsaber shit.
What the fuck was that?
I'm like fucking exhausted right now.
I've been going nonstop with this for three hours.
I've been drinking toilet water.
From the toilet.
From the toilet, by the way.
I just did this.
All right, that's it.
We're moving away from Star Wars.
I'm done with Star Wars.
Hi, I'm Jerma985, and you're watching the Disney Channel.
Hey, it's me, Jerma985, and you're watching the Disney Channel.
Hey, it's me, Jerma, and you're watching the Disney Channel.
Hey, it's me, Jerma, from the downtown of Center Sports.
You're watching the Disney Channel.
I'm already not from Disney.
Hey, it's Jerma from Jerma985, and you're watching Jerma985.
Oh, I hated that one.
I'm doing it again.
Expelliarmus!
Hey, it's Jerma from Jerma985, and you're watching...
Hey, you know, this thing!
That thing, da-da-da-da!
Hey, what's going on?
It's Jerma from Jerma985, and you're watching Jerma985.
No.
All right.
Hey, dude.
Hey.
Do you think I can reach?
Oh!
Oh, fuck!
Shut up, dude!
Shut the fuck up!
We're gonna get caught!
As you can see, I'm not very good at this.
Oh, I forgot about this one.
I forgot to put this on.
This is the one where I have to pretend I'm a toy from Toy Story.
Yeah!
It's a chance at spawning a Gmod rag doll.
All right, what's left?
Oh, god damn it.
I don't even have...
Oh, come on.
Get this one out of the way.
Can you see?
Oh, god.
Look!
That's fucked up.
Look.
Is that what that is?
That is a weird, weird image there.
Get the string off!
Is there like a...
That's like Gears of War, right?
That's like Gears of War shit, isn't it?
Just put like a chainsaw sound in here.
Sure.
All right.
I gotta look at my list, because I think there's only like three or four things
left to do.
Do the meme shit.
And that's gonna be it.
He looks like Mark Zuckerberg.
Okay, man.
So, here's the new, uh, here's the new phone.
Is that what he does?
What does he do?
Here's the new phone, dude.
All right, it's time for meme shit.
So, here's the new phone.
Wait, Mark Zuckerberg's Facebook now?
Well, I was gonna say like...
What?
Why was I like...
Why was I like an Apple?
What does that have to do with anything?
Pretend to pull a lever?
You got it.
Oh!
I didn't do it.
All right, let me look at my list.
There's probably not much more.
Um, perform CPR.
But on what, though?
Oh, I need to do this.
I forgot.
It's a different green though.
Stupefy!
We have to get out of here!
Expelliarmus!
Quick!
Hagrid!
Gedondo!
Be right back!
Get out of here!
Are they gone?
Stupefy!
I had to do that at least once.
Oh, I need to do this.
This is going to be hard.
This is not going to work.
It's not going to work.
This needs like a green mask.
I can probably do this.
Two different greens.
This is wearing a dress.
I'm just wearing a dress.
Frieza versus Goku.
I already did all my Spirit Bomb.
Let me try it again.
Somebody really wanted this.
I'll try and get it there.
Nope.
That ain't going to work.
Oh!
I can't get up.
I'm stuck in here.
Actually, I'm stuck in my shirt.
I don't look like such a dickhead.
No.
All right.
Let's move on to some meme shit.
Start with this one.
Here we go.
If two of the handlers were one in the bush, it looks like this is going to
be the end.
This is going to be the end.
It's gone.
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
Aren't you glad I didn't say banana?
Put this guy in a body bag.
He's dead.
Well, well, I mean, they do say it's got to be five o'clock somewhere.
Oh, yeah!
Well, it's got to be five o'clock somewhere, as my professor told me.
It's high in noon somewhere.
Yeah, that's too bad.
But they do say it's got to be five o'clock somewhere, as my professor told me.
It's high in noon somewhere.
Yeah, that's too bad.
But they do say it's got to be five o'clock somewhere, as my professor told me.
It's high in noon somewhere.
Yeah, that's too bad.
But they do say it's got to be five o'clock somewhere, as my professor told me.
It's high in noon somewhere.
Stop going off screen, Mr. Green.
Last one.
You know, they say the stars align for this wine.
So, what do we got here?
Two.
We know what they say.
Two is more than one.
All right, that's one.
Next up is...
Oh, what was the other meme shit?
It was Jojo poses.
I don't even have any idea what the fuck.
What was the other one?
What was the other meme one?
Oh, okay, right.
What was the other one?
What was the other meme one?
Oh, okay, right, right.
It was the snaps.
All right, so I need...
Spoilers for Infinity War.
If you haven't seen it yet, you have.
You've fucking seen Infinity War.
There's nobody in this chat that has not seen Infinity War.
Not one of you has not seen it.
But mute for the next 45 minutes.
Are you sure?
I don't even have an Infinity Gauntlet on.
It's like I'm just a guy.
You should have gone for the head.
And because of this, I'm going to do it with two hands.
And everyone dies.
Wait, wait, wait.
That means me, too.
No, wait, wait, wait.
No, that means me.
No, no, no.
I didn't not take it back.
Hey, Mr. Stark.
I don't feel so good.
Oh, there I go.
No, no, no.
Please, please, Mr. Stark.
Please, Mr. Stark.
I don't feel so good.
I don't feel so good about this.
No, no, no.
I don't feel so good.
No, no.
That's all I took myself back together
is to get the particles back in me.
Do the slap chop.
Hey, it spins with the slap chop.
Yeah, you're going to slap.
You're going to cry.
Your onions cry.
You're making me cry.
Yeah, throw it in the fucking sink.
So what we got here, quickest tuna salad you ever made.
Here we go.
Slap it a couple of times.
One, two, three.
Easy as pie.
The thing to clean it, it opens up like a butterfly.
See?
Take a look at that.
It's easy.
No, no, no mess.
No bullshit.
Throw it in the fucking sink behind me.
Oh, my God.
I just died.
All right.
Time to do some JoJo poses.
I was turning into Trump.
All right.
I'm looking at it.
I looked at this.
Somebody sent me like a compilation.
JoJo poses.
Which one am I typing in?
I'll do like three or four of them.
Am I going to hate this for the rest of my life?
What's worse?
Like, honestly, what's worse?
JoJo poses or the Velociraptor?
Really?
The Velociraptor is probably the worst thing I've ever done.
I mean, in my whole life.
In my actual entire life.
I can't think of anything that I would rather go back and redo.
You know, if I had a time machine, it was like, oh, hey, you could go back and fix one thing.
What would you fix?
It would be me doing that Velociraptor.
Now I understand why somebody wanted me to do it.
Now I get it why it was like one of the things that somebody put it in the channel there.
Because holy shit, that was the most embarrassing thing I've ever done.
And I can never take it back.
And it was on a green screen.
So now it could be used anywhere.
All right.
So could some of the mods help me out here?
I don't know what these are.
Are there any mods that like know JoJo at all?
JoJo is embarrassing.
People, everyone's telling me it is.
I don't know.
I know like three JoJo.
Somebody help me.
Okay.
JoJo poses.
I'm just going to look at a video and try to recreate it.
Okay.
Here's the only the best JoJo poses.
I can't like do half of these.
All right.
I'll do this one.
I need to look at it one more time.
So this one looks like it goes like this.
Like that.
That was awful.
I thought that was a pros practicing.
All right.
Let's pick another one.
Okay.
We click this one.
How does this one work?
You go like this.
This is worse than the Raptor.
Who else?
All right.
This one, he turns his hand into like a snake.
He goes, I'll do this one.
Oops.
He goes like, no, it's just look at me.
Look at me.
The Imgur link had a bunch more.
Okay.
I'm not doing that one.
I'm not doing the one with the guy puts his dick out.
What?
I don't understand.
Okay.
What?
I'll do Mewtwo.
All right.
Mewtwo goes like this.
It's like.
So that was, that's Mewtwo.
His fingers are different.
Okay.
They go like down too.
I'll do it.
He's getting into it.
All right.
What do they do?
The one above Mewtwo.
He's got like a surprised face and he's like, he's going like left foot out.
What?
You got it.
He dabbed.
So his feet, one is out like that.
All right.
Well, there it is.
Any more Jojo poses?
I want, I need one more that people really want and that's it.
This is like the highest voted thing in the entire poll.
The point.
Well, you guys are saying names like I, like I know these characters.
All right.
I see the point.
I'll do the point.
This one is just like a, a sideways stance with a point.
He tilts his head down.
Like this one's a little close.
It's like.
It's just Phoenix Wright.
Okay.
I'm done.
Phoenix Wright.
It's my favorite Jojo character.
Oh my God.
I think somebody gave a hundred dollars.
I don't have my stream labs really set up here, but Kyra Toby just gave a hundred fucking dollars.
One hundred.
Thank you so much Kyra Toby.
One fucking hundred dollars.
This is for you Kyra Toby.
One hundred bits.
One hundred dollars.
Bam!
All right.
Now delete that.
How many things need to be deleted from this stream?
At least like, look at my sweaty ass hair.
Delete it though.
After the stream's over.
I thought I could trust you.
Oh my God.
There's like so many subs coming in.
Are you serious?
Oh my God.
Well.
That was terrible.
Delete that too.
What does he do?
I don't know what he does.
I don't get.
He goes like.
Right?
Like.
Okay.
I'm getting like addicted to the green screen.
Oh my fucking God.
Are there people still?
People are subbing.
Oh my God.
Jacket goes on the arm.
Oh my fucking God.
There's so many subs coming in.
This is fucking ridiculous.
Hey.
So many subs are coming in.
Let's do some JoJo dances.
I'm going to do them all.
He does that.
Praise the sun.
Oh my God.
More.
I don't know if I have any more in me.
I'm like.
I'm so exhausted.
What I put.
Alright.
Let me tell you.
When I put.
When I put on this jacket to do the fucking weather man.
I was already out of gas.
The gas was out of the tank.
You need to do the dance.
The dance?
What dance?
Kyra told me to give a hundred fucking dollars.
And then another.
Oh my God.
I can't even keep up.
I don't have my like stream labs like available.
You guys are subbing like fucking crazy.
Tons of community subs going on.
Thanks so much guys.
This dance.
This one.
I can't.
This chats going so fast.
But let me.
Oh my God.
Five more.
Holy shit.
I can't.
Improvise.
What's my laugh tonight?
Jesus.
Dengustown fifty dollars.
Pocket Pauling fifty dollars.
Kyra told me a hundred dollars.
Like a hundred subs.
Holy shit.
Alright.
The Jojo dance.
Everybody in chat link this dance.
Because I can't click it.
Twitchy Pyro just gave fifty dollars.
Oh my God.
Alright.
Let's see what the dance is.
So let's see.
I can't.
This is like a whole thing.
I'm not going to be able to do this.
So it goes.
That's all I got.
I think everyone's going to be subbed by the end of this.
Holy shit guys.
I can't keep up with.
I don't have any of my stuff here.
I just have a laptop.
You guys are fucking amazing though.
Thank you.
Hope you guys had fun.
Because we're getting down to the end here.
I look forward to whatever you guys do with this.
The creativity from this community is second to none.
So I look forward to whatever you guys come up with.
So let me just while there's still a lot of people.
Let me talk about this.
So two weeks from now in two full weeks.
We're going to sit down and we're going to have a movie night.
So whatever you do with this footage.
Whatever you do with it.
Keep in mind a couple of very important things.
It has to be at least ten seconds long.
Ten seconds long.
So no like up.
Like we talked about right.
It's going to be ten seconds.
Or up to two minutes.
Nothing more than that.
If it's more than if it's two oh one.
It's out.
So up to two minutes at least ten seconds.
And these videos are going to be pre-screened.
So whatever you do with this.
Keep in mind if it's going to be shown on this stream.
Then it's going to be pre-screened.
So that means all potential bullshit that I don't want.
Obviously shown on stream will be taken care of.
This is not a contest by the way.
This is not a contest.
It's just for fun.
I just want to do it because it seemed like something fun to do.
No it's not.
It's not a contest.
But if you want to participate.
If you want to use this footage for something.
I hope you have fun.
How about this one?
How about Michael Jackson?
How about Moonwalk too?
See I went backwards.
I did it all wrong.
Oh reenact the gnome video.
I'm not even going to give you a chance.
All I said was I'm a gnome.
I didn't say anything else.
We said dude of Norman Osborn.
Peter you're a scientist.
I'm something of a scientist myself.
You know I find myself to be something of a scientist myself.
What?
Peter!
I hear you're quite the scientist.
Well I'm something of a scientist myself.
Get that in a fucking petri dish motherfucker!
I'm already editing this.
Oh somebody said do a fat roll.
Yeah I will.
I'm going to get hurt.
I'll do a fat roll with my fucking sword.
I'm going to be a Dark Souls character.
There you go.
Alright guys.
Dark Souls emotes.
TF2 taunts.
I'll do a scout.
Hey you're simply keeping track of my hands.
What?
Do it again.
Dark Souls emotes.
What?
Alright.
The sun.
The very sun is this right?
Right?
Like up here?
I'm doing that right?
You go look up into your tippy toes alright?
Hey!
There you go.
Very good.
I did the T-Pose.
I did like 30 minutes of T-Pose.
Oh I got it.
Yeah I already T-Posed.
Let me actually do some jumps.
I know a lot of people just like Mario.
Alright the cereal bowl.
Where is it?
No!
Get away from me with the spoon!
Don't eat me!
No!
No please!
Please don't do it!
That was me in a cereal bowl trying not to get eaten by a toddler eating cereal.
I did Toy Story earlier.
Alright.
I'm going to get out of here.
I am exhausted.
I want to make sure I got everything that I wanted to get.
The race!
The scooter!
Oh my god!
How do you work this thing?
I don't know how to work this.
It just like kicks up right?
There's some kind of locking mechanism on it.
Oh there it goes.
Just like that.
This is made for a small person.
I don't know how to ride this.
Do you see this shaking?
What's up man?
Alright one more.
Big trick.
There it is.
You know what I'm saying?
Alright.
Fine.
I'll do the narrow toe run.
Alright.
Jump from the tree to tree.
I made it on the mount.
What do you have to say now?
Alright.
Do the spy crab?
I'll see you guys later.
I got to clean up.
So have fun.
Good luck.
Two weeks from now.
Bye.