Hold on, wait a minute. Maximum Action won the poll? When did that happen?
I... there has to be some type of... no, there's got to be some type of
coordinated effort here. Because Maxim... Fishing Planet. It's already open. I'm gonna play it. It's
already open. I've already installed it. Well then just uninstall it. That uses data.
I've seen a lot of people talking about this title. It's very simple. Yep. That's it. Yep.
Somebody voting over and over again. Well, the poll is still open. Looks like Fishing Planet seems
to have crawled over with 42% of the vote. Well, it's okay because like all these kinds of games,
I'm either going to think this is really cool and play it for six hours or I'm going to immediately,
within 20 minutes, change to something else. We'll find out. What's the link? Here. Anyways,
how you guys doing? Here's the poll. I've already got it open. Like the election's over.
You know, I'm not going to get like sworn in and all of a sudden it's just like,
wait a minute, but what about Jupiter? You want to recount? Here it is. Millions of votes cast
for Fishing Planet. Actually, what really happened... I'm going to give you guys a breakdown
of exactly what happened here. I sometimes... Well, not sometimes. Every time. Because when
I'm setting up a stream, I come in and I'm doing scenes on OBS. I'm making sure the game is captured
correctly. I usually sit here for about 30, 40 minutes before a stream. I'll go eat. I'll come
back. I'll go to the bathroom. Whatever. The first message that I saw when I sat down into the pre-stream
chat was, wake me when he starts playing Fishing Planet. And I said, okay, wake up. Like I'm going
to do it. I won guide the one guy. And I thought that was funny. And then I put it on the poll
and people voted for it. One guy. Wake up. It doesn't matter. It's already open.
Hey, he didn't even know. This is... It's this person's birthday today.
You didn't know that. It's happy birthday to this person. Here's your birthday present.
It's already open. Thank you. There he is. It's a special birthday present.
Anyways, Maximum Action is the other game that I have. So whether that's today, if that, you know...
No, I'm not sure. Quit. Maximum Action is the other game. So if I played this for like all day,
then whatever. We'll play it tomorrow. Right? This is Fishing Planet. This is going to be a relaxing
day. Hit enter. No. Approach the shoreline. I was ready for this. Make your first cast. Aim at the
ring. Click... By the way, this is an MMO. People didn't know that one before they came in.
Talking shit. All right. So just... What do you mean aim in the circle? Aim at the ring.
Okay. And that was not really a cast. I kind of just dropped it in there. Hold left mouse button.
Oh, I have to hold it. Okay. What am I doing wrong?
It's funny because this is the kind of shit that I would do if I went fishing. I never go fishing,
but I don't know what to do. I always found fishing to be just like a strange thing. You
throw this little wire into the ocean or into a lake and you hope that somebody walks by and bites
it? I don't think I could... No. I'll tell you, I think fishing is going to go away with the iPad
generation. Because within five minutes an ad didn't pop up for me to click on, like warning
me about the weather in my area. You think Zoomers are going to be able to handle this?
Playing their like iPad game? Oh, yeah. Right. F11. Right. Okay. I gotta wait for fish to bite.
This is what we're doing. I got bread on there. What kind of bread? Bread. I don't see. I don't
see bread. Click right mouse. All right. Watch that line tension. How do I... What do I do? Real?
There's no more instructions. Go get them? How do I reel? I'm holding down left mouse button.
What's reel? What if I just walk backwards?
Pick it up. It's right there. Just pick it up. I swear to God. I'm like slingshotting him around.
I just want to pick him up. What am I doing? I can't reel him in. Is he still on it? How do
you reel this in? I think I'm stuck on a tree. I'm tying myself up. Imagine walking by this poor
sucker. He's like... It's like a dog leash. Like I went to the dog park. Oh, no, no. You're just
going to me. I'll go under you and... It's like seeing another person with a dog. Except it's just
me. Try to reel it in. I don't know how to fucking do this. No, no, no, no, no, no. Not yet. Reeling
speed. Turn move rod. Where... Reeling speed. Where's reel it in? Hold right click. That just
holds it in the air. The fish is still on that. No, he's going back in. No, I can't... He's... I
can't let him back in the water. He's gonna make it. Are you fucking serious? There's like bugs on
me. Get over... I can't, dude. I'm fucking... I think I'm done. I can't reel it in. Right and left click.
All right. Do I need to turn the webcam on to prove to you guys that I'm pressing left click?
Pitch cast reel on. Pull strike aimed cast. Reeling speed. Turn move rod. It's a bug. Snap
the line. Line break is B. All right. Well, let me bring him over here. Can I like pick him up?
Where is he from here? Where is he from here? Come on. Just break the line. Line break. B.
B. I think I have to restart the game. B. Line break is B, right? Maybe like one, two?
How do I get the line to snap? Hold right mouse button. Yes. And then hold left click. I just...
I don't have like a dummy mouse that I'm pressing. I am doing the... I don't have two... Listen.
What the fuck? I... Let's try it again. Is it capturing? Can you see it? Harder than actual...
No, I ran into a bug. Okay. Now I thought I had music for a second. Approach the shoreline.
Shoreline approached. Make your first cast. Aim at the ring. Click left mouse button. Got it. Okay.
Wait for fish to bite. This might take a while. Is that one right there? Click right mouse button.
Got it. Reeling to... Hold left... This wasn't happening before. I swear to God that wasn't
happening before. I told you. It took so fucking long. All right. Got 4 XP to this confetti coming
down. All right. Make a few casts and catch some fish. All right. Now I'm excited. Now I'm into
this. Why is this an MMO? I have no idea. How can I tell when there's a bite? Is it just bob?
That's what that means, right? All right. Is it too shallow? You can't... I can't walk around,
right? That scares the fish. You have to stand completely still. You can't talk either. You can't
like move your mouth. See? Told you. That wasn't somebody on the line? I'm gonna go over here.
Too early? How is that too early? Your... Your viewer count is dropping. Quick. Do a face cam.
Oh, the viewer count is fucking rising. 7.4 inches. Release it. All right. Let's get another one.
Too early. Too early. Too early. Wait. Wait. Wait. Was there one on there? Right there?
Ooh. That's a big one. 8.6. Time for a real catch. Ooh. Open inventory and change your bait for a
bigger fish. Uh, drag and drop to set red worms as bait. Crappy bluegill pumpkin seed. All right.
We're putting worms on here now. Now let's go to the local shop and get a fish keeper.
Choose tools and equipment. Buy a fish keep net to keep your catch. How much is 150 bucks?
Seems like a lot. We're all set here. Open the lake map. For bigger fish, prefer a good hiding
place. So let's select a different fishing spot. All right. What is this? Homes is my house. I have
a basic business license. Okay. I'm ready. This is an actual iPad game. I know. All right. Here we go.
Float is on the side because the bait hit the bottom. Reel the bait back in. How far? Decreased
the line leader to 19. Use the zero button. What? Oh, line leader change to 19. All right. So I
have no idea what that means. That's like fish talk. I don't know what it means. That means how
much line I give. Is that too early? I think it was too early. Pop one. What is it? Oh, it's a big
mouth bash. It's a crappy. Should I keep it? It's 13 inches. Keep. Level up. I've got 1500 bucks. I
got a new pond. I got a dart, a net, and two. You guys are gonna have to help me out here with this
shit. Callisto. That's a head. Hook six crimson cold water golden. I don't know what any of these mean.
Open the lake map to continue your adventure. You know what I need to have happen? I have to get
I don't know. I'm gonna have to hook it up to a button on here. I think I want a song to play
when I catch a fish like while it's on the reel. Okay. You can leave the lake now and go
home like a real winner. Okay. Result in rewards. So where are the other players? Challenge
complete. Complete the tutorial. All right. So where are we going? Where are we dropping?
Huh? What do you guys think? That's this. How many people are here? There's four people here.
These servers are the I don't know how this is supposed to be. Hold on. Did I actually just say
where are we dropping? And it automatically is a bad Fortnite joke when I actually just was asking
where are we going? All right. Um let's go to the lone star lake mud water river. How much is this
to unlock? For six coins. How many? I only have two coins. Where should I go? Go to Alaska? I need
$10,000 to go here. I don't have that kind of money. Don't have any missions. These numbers are
levels. Oh. So what? Just go back to my lake? It's been like 10 days since my prime sum ended and I
keep forgetting to resub. I'm sorry. Why did I read that? Don't you don't have to be sorry
that you didn't resub. All right. What about this one? How much is to go here? Oh okay. We're going
to uh we're going to France or wherever this is. France? Yeah. Let's go. We're going to the check.
We're going to check. Here we go. One coin. Successful. Pond Lesney villa fishery unlocked.
Let's go. Travel. I have 4,400 bucks I can go. What do you mean travel cost? One day? Two days?
Three days? This is how long I'm allowed to be there? Five days. You have no fishing license
for this state. What do you mean fishing license? You have to have a license to fish? You do? In a
different place? Uh Lexi just gave 10 community subs. Thank you Lexi. That's a lot of subs.
10 community subs just came in. All right. Buy a license. Thank you Lexi. Basic check license.
One day. Three days. A week. A month. Unlimited. Advanced. What's the difference between an advanced
and a basic license? Common roach. Take no restrictions. Night catch is allowed. I'm doing
it. I'm gonna get an advanced license. One day. Oops. Okay. It's fine. We're gonna go there for
one day. Are these friend requests? Are they? I don't want to even like click on it. All right.
I got my business license. I'm going there. I'm gonna get. I'm going for one day. Find me. Okay.
Hold on a minute. I'm going. Let's go. Okay. What do they like here? What do they like to eat here?
Fish species. Carp. What do you. What do you like? What do you. What are you into?
Preferred? Uh semolina balls. Corn. Peas. All right. We're going for this one. I need corn and peas
and pea dough. What is pea dough? Is that like cookie dough but peas? Okay. I'm gonna go for one
of these. Semolina balls. Feeder starter. What's in here? Red worms. Dough balls. Um I think I need
these. Dough ball fish bait. Uh it's pumpkin seed. Uh this must be the starter bundle.
What do I. Don't I have something right now? I got like a new thing, didn't I? Bread worms.
I'm just gonna go in. There's at least a few people here that like worms.
Uh oh. I unlocked it to buy. Okay. I get it. Buy beef jerky and bud lights. There's somebody here.
Somebody's waiting for me. This is scary. All right. I need to follow. I need to follow along.
I need to be. They know the spots. Right here? What. Should we go in the same place? That's
probably not what we should do though. Somebody across the way. Oh there he is. There he is.
This person is the person that told me to play the game. This is the chat message. I remember.
Level 32. All right. You're gonna show. Gonna show me where to go. How do I get a mining helmet?
I'm just gonna. I'm going for it. This is my spot. Is there any bait on here? Yeah. This is worms.
Oh really showing off here with like the really big cool pole. Got something? Shit. How do you
get in one of those outfits? All right. Watch out. Watch out. This is one of those scenarios. This is
how you go to get to the hospital. Hey. Watch the cast. This is how you end up like going backwards
and like grabbing somebody by like the fucking cheek. Easy. I think I'm stuck. All right.
This is just scaring away all the fish. All right. Right here. I have bait still, right? Yeah. Worms.
I need to get something. All right. Shh. Don't you have to go really easy? Like gentle reeling?
I thought that's how you did it. How are you guys getting all these things? I need to get one.
Am I stuck on the lily pads? I can't look. I can't move. Come on. Somebody. Something. Anything.
I'll take anything right now. Got it. European perch. That was weird. Let me see.
All right. I'll get a European perch. I'll keep it. All right. Now how much is left in the day?
Five a.m. Is this in real time? You guys thought I was going to take not enough time to do this.
All right. I'm going over here. How do we get um person that has 32 levels in this game? Do you
have a boat? Can we get on the boat? Can you can we go on a boat? I kind of want to see that.
Is it possible? I can't use boats here. Well can I borrow your license? I know that's not how it
works but can I just borrow your license and go on your boat? That's a crime. It is a video game
though. This is a video game. There is no like add to friends, add to your business license.
I've got news for you guys. This is a fishing video game. You'll be lucky to catch one fish
over the course of three full days. Not ten. How do I chat? What's the chat menu? Chat is tab.
I can't even go into the menu while the rod is stuck. I had that same problem earlier.
Did I? Did I ever tell you guys the story about how my brother got banned from Warcraft
for like three days for writing in the trade chat? You know how people used to do this? They'd go
like oh hey we like wants to buy a um like uh 20 thorium bars right and they would put that in the
chat. That would be yeah like it's something we don't know. It'd be wants to buy like this 20x
thorium bars like please send help right and you'd be like oh okay that's what they want.
My brother got banned for three days in WoW for writing this. It was like what the fuck are you
doing? I was like we were like 15, 16. They had to I didn't say it. Where's my line? Where am I stuck?
What? Who am I attached to somebody? Is that the person that's saying help?
I'm not like attached to that person am I? Uh oh. Anyways Blizzard anytime you got in trouble in
WoW they had to tell you. They like he thought it was like the funniest thing that they had to
quote that to him like for the reason why he got like a suspension. I remember just being like
you're a fucking idiot. How do I get this off? I don't know. There's 43, 44, 45, 46, 47. How far
does this go? 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54. What happens if we get to 216? What am I doing? Oh I'm I think
I'm letting the line out. I gotta spell my name. I'm trying to make the E. It's not gonna work. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. What are you doing? People are just coming over here watching. You
run into the line. All right now. All right let's let's make it. That thing is huge. All right now
let's try to reel it up as fast as I can. Wait can I cast it? Lash all them up. All right let's
catch a fish. I still don't understand why where this is. It's stuck in there but how do I get it
out? Break the line. Are you sure you want to break the line? Yeah. Did I just break the line and
hold on. Did I break my rod in half? Why would I do that? Oh it looks like my fishing line's broken.
May as well snap this thing over my knee. No I did not. Inventory. There's the okay I got line here.
Adjust the line length by like 140. There we go. Okay what's this? This is still on here. Where's
my rod? Hook. Okay I got a hook on there. Red worms. All right I'm ready to go. How do I equip
a fishing rod? It's tough. That was a weak throw. It was fine. Let me reel it in a little video.
Excuse me. What if we all touch? This is probably giving actual people that fish in here anxiety.
I need a better f11. What did I just do? Holy fuck. Why is my instinct to turn and hit the
person next to me in the head with the rod? I don't know. All right let me get that again.
Nice. That was not even further than just tossing it out there. Catch some grasshoppers with your
hands. Oh what's that? All right come on now. Come on reel it in. Forget this. I want to see
what you get. You have like a shark on there. Easy now. Easy. Easy. What is it? Oh what? That's
insane. All right Jeremy this ain't mini golf. Like let's go. Why am I only going that far? Zero
feet? Wait I saw. I know those are raindrops. Never mind. In every fishing game when you see
the little doop doop doop that means a fish is in like a fishing company's over there.
All right I'm just gonna leave it in. I'm not gonna move. I don't even like beer especially bud red
but I want to just drink a bud red right now. It's the only time you'll ever hurt. I will never say
that out loud ever again except for right now this only instance. I want one of those but regular
Budweiser. Did I get it? Okay I actually did it. I ripped it out of the water. Guys guys come look.
Show and hide. Let me examine. Look. Look. Look. Look. Look. Look what I got. Look what I got. Look
what I got. Look what I got. Look at this. Look at mine. Look at my fish. All right release. Level
up. Cheese. Camo fest. I want the cheese. Can I? I just want to eat that cheese. I don't even want
to put it on the lure. Sinker. Barley. Chainsaw. What else is in here? I unlocked. I pretty much
unlocked the whole game. Go to the settings and enable big bobber. Big bobber. Big bobber. Oh I
see what you mean. Now you can actually see what you're doing. Mod me. Give yourself an atomic
wedgie. Why do I feel like they did that on jackass at some point? I know I just said hurry up in a
fishing game. Come on. Anything. What is that? Why is that a swear? You can buy the semolina
excuse you. What are you saying? Can you can you not write? Got one. I'll keep this one. You can't
write like ball. I need more line. I need I want to buy some cheese. Where are the big fish? Can you
catch like huge things in this game? Where do we find the big ones? Throw at green not yellow.
Throw at green. What do you mean? Go to the ocean. Go in that house. Can we go in the biggest fish
there is? Biggest fish here is a carp and they get to like two pounds.
That sucks. I want to do like the I want to catch like the tuna. Those things are 13 pounds.
Add a zero and another zero. Rude. Thanks. I think my fair part of both is wait a minute. That's a
splash. It's only one pound. That's actually pretty good. All right. This ain't gonna I get a cast
again. I need more line. I need more line. Give me some more line. Missions. Loan start to come
true. Loan start floor start to catch the listed fish in this lake. I'm in another country right
now so you're gonna have to wait a minute. I need the spin master. That's what I want. Where's the
cheese? Bait. Cheese. Okay how much money do I have? I want a lot of cheese. I don't I'm it's
weird that oh there it is. I can't buy it. Why? I need to be like level 11 for a barley. We'll get
some of this. All right here we go. Looking for a bluegill. What have I got? I want a bluegill.
Now we also need a slingshot. What? Why do I need that? Lures. What's a good one? Gold. I'll take
the gold one. Ground baits? Hold on. These just bags of chips? All right I need reels. Okay this
is where it gets good. I can buy a mini spin 1200. Weight. Recovery. Look at this thing right here.
Check. A mini spin 1200 right? That's a better version of this. I don't even know what any of
this means but I'm just gonna get it. Why can I not equip it? Okay lions. I want some good shit.
Mono. Why is this more expensive? XXL. Length 300 yards. All right we'll get some.
500 yards. Okay. Mono leader. Floor row. No no that's in-game currency.
I'm just gonna get them. I don't know if they really do. Tackle. Hooks. Hook six. I have hook
eight. Oval. I need a good one. Chubby. Floating weight high. Shape chubby. Make it easy to see
at long distances. Anything from hand fish to salmon to steelhead. I guess it's just
aesthetically pleasing to get the chubby one. All right let's go. I already own this. All right
six. Hook six. Line. Mono 005. We'll take it at 139 feet I guess. Cheese. Looking for a bluegill.
What kind of hook do I got on there? All right where do I get a bluegill? Map. None of these
bluegills. There's a goldfish too. All right not this way. No no no no no. Back up. What about
over here? Oh look at this. Carp. Roach. Perch. No I need a bluegill. Where can I get a bluegill?
What's my level three? They eat cheese? Who eats cheese here? Me and the common carp have the same
diet. Like in order of how often you consume them. Nobody wants cheese here. Cheese. Okay I'm
leaving. I'm going home. Nobody here wants cheese. I have to leave. All right we're out. I'm gonna get
I'm gonna do one more attempt here. What's this one? No. Let's get one more fish. All right what
have I got for? I got cheese on here. Who? Anybody wants cheese? What's my favorite cheese? It really
depends on the scenario because there's a lot of different answers to that question. Swiss cheese
is the best on sandwiches. I think without a doubt. Asiago cheese is really good on pretty
much everything no matter what it is. Especially when it's baked onto something else into a crust.
I don't like brie. It reminds me throw up. It smells and tastes like puke. I don't like it.
Aguda. Blue cheese are both very good. And I don't trust any cheese where you can eat the rind.
Oh the brie. Have some brie. I don't want to eat the lemon rind. That shit's pretty much made out
of plastic. I don't want to eat it. Bavardi is good. Yeah. Do a cheese tier list. Of course that
exists. Do I like monster? I only like monster cheese when it's on a plate sliced into small
squares and there's a cracker right next to it. I don't eat it anywhere else. Blue cheese I would
I it's my favorite on anything. I would put blue cheese on anything and I'm not talking about blue
cheese crumble. I'm talking about the blue cheese sauce. Not blue cheese dressing. Get it right.
Oh blue cheese dressing. No no no no no. Blue cheese sauce. The thicker blue cheese. See people
always confuse this and when you sometimes when you go to a restaurant you get blue cheese. Oh
you want blue cheese. Yeah I'll take a side of blue cheese. Yeah I'll take blue cheese on that.
It's the blue cheese dressing that you put on a salad. No get that away from me. What is blue
cheese sauce? It's thicker as it has a thicker base. It can be dunked into with like chicken
fingers especially buffalo chicken. Buffalo chicken tenders and that blue cheese thick
sauce. The thick dunkable blue cheese. Find me a better appetizer and I'll fucking say all right.
The biggest offense of any restaurant. I don't care who they are. I don't care what they specialize
in. I don't care what their star rating is. If you order blue cheese with a meal and they give you
a packet of blue cheese dressing on the side, do not ever go there again. I think my line's too
long. There we go. This woman. Do you see this swarm? It's mold. Yeah and guys please. You're
eating mold. Do you know. Did you know that you eat over 12 inches of dirt every single meal? Did
you guys know that? Every single meal you eat over 12 at least 12 inches of dirt. Something I
I've been talking at least that much. Do I have a source on that? Yeah because you're eating about
12 inches at least off the ground. I got another one for you. Turn my mic back on. Why don't we
eat cheese here? Did you know you drank over 12 liters of monster energy a month? Um no don't do
that. That's like that's like an easy way to get a heart attack. Don't do that. Do a cheese tasting
stream. I'd like to do a catch a fish on game stream if I could do that. Here we go. Here we go.
Here we go. Here we go. Come on. Got it. What is it? Oh it's a common roach. Release. How about uh
this game's actually like kind of fun. I'm not gonna. I saw at least 150 comments of people
saying why don't you play one of the good fishing games. This is this is all right. This is like a
not a bad one. The line's a little too long. Ban that guy for three days. No cheese. Cheese is good
but you can't eat cheese too often. It just turns into cement in your body. Got it. European
perch. No. I want like a at least half pond. Can we go ice fishing in this game? You can?
That's actually kind of cool. Has anyone ever tried to make a fantasy fishing game?
No. People make a fantasy game and then put fishing in usually. We got a little bit of a bite there.
Unlock mud water river as soon as possible. Okay. There's big catfish there. Do they like cheese?
I'll tell you. You know what I do love? A restaurant that has a good. I'm gonna say
this wrong because I don't know the names of things. I just know what it is. I just know
when it comes in front of me. I just know what it is. Uh I'm gonna say it. I don't know.
I just point at it and I go oh I want that. I don't I know what it is. It's the board with
the the figs and the cheeses and the the prosciutto and the ham and the salami and the olives.
I love those things and when a restaurant does one of those good they oh that's all you need.
Just order one of those and just eat it. Uh chikurri board. Chikurri board. There it is.
Just eat raw meat off the plate. What do you mean raw meat? Prosciutto's not raw. Is prosciutto
raw meat? No it's not. Raw meat? Yeah it's cured. It's cured. It's not. They don't just like do an
ice cream scoop of like 80 20 grocery store ground beef. It's cured meat. Cured is raw.
No it's been cooked because it's been cured. It's it's salted to a point where it cooks it.
I don't know what that means. I told you. I just point to stuff at the menu.
I had it right. I asked it's salted to a point where bacteria can't. I know. I know and I said
it right but people go to question mark. They go like this. What does this guy just say?
It's salted to a point where it's been. Why am I not getting any bites?
Yeah I know curing meat doesn't cook the meat but I know. I'm just I'm listen to me. I'll take a
chikurri board please with extra figs because they're delicious. You sound like an annoying me
with that voice. Which one? An annoying me? Me's don't talk. Do me's talk? I've never heard a me
talk before. The only closest thing I can think of is just when you hit okay on the menu with a me.
It just goes like they don't have a voice. Fortnite okay. Fortnite Jimmy just like screwed
up that whole thing. I was seriously about to catch a fish right there. Watch it. Watch it.
What do you got? Let's see it. What do you got going here? I want to see. What do you got going
on here? You got something don't you? What is it? That's a that's pretty big. For a second I
thought that one pound almost a pound and a half. Nice. Kick that person so I can get in. I didn't
think there was that much demand for a fishing planet. Apparently there is. There's not. Here we
are. I would have had something here too. Uh-oh. Fortnite Jimmy 2010. Starting to show signs of
agitation. All caps. Come on something. I teach elementary all my kids love Fortnite.
Yeah it's Fortnite. You know whatever. I'm trying to think of the games that I liked
when I was younger. It's hard to compare though because we're in a different world.
We're in like a constant completely connected and somebody the same person has walked by my
screen like 10 times. Am I going crazy? That was the same person right? Okay I'm just like I want
to know if I was freaking out or not. Yeah games have changed. We're constantly connected. Diablo
2 is probably that game for me. You can play that game online but it got to a point. You want to
know when Diablo 2 was ruined completely forever? When you would join a game and no matter what,
every 25 seconds a bot would enter the room and spam a buy items website. It happened thousands
of times if you joined a public server. That was the day when that started happening that
the game was over. They would come in. Oh here it was. And they'd have a name like this. Like and
okay here we go. And you'd get that and then they would get they would get like booted from the game.
They would just spam. It would be like you'd get that message sound in Diablo 2. They walked by
again. So you had to make private rooms. At that point it was hard to play the game online
unless you had specific people that could join a room with a password. Hold on. Finally. Finally
it's been so long. I just caught it. Almost seven tenths of a pound. Whatever that denomination
is. Almost a pound. Seven almosts of a pound. Pretty good. Keeping that one. Chunky baloney
thanks for the 10 community subs. Thank you Chunky. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. It's a lot.
The last two days people have just been coming in with these huge community subs
and huge amounts of money. I see one right there. Thank you guys for real.
This is an outrage. Play the next game. We're just hanging out and talking.
I'm trying to give you guys the real fishing experience because what happens is when you
go fishing. I've been fishing a few times. Is let's say you go three or four people.
Two or three of those people want to just sit silently and just hang out.
While the other fourth person, which is me, does not stop talking and annoys everybody there.
Always bringing up new topics. Always bringing up things to discuss.
And I'm the fourth annoying guy. And then the other three in a private chat text on their phones
are talking about how we're not going to bring Jeremy next time. Like hey you want to go fishing
again? Yeah just like us. And they don't have to say anything. They don't say a word. They just
make the group chat without my number in it. That's it. That's their way of doing that. They don't go
oh that was annoying. No no no. They just make that group chat without me. And I'm like hey guys
you want to go fishing? Let's go fishing again. Yeah yeah no maybe. And then yeah maybe.
Weirdly now they say a certain line every time. They're like oh yeah we'll look into that. I'll
look into that. I'm like oh look into that okay. Oh that's the biggest one yet. I got 44 dollars
for this one. Let's show this one off. This one's got this one's like thick here. Let's show it.
This is my keep net. All right I got a nine inch Russian carp. This one. I mean get rid of this one.
Can I sell them? Or does does releasing sell them? Or do I have to sell them in like a shop?
Because that one's not good enough. Keep this one. Buy a casting rod? Well I gotta get money first.
But not fishing is. Okay that screwed that up. After you start the next day you'll sell them.
All right what time is it? 7 44 a.m. This is going to take a very long time. I can't believe I'm
spending my Tuesday afternoon playing a virtual fishing game with some old boomer.
Well believe it. Um I'm sorry let me I'm gonna level with me here. Tuesday afternoon it's just
like kind of right almost in the middle of the week. Weekday like that's not a problem. What's
wrong with that? You know it's like five o'clock pacific just hanging out. There's nothing wrong
with that. This is when you go fishing. You go fishing on like Tuesday afternoon at like
four in the morning or like four or five o'clock at night. This is the time to do this. Hey guys
let's not bring Jeremy to the next fishing trip. He just won't fucking stop talking.
You got me. So what happens if you end the day early? Do I have enough money to end a day early?
Should I just go somewhere else? I need to find a fish that's at least worth selling that's worth
some money. Come on right here. You know sometimes you look over the chat. You look at you know
something that somebody in a community will and will say something along the lines of
Wow I like this stream a lot. I'd watch him paint a fence. You're being tested right now.
This is where I cut to a live camera of me with like a painter's outfit on and I got like a bucket
of paint in my hand with a fence behind me. Now that would have been funny. Damn. Damn. He streams
twice every other week and decides to play this. You're not keeping up. That's not fair. That's
inaccurate. Inaccurate. It's an inaccurate statement. Do I actually do I know how to fish?
I don't think you can know how to fish. I think it just happens. That means he doesn't.
You guys are fucking funny. Streams. Streams twice every other week. That's bullshit. Oh this one
sucks. If you go to a twitch stats website actually this is real data. I actually stream about
15 to 16 times a month. Probably like 17. 15 to 17 times a month is my accurate stats on twitch.
That means that means statistically there's a stream every other day. Statistically speaking.
Three days in a row. Two days off. Two days in a row. Three days off. Three days in a row. Three
days off. That's kind of how it happens. Every other week. No that's not that's that would mean
that I would stream seven days in a row. All right you know what they're correct. You're right.
You are correct. That is accurate. That means week one I don't stream for seven straight days.
Week two I stream seven days in a row. Week three zero. Seven days straight of no streams. Week
four seven straight days of stream. That's inaccurate though. That's misleading. My brother
typed that. Every day for a year and then don't stream for a year. Yeah I'm an every other year
streamer. You know I love board chat. It's kind of it's one of my favorite chats. Wiggle the poll.
That doesn't do anything. Board chat board chat does get bad real fast you're right.
Just wait till I go get a catfish and everybody pug champs and you forget. Still waiting for your
opinion on French cuisine. Why would I do this when I can fish in real life. I'm not sure if
you know this but I live in the desert. This is all I can do. Fish for sand worms. Go fish in the
Hoover Dam. You guys were giving me shit earlier about me not having a business license to go to
Czech Republic to get a fish and now you're telling me to go fish in the Hoover Dam. Go fishing.
I wasn't even paying attention. That's what happens. Everybody falls asleep. I wonder how
many opportunities are missed to fish because three or four people go to bed in lounge chairs
and all their fishing poles are like shaking around and they don't even do it. Oh let me up.
Let me help this guy out. Holy shit. Wow. Great minds think alike. See now that person's gonna
think that's real. There's a lot of smiley faces here. There's this smiley faces here. There's like
I gotta correct this. There's too many. There's like happy smiling faces. What's wrong with that?
The drake sword sucks. The drake sword is the best early game weapon you can possibly use in that
game. Just get it and use it without even upgrading it for like fucking 12 hours. The drake sword is
for idiots. We're not talking about like intelligence levels. We're talking about like how to make the
game easier for you. I lost my one opportunity. This guy probably likes TF2 more than the classic
game Overwatch. Yeah I do. Whatever. I want to get on a boat. All right. How much money do I have?
There's not a fish on the line right now. If there is I'm gonna laugh my ass off. Nice. I got lied
to and I could have probably sat there. And I'm going over here. Get a jet ski. Get a jet ski and
drive like really fast and turn, pull, brake and like spray everybody. Get to level four for the
next area. Am I there now? Level two? What level am I? I have to type to know. Level three.
Give me something. Can you wake me up in 30 minutes? Yes. Lewis Cheese. In 30 minutes I'm
gonna fucking call out your name. Exactly 30 minutes from right now. That'd be one hour and
54 minutes stream time. Gonna forget? No I won't. Yes you will. I will not forget that. What's his
name? Lewis Cheese. Didn't forget. Go to bed. See you in 30 minutes. Is there even bait on this?
I have french toast sticks in the oven. Wake me up in five minutes so I can flip them over. Don't
turn the oven on and go to bed. What do you got? Do you mind? All right. That's something's got to
change here. This is not working out. I need a bread. I'm gonna try bread. Worms aren't working
right now. Try to get a crappie with these. Crappie. Where's my other? There it is.
Slop spoon. I can't use that here. It's time for fun boat time. Not yet. I'm going over here.
I need to get to level four so I can go to the next area. Beer powers up your fishing rod.
How does it? Wow. You gotta buy the brackets quote funny line. It's right there.
How do I wall run? All right, Jimmy. Jimmy. Drink monster. Drink bite monster. No, why would I do
that? If I drink like a monster, I just get heartburn. This, okay, I'm just going to give
you some anecdotal evidence here. Just anecdotally, whenever I drink an energy drink,
I get heartburn and my eyes hurt. I just don't, I'm not going to drink one of those.
All of them across the board pretty much do this. Too much energy from my
body. No. God, you should just, you should be eating fucking vegetables and fruits and shit.
How many times do we have to have this conversation? Eat a banana. Pretty good. Keep it.
Yes. Mud river. Mud river. Let's go. Sayonara. It's time to go to mud river. How much money did
I get? 105 bucks and not premium. Premium. Does that have to buy it or something? Sorry, Jimmy.
Day two. I didn't, let me day two. This is the first time I've ever played this game. All right.
Where's that mud river? There it is. Let me get a license for it. 1200 bucks to be here. Whatever.
Uh, advanced license. No restrictions. I don't want any violation of license
rules. There's nothing fine. One day advanced license. All right. Let's go.
One day. Let's go. Mud river. Catfish heaven. Pike challenge lost. It's not catfish heaven.
These are big. Enjoy exploring mud water river and its premises for a certain number of days.
I don't stop advertising to me. What's this? Nice. All right. What's up? So what's what if
what fishes are here? Fish species. We've got catfish. They like marshmallow, pet food, leeches,
and okay marshmallows. Dough balls. I don't have any of those. Dough balls. I gotta buy some bait
here. Blood worms. I need marshmallows. All right. Marshmallows and pet food. How much are
marshmallows? Did I unlock marshmallows yet? I can't even get marshmallows. How much is both?
But there is pet food. Okay. The buy the balls. I can't have to be level 11.
All right. So let's get the pet food on here. Do I? Okay. Do I need a certain line or something
or a certain hook for this 150 length long line short line hook six. Okay. Let's see. Let's go.
Got my line here. What is my lead? 18, 25, 30 inches. That sounds about right. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. That's not right. I got pet food on there though. No, no, no. I gotta throw it.
F11. One and a half pound catfish. Nice. Nice dude. Right here. Here we go. Hey there, new to the
streams anyways. Do you think you could do a dab at some point? It's no pressure. It's just my
it's red on my screen. So I have to read them. Here we go. Here we go. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Strike it. Strike. Come on. Get on there. I know you want to get on that. You showed interest for
a second. Come on. I had it. There it is. There it is. There it is. Oh, easy. Easy. Pumpkin seed.
12 bucks. No, get out of here. I want to go to another spot. You want to how you make this game
insane and have everybody talk about it and just be like, Oh, you have to play it.
Have like a werewolf jump out of here. Jump scare the fuck out of you. And then you put like your
rod, you flip it upside down and it becomes a weapon. And it's a first person fucking like
fantasy fighting game. Entirely different game. No, just for this one spot. You know how many
Buzzfeed articles will be written on your game. You can have this fishing game being completely
normal. Everyone would just camp that spot. Yeah. Make it like a 0.2% chance to happen.
I should pee. Peeing in the river helps attract fish. I feel like that's weird enough to be true.
Interest. Interesting. It might already be in there and nobody's done it enough to trigger
the warning. It's possible. It's true. Fish smell the ammonia in urine. See the first person that
said that it was weird enough to be true. That second comment was just specific enough to be
false. Somebody bite this. Try again. This way. When am I going to close this game and stream
Just Dance 4? I'll give you a spoiler for one of the 37 Connect games that I have. You want
to get spoiled on one of them? I'll do it. I'm going to, I'm just going to show a flash on cam.
You ready? Hope you guys can catch it. How's fishing going? Pretty good. I've done nothing bad.
Somebody's on it. Come on. Somebody's looking at it. I want a catfish. Please
catch a fish. Dumbass. That's not how this works. You could be the best fishermen in the world
and they'll fish just don't want to bite today. I am solely reliant on another party to be able
to be good at this. What do you mean false? Sometimes the fishes don't want to bite today.
You could do all kinds of like little tricks like this. Like turn, turn, turn, turn, twist,
turn, turn, turn, turn, twist. Everybody has their own little thing they do. Right?
But the fish isn't hungry. They're not going to bite you. It's not going to work.
Different spot. Yeah, this spot sucks. Watch out for the fucking werewolf. You're not going to find
a catfish here. Just go on tinder. 10 out of 10 joke. I didn't make it. I was responding to it.
I was reacting. React more. There's still pet food on here. Right? Yeah. Nice and easy. Just quick.
Just to show that I'm moving around and see on the left side, left side of the screen.
Did you see that? Oh, somebody get it. Get it. It's right there. You're right here. I want you
to grab it. Just get it. Almost there. Please. Just pull it down. Got him. Now that's a big one.
13.3 inches over a pound. I wish you could walk in the water. Just walk in there and show.
That's big. All right. That one's money. We'll have some money for that.
It's too bad catfish taste like ass. I have to say, I don't think I've ever had it before.
I don't think I've ever eaten catfish. Let's just relax here. Oops. No, I don't want to open the
menu. I don't want to open the menu. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Here it comes. Here it comes.
Somebody coming. Somebody coming. Timed out. What? It didn't even move. It was just barely
bobbing a little. That's annoying. Catfish eat mostly just shit stuff, so they taste like shit.
Hold on. It's still here. Come on. What is it? That's even bigger. 1.2 pounds. Almost 13.7 inches.
Larry, keep it. Nice. Okay. This spot actually is pretty good. Let me check this spot over here.
Is there another spot besides this way? Can I go this way? Like to the left? What the fuck was that?
What the fuck? What? What the fuck? How do I take the weapon out? How do I take out the weapon?
Let's go motherfucker. I'm ready. Is it gone? So I've never had it before. Catfish is one of
those things that I feel like it's at a ton of restaurants, but not at any restaurants.
It's weird. I see it on menus and I'm like, oh, they have fucking catfish here all the time,
but then when I want to try it, it's never there. You have to cook it really carefully.
I scared your cat. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to scare your cat. You scared me.
But why the fuck would they put that in this game? That's not fucking cool. That's stupid.
Why would you ever put that in a game and scare the shit out of everybody that plays it?
What a bad idea. It's supposed to be a relaxing fishing game and you're gonna have like a werewolf
jump out and scream. That's kind of like, that's not a good idea. I can't wait for the next five
sound effects. That's what this is. The funny sound effect. I can't wait for the funny sound,
the next funny sound effect. Me either.
Stop. You're going to lose all your plus twos. Watch out. Watch it. It's going to happen again.
They're already gone. Market manipulation at its finest. This was a much better spot,
though. It actually was. Come on. Somebody's freaking out over there. Yeah. It's all right.
They're probably lagging. Fight it. It's right there. Talk to the guy across the river. Would
you do something like that? Are you serious? The thing bopped all the way down. If you were fishing,
if you're the only person here and that person was fishing and you were fishing and you were sitting
there for like an hour or two straight, eventually, don't you think you would be,
you'd say like, catch anything or something like that, just to lighten up the mood or something.
I feel like somebody would do that. No, not as big as the other one, but still all right.
Yeah. You wouldn't yell over there. Hey, did you see the werewolf put a boombox like in the
bush over here, hit play and run back over here. That's the equivalent of what I just did to you
guys. And then run around like I'm scared. Or someone just pick up their tackle box and just
move a hundred feet that way. What's a taco box? Tackle box. We already went over cheeses.
My favorite cheese is Swiss cheese. That's unpopular though. People don't like Swiss cheese.
They think it's just smells and is gross. Why? The same people that will eat brie and talk about how
brie is the best will be angry that I said I like Swiss. They both stink. They both have like a very
distinct flavor to them. Why? Why is your cheese better than my cheese? I think it's pretty big.
Nine and a half inches. That's a, that's a big one. Brie cheese tastes like plastic. Brie cheese.
I don't like brie. I don't, I'm not a fan at all. This one's a big one. Wow. 1.7 pounds,
14, almost 15 inches, $45 keeping it. So I have a question. I feel, I feel like I'm,
it's not hard to do this. I just hit right click and rip them out of the ocean.
It's not hard to fish germ. I don't, I don't say that. I said that like an hour ago and everybody
told me I was a dumb person. What was that? There's actual noise behind me. I'm not playing that.
I'm not doing a werewolf thing again. Oh, it's, it's you. Okay. I, I'm over that. What level am I
for? Something's right there. I'm still playing this. Yeah, that's all right. I'm having a good
time. That's not a bite. That's just a little pull. I feel like this is going to be a big one.
Right there. Come on. Right there. Right there. Right there. Right there. Right there. Right there.
Pull it down. Get that pet food. Oh, this is the good shit. Nice. Oh, impossible to place. Oh,
I can't take this one. I have a full bag. I think it might be time to go to another place.
Sell, sell. Is there a, wait, hold on. Can I just sell? Backpack. Fish keeper. Okay. How do I,
can I sell early morning, early morning pet food? How do I, can I sell specials, licenses, fish
keeper? I don't think I can do anything else with this. Dude, look at it in 3D. Yeah, this,
I gotta release this one. All right. So we got one pound, one pound. I want at least another,
at least one pound. Give me like another full pound catfish and we can go. This is the good
spot for the catfish right here. This is a good one. But what is that bird? That is the most
distinct bird. I know what that is. Is it a chickadee? The one that goes, I hear it's,
it's the only thing that they do. I gotta recast this. Oh, by the way, Lewis cheese, Lewis cheese,
Lewis cheese. It's time for you to wake up. Lewis cheese. Wake up now. Wake up now. Lewis cheese.
You guys were fucking early. I looked over here. I was going to do it in about 20, 30 seconds
because it was 1 54 30 is when I need to do it. You guys did it so early. He's here. All right.
You guys have given this, this, this poor dude, you've given like 5,000 dings. I hope this,
yeah, this, if you have notifications, sounds on Twitch, I didn't even need to say anything.
You guys just pinged him like fucking 6,000 times. He's probably going to be screaming, holding his
ears. Let me know when you start playing something entertaining. Thanks. Yeah. What was your name?
What was your name? Who was that? Who said that? I need one more catfish. Then we'll go somewhere
else. No, we're not doing this. I, I ain't the front desk at a hotel. I'm not going to.
Hello, Mr. Albert. It's your 8 AM wake up call. Give me, I gotta go back to the other one. Oh,
what's going on? Oh, the werewolf is coming back. Well, um, we're staying here. Thanks for recommending
places in Boston to go. I had a great time. I'm glad you did. Boston's a great city. This stream
is making people fall asleep actually. So he needs to yell people's usernames to keep viewers up.
What's the best burger in Boston? I don't know. I actually don't know that answer to that question.
Best burger in Las Vegas. I got that one. You already know it. Let's already say it for me.
I'm not Shake Shack. What? Hash House or Go Go? Oh, McDonald's. Who? What? All right. Listen,
wait, wait, there may be people here that were not here when I've talked about this before a few
times at the link. It's the name of a casino. It's a casino hotel. There is a restaurant inside of
that restaurant is a little place that we like to call Hash House or Go Go. It is a 24 hour
establishment. And inside there, there's an expansive menu of chicken, hamburger, waffles,
24 hours. There is a burger on that menu, which I highly recommend. It is the blue cheese stuffed
burger under the hamburger section. It is the best hamburger I have ever had in my entire life.
All right. We're on a fishing trip. Somebody's asleep and no one's listening to. I'm like so
close to this person's ear telling them this. Why am I turning like a castaway like Tom Hanks right
now? I'm like losing my mind. God just wakes up. Dude, what are you talking? What's, what are you
doing? Did anything, did I get any bites? Sorry. I just, I just, I needed to like make sure you knew.
Wake up, wake up. Inception.
Everyone's asleep. I get up and I stand in front of them and I do a full like just presentation.
I need to tell you this. It's so important. Hash House or Go Go. Bring your laptop over. Yeah,
open it up. I need one more fish and I can get out of here. But for real, the burger at Hash
House or Go Go in the Link is so good. I've not eaten a hamburger that was better than that
in my life. L-I-N-Q the Link. Somebody eat this. Now I can't speak. I know there are other Hash
House or Go Go's, but I cannot speak to the quality of the other ones. Whether the executive chef is
of the Las Vegas in the Link chef. That's the one I'm speaking of. So if you go to Hash House or Go
Go in Florida or something and you're like, this sucks. Well, I, you're not the right one.
I have to, okay. I think of my games broken. I do. I think of my game. My game is broken. I need to
go that. Okay. Finally I can walk over here now. Do I like shellfish? I'm one of those weirdos that
loves crab, but hates lobster. It just, it seems impossible. It seems so stupid and impossible,
but it's, it's true. See, that's weird. Same really. I was assuming people are going to think that was
odd. Here we go. Crab takes a lot of work. Yeah. That's why I usually just have somebody do it for
me. That's not big enough. That's not big enough. What do you mean? I can't keep this? Why didn't I
throw away one? It's too much weight. I only have 4.4 pounds. I need a bigger fish hut. Damn it.
Okay. That's what's going on. Fish hut medium 15 pounds. All right. That's the problem.
What am I? I can't keep. All right. I have to leave. I have to go back to my house.
All right. I'm out. Back to my house. King crab is my favorite. Probably my favorite seafood.
Somewhere. King crab is similar. King crab is expensive. I don't, you can't really get it
all the time, but it is, I love king crab. Blue crab. Blue crab is good, but I, it has a different
flavor profile for me. I'm not a huge fan of blue crab or like dungeon crab. I've had dungeon crab
once and it was strange. It was really, it was like a very ammonia tasting story. It was very
weird. I didn't like it. Dungeon crab. Is that my dungeon? Dungeon? Yeah. Rocky Lake. What level
my four? Any fours? Dungeon is crab is harbor trash. No, there's, there's a really expensive
crab that I really didn't like and I could, I could barely eat it. Damn it. I need, what level
do I need to be? Is there any fives? No, that's, this is not here. What about snow crab? I don't
know. I, Rocky Lake's the next one. I need to go home. Inventory. All right. Where's my stuff?
Home. There we are. Mudspin 1200. Get that on. Mono 007. Two, that's, I, that's, I don't know.
I have no idea. Can I put this on? Fish hut medium. Why can I not put this on? Something
going on here? Backpack. Do I like calamari? Only fried. I think it's just open some loot boxes.
There are no loot boxes in this game. Is it just on or am I not allowed to use this yet?
I think that's on, right? Well, whatever. I'm going to, who likes cheese? Anybody in Lone Star
like cheese? Shiner. Dough balls. Dough balls. Pet food. Ooh. I'm going, I'm going back to town.
Let's see. Catfish right here. Pet food. Leeches. I have pet food right now. But yeah. King crab's
my favorite. Holy shit. Look at how misty it is. Now this is cool. I would go fishing like this.
Uh oh. He's queuing up the werewolf sound again. No, I'm not. Don't listen to these
liars in chat. They're lying to you. You vape. We get it. Oh yeah. I still have to do that.
I still have to do that thing that I was going to do a long time ago.
And remember that thing that I was going to do? I don't think any of you guys remember.
Maybe I shouldn't talk about it then. That's, it's just, it's just, it's just stupid.
I remember. All right. Some people remember and promise a lot of things. Yeah, I do. I don't
promise anything. I just come up with ideas and then I see minus two, minus three, and then I go,
oh, that's not a good idea. Maybe I should change my plans. You promised Dr. Oz in the next rumble.
I know. You think I forgot? That's one of the most important new characters. How could I forget that?
Any bites? Nah. Did you wake up Louis Cheese? I did. I promised Ace Attorney. No, I didn't. I said
I was going to check it out off stream and see if I wanted to stream it and it turned out I did not
want to stream it. I was very honest. Nothing over here. Changing spots. You promised you would start
drinking wine instead of beer. I don't drink beer. I drink, for low alcohol content, beverages for
alcohol, I drink wine and I drink red wine. Well, I don't drink beer. You guys, you guys have known
that for almost two years. Fucking werewolf. What about high alcohol content? Good vodkas, like high,
quality vodkas. Not the fingernail polish removal. That's like four bucks for a handle. No.
And scotches. I like whiskey. I don't drink it that much anymore though. Crystal Skull, Dan
Ackroyd vodka. Crystal Skull actually was pretty good. It was not bad. I didn't hate it. You know
what I do want to get though is I want to get, I want to get Stone Cold's beer. What's it called?
Like Stone Cold's beer. It's like Skull, like Skull Crusher or something. It's called something.
I want to try it. Broken Skull IPA. There it is. Has anybody had Broken Skull? I'm not a big beer
drinker, but I mean, I feel like I've been pretty good. It's really good. I have to put new bait on.
This is ridiculous. It's pretty good. I'm going to track it down. IPAs taste like a new carpet.
Is there a certain like time of day should I put new bait on? Do I like it? That song always kind
of jumps up on me. All right, Pep Foods is not doing it. Let's go back to worms. I need to get
to level five. Can I buy a casting rod? I don't think I can. Rods. Value Spin. Telefloat. Value
Spin. Is this a casting? There's a lot of money. I only have 2100 bucks. Spinning rod. Value Spin.
Okay, well I own it. Try Polish vodka. It's incredible. Yeah, there are some really good
vodkas. There are. I worried about my sleeping schedule, but this stream fixed it. You're welcome.
I'm glad I can be of service. I got a bluegill. Jerma, look at the game chat. You know, I've never
once ever thought it was something that I was going to do or been told to pay attention to in
game chat. I will take things that I've never thought of to do for 5000 Alec. You guys couldn't
press minus two fast enough for that one. Well, that's good. Why am I trying to game minus twos?
I should be trying to game plus twos. That's how it works, right? I have to balance it out.
He's fighting like crazy. Don't take this fish to avoid a hundred dollar fine. This is my backyard.
What? Fish verification in progress. What? I don't have a license to be here? I thought I did. It's
still the same day, isn't it? It's not a different state. Your license has a maximum. Isn't it the
same day? Oh no, it's the next day. Well, I just need to get to level five and I can go to the next
area. That's all I care about. Come here. They didn't verify that fish on Twitter. I'm not verified
on Twitter. Like my Twitter could be fake. I don't put anything there worth any real value to anybody
besides the like stream starting message. Oh, what's that? That's new. Blacktail Shiner.
This used to be a main A stream. Well, that's a, that's like a 2014 reference. Whoa, that thing is
big. Big but small. Wide but short. 39 bucks. Worms are doing a good job today. It's a larper.
Come on. Where was there? How much money is it to go to the next area?
I'm gonna move this way. I'm gonna get close to friends. What do you do with the fishes that you
catch? You sell them. Okay. Are you fishing or are you like trying to get free television?
Oh my god. That can't be real. That's a joke. This is, that's a radio tower. This is not a fishing
pole. How do you cast this? I feel like the only way to cast this is if you spin in a circle for
five, 10 straight seconds and then just let it go. Holy shit. That thing is big. Give me level five.
Wow. I forget what that. Remember what I said at the beginning of the stream? This is how it happens.
10 minutes or three hours. Yeah. Yeah. We made it. Oh, a crappy. But why? I don't know.
It, sometimes it's nice just to talk to you guys. You know, level five reached. Let's go.
Rocky Lake, Colorado. I unlocked dough balls, grub one, uh, schlopp schlopp schlopp spoon,
narrow spoon, spinner, flies. Oh, cool. I got to, okay. This is where the level,
this is where the game really begins. Look at all this stuff. Open feeder. All right. And then I want
to go back in inventory, go home. I want my, I want my rod. I'm going to go back to my house,
right? I am in my house. 196 bucks. All right. Inventory. Where's the rod? Home. Here we are.
Okay. Value spin. Six, three. Item can, item can be replaced only with item of the same type.
What are you talking about? What does that mean? I'm already using this one?
Oh, all right. Shit. This is all right. Camo vest, fish hut, extra small. I think that I already
have it on. All right. I got it on. I have a new, the rod is on. I need a new hook. Shop. Wait, how
much is it to go to, uh, Colorado? Rocky Lake. It's $2,000 to go here. Come on. And a license.
Six. So I need 2,600 bucks to go to Colorado. Damn it. All right. I can do this. Let's just go
back to Mud River. I still have a license. 821, right? Let's go. 1,200 bucks to be there for a
day. What? I just go here. I just need to make money. It's time to grind. No, I only need like
five, 600 bucks. It really is an MMO, isn't it? Yeah, it kind of is. Is this the new rod?
I think this is the new rod. Hello. Four, five, six, two, four, five, six, two.
Uh, the water is over here. I didn't even, I guess I caught that. This is gonna take a while.
How do I make money fast? You can't. I just want to see Colorado. Damn it. I gotta get back to
throwing it. It's not the shore. I'm gonna go on the bridge. What's on there? Worms? Yeah. I need
money. All right. I'm just gonna fill my backpack. 15 pounds. Shouldn't take long. It actually,
it may take potentially like an hour. No, well, 24 bucks. All right. Keep it. Five, you know,
10, 20 more of those. Just buy it? No. I'm not hitting the free to play wall and climbing over
it with a briefcase full of money. Yes, there's somebody standing here. There is. In case you
didn't know. These things are so cheap. I need something bitter. Like an IPA. That sounds good
to me. Something bigger. I caught a fish. How do you do like a thumbs up? I guess, hold on. When you,
when in doubt, just do Homer Simpson. No! That's Homer Simpson. Sideways. Homer Simpson. Look, it's,
imagine Homer Simpson lying down on his bed. On his back. You can't see that?
Bait was eaten. Horn wart? I wish there was in-game voice. I would be right behind this guy and I
would just turn on the voice and I would go and do it until he until he turned around. No more bait.
Pet food. I want to catch one of the, let me just check and see something here. Species. Channel
catfish. Pet food. There's, there are over, they are, they're over here.
Somewhere. Stay out of my spot. We can share. Look, you guys should be able to get along. You
both shop at the same clothing store. In fact, so do I. And we should all be friends because
we all go to the same store. We're all wearing the same like plaid shirts. All right, I'm going this
way. Get out of his spot. No, there is no my spot in this game. We share it as a group of fishermen.
This is definitely big enough for all of us to stay here. They both have those gigantic antennas.
26 bucks. How much? I have 1.7 pounds. There, this is my spot now. You don't have to complain
about me being in your spot. Lots of drama in the planet fishing competitive community. That's a
good one. Kick. You can't kick people. Do you think that that is a service available in this game?
Kill them with kindness. See? Like, no, why are they going over to the lily pads? That's passive
aggressive. You can pass time with tea. I waited an hour to remove the fog. What? No, you can't.
Is that real? But what about everybody else on the server? This ain't working. This is, this spot
sucks. Somebody give, somebody give $50? Oh no, that means that they're watching. Oh man, okay,
big bitch. Casted it back out. Oh my god. That was, thank you shitty viewbot for the 5,000
bits. 50 bucks. Big bits. Challenge the toxic fisher to a 1v1. You won't do it, I bet.
Well, thank you, shitty viewbot for the $50. It's a huge amount of money.
And, um, they're probably watching the stream right now. In fact, they're right next to me.
Uh, how about this? Whoever gets the next, next fish, whoever has the bigger fish, pound wise,
wins. Starting right now. I love the eye, eye blinking. That's the kind of eye blinking that's
like, motherfucker, you think you're gonna, mm, mm, whoever gets the bigger fish, right? I fucking
guarantee it's gonna be me. Asshole. That was, that was going on inside of the head there.
There's this place at the Link Casino Resort, Hash House of GoGo. Some of the finest hamburgers
you'll ever eat in your life. Tasty, juicy, full of flavor. With a dash of Worcestershire sauce.
There's no fish over here. There's no fish over here. I'm, all right, I'm going back to,
I'm going back to your spot. Stop using the pet food. I want a, I want a catfish. They're over here.
And they eat the pet food. It's their favorite food. That thing's fucking tiny. Oh, that's not
even the same guy. Not even the right guy. What I meant to say was that, that's a good fish.
Oh, my stomach. I thought he was coming to show. I thought it was the guy going,
yeah, look what I got. Here we go. This is my time to shine. Look at this thing. This thing is huge.
Holy shit. That's 10 inches. 10 inches. What do you got? Hold it up. I just saw it on the line.
Did he throw it away? I think he threw it away. Disqualification automatic one.
0.7 pounds. Where is it? Oh, it doesn't say 0.2. Did you get something? I'm waiting. 0.748,
10.1 inches. We'll see it. You can't lie. This game has a, a kill feed, a fish feed.
All right. We know what I got. He's telling the truth. All right. Fine. Round. Did he actually
win that first round? Cause this is round one, two out of three. Scroll up the chat. I can't,
how do you scroll up? I can't. I'm watching his stream. Yes. He's got a better pole than me,
though. He's got a bigger pole. He's got a more like, he's got more experience in the game.
All right. This is it. What'd he get? 0.97 pound trophy bluegill, 0.66 pound sunfish.
Well, how long was it though? Smaller fish. Yeah. Well, I, we don't use them the same rods.
It wouldn't be no change in the rules. This is like having a boxing match,
but I don't have to put on boxing gloves. That's not fair. That person's going to beat the shit out
of the other person. If we're at a competition, why do I get to, why do you have to wear boxing
gloves? But I don't, I can just like punch with my hands. Boxing gloves protect the hand, not the
other person. It doesn't protect the other person's face. Do you see what I'm getting at here? No,
I'm saying without the boxing gloves, if a boxer punches somebody in the face, it's going to do
like damage. Boxing gloves are worn to make it so they don't like, they don't do damage. What do
you guys think boxing gloves are for? For boxing? Is he showing me his fish? I'm not paying attention.
I must have been thinking of, I must have been, I'm sorry guys. Let me correct myself. I must
have been thinking of sockum buffers. That's what I was thinking of. Wrong thing, wrong sport.
He got one. What is it? A 0.2 pound, 0.29 pound. I can do better than that.
Push him. That's so fucked up.
Soccer shoes are for protecting the feet. No, how come you don't just walk around barefoot?
It's nice work. He didn't win. I need to catch something. He won twice.
I get to win. I get to win because it's my stream. I get to win. It's my stream. He won on his stream.
Yeah, so now I get to win on my stream. I'm just going both hands just into the water. Fuck,
I missed my time. What's he got? Uh oh. Let me see. 0.5. I can do so much better than this.
I'm just not getting distracted by talking about how boxing gloves hurt more or something. I don't
even remember what it was. Come on. Why are they getting stuff and not me? I got to take pet food
off. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Here it is. Oh, this is a big one. This is a big one. This
thing is fucking huge. Look at that thing. Don't break the line. This is the biggest fish in the
whole fucking lake. Too much tension. No, no, no, no. Look at this thing. It's like a whale.
Come here. Come here. Can he grab onto my hips and pull me forward? It's getting away. Come on.
It's right there. Where is it? Holy shit.
Three and a half pounds. 18 inches long. That's a small mouth buffalo. 81 bucks. You got it.
Let's take a look. Take a look. That's as big as as we are tall. Let me stand back. You win.
Winner is you. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I lost the first two. It's okay. Keeping this one. Let's go back to
back. Throw it at him. No, why is that not? It's only supposed to be like five up. Oh, come on.
It's supposed to only be five up. Give me a break. Someone on here doesn't even need to try. I'm so
happy about that. This was worth the three hours in this game. New pond, new pond. I need, I don't
have any money. I need more money. Is it worth another three hours? I don't think so, but I'm
not giving up yet. Not until we get to the new pond. I'm not going anywhere. What's the name of
this game? It's called Fishing Planet, I think. Planet Fish. One of those two. Just type in
Fishing. Fishing Planet. Why the second one? I feel like the spot was right here.
I'm not going to play a Dance Dance Revolution game. That's not going to happen.
I'm sorry to get everybody's hopes up, but I'm not going to play that game on stream.
You can go ahead. You can ride. That's fine. It's not going to happen. And if I ever did it,
I would be sober. All right. 34. Oh, how much money am I? Okay. I'm going to fill the backpack.
You couldn't dance sober. Actually, I do know how to dance fairly well. And not like, not like,
oh, look, I'm jokey. I'm wearing a fat suit yesterday. No. With the right beat, I can move.
That's not a lie. That's for real. With the right beat, I can move. I'm hitting my body. My legs can
spin around. Nobody does the finger snaps anymore. That needs to come back. Like the wrist,
the wrist and the elbow go down. Bang. Bang. Bang. Why did that go out of style?
Hasn't he? I'm still waiting for you boomers to move on. No. Go look at the green screen dancing.
Remember when I was like moving my legs around? Like bang. I was doing some like leg snaps.
Go watch the full screen green screen dancing and you tell me that was bad.
You did one good clip. Oh, did only one. It was like four. You did dad dancing. No, I did not.
That there's a very dad dancing is two fists up. The your left hand goes slightly above.
Look, I'll just show you. This is the dad dance. It's like this. Two fists. One hand is slightly
above the other one. And it's up down like this. That's the dad dance. I used to film weddings. I
know. Why do I have grandma hair? Because I fucking want it. Did you get paid to film weddings or did
you just what you do? You act like I'm just like filming a wedding that I'm what are you talking
about? Why would I do that? Yes, it was a service that I was hired to do. All right. You kind of
look like a creep to be honest. What kind of like what kind of comment is that? That's a comment
I would remove typically. I'm going to remove that comment. I'm going to remove that one. I think.
No, it's already gone. It's all right. You only read mean messages because they put a fish next
to it or they put it in red text. All right. I'm on. I got it. This ain't working. I got to move.
I want to go a spot that I haven't gone to before. Like over here. Here we go.
Phylactery Lich just gave four gifted subs. Thank you Phylactery. If you missed last night,
Phylactery gave an absolute shitload of money on top of this and it looks like we're getting
part two of that. There's 20 more from Phylactery Lich. 20 more community subs. That was 24 which
makes 420. There you go. I get it. It's been fulfilled. Yes. Thank you so much though for
those community subs. It's a lot of subs. 24, 420. What am I? What's going on? Is this a big one?
I think I got stuck on a lily pad. Wait, pull this back. What is this? I don't even. How am I
doing this? What the fuck? How did I do that? I could do a super cast. That didn't even go that
far. What? I'm missing something here. Am I going to aim up? I can't. That doesn't work. Why is there
cat? Got it. Okay, $29. Where'd it go? Why didn't do that when I can just do this? It goes further.
Can we get another blue cheese burger ad please? Fishing level almost level six. Run ads. Not with
4,000 people here. How do you do the long cast? It's you hold it. If you have the right,
you hold right. Bugs. Okay. All right. What's that? Red with honey. All right. I got some new stuff
here. Nah, no ads. Getting to 15 pounds and hoping that's enough money. New lake. I'm trying. I need
to get to 15 pounds so I can sell all my fish. Answer their question. What do you mean? What
question? What was it? Was somebody in here? Who said something? Don't get stuck in the tree. All
right. These are all 35, 35, 35. They might be enough. How did I forget that fast? Because
there's, I don't know, there's like three or four things going on at the same time. I forgot. I did.
I have no idea what's going on. What happened? Hydrate from the pond. Okay. You hold right click
and then you press left click. If you have the right bow, the right rod. That's a $36 fish
right there. 11.2 pounds. I can do like three or four more, but it kind of sucks that I couldn't
get it to work. That's a big one. Don't take this fish. I'll take a, that's all right. I'll
take a $44 fine. Verifying. I still get to keep it. What was the thing that we were talking about
before? I forget what it was. It was not the best ice cream. Oh, ads. Right. Yeah. I'm not
going to run ads because when you run an ad, if I were to do like three minutes of ads right now,
1500 people would probably try it. No, I don't, I don't run ads on my stream. This is an ad free
viewing experience. I can't control when you come to the stream, if you get a pre-roll,
but I, this is an ad free viewing experience. I don't run ads ever. My default dance. How much
money do I make if I run an ad? I have no idea. I don't have any, I have no gauge to tell you that.
I don't do it. So I can't really tell you. He gave us ads during Terraria. Yeah. As a joke.
All right. There's a fish are all gone in here. You guys stole them all right here, right in the
lilies. No, this is also a joke ad. You literally caught the three sunfish. I need one of I'm sorry.
Well, you got a two pounder. Oh no, that's not you. What would you rate this game? Um, uh, come
back to me in like 20 more minutes. I have to deliberate on this one. Uh, four, but, but, but,
but, but, but, but it gets, it gets two and a half extra points full on that meter for being
relaxing. So it's a 4.2 out of 10, but it turns into like a 6.8, 6.6. That's a good one. 6.65.
Cause I could see like two or three of my friends just hanging out,
just catching fish and comparing how big they are. It's free. It's free to just do what I'm
doing right now. There's no reason to not at least try it if you wanted to play a fishing game,
whatever. It's just here. Increments of a thousand. What? 6.65. That's increments of a hundred.
So yeah, it's a 665. It's a, it's a 441 without the extra 2.2 percentage, 2.2, 221,
whatever, of friend interaction points. You get it. And it's free.
You've messed me up with this whole hundred point scale right now. This thousand point,
hundreds, hundreds of a decibel denomination. It's a four out of 10 with 2.6 extra points
of friend and free interaction. Just say seven out of 10. I wouldn't give this a seven out of 10.
It's point scales, point scales are dumb anyways. Do you know why? Cause everybody's afraid to give
any game a rating. You give a game like a six and you anger a bunch of people. You give a game like
a nine and you anger a bunch of people. Everyone's terrified to rate anything. That's not a 7.5 to
like an 8.8. Star made a whole video on this. That video is, I will go down in history saying
that I think that is the best YouTube video ever made. That is the best video game related YouTube
video. I'm just going to say it. I think it is the everything is an eight out of 10 star video.
I think it's, it's got some great comedy points on it. Just put it on the corner of the stream.
No, no, I said, no, no, no, no, no, no. Everyone needs to like what I like.
Anger face. Can I please catch one more fish? I got to put the worms back on.
I got like three, four in a row and I haven't seen any paper view. Would you guys, would you
guys watch a pay per view stream? Just curious. If it, if it was like $12 to watch a stream,
would you do it? No, not like me playing fishing. What if it was like German rumble live two and
they were like, and they were like five WWF superstars in it. And I, and I promised that I
was going to take a chair hit in the face. Like you knew at some point during that stream, I was
going to take a real chair shot to the face for real. And I would like train and practice and do
it. No, I would never do something like that. Didn't they, they just recently did the
sub streams, right? I would never do that ever. I can't think of one reason to do it. Maybe I,
no, I can't. It's hard to think of a reason why. If you do a sub only stream, that stream is just
going to be restreamed on YouTube on like 500 accounts. It's just how are you going to stop
that you alienate and annoy a huge amount of your audience, a majority of your whole audience.
And it doesn't even matter anyways, because somebody will just, it's just going to clip it
and put it somewhere else. Use it as a prank. The way I see it is like a maybe a private creative
stream, like a review mentorship thing. Yeah, I honestly, I forget about sub only streams.
Why not? I mean, maybe is a bandwidth a concern? No, why would anybody can just stream on Twitch?
Why don't have password streams? Or just, you know, that would be right. Instead of sub only,
why not do password protected streams? It's kind of the same thing, isn't it? The password is sub.
Password stream could have use. Yeah, you could do like company. Well, I think didn't,
Discord really is starting to drop this whole thing here, right? With doing private streams.
It used to be, this is now, here's a story for you. Back in the day, and I'm talking maybe
six, seven, eight years ago, if you wanted to, we used to do this thing where somebody would screen
share on Skype. We'd have a group call going. And we were always begging, begging and hoping
for a solution just to have kind of a private session where three or four people can just watch.
It was horrible quality. It was really, really delayed. It was really shitty. It wasn't very
good. Discord is start is doing that now. And then steam brought in the streaming too. But it was
super delayed as well. A password protected stream on Twitch is kind of that same deal,
like a screen share. I have not caught a fish in probably 35 minutes. Something's not something's
wrong. But sub streams, I feel like you just kind of make a lot of people angry. I think there's one
way where that works. And it's really, really bad. Honest to God, I think the only way that that
really works if you wanted to do it is permanently turn it on. It's awful. And that's not I think
that's a really, really terrible idea. But I like what are you going to turn it on half the time?
You would never get new viewers. No, but if you get if you mean, if you're gonna go all in on
something like that, you've got you're gonna go all in on that. I don't think you can kind of do
that. Like, well, should I I think you either you go all in or you don't. Alright, finally,
there it is 1000 bucks. All right, but I want to fall back. Have it as a patreon reward. That
makes sense to maybe what's my discord? Do exclamation discord, you'll find the link public.
Anybody can join it. Anybody can use it. That's a pretty good one. You already make thousands
a month from subs and bits. I think that's kind of the like the point too, though, is
now you if you if you have like a bunch of subs, and you're doing well on Twitch,
you're doing good on Twitch. I feel like that's like too daint. Why would you do that? Like,
it's kind of daint. Like, oh, I think I'll turn that on. Like, you don't really need to do that.
It's not going to gain you any more money. If that's what you're after. I don't think that
would work. I think that's how you lose money. If money is what you're after. There are other
avenues to do that. Alright, 14.3. I'm done. No, I can get one more. One more small one.
Some strivers do sub gate on video playbacks, like on their streams, like on the past broadcasts.
I would never turn that on. Because if a new viewer comes to your channel and wants to know
what you're about, they either have the second that they are currently watching, which we've
talked about, like shitting our diapers before. And that person that has to have a conscious
decision to go, Oh, look, is there anything else that this guy has here that I can like see if I
want to watch this or not? Having VODs, let somebody go back and pick something that they
may think is interesting. And maybe they'll stick around, maybe they'll go, Oh, that was cool. I
like that stream. That was a fun stream or something, right? When you have a sub gate on
past broadcasts or on video highlights for Twitch or something, you are banking completely on the
fact that you are going to be that second that that person comes to the stream is all you got.
15 point. All right. All right. All right. I've got, I've got, I'm good. Time to end the day. I got,
how much money do I got? 4,200. We're good. People who aren't subbed can't catch up on streams either
with it. Oh, that's true too. Like, let's say you subscribe for like three or four months
and then you unsubscribe, you know, for whatever reason, you know, no one is ever obligated to
subscribe to anybody's channel. So if you're subbed for a few months and you have, you know,
you're not watching every single stream, you have a, Oh, I'm subbed. Now I can actually see the other
content if you wanted to watch it. If you aren't subbed anymore after three, four, five months,
two months, even one month, whatever, you lose access to the thing that you had before.
And it's like, I mean, I kind of, I guess that kind of, that's, you know, I just want everybody
to be able to see stuff that we've already done. I wouldn't, I don't want to put a paywall up for
stuff that's already been done. I need a license here. One day license in Colorado,
$2,000 to go here. This is such a joke. Wait, wait, wait, what's in here?
Crappy. Marshmallows. Have I unlocked marshmallows? Preferred lures. Oh, hold on. I need,
I need a nano spooner. Nano spinners, nano spoons, nano spoons, nano spoons. Do I have a nano spoon?
Nano spoon. What do they like to eat? Marshmallows. I can't buy them. Is there a spoon?
Thing here? Am I just, am I dumb? Oh, I am. Okay. There is more.
If you didn't know, it would be under lures. All right. Spoon, nano spoon. I think I have to,
there are 48 pages. Nano, nano spoon, nano spinner, nano spinner, nano spinner, spinner, spinner,
nano spoons, but I'm not old enough for that. Nano spinner. I guess I'll get this one.
Which one looks coolest? I'll get the, I'm going to get the Spider-Man one.
Okay. Barbless nano spinner. Okay. And what food? Marshmallows, maggots, crickets, maggots.
All right. It's live. We're going to get crickets and maggots. Crickets. Here we go. It's got,
I don't, I can't, it's gotta be crickets. Maggots, I'm not old enough. Okay. All right. All right.
New rod. Oh, what have we got? Creek Pro 8, the Omni Float, value spin, the Elemental 6-7.
Think so. 1700. Put it on. Where's my inventory? Okay. Glowing Peership Float. Where's my
Horn Warp? Where's the home storage? Okay. The Telefloat. Elemental. All right. Nice. Barbless
spinner. The rail must be equipped first. Is it not equipped? Oh, the rail on. Get that barbless
spinner on there. Line must be equipped. Oh, will you fuck off? 262. Got it. Line must be equipped.
I just did. Right there. 209. Backpack is full. What's happening here? What's going on? Please.
All right. I have it here. Backpack is full. How is my backpack full?
That's a slop spoon. I don't want the slop. Five of these? Why do I have five of these?
There we are. Terminal Tackle Weight. Let's go. Rocky Lake. One day past 2,000 bucks.
Colorado. That was it. This rod is probably cool though. Let's take a look. I only need like 100
bucks. Look at this beauty. This thing is a beauty. All right. What we got on here for bait.
That's all we know. We don't use bait. This is just this thing. I would love it. I would love
it if it just snapped and just broke. That's a nice rod. Nice new rod. That went very far. That
went across the whole lake. What does that mean? I need to keep it somewhere floating around like
Flappy Bird, right? I can't let it touch anything. Wait. Why is everybody saying minus two? Flappy Bird?
I didn't even know there was somebody on there. That's far. All right. Slow. Stop and go. What
does that mean? Stop and go. Oh, I think somebody's on it. Is that what that means?
Somebody's on it. Somebody's on it. Somebody's on this. I think this is a big one. Oh, that is
a big one. That's a spotted bass. $100 fine. Nice. That thing's... Okay. I've done this three times.
Am I going to be three for three and getting in trouble? Yeah. What is the percentage? That seems
like a really high percentage chance to get arrested for it. It's definitely more than one
out of three. It's probably like a 10% chance to get that. Is there anything on this? I can't believe
that Disney and Sony did not come to an agreement for Spider-Man. That's fucking unbelievable to me.
It's turning into a podcast. Big Whoop. 50th superhero in five years. Yeah, but the... Okay.
Those Spider-Man... What the fuck over here? Just Spider-Man. All right. 13 bucks. How much do I need?
Far From Home is my favorite Marvel movie. It just is. Homecoming was very, very, very good too. I
think the... I think the two Spider-Man movies in the MCU are the best. Out of the... All of them
combined. Homecoming sucked? What? Michael Keaton. Michael Keaton is in that movie. It's
automatically... It's like Michael Keaton being in a movie is the same way I feel about when a car is
drivable in a video game. It becomes a full letter grade hire. I am sorry. That is... I will... I will
take that all the way to the bank. Spider-Verse is better. If Spider-Verse is... I'm talking like
the Spider-Man MCU movies. Not... Into the Spider-Verse was great, but I'm talking live action
Spider-Man. There was somebody on that. Spider-Verse was Sony Pictures. Yeah, but that... The amazing
Spider-Man one and two was also Sony. And yeah, you go back to the the Sam Raimi movies. That was
Sam Raimi. That wasn't, you know, Sony. Easy, easy. Big one. All right. If Sam Raimi comes back and
does Spider-Man for the next Sony movie, maybe. We'll see. But that... That is not going to happen.
You all know it. What is this thing? Ooh. Illegal? This one's illegal as well. This would be four
for four. I'm... I'm losing money and I'm trying to gain a hundred, two hundred dollars. The article
said that the director and Tom Holland is still going to be doing the next two planned Spider-Man
films. They'll mess it up somehow. Not those two. You don't got all the other... You don't have all
the other production in the Marvel Studios teams. Takes more than a director and an actor to make a
movie. Is anybody on this? No. I want more Taskmaster. They have to explore more of these
interesting characters. Mysterio was just one of those insanely interesting characters that I...
I'm so happy that... At least that last one was Mysterio. It was fucking awesome. No, no, no, no,
no spoilers. If anybody says a spoiler, they're fucking gone. This is a great character. I loved
every second of that movie. Vulture... Vulture was... Michael Keaton, man. Like, God. I wanted...
Hear me out on this one. When I found out that Michael Keaton was going to be in a Spider-Man
movie, I shit my pants. I remember I was driving my car and I was just driving along and I was on
the radio. There's just an Michael Keaton is picked to be cast as a villain in a new Spider-Man
movie. And I was like, what the... And I just started... Yeah, there's nothing I could do about
it because I thought he was going to be Carnage. I'm just thinking, imagine Michael Keaton,
Beetlejuice, Carnage. Oh my God. I was so ready for that. Too bad. But he did a fantastic job as
Vulture. This is my number one podcast. Hey, welcome to the cast. Hey, guys. Let me be the first to
welcome you to my new series, the Comcast. As you see, we're using our fishing rod here.
Welcome to the Comcast. We talk about movies, TV shows while we fish. If you have anything,
any topic you want to talk about, anything that you got on your mind, throw it up there.
All right. No, no, no, no, no. Listen to me. This is important. You cannot do a minus two
and then an LUL after that. Doesn't that contradict that minus two? Don't correct me here.
I'm sorry. I don't think that matches up. Do I have enough money? Worse streamer on Twitch?
Worse streamer? Really? Worse than like the dickhead that streamed porn? Worse than that?
Yeah. How could you compare yourself? That stream was... I'm not even going to say it.
I am not going to take this because I get arrested every time I'm doing it.
Look at this. Yeah. How do I just end the day? I have an unlimited license here. End the day.
I need money. End the day. End the day. How do I end the day?
300 bucks is exactly where I was started with 20, 30 minutes ago. That's exactly where I was
30 minutes ago. God damn it. Just pay. I need to catch five fish. I'm not going
to keep any illegal fish. Promise. Sell old rods for cash. Sell old rods. Sell old rods.
What do we got? Sell old rods. I gotta go home for this. Okay. Inventory. Home. Ooh,
shit. Okay. Mini spin 800. Sell off a net. Yes, I do. Value spin 63. Done. All right. Let's go.
Rocky Lake. First time ever. We're getting there. Rocky Lake, Colorado. Travel for one day.
Got my license. Let's go. I'm not going to spend anything. Okay. We got what we got here.
Marshmallows. I have whisked crickets. All right. I'm going to get some bluegills.
Colorado golden trout is crickets as possible. Anything else? What about... I need crickets as a
much higher up on that list. Doe balls, crickets, crickets. I think we're going to go over here.
Golden Shiner. This looks like a good place to start. What do you guys think? Don't write.
Nobody write that. Okay. Now I've got my... Let's try it right here. Right off the rock. Look at
this beautiful mountain, rocky Colorado. Fabulous nano spinner. Stop and go. Stop and go. What are
your thoughts on the potential Disney theme Super Smash Brothers game? With the amount of
shit owned by Disney, you could have Tom Brady versus Darth Vader versus Donald Duck.
I mean, I've said from the very beginning that I think Scrooge McDuck would be a
perfect addition to Smash Brothers. That move set is already there. I can already see it.
The issue is, didn't Sakurai already say, that they have to have originated on a video game
console, right? But what a perfect addition that would be. And there it is. Bluegill.
Sorry, I'll keep it. Nintendo and Disney hate each other. Where do you get that from? Tom Brady's
special move is invoking Gronk, who spikes the enemy into the turf. I think at that point I
would probably quit video games. That would probably be time. I would probably look at that
and be like, I think I'm done with this. I don't think this is for me anymore.
The lines are getting tangled. This is kind of a big one. I'm gonna like choke this guy.
I just rip his head over. What is it? Whoa! All right, that's pretty good. Why do I think
this guy cares? I'm just automatically assuming that everybody here is in chat.
And look, look what I have. That's pretty good though. Oh, I do care. They say
127 bucks. Pretty good. Let's get another one. That was a big cast, I know. Jesus Christ,
fishing. I'm not sure if that's somebody coming in with a saying that, oh, I can't believe you're
doing this or like, this is cold to me. I'll take it. 20 bucks. Oh, narrow spoon, small minnows,
small cut bait. What's the biggest thing in this game? How do I get, I want to go on a boat.
Can I take out a loan? Jesus Christ, fishing. What? Hold on. Do you have a, you're doing two
at the same time? What happens if you, if you catch one on there, you have to drop the one
you're holding? Do people actually, do people multi-box fishing? I don't know if people did
this. How many of these can you reliably do? That's kind of big. Let's see. That's all right.
That's 0.28 pounds. Sorry. That's pretty good. Not bad. See, now I get to be the guy that has the
cool rod. Here we go. Another one. This is a good spot. Don't lose it. Another big one. I want, dude,
nothing can replace that like four pound fish that I caught. I think it was awesome. I took your name
and wow, catch one fish for me to get it back. See, that's where you've already played yourself,
unfortunately, because when was the last time you've ever seen me in a game, especially a
multiplayer game, where German985 was my name? It's going to be like fucking Harold26.
Do it quick. Take that one. Don't take that one. Don't take Harold26. That's my name. It's going to
be my wow name. He's going to be, doesn't matter. I'll find it. I'll find another one right at the
end. Got one. I just turned on like the developer console. Make your wow character for where they
take all the names. I don't care about like the name of the character. It's okay. Did I lose him?
I think I lost it. Oh, I was going to look. I want to see it. Nah, I'm doing this stupidly. Nah,
just get it back in here. Okay. These are all 30 to 50 bucks each. I feel like that's all I'm
getting over here though. I want to put on, why is it got a bunch of crickets? Different line?
Can I not put a, shit, I have to use this. I mean, I'm catching stuff all over the place, but
I want to put on that new bait. I took the hook off. This is the spinner rod, right? Am I going
to play Final Fantasy, the entirety of Final Fantasy? I'm not going to do that. I don't think
so. Sorry. Stop that. Did that in one stream. Is there ever been an RPG I have considered?
Uh, I guess I've technically played some RPGs on this stream. Not, I don't know. Have I ever done
a turn-based RPG on this stream? I don't think I have. No, I don't think so. I think all the
fish are gone here. I'm moving. I'm moving. I don't like this spot anymore. I'm going to go
down here. All right. So I've been playing Fishing Planet for four hours.
Now I'm just, this is just a, I'm liking this though, but okay. Trying to think about something
here. Hold on. Fishing Planet 2 incoming. I actually like this. I catch a big one. I did.
I got a huge one earlier. If you were here, you would have been like, what the fuck? All right.
I feel like this is a rubber band. What's going on here? Am I stuck on the weeds over here? Come
on. I would just swim over there and take it out. That's not that far away. That's right there.
What a dummy. I lost that. I lost that. That, that thing was expensive, wasn't it? Oh, fuck me.
That thing was like six or seven hundred dollars. All right. I'm, I need to go back to my house.
Is this not going to, is it going to be a whole day? How long does it take to go back to your
house? You can fly from Colorado to Texas back to Colorado in a day. Okay. I'm good. I just got
this wave of craving in my brain. It just happened to this a second ago right now. Stuffed crust
Pizza Hut pizza. It just, it just deposited into my head. All right. Um, where is it? I got it back
to my home here. Take this off. Tele-float. Item can't be replaced with only item of the same type.
Tele-float. And then I'm going to put on the hook. Reel must be equipped. Okay. Relax. Where's my reel?
Let me spin. This looks kind of cool. Too heavy. Break the line. Now I want crickets. Must be
gripped first. All right. Tackle's too heavy and we'll break the line. What will break the line?
This is going to break the line? Two pounds. Here. Put this one on. There. You all right?
Crickets. Here we go. It's not sponsored. Sponsored. This game came out three years ago.
All right. I'm back guys. This time I got crickets. Looking for a different fish. I have, yeah. I've
gone fishing before. Plenty of times. It's an interesting thing for a minute. I get bored
really easily though. Here we go. First catch with the crickets. Ooh, this is new. What is this one?
Ooh, black crabby. You're out of current bait. I only bought one cricket. You buy one cricket.
What the fuck is going on? They're right here. What? 98. How do I put them into my backpack?
Why will they not go to my backpack? Why am I putting one? I'm putting on. I'm baiting one
cricket onto my pole and then putting that in a backpack and then going, like getting on a plane.
Getting out of the plane. Taking the tackle out of my checked bag and everything. Doing that and
then leaving. Why would I do this? How can I not put this over here? I need, how do I bring more
than one? Bait. Cricket. Put it over there. Oh my god, you said to do that. Really? Oh, that stinks.
Well, whatever. Let's, I still have a day pass. It's $2,000 to do that. Did I seriously spend
$2,000? Did I spend $2,000 to go there and come back? Anybody here like crickets? Crickets. What
is a crankbait? Blood worm. Of course not. Nobody. Crickets. Nobody. What about the other side?
Well, that was Fishing Planet. Fun little game. Free. As you can tell, it's interesting,
roguelike. You can run out of money and you have to, you know, go back and try it again and start
kind of from the beginning. They'll hate crickets. They will. A cricket and a grasshopper are the same
bug. A cricket and a grasshopper. God just randomized the role between the two of them.
It was just like that you made a grasshopper and then you did the random button like 10 times.
They're the same fucking thing. One chirps like a bird. Big deal. That's like saying blue cheese
sauce is the same as blue cheese dressing. I fucked up, okay? I'm sorry, I fucked up.
FortniteJimmy is joining us again. That's a, I'm actually happy about that. Jimmy's back. I am
really excited about this. I can't wait to see what FortniteJimmy asks. Hi. Um, I can't.
Can I tell you guys something? I, I love this stream. This is like one of my favorite streams
in the last like two months. I am, I am very happy right now. Can I just tell you? I think for me,
best stream, like favorite best streams of all time. Sims 4 mod murder house. Fishing planet.
Close second. Nobody wants crickets. That's okay. Fishing is just outdoor gambling. It's really
strange that I know exactly what you're talking about. That's funny. That's weird. Yeah, it is.
Yeah, that's fair. They don't eat cheese either. You only get one? What's that even mean? Yeah,
I'm busy, but like I only get one though. But I'm here. I'm available for questions.
This is turning into a dad stream. I was going to take the cheese off. This isn't working.
Guys, this is not, this is not like a, like a 10 year old. All right. This is, I'm being
trolled right now. Why am I like, I'm like getting in my own head like, wait a minute.
I better like be, tell this person like, hey, it's like fun. Like just, I'm trying to like backtrack.
I'm like getting in my own. Wait a minute. Hold on, dude. Is this like, this person's following me
into service and talking about free Fortnite skins. This person's not real. I can't, you can't type
like that. And I couldn't type like that at nine. Yeah. This, yeah. That's okay.
Hey, you want to know how to respond to any, like any, doesn't matter what it is.
Damn. Damn. No, it's a kid. I can't, this is not even, this is a, this is somebody,
this person's like 30. I'm fighting it. It's like, it's, it's faking me out. I'm fighting it.
I didn't, this is a troll. I'm being, I didn't just leave them. I'm being
fucked with right now. You guys have been, you guys have fallen for it.
You can never go back there. I can't go back there.
I didn't, I didn't answer any questions. I can't go back. I can't go back in there.
Okay. I'm going back. I'm coming. Okay. I'm back. Everybody can settle down. I got a good cover.
Okay. The internet cafe. I'm being trolled. He got lost in the realm.
He went to go pick up some herbs. Why did I leave them? How could I have done that?
I'll be right back. I'm going to go get a water. I keep laughing. I can't stop. I keep laughing at
just like the mom's MacBook, like overheating. And I just keep seeing this image in my head.
It is like the mom's MacBook overheated and like did it auto, like Intel shut down the computer,
you know, Intel has that shit. And I just see him standing there still for two minutes before
he just because he's gone, but he doesn't get disconnected yet. And he's just standing there
lost somewhere. And he just gets fucking disconnected. And it takes two minutes for
his portrait to disappear. I can't, I can't even, I can't even play this anymore. I can't play this
game right now. It's all, it's ruined. It's ruined for me. I can't play it.
Fortnite Jimmy 2010.
All right. I'm sorry, but if somebody comes into a fish game and asks me how to get Fortnite skins,
I'm going to automatically assume that that person is a viewer just trying to get
like onto my skin. Jimmy, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Jimmy, if you're watching. You're the only streamer
that's played this long enough to become a villain. You don't become a villain in a fishing game. I
just, I didn't do anything. I, all I said, I said, hey, I'm ready to answer questions. I'm busy.
But like, you know, I'll give one question for every, any person in the server. I'm not the bad
guy. I was answering questions. Then you left. Yeah. I said, I was like, Hey, good luck, man. I
got to go. Like what you got? I'm not allowed to leave a game. I can't leave. Uh, if I lacked
your lich gave $50. Jerma bullied Jimmy. He was just a kid, Jerma. You left him in the realm
where there were no fish to fish, no walls to wall run. I have to. Oh, God damn. This shit is
fucking ridiculous. Nice cast. I'm with Jimmy right now. What do you want me to say? Tell him
I'll answer any question. I got extra time. I got extra time on my internet cafe card
and I'm around. Now we can't just go back to fishing after this. Can we? I think maybe,
maybe if I'd like just go back to normal, I just need to go back to normal and get the cheese off.
I'm going to put some pet food on here. I'm going to go back to normal. I didn't do anything wrong.
I didn't do anything. I'm fishing. That's what a villain would do. He sent you a friend request.
Did he? Hold on. Wait a minute. Did Jimmy send me a friend request?
This is too many Fortnite characters. Too many Fortnite characters. All right. I'll take them
both. Are you happy? I'll take Kyle 2007 and I'll take Jimmy 2010. Sure. I'm going. Wait,
this is his whole profile. 2020, 2019. How do I leave this screen? Can I take his stuff?
What? No, I'm not trying to take his stuff. I can't leave the screen. There we go. All right.
We're going to, we're going, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go to
Jimmy and I'm going to say I'm sorry. Smotherim just gave $50. Thank you for the 50 bucks. They
say local streamer annihilates poor Fortnite kid in fishing game. No, I'm going. How do I join?
How do I join this game? All right. The fishery. I can just do it, right? I don't have $120. How
is it possible? Sell something. Sell one of these. $8. That's nothing. What? How much money?
I got it. I have enough money. All right. Quick, quick, quick. I have to save. I have to go say
what's up. I have $120. Okay. I think I'm in this one, right? What the heck? Where is he? Jimmy,
he's stuck in the realm somewhere. Is he in another room? That's the one. Let's go.
En1. The room is full. Why am I fucking 15 feet tall? Jimmy. He's lost in the realm.
Somebody left? No, there's nobody in this one. This is a new room. I feel like I just got to the
end of an RPG dead end. Wrong room, Jim. Find Jimmy before it's too late. Oh, fuck. I gotta
turn around. Shit. Whatever. Oh shit. Five minutes left on the internet card. I don't have much time.
No, I can't just... I can't just like go PM. No, I've got to like just... Hey, I got five minutes
left on my internet card. Just checking the rooms. Just checking the realms and see what's
happening in each one. What do you mean PM? No. What? Come on. What? He went into a different room.
He went into another realm. Okay, we'll go. I'm fine. Yeah, I think people are weird. Don't worry
about that. Damn it. The fucking coffee pasta. I can't. I've done. I just want to say hi.
I don't know because people have... I don't know. Some people are fucking nice.
Why is... That's very easy. I gotta like... I don't know. I'm just nice to everybody. I think
being... I'm just nice to everybody. I don't think... I think I just try to be nice. I just try. I just
try to be nice to everybody. Yeah. That's it. That's it. Because that's true. That's just true.
I don't matter. I just try to be nice to everybody. That's just... That's a true statement.
All right. I've closed the book. I've closed it. Oh, my internet cafe card.
Jimmy. I'm just a huge fan of Fortnite. It's a little rude, I think.
I talked to them earlier. I did, which I did. I did. That's true. I talked to them earlier.
Remember we were talking about like, oh, look at my fish and look at your fish. What's the contest?
All right. It's been fun, Jimmy, but I've got to go. Okay. Yes. Okay. Everything's fine. We're all
done. You're a nice guy. Thank you. Hey, thanks. It was... It's been a pleasure. My internet
fucking cafe time is up. The ding went off. Okay. I... Get out. I don't want... This is... I don't...
I'm gone. I didn't... I'm... That's it. I just said, I have a great time in the game. It was
fun. It was nice to meet you. Have a good day. Goodbye. I just want to fish. I can't block them.
All right. That was... That was interesting. Okay. Let's go back to playing the game.
That was... That was... You know what? Yeah, that's right. That was two grown adult men.
How much? I have zero dollars? Oh my god. He knows you're online. Yeah, but I'm just... That could
be any... That could be online, but not... In fact, you spent all your money stalking this person.
No, I'm just trying to... My internet... My internet card's up. All right. That's it. Thank you. If I
liked your glitch for the $50, you better hope to have Google Fiber in prison. Why? What are you
talking about? What does that mean? Look, I just want to fish. I just want... I just want to fish.
I want to fish. I'm just gonna... I'm going to the basic fishing zone. I'm gonna fish.
Can I do this? Let me see. It's 160 coins to change your fucking name? What? This is why I
don't enter in-game chats. I never do either. And I was pressured to answer questions from the chat
room. This one. This is an in-game chat right here. Fortnite Jeremy. You have to quit streaming.
Did I just... Wait, did I just PM him? Why did somebody write that? Uninstall the game.
Ugh. I'm staying. Terrible. What a shitty internet cafe. I'm fucking crying. Fishing planet.
Why would you pay to do this? Good to see you. Bye. Yeah, it's my turn on the VC. We got a lot of
them. I just love Fishing Planet. You just left your coat and leave all your stuff. You play Fishing
Planet for like six hours at an internet cafe and you leave all your stuff on a chair? Where were
you going? It's staying logged in. Yeah, you're still logged in as you... No, it's an internet
cafe. They have like the internet cafe account. God, that's fucking ridiculous. My fucking head
hurts. That was fucking... That was unreal. I'm gonna do put some bread on now. What the hell's
going on? How's Cox? Cox is doing actually pretty good ever since they fixed it. Flying pixels,
thanks for the five community subs. Thank you. What did they do? Their service is just awful,
unfortunately. I went away for three hours and the stream looks exactly the way it did.
Yeah, because not much has changed. Did I get anything? Did you ever wake that guy up?
Oh shit. Lewis Cheese, it's time for you to wake up. Lewis Cheese,
wake up. I hope you didn't miss your appointment because this is three and a half hours late.
I did it already. You can change your reeling speed. Oh yeah, I know. You can do slow. You can
be fast. Come on. Let me catch one fish for the first time in an hour. There it is. Got it. Another
thousand pings for Lewis. Oh god, my head is fucking killing me.
This is worse than the Labo streams and the Birdhouse streams. Somehow I disagree. I'm not
sure why. This is cozy. This has been a cozy stream. I'll be live tomorrow too. Tomorrow we're
probably gonna play Maximum Action. I missed it? What? Yeah, it is a constant conflict game. You're
right. How long is Maximum Action? Is it more than two or three hours? Or is it a quick game?
It's long, right? Long enough. I could probably do a whole stream on it, right? What's the best
fish I've ever eaten? A piece of king salmon from an Italian restaurant in Boston. And I don't
remember the name of the restaurant because I'm stupid. That is true. Yeah, I wish I remembered.
It was one of those scenarios where I was with my family and it was like, oh, let's go out to this
place and just kind of blend it together with everything else. The thing is, though, a lot of
those, a lot of Boston restaurants, especially the, they can have not only very similar menus,
but there's a ton, especially in the north end. There are so many Italian restaurants that it's
this, this probably hundreds of them. Oh, who is that in the distance? Well, somebody on the server?
Look to your left. This fishing man 62. He's just playing the game. Oh, I'm keeping it.
That, that, that crept up so fast. I couldn't stop it. Oh, yeah. I wish I knew this menu.
Why did I not know that there was a Metal Gear Solid menu? Pet food. Who uses cheese to fish?
A lot of people. It's used a lot. Talk to fishing. No, I'm no longer speaking in this chat. I'm just
guy playing video game. Is it the game's feeling eerie? That's because it's covered in smoke.
There's like a whole fog over everything. That's just like, that's just scary. It's scary. That is
a scary trope. This is illegal. I'm going to release it. I'm not getting in trouble. I don't
have any money. Why do I have so much? I have 198 pieces of cheese. Why do I have all this? This is
too many. Can I sell it? Can I get market value for this? Another illegal fish. Don't think so.
He's here. He's here. You know how many versions of Fortnite Jimmy I've seen in this chat? There's
like four of them. Five hours. What am I going to eat for food after this? Please press T. All right,
let me try that. It's been 5 a.m. the whole stream. 2 p.m.? Am I going to do this? What about all the
people in here? I guess I just can control time. This actually looks really nice. It's client
side. Idiot. No! What? Hey, what? No, no, no. No, no, no. Why am I being? Oh, no. Why is it doing this?
Say you're sorry. You don't know the controls. No, that's assumed. That's assumed. I'm like the
third person at this point. Can I get a manager? I don't understand. I'm trying to talk to people
and I'm just PMing this random Fortnite person. Oh, no. What the fuck have I done? What the fuck?
Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy. Wrong message. Sorry. Easy. Easy. Easy. That's like very simple. Easy.
How do I get out of this? No, no, no, no, no. No. No, I just was like, I was wrong. That would make
no sense. What did I just take? Not like, oh, sorry. Like, that was my wrong message. I was
sending it. Like, oh, sorry. Is it? Sorry. Out with everybody. That's the wrong message very clearly.
I'm just nice to everybody. Why do I have to message Jimmy again? I was trying to prove
somebody wrong in chat and they were right. But, uh, German sucks. Thanks for the five community subs.
Thank you. No, it's not the same person. It's not the same person. Like, oh, I was the wrong
message. I'm just another person at the internet cafe. I'm just another person. Don't you guys
understand? Like, I don't know who that person is. Asking for bits. Why did I have to fucking type?
I said, didn't I specifically say I'm not writing in an in-game chat ever again? And look what
the fucking happened. Look at what happened. I messaged the Fortnite troll person. He's in
chat right now. Well, then he'll know that I'm streaming from an internet cafe. It's really
loud in here. Fucking really, really loud in here. Hey, sorry. I'm sharing a space with
like two or three different, like three people that way and like five people that way. There's
like another 20 people in the other offices down here. I'm looking back. All these computers are
doing a good, they're all playing, we're all playing the same game. Hey, easy. Quit dropping
glasses back there. We all have to share this space, you fucking asshole.
Hey, hey, easy. It's just a game, man. You don't get to smash the computer.
We all lose them sometimes. You can't catch the big one every time.
Thanks.
Thanks for watching, Jimmy. You can see my time is almost up. My time's up now? All right.
Oh wait, sorry, I forgot. There's still people here. There's still people here.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Could I get another 25 minute card, please? Yeah, here, over here.
Meet number 42. That's not, that's, that's, I don't know why you played flute at me. I guess
that's a sign of a place when you call the person over to come over and ring you up.
Okay, so I'm over here. I'm over here. Please come over to me.
Thank you. I'm over here. My God, I need, how many? Yeah, thank you. Yes. Yeah, I got, I've,
it's a visa. I'll take one 20 minute. Yeah, I want a 20 minute. Thanks. Actually,
it's a, I want, give me two of those. Yeah, just keep going.
Yeah, maybe grab a 45 minute too. Yep. Another one. Thank you. Thank you. I'll take, that's my,
my card. Let me scratch off the back. Oh, good. This is, this is a 20 minute one. Yeah,
this is what I asked for. Let me just punch the code in real quick. Thank you. Fortnite Jimmy's
dad gave $50. Are you the guy that's harassing my son? Stop playing in that cafe. Oh God,
get out of here. Well, I hate to tell you, Fortnite Jimmy's dad, you could, you didn't have to give me
$50 to say that. Screw, you could have read the, the, the info down there. It was 250 for me to
read that. Okay. I need to relax. I'm going to fucking die. I'm going to pee my pants.
All right. Really? How many, how many fish do I have? Did you lose 600 viewers for that joke?
I don't know. Probably something like that.
They thought the stream was over. That's true. You know, it probably is. I'm going to be
real. It's probably, it probably is. Fortnite Jimmy's dad, another $50, a hundred dollars.
Fortnite Jimmy's dad. I know you heard my car streamer consequences will never be the same.
That's a mean thing. Thank you for the a hundred bucks though. For real. I've been making a lot
of fucking old man noises. Caught any big ones. I did. I need to get some bait. Man, you guys are
fucking hilarious. That happens sometimes. Sometimes a stream will happen where some of
the shit that you guys are doing and saying is it just, it just does it to me and it fucking throws
me off. And you guys are hilarious. Like seriously, I just, yeah, I aged like 30 years in the last 10
minutes. I think this is going to be the end of the fishing trip though. I actually laughed myself
into a migraine. I have a headache now, like a bad one. There's too much stim, like too much
stimulation in my brain. Oh, but yeah. I will see you guys tomorrow. Thanks for joining me.
This stream really, yeah, that, that's, how do you go from here, right? It's been over five hours.
I'm gonna do the bits. It'll probably be about five or six hours. That's, that's, that's good.
I'll be live tomorrow. My goodness. I will see you guys tomorrow for Maximum Action Fishing Planet.
It's a fun, yeah, it's a fun game. It's a solid 6.7. It's, it's fun. It's just, come on. You can
sit here and relax and pretend to be at an internet cafe. Hey, special thanks to Fortnite,
Jimmy. Hope you have a wonderful rest of your in-game time. My time is up right here. I will
actually for real see you tomorrow. Stick around for the bits if you want to. Maximum Action tomorrow
same time, probably around like three-ish p.m., three to four. As always, see you soon. Thank you
for watching. We are going to go back to a little bit earlier. We had 250 from Gnarly.
So when are you going to come visit? I'm available this Friday if you want to come over for lunch.
Uh, for lunch? Sure, yeah, then there's another one from Gnarly. Also, by the way, very excited
for the carnival stream. Thanks for working so hard putting it together. I hope I can watch it live.
I hope you can too. I hope as many people can, that's why I just, like I said, September 21st,
trying to get as much time for people to realize if they can go or if they want to participate or
they're going to be around for it. It's, I believe that's Saturday or Sunday 21st.
Should be a lot of fun, a lot of time, a lot of work is going into it. So I'm as excited as you
for real. Thank you Gnarly for the five dollars. Appreciate it. Uh, Shalashka, thanks for the 250.
You're an actor. Do you have any tips on memorizing something in your own way? The easiest way to
memorize lines is to have somebody else do them with you because instead of just staring at a
paper, you take the paper away and they have the paper and can correct you. It's much more fluid,
it's much more, it's much easier to memorize something when you're not the one staring at
the paper. Then they steal your part. That's not how it works. What is the carnival stream? The
carnival stream is going to be a twitch controlled stream. There are going to be a series of large
robots who chat is going to control to play carnival midway games throughout the day.
On the 21st of September, mark it on your calendar. Should be a lot of fun. Can we physically be at
the carnival? No. No. There's going to be, I thought about like, oh maybe have people there.
When you have something like that with, I'm not saying that anything here is going to be dangerous,
but legally and liability speaking, I don't want anybody that's not part of this production
to be on this set with machines that are able to, with big machines, you know what I'm saying? I
don't want anyone to have any, that's just not something I want to do. Is it going to be free?
Absolutely. It has nothing to do with how dangerous the machines are, but the functions of the
machines. You know, if somebody somehow touches one of them or, because they're going to be
engineers here, that they're responsible for them. I would never want a scenario where somebody,
I don't know, think about any scenario where somebody would touch it or fall onto it or
trip or grab it or try to take a picture with it or something. You know, I just, you got to be
careful and I don't want any of those scenarios to ever be a possibility. How are you controlling
the machines in chat? Good luck. What does it take to get word out that said twitch controlled
stream is going to take place? Well, I've been talking to Twitch and they seemed
seemingly somewhat preliminarily interested in maybe, they're not working on it or anything,
but I went back and forth a couple times with some of the people there to see if they, if
anything wanted to happen from it or if they wanted to do something with it or,
but nobody at Twitch is like working on this project at all. Yeah, something like maybe grab
a front page slot or something possibly, maybe I'm going to see if it's available. That's another
thing. I don't know. We'll see. I can't say that anything like that will or will not happen,
but it might be interesting if it is. How many viewers is it going to get? I have no idea.
That's something that I cannot give you a prediction of. I would say, yeah, I would say
at least four. Hey, deep fried Gundam. Thanks for the 250. They say been stressed out about
my future due to recently graduating college, but your streams always help me relax and
to not lose my shit. Love you, Jermbo, despite your garbage cheese takes.
Garbage cheese takes. I just wish cheese I think is the best. That's what they're referring to.
But no, any time, graduating college is a huge change because it's one of the first times in
your life where you're not sort of in schooling for the most part. Most people that go to college,
you know, you typically do K through 12 and then maybe you take a year maybe,
or maybe you go right into college and it's a huge change. So it is like a big turning point
in a lot of people's lives, right? I mean, when I graduated college, it was, it was kind of scary.
It was because you just, you've never known that before. So, okay, it's time to do something.
And what that is, I don't know. You look around for jobs, you try to find something that you're
good at or that you think is interesting, that you really care about at least a handful of things.
But hopefully over time and over, you know, months, years, whatever it takes,
try to get something going, try to do something.
People usually fall into something somehow. What did I do after college? After college,
I kind of went right into, I'm going to do video stuff. And that's where the wedding video stuff
came from. I just was a freelance video maker. And oh, you, you're a friend. I know a friend
that's getting married. Hey, I'll do your wedding. I can do that. And then that person told a friend
who was getting married and that person told a friend and I kind of worked off of just complete
word of mouth and that was it. I did not have a professional setup. I had a really nice camera
and obviously I had, I thought the skill is necessary to be able to cut stuff like that
up together and people thought they were good. I got a lot of good comments of, hey, that was
really well put together. Thank you. We, we loved it, you know, whatever. And you just
work off of that. That's kind of what I did for at least a couple of years.
And I also substitute taught. I was like a substitute teacher. I did teacher's aid stuff.
Teacher noise. Yeah. I was, I was kind of all over the place until I really started to put,
because when I started that YouTube channel, it was just, I just did it because I thought it was
fun. That was it. I didn't really have very many expectations on it. And that's kind of how I've
kind of fallen into this is just kind of just keep going. It just worked out. If I did not,
if I was not a streamer or a YouTuber or anything, if I wasn't doing this and putting all the time
into it, I probably would have continued to do, I probably would have gone into education. I
probably would have. And I know like that, I know, hold on, you would be a teacher.
I don't know. I think about that. I really like computers. I really like games. I really like
talking to people. It would be some, I would find something to do even being in just in a,
like a school system or something. Right. I probably would have fallen into that somehow
or customer service because I remember we talked about the fishing trip. I just,
I just talk. But thank you Tingy for the 250. Since you're talking about streaming stats,
I want to bring to your attention that you are no longer a top 1000 streamer.
What do you mean? You are a top 500 streamer. What are you talking about? Top 500?
Twitchmetrics.net. That for real? These real stats? 400, number 400. Hold on a minute.
Number 447 most watched. That's top 500. Number 42 most watched English variety channel.
Guys, that can't be correct. That's top 50. What? This is not like a, like a edit source,
right? Like this is a real website, right? You did, you're not just like giving me like an
edit source with a thing. No, no, but that's on my end. All right. Let's go. Top 500. Damn. All
right. I'm going to, I can't wait to tell my mom. No, I don't, I don't get there without people
that watch this channel. This is you guys, not me. See if we can break top 100. We'll see. I don't
know about that. But anyways, yeah, no, thanks. Thanks for watching. Thanks for being here. Thanks
for getting this channel even in like, even the top thousand, top 5,000, top 2,000. That's
still a fucking huge deal. That's a big deal to me and a big deal to this community. So for real,
peak viewers, I believe that's just for the month. Yeah. If I was a day, you'd be number one.
That would be impossible. But yeah, thanks. We'll check back in on it in another six months. See
where it is. Lewis Cheese, $10 from Lewis Cheese. Thanks for waking me up and for the new alarm
sound. You're welcome. Whatever you woke up for, hopefully you got it done. Whatever it was. Thank
you for the 10 bucks and good morning. Hey, Lobotomized Teddy Bear, thanks for the 250. Here
is a stream idea relating to fish. Eat Fugu puffer fish, but you have to cut it and eat it on stream.
You have to cut it and eat it on stream. It's a great idea. Nothing could go wrong.
No, I don't care if it's honestly, I would never eat that even if it was prepared by the most
talented chef in the world. I would not do a mini F. That's 58 drop frames in five and a half hours.
It's pretty good. I think we're back to normal. Yeah, great. Great stream idea. What's the next
one? Hey, I got a great stream idea. Roll around in cactuses. It'd be fun. I think I will abstain,
but thank you for the 250. Thank you Gnarly for the 250 again. How come whenever you do an
impression of someone, you start by saying, let me tell you something. Is it a voice acting technique
or just a habit? I don't know. They call those cadences. I guess that's one of mine.
Mannerisms, cadences. Let me tell you something. Hey, let me tell you something. Yeah, you're right.
Hey, let me tell you something. I think what that is, it's a way to tell the audience,
here comes a joke in my somewhere without me even being aware of it.
Maybe. Or it's a this is somebody else talking. Minus two incoming. Probably something like that.
Hey, feel 64. Thanks for the five dollars. I am glad you like fishing planet. It was fun playing
with you. Thanks for the recommendation. I did do the one guy in chat. It turned out to be a very,
very fun stream. So thank you. Feel 64 for the five dollars. The game is fun. It is.
Phylacter Lich gave $9.11. Sir, I'm going to need you to see how many fish you have.
Well, what do we have here? Someone's going to streamer jail. Oh, okay. I get it.
Thank you, Phylacter. And thank you for the 420, the four subs and then 20 subs,
community subs earlier. Thank you. Invader Z. Thanks for the 250. Hi, German. I was wondering
if you chose the carnival to be on the 21st because you sang the song September poorly once
or is that a coincidence? There's a 100% coincidence. Just happens to be on the same
date of my favorite song ever. I mean, it was just a coincidence. Thanks for the 250. Stinky
Beavers. Thanks for the 250. Hey, everybody. German here and welcome to a coffee commentary
of Justice in Doom. I remember those. I remember thinking that the ironic, like,
doom thing. I was doing like the ironic, like of doom thing. I don't think anyone
knew that. I think I just thought I was actually saying that, but I was.
You guys know what I mean. Like, oh, it's me of doom. Ha ha. It was like a meme for a while.
Yeah, yes. The Penguin of Doom, right? That was a meme for like a while, like 10 years ago.
Yeah, that's an old one. Surprising how more of you guys know what that is.
But thank you for the 250. Hey, Smelly Boy. Thanks for the 250, Smelly Boy. Put Fortnite
Jimmy in the next germ rumble. He deserves it. FlyingPixels. Thanks for those five community
subs earlier. I'm not sure I got them. Techno Rift. Thanks for the $14. Thank you, Techno Rift.
This has honestly been one of the most entertaining streams you've had in a while,
from the fishing escapades to the father-son fishing bonding experience.
Oh, I also got all these bits from watching like 500 ads for the last few months. Keep up the good
work. Well, I thank you for giving those to me. That seems like a lot of time spent watching ads.
Thanks for the $14. Really appreciate that. And it was a fun one. I had a great time. This was a
very, very fun stream for me. Thank you C4G for the 250. My girlfriend is watching this stream on
their PS4. And you were so audibly upset when you accidentally DM'd Jimmy again,
that someone came in to check if they were okay. Wait, what? Wait, they thought that they were in
there going like, no, I don't want to play. Jesus. Like, the person's being like beat up.
Oh, I don't want to, I don't want to type it. I don't want to type to that person.
It's like, is everything all right in here? Like, is there like a swarm of bees in your room?
What's going on? Oh, there's a wasp in your room. There's always a wasp in my room. But thank you
C4G for the 250. Everything's fun. Everything's good. Hey, Squibble, thanks for the $5. This is
probably the most activity fishing planet has ever seen. Thanks for the stream, dude.
Maybe somebody can play it and we'll like, yeah, this is actually a pretty fun little game.
Whatever, play it. It's just a game, all right, to play. That's a message from the dem.
But thank you, Squibble. I'm going to get the credits on the screen. We're going to get to the
end of the bits. Here they come. Special thanks to all of the new subs, the resubs, the community
subs, all of you. See y'all tomorrow for maximum action. That one's going to be a gamer stream.
So yesterday was like an on-camera like dickhead stream. Today was a relaxing fishing stream.
Tomorrow is going to be a gamer stream because that's a skill-based video game.
This was relaxing. I was relaxed. You can't tell me the first four hours of the stream wasn't just
hanging out and relaxing. It was. We talked about cheese. We talked about prosciutto.
That's all I remember. We had four and a half plus hours of conversations on this stream and
I only remember that somebody told me that I was wrong when I say the prosciutto is raw or something.
That's all I remember. Talked about the MCU and Far From Home is the best Spider-Man movie.
I remember writing that in the true true true true true true true true true true true true true.
That's all I saw over in the chat. But thank you everybody. Thank you snoozingcopter for the 250.
Oh my god Jeremy. I finally found you. Remember me? We were fishing together but then I got
separated from the group and fell into the pond and couldn't get out. I screamed for help but
nobody heard me. This game was more fun than I remember by the way. I feel like it's fun
just to open and play a game for a while. Yeah that's what I'm saying. Yeah that's right snoozingcopter.
Thanks for the 250. If I liked your elixir thanks for the five dollars. That was one bad mad dad.
Thank you. Thank you Sergio but for the 250 to be honest. Oh so no so be honest. Did you choose the
21st night of September intentionally for the carnival stream? I'm being honest it was I didn't
even pick that date. I gave a range of time and we sort of went back and forth on when it would be
and the 21st turned out to be the best day for everybody. So yes by coincidence.
Hey orange power thanks for the ten dollars orange power. Ten bucks. Hey Jeremy I've lived in Texas
all my life and I'm actually transferring to a college in New York for my sophomore year. I'm
actually really nervous about being in such a different environment from the one I've been in
all my life but your streams always give me the break I need. Keep it up. You keep it up as well.
That's a big change. I've never really been in New York for very long but the times that
I have spent there it's a pretty interesting place. A lot of cool stuff to do. A lot of cool
stuff to see in New York especially New York City. Not sure exactly where you'll be in New York
but good luck. I'm sure you do just fine. True Bostonian. He's never been to New York.
I have a few times. I have. I've been to Times Square but thank you orange power. Whatever you're
doing. Whatever college you're going to. Keep it up as you said to me. Finally Wolfgang 6789 gave
five community subs a few minutes ago. Thank you Wolfgang. And the last bit message of the night
250 from Colusia. Colusia thanks for the cozy stream. Now I can sleep peacefully. Have a great
night. Good night. Apologize to my cat who you terrified. I'm really sorry to Dubsky dude's
cat and whoever I scared from the werewolf. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Have a great night.
Take care. Talk soon. Like tomorrow.