Hello? Hello? Sorry, I'm late. Very late.
I had fucking car trouble. I had trouble with the car.
Oh, okay, okay. Therefore, all of your- all of your crimes are resolved.
Okay, all of the- that's fine. Yeah, I know what that's like.
Dude, what the fuck? It's my sister's birthday. You're here an hour late?
We've already did the cake and the candles and shit.
I had fucking trouble with the car, dude. I had car trouble.
Oh, yeah, all right. All right, man. Man, do you need anything?
You want water? You want like a soda or something? Are you good?
Yeah, I'm good.
It's time to play Destiny 2. Never gonna play Destiny 2.
Mark that and put a stamp on it.
I'm sorry, I have to tell you, I'm never gonna play that game. Ever.
Ever. I'm sorry, and I'm gonna make somebody really upset by saying that
I'm never going to play Destiny 2.
Now, about a year or two ago, if you had said,
Hey, Smite Thursdays, I would have said the same exact sentence.
I'm never gonna play fucking Smite on stream. Why the hell would I do that?
But here we are. So never listen to anything I say.
Everything I say is wrong. Incorrect. Did I tweet this? I did.
I figured, I don't know. I've played it recently. I think it's fun.
Somebody in chat, people in chat were saying to play it and I was like,
All right, yeah, let's do Smite Thursdays.
It's obviously subject to change, as per our agreement.
You know, Smite Thursdays may be on Friday, Saturday, Monday or Tuesday.
Smite Thursdays also might never come back ever again.
Depending on community sentiment.
But yes, Smite Thursdays.
Oh, but Andy. I was waiting to see what people were gonna do about this.
I wonder if this is gonna be the most toxic chat in 2021.
Stop being so toxic, okay? I wanted to play this game, so I'm playing it.
Isn't that what you what I'm supposed to be doing as a live streamer?
I want to do something, so I'm gonna do it.
And that's exactly what I'm gonna do. You understand?
Karma hates mods. What happened? What'd I do?
Oh, I'm sorry. Right. This stream.
This stream is me hating mods. That's right. Sorry.
What's your favorite class? Oh, I mean, I got a few.
But I have really bad performance anxiety whenever I play something like this.
Hearthstone's a really good example.
I have come in first place in Battlegrounds, I believe over like 150 times.
I was at my rank was like five or six thousand last season.
If I were to turn that on right now, I would be like, I don't know what to do.
I don't know. I would fuck up everything.
You guys watched it. You guys saw me do that.
Like, I could actually play that game, but I can't in front of people.
Off camera? I can play this game pretty well.
I wouldn't say very well, but pretty well.
I'm gonna forget what the buttons are.
I don't know why this happens to me. I don't understand it.
I haven't played Hearthstone in probably three or four months, maybe five months.
Not since the last Battlegrounds season.
Use an Xbox controller. No, I play on PC.
I'm playing on the computer.
Nobody wants to see you play Smite. Nobody.
Well, I'm sorry, but there's at least 10 people in pre-stream chat
that have been saying play Smite every pre-stream for the last six years.
So there are people that want to see it. I know them.
Smite Tuber.
Well, I think we can get started.
We can play. I want to make sure I can see things, though.
Hold on just a moment.
Where's my info? Where's my info?
There it is.
Because it's been a while, I do want to make sure that I get my brain
recombobulated into the world of Smite.
And what better way to do that than to watch a tutorial on a god tutorial, potentially?
I know there's a lot of them that exist.
I found one.
I'm really into the god Anubis.
I think it's a cool god, but I haven't played it in a while.
So I looked up a guide and I'm just going to try to get back into this world here.
Let's go ahead and watch it.
Just to refresh my memory, it's been a while.
Hey, what is going on, everybody?
Jerma here with Smite Sunday.
Welcome to the first Smite Sunday on this channel.
Wait, what?
Where I break down a god or I show you a good gameplay and talk about it potentially.
What?
Or I do a live commentary.
But today is going to be a god breakdown.
I don't know, it's Smite Thursday.
All right, I'm going to be quiet.
The god of the dead.
And the reason why I'm picking Anubis first to do sort of a god breakdown and sort of small
tutorial video is because Anubis is one of those characters in this game
that he's not a free god.
He's not one of the free gods.
When you install the same joke, this wasn't a joke.
I actually did this for like three weeks completely incorrectly.
I was one of these people that I first downloaded this game.
I said, oh my God, Anubis, the god of the dead.
Oh my God, I get this guy.
I got to play with him and see.
He's so cool.
And I would just get trashed on.
And that's because Anubis is one of the most damaging gods in the game,
but he also dies incredibly easily and incredibly quickly.
So I figured because of my early struggles with Anubis,
I figured it would be a good one to start with.
Anubis, the god of the dead, the Egyptian lord of destruction.
What happened to your sexy voice?
I stopped trying so hard.
So instead of reading off of the wiki page and telling you all the damage numbers,
which are very, very easy to find on the internet,
I'm just going to tell you what the moves do and when you should be utilizing them.
What do the moves do?
How do I do that?
Not using them in different situations.
So we're going to talk about his number one,
which is Plague of Locus.
It's on the one key skill key number one.
And upon activation, Anubis will stand still and launch out a bunch of bugs at people in a cone.
Kind of disgusting.
It lasts for three seconds.
This didn't exist back then, guys.
So when should you use this move?
Now, I would typically say that this should be part of this smite beta from 2013.
I'll get into that in a few minutes.
But they didn't have half the features that are in the game.
Although it does a ton of damage, you won't really be using this early game.
And here's why.
Anubis does not have any escapes.
And if you don't know what an escape is in this game, it's a jump.
It's a dash.
Why is he so normal?
It's really any way to distance yourself from another god or from another player.
So trying to utilize a move like this, when you have to stand completely still,
you're just going to get destroyed behind the other lane.
What about Dexter?
Like, was he pretending to be a normal guy?
In a situation like this, you were level one, level two,
would have been a very, very, very early game.
You're up in the lane with a buddy of yours, you're playing Conquest.
And you have this move, you go up and you use it on a minion wave.
And you're standing still, the other team sees you.
They know you're Anubis.
They know you cannot get away.
So they jump on top of you.
You got to play it safe.
And standing still up at level two in a minion wave.
I can't watch this anymore.
This is a lot.
Seven more minutes in this video.
Seven.
You need to use your three early game for Anubis, I would say.
But we'll get into that when we get to that.
Also, that kind of leads me to another point.
Oh, that was a good grab.
That was a good grab.
Standing still is bad.
It's very bad.
If you stand still and do it at times two speed, fine.
This game, because everything is a skillshot.
Well, most of the things in this game are skillshots.
There's so many stuns, there's so many slows.
There's so many people that will be able to hit you with all of their moves.
You don't want to be standing still.
So that's another reason why the number one is not the best choice early.
So moving on, let's talk about his two, which is arguably his best move.
And that move is called Mummify.
And basically, this is just a stun that you can do very, very frequently.
And it wraps up anybody you hit with it for a maximum of two seconds.
This is an offensive and defensive move.
This is just like when your buddy is explaining the game to you, and they're really happy,
and they really, really badly want you to download it.
This is what I hear.
Move and it slows people, you can get a lot more utility out of this.
You don't have to stand still to use it and a little bit better in team composition situations
where Ben Shapiro because of the slow before I go on any further.
Talk about his number four is ultimate.
We're going to talk about what I said previously, and it is the non ultimate combo.
This is really what you should be trying to accomplish when your ultimate ability is on
cooldown and you instantly place your grasping hands underneath them.
And while they're still wrapped up getting them in the cone of your locust swarm, you
do one instantly as well.
You're close enough.
That's assuming you're close enough.
It takes some practice, but late game, you can really instantly kill people with this.
I got to turn it off.
It's too much.
You can just place your three mummify.
Let's see what it is in slow mo 720p.
What year is it?
That's one of the best things to do as a new person.
Hey, those of you guys that have heard me do this before where I go,
I don't want and people give me question marks.
Listen up.
And one of the things about this is if you do not kill the person,
let's say you do this, this non ultimate combo, you wrap the person up, bang, bang,
do both those moves and you don't kill them.
It really is a drunk person.
There ain't a whole lot left for you to do besides turn around and run away
or try to auto attack them to death.
I should have just uploaded the video like this.
I feel like more people would have liked it and remembered it more fondly.
Finally, we're going to talk about his ultimate ability,
which is very, very self-explanatory.
I'm not going to spend that much time.
All right.
We're not going to spend any time actually.
I'm going to skip.
So you can put people in a very, very large false sense of security landing your two.
You're in the jungle and you got like an area here, guys.
I think I've covered most of the things I want to cover with an Anubis.
And the next God will probably be Ares for Smite Sunday.
I'm going to break down Ares.
I'm going to talk about why he's my favorite God in the game.
Yes, Ares is my favorite God in the game at this point.
It used to be an Anubis that used to be Loki, but now it is Ares.
And we're going to talk about him next week.
Going to break down his moves, going to break down how I play him
and some of the things you should be doing as Ares.
And that's going to be next Smite Sunday.
So thanks for tuning in, guys.
I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.
I did that two more times and never did it again.
It was the lowest viewed thing I ever made on my channel.
Everybody, nobody watched it.
I did it two more times.
I was, in my mind, I was going to do every single God in the game
and Smite was going to be a new secondary game next to Team Fortress.
It was like, holy shit, man.
I'm going to have like TF2 and I'll have like Smite content.
I'll be like a TF2 Smite guy.
I made three videos on it and it was like I'm never doing that again.
Nobody liked it.
Everybody, nobody watched it.
So, yeah, I think I know how to play Anubis now.
Okay, cool.
Where's the audio?
Uh, yeah, Ares, this is, um, yeah, what the fuck?
The Smite guy is back.
Yeah, I'm back.
I took a, I took a seven-year vacation.
I'm back, eight-year vacation.
Now I'm the sus guy.
I never was the sus guy.
That implies that I made Among Us videos.
I didn't.
Uh, so here's one thing you need to know about Smite.
There's only one thing you have to really know.
And that is, uh, they, they added, um, they added Ninja Turtles.
All the Ninja Turtles are in the game.
And, um, Airbender is in this game, too.
Legend of Airbender?
What's the fucking goddamn name of that show?
Can I, don't tell me what it is.
Oh, shit.
Hold on.
Aang, the last Airbender?
Avatar, the last Airbun-bun.
Avatar, the last Bundy.
It's Al Bundy's son.
Uh, I, hold on.
I have to, I have to shut this off for a second.
Because I have to figure out how to fucking make it so nobody can, like.
I have an invite.
Oh, what the fuck did I, what have I done?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hold on a minute.
I thought I did this.
What the fuck?
No, stop friend requesting me.
How do I turn this off?
Stop it.
No, I don't know how to turn this off.
Oh.
Can I not turn this off?
Am I gonna get, like, where is it?
Profile.
Private profile.
Account.
Private.
How do I do this?
Somebody please tell me how to do this.
How do I do it?
How do I actually do this?
I can't find it.
Turn it off?
From a new house flipper DLC.
No, that's not what I asked.
How do I, what, how do I turn this off?
Write slash DND in chat.
How you doing?
Am I being lied to?
You're now in DND.
But how do I make it so people can't do that?
What the fuck?
Option settings, privacy profile, sus.
Fuck.
God damn it.
Why did I read that?
All right.
You guys ready?
Put a sensor bar over your name.
It's, I don't, I made a new account specifically
because I knew that was gonna happen.
Go to view.
Somebody's got it.
Go to view friends and click the little down arrow
and press do not disturb.
Can I, can I, like, make myself private?
All right.
I'm just gonna get, you know what?
I'm just gonna, I gotta practice.
I gotta practice.
Profile bar in the top right corner.
I don't want you to fucking see this shit.
Oh, I got a Royale coming my way.
That was my Fortnite name.
Okay.
Um, I think I did it.
I think I'm fine.
Whatever.
Yeah, I was gonna play Fortnite for like an hour
and I was like, that's a fun name.
All right, play.
You guys ready?
I just gotta, I gotta get back in the swing of things.
I gotta adjust my chair too.
This is a chill stream.
I wanna chill and play this game.
I'm only level five so I can't do anything interesting.
Go to profile and click delete.
All right.
So this is like the ultimate stream sniper game
because it's just a countdown and when it gets to zero,
it just takes a pool of the people there.
So like, I can't.
I was gonna pre-record myself clicking this and waiting
and then just like, like I didn't Hearthstone that time
but I ran out of time.
So like, how do I make it so the least amount of people
can like, can spawn camp me?
Turn on streamer mode.
There's a streamer mode?
Where's the streamer mode?
What?
Did I not turn this on?
Where is it?
It's in the settings?
No, you fucking liars.
There's no way it's in here.
Look at the goddamn options.
Holy shit.
I already did.
Settings.
Spectator.
Friendly team.
Key bindings.
Interface.
Options, profile, privacy, streamer mode.
Options, profile, privacy mode.
Options, profile, profile, privacy mode.
That's not here.
Privacy mode.
This is a lie.
I'm just fucking queuing up.
I don't even care.
And I look, I'm not gonna tell you guys when I queue up.
No one's gonna fucking know when I do that.
I'm not gonna tell you what I queued up for either.
Well, look at that.
How does that sound?
I could have queued up for anything.
What am I gonna, what am I playing?
Who knows?
Windows G.
That's like the Windows gamer mode.
That's not accurate.
Oh, it's a Windows G.
By the way, I'm gonna show you guys.
Hey, hey, queues up.
Okay, queues up.
This is the point where everybody that you know
that plays this game fucking sprints to the bathroom
after hitting accept.
You can like hear them over the microphone.
Just like, okay, queues up.
I don't want you guys to know what I did.
All right, here we go.
What did I pay?
All right, who do I want to play with first?
This is like, it's a warm-up game.
This is, this is arena.
Audio is really fucking low.
Who should I play with?
The frog?
That's a skin, man.
That's like a $20 skin or something.
I don't have that.
Random?
No, I can't do that.
I don't know how half these guys even work.
I've played like seven characters.
No, we're, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I know how to play.
We need a fucking guardian is what we need.
Oh, we got one.
All right.
Should I play?
All right, we got, we got magic, magic, physical, physical.
We're good.
No, this is good.
I'm not, I don't know.
Anubis?
All right, yeah, because he asked.
Yeah, and I bought the skin even on the,
I bought a skin even on my dummy account, which is this one.
I bought two skins.
I love this character.
All right, do you guys want Stargazer or the Senko Sage?
Which one?
I need a few warm-up games.
All right, I've seen a lot of sages.
Boy, I got boosters.
Okay, everybody gets a voice pack.
I'm on it.
You got a furry skin.
Every character has a furry skin, okay?
Half the characters in this game are furries.
So what's wrong with you?
All right, we got, we got a level 10 Thanatos on the other team.
This is bad.
This is, this is one of you guys, isn't it?
You knew I was going to pick Anubis,
so you're just going to execute me over and over again.
All right, I got, I got to prove that I could play video games.
All right, let me prove it.
Okay.
One thing that I noticed, did they, did they delete boots from the game?
I remember you used to buy boots.
Did they fucking delete it?
Where is it?
So you're telling me that eight years later, they removed boots from the game.
So what do they, is it, is it, do you, does everybody run the same speed?
No, I don't understand how that works.
All right, let me just fucking get my, oh, that's, I'm ready.
That's all I need to do.
Okay, so I have, this is arena.
And in arena, what you want to try to do, it's very important,
is stick together with your team.
One thing people do all the time in Smite is they break up too frequently.
These are the damage buffs over here.
Well, they're not, they're not all damage buffs.
Look at this guy over here.
Hi, my name is Ra.
Yeah, he's funny.
He's a funny character.
But you, you, you don't want to break up too much.
Be careful, stick together and utilize your abilities as a team.
Oh, what's that?
Oh, somebody got you.
As you see, what I did there is, I'm going to kill this meat.
Kill stealer.
Go away from me.
What are you, are we a watcher?
Are you a sniper?
Are you stream sniping me?
Is this main channel material?
It is not.
All right.
What do I want to do?
Well, I want to cool down.
Chrono spin.
Let's go.
I did, oh, he doesn't finish, it doesn't finish item Andy.
Relax.
I got it.
Let's go.
All it takes is a minute and I get the fire.
I get it again.
Just give me a minute.
That's all I need.
Where are they going?
Oh, that's Tinnitus.
That's Tinnitus.
Help me.
Somebody help me.
Oh, that was pretty good bait.
I'm good.
Where your mic is on?
What are you talking about?
Speaking of killing sprees, we've got one coming up.
My mic is on?
To be honest, I don't think anyone's surprised.
Mike.
Where?
Are you Mike?
Turn your mic off?
I don't have it.
What do you mean my mic?
What shit is off?
No, you're talking about it.
Oh, you.
Okay.
I see what you're doing.
You're talking about like you guys are in the game and I'm an annoying guy.
Okay.
I get it.
All right.
You guys stop fucking with me.
I would have killed that guy.
Stop fucking with me.
I'm in arena.
What did that guy say?
You should stick to arena.
I'm playing arena right now.
All right.
I'm going to be quiet.
Jump.
There it is.
It's Mike Pro League.
Here we go.
I have no, we're just playing for fun.
This is a fun game, Andy.
Okay.
You want to see me jungle?
We're going to do custom games, right?
If you want to see an absolute disaster, then you put me in the jungle,
but I need some pros on my team.
I need some people that really know what the fuck they're doing.
Oh shit.
Stop talking.
Okay.
I gotta stop talking.
All right.
I guess this is why I can't play games like this and scream.
I can't, I just talk and my brain doesn't play the game.
All right.
Quiet.
I get into like autopilot mode whenever I start talking.
I don't have two hemispheres in my brain.
I have one.
It's just one gigantic circle.
Get her.
Careful.
Hey.
Fuck.
I missed.
I'm so sorry.
I was trying to make a joke and I missed.
Oh, I hit the wrong button.
Shit.
Oh, give me that triple.
Oh, yeah.
You, you're a viewer.
I don't get out of here.
Remember everybody that's good that hurts me is a viewer.
Doesn't matter.
Ice.
Oh, come on.
Fuck that.
Where should I be?
No, stand in the way.
I got it.
All right.
Done that.
What the fuck happened?
What's going on?
What the fuck just happened?
What's the range on that motherfucker?
What?
I don't think anyone's surprised.
Trips for days.
A gift from my most loyal observers.
I must go all out.
Ego.
And that guy.
Oh.
Oh, let's use speed.
I know it's the worst thing in the game, but I don't care.
All right.
Who do I want to grab here?
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
This is where it's time to shine.
Time to shine.
This is where a new...
This is truly where a newbie shines.
We're still in this.
I don't know.
I just...
I hit four.
Why did it not go off?
What the fuck?
Hello?
Excuse me.
Why...
I'm pressing button.
What the fuck is happening?
What?
What is going on?
Yeah.
What the fuck?
I was pressing buttons and it didn't do anything.
That was weird.
All right.
Here we go.
You got silenced?
No, no, no.
It was after that.
They added silences to the game.
Oh, now it's...
Now it's really gone.
Completely off the rails.
No, no.
I'm not...
I don't like it anymore.
Your mic is on.
Stop.
All right.
I need to pay attention because when I pay attention,
that's when shit happens.
Ready?
I'll show you.
After that.
There's too many people on the team that are good.
Oops.
I just completely missed.
This is warm.
It's the first game I've played in like three years.
Relax.
I'm already running fast.
Wait, that was an enemy, wasn't it?
Why would I play Anubis like for the first game on stream?
He like sucks.
Why would I play this guy?
No.
Shut up.
He's good.
He's my favorite character.
Your only tank is AFK?
Oh, shit.
Oh, well.
Anyway, you're in Anubis main.
Now, I do the thing that we all do when we play games like this.
Like, you know what?
I love this character.
It's like my favorite character.
They're super fun.
They're super cool.
But anytime you lose with this kind of character,
it's like, oh, no, no, no, no, no.
This character is a low tier garbage character.
And like, why do I play this character?
Oh, I don't play fucking Thor, right?
No, I play Anubis because he's like a C kind of D tier character.
He's awesome, man.
It's like I'm like different.
I play the game like differently than everybody else.
I don't play the meta.
And then when you lose with this character,
this character sucks.
And the only reason why you are losing is with this character
because this is a bad character.
And I've chosen to play it because I want to look like different.
That's what I do.
And you all do it, too.
Don't lie to me.
I'm actually not really doing that poorly.
Jerma is just built different.
And now I left the game.
Oh, this is low MMR, right?
In low MMR games and in every one of these MOBAs,
people just leave.
I forgot this low MMR arena.
What do I expect?
Oh, get him.
Nice gag game.
Now play Deathloop.
I'm having fun.
Let me have fun.
Okay.
Wait, watch out for the big guy.
Play House Flipper?
I don't want to play House Flipper.
I don't want to drink the same coffee every day.
I want a different coffee.
Sometimes you want a hot coffee.
Sometimes you want a cold coffee.
Sometimes you fucking get a guaranteed kill.
Maybe even two of them.
I mean, it's my favorite character for sure.
Yeah, more than two to one Katie.
Yeah, this is my favorite character in the game.
Yeah, I mean, this is a really good character to be trying to play.
What does that mean?
What the fuck does that mean?
Why is every character talking?
No, I have to turn that off.
I have like a voice pack on.
There's a Thanatos execution.
Is that what that was?
I don't know.
I freaked out.
Thanatos does so much damage.
I probably could have gotten really embarrassed if I didn't do that.
Get it.
Dude, what's going on here?
We're down a player, right?
It's a skin.
Okay, I see.
All right.
What are we doing here?
Run.
Do you look up builds?
No, I'm not playing Conquest or anything.
I'm just playing for fun.
You play Metroid Dread?
I don't think so.
Nice.
Good job.
Excellent work.
Oh, this is how we get it.
This is how we bring it back.
Let's bring this shit back right now.
First game win.
Come on.
Even with down a player, we can do it.
Yeah, let's do it.
Come on.
Speaking of killing sprees.
We've got just like my hopes and dreams.
They're all.
I got that kind of money.
I got it back.
Let's use the opinion of Sora and Smash corporate.
Did somebody report that guy from my most loyal worshipers?
Okay, let's go.
Wait.
Oh, you bastard.
Why did I do that?
That was so stupid.
I just got so greedy.
I was obsessed.
What was wrong with me?
Anubis is the easiest at far away range.
Anubis is so easy to dodge.
All right, we're going to win.
We're going to take this back right now.
Hey, defensive.
Defense.
Let them come to us.
We win four more team fights and nobody dies.
We win.
There was a type of guy to put to pee in the sink.
Only in an emergency.
Defense.
Get him away from us.
One ticker left.
It's over.
Sorry.
I don't care.
We're guaranteed to lose.
Who cares?
All right.
You don't change topics.
What was the topic?
Appealing.
All right.
Nice.
Good job.
We were down a player.
Level 14.
I was like what?
Oh, shit.
Okay, let's play again.
Toxic streamer.
Wait, I said only in an emergency.
I don't know.
I said the first thing that came to my head.
Are you going to play Diablo 2?
I'm not going to play Diablo 2 on stream.
That is a me game.
Only for me.
Oh, turn the announcer off.
Right.
How do I do that?
It's in my like loadout, right?
Profile.
What is it?
Is it in the God screen?
Where is half of this shit?
Look at all these.
Oh, my God.
Jesus Christ.
Wizard 101.
No, don't press.
I press.
Fuck.
I was trying to like hide.
No.
I did it too late.
Oh, God damn it.
I was trying to hide that.
I'm so stupid.
How do I turn this guy?
Loadout.
There it is.
Okay.
Announcer pack.
Turn it off.
Okay.
Got it.
Toxic waste mask.
I don't want to do any of this.
Wait.
Okay.
I was trying to hide the game.
We want Toon Town.
I can't get Toon Town to run.
I already streamed Wizard 101.
What are you talking about?
I streamed Wizard 101 like three or four years ago.
Whatever.
If you're going to stream Snipe Me,
you're going to stream Snipe Me.
You have to have like a two MMR to get into these games.
That was part of the point.
You have 10k viewers on Smite.
That's cool.
Yeah.
You know, look.
I'm just hanging out just having fun.
If you find this stream to be not to your liking,
then you don't have to stick around.
But there's a lot of people here.
What's up?
We're going to do viewer games later.
We're going to do some like comedy games.
I promise.
All right.
Who should I play with?
Well, we got Hunter.
Brawler.
So we have Warrior.
All right.
We have physical, physical.
I got to be a guardian.
I can be anything.
Be anything I want.
Play somebody on the bottom three.
Like Cthulhu.
I don't know.
I don't know that character's moves.
All right.
I got to make a choice.
We got magic, magic.
Physical, physical.
Jormungandr is a tank.
So maybe I should play Cthulhu.
I don't know how to play Cthulhu.
How about Amazenkab?
Amazenkab.
I think that's what I'm feeling right now.
Double Hunter.
I'm just going to spam Machine Gun.
That's the one.
This actually was my favorite character back when I played a lot.
Literally nobody wanted this.
Look.
Do you understand?
Okay.
There's 10,000 people here.
If I asked all 10,000 of you what your favorite ice cream was,
you're all going to have different favorite ice creams.
Some of you are going to say chocolate.
Some of you are going to say vanilla.
Some of you are going to say strawberries.
Some of you are going to say like cookies and cream.
Everybody has things they like.
It's hard to agree on exactly what game everyone wants to see.
And then maybe you like all ice creams.
Maybe you only like a few.
Maybe you like frozen yogurt.
Maybe you don't even want ice cream.
Are you a hard ice cream or a soft ice cream?
Soft serve.
A lot of different opinions here.
That was a very long-winded way to say time that person out for 20 minutes.
Okay.
Here we go.
Now make it two.
Make it 10.
Make it 10 seconds.
Wait.
I need a relic.
What the fuck was that?
Why is a cookie monster in my game?
What's going on?
Fuck.
I need to buy one of these.
This is cool.
If you don't know about Amazenkab, he's the god of bees.
He plays hives.
They give you attack speed, movement speed, and I believe mana per five.
He also has a bee swarm, which is his second ability, which swarms.
He's got sticky honey goo, which is a slow and it's trail.
And his ultimate is the stinger.
And if you get it in somebody, you get to pick it up and do it again.
But the way you should be playing Amazenkab is strictly auto attacks only
and build a shitload of attack speed.
Oh, this is it right here.
Baby, come on.
This is it.
This is the one.
Thank you.
I'll pick that back up.
And the cooldown is only 15 seconds rather than 80.
Did I get that kill?
Somebody stole it from me, but that's fine.
I have this opinion if you are.
I get him.
If you complain about kill stealing in arena.
All right.
Don't be cocky.
Don't be an idiot.
Bop.
Who is the cookie monster?
This is one of the most boring gods in the game.
Yes.
But if you take boring and remove it and put like put white out over it
and then write effective on it, it's essentially saying the same thing.
Aren't you?
Oops, that was the wrong item.
Oh, that's all right.
He's very effective.
Yeah, sure.
Just going boom, boom, boom, boom.
That's like boring.
You don't have to like, you know, there's no jump.
Did I just hit a fucking minion with that?
I just hit a fucking minion with my ultimate, of course.
It's awful.
Does it go through minions?
I don't remember.
Nice.
Don't get cocky.
Come on.
Back it up.
Let him have fun.
Oh, thanks, guys.
Just body blocked.
I'm sorry.
Oh, three in a row.
Let me get it.
Let him have fun.
I'm just trying to have fun, right?
It was no plan with this stream.
I just it was a joke in pre stream chat like three days ago.
But now it's not a joke because guess what?
I hate when people do that.
Now it's not.
You know what?
You know what I'm saying?
It's not a joke because I'm having a good time.
If the god is alerted to bees, do they take more damage?
No, it's not.
This game is not fucking realistic.
It sucks.
All I ask for is a little bit of realism.
Like actual like bullet damage and like cut damage and stuff.
And actual like body damage to the cars and stuff like that.
That's not bad.
All right.
Yeah.
Put him right.
Put him in the tower.
Good.
What are they doing over here?
Why are you doing all this, man?
Fuck.
Don't let her kill me.
That's not based of you.
Worst stream of 2020.
That is a game.
All right.
A gaming stream.
I'm just playing a game.
Well, I can't play a game on stream.
And I've been playing a game poorly.
I'm 4 and 0.
Excuse me.
Are we going to calculate stream poor like levels of poor quality based on video game playing?
Keep it up.
Yeah, I actually really like that character.
Um, wow.
This gives me nostalgia to the old smite videos.
I actually really enjoyed this game a lot.
Used to play this game.
Oh, yeah.
Back in the like technical alpha.
Whatever it was.
I played this game all the time.
Uh, I don't you know, it's funny.
I only pick these three.
I don't even know what the other items even do.
In the years that I've played this game, I've never scrolled over them.
Back in the MLC stealth days.
Yeah, you wanted something crazy.
I mean, maybe some of the newer um, newer viewers might not know this.
Uh, so I had a friend.
We used to make videos and shit all the time.
MLC stealth.
The guy and his team.
They were all really good at the game.
They won two and a half million fucking dollars playing this game.
During like the first smite world championship.
I remember watching it.
It was insane.
That's the only time that I really ever cared about esports stuff.
Really, to be honest.
It was just like, oh my god.
This guy's gonna, this team is gonna win fucking millions.
Got him.
That's pocket change.
What planet are you from?
What?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
All right.
Group up.
See those auto attacks?
They're so deadly.
All right.
I just don't, at some point when you play moves and cop, you know, you don't even do moves anymore.
Why, what am I doing?
You just have to be good at landing shots.
Which I'm obviously not very good at right now.
Don't silence me.
Okay.
Is that mostly still the pro esports man now?
No.
I'm fairly certain that they won that tournament.
And then I think he started working for high res.
He works for, he's working for high res.
It's a very interesting story.
How do you set a stream to times two speed?
You wait until about six to seven hours from now.
There'll be a clickable video that you can click on.
Oh, you know, you can't even do that on a VOD, can you?
Oh, that hurts.
Oh, that hurts too.
You're gonna play for seven hours?
I don't know.
I don't have a plan.
Ah, no.
Losing subscribers, losing subscribers.
No, don't, don't do that.
Definitely want this.
I want to just be a machine gun.
Then I got to get the crits.
Tack speed baloney?
What's the tack speed baloney?
We put you in the top 100 list and we can take you out of it.
Yeah.
Yeah, no, I, whatever.
Tack speed Andy.
Oh, this person's not happy with me.
Oh my God.
This person just dove to kill me.
Holy shit.
All of them dove.
The whole team dove.
Stream sniped.
No, I, I highly doubt anybody's stream sniping.
I really don't think so.
I'd be shocked.
I missed every fucking single shot.
Come on, dude.
What was that?
That was weird lag.
Once you start firing so fast,
it's so easy just to like just miss everything.
Wait, silence even works for auto attacks?
Watch out.
Come on, hit him.
I had to dive and kill that guy.
That was embarrassing if I didn't.
Press VVX.
I don't understand what's going on in this game.
I'll tell you.
5v5 in an arena.
This is not the regular game mode.
The regular game mode is more akin to something like League or Dota
that you've probably seen a million times.
This is just a for fun mode.
It's a warm up mode.
And I promise I will jungle.
I will jungle in a conquest game if we do some viewer games, which we will.
It's going to be embarrassing.
I'm going to get probably really pissed off.
It will play assault too.
Don't worry if anyone wants to look.
I know that if I open up to viewer games,
I'm going to get absolutely stomped.
That's fine.
It's all right.
We're just having fun.
Now I'm just going to watch Omega Low.
Ooh, that stings.
So does that.
All right, I got to go back.
Sorry, my ego can get shattered.
No, it doesn't.
I don't care.
I'm just fucking around.
I'm just going to get every bow.
No, what am I doing?
Can I refund?
I want to refund.
All right, here we go.
I want crit.
Are you going to play DOS games in the future?
Probably.
I'm open to anything, man.
Oh, fuck, that hurts.
Oh, my God, get her off me.
I think I'm all seven of that Belonis kills.
Well, five.
Mr. Jeremy, we politely ask for Germacraft
to be played on this broadcast.
We politely ask.
Just we're going to win.
We're good.
10 years later, Belonis still OP.
What even is the tier list look like nowadays?
I have no idea.
We could really easily fuck this up
if we're not careful.
All right, good.
Yeah, Amuza Cup is weird
because when you auto attack,
it almost feels like it comes from the right shoulder,
not right in front of you.
Should I unironically get into this game?
That depends.
Do you like a MOBA that is a third person perspective?
That's not click to move.
It's WASD.
I mean, that's up to you.
Bull is the best hunter.
Well, yeah, you have to stop at that first sentence.
Do you want a MOBA?
Don't say anything else.
All right, we'll do one more of these
and then I'm going to do,
we'll do some assault viewer games
so I can warm up.
You still get the TMNT skins.
I think you can.
I'm pretty sure you need to be level 15 for assault.
Not if you do a custom game.
I can just create a custom game.
That means it's just people in this chat.
Weren't there avatar skins?
Yeah, they added so many skins to this game.
It's hard to even keep track.
I see screenshots of skins
and think they are other characters.
It's not just skins anymore.
It's like, I don't even know.
Okay, I know Aang is in the game,
but I have no fucking idea what character he is.
I have no idea.
All right, what am I going to play?
Merlin, okay.
All right, we got tank, image, mage.
Oh, no, I have to play the tank.
All right.
Oh, no.
Should I?
All right, he's flipping back and forth
showing that he's willing to play tank or damage.
What should I do?
Play Ymir?
No, Anubis?
All right, I'm going to play Bacchus?
Bracken?
Shit, I hate being the last person to pick.
Everyone just sitting there tapping their foot for me.
All right, I'm going to play as Cthulhu.
All right.
I don't know how to play Cthulhu.
You're going to play Darkest Dungeon 2?
Absolutely.
Is Cthulhu a tank, a guardian, or is he a war?
What is he?
I think he's a guardian, right?
This is epic.
You're going to play a game, Zooted, on stream?
I stopped doing that when I couldn't read
an analog clock on camera.
That was the last time I believe I did that.
All right, what do they got?
Physical, magical, physical, magical.
All right, we need magic.
We need magic protection.
Go.
Good.
Now let's play a game called, how do you play Cthulhu?
All right, this is too much reading.
It's too much.
Damage sends out a terrifying blast of energy.
It does damage and reduces stuff.
Ground target.
Cthulhu summons a portal, creating a slowing field
of Eldritch Mire at the target location.
While Cthulhu channels, the Mire continues to grow as a portal.
Fires out two massive eruptions, but it does damage.
Okay.
It's a dash.
Cthulhu creates two twisting projectiles at his side.
Is there a button I can press where it just tells me
what the move does?
I don't like when the lore is inside of the explanation
of the move.
I know I get it, but I want a distinct,
just press a button and tell me what it does.
Dash, and this is a stim.
True form.
All right, let's go.
He's so slow.
I don't know, I'm just going in.
I'm just diving.
I don't know what any of those moves did,
but I think I heard somebody.
Just press buttons.
You can't street fighter.
What am I doing?
Oh my God, it worked.
I'm dead.
You can't play a MOBA and use the street fighter
button mash concept.
It doesn't work like that.
With Cthulhu, you literally mash buttons.
All right, should I just alt in?
Holy shit.
So that's what this thing is.
Does he have moves?
This feels unfair.
Holy shit, that's insane.
What am I doing?
Oh no.
Oh no, I'm going to be feeding.
This is bad.
Oh, this is not good.
If there's a time where you can feed
and not be feel bad about it,
it's probably arena.
Just blame your team.
You want me to dive the tower and then say,
you rock, you rock, you rock.
You rock, you rock.
I don't do that shit.
Don't be annoying.
Oh, somebody's doing it.
Wait, they're doing it.
Oh, wait, this person was doing it?
No, they weren't.
Oh, they're watching the stream.
So what does the best?
Okay, that's pretty good.
I got to get up in there.
Oh, they killed that guy.
That was all right.
V-E-R.
Oh no, I didn't want to do that.
Stay in.
Let's stay in.
Oh, get out.
Everybody out.
Everybody get out.
Shit.
They were V-R-R.
Now that's a little late.
I can see why people think he's fun.
He's just like a huge slug guy
that can grow 50 feet tall.
So this is arena.
I wonder how awful it is to play with
against a Cthulhu in the regular game mode.
He takes up the whole screen.
Wouldn't that be awful in a team fight?
Oh, fuck it.
Let's go.
You still in?
All right.
Nice.
Good job.
You're big.
You don't have to do shit.
Oh, I have to go back.
Cthulhu is not actually that amazing.
Please pick a different character
that's not so scary.
Probably cooldown, right?
Who's doing all the damage?
There's only like two people
that are physical on the whole team.
Whatever.
If you build him correctly,
he hits really hard.
Get over here.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
This guy's pretty low.
You just fucked over the Ra?
Where'd he go?
Is he dead?
Ra, you got to get out of here.
Run away.
Get out of here.
You got to get out of here.
Ra, you got to get out of here.
No, I shouldn't.
I don't want to stand in that.
It's not mine.
Sorry.
I'm the tank.
I'm supposed to die.
That hurt my ears.
Sorry.
I was doing the walrus.
Does he have a...
He does.
Okay.
It's a three-hit combo.
It's one, two, three, and a cone.
Damn, that's good.
We need everybody here.
There's only three of us here.
I need another coffee, man.
I'm going in once we get here.
When the Ares pulls everybody,
that's when I'm going to go in.
Oh, shit.
They're going in.
He's going in.
Oh, okay.
All right.
We did it.
Nice work.
Oh, shit.
No, back up, back up, back up.
Run away.
You can tell he's stoned.
I'm not...
Why would I do that and play Smite?
Are you kidding me?
I'd get stuck in the menu.
People are like,
what do you mean?
Like, question mark, question mark.
Let me ask you something.
I don't know why this is a trend
in current video games,
especially in mobile games.
I'm not calling Smite a mobile game,
but holy shit.
Do we need to have
like 30 sub menus
throughout the course of the game's menu?
There's like 15 different like things
to purchase and bundles,
and you get like a bunch of ads
pop up of different chests
and bundles and packs,
and I don't even know where to start.
I remember I played a mobile game one time
and I'm not kidding.
When I got to the game's main screen,
where it's like, okay, time to play.
I think like eight different pop ups
happened before I was actually able
to even see the menu,
and the menu is a fucking mess.
Just like 12 red exclamation marks
across eight different,
five different menus,
12 different menus.
It's like, I don't want this on my screen,
and you have to click the fucking thing
to get the red exclamation mark to go away.
It's like, I don't want any red exclamation,
make them all go away.
And then sometimes you have to find
where the red exclamation mark even is.
It's like, oh, I have a red exclamation
in achievements.
Okay, I clicked achievements.
Okay, now you have to scroll
and find the fucking achievement it is
and click it and look at it
before it goes away.
What is going on here?
Holy shit, that was a good snipe.
Nice job.
We got this big guy.
Get some damage.
I have no idea how to play this character.
I'm terrified.
I'm just going to play only
to just straight up damage sync.
I'm just taking damage for no reason.
Can you play League of Legends?
No, that's different.
It was one game that I considered playing
back in the day.
It was Han, Heroes of North.
Why is that, you ask?
I cannot stand, cannot stand it
when a game has click delay to move.
Han did not have click delay.
When you clicked, you moved instantly.
Your character turned.
I don't like the like one half second,
a full second delay
when you click to go somewhere.
I hate it.
That's why I play this.
All right, I think we're going to go
in a second here.
League doesn't have that.
League has, I think, the biggest click delay
out of all the games.
Let's go.
I don't even know what these moves do,
but I'm doing them.
Oh, shit.
All right, let's go.
Everyone leave.
League is instant?
League is not instant.
Run away.
Oh, that might kill him.
You didn't do any damage.
You overextended.
League is instant.
That has to be new.
What's the click delay in League?
You had bad internet.
No, I didn't.
My internet was fine.
All right, fuck it.
Let's go in.
Not too far in.
All right, everyone back out.
Whoa.
It's instant.
Always has been.
You're thinking of Dota.
It's not delay.
It's turn speed.
Well, whatever the hell it is.
When I right, when I click to move in those games,
they don't move there immediately.
They like have to take a second
and then they move on was not like that.
And I'm talking like I was some big player
of Heroes of New Earth.
I played it maybe for 15 minutes and said,
no, I don't want to do this.
Ooh, they.
All right, all right, all right.
I'm in a minute.
I'm in.
Let's go, let's go.
Just break it all up.
Just be a fucking nuisance.
That's what I'm supposed to do.
All right, retreat.
You got it.
He's really cool.
This is definitely a little brother character, by the way.
Absolutely.
You want to play spite with your little brother,
have them pick Cthulhu and build only tank items.
And they're not doing anything.
They're just kind of a nuisance in the way,
but like they're going to be alive.
They'll be okay.
And they get to get huge.
Like, oh, I'm huge.
You could be like, oh, there you go.
Mike, there you go, Michael.
Oh, you got that guy.
You got that guy.
And you do player damage and he did one damage.
Oh, shit.
We're really kind of tearing it up here.
BM, BM, BM, BM, BM, BM, fucking BM.
That's so stupid.
Imagine hearing that over voice chat.
I turn on voice chat.
BM, BM, dude, get the fuck in there.
BM.
It's like, relax, man.
I need physical.
Actually, really shouldn't have done that.
Because this is a pretty close game.
Why do I think we were really running away with it there?
We weren't.
What the hell are these stupid rings?
These fucking Sonic the Hedgehog rings.
I've stopped so I'm not going to swear anymore.
What the fuck is going on?
All right.
What is happening?
Why?
No.
All right.
I got to let it be known that me and that rod just saved the day.
Is Sonic and Smite?
I don't know.
No, Sonic is not Nickelodeon.
There it is.
Nice work, everybody.
Oops, that's the wrong one.
I want to say you rock.
Who's your main?
I really don't have one.
I'm going to give teamwork to the raw.
Because that was a very clutch moment in the very end.
I'm going to burp.
All right.
So now, let's see how this works.
So if I go to play, and I go to custom, okay.
And I go to create match.
Match type, assault.
Let's do an assault.
Team size 5v5.
Player pick, there is no...
It's random pick.
It's assault.
Starting level.
What level did you start at?
Start at five?
I think you start at level five, don't you?
Yeah.
How much gold do you start with in assault?
1,500?
Pause type, no.
None.
I'm not going to let anybody just ruin the game
by just pausing over and over again.
It's 3k.
Start with 100,000.
No, we'll do that later.
Have you seen the handsome edits of you recently?
I've seen the handsome photos.
I haven't seen...
What do you mean, edits?
Lane minions, North America, no.
And low latency, low delay, spectate mode, no.
No spectators.
No one's doing that.
You're going to fucking like kill the server, okay?
Password.
All right, this is where...
I got to...
Okay, I got to turn the screen off, right?
Screen has to go off.
Great match.
All right, so the password, you can't see it.
I got to remember the password because it's grayed out.
Okay, great match.
All right, so you ready?
We're doing assault.
The password is...
Hello there.
No spaces, no capitals.
Didn't take very long at all.
What are these?
These are cool.
Where'd you get these?
I have what is the equivalent of the Twitter egg.
All right, you guys ready?
Let's go.
I can do Neath.
I can do Neath, but I remember a little bit.
Northeast?
What?
Is this TOS?
What, the character?
What are you talking about?
Do I have some good players on my team?
I'm going to get shit on.
I really am.
Why are people saying TOS?
Because I have Neath.
It's not Neath the character?
What are you talking about then?
I don't know.
How much is this?
1,200 gems.
You need to click this.
Hold on.
I'm in the middle of a smite game.
Just relax.
This is not the game to watch videos in the middle of a game.
Remember TF2 added a snake.
Come back.
Is this a pizza?
All right, I'm playing with people that are very good at the game,
I would assume.
So I have to be careful.
Watch this shit.
I'm going to scare the absolute shit out of somebody.
What does she have?
She has the backflip.
I don't even know what that was.
Okay, I forget her moves.
Whatever.
Let's just shoot.
She's a damage carrier.
That's fine.
I want life steal first.
And then potions are very important right now.
And potions.
Oh boy.
Why does that feel like it's lagging?
Don't forget the relic.
Oh dear.
No, why is that lagging?
It's not.
It's just turn speed.
They're going to die at the tower, right?
Like they're going to.
Doesn't she have like an explosion thing where she shoots?
Whoa.
All right, this is viewer games.
Why did I do that?
I just panicked because we're playing against players that know what they're doing.
Oh, B.M. B.M. B.M.
Oh, that guy's.
That guy dead?
Oh shit, we have to shoot him like three times.
Don't think I fucking knew how to do that, did you?
If only I had my ult.
B.M. B.M. B.M. B.M. B.M.
That's not B.M.
That's like what you do.
What the fuck is B.M.?
It stands for bowel movement.
Or actually bad manners is the other one.
Good job.
Not really.
Shit.
Oh, I got it.
Oh no, this is.
They're going in.
No, they're not.
Oh god, run away.
Oh my.
What?
Somebody just killed that guy in the middle of his sentence.
Oh, he's so close.
Boy, there's a jungle buff.
Wait, I don't want to go in there.
That's dangerous.
Use your ult.
I won't kill him if I do.
Oh shit, you really.
You thought you were really slick, didn't you?
Oh god.
I need mana, I need mana, I need mana.
Mana, mana, mana, mana, mana, mana, mana, mana, mana, mana, mana.
Give me mana, give me mana.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Oh, at that tower.
We'll get it.
Where'd he go?
Oh, up.
Cool.
We can get the tower right now.
Shit.
She's got a slow shot.
Very nice.
Good.
What do I, who do I got it?
That weave through a few people.
That was pretty good.
It was actually not that great.
That was a good little brother kill, I would say.
Excuse me.
We're just rolling here.
Oh my god.
Good little brother kill, says the little brother.
Yeah, I mean that.
I was the little brother.
That's what I mean.
That Neath ult was like a you would turn to your little brother
and say nice job.
You got him.
Earth, Earth, Phoenix.
This is not going to last very long.
You know why that playing assault in viewer games is actually awesome?
Because it truly doesn't matter.
Because it's just five v five team fights.
It doesn't, I'm not, there's no stream sniping right now.
It's just a mess in the middle.
This is great.
I do need to go.
I need mana and you can't get mana.
By the way, if you just don't know what's going on.
I have to die to buy new items or get mana.
So sometimes it's actually a pretty good technique just to die.
Oh, got a guy back here, but it's always an awesome feeling.
If you can complete a whole assault without going back one time.
That's great.
Let's see if I can steal this.
I don't determine.
Hey, thank you.
What?
Did I miss something?
Oh, that is just being weird.
Oh, yeah, this is, I might not have to go back once.
I'm getting Omega carried.
That was weird.
All right, that's fine.
I'm going to die here.
See if I can just eat some hits.
That's fine.
All right, now I can spend money.
Lifesteal, lifesteal.
I want lifesteal.
This one.
No, never mind.
The attack speed.
Yeah, and this one and potions.
Found it offline.
You know, oh, shit, I forgot.
No, it's all right.
I got a meditation.
I'm good.
I'll be good.
Purple potion.
They made a purple potion.
When did he say he was playing smite?
I haven't checked.
Well, if you probably haven't been on the stream for a while.
I actually became like a pretty much full-time smite streamer.
Just doing some viewer games hanging out in between kind of competitive matches.
Did I kill that person?
I hope so.
Oh, oh, my God.
I can't believe I did not die.
You got to be kidding me.
This could be the end right here.
We're going to get the phoenix at least.
Yeah, that's it.
We might not kill the titan.
We'll probably not going to kill the sitan,
but we'll probably get the phoenix at least.
Or I don't know.
Maybe not.
Let's find out.
Oh, boy, this is an explosion right here.
It's just narrating.
I'm just shout casting my moves.
I've noticed that when you play a game like this and you're streaming it,
like the concept of dead air is not a good concept as a streamer, as a broadcaster, right?
So what ends up happening is you end up just saying what you just did for a move
or say the move you're about to do.
Got that one.
All right, I got to move by one.
See if I can get an ult here.
As I'm not even saying any words.
Oh, we're good.
Don't you dare do it.
I'm going to do it.
Hey.
All right, kill the titan.
Kill the titan.
Nice job.
Oh, here it comes.
It's coming.
Oh, GG, Jeremy.
You got me into smite and I lost worlds four times.
Oh, no.
Hey, but you got to worlds.
That's crazy.
The VOD is going to get muted.
Oh, shit.
No, it's not.
It's fine.
All right.
Again, the link.
What the hell do you want me to click on?
What is wrong with you guys?
What's wrong with you guys?
This is it, I think.
What is this?
This is called Derma Unedited to Andy.
Why does this have 80,000 views?
This has 80,000 views.
It has more views than like a video on the second channel.
Is this...
Am I going to get DMCA for this?
Find out.
Derma is ugly.
All right.
Well, I guess we're going to play it.
Derma is ugly.
Let's see what it is.
John McAfee.
Okay.
Well, thanks for the video.
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
That was a good video.
Let's go ahead and do this again.
Do another assault.
Five to five, same thing.
We're going to do a game of conquest, too.
And I'm going to...
It's going to be bad.
Okay, random pick.
No pausing.
Get out of here.
Don't allow spectators.
And the password is...
Well, it's like blocked out anyway, so you don't know.
Wrong game mode?
Oh, shit.
All right.
Password is going to be...
How do I spell this?
All right.
Let's go.
Password is...
I will tell you.
Make us guess the password.
The password's Aaron, okay?
Yeah, I guess you guys got it before saying anything.
What?
All right.
Well, good job.
Let's go.
It was Aaron.
How do I...
I forget how you play, Agni.
I can probably do it, though.
You just do the gigantic meteors on people?
Say it.
Say what?
Thank you for Smite Thursdays.
You're the best.
Hope to see more content like this soon.
Oh, my God.
I completely fucking forgot.
I completely forgot.
I have to tweet this out, I think.
But...
So, I was...
This is a long story.
Okay, this is going to have to be after the...
Yeah.
This is going to have to be after the match here.
This is a long story.
Yeah, we'll talk about this later.
Do it during...
No, I can't.
After this match, I'm going to take a second and I'm going to show you.
So, I was a little high.
I was, you know, just did a little bit.
A couple nights, maybe a few nights ago, maybe.
I don't remember exactly what it was.
I was a little...
And so, I did something.
I did something weird that it's hard for me to explain.
A few days later, I'm thinking back.
And what was the point of me doing this is the question that I had.
It's a long, embarrassing story.
So, I'll tell you after this.
What do I want to do for moves?
What do these do?
All right, that's the dash.
That's the fire.
Probably the fire.
Don't do that shit in the streamer's ear.
Don't do that in the streamer's ear.
It's not even embarrassing.
It's just like...
At this point, you guys should expect it.
All right, so it's the...
You get four of these, right?
And you really want to put the gas down.
Because there is gas.
You put the gas down, you ignite them.
And then you go...
You throw up no more Oreos?
No.
Let me see if I can describe this.
So, I played...
I don't...
When I'm lying in bed, sometimes I do things
that are just a way for me to pass some time
before falling asleep and just relaxing.
And having the iPad in bed is very, very easy.
There's also an app store.
And I download and play just random shit all the time.
Even if it's stupid, even if it sucks.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter what the game is.
If it's new on the app store, I usually get it and just go,
oh, okay, play for 10 minutes.
And then fall asleep.
So, I downloaded Cookie Run Kingdom.
Because Cookie Run Kingdom did this thing
where they hired every North American voice actor ever
to be a hundred characters in the game.
And I was like, what the fuck?
That's crazy.
So, I downloaded it and I played it.
Remember, I had had a little bit of THC, right?
Hold on a second.
I gotta fuck shit up.
Let me just fuck shit up.
Oh, let me just chill out a minute.
So, I'm playing Cookie Run Kingdom.
And I thought of this idea.
And I thought it was a brilliant idea.
I was like, holy shit, I have a great game, video game idea.
And I opened up my notepad on my iPad and just started typing.
And what I typed is bizarre.
And I tried to break it down a little bit.
And it's just truly weird what I wrote.
But this was my idea for a video game.
And I took a screenshot of this to remember it.
Not with the iPad, with my phone.
I held my phone up to take a picture of the screen.
So, I would remember it.
How high were you?
Not really.
It was just like, I was just kind of relaxed.
I could say it, but I think it's better for you to read it.
But that's the context.
Ooh, so fun to do that with Agony.
Oh, I got it.
You just sit in the back and just drop bombs.
Nice, very nice.
Oh, what are you doing?
You said you only really do edibles.
Well, I do tinctures and edibles.
I don't smoke.
Tinctures are really easy to do.
Like a cup, just two or three milligrams and that's it.
Just to kind of relax on the couch.
I don't, this is not, I'm not condoning anybody doing any type of drugs.
Described my reasoning for why I do, sometimes, THC, marijuana.
It actually is one of the things that helps incredibly for me, personally.
I'm gonna do a little bit for the pain bullshit.
There you go.
It's a, we're in a progressive decade, Jeremy.
You don't have to, well, so drugs are, no, I don't,
I would say the same thing about alcohol.
The whole point with Agony is just being annoying.
Oh my goodness.
Oh fuck, I'm doing bad.
All right, I'm paying too much attention to like telling you guys a dumb story.
My little brother just heard you.
I want to read that.
My little brother just heard you use drugs and he already got two kilograms of meth.
Please next time instead say math books to trick him.
You have to click that you're over 18 to watch the stream.
So, excuse me.
Or mature audience warning, right?
He's not watching his little brother just heard.
Yeah, well, maybe you shouldn't have the TV so loud while you're watching The Sopranos.
Because I remember that used to happen to me.
I remember being in my house and my dad watching The Sopranos in the other room.
And he'd be like, oh, you fucking idiot, you fucking guy, stupid fucking.
And I would be in the other room and I would kind of walk out and he'd be like,
hey, hey, hey, hey, you shouldn't be in here.
It's like, well, you watch it at like fucking 80% volume.
Ooh, kill.
Oh, let's be fucking cheeky here.
Oh, I had the idea halfway through.
Shit.
I was going to put the gas down and stun him,
but I had the idea to do that when I was like at the last second.
Shit.
Oh, oh, god damn it.
All right.
This is not a great game right now.
Yeah, I remember specifically, I remember my dad would watch The Sopranos
and I would walk in the room and he would just like change back.
I don't know if the remotes still have this,
but remotes had this thing called like the last channel button
where if you pressed it, it would just kind of,
it's like when you pressed Q in Team Fortress or an FPS and it goes to your last weapon.
He would just press Q on his keyboard essentially and switch to like the news.
So I would walk in the room and I would hear like,
let me tell you something.
You are, the local weather today,
we're going to be having some sunny sunshine outside.
And of course, make sure you go to the rat festival next week.
That's what would happen every time.
I would leave the room and it'd be like,
oh, yeah, Janet, that's a very good quit.
Fuck it, idiot.
Get him, shoot him in the fucking head.
Shoot him in the, last night, a cat snuck up into the,
it was switched so weirdly between the two of them
that it was so confusing to pay attention to.
I don't even know how he enjoyed the show
because he had to do that all the time.
No, this is a bullshit story.
This is not a bullshit story.
I swear to God, you were very good at this game.
Um, yeah, what do you say now?
I killed the guy with two centimeters of health left.
Look, I'm also in like story Andy mode,
which means I can't play the video game.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, don't hurt me.
All right, I'm going way too hard here.
Why was your dad afraid of swear words when you were 20?
I was not 20, I was like fucking,
I was like 15.
When did the Sopranos come out?
Sopranos original release date was, uh, when was it?
1997?
How old was I?
Oh, 30?
Okay, hold on, I gotta, shit.
I wasn't 30.
How old was I in 1997?
Help them, I know.
Look, they knew what they were signing up for.
They're playing with a streamer.
They're playing with a streamer who's not very good at this.
I think they know what they're getting into.
Oh, you were 12.
Okay, so those of you that said that I was 20,
I was like 13.
12 is fine for swearing.
Okay, well, uh, look, when you raise your kids,
I, hold on, god damn it.
I was so greedy, but I think I got it.
Ah, come on, I need to get that.
Whoa, look out, it's Jormungandir.
They're going to be swearing by 12 whether you like it or not.
Okay, all I'm saying is that when I was like 12 years old,
my parents didn't want me to watch like fucking,
it's the mafia guys shoot each other in the head.
Okay, what are we having?
What are you talking about?
Internet generation versus Jormungandir who didn't swear until he was 40.
You guys, I'm 26 and I still don't swear in front of my parents.
Look, I don't know.
I wasn't allowed to watch R rated movies until like later on in my teen years.
Is that so bizarre?
No, not really.
It's pretty normal.
Fake Jormungandir doesn't even look like the one from,
I don't know why I was going to say guilds of war, god of war.
I don't know why I'm just trying to stun people that are not over here.
Oh, they're close.
I don't even care if I die.
Damn it.
I thought they were going to run to the right, not left, to try to juke me.
We're going in.
It looks like we're going in.
Oh, shit.
Good, good.
Keep it up.
Get him on the run.
Why is he playing this boomer game?
I don't know what any terminology is anymore.
I don't know any of this terminology is.
So over my head.
Oh, you're in trouble now.
We really pulled this back.
We were losing.
Sorry, my sacrifice is mine.
No, we already went over this.
You can't say this is the worst stream because you don't like the game.
That's not how that works.
This would be worst stream if it took me an hour of technical problems to get here.
And then we didn't talk about anything fun.
And like, I'm not having a good time and the game sucks.
Well, I mean, if you don't just because you don't like the game
does not make it a contender for worst stream 2021.
That's just your personal preference for video games.
Excuse me.
Is that a hairball?
Yeah.
Come on, Ra.
Do I have enough money for anything?
Why did I buy the Rod of Tahootie right now?
God, you know, we play smite, us gamers.
If you know, if you know, you know.
Why do they get Rod of Tahootie as my fourth item?
It's my gamers.
No, this is the worst thing you can stream.
I disagree.
Holy shit.
I didn't even know you were here.
What the fuck?
Oh, my God.
I just came out of nowhere.
Yeah.
Holy shit.
I wasn't paying attention.
I'm reading chat.
I should just delete chat.
Read the iPad thing.
Actually, let me get this on like Discord so I can link to it.
Oh, I got 24 seconds.
Nice.
That's enough time.
Now, let me get this on screen.
Because I think this is going to be over in a minute.
Shit, I got to hold on.
Do I have any money?
Why don't you do the hangout portions of the stream anymore?
OK, hold on.
This is important.
I'm reading the fucking chat room.
It's like you can't, OK, this game,
you can't just like turn your head to the left and just read it.
I just lost us the game.
OK, anyways.
Yeah, Chad, why are you talking?
You just lost us the game.
What the hell?
All right, let me let me get this thing.
Hey, I want to put this on screen and we're going to get
I'm going to give you a second to read.
Remember, I'll give you a little bit more context.
It's there.
Is it there?
OK, so context wise, again, don't do context.
I have to do at least some context.
This is oh, this is kind of blurry.
All right, can you guys be able to see this shit?
Why is this so huge?
OK, context again.
This is I was high and I was playing Cookie Run Kingdom
and I had a brilliant idea for a video game
like the storyline of a video game.
I'm not going to say anything.
I'm just going to let you read it
and we're going to show it right now.
This is just the Avengers, but they're evil.
A party of Earth's five, weren't there six Avengers?
A party of Earth's five most powerful heroes.
Heroes storms the enemy's base.
They defeat the ultimate villain and claim the castle.
These are the antagonists of the game.
They become evil soon after.
Are you eight years old?
This is an AI.
Yeah, that's like Talk to Transformer.
And I took the screenshot.
This is me taking a screen.
Like I held the camera from the phone up to the screen
and press snap camera button.
There's a dog hair on the screen.
There are like five dog hairs.
Oh my God, look at them all.
There's one, two, three, four.
There are like five or six dog hairs.
A party of Earth's five most powerful dog hairs.
Well, there you go.
That was my brilliant idea.
By the way, Hi Me wants 5% of royalties
from all the money you make from that awesome video game.
Let's play another one.
All right, we're going to do one more assault
and then we're going to move.
We're going to play a game of conquest one
and it's going to be horrible and I'm going to hate it.
The game's already been made.
All right, we're going to play a game called Guess the Password.
I'm going to make it easy for you.
Let's see if you get it.
Here we go.
Somebody got it.
Wow, that's actually surprising.
That's really surprising.
More of you get it now.
I mean, there's a lot of people here.
The password is susguy with no spaces, no capitals.
Do Fortnite Friday.
No, I don't think that's what we're going to do.
After this, we're going to take a break.
I'm going to get some water, maybe another coffee and I'll come back.
This time I'm actually going to.
That's so loud.
Okay, I kind of know how to play 100 bots.
Not really though.
I want to really pay attention to this one.
So this is going to be a gamer match.
What that means is I'm not going to be talking to chat really.
I'm going to be focusing.
This is going to be a gamer one.
Why are you not playing Dota?
I think the difference between Dota and Smite for me is one requires an entire lesson plan.
One really requires you to do a full class with a professor for a year
before you're comfortable really playing the game against people.
You guys think that in the future there'll be classes for video games?
Before you laugh at me.
Everybody laughed at me when I said that gaming would be in the Olympics.
Remember five to ten years ago when I made that video?
Everybody laughed at me.
Do you think that in some of like the most prestigious colleges
there will be League of Legends classes?
They already exist now.
Okay, well, all right.
All right, here we go.
All right, quiet.
You know, just put me on in the background.
Just chill for a little bit.
We're going to hang out.
Just have me on in another tab while you're in your League of Legends course.
Okay, I want.
Do you people build pun bats?
Tanky?
Do they?
What do they have?
That's so much physical.
Yeah, I got to get a physical protection.
Any of these physical?
Magic?
No, I need physical.
We'll do the cool down one.
Okay, that's good.
What's the weather like in Vegas?
It's actually really nice recently.
It's cooled down quite a bit.
Okay, everybody.
Here we go.
Time for a gamer stream.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Here we go.
I'm going to play as if no one's watching.
Never to jump up.
Don't shoot me.
Nope.
Oh, good grab.
I didn't capitalize.
The streamer gets that.
I'm the streamer.
I get it.
Sobek is godlike.
I don't think the Sobek has missed one pull.
And he's just talking.
He's just like monologuing.
This Sobek is also streaming.
See?
And what a distraction that was, wasn't it?
Wasn't that quite a distraction?
I have no mana.
What are you beeping?
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I've loved your stream, by the way.
I love Sobek gaming.
I get all these tips and tricks.
Ooh, you always got them.
That was close.
I wish I could go in.
I think I'm just going to go in and die.
Yeah, this is the time to do it.
This is the time to just die and get a few hits.
Okay, I got somebody.
Shit, I don't have enough money.
Turn up the game volume?
Oh, if I'm not going to be talking,
then yeah, you should be able to hear more.
Bro, it's weird to see you play against regular players.
What do you mean?
There's no way I'm going to turn on voice chat.
Zero percent chance.
All right, quiet.
I'll set around.
Ace cam?
No, stop distracting me.
I heard a cool video game sound.
You get that.
I don't need it.
Oh, shit.
Ace cam.
I don't have a shirt on.
I can't put a face cam on.
Sorry.
Come on, I'm 0 and 2.
This is stupid.
All right, I'm going to do the thing
that is really frowned upon
and that stands still in spawn
so you can complete your item.
See how it works.
Ooh, full body cam.
Nobody does that, do they?
Is there a streamer that has a full body cam,
not just a head face cam?
They're sitting here playing a game
and they just have an entire body cam?
I'm talking head to toe.
Nice job.
It's perfectly aligned to make it
so they're always in frame,
their whole standing body.
We going in?
Oh, I think we're going in.
I think we're going in.
Oh, they're all so close.
All right, let's go.
Oh, kill him.
Oh, he's so low, this tier.
God damn it.
I didn't feed.
I did a lot of work.
What are we throwing?
What?
We killed like three people.
I can't make decisions on my own
so I just pick what other people pick.
What should I do?
Fuck.
Um, this one.
Jeremy, please, I need to know
who your favorite smite character's ass is.
Do you think the first time you said
that I was going to give you a response?
I'm that person enough for five seconds.
Nope.
Just got to defend.
This is anybody's game.
We have a lot more kills
and a lot more money than they do,
but that's fine.
Is that a capo?
You do emotes?
He's just going in.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't know if that's a good idea.
God damn it.
Oh, no, no, no, please.
I played up a hundred bats in assault
is essentially just like,
please kill me for free.
You finish your homework?
I don't do homework.
I never hand in homework not one time
and I get an A on every test
so I get a C.
I did the same.
No, I did homework.
Fairly decent amount of the time.
I do think we actually can go in though.
Yeah, we absolutely can.
I'm jumping in and just throwing it.
I don't even care.
No, no, fuck.
I saw it happen.
No, I thought I was in the clear.
I see this guy in the sky.
I walked right into it too.
God damn it.
I have one in five.
I can't be this shitty one.
Use your three to teleport.
What?
That's actually okay.
That's really helpful.
That's very helpful.
Who's doing all the damage?
It's all physical.
This is good damage.
Whatever movement speed.
I want that.
I put my headphones down
to focus on a math problem.
That's in that sound you made.
I could hear it across my whole desk.
Careful.
Oh, shit.
But no.
What the fuck, dude?
Why?
No.
That was bad.
God damn it.
All right.
No more talking.
I'm paying attention.
This is bad.
Get off me.
Get off.
Nice.
Good work.
Oh, he's in the air.
What else?
Get the tower.
Oh, are you serious?
What a fucking god.
No more swearing.
I'm not going to say the fuck anymore.
All right.
That was a good team fight.
Oops.
I thought I didn't teleport.
I thought I teleported.
What was the one I wanted to get?
This one.
I hate it when you play video games.
You just have an entire room full of fidget toys
that he uses on face cam.
Do you want to watch a cat?
I think there are plenty of streams
where it's just a cat in a room
with a bunch of cat toys.
Believe those already exist.
They're at the Phoenix?
Oh, my god.
The Thanatos is going to kill me
and I'm freaking out about it.
Oh, my god.
Oh, they wasted their ult.
I wish that indicator was smaller.
It takes up like your whole character
and it's like just making you panic.
I'm playing Hunbats.
This character sucks.
It's like literally F tier.
I think on every Smite tier list
this character is actually at the bottom.
It's never picked.
Yeah, I looked up Smite tier list before this
and it was like Hunbats,
they didn't put him on the list.
They didn't even place him.
He's only been played in one game in competitive
is because they banned everybody.
They banned all the characters
that their hunter was really good at.
Their hunter?
Whatever, assassin.
Oh, I'm the only one alive.
Oh, they think they're going to fuck around.
My god, run.
My god, this person's terrifying.
Oh, my god.
He's getting closer.
I hate Thanatos.
He's terrifying.
Damn it.
Get away from me.
What are you doing?
Where is he?
Where are you?
I successfully defended the fortress.
This is it.
This is where we win.
You're playing smart.
Just kill the Titan.
Who cares about anything else?
Kill the Titan.
Oh, thank god.
Nice work.
Hunbats is actually pretty fun.
I'd put him on C tier.
I've seen some tier lists that put him pretty low
and that's not fair.
He has a really good kit.
I really like this person's stream.
Very friendly.
They gave me the buff like three times.
I'm going to take a pee break
and get some water, maybe a coffee.
I'll come back and we'll do a little bit more.
I will be right back.
When did Cash App give 69 subs?
When did that happen?
I missed that completely.
Oh, it was like 20 minutes ago.
It was like an hour ago.
What?
Was I just locked into gamer mode?
Oh, okay.
Well, thank you Cash App for the 69 community subs.
That's a lot.
Thank you Zap X for the 10 community subs.
And Loxbury, thanks for five community subs.
Thank you, thank you.
I'm always in gamer mode.
I'm not.
I'm in gamer mode for like five minutes a week.
Let me go here.
All right, let's do...
I got some skins.
I did.
Because I had to buy the god pack on this account.
I got the god pack and then I got some gems
just to play around with and I already...
I think I like freaked out and I bought like four boxes.
I don't even know what I own.
Is there a way to see what I actually own?
Can I see the gods that I actually have skins with or no?
Sort by purchased.
Purchased, purchased?
No, sadly.
Oh, okay.
I got a skin for somebody besides Anubis.
Who was it?
I feel like it was Achilles or something.
Let's see.
Yeah, what's this one?
That's all right.
Can we go through and look at the skins?
Is that boring content for you guys?
How boring is that?
At a scale of one to ten.
All right, that's fine.
Who's this?
Charibdis?
Charibdis.
How do I say this?
Charibdis?
Who is this?
Charribdis.
All right, what do you got for skins?
Ah, it's just blue.
That's cool.
What is this one?
This one's limited.
This item will never be available through special promotions or events ever again.
Oh, okay.
Who's a god that I like to play?
Not even subtle about the FOMO.
Oh, here it is.
Okay, here.
It's just Aang.
He's dead.
I kind of want this.
This one's 3,500 gems.
What is that?
Is that like a $50 skin?
How expensive is that?
Okay.
Is this the same actor?
No, it can't be.
It's a middle lane.
That's really nice and great and dandy, but what does it actually sound like in-game?
And then they don't do it again and they just play the game.
Whoa, Ghost Rider.
This is the one that I like.
This is the Merlin I want to see.
Yep, that's the one.
They got a lot of Merlin skins.
It's the jewel wizard.
Yeah, it kind of is.
Cool.
I tried to play King Arthur in a training match,
but the moveset was so weird to me.
I just couldn't even.
I just exited.
Where is he?
Where's Arthur?
Is it King Arthur and not Arthur?
King Arthur.
King Arthur is just Arthas.
Didn't they base everything on the Arthurian shit anyways?
All the way around?
There was an Uther before Uther in Warcraft.
Just to let you know.
Okay, we got a dragon one.
That's kind of cool.
Look at Cthulhu's skin.
Oh, that's what we're going to do.
I've got a pretty good bugleberry skin.
It's young Arthur.
Cthulhu has a cuphead skin.
You're losing viewers.
That's okay.
Why is that surprise anybody?
I'm in a menu looking at skins.
Actually, I like this one.
All right, Cthulhu.
Let's see.
What do you got?
This one's exclusive.
Purple.
His purple skin is only available for a limited time only.
What's the difference?
Oh, he's purple.
That one's cool.
Yeah, okay.
I could see that.
That one would be fun to have.
What is this, like, America one?
Okay, cool.
Okay, this is one of those cases where
I would play against this person
and I would not know this was Cthulhu.
It would fuck with me.
This changes the whole character to a point
where this is a different character.
This item can be earned through an event
or purchase for its full price once the event has ended.
Why is this just the single player in Mortal Kombat?
What do I have to do?
Buy all.
I need 160,000 Odyssey points.
More points.
Quest map.
This is the shit I was talking about.
This is exactly what I was talking about.
Visit territory.
Okay, what does this have to do with the video game Smite?
What is this?
Complete all the quests.
Oh, okay.
Play an assassin in two games and you get this.
This is too much for my brain.
It's just a battle pass.
Okay, right.
Rules.
Is the end user license agreement?
Lore.
Bundles.
I already bought a bunch of these.
All right, well, that's cool.
There's one that I want you to look at as well
that is also kind of game breaking and bizarre is this one.
It's just so weird.
I like this one.
That's terrifying.
And look at this.
It's just a bunch of cartoon characters.
What is this?
I'm not going to buy this stuff.
I'm not going to play this game.
What the fuck?
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
What does it say?
What's this supposed to be?
Check out the Doge skin.
Is it arterio?
Doge is a Doge skin.
Where?
Wrong one.
Scatty.
Let's give them the benefit of the doubt here.
I'm going to give them the benefit of the doubt.
All right.
Did this come out this past like six, seven months?
Or has this been a thing for the last couple of years?
Five years ago?
This gets a pass.
Four or five years ago.
Okay.
Very old skin.
Yeah, okay.
But they're not just jumping on this.
Okay.
What's this?
Korra?
Whoa.
What other cartoon characters are in this?
Besides Ninja Turtles.
And who is Splinter?
I know he's in the game.
And Shredder.
Is Stranger Things?
Rick and Morty are not in this.
Please, I will buy them right now.
If Rick and Morty are in the game, I'm going to buy Rick and Morty.
I'm going to play the rest of the stream as Rick and Morty.
Is that actually in the game?
I hate that.
I want it.
There's a Pickle Rick skin.
All right.
Where are they?
Who's Shredder?
If you play as Rick and Morty, this will be the worst stream.
I could agree with that.
Bear Insomniac?
Okay.
Bear Insomniac.
Whoa.
Where?
Holy shit.
How much is this?
89,000 gems is how much money?
That's like a hundred bucks.
Why?
That's a...
What is this?
Oh, okay.
This is where they get you.
This item can be earned through an event.
Or purchased for its full price.
So I guess there's another way to earn this.
This is just if you don't want to go through all the trouble or something.
I don't know.
That's a lot of money.
This one looks cool.
I love the snapping.
I got to play as Baron Sammy.
Yeah.
This is the new main.
Baron's really fun.
I'm going to try him.
I want to find all the...
I know the Ninja Turtles.
But a Thanatos?
Yeah.
I remember Thanatos having a ton of skins even back when I played.
All right.
What the fuck?
That's just...
It's just Cupid.
This one...
That one transforms.
Which one?
This one does?
Go to Archon.
Who's Ar-Ar-Archon?
Arrocon?
Archon is the skin.
Oh.
Archon Thanatos?
Reaper.
Obey.
Where's Archon?
Grim Reaper.
Cyber.
Classic.
Ruby Rose.
Ruby Rose?
Oh, it's from an anime.
Okay.
Where's...
There's too many skins.
Where's Archon?
Demonic.
Golden.
There's no Archon.
Soul Harvester.
Reaper.
Final Boss.
Jack the Reaper.
Obey.
Grim Reaper.
Sci...
Where is this?
Ruby Rose.
Classic Ruby Rose.
There's a classic.
I skipped the only good one.
Where's Archon?
Are you guys lying?
Oh.
Okay.
What does it do?
Oh.
Level 1 minion.
Level 15 boss.
Level 30 boss.
That's cool.
All right.
I want to see if one...
Where...
Who's the guy that goes,
Stick around.
And who's the guy that goes,
Buttery.
Crispy.
Crust.
Flaky.
Crispy.
Buttery.
Flaky.
Crispy.
Crust.
Is Mario?
No, it's not.
It's not Peter Griffin.
If you don't know that video,
then holy shit.
Come on.
Have you ever used the internet?
Guys, I'm the one that's not supposed to be...
I don't know about the memes and shit.
You...
Come on.
Sylvanas there.
Yeah.
He goes,
Sylvanas!
Bob Ross.
Okay.
What's this?
They got a spoiled Stranger Things.
This is a...
I think I just spoiled the show.
I've never seen it.
What did you want me to see here?
Okay.
Now I want to see Splinter,
and I want to see Shredder,
and then we can keep playing.
Hachiman.
Okay.
Where is Hachiman's skin?
What is this?
It's a really good furry OC.
Okay.
Oh yeah.
There he is.
Master Splinter.
I want this.
Would you guys judge me if I bought this?
How much would I get judged?
What does that actually translate to for money?
No.
We already judged you already.
All right.
So that's Hachiman.
Where's Shredder?
Buy it on your main account.
That's also pretty true.
Ravana.
Yeah.
I really shouldn't buy anything on this account
besides the god pack.
All right.
There it is.
That's pretty cool.
Completed.
I was just going to say something,
and then I realized that I could just play
the Nickelodeon All-Stars game,
because I was about to say,
imagine a game like this,
but it's just like old cartoon characters,
and like Nickelodeon characters,
and like Disney characters.
Krang is in the game too.
There are enough old cartoons and old stuff
to be able to make a smite,
but instead of gods,
it's just old characters.
Let's see.
Is Krang in the game?
Oh my god.
It's actually in the game.
I have to buy this.
What?
You're going to make Krang
an exclusive special promotion?
Krang is Twitch Prime giveaway.
Oh.
Krang is free with Twitch Prime.
I don't want to link my Twitch Prime to this.
Not this one.
All right.
Cool.
Super cool.
What about Nuwa?
Where's Nuwa?
Nuwa.
Okay.
This is a League character.
Is there a Ninja Turtles character?
Or a Nickelodeon character?
Okay.
Well, that was...
This one's $3,600.
All right.
Well, what about Jeb?
What does Jeb have for skins?
Oh, Frosty the Snowman.
This is my favorite skin in the game.
$1,200?
Yeah, I think I have to get a Jeb.
What about this one?
Interesting.
What is that?
Jeb is cool.
The earth moves.
I'm playing Jeb next game.
Excuse me, Jeb.
We're going to play as Jeb.
All right.
We're going to do Arena.
Get ready for Arena.
Arena.
Blind pick is what we want, right?
Diving level three?
Pause type none.
Jeb sucks in Arena.
That's true.
Never mind.
All right.
I'm going to make...
You know what?
Let's really go for this.
I'm going to make this password very hard.
Let's see if anybody can get this.
I bet that somebody would be able to get.
I don't know.
I wonder.
What would I do?
Something very hard.
Okay.
If somebody gets this,
that's really weird that we're on the same kind of plane of existence, right?
Looks good.
It swallowed really weirdly and it hurt.
Will somebody get this?
If somebody gets this,
if more than one or two people get this,
this is just proof to make sure you have a good password.
A hint?
Okay.
It is food related.
This is a food related item
and it can sit in your pantry.
Does not need to be refrigerated.
You would classify this as a snack.
And the main ingredient in this comes from a cow.
By the way, I spelled it wrong.
Now that we're thinking and we're doing this.
The password is Cheez-It with no spaces, no capitals.
And it's not the brand name.
It's Cheez-It.
Whoops.
Have you seen Gas Station Simulator?
I have.
I was thinking about it.
All right.
What is it?
What does it move?
That was cool.
All right.
This is a arena.
Probably good.
He's a mage.
What about Jeb?
Jeb is very bad.
You have the Jeb skin.
Oh, you guys have the cool skins.
You have the frog skin.
Click the icon on the left to see moves.
Oh, here we go.
All right.
Baron shares Baron's Brew, a powerful restorative chalice
with his allies from the item shop.
Enemies hit by Baron will have hysteria applied to them.
Baron's abilities interact with hysteria
to provide bonus effects, targets, and max hysteria
from the item shop?
Okay.
So you have to hit people to get hysteria.
I've seen this before.
You put the mirror down and it's just me.
This one is god.
Okay.
Whatever.
I'll figure it out.
Well, this is kind of like the Anubis wrap.
Baron's Brew is a multi-potion that you can only get on him.
Oh, okay.
Add me on Cookie Run Kingdom.
I sounded kind of rude, but I don't play it.
All right.
So let me see.
So that's kind of like a little grab like Anubis.
What's this one?
That's this is what I like.
This thing.
You go boom, bam, the two beams.
All right.
So just a hit with abilities and then it does more damage.
Easy.
Simple.
Where's that potion?
Where's Baron's Brew?
He was 140.
Oh, shit.
That's actually really good.
Nice.
This dreamer hates his fans.
There's a shark?
That's an awesome Sobex skin.
I'll take the damage.
Why not?
All right.
Let's get it.
Learning the moves.
Just getting the feel for it.
Don't stand near me.
Immune.
I go back.
Throw it up the graphics.
Everything's on maximum.
Turn up.
Everything is on max.
Two is a heal.
Oh, it looks like 720p.
You're watching it in 720.
It is 720p.
It's being downscaled.
Well, 864p.
Sorry.
Wait, we have to help our friends over here.
I don't know what this does.
That was cool.
Whatever it did.
Are you sure you bought a legitimate 3090?
Would I have like a bootleg 3090?
Taped over the side.
It's like a 1060.
Oh, fuck.
That's bad.
Why can't you stream in 1080?
This question comes up pretty frequently.
But something that we have to keep discussing.
I will explain it.
I'll tell you again.
So Twitch only allows you to have a bit rate of 6,000 upload bit rate.
A full 1080p video at 6,000 bit rate and 60 fps does not look very good.
It's not enough.
The reason why most people stream in 720 or like 860 whatever
is because that 720 video looks okay at 6,000.
It's 8k.
It is not.
Okay.
Now I'm going to play the game again.
Now what people do is they might have a second computer
that they run the whole thing through
and they have it on the slowest preset possible for their CPU.
But if you look at the research,
like the things that people have done on testing,
once you go from medium down to slow for the CPU preset,
you can't even really tell a difference.
Until we can stream at like 10,000 to 15,000 bit rate up,
1080, 60 fps is not...
All right.
Whatever.
You get it.
Who cares?
I'm done.
Everyone's calling me a nerd.
What is this person doing back here?
He's a tech guy.
I have not hit that fucking one time.
All right.
Let me have a non-embarrassing game.
Excuse me.
It's still close.
All right.
Let me pull this together.
I'm just hitting the same guy.
Thank God.
He's going to destroy his PC in a rage.
What the hell are you saying?
Be toxic this game?
Why?
I don't want to be toxic.
I want to just play.
Get this guy away from me.
Come here!
Oh my goodness.
This guy, this wrestler.
Oh my God.
Am I joking him?
I joked him.
Holy shit.
I win.
More cooldown?
What do you think?
Yeah.
This one.
I like sprint.
I know.
I'm a noob.
This is different actors saying the same line auditioning for the same role.
That was really toxic kind of.
No, that's not what I'm trying to do.
What is this person doing?
Suck him in.
I don't even know what this does.
All right.
What does that actually do?
What does this do?
Jesus.
This is a god damn...
140 characters Twitter.
What the fuck?
Baron pulls the soul of living towards his coffin becoming immune to crowd control.
Okay.
So I take 35% less damage.
Enemies within the range are caught in a vortex.
Dragging them towards the coffin and taking damage every 30.33 seconds.
When enemy god gets too close, their soul is ripped out.
They get stunned and they take a lot of damage.
Okay.
I got it.
Ice award for teleport.
You're just gonna let that go in?
Stop reading.
What?
Oh my god.
What's with you guys?
Nice.
Get out of here.
Get away from me.
I don't like this guy.
Let's go.
Let's work.
We gotta kill this guy.
Oh, come the fuck on.
Kill him.
Oh my goodness.
Run.
What?
No.
He's the tank.
Stop shooting him.
Yeah, I wanna reduce the healing on that Hercules.
It's still anybody's game.
I'm not gonna do that.
I'm not the tank.
Here he comes.
Get away from me.
That's not fun.
It's not fair.
Game's not fair.
Build boots.
Why are we even attacking this guy?
He's just here.
This guy.
Get out of here.
Nobody get this guy.
Why do I just hear a school cafeteria full of people?
Don't let him get away with that.
Oh, I got a ball on the fucking vortex.
Oh shit.
Oh.
I thought they were gonna keep walking.
Stop fucking.
Oh my god.
What am I doing?
Sprint.
Oh, I had to be like stupid and make a dumb little joke.
All right.
Next time I'm gonna play a god that I know what their moves do.
Okay.
Streaming smite and picking a god I've never played with before is probably a bad idea,
but this is a good idea.
Immune.
All right.
What do you say?
Let's pull back.
Let's go.
Back it up.
Bad.
This is a bad idea.
Oh my god.
That Hercules is running right at me.
Ice drop so bad.
Good.
All right.
I want to do...
Well, cool down.
Yeah.
Cool down.
Ooh.
That's penetration and cool down.
Hell yeah.
I don't even read the paragraph underneath it.
Just hit me.
I just absolutely smashed that cube in the face.
Oh, come on.
He's so low.
No, we can't have that.
City and shards second item.
I don't know.
I look...
This is why I'm playing arena.
Is that a beach ball?
You're gonna play tribes ascend?
Tribes ascend really is probably one of the best FPS games that's ever been made,
but I wasn't a big fan of all the grenade shit.
That game's long range skill shots is some of the most satisfying dopamine inducing gaming
ever that I've ever played in my entire life.
All right.
This guy.
Thank you.
Stop dying.
I'm drinking a big soda.
Every death is almost like you're trying to make me burp.
What?
All right.
I'm gonna play a character that I know what their moves are.
I'm gonna hear that in my dreams.
Place a ward for teleport.
Again, another one.
We're going conquest.
You guys ready?
Okay.
I have to play the easiest thing.
What's the solo lane the easiest still?
No, not support.
No way.
Do you mercury impression?
Sure thing.
Mercury!
Hank Arthur solo is fun.
Solo I think I could do.
Mid?
Yeah, I'll do mid.
All right.
Here we go.
Password.
Yeah, I'll do mid.
Not doing solo.
Very good.
Nice job.
You all have very good listening skills.
Password is I'll go mid with no spaces, no capitals.
I didn't have to even say it.
All right, guys, you ready?
I need to be mid.
I'm mid.
Now the question is who should I play with in mid?
It's either gonna be Anubis, Kronos, Olken, not Hades.
No, I'm not confident enough to play this game that way.
It's gonna be Kronos.
Kronos is ADC.
No, he's not.
It's unfair because people are brute forcing the password with quantum computing.
I was gonna say it's like tag.
Kronos is not hard.
Kronos is fun.
I love playing Kronos because you just kind of ski around and go
with attack speed.
He has some of the best sound effects in the game.
You guys all play.
Why are people talking to me like they don't play this game?
You have to have a thousand games on each one of these characters.
You guys play this game.
A shitload of you guys play this game all the time.
Oh, I forgot this was an arena.
I just pressed one.
Whoops.
All right.
How do I play Conquest?
You guys have to carry me.
Okay, you owe me 1500 gold.
What do I buy?
There's no boots.
I'm just gonna do this.
This is attack speed and this is okay.
Are these free?
Yeah, Kronos is a lot of fun.
I know that you have to I have to go get the buffs, right?
And help people.
I don't know anything about rotating the ultimate.
And why doesn't Smite do stuff like this?
Just get like a bunch of really good like pro players.
And then one like eight year old that plays mid.
All right, here we go.
One of the reasons why I like Smite is because last hitting really is not make or break the whole game.
It adds a little bit, but it's not the worst thing in the world.
All right, okay.
I think that's free, right?
Here they come, here they come.
I don't even know how to say anything.
Wait, I'm streaming.
Watch out.
Save yourself.
They can hear me talking.
Yeah, I can.
This is fine.
I don't have to do any like VGS or anything.
Athena's going left.
Athena going left lane.
Gank coming middle lane.
Gank incoming middle lane.
Gank incoming.
Fuck.
This is gonna be a long match.
I don't even have enough money to buy anything.
I need wards, right?
No, that's not my job.
I don't know what my job is.
All right, that's fine.
Nice work.
Remember the other team can hear you too.
That's right.
Oh shit, this is a bad like kind of leak.
Thank you.
All right, back to it.
What was that?
Enemy is continuing to be in middle lane.
I'm not pushing up too far.
I don't want to get in trouble here.
There's an enemy in middle lane.
Enemy in mid.
Enemy in mid lane.
Gank incoming.
Wait, people can see my map.
Oh shit.
What do I do about this?
Okay, that's better, right?
Okay, now I understand.
There we go.
Enemy missing middle.
Can I help you?
Gank left lane.
Get him.
I missed everything.
I have no mana.
Oh shit, I don't have any mana.
I don't think I can do this by streaming this.
This is too much pressure.
I don't like this.
Okay, you want to know the last time I played Conquest?
2017.
Or probably 2016.
I've only played Arena and Assault since like 2017.
I don't, this is too much pressure.
It's too much.
A fake map up there?
I probably shouldn't have played Khronos either.
Oh man, I'm trying to like look good for this stream.
Yeah, I'm gonna play Khronos.
Like he's got like a complicated kind of number two move.
Well, I don't know what the fuck I'm doing.
Okay, enemy has returned middle.
I'm afraid to go any further than this.
Well, they all know.
This was never gonna work out the way that I thought, right?
It's all right.
Hey, if we win, look, they have such an advantage.
They're all here.
Hopefully you can get out.
All right, I gotta go back.
Just cover your whole screen.
We're not playing Conquest again.
Okay, didn't I say earlier?
I did.
I said earlier that I am not going to play Conquest
unless it's a comedy game.
What am I doing?
Why are we doing this?
Honestly, God, what am I doing?
I just have to try not to die.
Enemy missing middle.
Enemy still missing middle.
All right, I need to level up.
See, they know.
They know.
I can't gank anybody.
Enemy missing middle.
Covering the map only helps.
God damn it.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, we're gonna play arena and assault only.
Enemy missing middle still.
I have no idea where the hell they are.
Oh, they're back.
Enemy missing left.
Enemy missing.
I found them.
I found their hair.
All right, they're coming to the end of the road.
Just look at my game, you'll know.
Okay.
I think everyone's rotating to the left side.
Team fight incoming.
It's time to do a team fight.
Never mind.
Everybody run away.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Stay there, stay there, stay there, stay there.
Check this shit out.
I'm gonna clean it up.
Did I get killed?
That's our tower.
What am I doing?
Enemy missing middle.
I missed.
Whatever.
Enemy has returned middle.
Enemy missed.
No, they're here.
Ooh.
I need to go back and buy.
I'm so afraid to move forward.
All right.
Careful.
I have to go back.
Be careful.
Mid is making a...
What are you doing?
Oh, I...
Sorry.
He thinks he's funny.
I'm not trying to be funny right now.
I'm trying not to embarrass myself and die like nine times.
Enemy is missing middle.
I have no idea where they are.
Hey, whoa.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
They were just waiting for me.
They're streaming Smite in 2021.
You're already embarrassing.
Get out of here.
Nine times?
No.
I'm not gonna die more than six times.
Can I even buy anything?
I'm just gonna buy this.
Whatever it is.
Okay.
Enemy is attacking the middle tower and I'm gonna show them to respect me.
See?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Everybody.
Here comes Jeremy.
Oh, everybody move in.
The infield moves in.
The outfield moves in.
Oh, yeah.
He can't hit past our heads.
No.
No way.
Just keep...
Yeah.
Everybody move the fuck in.
This is when I do a little blooper over the left fielder's head
because he's playing where the fucking shortstop would be.
There it goes.
And I'm gonna get an inside the park home run.
I'm scared of that.
Watch it.
This is bad news.
Yeah, this is bad news.
This is bad.
Bad news.
Why did I just do that?
I was supposed to...
All right.
I'm fine.
It's too much pressure to play this game.
I'm not playing this ever again.
Arena Assault or Fun?
I'm not doing this again.
End of Smite Thursdays?
Well, like all MOBAs, this is important too.
There was an ever-ticking-down bar
that is hovering over your head when you play a MOBA.
If you do not play, the bar continues to tick down.
Every day you play, you are keeping the bar just barely not moving at all
and maybe gaining a little bit of progress.
This game requires that...
Whoa!
If you don't play this game for a week, the bar goes to zero.
You dashed into the...
If you do not play this game for a full week,
you need to redo the whole thing all over again.
What does the bar represent?
Your skill in a MOBA.
Okay.
Before I look at chat and walk into walls, let's get back in here.
All right.
I didn't die nine times.
I'm fine.
I think it's a skill issue.
Get some better game sense, idiot.
Guys, I couldn't even tell you what all these buffs on the minimap do.
Get a better game sense.
Time that guy out for like fucking three days.
Permanently.
Ten minutes.
All right.
Is there any missing middle?
Oh, no.
There's somebody here.
You wouldn't be doing this if somebody wasn't here.
Holy shit.
I just instantly died.
Fuck.
I'm just feeding.
You can't play Conquest unless you play Conquest every single day.
That's a fact.
Like, if you are not playing Conquest, don't play Conquest.
Uh-oh.
Little brother down.
Get...
We need help.
Little brother down.
And actually, I'm going to defend myself here.
We're playing with people in the game that have like 500 games
played on the gods they're playing right now.
They're like all exes.
I'm little brother Andy.
I can't compete with this shit.
Don't let him steal it.
Don't go too far.
Where's a time machine where I can like not queue up for Conquest?
If I had three wishes, one of them would be to not play Conquest tonight.
The genie comes out of the fucking container.
What are your three wishes?
You have three.
What are they?
I don't want to...
Make it so I didn't play Conquest.
We just kept playing assault.
You sure?
Yes.
You seem a little shaky and a little pissed off and nervous.
You don't want to take five minutes to like cool down and...
No.
No, do it now.
Okay.
This guy keeps feeding my games.
We're gonna be here for like another 40 minutes and I'm gonna die like 30 fucking times.
I'm gonna die so many times.
Just accept...
Accept it at this point.
It's gonna be a horrendous embarrassing moment.
Wait, this is a custom game and I am in complete control?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Only reason why you knew where I was is because you have fucking Game Genie on.
All right.
They got Game Genie.
They're just literally watching.
They have Game Genie stream.
All right.
I'm gonna delete it.
No one's gonna hit F7.
You know how hard it is to get into a game right now?
Think about it.
There's like 10,000 people here.
If you get into a game on this stream,
you're not gonna want to hit the surrender button.
You're gonna want to play this out.
Let's see if I can pull this back.
Let me pull this back.
We're not doing very well.
Just mess with the settings.
I don't think I can do that.
They can just see everything we're doing.
She had the thanks for the 10 community subs.
Watch out.
We're gonna get collapsed on.
It seems like an airplane.
Oh, shit.
This is bad.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Everything's all right.
Kill them?
I can't.
I'm Kronos with like two items.
Click on their head.
Who's the best cookie in Cookie Run?
I don't know.
They all do the same fucking thing.
We have one and eight, two and five, zero and eight, one and seven.
But it's all my fault though because I'm bad.
I'm like, it's my fault.
You had somebody in mid.
Amaze will be playing with their eyes closed.
Remember for God, why he stopped playing this?
No, no.
I just told you I have to play like 100 games of this.
You don't just open up Smite after four years and play Conquest
with a bunch of fucking level 10 legendary players.
You are right now.
Yeah.
And I'm telling you that it's not.
It's probably a bad idea.
What?
Did we swear?
Just let them take it.
Let them win.
It's not gonna happen.
Let them dive the fucking fountain on me.
I know they want to.
No, that was not.
That was 10.
Oh my goodness.
This Bologna is like, is just carrying our whole team.
Okay.
That was a Conquest.
We're literally never doing that ever again.
You will never see that on this stream ever again.
Ever.
Not in 100 years.
So let's go back to Assault.
That was fun.
100 years will have to go by before I do that ever again.
Yeah.
I can get rid of the minimap now.
One in 10.
Yeah.
I'm not even gonna have that.
I'm not even gonna give a response to that.
I'm not gonna even give a response.
But let me tell you.
Whoever gets this password, seriously, I have no idea how you would know this.
Thanks for playing though.
That was the worst gamer moment.
That's not fair.
It's a team game.
If that was a 1v1, then sure.
But that's a team game.
Oh shit.
I don't even know what the password is.
I already forgot it.
What was it?
Okay.
I remember.
All right.
So the password, I'll give you one hint.
It's an animal.
That has to do with an animal.
Some would say my favorite animal.
I would take a guess.
And it's how I feel about this particular animal.
That's what I think about them.
Still stumped, I think.
It starts with the animal's name.
And they are something.
They are something, aren't they?
Nice job.
All right.
They're getting it.
I wonder what you're gonna...
Well, you can't play Cabrac and it's assault.
The password is frogsareawesome with no capitals and no spaces.
How long have I been streaming for?
Really?
Four hours?
Oh no.
Somebody switch with me, please.
I don't know how to play...
I don't know how to play any of the characters that are on the screen.
I don't know how to play Achilles.
But sure.
Achilles.
Does anyone else want to switch?
Okay.
I don't want to play as that guy.
Stop.
I don't know how to play that character.
No.
I have to play with the character.
At least I know what their moves do.
You get a heal with blue orbs.
Yeah, I think I figured that out pretty late last time.
I can't tell you how internally happy I am
that we're not in that Conquest game anymore.
Nothing against the players that were there.
Like, I'm sure it was a lot of fun for you guys.
It was pretty cool to play.
Well, man, I'm so glad I'm not in that game anymore.
I'm so happy to be in assault again.
Salty gamer makes windows noise.
No, I'm not even salty.
I'm just embarrassed and sad.
I'm not.
I'm kidding.
I'm fine.
It's a game of Smite.
Oh, I'm just...
I'm just so sad about that and embarrassed.
It's a game of...
It's a game of Smite.
Relax.
It's gonna be fine, Jeremy.
Who cares?
It's fine.
Let's go.
These are expensive, but I want it.
Can I just get five of them?
And mana?
Here, let's go.
Is he actually mad?
Yeah, I actually am.
I'm very mad.
Jeremy, I got a little bit of milkshake left.
Do you want it?
That's what I'm talking about.
It's exactly the kind of shit I'm talking about.
I can't have a sip of that milkshake.
I don't know who the fuck you are.
I don't know where you are.
I don't know who you are.
And now I have to think about having a milkshake
and how delicious that would be.
And now I'm pissed off now.
God, it's so hard to be me.
God, I'm so fucking annoyed right now.
All right, let's go.
It's time for fun.
I freaked him out.
I freaked him out wicked bad.
Did we not kill anybody?
We did, right?
No, we didn't.
I thought that that was going to really just jostle everybody.
I think we're okay.
All right, let's go.
Quiet.
I'm going to place my...
Oh, somebody else get that.
I don't need it.
I shouldn't just get it.
Geez.
Oh, geez.
They're going to get it.
Really?
That was so close.
That was dead.
Oh, fuck.
Backflip, please.
Who's doing that?
What character is that?
Is that Knox's move?
Who has that move?
What do I need to drink every time Jerma dies?
Don't do that.
I'm very, very concerned about your health.
Block it.
Nice.
Very nice.
That's exactly what we needed to have happen.
Good job.
That was the Achilles in the Gilgamesh.
Nice job.
I'm not even looking at the screen.
Oh, my God.
Please don't kill me.
I wasn't even looking.
I was looking at chat.
I did not realize that it was on me.
I thought that we had a bunch of minions in there.
Oh, Jesus.
Okay.
This game looks like it would be in a movie about video games
made by people who will never have played video games.
Like, but this is the thing that's on the screen
that's like the generic video game.
I think this game actually looks pretty good.
I think it's actually like a really nice looking game.
Oh, that's not good.
What was that?
Oh, get him.
What?
Oh, come on.
This is so...
We're getting stomped right now.
No, we're not.
How did I miss it?
Almost.
Get away from me.
Jesus.
Yeah, that's right.
All the people can walk into it.
That's right.
What is that?
Does this game have twitchy modes?
Yeah, I don't know what that is.
I think it's some kind of skin or something.
Oh, fuck.
I'm in trouble here.
Did I just get picked out of the air?
Oh, we're getting kind of beat here.
Oh, and four.
We're getting collectively beat, okay?
We're getting collectively beat.
I don't want to hear oh, and four.
I want to hear collectively beat Omega Low.
Collectively beat Omega Low, okay?
There we go.
All right.
We don't have a tower anymore.
That's right.
Everyone, have you ever hit an auto attack?
This game?
Yeah.
Lag.
That's why this is happening.
Just lagged out.
Get that balona.
Kill.
Move.
We got it.
I didn't get any of those.
I thought I got one.
Don't let this thing kill me, please.
That's another embarrassing moment.
Is it hitting me?
I'm so concerned.
We go?
Holy shit.
Are we going to just roll this?
No way.
Oh, this is bad.
Run.
Nice.
All right.
Good work, everybody.
Get out of here.
Fenrir on the right.
Watch that.
Watch that Fenrir.
Oh, fuck.
Fenrir behind us.
Watch that Fenrir.
Fenrir is waving at us.
Watch out.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
We don't have a tower.
No way.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I thought we had a tower.
Oh, my God.
I'm so bad.
It's just I can't play.
I just can't play.
You know what I mean?
Like I just get...
I'm just in three different places.
My brain is like in three places.
It's like I'm looking at chat.
I'm thinking of the next thing to say.
And I'm playing Smite.
All those things have to be zero.
I have to only use my brain for Smite.
If we're ever working, don't talk to me.
If you ever want me to get anything done.
If you're one of those kind of co-workers
that would walk up to my desk,
just leave me alone.
You're almost an economy car that can only...
It saves money because it only goes on three cylinders.
No, I have a...
My car is awesome.
I have a really fast car,
but I can only operate one thing at a time.
Whoops, wrong button.
Kill it.
Don't let...
Don't...
It's not worth it.
Where's the auto attack guy?
Because you're right.
God damn it.
What was I thinking?
Why are they running after me still?
I'm not going in there.
Wait a minute.
Should we?
All right.
Be careful.
What's going on?
All right.
Okay.
This is it.
All right.
What the fuck just happened?
That feeling...
That face when we could be playing Charlie
and the Chocolate Factor for PS2
and we're suffering instead in Smite.
I mean, my first like five or six...
I can't hear myself breathing.
The first like five games were fine.
I was doing pretty good.
Did I hit gamer fatigue?
The first like six games we played,
I was like 10 and four,
like 12 and six.
Is that actually...
Is that game any fun?
Should I play Charlie and the Chocolate Factor?
I do not want to be up here alone.
I'll go.
Were you queuing with randoms?
No, even the random...
Even the ones when we played with the...
Viewer games.
I was doing all right.
I have to get at least one kill here.
This is ridiculous.
Come on.
I look like the villain from Amnesia.
Oh shit.
Move.
Thanks, I guess.
All right.
We have the advantage now.
I believe we have pretty good advantage.
I want everyone to remember to keep in mind
that if you don't think you have any power
on this channel or in this community...
Remember, this stream only happened
because three people in freestream wanted to see it.
Remember that.
You don't think that you have power here.
You remind me of it.
Destiny 2.
I'm never going to play Destiny 2.
Put your feet.
Get out of here.
We actually won the game.
I got one kill.
All right.
I'm good.
Let me show you how it's done.
Remember, this stream sucks, Rufflecopter.
How dare you use like a 2007 meme in my channel?
How dare you?
All right.
Let's do another one.
We're going to do a comedy game this time.
This one's just for fun.
Password is...
I don't know.
I don't remember.
I actually don't.
Do a V2 in Conquest.
Random pick.
Everybody starts at level 20.
100,000 gold.
No pauses.
Welcome to Japan.
What's the password?
Nice.
Password is 1, 2, 3.
All right.
Here we go.
Let's go for it.
We got to stick together.
Very important.
At least we got a Bolano.
Kamazots?
He has a swoop.
I don't know.
I don't remember.
What does he do?
Isn't Kamazots actually like F tier?
Build lifesteal.
All right.
Just buy every lifesteal item.
I wonder how the ping is going to be.
All right.
We got to move quickly.
Lifesteal.
Okay.
I guess.
I don't know.
All right.
I don't know what the character does, but let's go.
Wait.
Potions.
Potions aren't going to do anything, are they?
Wards.
We need wards.
All right.
Let's go.
I'm thinking.
Honestly, I'm thinking we just dive the first tower.
Just really quickly.
Just dive the tower.
There's no way it's going to kill us.
Oh my god.
You're Freya.
All right.
Get in it, Bolano.
It caused some havoc.
It's Freya.
It's over.
Freya is so good.
Oh, man.
Freya activates her 1, her 2, and then just does the link to the past spam and just kills everybody.
Sell everything and buy defense.
I, should I?
Apollo and Freya late game.
Oh, it's over.
But this Bolona.
I got Bolona.
I need defense.
Okay.
We're going to.
Physical defense.
Magic defense.
You good?
Let's go.
I ate that ult.
Oh, this is bad.
That's not going to work.
Power.
Power, power, power, power, power.
Whatever power is, I don't care.
Lifesteal.
I don't, I don't know what any of these do.
Whatever.
What's that super potion?
Am I still dead?
What?
They could have just won the game.
How are we going to do this?
I think we just ignore them and we just pick a lane that they're not in and try to just beat the game before they do.
You know what I'm saying?
2v2 on Conquest.
I don't know the game.
Something bugged out.
I queued up with my buddy here and I don't know.
Something weird happened.
Like, it just put us in a game.
All right.
Just get in here and tank this.
Where are they?
Are they just, are they looking at items?
Why, what?
He stealthed?
What the fuck?
Where were they?
What the hell happened?
Were they hiding behind the tower?
I'm very confused.
What just happened?
Paulo goes into the sky.
Yeah, but doesn't he?
Oh, right, right, right.
But I don't, Freya was right there too.
Where did Freya come from?
I think it's going to keep the game open.
This is so eerie.
This is, something about this is just not right, right?
Well, there's no way we're going to be able to kill them.
Two late game characters that all they do is massive amounts of damage.
What am I going to do?
Jump on somebody's back and bite them?
Like, can I just see, Freya?
Can I just see something real quick?
Let me see something real quick.
Just real quick.
No, no, real quick.
I'm supposed to see something real quick.
Real quick, just real quick.
Okay, let me see.
Can I even hurt you?
Oh shit, I can hurt you.
That's so crazy.
Hold on, let me just one more thing.
Kill them both, kill them both, kill them both.
Quick, quick, quick, kill them both.
Go, go, go.
Yep, that's the one, that's the one.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
No honor?
You fight without honor.
Yeah, oh, but he did.
Kill it quick.
Oh shit.
Hey, um, hey, wait, wait, wait a second.
Wait a second.
The Bologna's, uh, lagging.
Bologna's mom was, uh, calling him.
Bologna's mom was calling.
Oh, we can go in, actually.
Go, go, go, fuck the jokes.
This is it, we win.
We just have to end the game.
I got this sick Bologna on my team.
Thank God.
Kill, kill, kill, kill.
I'm wrapping around.
Oh no, she's so strong.
She's so strong.
She just kills both of us in three hits.
Not even.
What the fuck just happened?
What?
No, no, this is not fair now.
DC?
No, that's not cool.
That was a DC.
Yeah, no, there's a DC.
There's a DC.
We can, no, no, you can't.
That's not fair.
If I had somebody else here, this would be much easier.
I'm down a player.
Oh man.
If only you were still here, you'd be able to run and finish the game.
What we should have done is you should have just stayed in the
fountain, pretended to DC.
They wouldn't have even attacked you.
Then you could have just walked down the lane right now.
Can you come back?
If you log into the game right now and just walk.
Oh man.
I'm done with this one.
That was fun.
Thank you for playing.
All right, now we're going to do a regular arena and then I'm probably going to stop.
We'll do like one or two more.
It's been a lot of fun though.
Hey, you know what?
This is actually, it's been a very long time since I've done anything like viewer game related.
We haven't done this in probably two or three years at least.
It's fun to play with you guys, it is.
Even if half of these games are just comedy games, right?
Let's do arena.
For a Japanese server, that actually ran very well.
That was weird.
All right.
Good password.
Let's see.
I can't wait for next week's my Thursday.
This is never happening ever again.
Maybe.
All right.
Here we are.
Everything looks good.
Password is an emote on Twitch.
More specifically, an emote on better Twitch TV.
But there are no capitals.
It's just the word.
All right.
Password is Pippo Happy.
Very cool.
Very good.
I want to play.
That's like, I don't know, Zeus maybe?
Don't quit.
Yeah.
It's cool.
Although I don't know for arena though.
Probably bad because you need to fill the bag with minions.
Nah, probably not good for arena.
I kind of need a guardian.
All right.
I'm going to be a guardian.
I will be...
Oh, Ares.
We already have a...
I'm so sorry.
The person even selected guardian.
Looks like we're going damage Ares.
Yep.
Let's get a victory royale.
Let's try.
That's a crazy skin.
All right.
I'm just going to build magic damage.
See if I can get some kills.
Where's my eyes?
So the next stream is going to be...
I'm trying to keep...
I'm not sure if you guys have noticed.
I'm trying to do two days a week.
Instead of just once a week.
Once a week, Andy is officially probably over.
We are now twice a week, Andy.
Nice to meet you too.
All right.
What are they?
Voidstone?
Yeah, let's do Voidstone.
So whether that's Saturday, Sunday usually.
Or randomly during the week.
I'm trying to get back to two days a week.
I don't foresee a period where we ever will get back to three or four days a week.
But two is absolutely fine.
I think I'm very capable at this point to do it.
And the idea is that those will be on the weekend.
But as sometimes, you know, sometimes those plans change.
Current plan now is to stream probably on Monday or Tuesday from now.
Oh, shit.
Already?
All right.
Let's do it.
We all did the same exact move.
How did that miss?
Really?
All right.
I need to get blink.
It's really important.
Get him.
Oh, I'm stuck.
I killed somebody.
Who did I kill?
Magical power, physical protection.
Yeah, Andy, I can't get it yet.
I'll get that'll be the next thing I get, though.
For sure.
What are these little things?
What am I going to play after this?
I don't know what the next thing I'll do is.
There are a bunch of options.
We'll see.
Oh, I thought you're going to walk backwards.
This is bad.
No.
So mad at that guy.
I'm infuriated at that guy.
They all get beads.
They probably did.
Outer Wilds.
No, I don't think so.
GTA.
You know what?
I cannot hit this shit to save my life right now.
Maybe I will play GTA.
That sounds actually like a lot of fun.
All right.
We're going to do GTA next, I think.
Kill somebody.
Oh, that's annoying.
Grand Theft Andy.
It seems like it might be fun.
Which one do I want?
I wanted this one.
This one here.
No, not GTA RP.
I would just play regular GTA online.
Do like the casino update or something.
Just it would just be mayhem.
Play the steam games.
That's oh, yeah, I could do that too.
That's absolutely what we could do.
No.
What about no umbrellas allowed?
That's another one too.
There's options.
You cannot run from a reach.
Oh, that was a good one.
All right.
Can we do this?
Can we pull it back?
Yeah.
M Dicky Knights.
Absolutely.
Yeah, we got plenty of stuff to do.
Oh, this is where I die.
There we go.
Blink.
This is the good shit.
You do blink, hit four, and immediately run away.
What about Community Content Knights?
Community Content Knights can never return due to the DMCA stuff.
Those of you that remember those fondly,
we've watched almost entire uninterrupted scenes of Star Wars.
We cannot do that anymore.
I didn't get it.
All right.
Here we go.
Are you ready?
Ready?
Watch this.
Oh, it's a cooldown.
What happened?
What is wrong with you?
What's wrong with you?
I just can't pay attention to anything.
Geez, man.
I literally can't pay attention to anything.
I got it this time.
Kill him.
Oh, my God.
I didn't mean to press that.
Too much damage.
Oh, Thor.
Thank you.
Are you going to do anything for Halloween?
I'm actually not sure.
That's a good question.
I mean, I could do VR stuff again,
but I feel like I've done that the last couple of years.
Just do horror games.
Yeah, that's easy.
Should be fun and simple enough, right?
Maybe I'll wear a costume or something.
Oh, I didn't.
I did not do that at a good time.
What about public domain movie night?
There needs to be enough public domain movies for me to care about.
Free Stooges?
I don't think the Free Stooges is a public domain.
Didn't we look that up?
But yes, absolutely.
I would love to.
If we can get a good and I don't want.
OK, here's let me rephrase that.
I want to watch old movies from like the 40s, like 50s.
I don't just because a movie's public domain.
I mean, if it came out in like 2018 or something,
I don't I want to watch the old shit.
We're losing very badly.
How though?
Nosferatu?
Let's compile a list.
I'll do that.
Maybe we'll do that for Halloween.
Yeah, either the night before or the night.
At some point, a day or so before Halloween, we'll do that.
It sounds like a fun Halloween stream.
No.
Oh, boy.
I just walked into everybody.
I'm just barely paying attention.
I got to stop this.
Why am I playing this game like it's a fucking clicker?
Like, oh, yeah, just like the glance over at it every now and then.
How many grandmas do I have cooking in the bakeries?
I don't know.
Physical power and magical power.
What?
OK, this is not over yet.
We get anybody?
Holy shit.
I think we're going to lose.
If I were to take a wild guess, I would say we're going to lose the game.
I've never seen triple life steal Aerie.
Well, come on.
Give it a try one day.
Maybe it'll work out for you.
You see that, you know, the funniest part about that.
I didn't even know that's what I was doing.
You did.
I didn't even know that's what I was doing until I just looked at it.
What are you going to eat after the stream?
Oh, probably tacos.
That sounds good, right?
How did that miss?
It went between the two of them.
I don't know what's going on.
I mean, this is a game for nerds.
I'll make sure I'll never play it again.
You're right.
I'll make sure I'll never play this again.
I didn't know that.
What is the way that nerds play this game?
Oh, I'm never playing it.
Are you kidding me?
Yeah, no, fuck that.
Never playing this again.
I did not know that.
So let me just make sure I make that clear.
How come there's not a nice costume?
All right, what do you say? One more?
Yeah, let's do one more.
We'll do, uh, assault.
Those are the most fun.
Good.
All right.
Off.
And password.
Password is a related to somebody in space, a movie that takes place in space.
A series of movies that take place in space.
This is a character from that series.
They're in no spaces.
Password was Darth Vader.
No spaces.
I don't want to play this character.
I don't know how this character plays.
Thank you so much.
You literally just saved the last game of the stream.
How many people are still watching?
There's actually a very fair amount of people still here.
I'm actually very surprised about that.
Thanks for sticking around.
Just playing some Smite, just messing around.
It's not a big deal.
Sometimes you have to remember what a video game looks like.
Smite 2015.
What is that?
Let us bet on this one?
Sure.
Open it up.
Does my team win this game?
Seems like we have, we're up against a legendary Belona,
but we do have two level.
I don't know what that number that was.
Cool down.
Absolutely.
And of course, Aegis.
It's just the guaranteed pick.
Let's go.
We're going to win.
Don't let us down all in on me.
I wouldn't do that.
Where are they?
Oh my God.
They're hiding over here.
Aren't they?
Where's the other team?
Nice try.
Where is everybody?
Didn't that go much further than it?
That was weird.
Uh oh.
I know the fucking tactics with Kulkulkan.
Don't think I don't.
I do remember when Kulkulkan was out, Kwong.
That's very old.
Get away from me.
What?
Retreat.
Jerma, look over here.
Look over here.
Leave me alone.
I don't want to look.
I thought the Sobek was going to go get that.
Hey, watch this.
We doing this?
Get.
Watch out.
Need that cool down.
The thing is, it takes so long to get that back.
Jerma, look behind you.
Yeah.
Be heck up.
Just cool down in mana.
That's all you do with Kulkulkan.
Get in the chopper.
Hey.
Oh, we're going to all pog mana heal.
Nice job.
Make it so the lane minions hit that.
Did that not hit the Sobek?
Oh, come on, Gwyn.
Give me a break.
That's going to get...
I'm going to get two kills there.
At least one.
All right.
Let's go.
Jerma of Isolation is amazing as well.
Especially on Kulkulkan.
Who's left?
Just the set.
I'm so glad that I traded the soul with that guy.
With the sniper rifle.
I'm not playing Neith.
Get that shit out of here.
Those little firework things are such a distraction.
Ooh.
Oh, shit.
Where the fuck did you come from?
What?
Why does the person keep...
Why can they just do that?
What?
Where did the person even come from?
Was that Belona?
He walked right by me.
Did he blink?
How did I not see him?
I don't know.
This game takes a shitload of brain power.
I don't have any right now.
You have to understand something.
When you cross 30 years old,
your brain slows down every year till you get to 80.
My brain has declined since I was like 25.
It's real.
I'm closer to 40 than I am 25.
I'm closer to 40 than I am 30.
I'm playing incredibly well for a fucking 40-year-old.
Check that out.
Kill him, kill him, kill him, kill him, kill him.
Oh.
Damn it.
He's so close.
How old are you?
I'm 36.
I thought that was common knowledge.
Goodbye.
He just said you were 40.
Now I said I was closer to 40 than I am 40.
Stop.
Don't let him get away.
You age pretty well.
I feel like I have aged pretty well.
I think I'm aging pretty gracefully.
You could use that.
You're going to give it...
Did you try to steal it?
Oh, no, no, no.
I see.
Remember, stop talking about how old you are.
It makes me feel old.
Oh, he's...
It's way too late as top 10 videos of streamers you used to watch.
It's like, you feel old yet?
Number nine.
German985.
And it's a picture of me from, like, paparazzi getting out of the car.
And I have a bald head, gray hair, like, big bottle glasses.
Oh, my God.
This is what happens when I talk.
It's to hit somebody.
Yeah, I think.
This is very even.
20 years...
Number four.
The sus guy.
I don't think Among Us is going to make it another 20 years,
keeping the same popularity it has now.
But I would love to be corrected.
It's not even popular anymore now.
It still is.
You can gauge that...
All right.
Before you say that.
Oh, God.
No!
I have to...
Well, let me make...
Let me now make the point.
You have to judge that based on how many Halloween costumes you see this year.
If you see, personally, you walking around,
more than five Among Us character inflatable costumes,
it's still as popular as it was.
Gonna be squid game.
Yeah, it's gonna be squid game.
It's gonna be Among Us.
And a bunch of really in-character Dark Knight jokers.
That's every Halloween party.
What about sexy Among Us?
What do you mean?
Win the game?
I think we're in a pretty...
All right.
If I pay attention, maybe we'll do it.
I was gonna do it, but now it's not necessary.
I think...
How are you still...
The person's alive still.
Uh-oh.
Enemy has left the game.
Watch it.
Nice.
R.I.P. doubters.
Don't say that yet.
I've seen plenty of assault games where it's 4v5,
and the other team gets destroyed.
Get!
It's not over yet.
Not yet.
Now it actually might be over.
Very possible.
Treat!
We can kill this thing.
Good game.
All the doubters, yeah.
All right.
One more, one more.
One more.
I wanna do one more.
Last one.
This is it.
It's the final game of the night.
I'm gonna do a assault.
Password is going to be...
This is all lowercase.
Lowercase only.
I'm not gonna give any hints.
I wanna see if anybody gets it.
Please tell Hashouse or GoGo to update their online hours.
I told my parents to get the blue cheeseburger that you recommended,
and they were closed even though the website said open.
Oh, shit.
Password is omega lol with no spaces, no capitals.
Yeah, all right.
I'm not...
I have no affiliation with Hashouse or GoGo.
I just like the place.
I can't, like, rent a skin.
I'm sorry.
I know Sun Wukong's moves.
I don't know Apua.
Is it Apua?
Who is that?
Is it Donkey Kong?
I can't believe you're playing this game.
The power of three people in pre-stream chat.
Don't ever feel like you cannot influence my decisions.
Actually, three or four people in pre-stream, like,
yesterday, the day before.
That's the reason why we're doing this.
These skins are insane.
Oh, boy.
This is gonna be bad.
One, two, three, three level 10 legendary players.
We have two.
Diamond servers.
Ah, you have to...
These...
Yeah, it's like 500 games.
I'm so outclassed right now.
I feel like I got rushed and carried through a place I'm not supposed to be.
What do they have?
Physical, physical, physical.
It's all physical.
All right.
Yeah.
Let's go with this.
Sovereignty.
My favorite part about this is this.
When he goes,
TRANSFORM.
Say it.
He goes,
TRANSFORM.
Yeah, I gotta get him to say it.
The tank already has sovereignty.
All right.
I'll get another one.
Say it.
Don't ever do a funny noise.
It'll make me LOL.
Did it work?
No, try again.
I have no mana left.
Again?
Careful.
TRANSFORM.
Stunning.
Stunned him.
Yes, tank.
I feel like I'm playing Kingdom Hearts.
The AI characters are just talking to each other.
Say it.
I'm just waiting for him to go.
Don't give up.
Sora.
Attack.
They're gonna jump on us.
Don't touch me.
No, he didn't say it.
I gotta go back.
I got my help ready.
I'm ready to go in.
Say the word.
Say it.
It's done.
Fuck it.
Go in.
Let's go.
Clean it up.
Physical protection.
Crowd control reduction.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
Oh, it's that...
Is that Sir Finley Markleton?
I love how people hate that.
Can I change my bet?
We're gonna...
Oh.
Ultimate is ready.
I don't know how to do the key combination,
so I just set it on spring.
Oh, my ult's not even ready.
I don't know.
I feel like we're all larping right now.
Kill.
Uh-oh.
Watch out.
A guy's coming for you.
It's Loki.
He's a trickster.
What?
I tried to press the fucking button.
I could have killed all three of them.
If I just...
He's like a five-year-old having a tantrum.
You want to hear a tantrum?
I'll give you a tantrum.
I'll show you a tantrum.
That's a cool skin.
Oh, yep.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Oh.
This is hurting me.
Whoever did that...
What?
I don't know what move that was,
but holy shit, it was good.
Let's hit...
Ice cream is on its way.
Michael's been such a good boy this year.
Open up your gift.
Probably aren't you?
I'm gonna die.
I'm dead.
I thought you got hacked.
Good.
Come on, Cerberus.
Cerberus, what?
What is the Cerberus doing?
Got it.
Finally.
We're almost at a victory here.
You gotta go out on a good one.
I got it.
As I said, that would've been embarrassing.
He's dead.
Where is he?
Is he dead?
Yeah, we got him.
Yeah.
This is dangerous.
This is too dangerous.
I don't like this.
I'm out.
No, I'm leaving.
It's too scary.
There's too many.
There are too many.
I'll help you.
Oh, man.
Oh, kill this motherfucker.
He's got like no health.
Excuse me?
Why was he...
I couldn't hurt him.
I don't know what the fuck I was doing there.
Oh, no.
Stop.
I don't want that.
Favorite God, Anubis.
Stone of Fall.
It's OP on you.
Stone of Fall?
Stone of Fall.
Kill anybody's game.
Everybody's here.
They don't have very much health.
We could really cause a little bit of a problem for them here.
Oops.
Oh, actually, that was amazing.
That guy thought I was an idiot.
I've been so...
I've been playing so poorly
that he thought the decoy was actually me.
And he's like, this is definitely Jeremy.
He's an idiot.
Ouch.
It's gonna hurt.
The ultimate long con.
That's Loki, right?
That acid.
Oh, we don't get cocky here.
We have a tower still.
We don't have to get cocky.
That's from the Loki rework.
I feel like they re-did Loki three or four times.
Cut!
Where am I going?
Oh, shit.
I'm in trouble.
What was I gonna buy this?
Yeah.
I think we won.
Oh, no.
I keep pressing yes.
I don't know why.
I think it's funny.
All right.
Can you just, as Kuzenbo,
can you just say yes, the loud one over and over again?
Okay, cocky.
It's just sound effects.
That's just a cookie crisp.
Cookie crisp.
Oh, I was being cocky.
I was being cocky.
I am an alien character.
I am an alien.
It's me, an alien.
I am an alien character.
It's me.
Look out.
Take me to your leader.
I am an alien in every game.
In every piece of media.
Fuck it.
Don't let him out.
I turned into a lion.
I don't want to.
My KD.
Somebody else die.
I don't want my KD.
My KD is bad.
Get him.
Hit this guy.
Hit the guy.
One more.
All right.
But this one's gonna be a comedy one.
The last one.
Here we go.
This is the last one.
This one you're seeing right now is going to be the last one.
Last one.
Asper was the last one.
Thanks for playing.
I don't know.
I'm gonna re-roll.
I can't re-roll.
I thought you could.
Sure.
I'll play Sun Wukong.
No, that's too much pressure.
They have voice lines too.
I don't know if you should do a bet for this one.
This could be anybody's game.
It's just...
Everyone's gonna be level 20 with 100,000 gold.
It's gonna be an absolute nightmare.
We already won.
We win.
Osiris Horus Bakasura.
Yeah.
If we don't win this game, come on.
Although, find out.
All right.
This.
What do they got?
They got a lot of physical, physical, physical, physical.
Yeah, all physical.
Just build only physical protection.
Are we getting that?
I got it.
Okay.
Sure.
Whatever you say.
No comedy gamble?
I still have to damage them?
Or what if I just stay alive permanently?
What if we just...
Let's go in the tower now.
Let's just take the tower right now.
Why would we not just take the tower right now?
Let's go.
Take the tower now.
Go.
All right.
Get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out.
We got it.
All right.
Everybody out.
Shit.
Oh, we're gonna lose.
I forgot...
I forgot that we all have a 60 second timer.
No, this doesn't count.
That doesn't count.
Are you gonna leave it alive?
Oh, you...
Okay.
They won't want to keep this going.
That's the biggest mistake they ever made.
That was a big mistake.
As long as we move as a party, we're gonna be fine.
Oh, excuse me.
What just happened?
Why did they all do the Warcraft 3 town portal?
What?
Since when is that in the game?
Horus's ult can do that.
Oh, no.
It's still winnable?
Yeah, it is.
Our characters are way better for this composition.
We just need to not get teleported on.
Double mercy.
Well, there's no feeding because everyone's level 20 and has infinite gold.
There's no feeding.
It's just who has a better team comp at this point.
We just have to win one team fight.
We can do it.
Are they gonna do that again?
No.
All right.
No, no, no.
Look, he's got half health.
They're all waiting on the right side.
They're already...
Look, they're right here.
I...
Wait, how'd they get behind us?
Come here.
He's gonna jump around.
I'm gonna cut him off this way.
Fuck him.
Just go to the tower.
Who cares?
Ah!
Oh, I thought that was high.
Remember, your viewer count retreated.
It's...
I don't...
It's fine.
I don't care.
I'm surprised that more than 5k people stuck around to watch
a fucking dingus play smite for five hours.
We got all five?
No, it's all good.
Look, I know a lot of people are not into these games.
It's fine.
It's cool.
I get it completely.
Don't worry.
We just need somebody to overextend for a second and we'll win the game.
One of them's gonna get super cocky.
They're gonna get up here.
They're gonna try to attack and run away.
We're gonna collapse on them.
Uh-oh.
Someone's getting a little cocky.
Getting a little bored.
Wants to make something happen.
There it is!
Run away.
Never mind.
Oh my god.
What the hell?
Why do they all get Star Trek themed?
Oh god.
We're in trouble.
All right.
That's it.
That was fun.
Except for when I played the one game of Conquest that was not fun.
It wasn't its own way.
That was uh smite.
It's a fun game.
I recommend you play it if you like those kinds of games.
That was smite Thursdays.
Next Thursday.
You're not gonna see this ever again.
We will only play smite again if I can get some more...
I was gonna say skins.
That's all that matters.
Maybe you'll see it again.
It's fun just to fuck around.
Join my game clan.
No.
That's gonna be it.
So I will see you guys on probably Monday or Tuesday.
Check the sus the next day or two.
We are gonna play...
What did I say we're gonna play?
Something really specific.
What was it?
GTA, right.
We'll play Grand Theft Auto online.
And then we're gonna prepare the...
We'll prepare some more public domain movie stuff for Halloween.
What about Paladins?
Eh, I don't think so.
But yeah.
I'll see you guys in three or four days or so.
See you soon.
Thanks for sticking around.
I know it's not one of those games that a lot of people really want to sit down and watch.
I know.
But I figured we'd play some viewer games and just hang out for four or five hours.
So that's exactly what we did.
See you in a few days.
Thanks for watching guys.
Take care of yourselves.
Always a pleasure.
Oh, I also got something else to tell you about too.
We are going to get incoming some new BloorDow music.
And some new emotes and animated emotes.
BloorDow's gonna make a bunch of stuff.
As you know, BloorDow has made all the music you've heard on this channel.
These original music.
We're gonna get some more tracks.
I'm incredibly excited for that.
Because it's very, very obvious.
I don't even need to state this.
BloorDow's music.
All of them bangers.
All of them.
New sub badges as well.
That's right.
You're a funny fellow.
Hey, thanks.
Not the dollhouse theme.
No.
That's the one thing the original song that BloorDow did not make.
But we're gonna get another probably two or three new tracks.
We're still working on what the sub badges are gonna be.
Because there's years worth of subs now.
How does it feel to be a soulless streamer?
What?
Am I soulless?
I hope none of you think that.
You really think I'm a soulless guy?
I hope not.
I think I have a soul.
I think so.
That's like the glowy thing that's in the middle of your chest, right?
Thanks for subbing as always.
Thanks everybody.
We'll see you in a few days.
Thanks for playing Smite.
Thanks for humoring me.
Because this is not something I typically will do on this channel.
Thanks for watching nonetheless.
We'll see you soon.