This is gonna be fun. Uh, find the video game. No, what are you doing? My PS, my PS is fucked.
I don't know where it is. This is not, this is bad. Where is, I'm never liking. There it is.
Where'd the cam go? I turned it off. Boo boo boo, Jeremy you stink, Jeremy you stink.
So those of you that don't know, uh, as of tomorrow, tomorrow after tomorrow's stream,
I'm gonna be gone for a few days. Because the Halloween stream is fairly elaborate.
And it's, I'm gonna be across the world setting it up. There will be three activities
on that stream. Not just the slime stuff. A couple others as well. Yeah, 31st exactly.
Dude, he's doing Siren one, two, and three in a row. No. What time is the stream gonna start?
Um, probably somewhere in the afternoon Eastern. I would say, this just screamed in my ear.
Uh, probably at some point, two, three, four o'clock. I'm gonna lock it down once I know
exactly what's going on. Probably around three o'clock Eastern. Between three and four I think.
Oh wait, my money, my money card.
It's probably gonna be around four, yeah, it's maybe even a little later than four depending on
how difficult it is to get this whole thing set up over a couple days.
Load. Think we're good, right? Oh this, wait, what's stage, stage five?
Which is the airplane one?
Oh no, this one breaks, this one breaks. People actually like this game? Yeah.
I like this game. So it's four.
I just, I just wanted to play this song. I don't know, I don't know why. It's a little
bit about just hitting triangle over and over again. He's doing it for me. Let's go.
Oh, this is in Siren. Yeah, I gotta update that. I've been out of practice.
This is crazy Siren gameplay. That makes me laugh. Sorry.
I got the skills to beat you and knock you out.
From cool to bad.
That was the info, but look at me, I'm learning just how to fly.
I'm still wondering when we get to quest. I'm hungry, I'm sleepy, don't wanna die.
Thought I got cool. The very end, damn it.
That was gooder than good. Patience. Thank you. I'm in a hurry. Need to move on.
This game is so fun. Let me change it to that. What was another good one?
There's another one that I really liked.
Stage two. Yeah, that was it.
Wait, there are more. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
there. Stage two, Lamy Parappa team. Manual controller auto. Let's go. I broke something.
Wow. Look two. I got two controllers here. See?
Carry the equipment, buy snacks, and give us foot massage.
Put the PlayStation upside down. No, I don't have to do that yet. So this is, it's dual?
This one is hard. Okay, so Lamy controller one. Oh, this song is awesome. Okay, here we go.
Let's get on, let's get on. Who's doing this? This has been my long desire. This has been my long
desire. Baby, you gotta pull it out quick. Bring it down without a doubt. Bring it down without a doubt.
Oh,
yeah.
Are we stealing points?
Mike, you better not go down too tight and get ready for the fire.
Push the button and just pull the chain and I'm comfortable.
I'm gonna get stuck.
You can tell Catherine I am.
What the fuck?
This is, uh, Lamy Parappa.
This is the last.
Forever?
I'm not a liar.
Who won?
Okay, that was pretty through now.
Okay. Oh, yeah.
Is there any more Parappa levels? Like that I can just do? Parappa levels?
Is it just one?
Oh, I remember I got, uh, the game fucked up here.
Stage two Lamy Ramy battle.
Auto level. I need to do this so I want to do the other Parappa levels.
Holy shit, what is going on here? Auto assemble player.
I remember this broke. Let's do auto.
All right, let's do stage, I don't know, stage two, stage four versus, uh, AI.
Let's go.
It won't break in two player.
But then I have to, like, switch controls and that's annoying.
Oh, right, it's this awesome, cool song.
I just did this one, but I like this one.
Oh, that's my first, that's my alter ego.
Never give it up, soldier.
Take this one, put it on the track, show what you got, soldier.
That was awful.
How do you do that?
That was dumb.
I'm good.
It's always my brain.
Take this one, put it on the track, show what you got, soldier.
Still ahead.
I got a few notes there.
Take this one, put it on the track, show what you got, soldier.
That's gonna be cool. What if I get cool as a twin?
Now it's time to move on.
It only gets much harder, so carry on.
Think I'm bold now.
I got the skills to beat you and knock you out.
He's a sparrows.
It's always my brain.
Roll rock, clap and scream it.
I want my sheets.
We got to zero points.
You lose.
I just got super insane.
Insane.
Like, I've heard that exact voice.
Then Lemmy just said
Total Distortion.
Total Distortion is one of the people you sell videos to.
Yep.
That was weird.
I want to do the Parappa shit.
I want to do the Parappa levels that I haven't done.
Lemmy and Parappa team.
I'll just do auto. No, but I want to do that.
You think I can get through this without it breaking?
Let's see what happens.
It's had like four days to rest.
I've got to get in a different category.
I've got to get cool on this and stay on cool.
Sound of the alarm work.
Alright, let's try to get this thing.
That was good.
That wasn't even bad.
I could hardly hear him.
He's like speaking through a wall.
I'm getting some crazy here.
Tool.
Boy, break the game.
I can actually do the other Parappa levels that we didn't see because the disc would break.
Don't ask me how this got fixed.
I have no idea.
He was just splitting the screen the whole time.
So now, what's level two?
I don't know.
I have no idea.
He was just splitting the screen the whole time.
So now,
what's level two?
I don't know how this got fixed.
I changed the disc speed.
Don't hold your breath though.
It might happen right now.
You played an entire whole game about how you want to eat wheat.
The whole noodles thing.
I thought I got stuck.
Shit.
It's the baby level, isn't it?
Why is it always the baby?
It's just above the disc.
I'm not putting the PlayStation upside down.
It's in the PS2 right now.
That'll break it.
I'm going to try to skip the cutscene.
That shit again.
Put it on its side.
I'll do that.
See if that fixes it.
It's on its side.
Toothpaste on disc.
No, I'm looking forward to
Jackbox tomorrow, to be honest.
That should be a lot of fun before I leave.
Because it's all new stuff, right?
I haven't used the toothpaste trick in forever.
I actually brought up the toothpaste thing
and everybody yelled at me.
They said, don't do that. That's a bad idea.
I was like, what's going on?
I thought it worked.
It actually works.
Fixed my melee disc.
Yeah, you told me I was wrong.
Okay, here we go.
Let's see if I can do this.
Skip the loading
and just see if we can get to the game.
Shit.
That's a rest.
That's a rip. That is a rest in peace here.
Damn it.
It's all good.
At least I get to play the airplane level one more time.
TS1's got the better laser.
Do I really want to do that?
I don't know. Do I really want to?
Alright, hold on.
Yes.
He's motivated.
I don't want to see
what's there.
I'm interested to see what
the actual other Parappa levels are.
When am I going to go back to do this again?
Probably never.
This is probably the last time.
One of the last times you're going to see
the PlayStation 1
even turned on.
There's still a few
things that I want to do.
But we've done a lot.
There's a lot that I'm forgetting.
But for the most part,
maybe this might be one of the last times
you see it.
Never say never. We'll see.
Alright, let's see if we can get through this.
That's a great sound.
What happened to the startup sound?
PS4 doesn't really have one.
I mean, kind of.
It's more of like a...
What is it?
You know you don't know what...
This is bright as...
Why does this brighten up?
This is really bright.
Alright, I'm just going to skip the cutscene.
New content.
Let's go.
I win?
I think I'm wet.
I think you're wet.
I think you're neck.
I think I'm neck.
I need to go, you know.
Can't hold much longer, you know.
Are you the person who's never ever ever ever?
Mama, mama, mama.
Mama, mama, mama, mama.
Now put these kids to sleep, will ya?
Hey, hey, papa, don't you think I'm good?
Now, can I please have my chicken?
Now, can I please have my food?
How do you get cool on this one?
These kids to sleep, will ya?
Papa makes a sound, can...
Mama, can I have the food?
This is freaking me out because...
This is that Papa song.
What is it? I'll get it this time.
I'm going to get cool right now.
Mama, mama, mama.
Papa, papa, papa, papa...
Mama!
Mama, can I have the food?
Mama, mama, mama.
Chicken, no, chicken, no, no, no.
I'm for a Women'seled chicken, ba-ba-ba-ba.
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa
Mama can I have a body toy? Mama can I have a body toy?
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa
Next level!
This is extra sacred fucking content.
This is secret.
...
Rapa, please don't hold the baby like that.
Skip it!
...
Skip it! I don't care.
I'm sorry, we have to skip it.
I don't, I'm not getting locked out here.
It's the airplane one.
Come on!
Same as last time, yeah.
The Playstation 2 plays the airplane level.
Switch back and forth, that's what we did last time.
And it was a pain in the ass.
Although, they're both right here now, so...
Pokemon doesn't understand technology. He doesn't get it. He doesn't know what he's doing.
What does this plug into?
We'll plug this in, without the laptop.
Who did this?
Why is this here?
Why is there a printer on the floor?
These are all very important questions.
I did this.
Oops.
That was a full drink. Fuck it. Who cares?
Here we go!
Ba ba ba ba, ba ba ba ba ba.
Ba ba ba ba, ba ba ba ba.
Ba ba!
Use a coaster?
Oh, I use a coaster. Absolutely.
This is actually a pretty nice desk.
Use burrito blade 2 as a coaster.
That's not gonna happen.
Why would you want me to do that?
All the games that you've seen tonight have been worth playing.
You know what I'm saying?
Don't skip it this time.
Oh, I'm gonna skip it.
I'm gonna skip it as fast as I can.
Something bright this time.
Nice.
Just like it normally does.
Different kind of song, too.
Not as fast.
I dig it.
Set up the lights, turn on the lights.
Fasten the seatbelts for the fight.
Fasten your seatbelts for the fight.
Get up in the morning, run on the track.
Show me what you got, soldier.
Get up for the morning, get up, run on the track.
For the morning, get up for the morning.
Get up for the morning, get up for the morning.
All right, Mom.
Fine.
Run on the track, run on the track.
Show me what you got, soldier.
Get up for the morning, get up for the morning.
Get up for the morning, you must be bored.
Me?
Run run on the track.
get up for the morning, show me what you got, get up for the morning
what's happened the last time?
he just got hit in the head
I thought that milk was shit
this plane is going down
Come on
Thanks for watching the stream everybody, it was fun. Let's see if I can do this blindfold
No, that's not I'm gonna hit loads the first part is it?
Upside down
Oh
Hit me with it what hit me with it hit me with it
Came up
Yeah, thanks put the disk in upside down and then I break my
$44 PlayStation 2 you can get a digital version of dumbjammer. Lamy. How?
Is it it's not on PSN. Is it on like the PlayStation 3 PSN?
Well, I know I can emulate it, but I bought the disk thinking it was gonna fucking run in the system
Just play the thing for 15 seconds and you can buy a new one. Well, I like playing on original hardware
All right, that's gonna be it for tonight
If you bought the actual game already, you shouldn't worry about emulating it. No, but I have to get the control. I feel like alright
Let me show you why that this is something that I have to like plug in a ps4 controller
Right. So if I emulate this game, I have to like emulate the controller which is like ps4
Which is dual shock, you know what I mean? Like it's just it's annoying. I already have all the original hardware
I have a
Capture device to pull in old hardware. I have all the old hardware. I have all the controls and everyone. I just do it
I have it
I have like a capture card that's designed for old consoles
Why am I afraid of technology? You see the fucking goddamn technology that's down here capturing the goddamn game
Dude, I got cords
I got a whole capture device down here
Who needs a fancy phone when the landline works?
Thank you streamer
Thanks streamer
The landline does work
Come on. That was that was the only disc that has done that. It's the only one that's done it. We've had
we've played like
Honestly, we've probably played like
PlayStation 1 and playstation 2 games as the only one that was scratched
Somehow come on. Can we just enjoy the waves of the ps2? Yeah, actually I gotta pee really bad
Uh, I haven't gone to pee this whole time
In over five hours, so i'm gonna pee we'll come back we'll do the bits
And we will hang up
I will see you guys in
Five minutes maybe
See you soon. Hello. I have returned
Put the ps2 sound back on really well. We're about to do the little outro now. We got the cool music, man
Hey, thank you phylactery lich
for your 270 subs
Because this shit won't ever update I even tried to go in here and fix this too and it wouldn't work
What a piece of crap. What a piece of fucking
Crap
No, yeah, that'll be it for tonight. We kind of jumped around all over the place
We played four games tonight. Can you believe that?
And we beat two of them. So for the next
Week or so, let's go over this
So tomorrow we're gonna do jackbox
And then I have to get ready to leave
So after tomorrow's stream you'll see me again on 31st
for halloween
The special halloween stream that's gonna happen and then I will be back a few days later
obviously have to
Clean up and i'm probably gonna visit some family while i'm down there. So
I'll be back a couple days. Maybe three days after that four days after that
and then
after all that
once the halloween stream is
Gone
I kind of wanna i'm either gonna start dead rising
or
Uh outer worlds
I'm not sure which one
One of them will be started
I probably will start with outer worlds just because
it's new
and
I kind of want to play it just see how it is
And then somewhere in that somewhere in that week, there'll be the other community content night
So yeah, there'll be community content night dead rising and outer worlds
After the halloween stream is what you can expect
And that sounds like a good plan to me, but
for right now
Let's go over the bits and the community subs
Thank you for watching everybody
See you tomorrow as always and let's go back
Back back back back back back back back back back to sad vega. Thanks for the 250
It happened again and it's your fault. Why is everything gonna be my fault?
I had a dream about streamers last night
I was on jeopardy and I was getting my ass kicked by some five-year-old zoomer rapping baby
what
Until double jeopardy came and it was vine sauce question
And it was a vine sauce. Wait, where'd that just go? Here it is
It was a vine sauce question and a final jeopardy question, which the answer was germa 985
Well, did you win?
Did you win the game?
I did. Well, there you go
As long as you've won
That sounds pretty good
Thanks for the dream
the 250
Gnarly, thanks for the 250. I had a dream last night. Oh my fucking god
We're gonna start to get fake ones here now
This is gonna become a thing. I can already predict it. I had a dream last night
Don't worry. Not about you. Here we go where I ate a high high
Class restaurant with my family in the menus. They gave us were screenshots of twitch chat
Like one user wrote spaghetti and meatballs 899
Chicken alfredo
I
The funny thing is that they wrote the menu in someone else's twitch chat
So they were just pogchamps and lul's woven between
Should I stop watching streams before bed?
That is so
Dream, you know
That is such a dream thing to happen
That's hilarious
Um, you don't have to stop watching streams before bed. Just stop having streams play while you are sleeping
I know a lot of you guys have your phones or your ipads in bed and you just fall asleep and there's just it's still going
Put like a sleep timer on your phone. So after like an hour of no activity, the thing will just turn off
They used to make tvs like this back in the day
You could set it so to make sure the tv would turn off after like 40 minutes or something
Now I know the hardware I got all this hardware, you don't think I got hardware under here
I know it's a boo. I know boomer, but you see have you seen my hardware, dude?
It's a tangled mess of cables that my vr is still plugged in and I haven't used it
It's still tangled up in there, but there's a bunch of fucking wires of technology. You don't think I know technology
Vr never again. No i'm waiting for this i'm waiting for them when there's too much vr to ignore it
You know what i'm saying? So like let's do like 20 games
I'm waiting for wireless high quality vr
um
It's possible
But thank you gnarly for the dream. I think i'm thanking people for their dreams
Thank you for the 250
Uh rogue of mv. Thanks for the 2000 bits earlier
20 bucks from rogue of mv
Here's the ransom chat has to set you free now
Thank you. Appreciate it. Thanks for the $20 ransom
Appreciate that. It's 2000 bits. It's a lot. Thank you
Mostly lost. Thanks for the 250 the year are only two paper marios and anyone who says differently is kidding themselves
What's the third one three?
What's the third one?
super paper mario
Yeah, because it's super this this paper mario and this paper mario
Like the thousand year old door or something, right? What is it the 10,000 year old door?
What was it called? Yeah, that was right. All right. We have another one. Here's an image. It's uh, this is from airless
Thanks for 500 bits airless
And they say gerbas smirk
Why is this so small? Oh, I just look odd
Anthony bantony became relevant again is what some of what he said
I did that. I just look strange that doesn't that looks like i'm missing the lego hair. No, I do have the lego hair
But that's the mouth mouth is too big and the nose is too long. The eyes are too big
Something weird about that photo
Uh, thank you airless though for the 500 bits need a lego stream
Uh, anyways dark soul. Thanks for the 500 bits really enjoying the streams and thanks for doing them
Thank you for watching was awesome meeting you at the supermarket today. What and really like what you did with your hair
Right. Okay. I see what you're doing here
uh
You even let me get a great picture with you
Thanks a lot
You motherfucker
God damn it. I'm shaving my head. I'm gonna actually be bald
You won't I know I want it's a lie. I would never do that
I would look like a fucking serial killer if I ever shaved my head
Smelly boy. Thanks for the 250. Hey germ. I'm still loving the content. You're such an amazing streamer
So what are your honest opinions on sherbert as opposed to ice cream?
I think it's great
I think there's a time to have sherbert and it's time to have ice cream. I think they have both incredibly talented ice creams
desserts
They both deserve
your time
I do love sherbert, especially arren sherbert. He's a centrist
Sherbert tastes good and ice cream tastes good
What what what do you want me to say here?
What have you have you seen the hardware on my desk? Do you know what's under there? There's a capture card
There's another device that feeds
Into another capture card that is specifically for old video games and then that splits the connection
forty eight percent goes
This way and forty eight percent goes the other way
And then it uh shit
Into both monitors and they all come they come together for the middle monitor four percent goes into the back of my neck
Only two monitors in 2019
I got three
I got hardware here
And I don't I don't know. Hey, here's like oh look at what I look at my desk and here's all my equipment
I don't even do that
I got three monitors in a connect on top
Do I have 144 hertz monitors? No, it's a scam
Human eye can't see over fucking 120 hertz
That's a fucking scam
I'll tell you though
Uh, here's the real answer to that question. So do I don't have any hundred 144 hertz monitors
And the reason for that is because all of my monitors are 120 hertz
so justifying buying three new monitors
for
24 hertz on each of them
Is I can't justify that it's not enough
Now if I was going to go to like 244 maybe
But I have the opinion that 120 hertz
is
I don't
Okay. Look, I know that like oh, yeah, you're talking about like the analog watch before it. Okay, that's fine
Right now I don't think anybody needs more than 120 hertz right now right this second
some people maybe
If you're really really if you have a 4k monitor and you give it you blasted huge frames
What am I talking about? I'm talking about
that 120 hertz versus 144 hertz is not worth spending like
15 to 2 500 to 2 000 dollars to get three new monitors
Not enough to do that. I do guys. I'm just playing parapa the rapper today
Do I need a 244 hertz monitor right now?
I need all the I need to the power that I could get
csgo players
right
Uh, I haven't opened csgo in probably two and a half years
cs
Omega low
I don't know why that makes me laugh every time. All right, but there but no fucking no bullshit like no kidding around
Um, yeah, I already have 120 hertz and as much as it'd be cool to have them
Uh, I don't have a this not necessary maybe eventually
But not now thanks for the picture dark soul and thank you smelly boy for the 250. Uh, great sherbert is delicious
And well, though, thanks for the 300 bits
What are you linking me here? You're linking me like logs of the channel. Can we uh,
M well does this can we agree? This is an epic moment
This is a chat log of what are you writing?
Because you're doing the whole alphabet, but somebody but you say p you ruin it yourself
Wait, this one is you did you did the whole alphabet and then from m n o
Oh, you wrote p ee. I get it. We did the whole alphabet. How'd you do that?
This is what I see right now. I'm just gonna show you guys what I see
This is it's a log from the channel
They said this is an epic gamer moment
It's just the alphabet. I don't even know when you did this and then you said german nose wipe like 40 times
Did you do this at like two in the morning?
That's pretty cool. Nice work
Let's get the credits on the screen. Why not? Thanks everybody for watching. Thanks for supporting the stream
Thanks for the ridiculous amount of subs and bits as always seriously
We're gonna do jackbox for a few hours tomorrow
It's gonna be a chill stream before I have to get ready to leave
Get ready and do another one
Because just like the carnival stream, I think some people might not realize that this is a lot more intricate than
Uh, i've been maybe coming on over the last week or two
We've got activities to do
Should be fun
But as always, thank you. Seriously here come the credits here come the subs
for today
Gifted subs regular subs much love to all of you
Thank you again. We do have about three or four bomb bits to do
Freudian weapon. Thanks for the 250 no message. Just 250 cheer. Thank you for odium
Putra
Every time I get this wrong
Putra fin putra fashion road clown
Thanks for the 400 bits
German missed the toilet
Ray Joel. Well, yeah, we'll we'll raid y'all
That sounds like a fun thing to do. Thank you though. Uh, mr clown
Thank you hippo rider for the 500 bits throughout the last year. I've been dealing with some very
Uh some very affecting family issues and I know it's cliche
But watching your videos and content has really helped me and I know I haven't been
With the channel throughout all of its years, but i'm going to continue to watch and support it. Thank you
i'm sorry to hear that
Hopefully they result and whether you've been watching for two months or 10 years
Glad to have you. Thanks a lot hippo. I really appreciate it
You hanging out and I appreciate the 500 bits. Thank you
Gnarly, thanks for the 250
You know what before I go to bed when the stream ends
Can you just come up with my dream for me so that I don't have to donate about it tomorrow?
Yeah, sure. Okay. Here's what you can dream about
you're going to
Boom eyes open
Where am I? Wait a minute to get completely pitch black
What's going on here? If you're gonna be breath you can start breathing
This is fucked up. I know you this dead silent. You can't hear anything you do hear
Over you're a little disoriented somehow you look over here in this you keep you
You're making it almost these figures and there's noises little like click like clacks and
You just like what the fuck is going on here. You hear a little cough somebody coughed over there from the left-hand side
There's like a five or dozen different silhouettes all staring at you
Finally, but right before you wake the fuck up light turns on and it's happy birthday surprise
And it's like all your family and your friends and they they're all there and they love you
And it's a you eat a new cake that you have pizza and it's a really really fun day. It's a great time
Somebody said I hate my family. We'll
Replace them with all your favorite marvel characters
And that's my time. I'll see you tomorrow for jackbox
Wait, sir. Rock just came in right now for 250. This is bia
7632 million nine hundred seven. I come from the future of 2017 to warn every bia
That the next month burger king is gonna have a whopper two-for-one special if that's real
And that's pretty cool. I will say
Wait 2017 never mind. That's not happening anymore
Good night guys. See you tomorrow
thanks for hanging out on the
PlayStation 1 and playstation 2 clean upstream
I had a blast. It's a lot of fun. See you tomorrow jackbox
Good night. Wait ray joel right? Let's ray joel
Can I do it from here? What is what's joel doing right now? Oh, he's playing i'm jammer lambie
That'd be really fucking funny
Okay. Are you ready?
Start to cue it up
Oh the music right? I screwed that up
No, I didn't it should be fine. Well now it's gonna be going like this
Different music. All right. Go say hello
See you guys tomorrow
Goodbye. Good night