Hey, Jermashito. Oh, the misery. Jermashito forgot to get me my batteries.
That's what you guys are spamming. That's what we're going with today. That's what we're doing today.
Doing all right. I'm doing okay. Well, you know, I've been waiting for this one.
Yeah, we're playing Wrestling Empire today. This game, it's probably one of the hardest
times I've laughed at a video game in probably at least a couple of years, right?
We played this months back, many, many moons ago. Only this time, there's been a significant
amount of updates to this game, including outdoor environments. Like you can literally walk around
outside and like go do things. There's a general manager mode where you play the you play the owner
guy. You play the manager that writes the contracts. I mean, we kind of need to see how this plays up.
Be a manager. Oh, yeah. That's what we're doing today. We're gonna see some content that I might
have. I'd have missed. Yeah, I'm ready to go. You need to touch grass. How much is this game?
It's not expensive. It's it's very cheap. Whatever it is. Hold on one second. Yeah,
this is not an expensive game. It's $15. It's worth is worth it. I got to remember how to play.
I got to get the controls down again. We'll do that on the fly. I'll remember it.
I have to do the tutorial again. That's fine. Omega low. He's gonna laugh. Yeah, I'm ready to
go. Let's do it. Alright, so for very important to get this mouse off the goddamn screen.
Alright, so what we're gonna do is I have a very sad thing to tell everybody. See booking career.
I'm very curious. Mr. Satan is gone because I uninstalled this game and didn't do steam
cloud on it. So this is this is a fresh fresh playthrough. Yeah, fresh, fresh, fresh playthrough.
But we're making a new person anyways, making a new character anyways. So we're doing booking
career. I have to I have to pick somebody but we need to edit somebody. What league should I even
do? What league was it last time? It was Hollywood? Or was it wrestling school? I forget. You jigsaw
Jeremy. Where was jigsaw Jeremy? Let's do Hollywood. I have to pick somebody to change.
Eddie, Eddie Schwarz. I could just change Eddie. Who should I because one I have a beast. This is
a good one to do. Okay, we're gonna make this character. This is the remember I'm not a wrestler.
I am a person that books the matches. So keep that in mind. Now I can't change popularity. I'm
not that I wouldn't be that popular. All right. Well, first of all, let's get this right.
I need a better theme song here. I'm not gonna make Vince McMahon. I want to slow down. I just
I love this one. This is the best song that I love it. What is a little faster?
About all the misery. All right, we're gonna take my strength. I'm I want to I'm 80. No,
I'm probably like a 72 skill though. I can't even change that. I can't go higher. Why not?
Porn music. Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I hit B. No, no, no, I this is wrong.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I just pressed the B button to go back.
Just skip, skip, skip, skip, skip. I'm gonna retire. Fuck. Just go with it. I'm not gonna
just go with it. I want to make a character retire. I'm retired. Okay, I'm retired.
Eddie Schwarz. Who cares about Eddie Schwarz? It doesn't matter. I didn't I pressed the.
Okay, here we go. All right, Hollywood. We lost it. All right, Eddie Schwarz is here.
Whatever. Who cares? We'll do this one. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Well,
we can edit this and I'll pick this name of this character is going to be I don't know yet.
I'm not sure. Where is it? Where's my song? Looks like. Did he add tracks? I feel like
there weren't this many sounds songs earlier. Hmm. Yeah, I want to look like a total dick.
Ooh, slow it down. I like 90%. Okay, check the others. What the fuck?
I like this the most. Do it. Do it. All right. 13 is the one. This one's not bad either.
Oh, but what about the medieval music? Should I put it with like a knight costume?
Or that's the guy that owns the league. Yeah, make it like a king. There's too many good options.
Make it keep it hardcore, but make them a little dweeb. So you. Yes, I like the ones with lyrics.
I had this one. This is the old theme song. I remember this.
Yeah. Yeah, it's a Mario level. I think keep it hardcore as to stay. Make the owner of the
league. Horrible. No, I'm not doing Eldon rings right now. Nope. Nope. Nope. Make him me strong.
Fine. Me strong is that. Okay. Here's your me strong playthrough. Hold on.
This is good too though, guys. Slower. No, it's going to be 13 or 41.
And of course, I'm not playing Eldon ring. Why am I doing that?
Though actors they get for the From Software games, they're the best. I want to know more
of the stuff that they do. Seriously. The person that does the intro for Eldon ring, the narrator.
God damn it. You're so good. You are so good. Like it's unbelievably talented. That was like,
you're so good. I want, please tell me you're in more shit. Please. How about if you know,
how about if his name is just the dweeb that this is the manager? Yeah. How about I don't like Don
dweeb. Don dweeb. All right. How about for lighting? What's hardcore? Dark. Twilight. Dusk.
Definitely doesn't. Fireworks. All the works. Barbed bat. Baseball bat. Beer bottle. Bell.
Grass knuckles. Briefcase. Brim. Burger. Page piece. Camera. Pain. Cardboard. Oh my God.
Extinguisher. Glass pane. Guitar. Gun. Wait, there's a gun? They added a gun?
Hot dog. Picture? There's so much stuff now. A water bottle. He comes out with an orange.
What a dweeb. Okay. Popularity. What? Oh, okay. Sorry. Very unpopular, I would say.
Not very strong at all, but I'm the one booking the events. It doesn't matter. I'm pretty highly
skilled. Agility is pretty high. His damage is very low. Attitude is terrible. Okay. All right.
Now we're going to do the build. I think we're like 50? 55? Five? Oh boy. Should Don dweeb be
four foot six? How tall should Don dweeb be? This song really just pumps me the fuck up. It does.
All right. How about like five? Five feet tall. Five like six. This is not a wrestler, guys. This
is Don dweeb, who is a general manager. All right. Hair. Hairstyle. Okay. It's already kind of there.
Well, I need a dweeb haircut. What is variation? No. This guy sucks. That's not bad. Am I going
to have a little hair on top? Do balding mullet. No, I think this is fine. This is fine. Somebody
said shit on his head. Okay. What about the color? I don't want his hair to be purple.
Now it's like green. Whatever. That's better. All right. I need face. Oh man. Do I have to press
any more buttons? Perfect. Not yet. Hold on. It's not perfect yet. What a fucking loser.
You don't know that. I like this one a lot. It just looks so funny.
This dude sucks. Oh, perfect. I like that more than anything.
He's just a hello neighbor guy. Glasses or a hat? No. No, I just think like this.
Okay. That looks all right so far. Let's keep going. Body. Is he like chest hair? Hold on. Can
I have just chest hair? Please let me just have just chest hair with an open shirt. Come on. Come
on. I can kind of do it. Please give him a fedora and glasses. Oh man. Make material zero.
There is no zero. Shit. It's okay. I think it blends in. That's fine. All right. Under pattern.
We got to do over pattern. Oh no. Nope. I don't think it's going to work. That one kind of worked.
Do we really care about what Don Dweeb has on? Does anybody actually care about what Don Dweeb's
attire is? Is there a long sleeve shirt? This is fucking weird. You just made Saxton Hale.
I kind of did. What is this material thing? How do I add a shirt?
What's happening with this? I mean, I kind of, I, how do I, what's going on with his shirt?
Oh, you have to, okay. You add sleeves. Okay. He looks just weird now. No elbow pads.
Uh, no gloves either. Shape. Uh, tight is fine. All right. Now let me go fix this body.
Way better. All right. Much better. We're going to make the, uh, suit gray.
Give him a beer gut, please. We'll, we'll fix it. All right. Let's do the, uh, sleeves. How do I get
this right? There we go. Okay. This is a cyborg goofy looking ass. I, I don't know what you,
what are you talking about? He looks fine. I just, this pants have to be fixed.
Why does he have prosthetic arms? He doesn't have, he, this is a suit. He's,
he does kind of look like it. Why does Don Dweeb have such a huge bulge?
I didn't say it. You did. Okay. Here we go. Let's do it. Uh, legs. That looks good. I don't think
I need no pattern. Okay. I don't think Don Dweeb would have these on. Right there. The laces go
all the way. He doesn't even have the, he looks like the snack cake thing. What are those things
called? Dung? What are they called? They're called something. Ohos? Yeah. Little Debbie's. Yeah.
All right. That looks fine. I don't want to, I don't want this to be green.
Better. Less green or red. Brown. Yeah. It's fine. All right. These green jeans. You gotta go.
These, uh, all right. Fine. My soul is leaving my body. Why? All right. That's his wrestling
attire. Casual. I think I'm okay with casual. All right. That looks good. Looks good. All right.
Moves. God. We've got stance. Missed up. Missed low. Martial arts. Grapple.
I like that. These are taunts. This is weird. Oh, that's entrance. That's entrance.
Yeah. He's just like, I'm the puppet master. It's not Costanza. Yeah. I'm thinking about something.
All right. Raise the roof. Raise finger. How about roar? Yep. Celebration. I don't know what
he's doing. Yeah. Constant disappointment. Our stance, you guys said? Yeah. Without a doubt.
All right. Attacks. Upper attack. We got right hook. I like the straight jabs. Chin kick for sure.
Do I, do I even fight anybody? I'm the manager, aren't I? I'm like the general manager of the
league. I don't think I even do anything. That just hurts. Fine. Super punch. All right. Those,
the rest of these are fine, I think. That was a magic harp attack. This is from the top rope.
Okay. Why is he holding? Okay. Why is he holding his, he's holding his pants up. Did I not give
him a belt? This guy, he's going to be fine. All of his moves are just falling down. This guy's
going to get really hurt. Okay. Crushes. Definitely kick. Definitely leg drop. Flying crush. Yep.
Just land on his spine. Anything that has him land on his back, I'm going to do. Let's see if I can
get this guy injured and retire him immediately. Okay. Good. All right. These are the ones that
really, really matter. All right. Attack and up. So these ones are okay. I don't need to change
these ones. It's the specials that I care about the most. All right. What is Don Dweeb's special
move? That's a really good question. What should it be? How about a stunner? I love the stunner.
It's like my favorite move ever. I could watch stunner, stone cold stunner compilations and I
wouldn't get sick of it. It's like, it's like a lot of people's pizza. Like, oh, I can eat pizza
every day. I could watch people get stunned every day. Rope toss. Tombstone's pretty good.
Hold on to this. Yep. Climb buster. Spear's good too. MDKO? It can't be that, right?
What if it was just a hip toss? How fucking lame. What a dweeb. If your special move is a hip toss.
Oh my god. How about head stomp? Go, go, plotter. Nice. Diamond cutter. Death valley driver.
Close line drop. Canadian destroyer. That's, yeah. I don't need to see anymore. All right.
These ones are okay. Usually I can keep these ones normal. What about these ones? I like the
neck breaker. A big fan of filler moves which are, what the hell was that? I like that one.
He has to have a hip toss. Air crash. Yep. Run and up. I like it. Headbutt. I like it.
Northern lights. Power stunner. Oh yeah. And fireman suplex. That looks good to me. All right.
What about rear moves? Yep. Bull nelson. Absolutely. Sleeper hold. Absolutely. That's such a boomer
wrestling move. You know what I mean? Oh no. He's got him in the sleeper hold. Of course Don Dweeb
would have that move. That's good. Shoulder lift. I never liked those moves because they just pin
and they're not powerful. We're doing reverse DDT. No. I want moves that hurt people. I don't
need to change that one. Just, just choking. All of his moves should just be choking people.
Recliner. Vice grip. Okay. Yeah. That looks good. I'm happy with this. All right. But anything else
I need to do? Relations. I don't really roll. This is a, this is a booker and heal. That's fine.
Promotion will stay in Hollywood. I don't need to have any friends. Is this the first time you're
playing this? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Oh, you're not a random chatter. That's bark
skeletal. That's Joel. I was supposed to be like, excuse me. No, I've, of course I played it before.
Random chatter. That was Joel. I was supposed to like correct you. Like, um, excuse me. Of course
I've played it before. What are you, what are you dumb? No, I have played it before. This game is
fucking amazing. It's toxic. Hope you've been good. Hope you've been good too.
We got to fucking do something. Let's do something. You want to hang out like soon. What are you doing
this weekend? I'm going to play like, you want to play halo this weekend on insane difficulty
and then die in the first 10 seconds, a hundred times and not talk to each other for a year and
a half straight. That's not true. That's not true. No, let's do something, man. I, I, it's been too
long. Let's do something. I mean it. All right. Don Dweeb. There it is. I'm ready. Stop with the
networking. What Joel and I have been buddies for like five years. So excuse me. I need you to take
a quick step back and understand Joel's been around for a long time. You serious? Here we go.
Booking career going to Hollywood is Don Dweeb. I'm ready. Yep. We're good to go. Welcome to
Wrestling Revolution, Don Dweeb. I understand you'll be taking over as the Booker. You got banned?
Wrestling is currently in the worst brand of wrestling with a rating of 70%.
What? You've been brought in to turn that around and make Wrestling Revolution a viable brand.
Is $40,500 available to invest in the talent you need to get the job done? Well, we aren't
fucking going anywhere. That's all the money you're giving me? Although I'm stepping down
as the Booker, I remain the owner and will be checking you don't screw things up. But ultimately
we're on the same side and we all want Wrestling Revolution to succeed, right? I wish you the best
of luck and hope you enjoy running the show as much as I did. Okay. So this is the, here it is.
It's a TV taping in Scandinavia. How much money is this costing? Map? What? We love promos. We hate
botches. Wait, what is this map? We love weapons. We hate feuds. We love ticket prices. We hate
what? We, oh god, I'm realizing this is a map of the world. Okay. All right.
We love tickets. We, we love pro, why can I, with a whole world? We hate vene, what the fuck is
happening? We love cages. We hate intruders. We hate managers. We love time limits. We hate near,
what does Canada hate? Watches? They love holds. We love furniture. We hate countouts. We love
high flyers. We hate, that's a Carrera? Is that like a wrestler? We love furniture.
We hate weapons. We love high flyers. All right. So where are we going? We're in, where are we?
Where are we? Okay. So where's my, is my card? Okay. Undercard. All right. I gotta plan this.
Did you go to Antarctica? All right. The rules, this is fine. The first, where, where, what is,
what is Scandinavia like? It's just changing what they like, right? Where the fuck is Scandinavia?
Okay. We love promos. So mid card, we're going to have a promo script. Uh, promo. All right.
Announcement. And it's going to be a, uh, face turn. That sounds good to me. Cast is fine.
Oops. Well, whatever. That's okay. That's okay. It could just be an announcement.
Is this all that I have for the mid card? Oh shit. Oh, there's no ref. I keep deleting people.
What about the, all right. What about, what's the under, why is there only one thing?
This is every, this is the whole thing. The entire event is just this guy. It makes an announcement
and the event stops. That's actually kind of funny. Okay. Arena crowds, 1400 lighting fog.
Okay. Rules, individuals, you have to make it and then play the matches. Oh, okay.
So this is just the one match that's happening here, right?
Does that be a furniture smash? That's fine. Yeah. Elimination. No time limit.
All right. Yeah. Hardcore. Cast is going to be, you're fine. That could be whack axe. Oh,
it's okay. I see how it works. You have to actually move this around. All right. Let me get rid of you.
Um, how do I add them? What's going on? How do I add a wrestler on the other side?
I can't, how do I move this? Press Y. Okay. So they're in different teams, right? Okay.
And the script is announcement face turn. That sounds good. It doesn't matter who it is.
So is that, is that it? Can I change the other? Is this, this, this, this is just it?
Is the, I'm the undercard. All these matches are the exact same match. How do I add it?
There's no rep. How do I add a ref? Um, this menu is kind of freaking me out here.
Ref. No refs, no rules. How do I add a referee? Um, can I, how do I change this?
Go to the middle and add. Yeah. That's what I'm doing. Haven't you played this? Yeah. But I mean,
this, I haven't done like much in this menu. You have to add someone and give them the ref
role. Okay. Um, so how about you script rules? Uh, what the fuck? I don't think I can do that.
Okay. Well, I, I just need to do this because you have to add someone with a gray name. Wait,
I have to play the match too. I thought I can't just watch it. Oh, Tony land. Uh, what?
All right. Well, I, I'm just going to, I'm going to play the match. I don't,
this is very confusing. Who should I play as? Ray is retired. All right.
Drag them to the middle. I'm on a controller. Um, I'm just going to see what happens when I do this.
Is this me? No. Don't Thanos snap the ref next time. I mean, it was very easy to accidentally
delete somebody. All right. This is me apparently, but I thought I was the Booker. Okay. I remember,
I remember, I remember. Listen up everybody. There's something I need to get off my chest
before we go any further. I know I've been a jerk in recent times. I've said and done some things
I'm not proud of, but I realized we're nothing without the support of the fans. You're the
electricity that gives us life. This guy's going for the back of the head with your help. I know
I can be a better wrestler. I hope I can repay you by fulfilling my potential. We're done with the
life changing crap. The only drama that matters is in the ring. What's going on? Oh, that wasn't
very fair. There's no ref. How are we supposed to do this? All right. Let's go. You have to fight
until the death. You deleted the ref. Well, I'm sorry. If it's as it's, if it's so easy to
delete a ref, it should be easy to put a ref back in. Yeah. There's a new UI too. Who says who's
Batman over here? All right. I think I got to remember how to do this. Is it a camera? Wait,
they don't want to fight anymore. I got to remember grapple is okay. There we go. I remember
your ratings are going to go from seven to zero. How do we end the match? I don't understand.
Does somebody actually have to like go to zero? Oh my fucking God. I was going to kick this shit
out of this guy's chair. There are no rules. Give me, give me, give me, give me. Yeah. Honestly,
I probably want to start another career. I mean, I, we're not going to get attached to any of these
characters. What are you going? You're not going to the top row. What are you doing? Get the fuck
out of here. All right. There we go. We're not going to get attached to anybody. What do you mean
too late? You're not attached to this character yet. Oh my God. I'm going to die. Read the PDF.
Oh God. Out of the chair. So I forget how you pen. Here's the manual. Good luck. Oh God.
Should I open the manual? Why is he pissed? I didn't even mean to do that. Tony. I'm sorry,
Tony land. I didn't mean to do that, but I did mean to do this. I want nothing to do with this.
All right. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I do. I do want to
remember how to play and I do want to hit Batman in the head with something. This dude's supposed
to be a face. We're fighting for this guy's amusement right now, by the way. He's sitting
there like, yes. Yes. Kill it for my amusement. Get out of here. Come on. He looks like he's
wearing an American flag diaper. All right. It's just somebody pin somebody. Wasn't this a specific
match? I forget what this match even was. I just hit myself in the head with the chair.
No cheering silence. Yeah. Cause this, like this, nobody likes this league. Didn't, didn't he say
this league sucks or something? I won. All right. Maybe both progress is being hindered by the
limitations of wrestling revolution. It Bob Orson's profile suffered after losing that match.
This is Don Dweeb. I'm not sure there are work. Things are working out for me at wrestling
revolution. I know I still have 38 weeks left on my contract, but how would you feel if we
terminated our agreement? No, see out your contract. Sorry. I knew it was too much to
ask. Let's see if we can turn things around. 38 weeks. All right. Hardcore furniture mash
baby bowl versus big Bob Orson just happened. So this now is a mid card. I think I'm starting
to get the hang of this. I don't delete the referee under any circumstance. Last laugh.
Oh, last man standing street fight. Please look at the guide, remove the referee, read the manual.
Let me, let me just take a quick look at it at home. Re-Rome is only in wrestler career.
This mode may be too complicated for you to start with. Shit. Okay. All right. Okay. Okay.
Where's Don Dweeb? Time for Don Dweeb's wrestling career. You tanked the company by not reading the
manual. Let's see what, let's see what we can do with Don Dweeb. All right. I'm in wrestling
revolution. This is singles match versus mid winter at 8 PM. The gimmick. Okay. Database.
Let's go. Proceed. Rome. See, you've decided to take responsibility for what happens behind
the scenes Don Dweeb. You didn't read the goddamn manual. You lost your job in 15 minutes. If you
take this route, it's your responsibility to get through the curtain in time for your match.
But only enter when your time is lit up green as Amber means somebody else's match is taking place.
What? Spend your energy on the right things at the right time to stay healthy. This world
is full of distractions, but try to make sure you get a good night's sleep at a sensible time.
You must also look after your mental health along the way as I've seen a lot of wrestlers lose
control. I got five grand. I don't want to spoil all the surprises so just get out there and see
what the city has in store for you. Now this is what I wanted to do. You can always opt out and
skip straight to the action at any time. Who is he talking to? Jerk Hoffman? Why does Jerk
Hoffman have no health? Why is there a grenade? Why is there a fucking dynamo? Why is he so mad?
What's wrong with this guy? I'm waiting for my match? Okay. So where do I go? What should I do?
I'm on the street? Wait, don't I have a match soon? Why is everybody just walking around the street?
This is the whole roster. Don't let anybody scare you out of taking this route. There are risks,
but it can also be more fulfilling. He's talking to me? I gotta get this on camera. Just try to stay
out of trouble to protect yourself, and if you can't do that, I still have your back.
All right. Why does everybody have a microphone out here?
What? Why is it... Why is the show starting? Everybody... We gotta get in there and be on camera.
Get out of my way. I'm tougher than you, Don Dweeb. Why would they put us all outside? I don't
understand. Get him off me. Somebody get him off me, please. Get out of the way. Get him off of me.
He's still on me. He's breaking my ankle. Somebody help. Help, please.
I gotta get in there. My match is starting. Backstage. All right. Where's the arena?
My health is zero. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. God damn it. I'm coming.
I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm here. Here I am. What am I fighting? What's going... What's happening?
Drop it? What do I have? What team am I on? I didn't pay attention to whose team I was on.
Am I a manager? What's going on?
These people here. They just got us outside. We're just like fucking like rats in the city.
Why is somebody at a desk? There are just a bunch of random people here. Why is it just some lady
at a desk here? She's not commentating. Oh my god. Get off of me. Please don't tap out. All right.
I'm good. All right. Who am I? I have no health. Why do we just have a brawl outside for no reason?
It said here comes the show. The show is starting and everybody freaked the fuck out.
What's going on? What? I'm crawling. How is this not illegal? This apparently isn't illegal.
Why are there two people in the ring at the same time with me? This is unfair.
Okay. Can I please? I get one second. Okay. Let's go. Oh my fucking god. Please. You gotta be ready
for your match. That's so funny. What happens if you have no health though? I can't move. My
character's just stunned. I gotta get out of here. What? Will everybody leave me alone for a second?
Everyone's just out to get me. Did I really fuck up that bad as the booker? Does everybody just hate
my guts? You have no idea. There's no reason for that. Yeah, there was. What are you doing here?
Can I see the match details? I'm fighting mid winter. That's what's going on. I have no idea
who the fuck these other people are. He's not. What? All right. Now I understand what's going on.
I can at least pretend like I know what I'm doing. Oh, that's great. You leave here with
you a group of seven fucking wrestlers that were all out here at the same time together
on the same team. That was some dweeb. I was here alone apparently. Why did you get that many people?
Am I supposed to leave the ring? I can't even get up. What's he doing? I can't move.
What? It's what's my dust? I gotta get out of the ring. Oh shit. It's not my match anymore. All
right. I gotta go. Come on. Hurry up. How do I get health back? Don Dweeb's profile suffered
after losing that match. What about people with 10 versus one? Give me a break. Oh, a special has
generated a buzz by interfering in that match. He had to shit my pants walk. I mean, you get beat up
by eight people. I didn't make any money. I lost $450. Hold on a minute. You're trying to tell me
that a ladder that was backstage that I picked up on the ground cost me $200 to bring it out to the
ring. Just put it. I don't want this anymore. All right. I gotta heal. Can I see the map somehow?
All right. Office. I gotta go bathroom. I'm glad midwinter could teach you a lesson. You don't
belong at wrestling revolution. Don Dweeb. Wait, what? I have to face $700 in damages?
I just went out there and got my ass kicked for 15 minutes. I didn't do any. What are you talking
about? What? Oh my God. What the hell? This is so fucked up. All right. I need to go to the bathroom.
Please don't hurt me. Please don't hurt me. Please don't hurt me. Please don't hurt me.
Don't hurt me. Don't hurt me. Don't hurt me. You're walking at me with a bottle. Please don't hurt
me. Please don't hurt me. That guy was almost late to his match to see that. Let that be the end of
it Dweeb. I hope you've learned your lesson. Where am I going? I'm not controlling the character
right now. I'm not controlling you. You're in no state to. If you can't save your energy for the
ring, then I'll just have to keep you out of it. What do I do? All right. I have to looks like you
lost control for a while there. You need to look after your mental. What do you think?
Honestly, I haven't had one second myself. My popularity is dwindling. Please get...
What? How am I supposed to do anything when everybody just attacks me? What the fuck do you
want me to do? Oh, I wonder. I wonder. Please. This is the... That's the promoter. The promoter.
That's my boss. Oh, my fucking chest. I just need to get to another door. I can't run. I need to go
to the bathroom. Please. People are throwing weights at me. Everyone's trying to kill me.
Oh, my God. I popped when you used that ladder piece as a weapon. Remind me to never get on
your bad side. Can we be friends? Can we be friends? Can you help? Honestly. Can the three
of us work together or something? Can we be friends? Yes. Oh, my God. Please help me.
Thank God. All right. I don't know. How do I close the door? Oh, my fucking God. I'm the only idiot
that can, like, trip and fall and hurt... What the fuck is going on? Whose phone is that?
Whose phone is ringing? Is that my phone? Is there a telephone ringing in the bathroom?
How do I answer the phone? I don't... Okay. That was a good first day. Okay.
Okay. Boomtown's agility's improved. People's salary's risen.
Seven hours of uncomfortable sleep. Don Dweeb's energy levels are now at 30%.
Okay. No show today. Rome. Okay. Thank you. I need to eat some food or something. There's
nothing scheduled today. Wait. Oh, hey, what's up? I'm so glad I have one friend. I think there's a
phone in here. That's the phone right there. See the phone on the ground? I got it. Okay. What if
it rings? Anybody there? Okay. Let's go. I'm going to go out here. Go to the gym. Let me look at the
map. I need food. Barbershop. Studio. Hotel. Office. Cemetery. Airport. Hospital. All right.
Where's the hospital? It's connected to the gym. Nobody wins their first match at Wrestling
Revolution. Don Dweeb. Try not to worry about it. Thanks. Is that your buddy right there?
I'm gonna fuck off. We're gonna get out of here. Apple. How do I eat it? I said to eat the random
food that's on the ground. And you know, I didn't have any scraps in here for me. Is this corn in
the cob? Please leave me alone. What a weirdo. All right. Go, go, go. Hospital. Okay. You never
should have taken this step, Don Dweeb. You don't have what it takes to survive in the real world.
If you want to be escorted to the ring safely, just admit you made a mistake and back out.
Why are you here? I don't want this. I need to... Where's the hospital? Wait, there's a hamburger
on the ground. All right. If you really want to do this, then... This is the doctor. He's not treating
me. How do I get treated by the doctor? That person just fell out of the bed. You all right?
Phone. Hello? I was hoping to speak to Machine Murray. What the fuck is happening in here?
Let me just eat all the trash off his ground. Stop. Please. Okay. Well, I guess I can't get
treated from the doctor who's trying... You know what? I'm fucking sick of this guy. I'm sick and
tired of your shit. You understand? Where do you keep the medicine? What? This guy attacked me when
I came in here. You attacked me. That's what happened. I mean, I found it on the ground.
Yeah. I'll sell you my guitar. It was a pleasure doing business with you. Thank you.
I wonder what you're going to use it for. He's washing his hands. Can I lay in the bed? Why is
the bed on fire? Oh, that's how you do it. Okay. You have to go lie in the bed. Can I buy that
guitar off of you so I can club the doctor in the back of the head? We got more popular somehow.
I love how that's news. Don Dweeb got eight hours of comfortable sleep today. All right.
This is awesome. This is so fucking funny. I love this. Okay. Super Lucha Libre have sunk below
Wrestling Revolution. They're the least popular brand. All right. I got a Singles versus Boston
Blue Fly at 6 p.m. Okay. I'm not going to. I'm going to eat up. I'm going to eat something on
the ground. Listen Don Dweeb. I've been keeping an eye on your progress. I think some changes need
to be made. Fans pay to see people they care about, but you're not popular enough to move the needle.
I had one day. Increase your popularity to 58% by the fourth week of May or I can't promise
there'll be a place for you. Shit. I need to win my next match. Just threw an orange at him.
You have two hours till your match. I got to get the fuck out of here. I got to bring this.
No, no, no. I don't want to be on the street. I go to the gym and try to level up or something.
How do I train? It's got to be like a training bag or something, right?
Can I lift? Can I just pick stuff up off the ground? Does this count? Oh, okay. That does work.
Oh my God. Any more food in the ground? Lift weights and there are steroids.
I imagine that punching bag is important too. Okay. I need to go to the arena. How do I get
to the arena? Okay. The arena is I got to go from the gym backstage, which is over here.
All right. It's not time for my match yet. I'm in good spirits. I'm in good standing.
That guy has a bomb. That guy has a bomb. I'm not going to stand even remotely over there.
All right. It's my time. It's a singles match, right? How? Yeah, it's my time to go out on stage.
You're not going to follow me out on stage. Please. Let's go. It seems things have been
spiraling out of control here at Wrestling Revolution. You telling me? Well, not tonight
because I've been called in especially to restore order. If you step out of line in my ring,
I'll kick both of your asses as if I'm in the damn match. Let's go. I have to win this. Shut up.
Yeah. Clap this. Stop taunting. This is like, it's embarrassing for me when you do that.
Get out of here. How do you pin? I forgot how to pin in the game. Or shit reversal if you ask me.
It's the taunt button. Okay. Hit, toss. All right. Let's go. I'm, I'm not strong enough to lift the
guy. Oh my God. He just broke my neck. Knock him down. Get out of here. Oh, that hurt me more than
it. Wow. Um, is that legal? All right. I gotta pick you up. How do you miss that? I don't understand
how you miss that. Get out of here. Good. Come on. Get him down. No. What the fuck was that? Get up.
He's got the camera. Uh, okay. I'll take it. Camera, please come over here. I, if I could have seen,
that would have been great. Uh, hello? Good. No, you know what? Can I get, let me do this if I can
get it. No, I want to climb the turnbuckle. He just threw the guitar at him. Can I climb the
turnbuckle here? Shit. That's stupid of me. I'm not doing terribly though, even though I'm way weaker
than this guy. What do I do? He's okay with the ladder being here, which is weird. I don't know.
Might get it. Reverse, reverse, reverse, please. It's so stupid. Yeah. Uh, we're both at the same
hell. Uh-huh. What an idiot fell for it. This guy's harder than millennia. Grab. What do you mean?
Grab the gun. What gun? Is this thing over this over here? This is not a gun. I don't know if this
is, I think that's illegal. I don't think I can use that. All right. Come on. This dude reverses
every single submission. It'll tell you if it's illegal. Okay. Dude, this blocking that this guy
is really come on. What the fuck? Um, how do I stop reversing everything? The gun on the,
are you trying to tell me if I shoot? I'm not going to shoot this guy. I have to get my popularity
up. It means I have to win a match, not get disqualified. Let's go for Finn. Shoot. I'm not
going to shoot him. Not right now. My hand. Fuck. God damn it. How do you reverse? Get over there.
Choke him. Hit him. That's it. I have more health than he does. Jesus. Go. Oh, please. Get over
here. Who's, I don't know who's doing this too. Am I choking him or is he, I don't know what's
happening. I can't tell who's doing this. He has me. No. Oh, he's going to break my head off.
I need the gun. It's the only way that it's not the only way. Here we go. I got it. He hit his
head on the ladder. He hit his head on the ladder. We're good. We're good. He hit his head on the
ladder. He hit his head on the ladder. We're good. It's a gun. I'm not going to, oh my God.
Stop with the gun. It's a rope break if I've ever seen one. Yep. I don't know. What are you,
are you serious? This is so close. It's too close. I am actually having trouble getting up. God
damn it. Choke him. What's going on? Do it. Oh my God. Why? Finn, that's got to be it.
One minute in the match. One minute. Oh my God. There's a hot dog out here. I can't. I don't want
to do it. I can't. No. This is like Mortal Kombat rules. Do I have more health than he does?
I got him. I got him. What's happening to my arm? Who wins? No, put this down. Put this down. Put
this down. Put this down. Put this down. I'm not going to use this. I don't know how to put it down.
How do you put it down without shooting it? How do I put it down without shooting it? I need to
put it down. Okay. Good. I know I can't shoot him. I'm getting up. Good. Okay. What about my
popularity? Thank God. I'm no longer facing, was it 58, right? I made it. 58. I made some money there
probably too, right? 1,100. There we go. There it is. All right. I'm back with a 5k. What if I go
out there right now? No. I need to go to sleep and I need to train. Actually, you know, let me
let me go do an activity while I sell sometime. How's your first victory at Wrestling Revolution
Don Dweeblitz? Let's hope it wasn't the last. Okay. Are we buds? Can I like shake hands or
something? All right. What about the bar? Pizza. The show's over. I imagine people are going to
be coming to the bar. Is this your hamburger? I don't know. Remember you're on a mission to
increase by popularity to 58%. I got it. You only have until the fourth week of May. You better
make sure you're on top of it. I'm already there, man. Can I order a drink? Okay. I'd like a drink,
please. I'm not trying to do this. I promise. I just want to sit in the stool. I'm losing health.
What happened? Oh my god. I can't. That wasn't me. That wasn't me. But I, this guy is, we gotta,
I don't know. I'm so confused. What was the point of that? This guy's just a dick. Okay,
I gotta get my revenge. Get out of the way. Oh my god. Are they all here together?
Where are you? There you are. What's your name? I don't know. Is it this point right here? This
guy right here. Oh my god. He's unstoppable. Oh my god. What? Oh shit. We have to take that guy out.
I hit that guy in the back of the head with a chair and he just turned and looked at me.
You're faster than me, dweeb. What? Oh my god. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. What are you? I
love how the AI just randomly, but this guy over here just sitting watching. You look like a mess.
Why don't you take a shower? Oh, I have to clean myself. Get me out of here. The guy left anyways.
Oh boy. I thought he left. Okay. I'm gonna go to the hotel. Hotel's right here. No, you idiot.
Oh my god. The hotel is right there. I need to form a team. I can't do my next match.
I really don't think so. I lost popularity. I still have enough. Pables and table legs match
versus Berlin. Okay, this is at 10 PM. I need to heal or something. What time is it? What time
is it right now? I need to go to the hospital and lie down for an hour. Oh my god. I have two hours
each. Are you kidding me? You followed my advice and made your prospects better than ever.
Okay. Please accept a hundred dollar bonus as a reward. Just make sure you keep it up.
Keep up the good work. Thanks. Thanks for the hundred dollars. I don't think I don't have enough
time. I don't know what to do. My match is in an hour and a half. I just need to eat food on the
ground. Is there a cafeteria? Hospital. It's probably the hospital. The only thing I can do,
right? Just lie in the bed for an hour. Go to the subway. That's not a subway eat fresh subway.
That is a drive on a rail subway. This is all right. I have one hour. Come on. Just food and
drink on the ground. 30 minutes. 20 minutes. All right. I got to go. Where do I go? I forget
how to get there. It's backstage. Over here. What's wrong? I'm going to puke. What's wrong with me?
I'm holding my mouth. What's going on? Hurry up. Come on. We needed that sleep.
Apparently. Really needed that sleep. The guy's double fisting Mike. So what happens if I just
stay asleep here? What happens here? He hits a referee in the head with a bat. What happens?
Oh no. I think they're getting annoyed. The entrance won't stop. Oh, here we go. Okay.
Why do they have beds everywhere? All week we've been polling fans on which match they would like
to see. And they voted for Don Dweeb versus Berlain in a beds and barbed bats match.
They sure did. Which conveniently enough is the exact situation we prepared for.
In case you've never seen a match like this before, let's make sure that we're clear about
the rules. This is like first person to like go to sleep. We have to like go to like, oh,
I'm going to go to bed first. Pin or submission falls count anywhere and there are no disqualifications.
Those rules suit me perfectly. So it seems these fans want to see you suffer.
Oh, they just felt they had to do something this drastic to make one of your matches entertaining.
Okay. Well, that was nice. Thank you. You want to keep it hardcore? Fine. Oh my God. Look,
I'll take it. I just almost killed him. Look at his health. Stop. Okay. I'm all right. They're
painting. It's painting of the ultimate warrior. He's dual welding. I just have to pin him, right?
Good. All right. This is good. Give me that bat. That person's not supposed to be in here.
Get out of here. Are they bullying me? I'm just doing what I have to do. They're attacking me.
Outlaw Eaton is here. Um, is outlaw Eaton here to fight me or is outlaw? Oh, good. Perfect. That
works for me. Me and outlaw Eaton are going to be friends. I just have to pin them. What do the beds
have to do with any of this, by the way? That's the stupidest thing. All right. We're going to,
I'm going to do like a suplex to him on bed. Nice double team. I got to end it flashy. Come here.
No, get, let's go. Uh, that did not work at all. Don't ask me why that didn't work. I have no idea.
You know what? Just pin him, right? Like honestly, he fit hardcore. Give me that mic.
It's not going to work. Welcome to bed and pin pin. Now that's it. There's no way you get up from
that. You gotta be kidding me, dude. Um, no, excuse me, please. It has zero health. How is
this still happening? Oh my God. This guy's impossible. All right. This is it. We need to
get on the bed and then I need to, I need to finish. I need to, how do I say this? You need to,
I need to the table. I need to power bomb you through the table. God damn it. I'm done. Get
over here. Just, just start, just, this is happening to me again. Help me. Help. Why is this guy
unkillable? That has to be it up here. Climb up here. I want to do like a pile driver to you.
Come on. What are you so afraid of? I shit. Okay. Why can't I, I'm sick of this. Just give,
I'm going to bash his head in with this great until he can't move. You make me go against like
the hardcore champion guy, right? All right. This is it. Of course. Crush his head. No,
this guy seriously wants to come in so bad. He's fucking fed. Yeah. Dude, the guy back there
watching. Let go, let go, let go, let go. We're friends. Beat him. You need to find the gun.
Maybe I should find the gun. Seriously. I can't keep this guy not. That's it. Yes.
You cost me that match. Outlaw Eaton. If you mess with my career, I'll end yours.
Let go of my hand. Yeah. We keep it hardcore. Neck. Okay. Popularity way up attitude way up.
I lost agility though. Outlaw Eaton has generated a buzz by interfering in that
match. That means I got to find Eloy. I accept to sleep on a bed this time. Yeah, please. Big money.
Ooh. We're running short of staff tonight, Dweeb. Can I count on you to referee one of the matches?
Yeah. Am I going to get paid? Thanks, Dweeb. You just saved the show. Please accept an extra $350
for your time. Nice. Oh, it's right now. All right. Is this a false count? No. Okay. This is just
regular match. I'm going to spend this time to just heal. I don't care about anything else.
I'm going to go find like, I'm going to go in the audience and find like hamburgers and stuff. I'll
be back. Anybody have any food? Is there food back here? Anybody have any extra popcorn or anything?
There has to be somebody. Somebody has to have food, right? There's no stray food. Whatever.
What about your job? My job? I'm doing it. It's fine. Can I like grab onto the ring and maybe get
like a snack or something? That guy just tapped out. Whatever. I need to heal. Who do I want to
win? Self-insert character. Yeah, it really is. I got to get this out of here. This is not allowed.
Oh, count. Should I count to 10? Should I count him out? You lose. I don't know why you were
refereeing this match, Don Dweeb. You're obviously not qualified. I just gave you an extra five to
10 full seconds. You just made the biggest mistake of your life. Nice fucking Dark Souls roll. Excuse
me. God. Get up. Let's get back in the ring. That's right. He won. Congratulations. All right. I got,
that was easy. 350 bucks. I established Don Dweeb as a face. I don't know how that happened. Okay.
I need, so glad we won that match, Don. It was a pleasure working with you. I agree. So I wonder
if we can do a tag team or something together. Um, everybody's sleeping on the ground. This is
weird. It's a gas leak. Another win just makes you another target Dweeb. Now it will mean even more
when I beat you. Oh, you're not going to have very much health tomorrow, are you? Oh no,
I'm making enemies. All right. Dweeb, you proved your point. I don't want any more trouble with you.
Yeah. You went right to bed. Okay. I got to get out of here. Oh, you know, I'm tired too.
I'm a little sleepy. Oh, I can't sleep on the street here. Why not? Hotel, hotel. Yep. Where's
the hotel? Cemetery. No, I want to go to the hotel. What? Are there people in these caskets?
No, I don't, I don't know about this. I was right in front of it. Where is it? Podcast experience.
Share your where? Where? Where? The right? Hurry. Hotel. Oh shit. Hey, I know you. What's up? Oh,
cool. You want to like room together? All right. Yeah. Can I have one of your, uh, water? Well,
all right. I guess I'm, I'm going to sleep on the bed, I guess. Appreciate you letting me have the
bed. Hot bunk sleepover. Yeah. Four hours of comfortable sleep. That was it. I want to get
that championship. But your Libre is really not doing well. All right. There's a three way match
at 7 PM. That sounds good. I'm going to stay in the bed for a little while. I think it's for the
best. Can I go on the bed again? I know I wash my hands. So how do we work together?
Oh, we're like doing a good friend. This is I like this guy. All right. So how do we do anything for
me? I think we're just talking. We're just hanging out. This is healing me. Look at my health. What?
I just wanted to wish you luck in your match tonight. Dawn Dweeb. Who's this? After all,
dangerous things happen back here and it would be a shame if you ended up crawling to the ring.
But neither of us want that to happen. Hand over $870 and I'll let you live.
Okay. Yeah. Bring it. You piece of shit. I'll be ready. It's not even worth my time. Dweeb,
I'll get you when you least expect it. Mm hmm. Sure you will. You believe that guy?
It's not him, right? This is not this is this person that's not the person I was just on the
phone with. I don't know. Eaton. Eaton. I think this is the guy. Eaton. This is the guy. I think
Eaton. This is the guy. This is the guy that I was just he was literally talking through the door.
You're more popular than me. I don't want any trouble. Oh my god. The match.
Listen Dawn Dweeb. A lot has changed since we first signed you to $900 a week. Yeah. I got
I got something going on here in a second. Yeah. We have to make sacrifices to stay afloat. How
would you feel about a pay cut? Pay cut, huh? Yeah. Yeah. Just just a quick pay cut. Yeah.
You pay me what we agreed. Yeah. Oh, you're gonna cut me off? What? What do you mean cut me off?
Congratulations on beating Berlain yet again. That raised your profile to 64%.
Somebody's getting choked over here. Yeah, thanks. I appreciate it. All right. I have a match
apparently, I guess. Am I still signed with this company? I'm sure there are places you'd rather
be Dawn, but I'm glad to have you here. Thanks. I got I got to do my I got to do my routine.
I'm so fucking stressed. God damn it. One, two, three.
There's nobody here. This shit's empty. This is where your story starts, Dawn Dweeb. You don't
think I'll be you'll have to learn the ropes here each week before a major promotion even considers
offering you a contract. Why am I talking to myself? For some people it never happens while
others wish it never had because they end up back here broken. Be careful what you sign up for
because there'll be a lot of promoters trying to take advantage of you. If you look after yourself
and make smart choices, it's perfectly possible to have a fulfilling career. Anyway, let's see
what you got before we see how far you'll go. Huh? Who are these people? I thought this is a fatal
three way. Why are there five people in the ring? I'm back at wrestling school. Really?
I got fired. That's that's that's a horse shit. What are you talking about? I didn't take the pay
cut. What the fuck? I have to fight these idiots. It's not even a referee. I'll get signed. Don't
worry. I'll get it. Look, I'll take this opportunity. I'm going to sleep through every match and I'm
going to I'm going to level up my strength and shit. What do I care? I'm not signed any promotion.
I'm just going to go like lift weights, drink at the bar, make friends. Yeah, there's the redemption.
The redemption arc is coming here soon. Yeah, training arc. Don't ask me how the hell this
plays out. Honestly, just disqualify me. I don't even want to be here. It's not even a referee.
Yeah, what am I? Why am I even here? No, fuck this up. I want I want this. I'm taking company
property. This guy does not want me to leave. Come on. No, leave me alone. I'm the he's like
whatever. Oh shit. Oh, good thing for Rupert Royale. I spent $100 taking the chair. All right,
somebody signed me to a deal. I'm so sorry to see you lose to splitters McGinn. That knocked your
profile down to 61%. Yeah, that's too bad. All right, training arc time. I'm going to go sleep
at the hotel. I don't know what this is, but I'm taking it.
Losing your first match was a bad start on Dweeb. It's all downhill for you at wrestling school.
Yeah, I don't think so. I think it's only up from here because I'm down downgraded to the bottom
tier. It's only up. By the way, fuck you. Oh my god, that pissed a lot of people off. I was one
of you. I was one of you guys. We used to be tag team partners. No, I never had one. All right,
let's do it. Sleep. Very good. $160,000. Whatever.
At this point, I'm paying the newspaper to run these articles. I'm not doing this on their own.
Hey, run an article about how I got 10 hours of sleep last night. I have a singles versus
Sebastian slobber. I can win this. I need to heal though. What's the studio? I'm curious.
It's a studio. What's the studio? It's a bar. Studio? How do I get to the studio? Oh,
it's like a podcast. All right, what's going on in here? Oh my god, there's money on the ground.
Holy shit, that was $440 on the ground. Can I be on your podcast? Wait, let me try. Okay,
so what are we going to talk about? I can't interview everyone who sits there.
Go and do something worth talking about. Okay, all right. And I got it on camera too.
Yeah, you can take the tape. Okay, take the tape and I'm ready for the interview.
So what happened there? Well, I decided I was going to attack you and just like film it. And
then that was something you could upload and talk about. I mean, I got, did you see what happened?
I got knocked down. I got knocked down to the wrestling school, which can you actually believe
that? I don't know. It's unbelievable. Oh, I have a match. Nice talking to you. On my way to the bar.
Oh, I'm sorry. I can't go. All right. I'll leave you here at the backstage area. You
know where to find me if you change your mind. I wish I could go with you, but I got a match
right now. Oh my god. My attitude is so bad. Okay. No more lip syncing. This dude came out
and ate a fucking banana. Can you believe it? Anybody who couldn't beat Splitters McGigan
doesn't belong in the ring with me. Splitters McGigan is nothing compared to me. And that makes
you less than nothing. That's kind of not fair. Let me see. Let me see if I can just smash his
head in. All right. Fine. You want to do that? I'm in so much trouble. Why did you trust fall
outside the ring? Because I don't know. All right. Let's wrestle. Get it. Go. It might be too heavy.
Good move. How can you seriously get up faster than me? This guy's way stronger than me too.
Unfortunately. His stats are like five times better than mine. You were just on the referee's
podcast. Was I? Really? Is that the same guy? How did you get here before I did? He's too heavy.
I'm going to lose this match. It's possible, but I need to taunt more. The only way you can do a
special move is that bar in the bottom of the health bar goes up all the way. See if I can get
it. You should use the gun. I'm not going to use the gun yet. That's only in an extreme circumstance.
Nice. That was a really smooth transition. Come on. Yes. What happened there? Make it quick.
Is it possible to come back? I think so. If I can get that filled up, it will be. God damn it.
Bad. Bad. Come on. No. His arms are locked. Why did I make him five feet tall? My reach is so bad.
This is a great opportunity to do this. Taunt. He ain't getting up. Hurry. He's going to get
disqualified. Do it already. Swing it. Swing it then. Hit me with it. Hit me in the face.
Get yourself disqualified. See what I care. I got plenty of time. I'm almost there.
Nice. All right. This should be it. Here it comes. Here it comes. I'm going to be able to
do my... What was my finishing move? I forget. I don't remember. Go for it. Oops.
Do it again. Quick. Ow. That took a lot of health off. Get up. Please don't. How did I do the
Canadian Destroyer? And this guy is now kicking the shit out of me. I don't know what happened
there. I have absolutely no idea. I wish I could tell you what happened. Can I get a submission?
Can we close? He's not near the ropes. My goodness. He's going to fucking submit me, isn't he?
No. No. You get tired? What was that all about? What's going on? Oh, come on. The ref is doing
what I would be doing. He's just like going up on the top ropes, getting down, rolling around
on the ground. I would be just having... I would be jumping around. I do a move and then I get hurt.
This is stupid. That works for me. How come this is not filling faster? Fuck. Ow. What? Why?
Oh, my God. What's happening? Dude. This is illegal. That's illegal.
Oh, my God. Look over here. He's sitting in the chair. I didn't do anything. I can't move.
Oh, my God. Please. This can't end like this. Oh, my God. Please. Get off of me. Why was he
allowed to do that shit? But not me. That's so fucking unfair. I'm at eight, eight, eight, eight.
I'm fine. Count him out. Count him out. I'll do it again. Good. Keep him down. No, you piece of shit.
You got to be fucking kidding me. Dude, I grabbed you. Why are you able to reverse it every time?
Dude, this is... Dude. I keep just saying dude. This match obviously is getting out of control.
Allow me to restore order. There's 10 seconds left. Pin up. Pin up. Quick. No.
I just received word from backstage this match must be restarted immediately.
Huh? What are you doing to us? Dude, that's so stupid. I don't even know who this guy,
Sifu, is fighting. I think it's me. And at some point, don't you just call this match?
You know what I'm saying? Like, at what point is this over? It's been over for a long time.
One of us is going to get injured. That's it. Pin up. Row break is stupid. All right. Maybe I
can make him submit. Let's try it. There's no gun? No, there is no gun. Please just say...
Dude, I do a move to this motherfucker. He just reverses it immediately. Immediately. Every time.
I know. My stats are awful. I don't... Get off of me. I don't even know if I can play anymore. I
think I just have to die. Dude. Dude. Dude. Dude. Dude. Dude. Dude. Dude. Dude. Dude. Dude. Dude.
Dude. Dude. Dude. Dude. I lose. That's un-fucking-believable. This guy's so bad. I made him like a manager.
I made this guy a manager. And I gave him like 40% strength. Get over here. I can't even attack
him. Don't let him get away with this. At least it wasn't affected. Listen Don Dewey. I've got a
match coming up that I'm not sure I can win on my own. Okay. Would you consider assisting me at
ringside for 350 bucks? Absolutely. They made you pay for the banana. I need to start making friends.
I can't just... Everybody hate me. What is money used for? I don't know. This is a... We're doing
this in the gym. What else is over here? It's my water. Give me that water. Wait. Are you... Who's
on my team? Who's on my team? Has the match started? Okay. You got it. You got this. Go for it.
Okay. Orange. Good reversal. Let me know if you need me. I'll be ready. I missed. Oops. God damn
it. How does that miss? I don't... I can't get in the ring. How did you... I don't know how I missed.
Should have hit. Oh my goodness. You go so far. Okay. I got it. I'll take the hit. I'll take that
for you. Okay. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
I don't want to do that. I don't want to get me out. How do I get out of the ring?
Get out of the ring. Okay. There's a pin. I think there's a pin. I think... I couldn't have done it
without you. Jesus. I just wanted to just run and throw something. Can I stay in the gym?
Good fight. What more do you want from me? Excuse me. Oh, suffer it again.
Good. Okay. I don't have a match today, right? I don't think I have a match. I have no... I don't
have anything I can do actually. Read the posters in the gym. I need to sleep. I'm not going to go
to my next match. I'm just not going. I need to level up somehow. I am not going. Nine hours
of sleep. That's good. The industry will come together to stage a special event on the fourth
week of June where all proceeds are expected to be donated to charity. Okay. I have a shoot fight
at seven o'clock. I think I'm just going to skip it. You know what I mean? Should I just skip it?
I have to level up. I can't just... You know what I mean? I need to level up. I'm not going to do
that by just losing a match and then going to sleep. Waking up and losing a match and going
to sleep. It's not going to happen. So I'm punching bags. What do you think? From the track to improve
your stamina. Oh, shit. Really? What the fuck was that? You're not going to be working out
and get out of the equipment. Seriously. I need water. Okay. That was some stamina. Is there any
water lying around? Sleep recharges you. Lift weights for strength. Drink out of the toilet.
What's going on right now? You can try to interact with any scenery by taunting nearby.
Like this? All right. My stamina is at 61%. I'm not going. Should I? I don't have any health.
How is there one bottle of water in this whole fucking gym? There's nothing even in there. How
does it splash? Oh, wait. I need to go. Is there any water on the ground here? I have no stamina.
This is the one for charity? I don't think it is. There's actually people here in this one though.
What were the rules in this one? I didn't notice. Scorpions, I know you're cowering backstage
clinging to that undergraduate title of yours. That may be the safest place for you right now,
but that treasure can't stay buried forever. I want you to pay attention to what happens
in this match because you're next. Fuck. This is bad. This is bad. This is really bad.
I'm in a lot of trouble here. You know, I need to cheese this fight. Yeah, I do. I have an idea.
Did you just really hurt your back? Go get the gun. This is not a hardcore match. There's no gun.
I promise. There's a sludge hammer over there. Your character is 50. I completely forgot about
that. Goodness. He's 55. I'm going to lose immediately here. You designed the worst
fighter possible. Shit. Go change the character in the editor. I guess I could do that and just
put his stats to like kind of normal. How much longer am I going to be in this admission for?
All right. Whatever. This guy's done. I'm retiring this guy. Don Dweeb is being retired. I'm
literally retiring Don Dweeb. No, I don't want to get up. God, stop doing that move.
He's despised.
All right. Okay. Don Dweeb. I've had enough. Oh my god.
Yeah. Most hated man in wrestling school. Don Dweeb. Shittiest character ever. I'm just
going. I'm just going to the subway. I'm going to the airport. I'm leaving. Where's the airport?
I'm just getting on a plane. I'm leaving. Barber shop. It's across from the gym. This way?
Leaving town. Yeah, it's time to leave town. I didn't want to go to the cemetery.
What's over here? Okay. Let's go. Where am I going? How much is a plane ticket? What am
I? Am I going to a different state or a country? Where am I going? Country? All right. I'm going
to be that guy. I'm going to pick the only empty seat that's next to you and eat a bunch of food.
Is there a bathroom? The plane was moving. I just bought another plane ticket. What? No,
I was. I thought it was a bathroom. How long do you stay on the plane for? This is so ridiculous.
I want to sit next to you. Can I get healed? It's been a rough six months here. Something you want
to say to me, Don Dweeb? I mean, kind of. I have a proposal for you. Well, you have my attention now.
What do you want to talk about? Well, I'd like to work with you. How do you see us working together?
Would you be my partner? We don't even work for the same company. I don't see that happening
anytime soon. Can you believe this guy? Am I sleeping? Who's asleep? Why do you never have
health? Because this guy, this guy. What? What happened? What happened? What happened? What
happened? What happened? What happened? What happened? I threw like a fucking cell phone at
him. What? What the fuck was that? What happened? God damn it. Don Dweeb has been booked to face
score bends in a singles match on the third week of June. You're a menace. I honestly, I didn't mean
to do that. I didn't, I just threw something. No, no, no, no, no, no. No, I have to, I have to.
Oh my fucking goodness. I have to, he's retiring. He's trying. I'm starting over. I'm starting over.
I'm starting over. Just leave. Just leave everything. Get out. He's retired. Why is it slow?
Longest careers. Okay. Okay. We're going to, I'm making a wrestler now and it's going to be a good
wrestler. He's going to be strong. He's going to be fearsome. He's going to be, he's going to obey
all the rules and everything. It's going to be fine. We're going to make me strong.
He's going to be huge. What's a good place to start? What's like a actually like famous place
where I'm not going to get like just immediately kicked out? Is it Hollywood or revolution?
A-A-W. Okay. We're going to change a splatter. I'm going to make this quick. This guy's going
to be very good. No, not me strip. Why did that auto fill? What? I'm so confused. Me strong.
This one is going to come out with like a bat. If I come up with cash, can I just take it and
it's a $400? Definitely a hammer or a pizza. Blank. Strong. It's going to be 99% strong.
Well, that's too much. That's not fair. Let's say like 92. Really, really good attitude as well.
Me strip. No, this is me strong. I said 80, 85 popularity. Me strong is very popular.
At least 85. Okay. This is fine. I'm okay with this. Not too egregious, right? You think 85. Okay.
Me strip. Well, okay. Let's take the skill down because if he's really this strong and then,
I mean, he's supposed to be like a caveman. So me strip. There. You happy? Now he's, he's not
OP. All right. Age. Not 55. Seven, 10. That's too big, isn't it? Six, five. Six, five is okay.
Yeah. I need like caveman face. Okay. Shave. No, it looks like my face. That's kind of freaking me out.
This is freaking me the fuck out right now. Okay. We got to find a good one.
I kind of like this one. All right. 39. Definitely 39. I don't think I need to see anything else.
Yeah. 39 for sure. Baggy skin. How do I get rid of those arm bands? Material. I don't want
any material in my arms. How do I get rid of this? What? Yeah. What's your plaid arms?
I don't know how to take this off. Flesh. Okay. There we go.
I mean, it's this one. I need chest hair. No, no fish nets.
This is denim. Oh my goodness. It's denim. The denim is so weird. Okay. I like, I want the denim
for some reason. Okay. There it is. How do you copy? Can I copy this? It looks like I can, right?
Fish nets. No. I'm going to kick the shit out of everybody by the way. Okay. It looks good.
Looks good. What's going on with his arms? Oh, baggy sleeves. What's happening?
Casual can have glasses. That's fine. Okay. No collar. That's fine. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. I
need to change this to that. Okay. How do I get this off? Can this knock him off? There we go.
Okay. I got it. No, he's strict. Coward. All right. The moves. Okay. I don't want it. No,
no partners. No, nothing. No partners. No story friends. No promotion. All American wrestling,
wrestler face. I think the moves are fine considering it's that character. So that's
a big heavy character. Should be good. I don't think they're going to do much. Yeah. This is
going to be great. All right. From the Northwest USA. Where was the first man ever recorded?
We're in the Middle East. Africa. Make him Canadian. Okay. Okay. That's funny. It's Canadian.
Wrestling career. Let's go. Let's do it. I'm ready. Good. Singles versus wide tied 10 PM. I'm ready.
No more fucking around. Don't let anybody scare you out of taking this route. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yep. I'm unstoppable now. Look at how much damage I just did. I see you've just had to take
responsibility for what happens behind the scenes. Me strip. If you take this route,
it's your responsibility to get through the curtain in time for your match. Yep. I know
how this works. Only enter when your time is up. Amber means somebody else's match is taking place.
What if I make my own fucking rules? That guy's a gun. Look after it. I know. I know. I get it.
It's too much to handle. You can always opt out and skip straight to the action. I know.
This is a very weird taunt that I didn't know that I had. Me strong. Me pick up thing on ground.
What thing? What thing do? What thing do? I don't think you can shoot the gun. You can't shoot the
gun. I don't have enough intelligence to shoot it. I don't think you can shoot backstage.
There's no ammo. Is it my turn? Yeah, you can't shoot it. Singles match coming up. Haunt. Yeah,
I tried. L2 didn't work. You can't. You're not going to shoot me, right? Ow. Yeah, you cannot
shoot the gun. I thought I just killed that guy. My turn. Me strip. Wait, what does it say? I need
money more than I need yet another win on my record. For 20 to $2,000, I could be persuaded
to lie down and hand you a victory. What? Oh no, I have to pay you. No thanks. That's not happening.
Beating I give you will cost more than $2,000. Will it now? I don't know. You can't shoot. There's
no you can't shoot the gun. Unless there's some weird way to do it. What the fuck? Get up. This
is way better. Me stop you. Me slam. Me. Me lose match. Me lose match. Me lose match cause count out.
Come on, get in here. This is us frog. You don't know rules of fight. Me fight anyone who stand in
way. Wow. Oh my goodness. He's breaking my arm. I love how the punches are so strong. We get a pin
here. He choke. Pin. Oh my God. He's unbeatable. I'm going to be a millionaire. Me Canada. Me cause
injury. Loud sound startled me. Could be snake. Now strip. He's like scared. I don't know. Let's get
away. All right. I'm ready. Let's go. I'm ready. I'm going to get that championship belt. Yeah,
I'll take 2000. What was 700 bucks? Make a mistake. Congratulations on beating Y tie. That
raised your profile to holy shit. Everybody wins their first match. Me strip competition will get
stiffer at auto. Oh my God. I'm more skillful than you. Me strip. Don't start something. You
can't finish. How do we take this outside? Let's take it outside. Oh, menace. He can't be tamed.
Somebody needs to stop him. Why would he know what the stutter is? Why would he know what that is?
They're all trying to get away so bad.
All right. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I can't just do this
every time. Do I get popularity points for coming and just causing a fucking ruckus?
I thought that guy's name was Glitter Andy. I need health. I need to go to bed. Oh my God.
What a brilliant idea. We sleep on park bench. We don't know what bed is. We don't like you.
We skateboard. That's better. We sleep. Territorial. We refuse to pay income tax.
All right. Singles match. We're at nine o'clock. Ow. I want the skateboard. I'm taking it with me.
I'm going to the bar. It's a dull joke from chat. I did. You're right. Looks like you had a late
night me strip. Go to sleep at a sensible time for more energy. What's this guy doing? Me drink.
Perfect. This is 9 a.m. bar visit. Is it? No, it's not that early.
Wait, can I just drink this stuff? Oh my goodness. I'm sorry. What's up? Somebody,
you're a fire. Another stunner. All right. I have a match in like an hour.
And honestly, it doesn't matter. I'll be fine. I wasn't even looking at it.
This is such a shit show. It seriously is. What's this? Strange thing. Delicious.
Must eat more. Bring more food. Usually eat carcass of animal. Match. I don't know where it is.
Where is it over here? Where is it? I don't know. I actually forget where it is.
I showed up an hour late to the match. They wouldn't even be doing this anymore.
They waited an hour for me to get here. Let's be out here cutting another promo. But screw that.
I got something real to say. The truth is that all American wrestling is getting slaughtered
in the ratings by weekend warriors. And you can blame Matt Showman for that. Everybody knows I
should be the world champion. It's a perfect Sean as the future of this company. We all know who
should be the United States champion. Probably going to be fired for this, but I don't care.
The important thing is that the truth heard is heard for once. I don't think you want to go blow
to blow with Mee Strip. That's a big, that's a big problem. I don't think that was a, what a, what a,
what a dummy. What a dummy. Good. Good. Good. What is, what is, what is Mee Strong's moves?
There you go. Big suplex. All right. When do I get the title match?
Because I'm obviously better than everybody here. Big power bomb. Let's see it.
People like, uh, Mee Strip, right? Really good ratings, right? I gotta go find the title holder.
Okay. Sounds good. Just hang him here. Let the blood flow. I think I'm going to stun. Yeah,
it's a stunner. Why does he have a stunner? That's so stupid. No one's beating me. All right. That
was relaxed. Is he finally dead? Did he go too hard? Did he go too hard?
Oh, all right. Let's go. Profile has improved. I'm just ruining careers at this point.
This game is so ridiculous. It just really is.
So outrageous. I wish I, maybe I should have spent some time to learn about the, um,
general manager mode, but this is exactly what I wanted to do. All right. I should probably,
what should I spend money on? What do you spend money on? Show is finished. All right. Time for
bed. Still up. Did you catch that in midair? All right. Go to bed, bed, bed, bed, bed, bed.
Oh, wait. What about the studio? I'm notable enough to talk, right? At this point, I think I am.
Oh, wait. Actually doing taxes. Heard you've been starting fights, Mee Strip. You need to save that
energy for the ring. If you make this unsafe for work environment, then I'll just have to keep you
out of it. We're pleased to be joined in the studio by Mee Strip of All American Wrestling.
You ever heard of someone called Winston Barker from Maple Leaf Grappling? I'm a huge fan.
Winston Barker is an asshole. Well, let's just hope you don't bump into Winston Barker. You
might regret saying that. We never have any regrets. If you had to guess what percentage
of your matches would you say you've won throughout your career so far? This is where
Mee Strong holds up his hand and has his two, one finger up and he looks at it for a long time.
We have two. Me win two. That's exactly right. You obviously pay attention to every aspect of
this sport. How do you like working for Lance Monaco at All American Wrestling? This is him
right here. I like. Oh, Lance Monaco. We'll be happy to hear that. I'm sure you'd be there
for a long time. Lance Monaco is an asshole. You came across really well, Mee Strip. Thanks
for your time. You know, you can initiate conversations with people by taunting in
their direction. There's another person in here. What the fuck? What? Hi, Mee Strip. Do you have
time to answer some questions for an article we're writing? What box? Yes. Thanks for doing
this, Mee Strip. It'll be a great opportunity to raise your profile. Let's talk about your relations.
Who would you say your best friend is right now? Lance Monaco is my best friend. It's the last
person I talked to. Lance Monaco will be happy to hear about that. I'm sure he feels the same way.
It's literally the last person I spoke to. Tell us about your career at All American Wrestling.
How much are they paying you right now? I don't know. How much? Is it 24? 2,000. You're worth
every penny, Mee Strip. I can see you take this business seriously. Setting aside your
personal feelings, which promotion do you think has the highest TV ratings? Yes, Sun. Sun does
rise. No, Rising Sun is not. It's only at 87%. It seems you don't care what happens outside the
ring. I think you came across quite well. Thanks for your time. We're pleased to be joined in the
studio by Mee Strip of All American Wrestling. What is going on in here? You seem to have heat
with Winston Barker. So tell us how you feel about that. I just talked about my problem with
the Barker over there. I could never forgive Winston Barker. He's just sleeping. Oh, the
rivalry is never going to end. Tell us about your career at All American. How many weeks have you
have left on your contract? I have no idea. Are we 32? Exactly right. You obviously take this
business pretty seriously. Tell us how your training is going. How strong would you say you are?
Strong? Mee Strong. Mee Strong. 95%. Mee Strip. Strong? No, Mee Strip. Then I get up and start
dancing. I think you came across quite well, Mee Strip. So thanks for your time. That Mee Brother.
Twin Brother. Mee Strong. He went to sleep. I'm trying to use the phone. I don't understand how
to use the phone. Give me the skateboard. Yes, I'll use some new strikes. Good. It's important
for a fighter to adapt. I hit him in the head so hard that he I guess thought we were training.
Hello? Somebody said you factory reset him. Oh my god. Okay. All they would have discovered
a new talent known as slow petrol. I'm at 100%. $200,000. Damn. No show. Nothing scheduled.
To be fair though, let's be honest. If a caveman did come into this world, I wouldn't be surprised
if they were fascinated by a skateboard and a cell phone. So I think this actually plays this. This
is placed into the brand here. Mee Strip. I'm here to challenge you to a match on the third week of
July. Uh, on the wall? That's not me. What are you talking about? No, me tired. I should have known
to be too scared. I'll get you one day, Mee Strip. Sorry, me phone. Sorry, me need to take this.
Hello? I don't have a match today. I can do whatever I want. I think you had a rough night,
Mee Strip. Sleep on it. I've had, I'm literally at almost 100% HP. Learn to read. Barber shop.
Oh, Mattie McFly. We're friends. I got a haircut. Who's the barber? At a threat? At a threat?
Somebody cut, was somebody gonna cut my hair? Let's go. Somebody, I want my haircut.
Are you the barber? I painted a picture of me getting a haircut on this. Me want this. Me want
the beaver. How do I get a haircut? Oh, okay. You do it yourself. All right. Okay. I'll be nice,
but I won't be nice to this person. Oh, shit. All right. We're going for it. Since we're such
good friends, do you mind if I have that pipe? No. My stick. I'm tougher than you, Mee Strip.
Don't start something you can't finish. This food? What is this? What the fuck was that?
What is this? Ow. I'm going to go train other brass knuckles again. I want even more strength.
Nintendo 64? Oh, yeah. Me and Lance are friends. All right. Let's do some weightlifting. Better
attitude. That's good. I'm going run and lift at the same time. Oh, shit. That's bad. Can I
sleep here? Uh, I can sleep in the hospital. Slow down, Mee Strip. Running might get you there
quicker, but it also makes you tired. I'm going right here. This doctor always has a briefcase,
and he's always violent. 65%. That's fine. All right. This is singles hardcore match.
Bring some water, and I'm going to go beat the absolute shit out of this person. My god.
This is glass. I want this. Oh, my god. Thank god I missed.
Okay. Arena time. The arena's connected here, right? Yeah. Backstage. God. Come on. Really?
I wanted to put somebody through that. Hey, I want that belt. Can I talk to you for a second?
I want to challenge you for the belt. Why are you not paying attention to me at all? Talk to me.
Don't know a wall. I mean, kind of. Yeah. This is my turn. Not yet. All right. Hardcore match
coming up. This is my match. I'm fighting this guy right now. We haven't gone in the ring yet.
Get off me. They're waiting for us to come on stage. Oh, my god. Oh, no. That's bad. This is
bad. What are you waiting for? You need to go through the curtain now. Oh, shit. I'm getting
there. I'll get there. I'll get there. That was not the right person. I thought that was the person
I was fighting. What happened? Why? Is this for a belt? Dude, this is for a belt, I think. I think
this is... Why are there two referees? Why do referees have belts on? What the fuck is happening?
I'm sure you're all aware we're the reigning tag team champions, the referees. Unfortunately,
the competition in this division is so pathetic that we've resorted to finding our own. That's
why we're pleased to announce that we'll be granting a title shot to whoever wins this match.
Oh, shit. Please don't lose. Don't lose. I got beat up backstage by a gigantic coin.
Whatever that was. I gotta get out. Okay, I'm fine. All I gotta do is just pick this up. You
piece of shit. Give me that. Give that to me. Oh, my god. I got the belt. What if I just leave with
the belt? Can I run away with the belt? Don't. Oh, okay. What a fucking idiot. Please let me go.
Club. Yeah, it is. It's so stupid when that happens. These guys are just still standing here.
How did that catch on fire? I actually got it, thank god. The random guy with the
mustaches going up here. Careful, this thing's gonna fall. I need to... Something. There's a bat
in there, good. Get away from me. Get away, get away. Okay, I got it. I'll get the title shot now.
So, it's the tag team title? I don't have a partner. Holy shit.
It's not moving for some reason? Dude, stop doing that. I'm pinned him when he gets in the ring again.
This is fucking crazy, man. This is crazy.
You earned your shot at the tag team titles, but I don't have a partner. If what you wish for,
I'll turn your dreams into nightmares. Appreciate the opportunity, Addering Ron,
but you just made the biggest mistake of your life. Addering Ron is going to die. Oh, man.
This is always such a joke at the end of every match. It's just chaos every time.
He peeked his head out for one second, and that's all it took.
You in a little bit of music? I'm being limited by this organization.
I got a piece of that pie, right? Yeah. Nice.
Congratulations on winning your third match, Mestrip. You remain undefeated at all American
wrestling. Hey, thanks for the congratulations. Appreciate it. I've been starting fights,
you need to save that energy for the ring. So, I actually should be careful. They'll probably
kick me out. Yeah, I'm going to get kicked out if I don't stop. Of course, I threw it at the
magician or whoever that guy is. I'm going to stop, I promise. I'm not going to kill anybody.
Addering Ron's stamina has improved. Damn.
Wait, Bentley has developed a heated rivalry with Mike Bale of wrestling school. He's not
going to be the announcer. Okay. What's going on this week? Geez. What do you think of the
new hairstyle our stylist suggested for you? Yeah, I was going to say that. It's too clean.
It's over. Somebody says he's going corporate. Okay, no show here. I can roam around.
I'm still here. It's a weird shot. Why did I just puke? What was that? What's wrong with me?
I don't understand what just happened. All right. Can I take a shower? What? What are you two looking
at? You, you're a giant coin. Get out of here. I didn't start any fight. Okay. So I, does this
count as a shower? Should, right? I think that counts. Oh, I guess I go speaking of toilets. I
gotta go pee. All right. I'm staring at me. I've never seen somebody go to the toilet with fully
clothes. What is it, dude? What's going on? It's just, it's mayhem. This whole game is mayhem.
Fully clothed. I'm wearing a pair of underwear. These two hate each other. Look at this. They want
to fight so bad. What? This is not a dick, right? Is there a dick? No. What? I don't even know what
just happened, but I didn't mean to do that. Okay. I get, I'm out of here. These people are freaking
me out. Come on. I'm losing weight. Yeah. There's no match schedule, so I'm good. Anything you want
to talk about? Why am I setting up a shot at pool? Oh, that's right. I can't, I stopped starting
fights. You're right. That's really stupid of me. I think they got one of my attention, but
that title match is coming up too. Vstrip's influence has inspired everybody else in the
All-American Wrestling roster to improve their stamina. Eight-man tag team match. How is this
going to work? All right. This is going to be insane. I'll be back. I'm going to pee.
I'll see you guys in like two minutes. Here, pee. Eight-man tag. I don't know if this is going to
work, but apparently it is. Okay. That's good. Good. So I'm going to just, 8 PM. So that's pretty
quick. Wow. That's one way to get out of bed. Holy shit. That's like the government CIA training.
Like that's like secret agent training to do that. That's insane. American dad. Yeah. All right. I
got full health. I'm not going to, what's wrong with me? Why am I swaying around? Did you wash
your hands? Of course I did. Climb to improve. Oh, all right. That's cool. Glad I could influence
your look, me strip. I was wondering, I was worried that my legacy would be forgotten. Why
I took this guy's haircut? Hold on. We have the same haircut. Eating and drinking is good for
energy boost, but you'll make yourself sick if you're full. I appreciate it. Jester. We actually
have the same haircut. I don't even know who this is. What happened? What? Why did I puke?
He just told you? Yeah. I didn't think. I just woke up. I slept for nine hours and I wake up
and I have a fucking apple and I throw up because I have too much food in my stomach.
What are you on about? What do you want about game? Oh shit. My match. This banana was on fire.
Get out of here. All right. It's okay. It's an eight man tag match. I'll be fine. Who's on my team?
Just me. This is shit's going on in the ring right now. There are more than eight people here. One,
two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. There are like 12 people here. There are way too many
people in the ring. Legal. What? Hold on. Um, do we even know who's on whose team?
Okay. Apparently it's just me. These two, I think it's just me and this guy. They're not all against
me, right? I don't think so. Take them all out. Oh, that's illegal. That's illegal. I gotta get rid
of this. Take one step forward. I actually look naked. Danny DeVito coming out of the couch. Nice.
Pretty good horse tactic. Stunner. Let's go. So what's, is there balls count anywhere or
let's find out who's even on my team. Me strip looks like my father and it's weird.
That's really weird, dude. It's weird. It's dad. Okay. Count it.
What the hell was the point of all these people? What a joke. Why were they all here?
And now you're all in big trouble. Ain't nobody getting out of here alive.
No one's getting out. Oh shit. They get no lock on is just so hard to switch between people.
Okay. So what about my status? There were two teams. I guess you're going to get fired. No,
am I? I don't think so. We're almost at the top, almost 90%. We're almost at number one.
I got 10 grand. That Stunner is a nice finisher. I can't wait to kick out of it. Oh, I can't wait
to kick out of it. What's the point of this game? Become the best wrestler in the world.
I wasn't even going to use it. I didn't do anything. This guy, this dude's AI is probably
going to throw that eventually here. I want to be nowhere near it. I didn't do any of this. I have
nothing to do with this. People just squaring up in a lobby. Yeah, this is like the beginning
of a Fortnite game. We're waiting to drop out of the bus. Oh, here we go. Here we go. This is
at start. It just started. There he is. That's the guy with the dynamite in his hand. You know he's
going to throw it. There he is. He's going to take a little too much punishment and he's going to
throw it. Only a matter of time. He's not throwing it. He's smart. All right. I'm out. I need to go
to sleep. Jesus. All right. Goodbye. Where's the phone? It's on the ground somewhere. Who knows?
Get the fuck away from me. Is it by the trash? Where is it? There's the phone.
I was over here. It sounded like it was on the right side. All right. Hotel room. So when does
the title shot happen? I feel like that was like an hour and a half ago. Why are you sleeping in
a crib? We had a confrontation. I'm curious. I don't know what it is. Why did I get consciousness
when Mee Strong was just like a dumb guy that yelled, I hit you. Somebody gave him
consciousness. I always get a haircut. What do you want? Mee Strip, I'm tired of being mentioned
the same breath as you. It's time to change the conversation. Everybody talks about me like I'm
your inferior, but we both know that I've always been your superior. Down with this sort of thing.
I'm sure you would prefer me to stay in the shadows, but my light is too bright for that.
Don't worry about shadows too much because you won't be seeing any more of those after I knock
your lights out. What do you mean? What do you mean? She's got a weapon. Oh my goodness,
that was brutal. That was horrible. Oh my God. All right. I did it. I did it. I beat you up.
I did it. I'm good. I'm good. I did it. Poor guy. I don't want to... That was the guy with the
dynamite by the way. I guess I... Fine. Oh shit. How did we stop? Okay. I did it. I'm done. Bro,
back off. Okay. All right. That was it. Okay. Goodbye. Oh my God. Oh shit. Okay. I might
actually lose. Me strong never loses by the way. Well, when does this stop? It was like,
oh, a confrontation. I'll beat you up. Okay. We've concluded that we both have been beaten up.
We've concluded that we beat each other up. Is it a pin? I don't think so. That hurts.
That really hurts. I just damaged all my internal organs. I just have it out for this guy. I don't
know why. Stop starting fights. It's... But it's like GTA in Grand Theft Auto. When you're walking
around and it's just a person that you just like run into them. They went down. Okay. We'd make a
pretty good team, me strip. How would you like to make it a regular thing? This is the guy that I've
been beating up every day. We can make a much bigger impact together. You know what? Yeah. Sure.
I need a tag team partner for the tag team championship. This is it. All right. This is
the big one. Tag team championship. I kind of feel like an idiot because I've probably brought this
guy's health and stamina down by like 80% of the last three days. This guy gets no rest. I see him
and I attack him. I've hit this guy in the head with more objects than are currently in my office
right now. I'm kind of causing a problem for myself. What is gimmick? Gimmick I think is just
your kind of character sheet. All right. Tag team championship. You still have the... Okay. Let's go.
I'll see you when we... No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Hold on a minute. Hold on
a minute. Can you get it? No, you cannot. No. What just happened? Why did he just fall down?
What did he just do? He just fell over. He attacked her? Why? We don't have... We don't
try to make problems with other people. All right. I don't want to mess around. Hey Meshrip,
can I have that phone? Sure. I'm roaming right now so don't make any long-distance calls.
I know exactly what I'm going to do with it. Make a phone call. That was so threatening for no reason.
It's a 2000 like one joke. Oh please. Thanks for the phone back. All right. I think I dialed the
wrong number. I was hoping to speak to Karen Mahoney. Who did you call? I didn't... It wasn't
me. It was somebody else. Nice try. Where's my tag team partner? Any minute now we're going on
stage. I just keep thinking of that guy's dad. I don't know why. Like this guy's dad in chat.
I don't know why it's freaking me out. I don't know where my partner is but we gotta go.
This is for the tag team championship. Meshrip and Bubba Hyena. All right. Yeah, there you are.
Bubba Hyena and I have joined forces to become even greater than the sum of our parts.
All the other teams in All American Wrestling better watch out because we just raised the bar.
That's right but actions speak louder than words so let's show these people what they
what we're about. You idiot. Dumbass. I'm gonna do that again. Look where the... Where are you
fucking going? I think that seriously the person... I don't even... People on the other team right now
like seriously need to shut the fuck up. Okay. You might tap out from this I think. Whoa! I caught
his leg in midair. Oh no. Oh no. This is it. That was so long. I'm joking.
They're not even fighting. What are they doing over there? He's like rubbing his leg. What the fuck?
Oh that was so dumb. That was so long.
You can't tell me those two were seriously just sitting there lying down.
You guys are gonna kill me. Stop. Oh all right. Let's get back to reality here. Oh god damn.
No. The crowd is silent. It was just like an awkward... I don't like... Like this was bad.
This sucked. What a shitty match. Four people just like lying down like next to each other.
Why am I still joking? Okay I gotta get up.
Oh okay. I'm getting out of here. I'm getting the fuck out of here.
Music. Oh it's... All right. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Enough.
Oh we're just lying down. Everybody in the... Honestly what really kept me going there is the
audience is just quiet man. Quiet. Silent. It's like god damn. That was the tag team championship.
You got two guys coming out in like fucking gimp suits. We're just lying down. Okay and then you
kept going. I don't know man. It was just... Got those belts on though. You believe we're tag team
champions? Look how far we've come together. Yeah we have. Shake hands. All right. Okay.
Somebody's jealous. Where are you taking him? Where are you taking him? I'm on my way to the hotel.
You need a ride? Um sure. We can walk across the street. Just follow me and I'll get you to the
hotel as soon as possible. Bro it's across the street. We're gonna both walk there. What do you
want? What are you doing? Okay it's friendly. Why do you have that? Well I don't want you looking at
this. I'm putting this somewhere safe. Just go to bed. Whatever. What are you doing out this late?
You should probably get to get a good night's sleep. I'm about to do that. Can I have a title
shot? What was that? Why am I holding the championship belt? Am I asleep? Am I having like
memories? Like flashbacks? Go to bed. Go to sleep. Boomtown has been released by Wrestling Revolution.
Oh no. Why Tides feud with MeStripped peers who have lost momentum is no longer over with the fans.
What happened to my health? After five hours of comfortable sleep, MeStripped's energy levels
are 84%. What happened? MeStripped has come down with an illness and is in poor health this week.
That didn't die in my sleep right? No ring tag elimination? But uh look at me. He's gonna have
to carry. Your energy looks a little low. Find something. You can't eat that. That's not edible.
Bro that's not. Bro he's trying to kill me. He's trying to kill me. Get him. He poisoned me in my
sleep. He poisoned me in my sleep. Tell him to kill him. How could you do this to me? What?
What's happening? Help. Help. He's killing us. I need to have. Why don't you wear the same costume
as me? What are you talking about? No you should dress like me. Who's talking here? I don't want
to dress like you. Let's just leave things as they are. I know I'll be fine. You may have beaten me
in the ring but the result will be different outside the ring. This he poisoned me in my sleep
and he tried to kill my friend. Stop him. Stop him. I'm clinging to my last. The belt will always
be mine even in death. You don't want trouble? You shouldn't have fucking poisoned me. Get him.
Nice job. He's not talking to me right? Why am I sad in the corner? Um somebody help? I feel like
this is the one ring. Oh my god we have to get in the ring. I feel like Gollum right now. All right
we gotta go. We have to go. I need food. I need something to eat quick. I need water or something.
Food. Water. Leave me the fuck alone. Unless you have food. Food. Is there water on the ground?
I need a water bottle or something. Anything. Anything. What the fuck? Battering happens to be
a friend of mine. I just you don't. Dude let me up. Where's my tag partner? Square the fucking balls.
Whose phone? Um we have a match. Please. Is there anybody have any water? Is there any water or
anything? Food. Grapes. I'll take bananas. Oh shit. Me Strip and Graffiti? Who's Graffiti? Where's my
tag partner? Last week Graffiti and I became the new tag team champions. That's not their name.
It was like Bobby Hyena. We told everybody we're the best when we first got together and now it's
official. That's my partner. We're going to bring legitimacy back to tag wrestling. Am I shit faced?
Don't expect us to break up anytime soon because the only teams we break up are our opponents.
No my guy's over here. We got to the top sticking together and that chemistry would keep us at the
top. This is my guy right here. I'm holding the other end of the belt. I'm not going over there.
They can fucking kill each other for all I care. Oh god. Get away from me. Get away. Get away. Get
away. If you want to hit me you're gonna have to go through Bobby Hyena. That guy has water? He does.
Jesus Christ. I'm gonna die. No he's drinking it in front of me to like just spite me. Do you see that?
No please. I was too heavy. Give me that water. Give me that water now. Give me the water. No I
don't want this useless piece of junk. Where's the water? You guys have water over here? They might.
They're like a commentary table. No I think we need to break this up. I just want water. I just
give me the water. He's sitting there just drinking and taunting me with it. This guy is get step on
him. Stomp. He's somebody he's gonna win this fight right now. You guys understand the gravity
of this situation right now? Give me that fucking water you dumb ass clown. Give me the water.
I got it. You piece of shit drank the whole goddamn thing. How is anybody gonna get pinned? This lady
was just watching. I think it's yeah I can pin somebody if I can just get the bat. Get him off
me please. Somebody. This is it. Ready? Just no one's gonna get pinned. Just go sit in the chair.
I'm gonna count it. I'm actually still on the ground. Let's just leave the match. I think I'll
lose my tag team belt won't I? Is this a championship match or no? I have no idea. What
are you doing? If I can pin the joker I'll be fine. I hear a fire. Give me that fucking belt.
Come out here without me. Pretending like we're not a goddamn team. Give me that pin. Count it.
Why is the ref on fire? That's it. He's serious. This guy has zero HP. Zero. You're talking into
the microphone. Dude. Both of you idiots. It's gonna have to be the jester. It's got a Nintendo
64 and the belt. Get up. Am I? Is he about to leave the match? Spin him around. Oh my god. Get a pin.
That should be it. Thank god. One. What? I don't get it. I don't understand. I have to eliminate
the partners? Oh that's annoying. You know something? This lady, Sharon, has not been
fighting at all. She still has the belt around her waist. Really? We'll turn the lights off.
Why is the power out? Nobody got the power. Now we're friends? After all that bullshit?
Now you come and raise my hand? After all that? Really? What the hell was that? Um. I don't know
who that was. Somebody shook my hand and I fucking hit him in the head with the bat. I don't know
what that was. They freaked me out. I thought they were grabbing me. So I'm hurt again. I'm still
sick. All right. We got, that's not a bad rating. Who's graffiti? I, I have no idea, man. I really
don't. I think the game bugged out and thought we were tag team partners. I have both belts,
which is weird. You want your belt? Take your belt back, man. Yeah. Here. Take your, take that back.
That's yours. Okay. Glitter Andy. I want the phone. Okay. I'm out. I don't know this guy. I don't know
what this guy's doing. Oh yeah. We have the same haircut. I remember you and I were cool.
Please go to the doctor. Um, okay. If you want, I'm gonna do it for you. That's weird. All right.
Into the hospital bed. Good night. I don't know why the doctor is hostile since the very beginning.
It's like Dark Souls. I R1ed him three times and he just is permanently hostile towards me. I don't
know why. All right. I think I'm back in better health. You should talk to him. Meestrip, what do
you think of the new outfit our wardrobe department created for you? Let's see it.
No. You obviously don't know anything about fashion. This is what all the kids are wearing
these days. We're gonna defend the belts. 10 PM today. What? Hello? Wait. Hello? If you're looking
for a Yuri Yakuza, I saw him in the bar. Okay. Motherfuckers at the bar. Listen, I'm not sure
the name Meestrip captures the essence of your character. How would you like to be something
called something like Glitter Cesar? No. Did I make you sound like you have a choice? Your name
is Glitter Cesar now. Get used to it. I thought we were friends. All right. Where's this person
that the phone said go find this person? Where is this person? Oh, I don't know what you did that
for. I don't have any idea. Why did you do that? I can't miss this. This is the tag. Oh my god. What
happened? Am I? What happened? My god, what happened? What? Oh my health. Help. Somebody help me.
What the fuck? This is a, this is a championship match. What do you mean take a nap? Huh? You piece
of fucking shit. Who did that? Okay. Redneck Rosteen. Remember that. I hit my head on the
asphalt. Yeah. Oh god damn it. The show is about to start. Where's the entrance? Where's the
entrance? That was bullshit. It really was. Really? This is such a crock of shit. No way.
No way. Brain is leaking. Somebody said nice Tony Hawk hair. Glitter Cesar and Bubba Hyena. No,
that's not my name. Why are we fighting against these guys again? We're fighting. We just beat
you. You're too young to be a champion Glitter Cesar. You haven't got a clue what that responsibility
means. Last thing is more of a marathon than a sprint and that's why I've been awarded the gold
medal. I'm not doing all right. Oops. I need to, I need to tag out. Tag out. Thank you. All right,
go get him. How am I? I just, what? I just tagged him. Didn't I just tag his hand? The ref didn't
see it. Where's the other? Where's his teammate? Come on. Tag. Tag. There we go. All right. You know
what to do. Oh, good. Good exchange. Get back in there. You got full health, man. You got to take,
you got to take care of this. I'm going to go see, go sit down. That's a good idea. Um, money mark.
I need you to get out of that chair. Why am I getting counted out? I'm not even the legal
person here. I'm not. What are you talking about? What? Get, no, tag back in. Get back up here.
Get in there. Excuse me? What the hell? Help. He's going to beat us.
I can't even get up. Help. This is the championship. You can't do this.
Tag in. Thank you. Jesus. Don't tag me out. I need to go sit in the chair and relax.
Get me out of here. Roll out of the ring. Where are you going with this table?
I can't move. I, I mean, he's, I can't, I'd love to get up. Okay. Do not tag me in, dude. Please
spend one goddamn minute fighting the other guy. This is actually working. This is the worst fight
ever. Is there a drink on the ground? There is. Where is there, where do you see a drink by the
chair? I can't see it. It's a microphone. It's gotta be like a fucking water back here or something.
I'm stuck in the chair. Get up and stop moving. All right. I'm whatever. I'll tag me in and I'm
going to get the shit out of this guy. Now let's go to the right of the chair. Stop climbing. Oh
my God. Stop climbing. Ref didn't see it. Ref didn't see it. Okay. Okay. Ref didn't see it.
Get in the ring. Why are you going in the crowd? You're going to lose us the championship if you
don't get the fuck in the ring right now. I'm still on the ground. I'm not getting up anytime
soon. I think I'm, I am desperately trying to get up here. Is there a fight out here?
I don't know what's happening. Machine learning. Yeah, it does feel like it. Um, I don't know.
We might lose the championship here. Okay. How do I do it in the ring?
Come on. Like a fish out of water. Seriously, you just pulled me out of the ocean.
Like put me back in the ocean, please. I blame the guy. Seriously, the guy that
grabbed me and hit my head on the pavement just fucked me all up. And you know what?
I'm, I don't care anymore. I don't give a shit. I'm hitting this guy. I'm going to crush this.
Okay. Nevermind. Apparently I'm covered in like slippery cooking oil. I can't do anything.
My whole body is covered in vegetable oil. Sit in the chair. Dude, I would love to just walk up
this. Okay. There I am. That was a threat. You know what? Just tag me in. You're obviously
fucking useless. This guy doesn't understand who we should be fighting. They're just walking in
random direction. This is really bad for you to tag me in, but you know what? I at least have a
brain. That was a great save actually. Good. Okay. Yeah, sure. Come on in. We can, we can do a tag
team here. Now I'm going to go sit in the chair. I just need 10% of my health. Oh my God. We're
okay. All right. I have enough health. Now I'm not, I'm like not sloppy. This should be fine now.
All right. There we go. Now I can actually do moves. That's a rope break. Let me know.
Appreciate the help. Thank you. Beautiful. Let's get that pin. Who's drinking? You. No, give me
that. Stop drinking it. Why? Why? Why have all the time? It's been like 10 straight minutes
in this match of all the times for you to do that stupid shit. That's going to be it.
God damn it. Be careful. You're walking into enemy territory. Get that twist that leg. Oh my fucking
God. Pin. This guy is unstoppable. I can't hurt him. All right. Choke him. I don't know what's
happening, but I think I got it. Keep him occupied and this is it. There it is. Hell yeah. That was
some clutch performance by Bobby Hyena. Okay. I don't know what that was about. We can keep our
belts. Referee. Okay. We're good. I got to go. Yeah. Go after the guy that tried to assassinate
you. Yup. Bobby. Yup. Change the name back. I don't think I can. Now I'm very pissed off.
I'm out for blood now. I don't care how much sleep I haven't had. I don't care how tired I am.
Where is he? Where is that piece of shit? Not here. Over the bar. I'll find you. No, he's not in
there. No. Where are you? Oh no. That's all I need. I need 20% health. I'll be fine. All American
wrestling's proposed TV taping on the second week of September has been canceled. Tag team submission?
Oh, he slept in the street the whole time. Okay. It's going to tail him for a sec.
You got nothing to say? Well, yeah. Doctor's going to have a lot to say about what happens
to your face. Get him. Get him. This guy's probably been a menace to everybody. Excuse me?
Where is he? Get over here. I'm more skillful than you, Cesar. Don't start something you can't
finish. I'm putting you in the hospital. You're faster than me? Would you have a race? You better
not fucking break my neck. Find your own business, Glitter Cesar. If you want to be a hero, you'll
die like one. I've got no problem with you. My problem is with this guy. All right. You proved
your point. I don't want to make trouble. Well, that would be nice if... You got a match today?
Hey, dude. Hey, bro. You got a match today? Get away from me. Yeah, dude. I'm just curious.
Okay. I need to eat. Oh my God. I'm at zero health again. I actually need to go in the hospital. I
don't care. I could be an hour or two hours late to the match. I don't care. I can't believe that.
No, please leave me alone. Why am I holding my ass? What's wrong? What's wrong? Do I need to go to
the bathroom? Shut up. No, I can't eat this. Okay. Hurry up. Hurry. Hurry. I just shit my pants.
You gotta be kidding me. What? This is impossible. That's not possible. That's impossible.
It's impossible. You shit yourself. What? No. No. Don't believe those rumors. Don't believe those
rumors. That didn't happen. Those are disgusting rumors and I will not have them spread anymore.
You remind me the tag team champions this long by ducking me. Everybody knows that I'm the biggest
threat to that little title you've been up against. What is it? I'm so confused. You can't put it off
any longer and now prove why you were right to fear me. My weapons are not allowed, obviously.
Imagine shit your pants and not even like going and wiping your ass and going right into a ring
and doing a wrestling like theatrical routine. I didn't even change the pants. I'm not doing bad.
I just have to exchange it. You know what I mean? Like just me strong is all about the right-handed
exchange. In fact, you know what? You go in, please. Glitter shitter. That's not any water
down here. You guys have water? That guy chugged a water last time. I want it. Where is it? The
other guy that was here chugged a water. Please get off. There's no water. Oh my god. I just I
don't want to climb up. Oh fuck it. Whatever. There's nothing here. God damn it. You're doing
so good too actually. I'm trying to get out. You don't understand officer. You don't understand.
Where are you going? Weapons are not allowed. I gotta get this qualified. I don't care.
Wait. It's not illegal if I do it. That's correct, right? Oh my god. He didn't see it, did he?
God. My back. I'm getting out. I'm getting out. I'm getting out. Here we go. Come here. Get the fuck
out of here. Oh he's trying to hit the referee. Where am I? He's got me in the headlock. No.
Dude did shit just pop out? I just saw like brown splatters. Okay. I think I'm good. I am good. I'm
good. There's a bat right here. I'm gonna use it. I'm gonna use it very well. Oh shit. No. I gotta
help my friend. I gotta help my friend. I gotta help my friend. Pin. Pin. Pin. Pin. Pin. Pin. There
are more viewers in chat than there are in the whole arena. All right. I think he's got this in
the bag. I think. Why am I swaying? Oh now you're fucked. Now you're fucked man. Big mistake.
I'll make sure you have as little HP as I do. All right. Get. All right. Tag me in. Tag me in.
Tag me in. Tag me in. Right here. I'm trying to kick him so bad. All right. Tag. Come on. I'm right
here. That's illegal. What he just did was illegal. Tag me in dude. What are you doing? Are you all
right? Is that illegal? Oh my god. I think I killed that guy. Oh no. That's the ref. He's
seriously injured. I seriously injured the ref. What do we do? What do we do? What do we do about
this? Okay. I'm gonna break his ankle. Break it. What? All right. Pin this guy. I'm gonna pin this
guy right now. Get out. We gotta get out. With both of them we're gonna get double disqualified. I
can't let go. No. Get out of the ring. Get out of the ring. What was that sound? Hit that pin.
He's writhing on the ground in pain. Bleeding. Everyone's bloody. This is so fucked up.
I had to get in. I gotta get in the ring. I would love to be tagged. Oh my god. He hit him in the
head with a dumbbell. Dude. That was fucked up. What? He's kicking him out. He's kicking this guy
out. He kicked. That guy didn't do anything by the way. Graffiti is this guy in the middle.
There. Oh my god. We're gonna win. Why did he throw? This guy's been thrown. Oh my god. This
fucking scientist over here is just cosplaying as us. He's wearing our belts. He threw the wrong
guy out. Pin. No. No. No. I gotta let this play out. This is bad. I don't want to just go off
on myself. Come tag me in. I would love you to tag me in. Come tag me in please. You've been in
for so long. Tag me in so I can finish this once and for all. This guy. I'm not your teammate.
I think you might be hallucinating. Is the ref okay? Oh my goodness. You need to tag me in.
Why won't he tag? Just tag my ass in please. Tag. What do I have to do to get you to tag me in?
If you get pinned I swear to god I'm gonna beat the shit out of you in the parking lot.
Oh no. I'll do it myself. Doctor you just blew it. So bad. Get it.
Don't fucking do that shit again. Give our belt back. Oh don't forget this guy. The sister
watches the game. Why did he do that? I hope the ref is okay. I did not do that let's be honest.
Litter says there was upset that he was barely involved in that match.
Errol Hathaway severely injured his shoulder in that match and would be unable to wrestle
for the next two weeks. He may be a shadow of his former self. I'm not the guy that threw
a barbell at his head. I picked him up and I gently placed him over the ropes onto the ground below.
I didn't throw a bunch of shit at him. I didn't throw a heavy dangerous barbell at his head.
I did not do that. You had fun out there Cesar but you made quite a mess of the arena.
If you want to book this venue again you better pay $300. That's fine. Alright somebody's fighting.
I heard a punch. I've not had more than 10% health in like an hour and a half game time.
Oh my god a full night's sleep finally. Okay why do I have a feud?
Perfect Sean is coming down with an illness and is in poor health.
I feel like an animal stuck in a cage and I'm ready to go.
Fans insist on treating Glitter Cesar as a heel despite his attempts to play face.
8 man war versus High Note's team. 8 man war.
Alright I want some food. I want some drink. Did you get the fans on your side to be more popular?
Um I already was a face. Yeah I want to be face. Okay let's start portraying you in a positive
light. The fans will appreciate a chance to get behind you. How is High Note alive?
I don't know. Oh this okay this drops your HP. I want the pizza. I would love for somebody to
explain what happened. I tried to pick the pizza up and I fucking jumped off and hurt myself.
This is money on the ground. Ah yep I'll take 300 bucks. I did the same thing right.
Food I'm gonna just drink the stuff on the ground. I love how this costs money.
Alright I'm good. Wait okay now I'm ready. Get out of here. Why won't he shower?
Do not sleep through your match. I want. Oh my fucking idiot. Here's our team. I'm late for
school. This belt is glued to my body. I have not taken this off. Listen up everybody there's
something I need to get off my chest before we go any further. Did you just bite me? I know I've been
a jerk in recent times. I've said and done some things that I'm not proud of. But I realize we're
nothing without the support of the fans. You're the electricity that gives us life. With your help I
know I can be a better wrestler. I hope I can repay you by fulfilling my potential. Hey we're
done with the life-changing crap. The only drama that matters is in the ring. No I don't want to
give you that. I want this money. This is my money. No I want this money. How do I put the... I want
to pocket this money. How do you pocket the money? I'm trying to pocket this money. If I can't have
it nobody can. Wait is everything legal? It is. This is gonna be a mess. Um okay. Get that high
note. It is. It's dynamite? Why is there dynamite? Why did it explode? How did it explode?
I came out with some people and I don't remember who they are so everyone's an enemy.
Oh the misery. You can set things on fire by holding taunt and then pressing the pickup key.
What? All right time for just absolutely no remorse. There's too many people in the ring we
can't... I don't think there's a pin. I think you just have to knock the people out.
Excuse me? There's a... there are pins. And how do you expect for any single person to get pinned
here? Whose belt is this guy wearing? I don't think this is possible. I might leave. There's
no rope breaks either. Who's winning? I have to shock out eliminated. I need the chair. I need
something dangerous. Get up. Pin this guy. He's a teammate? You gotta be shitting me dude. No way.
Okay I think Harley is on my team. The guy brought money into the ring.
Yeah she is. I might just walk out of the arena. I don't think this is a title match. I'm just
going to be artillery. All right pin pin pin somebody. Am I pinning someone? Burn items by
holding taunt then pressing the pickup button. This guy off me. Save the ref. There is no ref.
Okay taunt. Pick up. Hold taunt. Pick up item. I don't think that did anything. Is that my guy?
All right break his ankle. Good. Oh judgment Dave eliminated. Excuse me don't pin me. You
gotta be shitting me. We're gonna lose. This is just absolute mayhem. Like I don't even know
what's going on. If falls count anywhere I need to bring somebody outside. That's gonna be it.
Thank god. All right I think it's even now. It only works if it's flammable. Can we get this
guy out? Because that's he's. That was 2v1. Good. Really could have lost that one. Yeah um get out
please. These guys shouldn't be in it. They're both still in here. This is horseshit. All right well
now the last one here. Let's make sure that he doesn't. Please. That's it. Apparently it's not.
Now it is. Somebody. You flipped the camera on fire. Get this. You gotta get this on camera.
Hell yeah. Too excited. Too big of a hug. Too excited. I know it can get confusing sometimes
Harley but I mean I want this. I want that 20. Okay I think we're doing fine.
Being hindered but I got more agility. That's fine. I tied as a disappointed that his client
lost that match. All right good match. I want to challenge the person for the world championship.
I don't know who it is. May have been an accident but Errol halfway got hurt because of you.
Before this situation caused any more pain you better pay him 900 dollars in compensation.
Get the fuck out of here. What are you talking about? What the fuck are you saying?
I didn't fucking do anything. That's not my problem. I didn't fucking do anything.
I didn't mean to put all the blame on you. I suppose Errol needs to take responsibility.
I didn't fucking do anything. We won that match thanks to me. Never forget that. True. You don't
look so good. You all right? This guy's got zero HP. Bro there ain't nothing in here. Give me that
back. No take backs. Are you serious? No. Get out of here. Get... Excuse me. I want that. Did I get
it? Give me that. Holy shit that was a nightmare. Oh my god. Wait a minute. Give me this. He's
sleeping. This guy always has a sledgehammer. You know what? Nobody's gonna have it. Give me back
that hammer. I'll show you what it is. All right. I need it for one second. I'll give it right back.
I promise I'll give it right back. That's fine. I'll give it right back. Oh I was gonna hit this
guy in the face with it but now it's just down. That's whatever. That's what a champion does.
Celebration. Why is there another hammer? What's the match?
Confrontation versus Jester at 8 p.m. You got it. Did I lose the hammers? I didn't. I didn't do it.
I just literally pressed left on the analog. What is wrong with this guy? Oh thank god. My
hammers are still there. Oh fuck. I've been playing way too much Elden Ring. I just tried to press
Y and R1 to put this in two hands. Can I take two hammers? I don't think so. Can you? Wait maybe I
can. Oh my goodness. Are you kidding me? Who was the pain in the ass? I can't double hammer. I'm
sorry. Okay. Um okay. Well I'm gonna. No pick up the hammer. All right. Glitter Cesar. What do you
want? Doink. What's this about? Hey Glitter Cesar. When you mess with my friends and you answer to me.
I know it happens to be a friend of mine and I don't appreciate what you did to him.
I not got what he was coming to him man. Don't worry. I got plenty left for you you fucking idiot.
Okay kid. Don't let him take the belt. That's disrespect. Where did the hammer go? Oh nobody
touches my fucking hammers. Oh my god. He got it. Nobody touches my fucking hammers. Threw it into
the crowd. Holy shit. He's still standing. I okay. I kind of want this guy on my team. This is face
behavior. The game wants me to take his health to zero. I'm just doing it in a very efficient way.
I'm the game is like hey take this guy's health to zero. Where is he? He's hiding in the crowd.
Oh man. He's you want to go? Fine. Hammer v hammer in the ring right now. You want to do it? That's
fine. Sure. A nice big hug. Um I want my hammers back. Those are valuable. What's the other one?
Okay there's one and there's two. All right I'm good. He came out and yelled at me and he said he
was gonna kill me. Oh we're almost there. Almost number one. How many runes did you get? All right
I want a championship. We've had we've had tag championships for like two hours. I want the real
prize. Holy shit. All right Lance Monaco you own this league but I honestly didn't do it. I just
oh I don't. If I pick up that other hammer I swear to god it's over for everybody.
I had my hammers in my hand too. Okay where's the other one? I'm not fucking around anymore.
Who did that? You know I've deserved it. I deserved it. That's retaliation for all the dumb
shit I've been doing. So I get it. Anyway that doesn't mean I'm gonna let that fly though.
You know what I'm saying? Oh shit I think my neck hurts. There's too many bodies in the way. I need
all right I'm out. I'm out. I'm done. This guy in the red shirt. I don't know. I don't know what
you're doing. That's your boss. He jumped on me and started hitting me in the head with a wrench.
Hey you got a title. Can we talk? I want to challenge the championship. Give me a title shot.
Title shot. Come here. Get away from me. Oh my god. Thanks for this hammer. I know what I'm
gonna do with it. No that's not yours. Wait can I have a title match? Hey look Errol has recovered
from his injury and looks forward to getting back to work. Have you ever heard of a wrestler
called Tate Madison from Weekend Warriors? I think we could do the gimmick better so how would you
like to be our version of him? What happened? Did I change my hair again? Why do I look fatter
than ever? I'm not imitating anybody. I should have signed the real Tate Madison instead of you.
Here's a champ. Perfect Sean. What do you want Glitter, Cesar? This better be worth my time.
I challenge you to a match. I'm busy on the fourth week of September. Let's talk about this some
other time. What about you? I challenge you to a match. There wouldn't be any chemistry between us
so long as we're both faces. That's not what I asked. I said I want to fight you for your belt.
Heavyweight Championship. I got no show. That means I can do whatever I want.
Anything else to talk about? Alright time to take a shower. Okay there we go. Much better.
The real weird way to take a shower. Would you be willing to sell that table leg for $10? Sure.
Unless you're doing business with you. Serious? Get out of here! Fine you can have it. Take it.
You can have it. I like the gun on fire. I'm just such a little shit. Oh no is he alright?
You guys been fighting in here the whole time? This is what I do on my day off
really. Bam bam. So the way that no match is going on so what's out here? What's going on outside?
Oh there really is nothing going on. Can I sleep in the ring? Go check the subway out.
That's a good idea. Um what happened? What was that? Do you want to talk? I mean I'm just I'm
there's no show or anything going on here. Not today. You know you can maintain your grip
after a move by holding attack or grapple. Actually really good tip. We should work
together. Alright I'll go to the subway. I ain't going without some type of protection.
How are you? Nothing to say? Pyroids. Where do I get them? Now you cannot get hit by the train.
Where does this go? How are you doing? This is the boss's son. Oh okay. Anybody else on the train?
I don't think there's anything else for me to do. Why is this so scary? Um it's just kind of scary
isn't it? Weird. What else is down here? There are more places to have random fights. I could go to bed.
Yeah go go to the plane. Yeah I I'm not fucking around on the plane. It really is Silent Hill.
Okay. So what's on the card now? Uh oh. Confrontation with the Aero Hathaway? This is the
the guy that I threw over the top rope and hurt. This is the ref definitely taking the hammer
without a doubt. This game is insane. Wish you luck in your match tonight. Is it a match? Why would I
fight a referee? Dangerous things happened back here and it would be a shame if you ended up
crawling to the ring. I would choose your words more carefully, God. 1200 bucks. Look at your
health. You think I'm bluffing? When I'm finished with you the only place you'd be going is intensive
care. Interesting because that's exactly what I was gonna just say to you. Whoa. It's almost time for
our match. We're gonna go hear what the referee has to say. Have you ever worked with a wrestler
called Matty McFly here at All American Wrestling? His contract is up for renewal soon so we'd be
interested to know if you have any feedback. Um, Matty McFly was all right. I liked him.
I'd be pleased to hear that. We'll do our best to keep him. Wasn't he a nice guy? I thought he was
nice to me. Was he not nice? Why is everybody following me? What are you doing? Leave me. What
the fuck are you doing? Wait, get out. Excuse me. What are you doing? Leave me alone. Dude, I don't
want to hit you with this but I'm gonna. You're telling me to calm down. You are the aggressor
right now. I am not doing anything. I'm waiting to go on stage for my match. Oh no, the tables have
turned. Everybody's. All right, almost time. When is our match gone? Ready. Where is he? Where is he?
Where is he? Where is he? Where is he? Oh, it's you. I wasn't sure if I would ever step between
these ropes again after I got injured. Thanks to the support of my fans, I'm back better than ever.
You can break my bones but you can never break my spirit. Do you think any of these people are glad
that you're back or even noticed that you were gone? Don't get too comfortable, Errol Hathaway,
because I'm going to send you right back to intensive care. I'm not a face at all. I really
don't want to do this but I think the story is okay. Well, now you put our belt on. That's like
the most that you that is absolute trash. What you've just done. There's no remorse for what I'm
what I you take the belt and put it on. My buddy Hyane is going to show you a thing or two.
What is that about? About respect, for god's sake. I don't want to hurt him again. I don't want to
hurt him again. I'm thinking about walking out. Oh, my mouth, my lip. Okay, I've had enough.
Okay, that's enough. Okay, I'm literally out of here. I don't want to do this. I don't want
to fucking kill this guy. Okay, that's enough. That's enough, right? That's enough. Okay,
that's enough. I like jumped on him. No, you guys are crazy. I don't want to do this. Listen
to you guys. Listen to you guys. I don't want to do that. I'm not going to hurt him. I'm just
going to take his health to zero. His face on like concrete. This poor guy. Oh, this is not all right.
I don't like this at all. This doesn't feel good. This feels bad. He's a referee for god's sakes.
He's a cocky referee. Okay, he's done. Do not put your foot down. Do not. Oh, my god.
Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Get me out. I thought if I held it, I could. Guys, I didn't mean to do that.
I've done so many terrible things today accidentally. Like, I didn't actually want
to do that to this guy. So many things have happened on this stream I didn't want to do.
How did you do that by accident? I was going to kick him in his leg,
but he lifted his foot up right. Oh, man. That's not good.
Caught in 4K. You're awful. No, I swear to god I'm not. I'm not. I swear. I didn't mean to do that.
I would never do it. I wanted to let him leave. I didn't want to hurt him. I don't want to hurt
anybody, okay? I don't want to hurt anybody. No one. I'm not hurting anybody. Look at this.
Look at this violence over here. Look at this violence. I didn't do this. They did. And I'm
just walking through. Look, I'm just walking through. I'm going to my hotel room and I'm going
to go to bed. What the fuck are you? What are you doing in my hotel room? We good? Are we good?
Are we good? We good? We good? Okay, sorry. You can have it back. Right. Okay. This guy's on crack.
This guy's on drugs. I came in here with that hammer. You stole it from him moments ago. I
did not. I can't believe it. Poor Errol Hathaway. I want to go apologize to him.
You can change your name in the gimmick menu. That's kind of funny though.
Strong new. We're a new man. New strong. Turning over a new leaf. Positivity. No violence. No
kicking anybody. No hitting somebody in the head with a hammer. None of that. I'm going to help
people. I want a good song. One that's like uplifting. Here we go. Nope. Alright. Nothing
bad. I'm going to be kind to everyone I come across. I promise. Howdy, big fly. I put a
good word in for you. See? Good start. Something you want to say? Yeah. I put a good word in for
you. I have a proposal for you. I'd like to work with you. I already have a tag team partner,
but I've challenged you to do a friendly match. No. No, I can't. I got it out of my system. I'm
fine. We are defending the championships today. Can I just shake people's hands? I'm not going to
pick up any weapons. I hear you changed your entrance theme, strong new. It sounds terrible.
Well, I mean, that's, we have, we have different opinions. We might have two completely distinct
thoughts, but that does not mean that my opinion is invalid and yours is invalid. We both feel
different things. You know, we come from different places. We may have different tastes and I respect
that for you. I respect that. Have a great day. Have a great day. I'm keeping an eye on your
progress. I think some changes need to be made. Nine matches without losing is quite a streak,
but you're making everybody else look bad. Put someone over by the fourth week of October to
prove that you care about this business. Okay. You know, I want to make sure that the fellow wrestlers
all have a good chance and everybody thinks that they're doing a very good job.
But someone over exactly. Yeah. I'm going to make sure that I lose a match because we want to make
sure everyone feels pretty good about it. Right. Of course. I want to support everybody. Of course.
Oh, wow. That hurt. I deserved it though. Oh, my shin that hurt. I must've said something like
annoying. Everybody's getting fucking beat up on your own business. You want to take a fall?
Where is he? Oh, I must've said something that you didn't like. Oh, you want to take a fall
Lance? You want me to take a fall? Is that what it is? That's F for a fall. I'm more popular than
you strong new. Don't start something you can't finish. Oh yeah. Well, that must've said something
that annoyed you, right? Yeah. Oh shit. I'm knocked out. I think I'm knocked out. I can't walk. No,
wrong way. Classic glitter shitter. No, I'm going to be a good person. You're a long way from home
Congo. You should have stayed at maple leaf grappling. I've gotten fatter. You may have a
big fish in that small pond, but all American wrestling is tough for a loser like you. I'm
not saying this. This is my yard and these are my fans. Nobody carves out a successful career here
without my blessing. I don't even have a championship. That's strange because I recall.
Oh shit. Sorry. Sorry. My face.
I didn't know that was, I didn't know that was the title of that. Oh, everybody hates us now.
I don't know. I like the new era of, I'm trying to be like a nice person. Now I'm getting the
championship and I'm going to be a nice person. I'm not going to talk shit. I'm not going to say
anything that's going to make somebody want to punch me in the face. Like I've, I've walked up
to people and said like, oh, hey, you're a fucking loser. And then they punched me in the face,
right? I've hit people and they hit me back. That era is over. I'm not going to be an idiot. I'm
not going to be stupid. I'm going, I'm actually going to try. Go talk to the boss. That's right.
I was supposed to do that with the boss. I was supposed to do that. I was supposed to throw.
Why can I not go in there? Wait for the mission to end. Probably the next day it was on the floor.
I think that's a Maddy McFly. Oh, maybe bailing doesn't count as a dive. Really? I feel like it
should. I might be in the office. I've been challenged to put someone over. Oh my God. I
didn't. Shit. It didn't count. No, it didn't count. All right. Wait, maybe it did. Oh, it did. Okay.
You followed my advice and made your prospects better than ever. A thousand dollar bonus. That's
not worth the titles. Sorry. Hey, do you know who stole my clothes? I can't go out there looking
like this. Would you be willing to sell me your gear if I paid you $790? That's funny you say
that. Sure. If you're $790, I will give you the pair of underwear that I shit in. You just saved
my life. Hope I can do the same for you sometime. What a deal. This is a steel cage match. Strong
new. How would you like to take me on in a match on the second week of October? I think I'm already
booked. I think I'm already booked. It's a shame. I hope we get a chance to work together somewhere
down. I have a match like tomorrow. Don't I? I didn't press anything. It landed on my head.
Good morning. Good morning. Good morning to you all. Good morning. Good morning.
I'm gonna take a fall. It's such a wonderful world we live in in this nice street. What did
the person say? Good morning. You're booked in a steel cage tag team match. Do you need to explain
the rules? No, I don't. But I would absolutely love to clean here. Nice Monty Python. I think I'm fine
on health. The amount of people that said stop. You know what my favorite thing is? I don't know. I
think it's so fun just to have... What am I doing? I'm just kind of waiting for the... I will have the
urge to hit somebody with this brump. I'm just wandering around until the match. If I stand still
for more than an hour, I'm going to hit somebody with this. Do you think it's fun to be annoying?
No, I wouldn't say annoying. It's fun to be really annoying. I don't want to hit this guy,
but I'm gonna... Leave me alone. I'm just kidding around, man. Why is a ref climbing this?
If he falls, it doesn't count that I didn't hurt him. I remember what it's like to be the tag team
champion. Yeah, because we just were. I also felt something wasn't right. Wait, is this for the
championship? He needs to be in here, doesn't he? You're a loser. Doesn't the referee need to be in
here? I can't... I don't think I can use the broom. I want to shake it so the referee falls.
The whole goal is to climb out of the ring, right? I think this guy tapped out. This guy's tapped
out like three times. Okay, who is actually... You climb out of the ring, right? What is going on?
Don't you climb out? I thought it was you have to escape. Oh, it's just we're in the... It's just a
pin. Okay. I'm sorry. I just thought of the good morning song. I deserve to get called out for
that one. It was awful. Please don't kill me. All right, the teammate disappeared. Is this to get
the belt back? How do I actually get the... The tag team championship is fine, but I want to do
the belt. I want the world championship. It's not in, right? The theater kid singing voice.
I hope you guys understand that I'm just fucking around 95% of the time, right?
I'm just fucking around. I'm just messing around. You are a theater kid. I'm a theater adult,
which is way worse. He's won the tag team back. Best part is the referee has to do this too.
Dude, I'm never getting out of here, I don't think. Get me out of here. All right, so we won the tag
team again. Only soulless zoomers hate new metal wrestling. Congratulations on winning the tag
team. The gold is where it belongs now. Oh, thanks Harley. I appreciate it. That was cool. All right.
Can we make a... I'm curious what's going on. You're still here, but what's going on out here now?
There's a fight going on. Everybody stop. What? Is it weird that I came in here? Okay. All right.
All right. I'm leaving. I'm going to leave. All right. I'm leaving. It's just chaos. Just no,
I don't have nobody I'm attacking. I'm just, I'm just K. I don't want to say that word. I'm chaos
because it's like, come on, dude, relax. I am chaos. Oh, my knee kind of ruined everything.
All right. That's, I'm probably going to call it here. Maybe like one more match. That's the guy.
That's the guy I gave my underwear to by the way. Oh my God. That's so stupid. Don't hit the guy
with the underwear. Let me challenge another person. It's in the menu. I want to try. I go for a belt.
If I can't get the belt, then obviously I'll call it. Keep streaming idiot. Oh, no. This game is so
goddamn funny. It really is just so fun. Oh, your buddy major Merc suggested that you might like to
join us at wrestling revolution. Okay. We feel he'd be a valuable addition to the roster and we're
prepared to make it happen with this deal. Hey Elden Ring, you're going to lose a fan forever.
Yeah. I played Elden Ring like a month straight. That's a lot of money.
We'll pair you with major Merc straight away to help you get you over a strong one. What do you
think of the new hairstyle? Our style is suggested for you. I think it's fine. Let me go for a title
match immediately. Who has like the world championship here? All right. This is a strong
new. What do you want to talk about? I want that title. Everybody wants a shot at my intertitle.
I'll get to the back. Okay. Well, is this just a one-off? Um, I don't know. Maybe I'll play it
again another time. I kind of want to see something really quick though. Did this change at all?
You could do some really, really wacky stuff here. Individuals, hardcore, the bathroom,
the barbershop, the bar, the subway. How do you eliminate people in a subway?
Plane. The tables again. Gauntlet escape to victory. What's escape? Okay. Rotation, singles,
singles, hardcore, no falls, no stopping, no countouts. Um, I think this is fine.
How did we put tables in here before?
What's my standing sumo contest? They're, uh, Reno.
Maybe not. Oh, here we go. It's probably going to crash the game. It did last time.
Uh, let's see what happens. Okay. That sounds good.
We can use it for just a second. All right. We're going to just
backflip off of this and do a bunch of tables. Oh God. How do we, how did I climb these before?
Remember I climbed all the way up. Jesus. I can't have the broom. Okay. Here we go.
Get out of here. Come on, climate, please. Whatever. It was a Monty Python joke.
I was standing on top of them before. Did they patch out tower climbing? Probably not. I'm
probably just not doing it right. Get off. How long are you going to, he just broke my arm.
What are this guy's stats? All right. I'll see you guys later. Next stream is going to be on, uh,
Saturday. Do some MS DOS. Have like 20 games we can play. Maybe even more, but it's going to be
hard to go through them all. Conquer construction, please. That's one of them. All right. I got to
get out of this. Thanks for watching as usual. That was a lot of fun. This game kind of just
drained me mentally and physically. It's just such a shit show. It's so funny. So much wild
shit just happens randomly. I mean, I'm not going to tell you, I'm never going to play this again
because obviously it seems like, uh, M Dickie is updating this all the time. So that was a lot of
fun. I'll see you guys on Saturday. Thanks for watching. Goodbye. Good night. Let me turn this
off. Here comes the glove eating stream. It's not April 24th yet. I've got at least a week. What's
time on Saturday? Probably around four. Same time as this one. I don't know what I'm going to start
with. Somebody said you kick ass so hard. I thought you said you suck ass so hard. Oh no.
Now that stream is a lot of fun. Start with Shito. Maybe I will. I can't believe the guy shit his
pants. We're glossing over that part of this stream. I was holding my ass with two hands,
backing up, walking around, getting chased by people and I shit my pants.
We kind of just moved on from that really quickly. All right. Goodbye. I'll see you guys on Saturday.
Take care of yourselves and good night.