Is that uh, is that, is that electricity on your head?
That is, that is electricity on my face.
So, so that's a new unusual. Is that like one of the new ones?
That's, that's one of the new ones.
Cool. I'll give you a high five, bro.
Yay! Oh!
Electricity!
You okay, mate?
The Sneeze Gun.
If I had a name tag, I would just rename this to the Sneeze Gun right now.
I don't have any name tags, but I will.
Eventually this will be the Sneeze Gun and
you'll understand why very shortly.
Alright.
Who wants to get destroyed
by the Sneeze Gun?
This scout right here? Did you say you wanted to get
sneezed on?
Oh, okay. What about the spy?
Oh, he's already dead.
Oh, man.
I'm sorry, I can't control my cold!
Oh!
I'm gonna get headshot.
Man, I gotta call into work today.
God, I'm sorry, guys.
Oh.
I really gotta put on one of those masks.
So sorry about all that.
Now you just sound like Ace Ventura.
I forget which part,
but it's the part where he's like
When he's climbing out the
rhino's ass, there you go.
And he's just like
When he's climbing out the
rhino's ass.
It actually worked!
I wanna get up there.
BAM! Wow, that was pretty brutal.
I like took his head off.
I took his head clean off with that swing.
And that guy.
And this guy.
No, don't kill me.
I'm just a DMO man.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
Spy! Get out of here, spy!
Have you been sword fighting again, German?
No, dude! Dude, I'm still here!
Sword fighting!
I killed the answers!
Please let me live!
Let me live!
Is this guy seriously just gonna stand right here?
He's not gonna let me do this, is he?
Please don't put a sentry here, Engie.
Please don't do it.
He's trying.
Don't do it, dude.
Did he?
Hey, DMO, come over here, mate.
There's a prize.
Hold on a second.
I'll help you out, mate. I'll help you out.
Wow.
Well, if anybody
walks down there on the rail,
they're fucking dead.
Oh my god, dude. This is gonna
instantly kill anyone that comes
over here. Even if they take a peep through that window,
they are fucked.
I would move this, but I think we should just keep it here
for decorations. I think it looks
kind of pretty. We should all get Wranglers
and get just big bubbles.
Yeah, this is gonna be good.
Oh, look. This person on the cart.
Sentry's gone. Now's your chance.
Do it! Sentry!
They didn't do shit!
They didn't do anything.
It's cause I've bubbled mine. I wanna get
a good view.
Oh, look how good we are.
We build three sentries.
He's coming up the stairs.
Where is he? This asshole. This spy.
He's got my...
You'll recognize him. There he is. There's two of us.
What?
I don't know which one is you.
I'm chasing him right now.
Oh, so you're the one. Are you in front of him?
There we go. There's another one.
I seriously did not...
Oh, there he is. He's here again.
He's going up the evil stairs to stab me.
Get him! No! He face stabbed me!
Why is he doing this
to me all the time? He face stabbed me twice.
I hate spies.
Shit.
I'm gonna get some metal first.
Alright, let's go. We gotta hurry up.
We got like a train to catch.
Oh, the sentry train.
We gotta get on that payload train.
Three, two, one. Moving on.
Let's do it.
If I get backstabbed and this dies, I will be so upset.
On the railroad.
On a live long day.
Keep going. Keep going.
Oh, keep going? Cause I... No!
Keep going, he says.
Keep going.
We must push further up the hill.
We're doing the upward
parade of engineers. I protect you,
you protect me. I don't see a spy.
Pyro! Pyro! Pyro! Pyro! What?
And a scout! Put it down! Put it down!
Quick! Get him down!
I don't have any metal!
Yours is facing the wrong way!
There's a spy!
There's a spy! Oh, no!
No!
Yours is facing the wrong way!
He's trying to stair stab me.
He's gonna face stab me again, I know it.
He's dead. Alright, my sentry
died. He just poked it
once cause it got sapped to shit.
I ran out of metal.
This is shit.
I need more metal.
Put him down!
We're gonna win. Alright, quick, get him in.
Get him inside before we win.
Get him in front of the spawn door.
In front of the spawn door, right here!
Come on!
Build you piece of shit! Come on!
Quicker! Quicker!
We did nothing,
my goodness me.
That was so dumb.
We didn't even build a teleporter or a dispenser.
We didn't do
fucking anything.
We did nothing.