Hey, what is going on everybody? Jirba here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm going to be playing as the Scout with the Default Scouter Gun, the Bok Atomic Punch, and the Candy Cane.
I don't think I ever take the Candy Cane off, ever. So just pretty much every Scout game from now on, just assume the Candy Cane is just always on, because I'd love it too much to take it off.
But anyways, this is a one-life gameplay on CTF Doublecross. I get a lot of requests to do more CTF, and this is fulfilling that request, hopefully. CTF Doublecross is a little bit of a turtle stalemate map, just like something like 2-4, where all the engineers just build in the flag room.
And unless you get an Uber Charge or you get a Scout coming in like me with the Bonk, it's almost impossible to get the intelligence. So it really just becomes a TDM this whole game.
But it ends kind of tragically. I killed 16 people in this one life, and it ends very tragically. You'll see what happens.
But anyways, I want to talk about a couple things before the video gets started. We're going to talk about some things about the gameplay. We're going to talk about the Bonk Atomic Punch. I'm talking really fast right now. Let me slow down.
We're going to talk about a couple of channel updates, and most notably, how to analyze yourself and how I've done it in this gameplay with the Scouts. Kind of some Scout tips and some Scout strategies.
Let's start with one thing. The unusual hat winner has been selected. And the hat has been given to him or her. I'm not sure if it was a he or she. But they got the hat, and congratulations to the winner.
If you didn't win the hat, I am sorry. But as you know with this channel, I always do stuff like that. So you'll always have a chance next time when I do another one of those giveaways.
And secondly, I'm going to bring back Scare Saturdays. I've gotten such an overwhelming response to bring that back. Last video, it was a top comment with like a hundred and something thumbs up.
I get that question all the time in PMs. Bring back Scare Saturdays. So I'm going to do that. This Saturday, I'm going to bring it back, and I want you guys to vote on the game you want me to play.
So in the description of this video is going to be a poll there with a bunch of scary games. Some that I've already played, some that I maybe have not played. But still pick one of those, and that's what's going to be there for Scare Saturdays.
Because you can only vote one time, so make your vote count, baby. And it does need to be noted about Scare Saturdays that I'm not going to be doing any more Let's Plays of horror games.
I know I did Nightmare House 2. I did the whole thing. It's on the channel. If you want to go look for it, you can just search for it.
Also, I also tried to do Grey, but I don't know. Let's Plays in me don't really work that well anymore, unless it's a short kind of a three to four hour long game.
If it's like a 10 hour long experience or like a 20 hour long campaign, like something, I don't know how long Dead Space 3 is.
But what I would do with something like Dead Space, if somebody, if you guys voted for it, would be a highlight reel of scares or a highlight reel of like funny moments during that particular playthrough I did.
So it would just end up being me scaring the crap out of myself, not a 75 episode Let's Play.
But now that that is out of the way, hopefully a lot of you guys go vote on that poll, but let's start talking about the Scout.
So I don't know if you noticed in this gameplay, and it's something somebody actually brought this up a long time ago about how I play Scout.
And I made a tip video about Scout addressing this sort of, but watching this game playback is how I really realize how much I do it.
And I'm going to call it the sway. That's what I'm going to call it. The sway back and forth when I'm shooting people and trying to get good meat shots on people.
What I'm talking about here is you'll see it. I go like me, me, me, me, almost like I'm sweeping the screen, not with my mouse, but with my A and D keys.
And it's something I don't know why I do this. And I think it's because I have a lot of trouble aiming with the mouse more so than I do, which just kind of getting people in front of my crosshair.
But I kill every single person almost by doing the sway in quotes. And if you're having trouble with the Scout, try doing this because I'm not very good at twitch aiming.
I'm not that great at like whipping around and like shoot, shoot, shoot like some of you guys are.
Some of you guys are unbelievable at this game and especially at Scout in particular.
But if you have trouble with your aim as a Scout or with your tactics as a Scout, try to implement the sway.
And actually, like I said, you guys brought this up. I didn't even know I was doing this. This is completely subconscious to me.
And I do this with the engineer with the shotguns. I do this with the Pyro shotguns and I do it with the Scout.
So it's become very evident, especially like I said, watching this game playback, I'm like, oh my God, I do it every kill.
And it actually brings me to the second point of this video. And it's a pretty simple one.
Try recording yourself. Try to record yourself and see what you do in all these different situations you're in.
It can really help you analyze your gameplay, find out what you're doing wrong, find out what you're doing right, and make yourself a better player because of it.
It's very much the same as, I don't know if you guys have ever done this before, but I do it all the time.
Looking into the mirror in the bathroom and smiling or making faces to know what you look like in real life.
Same thing, when I do these face cam videos and I do like vlogs, I watch the videos back and I go, oh, that's what I do when I like to laugh.
It's analyzing yourself to know where your flaws are and know where your strengths are.
And you can only do that by real self-analyzation. Self-analyzation, I do not think, is a word, but we made it up right now for this video.
But anyways, guys, that's going to wrap it up here. At the end, you see, I don't get the intelligence.
It's sitting right on the edge and I was trying to run in there and grab it. Pretty tragic, I know.
But that's going to wrap it up here, guys. I'll see you guys all next time.
Thank you, everybody, for watching. And, of course, take care, everybody.