Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm gonna be playing as the engineer with the Widowmaker, the Pistol, and the Gunslinger.
Vintage Gunslinger. This is also gonna be on King of the Hill Nucleus, one of my favorite engineer maps, my favorite combat engineer maps, let me rephrase that.
But this is a great gameplay, I kill a lot of people with this Widowmaker, and this thing has really taken over my primary slot choice. I used to always, 100% of the time, run around with the Frontier Justice.
That's not the case anymore. I put the Frontier Justice on now, when I have a big sentry, and of course I use the Widowmaker when I have the mini sentry.
But it's not really, that's not absolute. I do, I change it up every now and then, you know me, I'm a freak.
So what I want to talk about right now in this gameplay is, I want to talk about the new update that's coming out, and a couple other things.
I have a call to the community, I guess you could say, and I'll get into that in a second, but let's talk about the update.
So Meet the Pyro is coming out. Nobody knows when, it's just coming out in 2012. That's all we know, we don't know anything else, but they have a screenshot.
And it looks like the Pyro has lit an entire building on fire, and are you guys as excited about this as I am?
Because they took a long time to make Meet the Medic, and it feels like this is a joke.
It took them like 7,500 years to make Meet the Medic, and now right after Meet the Medic comes out, less than a year later, they're going to tell us they're coming out with Meet the Pyro?
And this always gets me thinking, and I want to know what you guys have to say about this as well, so feel free to chime in in the comments section.
So this is the last Meet the Team video. What's next? What are they going to do next?
They don't have anything to dangle out in front of us like a carrot on a string. This is the last one, guys.
And actually, I read somewhere that after this Meet the Team video, they are going to make a movie.
Like a 40-minute long Meet the Whole Entire Team video, or something like that, that Robin Walker has stated that they have not really turned down that idea.
And I'm just thinking, how amazing would that be? How insane would it be if they did like a straight-to-DVD release of Team Fortress 2, the movie?
Oh my God. If I had millions of dollars, I would finance that movie right now. I would send a check to Valve for $40 million so they could make that movie.
Like really. So transitioning with that, we're going to get a bunch of new items, I guess, too, in 2012.
So it's just really exciting across the board. But my call to the community is, I want to do something for the Steam Workshop.
I want to get in touch with a really, really good modeler, somebody that knows what they're doing, and I have a bunch of ideas that I really do think could make it into the game.
Especially one idea in particular, and it's not a weapon, but I won't get into the details with that, but the reason why this is a call to the community is if you guys know a really, really good modeler,
I mean, I'm talking somebody that is like on the pro level, that really knows what they're doing, and would love to do something like this.
Shoot me a YouTube PM and give me their info, or even if it's you, let's talk, because I really have some funny ideas that could really make it into the game.
So all of that aside, Team Fortress 2 is going places in 2012. I can't wait to see what they do next, guys.
It wasn't that long ago, it was only probably four months ago when I said in a commentary, I said, Team Fortress 2 I think is dying, they haven't come up with an update,
they're not doing a whole lot for the community anymore, and then, bang, look at this. All this new crazy stuff is in the pipeline, and it's great, because this is one of the best games I've ever played,
and I'm sure a lot of you guys will agree with that, so it really is awesome to see one of my favorite games, and a lot of yours as well,
to still be getting this attention that it deserves, and I don't even know when they're going to stop now, but it is exciting, exciting stuff.
So I got backstabbed right there in the gameplay. This was almost a one life gameplay, so I was a little, I was like, oh god, I almost had another one life, but it's okay.
We end up winning the game right now, they get on the point, but it's not a big deal. Only ten seconds left to go.
Drop your sentry gun right here, your mini sentry, because at this chaotic point when everyone's rushing over here to try and get on this,
no one is really paying attention that there's a sentry gun here.
But this is going to be the end of the gameplay, guys. Thank you so much for watching, I really do appreciate it.
And remember, if you know anybody that is a computer graphics modeler, or if you are, shoot me a PM, we'll talk.
But that's it guys, I'll see you all soon, and take care everybody.