Is that mine? Nah, that's Shibby's.
Oh, he's dropping it on Phat.
Oh, 3, 2, 1.
How do you see damage?
Hopefully Phat doesn't die first.
Wait, where am I?
Who did I even select? What? I didn't want this guy.
You don't get to pick. It's random.
Oh, it's random.
Alright, well you want a dynamite?
You see what happens right now.
5 seconds, Jerome.
Make him poop, bro.
I didn't even know what was happening.
Oh, the panic.
The 20 seconds isn't long enough.
It needs to be like 30.
Charlize Theron.
Charlize Theron, if I may.
I just butchered that name.
Charlize Theron.
Hey, don't shoot the wall.
Why are you shooting just me?
Chew up, son.
Oh my, you're dead.
Jerome is dead.
That was a bunch of BS right there.
Charlize Theron.
Fucking Jerome.
I'm so done.
Oh, by the way, for those of you wondering,
Orb is yellow, Shibby is blue,
and I'm red. If anyone is confused
right now.
I'm confused too.
You only have 3 seconds. Look at all...
No!
What the hell?
Come on, son.
Get some.
No!
What the hell?
Come on, son.
Get some.
No, you gotta get the crates.
Where's Puke? Oh, that crate is mine.
What is it?
10 coins? Oh, great. Thanks.
I only have 10 seconds.
How do you jump?
Get me out of here.
I don't know how to jump.
Worst player, NA.
How do you jump?
Oh, shit.
8, 7...
Dragon Ball.
Get Dragon Balled.
That was the...
Oh, great. That sucked.
Did I just do like 10 damage to you?
That was weird.
Oh, am I gonna spawn down there?
Oh, this is gonna be perfect.
I just have to figure out what do we have.
Dude, baseball bat me like a boss.
Who has the girl voice pack?
I'm using the Australian person.
What is this? I don't like what I see.
Oh, nice.
Nice job.
That was perfect.
GG.
Why?
Why are you getting all this free stuff up there?
This is the DLC bullshit that I talked about.
This is what he gets for the DLC.
MLG grandpa up in the top right.
Oh, what's this? Oh, what's this turret?
What's going on here?
What?
What the fuck?
My turret.
That is the best shit I've ever seen.
That's not gonna be good.
I don't know what all my options are.
You're gonna kill yourself.
Oh, shit.
The sheep, that's gonna kill you.
Oh, my God.
I don't know what's going on here.
You have to detonate it.
I think you have to detonate that.
Oh, shit.
Why did I tell him that?
I should have left him in the dock.
Well, I'm going to lose this match.
I think I'm going to win.
I think it's going against Orbeez here.
I'm sorry, Jerome.
You know who to shoot out here, Jerome.
Yeah, I know.
I know what I'm doing.
I know exactly what I'm doing right now.
What is this?
No, what are you doing?
Oh, shit.
Good choice.
No.
Oh, shit.
What?
I just killed myself.
Was that a cluster bomb?
It was a cluster bomb, but I'm an idiot and I threw it incorrectly.
I will get to you eventually, Chibi.
No.
Nice nosc, brah.
Oh, wow.
Wow, that was a perfect shot.
That aim, though.
That aim.
How did you get that right?
I don't know how you did that.
That is FPS aim right there, fellas.
Can I call upon the power of the rats in the background to come eat your faces?
No.
That would have been so funny if you had fell down.
Funny because you would have died.
That would have been so funny because you would have died.
It sounds so horrible.
Jump rope.
Oh, only a minute and 46 seconds.
Oh, you fall.
Hey.
Orb is going to win by default.
Only a minute and 15 seconds left.
You gotta do more damage to him, Jerem.
I can't.
Oh, no.
Yes, yes.
Get it, get it, get it.
Yes.
All right, here we go.
We got a game.
Get out.
It was worth it.
We are never playing this again.
It raises the water level, I forgot.
Oh, all right, so it keeps going.
I didn't mess up that cluster.
Go, go, go, go, go.
This is going to be it right here.
Oh, it screws it up.
Hold on, I got this.
Oh, yes.
Yes, yes.
Oh, you're so boned.
Oh, dude.
If you draw, no.
Seriously, seriously.
That's no way. The game is glitched.
Rick, tweet somebody.
Tweet somebody.
No way.
Where's my cursor?
I cannot lose this.
I'm waiting for players right now.
Where's my move?
This is going to be it.
I think you're going to both bounce back into the water.
It might not, though. The explosion is not that powerful.
Oh, my God.
Oh, that's it.
That's it.
Oh, my God.
Yes, thank you.
I can't believe it.