You guys, how are you? What's up? How are you doing?
Hi. Yeah, sorry I'm late. Yeah, yeah I know.
For those of you that were not in the pre-stream chat, and the reason why I am late,
I got an emergency phone call. Uh, nothing weird happened.
Nothing out of the ordinary. I had an emergency call.
I had to take it. And it was, uh, you know, I just had to make sure I took the call.
And it was important about, um, financial stuff.
And I went to make sure I got my financial stuff in order.
And, um, a few things about, like, a recipe that I needed for my mother.
Um, said nothing weird happened or anything, but sorry about that.
Yeah, I mean, it's like tax season and shit.
Like, I'm just trying to make sure I, like, I, you know,
cross all my t's and dot on my i's. You know what I'm saying?
I absolutely did not do something incredibly disgusting and embarrassing.
Well, yuck. Why would that happen?
Like, clog your toilet with your massive pastrami sandwich shit you had yesterday.
No way. Not, that didn't happen at all.
But frankly, it's revolting that you're saying it.
Like, why would that happen? Like, you guys are disgusting.
Do you see what people are writing?
Look, those are the that joined us after pre-stream chat.
Look at, look at how fucked up this community is.
I didn't, what is, what are they talking about?
Oh, look, Jerma the serial killer. Here we go again, right?
I'm so sick of this. Whatever.
Oh, how you doing?
Hope you had a good Christmas. Merry Christmas if I didn't see you.
I did see you, though. The day before Christmas.
Uh, I, I had a great Christmas. It was good.
I got a new wallet. It's nice.
I got some bath stuff because I'm a big bath guy, you know me.
Hey, thank you, Santa, for the five community subs.
Wham, wham, wham, deal with it, entertainer.
This is a boring title. What the hell?
We peeped the toilet. No, you can't.
Boring title. I don't even know what the game is.
I just, everyone told me to play it.
It looks cool. It's got buying and trading.
So, you know, I'm going to like it.
It was, it was Satan. Oh, thank you, Satan.
Yeah, this is, this is called Space Warlord Organ Trading Simulator.
It's a game where you fly around the galaxy
and you buy and sell organs of aliens.
I, it was recommended a bunch of times.
Like I said, I am ready.
I am ready to give it a try.
Question is, are you?
All right, so let me turn this up just a tad with my microphone here.
You ever played Rimworld?
No, it's too complicated for me.
Looks like a fun game. Too complicated for my brain.
Is that better? Can you guys hear me better now?
All right, I'm going to do some tests for you.
So you tell me if this is too much or too little.
Ready?
Too loud? You want more?
Better? How's this? Is this better?
Is this one good? What if I scream though?
Like, okay, I'm going to turn it down.
Better? Trying to get my audio settings better.
More? Is that better? Perfect.
All right, let's see. Let's just go.
Sounds good. Okay.
Maybe do a little more. We'll see.
Well, this is organ trader simulator.
I'm very curious.
Was my FPS weird?
Wait, what? What do you mean 23 Hertz?
Is this a fucking CRT TV on an iMac from like 1995?
Why does it look like this?
What's happening? Hold on.
This is weird. How can you even do 23 Hertz?
That's crazy. It's because it's cinematic.
Oh, I see. All right.
144 Hertz at 1440p.
I actually hate selecting this.
I am one of those old boomer people that really does.
I like 1080p. I don't want any.
I don't want 1440p. I don't want 2560.
It's too high.
Text effect? Wiggle?
No, I don't make the Alpuc.
Music's all right.
All right, I'm going to apply.
Hopefully the stream isn't crashed.
Oh, look at how much better that is.
No wiggle? No, no, no wiggling.
No, I don't like when shit moves around.
Was this full screen?
Okay, that's fine.
Are you ready?
I'm not turning the wiggle on.
The wiggle's not going on.
Set the stream to 1080.
We're going to go.
I'm very curious about this game for you guys.
There you are.
Uh, thank you.
Thanks to usually Zane MysticQuests
and anonymousgifter for the five, five, ten, five community subs.
All right, I'm ready. Let's go.
Great new game.
Who are you?
Dog. No.
Dog with a hat on.
Wait, what the fuck?
All right, a, uh, the mage from Final Fantasy.
Sus.
Frog.
The guy from that Netflix show with like the super powered people.
They live in a mansion together.
Explosion guy.
Double Knight.
The new ice cube thing that people do on Twitch right now.
Spider-Man.
Peter Parker.
This guy.
I don't think you understand your position.
I cannot touch you.
You are an organ trader, a supplier of meaty demand
with a moral flexibility ranging in the parsecs.
You buy organs, you sell organs, you take on client requests
and fulfill them and use their money to fuel your future.
Why is it?
This person's talking like me.
I type like this.
This is how I talk in chat.
You buy, you fulfill them and use their money to fuel your future.
I don't know.
I like emphasizing words.
You will not lose money fulfilling a request unless you want to.
You cannot be held accountable for your actions.
Everyone has organs.
Everyone wants organs and everyone needs organs.
Which means they need you.
This is an angry YouTube comment.
They need us.
So congratulations.
The universe is your fleshy parasitic playground.
Everyone else just lives in it.
Can you stall?
What do you mean can I stall?
It's 4 30.
I was supposed to start a half an hour ago.
Don't worry.
You can, you don't have to turn laundry over.
You can leave the laundry in the washing machine for at least like 30 to 40 minutes.
Anything over an hour or two, that's bad.
You're going to have to rewash.
Just saying.
Scroll and then left and right.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
How much?
I have 2,300 bucks.
Type, size, trade.
So I got this.
Cargo and holds.
Personal.
Holds.
I like to click.
I'm slow.
Okay.
Q and E.
I don't like it.
It's too fast.
I feel like I'm playing StarCraft.
Okay.
So holds.
Where am I?
What's my favorite organ?
The spleen.
So day zero.
Personal.
Title.
Scum.
Current face.
This.
2,300 credits.
Reputation progression.
Reputation credits.
Stock portfolio.
So you trade stocks.
Organs touched.
Intestines owned in meters.
Breaths taken.
What the fuck is this?
All right.
So this is just like my personal little card here.
So this is what I'm hold, holds.
Refer.
Oh, okay.
So I can upgrade my shit.
Close decay of all organs by 25%.
Oh, I'm going to be into this game.
Let's see.
Wait.
A cargo.
Okay.
I only have what?
Five slots?
Six slots?
Don't breathe for two minutes and see what happens.
Don't ever fucking don't breathe for two minutes.
Breathe.
Don't play these dumb games.
No.
Refill.
Audio log?
Is this a guitar?
What does a guitar want with an organ?
Or is this just the annoying guy that I call that plays this first and then says hello?
Okay.
Here we go.
Refill.
All right.
What about trade?
Can I trade?
How do I know what people want?
Can I go trade?
Trade.
The market is open.
What?
What do you mean the market's open?
Buy?
What is this?
This is a liver.
It's a large liver.
It's in a 46 blood type B+.
What do people...
Wait, wait.
Request.
Hello, scum.
Hello.
Right now you're nothing.
They wouldn't trust you to trade shoes and we're going to fix that.
Get me a stomach and make something in yourself.
I only have two minutes.
All right.
I'll get your stomach.
I a stomach.
This is a heart.
Liver.
Heart.
There are no stomachs.
Stomach.
All right.
Blood type AB.
Rarity mythic.
Natural, neutral flesh.
No special traits.
Can I filter stomachs?
This one's cheap.
Rarity rough.
Rarity rare.
150.
I'm going to buy this.
Okay.
Request.
Where are you?
Fulfill.
Hey, I got you.
I got it.
Reputation descended.
Trash.
What do you mean?
What?
New organs on log.
What did I do?
Breaking the...
Wait.
What do you want?
This guy's got $5,000.
Want cold companions.
In high gravity on cold nights,
I like to clutch a warm lung between my fingers.
I need another one for a friend.
All right.
You want a warm lung?
What do you want?
I need an eyeball.
Okay.
Lung and eyeball.
There's too many people that want stuff.
All right.
Can I filter?
This is $4,300.
I don't have that kind of money.
I know I've done that.
$4,300 eyeball right here.
This one's common.
Buy it.
I don't have enough to buy.
Oh, right here, right here.
B plus rarity rough.
Just buy it.
How much are you going to give me for this?
Oh my God.
It was a lot of money.
Okay.
Yeah.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Fulfill, fulfill.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
I got it.
I get it.
That's how much they want to give you.
All right.
Uh, what do you want?
Three more.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want a heart.
Now give me a heart above 74.
I got 10 seconds.
Oh, I got it.
What?
What the hell?
I got scammed?
You got to go quick.
Okay.
What about...
This is day one.
Do I have any?
Oh, I don't have to.
I don't have to sell it immediately.
I can just buy it.
The condition was wrong.
Oh, okay.
So my reputation enabled eternal war effort.
What?
It was 90 though.
Yeah.
I thought it was high.
You scammed them.
I did?
My reputation is going kind of high.
All right.
Listen, this is kind of cool.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
So can I do anything else with money?
I just have to buy a bunch of shit.
Can I, can I filter or do I have to actually scroll?
It was...
Oh, you only got two minutes of too much pressure.
High reputation, you trash.
It won't be for long.
You just have to scroll.
All right.
25 gram.
What does this get me?
A refrigeration unit welded onto the space.
A cargo hold should occupy and miraculously it works.
You don't have to do requests.
Really?
I'm gonna go for it again.
Let's go.
Rating.
Argo.
Bye.
All right.
What's...
How can I see the...
Warlord Orbis always wants to greet new traders.
With a gift.
Says it helps grease the wheels for everyone.
Would a mythic heart be useful?
Uh, yeah.
Can I sell it?
All right.
Small, condition 68, blood type zero.
Mythic.
I can sell this for 2,500 bucks right now.
No, I'm holding it.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
What do people want?
What do you want?
You want a...
I want a stomach.
I don't think about the thunder of the war harvesters or the...
I just want a stomach.
All right, you want a stomach?
I'll get you a cheap stomach.
Stomach.
It's a liver.
How much was he going to pay me?
I don't remember.
Stomach.
How much was he going to get?
Is this a bad idea?
Yeah, okay.
Got it.
Wait, what?
What happened?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, fulfill.
Shit.
Wait, what do you want?
I need an eyeball.
Filled that.
I'm holding this.
I'm not selling this yet.
Uh, okay, wait, wait, wait.
You're going to be a thousand bucks for...
That's a warm heart.
I want a heart.
You're not getting the one that's in here.
So I got to buy something cheap.
Warm heart.
No.
No, eyeball.
What the fuck?
These are so expensive.
This one's not bad.
All right, bye.
This is going to be a thousand bucks.
I made a hundred dollars on that.
Made a couple hundred dollars on that.
Can I see the chart on this?
I want to see the chart.
Maybe do I unlock a chart?
The dev is in the chat.
Going on, dev.
I can do another quest.
200, do you want me to give a...
You need to give me a stomach.
For 200 bucks, bro.
No, I need a cheap stomach.
There we go.
Oh, I got...
I ascended.
I'm dubious.
New organs unlocked.
The dev in chat said you have to put a face cam on.
I don't have any clothes on, so I can't.
Maybe I should just buy something.
Rarity, rough, rarity, common, condition.
This is in such bad condition.
Should I buy something?
Um...
Ooh.
All right.
What's wrong?
All right, where will my car go?
This thing was worth...
I lost a little bit on this.
Why is that an excuse?
I don't have clothes on.
I'm not going to stream naked.
All right, I leveled up.
Now I know why it's Q and E.
Because this is a game where you have to go very fast.
Oh god, this is going to be fucking horrible.
We won't tell Twitch.
No.
By the way, I just want to make sure everyone's aware.
The New Year's Eve voting is open.
I'm going to give you a link.
You can now go vote if you haven't already.
I'm going to paste it.
Actually, I think some of the mods probably have it already, but...
Let's see.
It is.
I'll get it to you.
This is going to take you a while, potentially, just to let you know.
There are 26 categories this year.
Now make sure you take a lot of time to understand and figure out which one of your favorite errands
of the year it was.
There were so many best and worst noises.
We...
You guys don't understand.
The noise categories had to get split up into four plus.
I think three or four of different categories.
And then they had to get whittled down.
There were like hundreds of best and worst noise nominees.
Hundreds.
Too many.
Yeah, there is worst beater as well.
I don't know. I just felt like putting it there.
I didn't think anyone was going to nominate anything.
I thought it would be funny.
Oh yeah.
That's going to close in a few days.
You only have like four days to do that.
You do want to participate.
That's only going to be open until probably the 30th at midnight, I would assume.
Are you naked?
I am comfortable.
You say naked.
I say comfortable.
Is there a problem?
All right, let's go.
I feel like I'm getting the hang of this.
Traders.
BribeMate has been installed.
You can now buy, favor, and earn reputation from fellow traders,
as well as pay them to stop trading for a day.
What?
I can pay other traders to stop trading?
What's this?
Name the quartermaster.
Goal brains, hearts, and lungs.
Resupplies the scant human colonies.
Focuses on the bare essentials, just in case.
So this guy's buying all the brains, hearts, and lungs.
So I can get rid of this guy.
Favor.
So what?
I get reputation with this guy.
Or I can just say don't trade tomorrow.
I'm not comfortable with that yet.
I don't have enough money to make these like weird moves.
All right.
What do I got?
I still got this.
Do I have any orders to fulfill?
I don't.
All right. I'm ready.
Let's go.
Turn it on.
Yo.
What?
All right.
What do you got?
Holy shit.
What do you need?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know this.
Lung replacement.
See, could you get a lungs?
I need a good lung and eyeball, lung, and eyeball.
Two eyes and lungs.
What's this thing?
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh, he's buying shit.
All right.
I need lungs, lungs, lungs, lungs, lungs.
What is this?
Antlers?
Eyeball?
This guy's taking all my shit.
Lungs.
3,000.
No, no, no.
2,100.
I need the eyeball.
Eyeball.
This is an eye?
It's a soul?
What? You can trade souls?
I need another eyeball.
Nice.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh, my God.
This is rare and it's worth a lot of money.
I got it.
We got.
Holy shit.
I don't even know.
I don't even know what they want.
Just take it before the other guy does.
What do you want?
A new soul.
You want lungs?
Soul, lung, lung.
Soul?
You dick.
This is too expensive.
I'm buying.
This is cheap.
I don't care.
Soul, lung, lung.
Make a mint.
Learn the secrets of the galaxy's top organ trainers.
Read organ barcodes.
All for the low, low price of $730.
Read organ barcodes?
What does it do?
Soul.
Got it.
I need two lungs.
Cheap.
I need cheap lungs.
How expensive?
Cheap.
That one's good.
That one's fine, fine, fine.
Get that one.
Oh, bingo.
Look at this.
Hell yeah.
$4,300 for what?
$4,400 for what?
I only have 10 seconds.
I don't even know what he wants.
Delete it.
I don't want it.
Before they get mad at me.
All right.
That was a good day.
Buy cheap balls.
Your heart's worthless?
Okay, what?
It's mythic though.
Exemplary flesh.
Inspirational.
Improves condition of nearby...
Wait a minute.
What?
Improves condition of nearby organs.
It does?
Blood type condition 49.
The heart will...
Sell the heart.
The condition gets worse over time.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
So these just drop in...
All right.
I bought this for 70 bucks.
I like this.
This is fun.
Mark it.
Oh.
Oh, boy.
Okay.
The heart index?
Mark it in for X-Cormix.
Liver index.
Lungs.
The brain index is pretty...
The brains are doing pretty good.
Expensive.
Wait, I can...
Wait.
Hold on a minute.
I can buy...
These are like ETFs.
These are organ ETFs.
So I can just buy essentially a weighted index of the hearts.
I don't have to buy hearts.
Okay.
Because I can buy stock.
Yes, this is an ETF.
All right.
What's cheap right now?
Eyeballs.
Uh, okay.
Hold on.
Let me...
This is a lot.
All right.
Nothing looks like it's down or anything.
Yeah.
I'm not going to buy any of this shit.
What do you got?
What's wrong with you?
Okay.
Yeah.
If you don't know what an ETF is.
So an ETF is...
And it's called an exchange traded fund.
What an ETF is, it's essentially like a big kind of colony of stocks in one ticker.
So it rises and falls based on the performance of the stuff that the ETF owns.
So let's say you talk about the S&P 500, right?
The SPY.
That's the weighted index of the top 500 companies in the United States by market value.
I'm smart.
I know what I'm talking about.
Okay.
So what that's saying is it's just like...
It's taking the average of all the hearts, essentially.
You are wrong.
I'm smart.
You're wrong.
Excuse me.
This guy right here lost a substantial amount of money
betting against Beyond Meat a few years ago.
I mean, I think I know what I'm talking about.
Anyways, I don't like Jerma when he talks about smart stuff.
No, I'm supposed to be just an idiot, right?
I'm just a dumb guy.
I didn't know anything.
I don't even know how to drive.
I don't even know what state I'm in.
I'm dumb idiot guy.
I did clog the toilet today, though.
And that was embarrassing.
And he's like, I did too, whatever.
I am pretty dumb, don't worry.
And I'm smart where it counts.
Okay.
You go ahead and read your books.
And you go ahead and read your books and get your A pluses.
I don't care.
I'm smart where it counts.
I haven't read a book in 10 years.
That's how you know I'm smart.
Okay, I'm fucking done.
Let's go.
Market open request.
Nerve clusters.
Okay, nerve clusters.
I don't care how...
All right.
This is dog shit.
I'm not...
They're on 9,300.
What do you want?
What is it?
I need something for an old trick of the trade.
If you run out of disinfectant, you can drip rock...
Rot cane juice into a wound?
What does he want?
I don't really want to know what you want.
What do you want?
This is x6 bladder.
How do I do it?
Bladder and liver.
You dick.
Got it.
Does a bladder look like?
This is x6 shit right here.
Is it not?
Does it say x6?
What does he want?
Two nerve clusters.
Do I have enough?
I need one more.
9,300 bucks.
What is this?
I don't understand this rot...
It means you have six days.
Oh, I thought it was x6.
Run out of disinfectant.
Cut and solder.
I don't even know what this is.
Rare lungs.
Rot cane?
Is it something I have to buy?
Okay, you want a liver.
I don't think I...
No, fuck that.
He wants the juice from what though?
What does rot cane juice come from?
Get rot cane.
Pipe, eyeball, size, common, soul.
It's the rot cane.
What is a rot cane?
I feel like you guys are making up a word
and I'm going to say like I like balls or something, right?
Like lick my balls.
It's the DNA logo?
I'm buying this bladder.
I'm going to hold it tomorrow.
I don't understand where it is.
I don't see anything.
Oh, it's closed.
Rot cane is a fluid found in...
Watch out for eyes.
It's the organ next to the heart.
I've never heard of a rot cane.
How's everything doing?
Rot cane.
All right.
Is there a rot cane index?
I should...
Holy shit, dude.
Look at this.
This is only $4?
This is cheapest shit.
I wonder about 100 of these.
That'd be 500?
Yeah.
Just watch.
This shit's going to go to like $1,000.
This is XCormix index.
We've got $2,000 in XCormix.
Just wait 10x in like five or six weeks.
This is really cheap.
Dude, this is too expensive.
Damn.
Buzzwimble.
Rot cane.
All right.
Well, what the fuck?
I can't even buy it.
All right.
Argo.
I have this bladder.
All right.
Let's go.
Bill.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
Give me a heart, please.
Heart.
You want...
This rot cane guy again.
But I don't...
It's not showing up anywhere.
Eyeball.
Fine.
I'll fulfill your dumb request.
Oh, I have too many.
All right.
You want eyeball.
And you want...
Heart, eyeball, rot cane.
Oh!
Got it.
And go.
Heart, rot cane, eyeball.
I need an eyeball.
What's with this market?
There's nothing on here.
I just bought...
I just didn't even want to buy that.
Okay.
Heart.
There's nothing for sale.
What's with this market?
All right.
Now I get why this...
You're supposed to do Q and E and shit.
Another rot cane?
Right here.
That's too expensive, though.
I want a cheaper one.
Give me a cheaper rot cane.
That's...
What the fuck?
$7,500?
That's way too much.
$7,500.
Get out of here.
I get $4,000.
No.
Dogshit return.
I won't...
There we go.
Remember the guy that just told me to wait?
Remember the guy that told me just to do it?
Yeah.
That's a 10x return now.
I'm gonna buy...
Okay.
All right.
I wonder if I should get something else, too.
If I see a rot cane for under $2,000, I'm getting it.
There it is.
I'm buying up all the rot canes.
Another one.
Give me it.
Oh, what...
What's going on here?
Why is this blocked out?
Repair?
I could have just bought that fucking $1,000.
Wait, does that mean...
No.
Okay.
$800.
Oh, mark is over.
All right.
Not bad.
My portfolio...
Oh, what's this?
What's this?
Excuse me?
Where is it?
Um...
Excuse me?
Oh.
It didn't move.
Well, look at...
It says my thing.
My portfolio went up a good high.
Rot cane is bad for you.
Hull.
It is?
Corrosive destroys unprotected hulls.
Oh, shit.
Wait, what about this?
Man, this is sick.
Okay, there's...
All right.
There's upgrades.
Slows to the K of all organs by 25%.
I don't...
I don't want to go broke.
I'll do it tomorrow.
Oh.
What do you want?
Zero?
I'll talk.
I'll burn your life down.
So you owe me a mythic lung.
And I'm not paying shit.
I knew who you are before the fancy office.
What?
Did I just tell him to fuck off?
You exist on my mercy.
What...
Okay.
Urgent opportunity.
Everyone deserves to have organs,
but the powers that be benefit fighting each other.
I want a liver.
No.
All right.
I want...
First segment of the organ barcode
is the organ's market number.
Wait.
Heart is zero zero.
Know the number and you know the item.
Oh, so I don't have to...
Okay.
Heart is zero zero.
I can just memorize these.
So double zero is heart.
All right.
I need eyeball.
Eyeball heart.
No, this is all too cheap.
Do I fulfill this like this guy?
Trade already.
I'm going for it.
Oh, okay.
That's heart.
I see what they're doing.
So I can know exactly...
I don't even look at the icon.
Wait.
I gotta get rid of this shit.
I'll keep one.
Okay.
Hold on.
Does anybody want a rock cane?
What do you want?
Fuck.
I'm getting distracted.
What do you want?
You want...
Heart and eyeball.
How much you want to pay?
That's too stressful.
All right.
Heart for under a thousand.
Eyeball.
Buy it.
Heart for under a thousand.
Double zero, double zero, zero, zero, zero, zero.
Right here.
Got it.
Anybody else have a request?
Stomach.
You got it.
Stomach for how much?
168.
Get out of here.
Stomach, stomach, stomach, stomach, stomach for under a hundred.
Stomach for under a hundred.
Rock cane.
No.
Get it.
Sell it.
I don't want it.
Stomach for under a hundred.
Dude, I'm sorry.
I can't fulfill your request.
What does this guy want?
Mythic lung.
All right.
Well, I didn't do it.
Explain calls and puts.
No.
No, I don't think so.
This person is going to burn my life down.
Why?
How does this game work?
I'm walking my dog.
It's fun.
All right.
30 grand.
Oh, we have some more competition here.
Woohoo Charlie.
Liver, bladders, and kidneys.
Disgraced prince from a distant star.
Topping up on delightful necessities to keep the party going.
White emperor gold star.
Wants rare organs and mythical organs.
And I have it daddy personified.
The answer is always yes.
Just the worst.
If they're going to buy the expensive stuff though,
should I get favor with the rich emperor kid?
I feel like I might get some gifts.
So favor is...
Okay, I got money.
You're still brains, hearts, and lungs and you want rare stuff.
Yellow requests are unique.
Really?
So woohoo Charlie is cool?
Wants livers, bladders, and kidneys.
I mean, should I get a bunch of favor?
I'm going to try it.
I got money.
See what happens.
The requests, not the traders.
Oh, okay.
I'm going to pay.
I'm going to...
Okay, here we go.
What does that do?
Did I just give the rich kid 10 grand for no reason?
Why did I do that?
Do the yellow requests.
Okay.
He's a top 100 streamer like you.
Scammed yourself.
You gave them gift subs.
All right.
What should I do with this?
I bought it for $216,000 and I lost money on it.
But market, market, market.
This didn't move.
You know what?
We're doubling down then.
I'm doubling down on the XCormix.
We're tripling down on the XCormix.
I want 10 grand in XCormix.
Just wait.
It's going to be...
This could be a shortage or something.
Trust me.
All right.
I still have this guy thing.
I have to fulfill this.
Let's go.
This person's still here.
All right.
If I...
No, I have five days to do this one.
Need another eyeball.
Six days to get an eyeball.
Bladder, eye, bladder, eye, bladder, liver.
Eye, bladder, liver for cheap.
Eye, bladder, liver, stomach.
I already have one.
I don't.
Yeah, I do.
Here.
Eye, bladder, stomach eye.
Stomach eye for less than 200.
Stomach eye.
Bingo.
Got it.
Did I get it?
Oh, that piece of shit.
Bladder.
Got it.
Fuck.
I have to...
I can't...
I'm too slow.
I'm never gonna make the raid.
My DPS is gonna be too low
because I'm in competition with these idiots.
Did I get it?
I didn't...
What did I buy?
What do you want?
You want eyeball and a stomach.
No.
Stop it.
Give me that.
Eyeball.
There we go.
Oh my god.
I have to compete with these idiots.
This one's valuable.
My DPS is too low.
The second segment of an organ barcode
is the organ size.
D is tiny.
C is small.
B is average.
A is large.
S is gigantic.
Oh god damn it.
Okay.
So zero A is a huge heart.
Zero S is a gigantic...
No.
Zero zero.
Zero zero S is big.
Okay.
So it's just grades.
This is the size of the organ.
So for instance, if we go to the hearts,
this is zero zero D.
Zero zero heart.
It's very small.
This is a huge heart right here.
You know what I mean?
I think I need to drink a little
fucking cup of coffee for this one.
There's a B.
Got it.
That one was a pretty good one.
There's a B.
I guess.
I don't know.
Should I have it?
What do you want?
Liver.
What does a liver look like?
Kidney?
Stomach?
What is a liver?
Devs tweeted about you.
Oh, look at me.
What is a liver?
You guys know how big your liver actually is.
How much are you going to pay me?
I don't think that's worth it.
Oh.
All right.
Oh, 20%.
There it is.
Two grand in the bank.
I'm not selling it.
I'm not selling it to at least,
it's at least a thousand.
All right.
These are pretty valuable.
Common, common mythic.
I have a mythic eye.
Zero two is liver.
Okay.
Oh, I'm going to have to memorize this.
Aren't I going to be this thing
turned to papers, please.
Isn't it?
Stop losing value.
I buy some more.
Anything else like crash?
Nothing.
Everything seems doing okay.
Yeah, my stock went up.
Oh, yeah.
I'm not selling it.
You still need a liver.
Liver is zero two.
You said, okay.
Let's go.
This guy's back again.
Dude, like, oh, soul.
And I'm tired.
You want just, I want a soul.
Soul, nerve cluster.
Soul, nerve cluster, and heart.
Soul, nerve cluster, heart.
Soul, nerve, soul.
That's two, got it.
Fuck off, buddy.
Liver.
Wait, what?
What is all this shit?
Why do I have all these bladders?
I snipe that guy so bad.
All right.
Liver and I got new organs.
Liver and liver and wait.
The third segment of an organ barcode
is the organ's condition.
If the barcode is the condition is 60.
God.
So it goes organ type, size, condition.
Organ type, size, condition.
This is too much for my fucking pea brain.
Oh, this 9100.
Rot cane, got it.
Not a scam.
This is a scam.
I lie.
Do not send me a heart.
I cannot make amends for this failure of conscience.
But I am so sorry.
I deserve nothing in this world.
Goodbye.
I'll get it for you.
You want a heart?
Here.
Okay.
Now I need rot cane, nerve, liver.
No way.
Rot cane, nerve, liver, nerve.
Rot cane, rot cane, rot cane, rot cane, rot cane, rot cane.
Nerve.
That's too much.
Come on.
I'll buy that stomach and I'll buy that eye.
All bladder.
Okay.
Nerve.
I need a nerve.
Rot cane, nerve.
Stop buying shit.
We need more stuff on the market.
You idiot.
I'll buy that.
I'll buy that too.
How much are you gonna give me for the nerve?
Oh, buy it.
Eat shit.
I got it.
Oh my God.
Why do I have so many of these?
What do you guys need?
All right.
You want a nerve cluster for $3,200.
Oh.
All right.
That was a good day.
Still, I got 12 grand over here still.
I'm fine.
Maybe I should upgrade my, um...
Should I sell some stock?
Nah.
No.
Hey, a real-life Devon chat here.
I hacked Kinect support into this game before it launched.
This is not a bit, though it is objectively funny.
If you plug in a Kinect on PC and step in front of it, it'll work.
What?
What are you talking?
Why?
Why would you do that?
I don't think that makes any sense.
I need to get the Kinect drivers for the computer.
It's because it was funny.
I don't...
I don't even know where my Kinect is.
I don't know.
I have a feeling I'm gonna plug that in and the Kinect's gonna turn on.
It's gonna take a bunch of pictures of me sitting here naked.
I don't know if I want to do that.
Don't find it.
Maybe later.
I'm trading.
I'm wheeling and dealing here.
Give me a minute.
Just do it.
I feel...
What if it crashes my stream?
All right.
Hold on.
Let me...
I have to put clothes on.
Does it take pictures of you?
I'm so concerned about this for no reason.
All right.
This guy's Messy Marcus.
He doesn't have any goals.
A panicking, anxious, desperate wreck.
If they could escape themselves, they would.
Here.
Take $86 and fuck off.
Ipe Emperor Gold Star.
No.
Get dressed.
What if it crashed my stream with like the Spongebob text
leaning down doing like the Spongebob stance?
I'm trying...
Let me just get used to the game first.
It hasn't even been like 40 minutes.
It actually works.
I promise I will plug in my Kinect.
But not yet.
Is the Kinect USB?
God damn it.
All right.
I'm not holding anything.
Let's do trading day start.
Let's go.
Okay.
I like this guy.
Fratera Open Market sent me a heart.
I will compensate you over 20 times after it arrives.
Oh my God.
Okay.
Heart.
Eyeball.
Ah, naughty creature.
I know what you did.
If you do not want...
If you do not want everyone to know your big secret,
you'll send me a stomach via private...
All right.
Whatever.
What do we need here?
This guy is fucking weird.
Heart.
Eyeball.
Nerve.
Heart.
Liver.
Eyebar.
Eyeheart.
Eyeho...
Eyeheart radio.
What do I need?
An eyeball.
Eyeball.
Heart.
I'm fucking...
I'm messed up.
Eyeball.
Heart.
Just one at a time.
I can't...
Too slow.
I'm too slow.
Nerve.
Eyeball.
Liver.
Why do I keep buying stomachs?
Eyeball.
Liver.
Zero.
Two.
Eyeball.
I don't need two.
Liver.
Step...
What do I need?
Okay.
Um, I made money on that shit.
Nerve cluster and liver.
Got it.
Liver.
What's that?
Shift walks.
I don't know what the hell that...
How is that not a liver?
It's a liver.
What do you want?
I just want...
Okay.
Request.
Who wants what?
I got...
Give me a liver above 54.
You got it.
Uh, give me a stomach.
Sure.
Um, okay.
Liver.
This is liver.
54 liver.
Any liver.
54 liver, stomach, liver.
Whoops.
Damn it.
Didn't go up.
Ooh.
I dipped on that.
Jeremiah, have you on the background?
It sounds like you're just buying organs from chat members.
Imagine how fast you could do this if you were doing the minority report with the connect.
All right.
What am I doing?
Here we are.
54 liver.
Let's go.
All right.
What do you got?
I need a heart and a soul.
Thanks.
Heart, soul.
Heart, soul, kidney.
Heart, soul, kidney, liver, kidney.
Heart, soul, double kidney.
Heart, soul, double kidney, liver, kidney.
Heart, soul, liver, kidney.
I don't fucking remember.
Just one at a time.
I gotta have a system here.
Kidney.
Heart, soul, kidney.
I can do this like the planets.
Like my mother, uh, told me to whatever it is like doing all the planets.
Heart.
Okay.
Kidney.
Leave me alone.
Organ's blood type.
If you don't know what a blood type is, I can't help you.
That's a fourth segment.
Oh my God.
Heart, kidney.
Heart, soul, kidney.
Heart, soul, kidney, liver.
Heart, soul, kidney, liver, 54 liver.
Heart, soul, kidney.
Heart, soul, liver, 54 liver, kidney.
54 liver, kidney.
Heart, soul, kidney, liver, 54 kidney.
Heart, soul, liver, 54 kidney.
No, just fulfill these.
I already have them.
What do I have?
Nothing.
Kidney, liver, 50 liver, 50 kidney, liver, liver, 54.
Kidney, liver, 54, 54.
Kidney, liver, 54.
Okay, I need 54.
Come on, dude.
Really?
54 liver.
Kidney, liver.
I need that liver.
I'll give you 334 right now.
You have to decide right now, right now.
It's values depreciating.
Right now, before it's too late.
Okay, okay.
I know who you are.
Give me a lung.
I don't care.
Wait, what?
Liver right now.
Liver, liver, liver, kidney.
Liver, liver, liver, 54 kidney.
Liver, liver, liver, liver, liver, liver, liver, liver, liver, 54 kidney.
And there's a lot of livers on the market.
All right, I'm making money.
What is happening?
It's fun.
Okay, you know what?
I leave.
I don't want this.
This guy is buying all the livers and all the kidneys.
Go home.
Messy Marcus is here again.
You leave too.
All of you leave.
I don't care about hearts and lungs.
Go fuck yourself.
That was mean.
I'm sorry.
I need livers.
I have to get rid of the people that are buying livers.
Okay, apologize to the quartermaster now.
No, we're all rotten scumbags, okay?
Look what we're doing.
Such a weird image too.
Okay, so let me get this right.
I need a bunch of livers.
I think I need three livers and a kidney and one has to be above 54.
Go.
No, come on.
I'm not going to pay attention to any of that.
I need livers.
I need livers and one kidney.
This is way too much money.
No one's buying it so I can just sit there and depreciate.
I don't care.
There's one liver.
All right.
I need more than that.
Come on, man.
In the meantime, heart.
I need another liver.
I need a 54 liver or a shitty heart.
What's with this market?
There it is.
Finally, 54.
That's good.
All right, let's go.
Bang.
54.
That's so expensive.
I'm going to lose money on this.
All right, take that.
Now we need a heart, liver, and a kidney.
Give me this.
Okay, perfect.
Got it.
That was cheap.
I'll give some more requests there.
Okay, casual.
There's a cloning lab.
They figured out how to make organs but they need materials.
I don't have much but please help me help the rest of us.
One average lung, please.
All right.
Sure.
What do you have that idiot want ?
Stomach.
Eye.
Liver.
Stomach.
Eye.
Heart.
Stomach.
Eye.
Liver.
Heart.
Stomach.
Eye.
Liver.
Heart.
Stomach.
Eye.
Liver.
Heart.
Stomach.
Eye.
Liver.
Heart.
Stomach.
Eye.
Liver.
liver heart, a liver heart, a liver heart, steps on the car, liver heart, a liver heart,
Emma, god, liver heart, stomach, heart, stuff and I lyrical heart.
we double zero, come on, come on, come on, well, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait long, lung, lung, lung, lung, lung, lung, lung, lung, lung, lung, lung, lung,
lung.
Holy shit, that was 3,500 bucks.
What?
That was so expensive.
Oh, higher.
I'm sick of waiting.
And this is what we doubled down again.
I have 4,000 shares of this XCormix ETF, it's just going to 50 bucks.
Alright, you wanted a heart, take it.
You need to hedge your investment, massive loss incoming.
Now I understand why you lost everything on Beyond Meat, I didn't, okay let me, let's
be really clear, I didn't lose everything on Beyond Meat, I didn't lose everything.
I traded with a little bit of money and lost that money, I didn't lose everything.
I lost a small portion of what I would consider to be a small, it was a small amount, please
don't twist it.
Alright, this is still doing okay, notable traits, successfully scammed.
Alright let's go.
Chad Shakespeare always wants to buy high condition organs, decisive eccentric quick
witted kajillionaire, not a dog legally, shit, alright I'll just, we'll do competition,
Ah, naughty creature, I know what you did, if you do not want everyone to know your big
secret, what's with everybody wanting to, my big secrets apparently, what are they talking
about, why is everybody trying to scam me?
Let me stomach and I'll compensate you 20 times over.
Alright, liver, heart, liver, ooh it's this guy, you keep reading these messages so I'm
going to assume that you care, thank you.
Next I need a shift wux, we can use these to grow or shrink raw organs as needed, alright
shift wux.
Alright first of all, let's do this quick, this one is liver, liver heart, liver liver
heart stomach, liver liver heart stomach, liver liver heart stomach, liver liver heart
stomach, what do I have?
Liver liver liver stomach, liver stomach, liver stomach, come on you piece of shit,
liver stomach, liver, I can start burning these out.
Ok, I need a shift wux, can I just do this for this person, this person is going to burn
me down or something, whatever, alright we need more more more more shift wux, I saw
shift wux down here, $4100, this better be worth it dude, you need a liver, no livers,
lots of lungs though, maybe I should buy some of these, alright I'm going to hold these
for a day or two, I'm buying this lung, and I'm buying this bladder, and I'm buying this
liver, it's a shitty liver, it's B plus 51, no way, large liver, 19 condition, $600 get
out of here, alright I'm good, yeah fuck off, alright this is going to be huge, I need to
upgrade this ship, the more scams you accept the more scams will be offered to you, oh
it's messy marcus, it's another $100 get out of here, indecisive ricky, I can handle it,
but wait, I have a lung and I have a bladder, the bladder is actually pretty valuable, pretty
good condition, it's small though, you're losing money, I am investing, I have $24,000
in my portfolio right now, just wait, in fact you know what because you said that, I'm going
to have 5,000 shares of this company, let's go, alright, I already got it, no I don't,
soul an eyeball, soul eyeball, soul eyeball eyeball liver, soul eyeball eyeball liver,
soul eyeball eyeball liver, so whoa what was that, soul eyeball eyeball liver, soul eyeball
eyeball liver, soul eyeball eyeball liver, soul eyeball eyeball liver, the soul is an
eyeball eyeball liver, soul eyeball eyeball liver, is it meat, zero is meat, one is special,
soul eyeball eyeball liver, soul eyeball eyeball liver, soul eyeball, soul I need a
soul, alright, soul, holy this is a legendary kidney, what do you want, I need a rare soul,
fuck, I need a soul, what is all this crap, get rid of this, why do I have this tiny bladder,
oh it's actually, whatever, I need a rare soul and a soul and an eyeball, got it, is
this rare, no, valuable, okay, request, fulfill, you wanted, what the fuck did you want, you
wanted an eyeball too, rare, rare, I can't, is this rare, I like something meat, wet and
juicy like a heart, I need a rare soul, whoa, oh my fucking god I have no money, I need
a heart, can I afford any, that just went up in price when I pressed the button didn't
it, alright, alright, I'm good, I'm not broke, I've got, look at all the money I have in
the stock market, I could shave a little bit of my portfolio, what happens when you
run out of money, I have no idea, oh it didn't, no, I didn't make any money, I got 30 grand
here man, I thought it went up, oh, that doesn't matter, just wait, it's not gonna crash, I
do need to upgrade some shit here, I have a stomach and a liver and this is valuable,
okay, let's go, this is, we're running out of water, I need a lung, juicy lung, not a
scam, this is a scam, I don't care, lung, heart, lung, heart, liver, thank you, this
is a heart, I need a heart and I need lungs, oh fuck, I don't have any money, heart, bang,
alright, there you go, there's some cash, alright, I need a pretty cheap heart, pretty
cheap, I wonder if I should, the shift wux is cheap right now, did I buy a cheap shift
wux, that's good condition too, look at that, maybe one of these cheap souls, I don't want
to take this for quest, I need to get mythic lung, I only have 22, I have $2,000, yeah,
I think this is gonna be good, these things are worth a lot of money, accept it and throw
it away, alright, alright, slow down, the gallblad is usually really expensive and the,
these usually get expensive but I'm not buying it, no, no, no, no, no, no, let the clock
run out, the worst part is he averaged up, so, who cares, ooh, that's good, that was,
I had to do that, that was literally a steal, oh my god, it's three condition, that's why
it was so cheap, wait, increases in size every day changes surrounding organs in the
process, what do you mean changes them, can I do that, I'm confused, what does that mean,
changes in size every day gets bigger, alright, I have no money, just gotta go again, come
on, hurry up, okay, rot cane, I'll get this one immediately, good luck, enjoy the certificate
of completion and good riddance, no refunds, rot cane, stomach, eyeball, rot cane, stomach,
eyeball, oh, I got it, didn't I, just in case I didn't get it, eyeball, rot cane, am, slim
pickings, eyeball, oh, don't press that, I don't have enough, I don't have enough money
to buy a rot cane, unless it's cheap, I have to buy a wicked dog shit rot cane, dude, what
the hell, I can't afford this rot cane, is it gonna be a really bad one, 8300, shit, shit,
shit, no, give me a bad rot cane, oh yeah, oh yeah, I'm invincible, that stomach, I'll
give you 50 bucks for it right now, fuck off, no other requests, right, I buy that back,
I'm buying that back for 2000, oh yeah, I got gall bladders, I got stomachs and shit,
take the request, mythic lung, where am I gonna get a mythic lung, these guys just buy
everything that comes up, you're not, you're not using any strategy, lung, I need a mythic
lung, okay, well whatever, we're coming back, what is this game, this game is space warlord
organ trading simulator, it's very good, this is expensive, okay, I'm doing alright, so
I have a liver, a gall bladder, a shift box and a stomach, so I have capacity here, if
it's a bad deal or a scam, you can accept it and then immediately tell them to fuck
off so you don't get more, so you can get more, oh okay, read the request, idiot, read
the, read the request, idiot, yes, I read this one, I owe this person a mythic lung
or they're gonna burn my house down or something like that, so hurry up and read those requests,
idiot, go, heart, bladder, kidney and bladder, heart, bladder, kidney, heart, heart, bladder,
kidney, heart, heart, bladder, kidney, stomach, heart, heart, bladder, kidney, they can have
some, heart, heart, bladder, kidney, heart, heart, heart, bladder, kidney, heart, heart,
bladder, kidney, heart, heart, bladder, kidney, heart, heart, bladder, kidney, heart, heart,
bladder, kidney, heart, heart, heart, bladder, kidney, heart, heart, heart, bladder, kidney,
heart, heart, heart, bladder, kidney, heart, heart, heart, bladder, kidney, heart, heart,
heart, heart, bladder, kidney, heart, heart, heart, bladder, bladder, kidney, heart, heart,
heart, heart, bladder, bladder, kidney, heart, heart, heart, bladder, bladder, kidney, heart,
heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart,
heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart,
heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart.
So that's case number 3.
Heart, heart, bladder.
Fuck.
Heart, I got a bladder, I need a heart.
Art!
I'm a hunter, a huntin', flesigkeiten.
Getting their meat.
I can bring some to you when I have extra if you want.
Yeah, sure.
All right.
Kidney, core.
I need a kidney.
And go.
And you want a fancy lung.
What does he want?
A mythic lung.
It's common, an Daeus.
Mythic lung.
Any more requests?
Oh fuck yeah.
cluster the nerve cluster eyes nerve cluster double eye nerve cluster double
eye kidney nerve cluster oh my god nerve cluster nerve cluster nerve cluster
nerve cluster double eye done nerve I'm gonna pee nerve cluster double like that
soul is gonna be worth a lot their cluster oh I got it I'm in I got in come
on do something this soul I think is gonna be really good it'll come in handy
and but it's the only thing for it no this one down in value it's all right I
gotta pee I'll be right back it's pee time and yes we are still using the
Christmas we're using the Christmas BRB still as I want to see in one sec I'm
not kidding around I think I threw my connect in the trash let me let me look
one more time hold on I got it all right where's the dev expl- okay you explain
this to me right now you're telling me that if I plug it in if I plug my
connect in into the USB it's like it's impossible to be calibrated is this even
the real dev or we just getting fucked with is this a real person why did I go
get my connect is this is not even a real guy this is not even the real guy
I think you guys just maybe go get a connect and plug it in if I plug my
connect into the computer it's gonna be like oh I'm recognizing your connect let
me fucking take over your computer and calibrate the system it's real I'll try
this for five minutes and I'm moving on I hope I don't break anything it's real
it's real it's real just plug it in idiot all right I'm gonna plug it in
just give me a sec fucking mess all right I'm gonna plug it in oh he's
shaved he's a different guy okay hold on put it back put it back if I go like
this okay so work yes I'm wearing Star Wars
I'm not gonna go dressed for you I was it's a miracle I put this on it's a
Christmas miracle I found a t-shirt like tantrum okay so let me plug it in just
to prove that this is not bullshit here here's the pump I'm about to plug the
connect into the computer right now it's going in here it goes it's coming it's
going in this is not a USB what is this this is not a USB I can't plug this into
my computer what is this what's happening there's my mouse my mouse is
my mouse is not even plugged in I don't I can't even use my computer now this is
I can't even use my computer I need an adapter no I don't oh my god dude I can't plug that in I don't even what connection even is this what is that um this is HDMI this is not HDMI this is like almost like data port it's a
fought what is it it has to go into display port uh excuse me I have to plug
this into a display port how is this gonna work it's actually display port on
the back of the graphics card I don't have any slots I have three monitors
it's not a display port it's called a D port it's not display port do I have one
of these on the back of my computer you need the Microsoft OEM connect adapter
for Windows no you don't fucking flashlight I'm gonna freeze holy shit
holy shit that was that was unbelievable all right what do you look what do you
want me to do you have the connect 1.0 2.0 or the only the only the 2.0 has the
USB I bought this Xbox 360 he used that like a garage sale I don't know what
this is I don't know what version 2 3 or 4 it almost worked let's go back to
trading why am I so cringe because the alien fucking life force that came to me
ten years ago told me he feeds off of the cringe and I'm the only thing that's
keeping the planet from being destroyed so you should say you're welcome doing my
best all right well there we go the connect
there was fun it's so stupid you've ruined the mystery you the lung guys how
you progress the game all right cool let's keep on okay I got money the
market I it's hasn't really gone up or down so I think I'm all right the dev
just tweeted out that you're playing the game without clothes on there's nothing
inaccurate about that Mac ready let's trade Fingo let's get it anyway I'm
anyway what do you want I need a hot night a pleasure heart
whether art bladder eyeball art letter eyeball art bladder eyeball heart
bladder I would you want art latter art letter eyeball eyeball art letter
eyeball eyeball heart bladder eyeball eyeball what have I fucking just do I
I don't care, sell this.
They're gonna get my hearts.
Behold the organ barge.
A shipment of kidneys arrives.
The market quakes in fear.
Buy a ball, buy, buy, buy, buy, buy, buy, buy.
All right, eyeballs, heart, bladder, eyeball.
Heart, bladder, eyeball.
Get rid of this.
Dinosaur egg.
Heart, bladder, eyeball.
Shit, these are so cheap.
I need to get one.
Punch it down an extra stomach
and thought you might want it.
35 credits, yeah, sure.
Thanks.
Heart, bladder, eyeball.
Heartless.
Bladder, come on.
Come on, man.
Come on.
I only bought that because I know you wanted it.
Heart, bladder, eyeball.
Oh, this is gigantic.
I'll take it.
I need a lung, heart.
There's some hearts.
Heart, bladder, I need a bladder.
Ah, all right.
Come on, go.
The devs tweet.
What's the Twitter?
I need to see it.
Time to see it.
What are they saying?
Come on.
The fact that this is too late
for Jerma's yearly award show is criminal.
This entire Kinect bit is usually best joke
that took over five minutes.
You've given this man a mental breakdown.
Is there actually no such thing
as Kinect support for this game?
Was that like a 20 minute, I just got had?
He found his Kinect.
It can't be real.
54 liver, stomach, liver.
I can't believe you've now made Jerma worry
about the Kinect taking pictures of him nude.
Ah, this is funny.
It's not real.
I don't believe it's real.
It can't be.
I can't plug that shit into my computer.
Kinect FAQ.
Wait, okay.
FAQ, yes, we support Kinect.
Does this game support Kinect?
Yes, on PC only.
If you plug in a Kinect 2.0 to your computer
while the game is open,
you can play through the entirety of the game
using Kinect controls.
Grab meat with your meat hands.
Your body is to control it.
We live in the future.
Good luck.
I guess I have the original like dog shit Kinect.
Thing that uses like an orange display port.
What are you linking me with?
Oh, it's somebody using it with the Kinect.
Are you kidding me?
Ah, this is fun.
This game's fun.
I like this game.
All right, let's go.
All right, let's move.
What do you want?
Heart, bladder.
I need a heart and a bladder.
So we have a heart and now we need a bladder.
Heart is more expensive than what he wants.
Okay, just need a bladder.
These are going up in value.
Again, what do I need?
Heart, I need a bladder.
No, not a gall bladder.
The dev is debating me.
What the fuck?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I hit E instead of W.
No, heart is $180.
Are you kidding me?
That's cheap.
I gotta chill out.
Relax.
I need a bladder.
Get some more of these.
No, focus.
What the hell do you guys want?
Stomach in five days.
I want a heart and I want a nerve cluster.
Yeah, I got five days to do these.
Nerve cluster and stomach.
Stomach and shift works.
Oh my God, you idiot.
Just get rid of these stupid kidneys.
No, this one.
No, I wanted to find, no, dude.
What the hell?
Here.
I need a heart and a bladder.
I need a bladder now.
Bladder, now.
Oh my God, that was cheap.
Did you see this thing?
93 quality, small, blood type AB, mythic quality, $200.
This thing's worth at least a thousand.
All right, stop being like a fucking comedy guy.
Need a bladder, bladder.
I know I missed a bladder.
It's because people are faster than me
and I accidentally hit E instead of W.
Oh my goodness.
You want a fancy, what do you want?
All right, nerve cluster.
Ooh, bingo.
Two eyeballs for the price of one,
thanks to my last hunting trip, 400.
Get out of here, fuck off.
Little squirrely fella thought
they could hide their pancreas from me.
Made sure it's real high condition.
600 bucks, yeah, I'll take it.
That's pretty good.
That's pretty good quality, too.
Oh my freaking God.
Did I hold it?
No, sell it now.
Stomach and a shift wux.
I think I already have the stomach.
I do and I need a shift wux.
Shift wux, aw.
This is going up in value.
I just paid two grand on that trade.
Remember to please show your piss bottle.
I pee in the toilet like a human.
I have, okay.
What am I fulfilling here?
Let me do this one.
Mythic lung.
I need mythic lung and I need a shift wux.
Is that a shift wux?
Mythic, oh my God, I can't even read.
Mythic lung and a shift wux.
Got it, okay.
Thank you.
I need a mythic lung.
Let's take some more requests.
What's this one?
Rarity doesn't matter, get me a shard now.
Okay, you guys have terrible deals.
Need, what am I doing here?
Okay, shard, soul.
Shard, soul, mythic lung.
That's too expensive.
God, oh.
Mythic, the organ barge approaches.
Tomorrow ports across the galaxy
will drown in nerve clusters.
The market begins to whip itself into a frenzy.
Huh?
Mythic lung.
Give me a lung, come on.
Mythic lung, mythic lung, what is this?
Mythic, nope.
I missed it?
No, I didn't.
This is rough.
It's a spleen, spleen, come on, where is it?
Lung, common, common, common, rough.
No one's buying today.
Sell nerve clusters, I don't have any.
I'm looking for a mythic lung.
Damn.
Why would there be $3200 for a common lung?
Give me a break.
I don't think I'm gonna get it today.
This spleen is gonna plummet, sell it.
I don't have, why?
Mythic.
Oh!
That was so much money.
Oh, fuck these guys.
Ha, naughty creature, I don't care.
This is, I'm telling you, this isn't gonna play out.
My stock portfolio,
maybe I should buy some more securities.
You have to influence the stock market.
Yeah, but I mean, what do you wanna do?
Wait a minute.
Didn't they say that
something was gonna crash today, right?
What was it?
Something was gonna,
they said something was gonna crash today.
Nerves, okay, where's the nerves?
Nerve clusters are gonna crash today.
All right, so when the nerve clusters clash,
I'm gonna buy a shitload of stock on the UTF.
Why would people buy this?
So tomorrow, remind me to come back here
because we're buying,
buying the dip.
All right, let's go.
Aim it up front.
Enter, I'm entering.
The guy with all the TV ads, he's a bit visible,
but sure, I can take him out.
Just need my large rot cane up front.
Okay, large rot cane.
Soul, a new soul,
rot cane, soul, and a lung.
Large rot cane.
Warlord Artigan declares a temporary truce
in all territories occupied by his armies.
Organ traders react in outrage.
Oh my goodness gracious,
the market just fucking tanked
and I can just get a bunch of cheap shit here.
I think I'm gonna,
so I just bought, all right.
All right, I'm gonna buy a bunch of cheap nerve clusters.
And this lung.
I need more space in my inventory.
What is this?
Get rid of it.
Liver, I already have that.
Here you go.
You want a soul.
I'm buying low.
I need a soul though.
Oh man, that was a good one.
These are, look at this, valuable.
B plus 68 quality, 53, 45.
I mean, they're not great,
but like these will be,
this will go way higher tomorrow.
I need a soul.
Dude, somebody sell a soul to me, please.
I'll take that.
I know you're trying to make a profit,
but if you help me and some friends
undercut the price of nerve clusters,
it would let me treat a lot of people.
Sorry, I just bought like four of them.
I'm sorry.
Soul, soul.
Come on.
Shard, shards.
Maybe I should buy a shard and hold onto it.
Nobody's selling anything.
What is this?
I mean, see if I can get a heart,
heart or a soul.
I'll take it.
I didn't make it at this point.
No, no, all right.
Oh, hell yeah.
Look at this shit.
What about my, oh, oh no.
No, oh no.
Ooh, ooh, that hurts.
That really hurts.
I'm gonna get my cost down.
I'm gonna get my cost average down.
I can look at all this.
I got all this cash coming up here.
What?
No, I wanted to start the trading day.
I was just so confused.
I just sat there silently for five seconds.
What did I just do?
Jard, jard, heart.
Oh Jesus.
Okay, how much?
I need a soul, a shard and a heart.
Soul and a shard.
Ah, I can't afford it.
What?
That's a soul, I got it, I got it.
Oh my God, that's a huge return.
Thank God.
Jard.
What do you want?
I want large rot cane.
I gotta get rid of this.
Large rot cane.
What else do you guys want?
Heart.
Heart and a large rot cane.
That's the heart.
Need a rot cane.
Large rot cane, rot cane, rot cane, rot cane.
Any more requests?
Eyeball.
And you, fuck, outta here.
Rot cane?
Is it large?
It's tiny.
Shipment of gallbladders arrives.
A regulator shudder at the market impacts to come.
Fuck you.
Oh no, they're so cheap.
I want them all.
I just bought the worst ones.
I bought the actually worst ones.
Sell them, sell them back.
Almond, mythic, mythic.
That one's a good quality.
Rare, large and rare.
Large, rare and large.
Mythic, but bad quality.
Rough, rough, rough, rough, rough,
rough, rough, rough, rough, rough.
I want mythic.
No, don't just flood myself.
I need to upgrade my cargo space
instead of putting $40,000 under the fucking stock market.
It's all right.
It's okay, we'll be fine.
I need a rot cane.
No, too big.
Average rot cane.
Are these gonna go up in value?
Oh no.
Average price paid, three.
See, I'm fine.
But look at this, I could buy some of this.
Oh, I want it so bad.
I want it so bad.
Is this live?
Yeah, this is twitch.tv, man.
I need cargo space.
All right, I'm gonna just make money.
I'm not gonna look at anything, just make money.
Oh my fucking God, I'm trying to start the trading day.
Not sell something.
$600 less than what I bought it for.
Kidney, kidneys.
Okay, kidneys, kidney, kidney, stomach, eyeball.
Kidney, kidney, stomach, eyeball.
Kidney, kidney, kidney.
Ooh, you need kidney, kidneys.
This is not large, kidney.
I need that.
Don't buy that, you fucking stupid, you goddamn mutt.
I don't want, eyeball.
Don't buy that, you dumb dog.
I need a, okay, let's fill this mug.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, what?
Stupid dog, you make me look bad.
Bugga, buga, buga, buga, buga.
In two days, ports across the galaxy
will be flooded with lungs.
Okay, eyeballs, all right.
Oh boy, what the hell is going on here?
What, oh, can I have one of these?
All right, what do I need?
I have 45 seconds.
Shard, heart, heart, heart, heart, stomach, eyeball.
Oh my God, shut up.
God, God, God, God.
Drop the shift books that'll shrink organs
instead of growing them.
I don't have $4,000, dude.
Shard, liver, shard, I need a shard and a liver.
Oh, no, you don't want a liver?
I thought lives depend on it.
I thought I said liver depends on it.
Dude, I need to buy this.
No more bullshit, how much, is this recovering yet?
I bought these for $2,1400, $800, oh, this is bad.
I still need a, I need a bladder and I need a shard.
Let's go, oh, I got it.
Bladder, I need to buy another bladder and a shard.
Fulfill this shit, shard, come on.
Laura, what do you want?
Heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, liver, heart, heart,
liver, shard, heart, heart, liver, shard, rot cane.
Heart, liver, shard, heart, heart, heart, liver, shard.
Oh, I can't fucking, come on, dude.
Oh, thank you, all right.
Heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart,
heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, liver, shard.
Relax, what am I doing?
How have I not had any, heart, heart, liver, shard?
You piece of shit, I needed that.
That was a large rot cane.
That's too much money.
I'm not spending $11,000 on this, come on, man.
Get out of here.
$16,000, what are you talking about?
Heart, heart, liver, shard, heart, heart, heart.
No, no, I need a shard.
I'm not leaving here till I get one.
Okay, that sucked, but it was at least I got it.
Now you need a liver.
Wait, now I need a heart.
Heart, come on, heart, come on, heart, come on,
heart, come on, oh.
I'm doing, I'm doing all right.
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
My average price, that's why you double down.
And now it's a $60,000, man, that's 100% profit.
I average this shit down.
After these, I bought it three.
Sell, I'll tell you what I'll do.
I'm gonna sell some, I'm not selling all.
I'm not cashing out, no, not the whole thing.
I'm leaving what I put in.
I got 30 grand in here, I just took it, look at that.
Now let's go for it, bingo.
More spaces, more capacity.
25% slower decaying of the units
that are inside the refrigerator.
Nice, put it on, oh yeah, two more slots.
This is 40 grand, this is 10 slots.
Ooh, okay, so if I do this, then I can hold onto some stuff.
You hit the cap, they can't go higher.
What do you mean cap?
Sell all, price is at the max, dude.
What are you talking about?
Oh, I did not understand what I was looking at.
This is the maximum it can possibly be?
I thought this was just the range that it's in right now.
That is the maximum.
I thought this was just a sort of range
that this is currently in.
I thought I saw nine, yeah, I think,
wait, you guys, I don't think you guys are right.
It was seven before, they're bullshitting you.
Yeah, yeah, guys, you don't know what you're talking about.
Yeah, you have no idea what you're talking about.
One guy, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, you know, you didn't know what you're talking about.
You don't know what you're talking about.
I could come back then.
Why would you come back then?
We'll be closed.
All right, let's go.
I don't care, shard, kidney, liver.
Okay, let's fulfill this shit.
Okay, shard, liver.
Oh, God damn it, all these lungs.
They're too expensive.
That's your lucky liver.
That's like the best fucking character.
That's the best movie ever made, I think.
Fine Ghostbusters.
I don't wanna buy any of these.
Maybe they're all rough, common, common, rough.
This one's rare, but too expensive.
No, this would be somebody else's problem.
Stomach, I need a shard.
This is large raw cane.
I'm not gonna spend that much money.
What do you guys all want?
Kidneys, shards, kidney, shard, heart, liver.
Kidneys, shard, heart, liver.
Kidney, ugh, fine, no.
That's a few of them, at least.
1,200, I'll take it.
I need a heart and a liver.
Heart, I need hearts, man.
And go, all right, got it.
What?
I heart, a liver, oh, and a stomach.
I didn't read the second part.
I bought the wrong one.
I'm now a professional, all right.
Holy shit, eight grand?
I have emotions and they suck.
Get me a new brain.
I started screaming and I did not stop
and now we're crying, new lungs.
This is relatable, all right.
All right, all right, all right, all right,
right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right,
right, right, right, right.
Do I need, okay, I need, I'll do it tomorrow.
I can't do it, my brain's too slow right now.
Who are you?
I'll do it tomorrow.
This is why I wanted to buy into that nerve index.
Look at this, that's a 100% increase.
And it's not even a bad time to buy it, I don't think.
Liver, bladder, and kidney, okay.
Don't FOMO, the valve nerve index
is what you're gonna play Half-Life 3 on.
I need good lungs.
Let me fulfill these ones first
because I'm gonna get so caught up here.
Lungs, lung, brain, lung, brain, shard,
rot cane, lung, brain, shard.
Whoa, lung, brain, shard.
Brains are gonna be cheap.
Lung, brain, shard, I got the shard.
Lung, brain, lung, that's, that, lungs are awful.
Lung, brain, lymph, lung, brain.
Oh, my eyes, okay, I'm buying that.
I need to buy a brain, what is that?
Shard, wait, I didn't even need that.
Okay, all right, I need a brain and lungs.
Brain, lungs, give me some lungs.
That's a brain right there, dude.
I bought the fucking expensive one, idiot.
Give me a shitty pair of lungs, shitty lungs.
You need to diversify, you're too focused in biotech.
I need, any lungs will do, please.
Any lungs will do.
Ooh, I got it, how would you,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, how would you pay for this?
Oh, oh, oh, I thought it was 1,300, no, no.
Tell it back immediately, I'll buy a cheaper one.
I thought that was way cheaper.
A lung about, okay, I need lungs.
No, you stupid game, it's a great game.
Lungs, I hit E instead of W, it's my own fault.
Need to buy nerve agent.
I need to get rid of all this junk.
How much did I buy this for?
All right, I'm just like, I made money on it.
This is expensive, I'm losing a little bit on here.
People need this shit though, it comes in all the time.
Let's go.
All right, lungs, lungs and a large rock cane.
Good lungs that are over 54.
That brain is cheap and I'm afraid to pull the trigger on it.
Spleens will, the market price plummets
in response to Spleens.
Got it, I didn't even see what it was.
It wasn't good enough.
Can I just buy up all the Spleens?
At least the expensive ones.
All right, I'm out of space.
This thing's a piece of shit, get rid of it.
Lung above 54, didn't I just have one?
I'm just buying up all the Spleens, fuck it.
Never degrades, increases condition of nearby organs.
Are you serious?
Can I move it around?
All right, I'm getting overwhelmed.
Lung above 54.
Ah, brain above 68 and large rock cane.
Okay, brain above 68, no.
Spleens are about to be cheap.
Oh, they just did, they are cheap now.
I bought a bunch of them.
I'm running out of time.
Brain, no.
Lung 79, do I need that?
What?
Yeah, I need that.
Oh, come on.
Okay, good, good, good, good, good, got it.
Nice, hell yeah.
All right, let's get some more requests in here.
Liver under 26.
I need a heart and a pancreas.
I might actually have some of that already, I do.
All right, market.
Get up there.
Am I in my prime yet?
I don't think so.
When is the human skin market gonna open?
I don't know.
We can almost do this one.
All right, so Spleens are cheap as hell right now.
And this increases the quality
of everything around it, right?
Now this does.
How far does that reach?
I feel like this is a good idea.
Nice kidney here.
Got some valuable Spleens.
Buy Spleens stock.
Now that's cooking with gas.
Oh, I almost just tried to buy $32,000 worth.
All right, 10 grand, I'll do 10.
I'm not going all in.
Nerve cluster, all right.
I gotta get rid of these two.
Now, brain over 68 and a large rot cane.
Oh, shit.
Brain over 68.
Brain over 68, cheap too, come on.
Brain over 68, that's, no.
Large rot cane, yeah.
Now I need another rot cane.
Come on, what about my shit here?
They're going up in value.
This is pretty good.
Still need a rot cane.
Rough quality, no thanks.
Rot cane, valuable but terrible condition.
Terrible condition, just terrible.
Awful, these are all such junk.
Terrible, sell low, buy high.
Just awful, just terrible condition.
It's common, just awful.
Ooh, aw.
All right, I need some, anybody want a brain?
I still need rot canes and I need a pancreas.
Rot cane, pancreas and a liver under 36.
Can I just see a pancreas?
Pancreas, dick, come on.
Rot cane, 80 but, okay, that's a return.
That's a return.
I mean, it's a terrible return
No, it's not worth it.
I'll hold.
Here we go.
Of 21% today.
Damn it.
What's this person say?
Hey Jerma, I like to watch your streams
while I run and lift at the gym.
The games are pretty engaging
and your recycled jokes always get me pumped up.
Please play Doki, I'm never gonna play that game.
All right, do I sell the spleen stock?
Just take the return here, the 20%.
Just let it ride and just sell it 600.
Speed, oh my God.
The phantom buyer, legend of the trading community.
Hailing from urgent, origins unknown.
Browses fast and buys faster.
They're a menace.
I'm not gonna pay $8,000.
That's too much.
Shit.
The brain stock because of the market overload.
Not a bad idea.
I don't have enough money.
Pancreas and rot cane, let's go.
Market quakes if you're a large shipment of lungs.
I like need them.
You always need these.
I'm gonna buy the cheap ones.
Just scavenged like a little vulture
and just buy the crappy, cheap, terrible ones.
Yeah, 1,500, 1,600, just junk.
The shard is pretty good.
I think I'm gonna get rid of the spleens.
I have a return on all of them.
Oh, heart, heart, lung.
Ooh, hurry.
I have the shard.
I don't have the lung.
Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
Oh yeah.
Heart, a heart and a pancreas.
Oh, look at me just flooding the market.
Somebody needs that.
And let me read the heart, two hearts.
Heart, heart, pancreas.
Heart, heart, rot cane, pancreas.
Heart, heart, pancreas, pancreas, rot cane.
Heart, pancreas, pancreas, rot cane.
Pancreas, pancreas, rot cane.
Pancreas, rot cane.
Heart, heart, pancreas, pancreas, rot cane.
Heart, wha!
Pancreas, pancreas.
Do I get it?
Oh, hell yeah.
Look at that money flying.
Ooh, shard, brain, shard and brain.
Oh, fuck.
Sorry.
I think I'm gonna get, yeah.
I'm scared about this bottoming out again.
Why won't this move?
Yeah, I'm selling.
I'm selling everything.
I'm just completely cleaning out here.
I need the money.
Remember, you used to be cool.
I need that, listen to me.
Do you hear that?
It was always, it was getting there.
I was trying to make it happen.
I need $40,000 to get the upgrade.
There was nothing in that cup.
You just pretended to drink.
I'm an entertainer.
So I need to, like, if I'm gonna have to pretend
to do stuff to entertain you,
like I pretended to drink.
Yeah, I did.
But I'm an entertainer.
It's my job, right?
I'm gonna pretend to like slurp drinks and stuff
and people think it's funny.
What a theater kid.
Okay, let me, there's a lot of money here on the line.
Brain, shard, pancreas.
Brain, shard, pancreas, bad liver.
Brain, shard, pancreas, bad liver, got it?
Brain, shard, pancreas.
Oh, that was expensive.
Brain, shard, pancreas, liver.
Brain, I need a brain.
Lung, kidney.
I slept on my side yesterday and now my kidney hurts.
Dying.
Oh boy, rot cane.
All right, let's take a look.
Here we go.
I gotta do these like nursery rhymes.
Rot cane, rot cane, kidney.
Kidney, kidney, rot cane.
Lung, brain.
Kidney, kidney, rot, cane, brain.
Rot, cane, brain.
Rot, brain, brain, brain, brain, brain, brain, brain, brain,
brain, brain, brain, brain.
That's all I need.
Now what?
18,000.
I think I can learn them out with four souls
at wholesale prices, my treat.
Four souls.
I'll give you 200 dollars for that liver, shard.
All right, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I need a new rhyme.
Lungs, lung, shard, lip.
Universe-wide strike for better labor conditions.
Organ barges halt mid-delivery.
Huh?
I'm trying to make a song up.
Lung, lung, shard, lung, shard, liver.
Lung, shard, liver, four souls.
Lung, shard, liver, four souls with a brain.
Lung, shard, liver, so.
I got a lot of money.
I would hate to be behind this guy in the grocery store.
Just walking around like,
milk, eggs, butter, peanut butter.
Almonds, Doritos, milk, butter, peanut butter.
I would be like, this guy's fucking crazy.
Toilet paper, toilet paper, paper towels, paper plates.
Milk, eggs, butter, peanut butter.
Oh, yay, yay.
Oh, great commentary.
Coffee, Cheetos, chicken.
I don't think I'd want to do that
because sometimes my grocery list is kind of gross.
Ground beef, dog treats.
You're like, what is this guy making?
Cottage cheese, ground beef, raw chicken, dog treats.
Ugh.
I can afford the new upgrade.
Should have held, should have held it.
It's gonna die, hey, hey.
It's gonna double bottom right here.
Buying this one.
All right, bang.
This is 10 capacity
and no longer nothing corrodes in here anymore.
Oh yeah.
I should probably buy, hold on.
Something else tanked.
What tanked?
Everything.
What tanked the most?
Kendixes?
Oh, the mark is just dumped.
It's all right.
Strike tanked everything.
All right, okay, okay, okay.
Changes surrounding organs in the process.
I have, I need four souls.
That's a lot.
What's this one?
Loaning lab may have been lying to me.
I think they want to own the organ trade.
Send me a shard.
All right, four souls and a shard.
Go.
Soul, I gotta stop taking the ones that are souls.
Looked through my hunting traps
and found a prime nerve cluster 2400.
Sure, I'll take it.
What does it look like?
Ooh, I can already, 3500?
I'll take it.
Thank you.
All right, I need some more.
All right.
Do I already have any of these?
I got this one already.
Here's your soul.
Thanks for the 4000 bucks.
Okay.
Go.
I'll take that one too.
And I'll take that one.
Eye, bad liver.
Eye, bladder, bad liver.
Eye, bladder, bad liver shard.
Eye, bladder.
That's a cheap brain.
Eye, bladder, bad liver shard.
Bladder, bad liver.
Got it.
A lung in five days.
Look at how much money this is.
Eyeball and roctane.
Lungs.
What do you want for here?
You want bladder?
Fuck out of here.
This is worth so much more money.
All right, now let's get a song here.
Release something in my brain I can remember what to do.
Okay, stomach.
Stomach, soul.
Stomach, soul, eyeball, roctane.
Stomach, soul, eyeball, roctane, lungs.
Stomach, soul, eyeball, octane.
Stomach, soul, octane.
I forget it.
Stomach, soul.
Stomach, soul, roctane, eyeball.
Stomach, soul, roctane.
Stomach, soul.
Stomach.
Soul, I need soul.
Pain.
Eyeball.
Stomach.
Okay, got this one.
Got that one.
Stomach, soul.
Stomach?
All right, I have stomach.
Stomach, stomach, stomach, stomach, stomach.
What is this?
All right.
Ooh, I'm too slow.
This brain is, you need to pair them up.
Yeah, I'm doing the song wrong.
You're right.
Hey, thank you, ToastyBro, for the 10 community subs.
Thank you, Flybot for the 15 community subs.
Then we had an anonymous gifter with five community subs.
Thank you.
Somebody just got fucking banned, I think.
I looked over and saw, hey man, first time chatter.
I've been a long time viewer.
I was wondering if you're ever gonna play Among,
and then I saw them get deleted.
I don't know what you did, but apparently you're out of here.
To answer your question, no, I'm never gonna play Among Us
unless it's Among Us VR and I'm gonna play for 10 minutes.
And then I gotta smash my VR with a hammer.
All right, 60,000.
Hey, rovo, thanks for the 16 community subs.
Why'd I say 16?
You gave 10.
Where did that number come from?
I really don't know, I'm serious.
All right, let me see what I have to do.
Lungs.
Stomach, soul.
Lung, lung, stomach, soul.
Lung, lung, stomach, soul, liver.
Lung, lung, stomach, soul, bad liver.
Lung, lung, stomach.
Lung, lung.
No lungs today.
This is bad.
Liver and soul.
Nerve cluster.
Brain.
I need a new song.
What do I have?
I don't even know what these are.
I have kidneys, stomach, I have stomach.
I have a brain.
I have a brain right now.
I need to get rid of something.
All right, shit, I got a minute.
Nerve cluster, nerve, nerve, liver, soul.
Okay, nerve, liver, nerve, liver, soul.
Nerve, liver, soul.
Fuck.
Market rejoices, because he's murdering planets.
Holy shit.
All right, what do I need?
Nerve, liver, soul.
A mythic brain.
Give it to me.
Oh, 22,000.
That guy just, I'm glad I did that quest,
whatever that was.
Nerve cluster, nerve, liver, soul, lung.
Nerve, liver, soul, lung, lung.
Nerve, brain, rock cane.
It's expensive though.
Oh, fuck.
You, I know you want a brain, and I have it right now.
Oh, okay.
No longer broke?
No, not anymore.
Now I can invest a bunch of money into the stock market.
I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, oh, oh, look at that, oh, oh, oh.
It's capped at six, Jerma.
Oh yeah?
Time to cash out.
Hell yeah.
It's 45,000 more dollars.
I got almost 100 ring.
It doesn't cap at six.
Oh, that's huge.
I just had two big things happen there.
Oh man.
Everything is all the way up here.
I gotta wait for it.
This is gonna be a pullback here.
Will I just get the better one,
or do I hold onto the money and invest?
What do you think?
Cause this will give me 14 spaces.
Yeah, if I got the money, I'm gonna use it.
Okay, so what, allow you to carry more cargo,
but leave a precious thin shell between your organs
and the horrors of space increases the organ decay rate.
Okay, that's all right.
What do I have in my cargo?
I've got two livers.
Nobody wants a shitty liver.
I need lungs, lungs, soul, nerve cluster.
Lungs, soul, nerve cluster, let's go.
Here it is, lungs.
Ah, it was expensive, but it's okay.
I'll get another one.
I got money.
Nerve.
I'll get another one.
I need four souls.
Lungs, do I still need lungs?
Nerve cluster and I need, okay.
Boom.
Hell yeah.
I got new organs.
11,000 bucks, are you kidding me?
Oh, I said that if you mix a large shard into the soul,
you'll, it would make them crop.
Oh, a shard?
You got it.
Shard, two shards.
Oh boy, look at this money.
Two shards, lungs, heart, two shards.
I need a song.
Let's get it, let's get a good song here.
Heart, lung, heart, lung, shard, shard, nerve.
Heart, lung, shard, shard, nerve.
Heart, heart, heart, heart, shard.
I don't know what's wrong with my brain.
I forgot the whole thing.
Heart, heart, lung, lung, lung, shard.
Lung, shard, shard, heart.
Lung, shard, shard, heart, nerve.
Let's do it again.
Shard, shard, heart, nerve.
Take a half of it already, here we go.
One of these was done, this one.
This one too.
I have, I got two hearts.
Oh shit, I'm so slow.
Market's still going crazy.
Still at nine, okay.
Are you an organ donor?
I'm an organ trader.
I have to get rid of this, it's been here for too long.
Hearts are really useful though.
If you get a new stock, everything is just way too high.
Look at the market, it's crazy.
I need to wait like another few days.
Everything's going wild.
I need lungs and I need shards.
Lung, shard, lung and two shards
and that's a shitload of money.
Three shards.
You're buying organs from a hunter of flesh cryptids
and the organs are normal?
That's an unlicensed harvester, idiot.
He's hunting people.
I literally have no idea what you just told me.
All right, I need a bunch of shards.
Gotta get them cheap.
That lung is way too high.
Dude, is this, oh my God, look at the heart increase.
Let's go.
All right, shards.
I'm not seeing shards right now.
Shards, lungs, shards, lungs.
Oh man, come on.
Finally, that's just 4,300 bucks.
It better be worth it.
It is.
Soul, I'm gonna buy it because it's cheap.
Shards, I get common, no.
Remember, buy a penis.
I just realized I've been like leaning forward
this whole time.
All right, anybody else need anything that I can get?
What lungs?
I'm so sorry.
They found me.
There's too much money in organs
and they hurt me.
Oh God, I told them about the lab.
Only send a gallbladder if I'm worth saving.
Yeah, well, maybe tomorrow.
I need shards.
I got that lung.
All right, send a gallbladder.
Just saw one.
All right, here, take the gallbladder.
Be saved.
Mutual fabrication.
You asked for something exceptional
and I think I know of a way to deliver.
Send over an average shard when you get a chance.
I've got some cutting to do.
All right.
Oh shit.
Market's still at all time high, come on.
Still have the soul.
This thing is, look at how good this is.
It's a gigantic valuable liver
and it's pretty decent condition.
I gotta lean forward here.
They found me.
Send your credit card if I'm worth saving.
I have money to spend, but I don't wanna use it.
All right.
Average, we need shard.
I just need a bunch of shards.
Big leech lymph and just shards, shards, shards, shards.
Shards, large shard.
I just said, give me shards.
No, shards, they're so valuable.
Come on, soul.
I'm gonna hold onto the souls though.
Like, okay, I do some organ harvesting.
I'm meeting a demand of the marketplace.
I take care of my family.
Don't judge me.
Whatever.
I'm gonna get a bladder too.
This always come up.
Shard.
Just bought, insta-buy any shard I see, no matter what.
He just wanted any shard, right?
That's 11 grand.
Shot.
He's pissed.
Ooh.
Okay, here we go.
Send an average shard when you get a chance.
Is that what I got?
Oh, hell yeah.
7,500 bucks.
Look at the reputation I'm gonna get for this.
You kidding me?
Holy, what'd I do?
Unwrapping the package from Breckridge,
a pale ichor clings to your fingers.
It's a painted canvas, wet to the touch.
And in its muscular pulse,
you recognize the form of Mentor Minter is really the power.
Mentor was dangerous.
He was conniving and brilliant and petty
and eternally striving for goals
he would never allow himself to reach.
He hoped you assumed his best qualities
and avoided his worst ones.
It's no matter now.
You hang Mentor's stylish refurbished remains
on the wall of your office.
Mentor Minter is dead.
His threats die with him.
And if there's anything else you need to learn,
well, he's always around.
What?
Wait, did I just win?
Wait, what just happened?
Did I just lose?
I peeped the horror and died.
I peeped the horror and lost.
I think that's a bad end.
Holy shit, what?
Wow.
So there are endings?
How many endings are in the game, I wonder?
I concluded one of the storylines.
Reputation points, organs touched, request fulfilled,
your organs value.
Okay.
More endings await.
Oh, okay.
So that's one of the endings.
Shit.
Wait, I can just keep...
Oh, wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, wait a minute.
You had a conclusive impact on this universe.
Returning will permanently reverse that outcome.
I kind of want to keep going.
I don't think I want to start over.
Yeah, let's go.
I will lose that ending.
Well, that's all right.
What about the coin game update?
Oh, wait, there was a, what do you mean?
You mean for real?
There was a coin game update and it was real?
Did they add a bunch of stuff?
No, I'm going to keep going.
This game's awesome.
Yeah, I'm keeping going.
This is fun.
I'm not done with this yet.
Market fucking tanked as well.
Perfect.
Wait, no, it didn't.
Where did I leave off?
30, what was the last thing that happened?
Okay, so this is just like kind of the next day.
Yeah, I'm having fun.
Was a holiday update to coin game?
Well, we'll see.
I kind of want to play for a little bit longer.
This game is actually really fun.
This game is really good.
Highly recommend.
I want to like keep buying stuff.
It's just scratching itches in my brain.
All right, I got souls.
I need to, what do I have to fulfill here?
I need that gigantic leech.
I need shard, large shard.
This is not the one I just did, right?
No, I'm dying.
I need a brain, right?
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
What do I need, need, need, need, need, need, need, need?
Lung, lung?
Now we may speak privately.
The dark emperor, Zimforth, has slept for far too long
to breathe life back into this corpse.
Gigantic lungs, lungs, lungs.
Leech length, shards, shards.
I need big lungs, shards.
Leech, I think I can fulfill one, yeah, there you go.
Hell yeah.
All right, I need a large, large shard.
Gigantic lungs, lungs.
Oh, damn it, I don't know what I bought.
Large shard, fuck, what do I have?
Soul, I need a gigantic soul.
Average lungs, I need big, wait, let me get this right.
Got that one already.
Gigantic lungs, gigantic leech, large shard.
No, gimme that, gimme that, I don't even know what it was.
Why are these so expensive?
Oh, because they're mythic, okay.
You are a servant, play coin game.
I will play coin game today.
Just sit back and relax.
That's a good buy.
19,000, what are you talking about?
I need gigantic stuff, who are you?
I think it's time to buy some stocks.
I'm gonna buy stocks in, not stomach.
Something expensive, platter, earworms,
eye-roids, little Joey's heart.
I just bought one, is that a good idea?
I could sell a lot of this right now and make some money.
But I'm gonna hold them.
All right, let's go, I've got shard, bingo.
You need big, all these weird specific shit things,
you know what I mean, large shard.
Large shard, gigantic leech, gigantic lungs, hearts.
No, got it.
Okay, that's the quest.
I'm gonna get a couple more of these.
All right, let's get something going here.
Old little Joey's heart, I will.
Good platter.
What?
I can stop coming around if you want.
I know what I do ain't kind.
Sign this release and you won't see my hide ever again.
No, you gave me a brain that was worth $20,000.
Keep coming back.
All right, heart, I need hearts.
Large hearts, large shit, whatever it was.
Gigantic shard, right?
I don't remember, fuck me.
Large shard, gigantic leech, gigantic lung,
large shard, gigantic leech.
What does the leech even look like?
What does it look like?
Large shard, gigantic leech, too expensive.
I'll buy the stomach though, it's cheap and horrible.
Dude, these are expensive, just start selling them now.
Free up the space.
I gotta do something, I gotta get this out going here.
Leech is 20.
Oh, here it is, okay, okay, I need gigantic leech.
Please, please, please, please, please, please, please.
Large shard, hell yeah, who wanted that?
You did, that's 11 grand, hell yeah.
Dude, little Joey's heart.
Yeah, if you wanna vote,
the end of the year awards are currently available
to vote on, the link right now in the chat.
Go click it, it's 26 categories.
This, by the way, this stream will be on New Year's Eve,
not New Year's Day, still planning on doing that.
So there will be the rumble
and the awards on New Year's Eve.
I'm probably gonna start later in the evening
so I can hit New Year's at least on Eastern time,
because I know that New Year's on Pacific time
is way too late for a lot of people.
So we're going to count down the New Year Eastern time,
like we do every year anyways.
So the stream will probably start,
I'd like to at least go for an hour or two probably
before the New Year.
So I imagine you can expect that stream to start
at maybe seven o'clock, 730 Pacific,
starting somewhere around like 10, 1030 Eastern.
Then we'll be able to go for an hour or two,
say, oh look, happy New Year, we hit the New Year.
And then go for like another hour or two,
just like we did last time.
But let's keep going.
Good bladder, I did a large shard,
gigantic leech, just a lung,
gigantic leech, lung, good bladder.
Yo, got it.
Good bladder, gigantic leech, that's too expensive.
Thank you.
Whoa, I know I'm just an organ harvester
and you're a big old organ trader,
but are we friends, is that what we are?
I don't know what to say to this guy.
Did I say no?
I feel like I have to say yes, sure.
Okay, already I see a dark blush of life flooding
into Zimforth's cheeks,
give him the large eyes he deserves.
Are we building a person?
Okay, large eyes, we're making a person.
All right, let's see what I want.
Cormix, Cormix, nerve, big eyes,
Cormix, nerve, big eyes, Cormix, shit.
You're building a demon?
Jesus, anybody else want anything?
Ladder, lung, just any lung?
Wait, what does it have to be big?
No, just lungs, buy that soul.
Cormix, running out of time, there we go.
Hey guys, these are gigantic, does that matter?
No, they have to be large eyes, okay.
What, I didn't need to eat Cormix.
Tiny eyes, I should have bought that, idiot.
I'm buying the mythic shard, who wanted that?
Oh, I just, that was a bad trade, that's a bad trade.
Yeah, why would I ever sell this to this guy for 3,000?
That's a bad trade, I'm gonna hold this stuff.
Oh shit, nice, I'm up 30% on this shit.
Hey for the funny eyeball man, big eyes.
Let's just keep going, hurry up.
All right, my ADHD is freaking out right now.
I need a Cormix, Cormix, nerve, large eyes, ladder.
Cormix, nerve, large eyes, nope,
Cormix, nerve, large eyes, ladder.
Is it above or below, I don't remember.
Organ barges are again operational, does that mean?
Large eyes, yep, here you go, go make the guy.
Brain, Cormix, gallbladder, casino has been
approved for the harvest, leech limb.
All right, let's do these.
Can I have one of these?
Okay, liver, gallbladder, double E, Cormix.
Liver, gallbladder, double E, Cormix, brain.
Thanks for the fucking 10 grand.
Liver, gallbladder, double E, Cormix.
One of these, forget, how much does this thing worth?
This is kind of depreciating.
All right, I need E-Cormixes immediately.
Hi chat, the dev said your money will transfer
from this game to coin game with a new update.
That was pretty good, that was really good.
No E-Cormixes, this sucks.
Oh, I think these are all E-Cormixes and a nerve cluster.
I think I'm gonna sell Joey's heart, 25%.
That's a lot of money, I don't wanna lose it.
I got this, I hope this appreciates too.
Ain't just surrounding organs in the,
okay, wait, wait, I wanna do this.
Increase the condition, this thing kind of freaks me out.
What about the Cormix stocks?
How are they doing right now?
Dude, this is way too expensive.
We're almost done with this, there's an ooze
trickling from the corpse of our mutual master.
Bring me the best valuable kidney you can find.
Bring me the valuable kidney.
I need another song.
Rot cane, rot cane kidney, rot cane kidney,
double the Cormix, rot cane kidney,
double the Cormix nerve, rot cane kidney,
double the Cormix, rot cane kidney, kidney,
Cormix nerve, that one, that one.
Uh, eyeballs, rot cane, valuable kidney, Cormix.
Come on, valuable kidney, valuable kidney,
valuable kidney, Cormix, where's that other Cormix?
Cormix, what?
Make sure it's small, small Cormix,
rot cane, good kidney.
Oh, shut up, oh, shut up, I just bought so many of these.
What the fuck?
I'm buying them though, oh, that sucks.
I'm losing money on this, get rid of this too.
Small and it's not valuable, whatever, I don't care.
Cormix stock is a great idea right now though.
Oh my goodness gracious, yes, I'm going all in.
I'm not kidding, I'm going all in, $63,000.
Look at all this Cormix bullshit,
increasing condition of nearby organs.
That should be good, I kinda made a face.
So now, I wanna do this quest.
Valuable kidney, of rot canes are just expensive.
Small, okay, valuable kidney, nope, rot cane.
What, are you kidding me?
Shit, rot cane, come on, valuable kidney, somewhere.
Damn it, valuable, got it, heart, okay, I need it.
Heart, heart, rot cane, smaller Cormix.
All right, good, it's a good return.
Hearts, any hearts, let me see, heart, zero, zero is one.
We hold the organ bar, it's a small pancreas shipment
arrives at every port in the vicinity,
sending market prices into a freefall.
Buy, buy, buy, buy, buy it, buy it, buy the whole thing.
Yeah, okay, I need a, I got a smaller Cormix.
Take that, thank you, I need a heart within a few days.
These are all just kinda junk here.
I'm just gonna delete these, what do you got?
A small leech lymph, I need a lung and a liver.
Small leech lymph, lung and a liver.
Lung, it's valuable, no.
All right, all right, I'm just gonna go to tomorrow.
I'm withdrawing, German, please tell a joke,
please tell a joke, I'm withdrawing.
Withdraw, all right, we're good.
Okay, oh, it's gonna go back up here
and it's gonna be $150,000, that's a big, that's big.
I bet you the necromancer guy's gonna be back tomorrow.
I'll probably get another ending here.
After we get another ending,
we're gonna update coin game
and we'll check out the new update.
I wanna play Monster Rancher 2 again though.
In the new year, we'll figure that out.
All right, leech lymph, lung, liver, small leech lymph, heart.
Lung, liver, small leech lymph, heart, heart.
Oh, fuck, I don't have any space.
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
Oh, I'm gonna make a lot of money today.
That, you know what that means, right?
You know what that means.
That means that that stock that I bought is way up.
Where's the necromancer?
Okay, I love this game.
This game is, this is very, very good.
All right, nerve, large nerve cluster.
Large nerve cluster, shard, large nerve shard.
Large nerve shard, lung, liver.
Large, large, I can't even do my own songs anymore.
Large nerve shard, lung.
So I need, okay, it's so hard to find these ones.
I need a lung, I need lung, lung, small leech, heart.
Too expensive.
I bought them on the 15th, that was for 10,000
and I'd be pissed if I did.
New song, 20 seconds.
Lung, lung, lung, liver.
Lung, lung, liver, shard.
Lung, lung, liver, small shard.
Lung, lung, liver, small leech.
Lung, lung, lung, liver, small leech and a heart.
Lung, lung, liver, small leech, heart.
Liver, okay.
Oh, oh my God.
Oh my gosh, I hold.
I kind of have to hold this, right?
Sell half or just sell it all?
Yeah, let's get out.
I got 200 grand, hell yeah.
Oh, hell yeah.
Okay, now what is this?
I could just skip and buy this crazy one.
What's the difference?
15 capacity, slowest decay of all organs by 50%.
Okay, so it's not bad.
18 capacity, okay, so this protects the ship
from hazardous cargo.
26 capacity, oh my God, that goes up high.
Inside is pockmarked by shrapnel.
Anything to create one more pocket
for organs to squish into.
Oh, so it's a ton of supply, but it's awful conditions.
And then there's this one.
Lowest decay of all organs by 80%.
I'm gonna go with this one here, I think.
This one, or maybe not.
This one's 18.
Oh, should I just buy more stocks?
Yeah, fuck it.
Kidney index, I'm looking at.
Large intestine index, kidney index.
Pancreas index looks like it's bouncing back.
Yeah, there was a big flood.
Oh yeah, I'm doing pancreas.
We're going all in.
I have $185,000 in pancreas index.
This is gonna be the big one.
What do we need?
Already got one.
All right, we're looking for leech.
Any size leech, leech soul.
Leech soul, leech soul lungs.
Leech soul.
Leech soul lung lung liver.
Leech, leech soul lung lung liver.
Soul lung lung liver.
Leech, the organ barge, in one day fresh larynx
will flood the ports.
Thank God, I didn't have any of that. I got a rare soul for you compliments of well a friend. Thanks for your business
Hell yeah, what is it?
Was it rare rare soul? Oh
Okay invest in larynx. Oh
That's an insane idea. I
Love it
Alright, what do I have? I need I got leeches
Yeah, I need I need lungs
any lungs will do and
lungs and souls
Come on stop just buying stuff instantly dude, what's the guy buying every single product?
This dude is literally buying every single thing on the menu
You relax dude all bladder take it shit. All right. All right. All right. I got I got money. I got money
I got money. I got money. I got my
Pancras goes up. We're gonna be a trillionaires. Oh
Yes, see now let's play the game here now we buy a shitload of
What with what just crashed something just did it was larynx, right? Oh my god, look at how much this is gonna recover
All right. Do what do I wait till tomorrow? This might drop even more or does it recover?
Larynx is not crashed yet. Oh, it's gonna be that I'm gonna I'm gonna absolutely insane
I'm going to sell every cent that I have of this. I'm going to sell every single cent
I have and put it all in here. I'm gonna wait one day
Anchor is market's gonna go big it already has let's just yeah. Oh, yeah, let's go
I need the room to let's go
Market is open. All right. What do I need? I need
nerves nerves soul
lungs
Nerves so lung lung liver. Oh
Come on. I wanted that nerve you piece of shit
Wanted a heart one of you idiots did I don't remember I'm overwhelmed. I'm overwhelmed. I don't remember
What am I trying to buy? I don't I'm overwhelmed. I didn't do the liver. I think
nerve soul lung lung liver
Nerve soul lung lung liver. That's not bad. That's not bad either
There's that neither is that neither is that I need another lung. I need lungs
Nerves I need some souls. It's too expensive
30 seconds nerve souls
No souls at all, that's mythic definitely buy that shit. I'm out of space here though
I'm gonna hold tomorrow. It's gonna be a big deal. You're doing the coin game. I am I'm gonna play the coin game
I promise I think I gotta go for it now. It's already crashed
Yeah, it's time. I got two hundred and sixty thousand dollars. We're going with that larynx guys. This is a big deal
All in
$160,000 all in on larynx as it's coming back up to seven grand and then I'm way I win the game
I'm gonna see now. I have the phone. I got to maybe sell some of this crap
Tell the shard
Tell this I don't know. You know why I bought some of this stuff. I need the liver
Hearts, I just bought I'll sell the leeches
Yeah, I don't need them keep the eyeball. All right, let's go
I gotta get rid of this shit small leech limp. I can't find them nerves Lee small
Oh
my god
Come on
This is a good opportunity though. I knew small leech limp small leech limp to small leech limps
Small small small small
Small small got it. That's a big return
La wait a minute. I have another an ending here. Whatever it takes
The lab is gone, but I can modify a song valve and a mythic wrought cane with tech. I managed to salvage
I'll fill the damn sky with meat
Okay, I get that one. I'll take this one too. That's the necromancer one
Cool, what on earth am I trying to buy here? All right, we need and a Cormac's we have none of the lead
Anybody need leeches? I need a stomach and a small intestine stomach small intestine. Just mark. It's just flooded
Eminence, what is this?
Got a P again
Watchers skip the video. Hey, how about you tell you know, I'm not even gonna I'm not even gonna engage with you
I'm not even gonna engage with you
I'm gonna take the high ground. I'm taking the high ground on this one natural remedies. All right
I definitely want to at least do this one mythic wrought cane a song valve
Okay, mythic wrought cane. All right. How's my how's my how's my trading doing? We're okay
Maybe I'll get a mythic wrought cane
Remember you're gonna send Bitcoin assassins to eliminate to know none of these people. What are you talking?
Vaude watchers, don't forget to drink lots of water
That's true. You should listen to them. All right. I definitely want to do this one stomach small intestine. Let's go market truck
Anybody need these?
Or mix no wrought cane. No, nobody wants a soul
Nobody wants any of this stuff. I'm gonna I guess I'm gonna buy some of it
Mythic B plus I don't have enough space. I got all these hearts though. I'm gonna sell that I'm gonna keep the wrought cane
It's not even mythic and it just hurts everything. What am I thinking?
All right, souls are flooding the market. Let's just buy a bunch of them
Mythic I'm gonna spend money here. All right, I don't have it. I can't I have no money. Oops. You have a pea bucket
Small intestines. All right. Nice. I need a small intestine. Ooh
Wait stomach in a small intestine gets me the necromancer stomach. I need a small intestine
Tell me you see a mythic wrought cane
common
Bunch of bullshit not mythic bunch of bullshit. You don't there's no mythic wrought cane. You don't see shit
What would you think Hulk Hogan was a conjoined twin, but it was an active wrestler. I don't know
What are you talking about? What are you talking about? Oh, I need that
Give me a stomach now. No, none of these are stomachs and it's making me very upset still going. We're good cat is bored
So open up go get your switch and open up Mario fucking sunshine remastered and play the whole thing. I'm busy
Play the coin game. I'm
Yeah, excuse me
All right, emote only emote only for four hours. Look what you've done. Look what you've done
Emote only for four hours. Look what you've done. I didn't want to have to do this
Emote only for four hours. All right, let's go. Okay. No, no, no, I don't want these intestines. I want stomachs
I can't buy anything else
Shit
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm again coming. I think got it. Nice. All right, fill the necromancer. Oh, I can't wait
I think we're gonna be a final quest is tomorrow. I think me the mythic wrought cane as well if you can find one
Now I need a song valve, but the hell is a song valve, this is just gonna rot
Everything what the hell is that? Well, what is that? What is that? Oh my god, I can see an ending
I'm going for it. The lab is gone, but I can modify song valve and mythic wrought cane when I I'll fill the damn sky with meat
I want to see it. The guy that we've been giving the first meteor strike was greeted with joy
desperate and decadent alike saw cause for celebration
free organs new opportunities
Organs for everyone a place put in pogchamp only mode where they can only write pogchamp. Oh, they have to leave then the second meteor
struck and the third
Thank you. Appreciate it. The people that are writing like resident sleeper and other emotes. They're just they're hacking the website
It's a kind of it's ridiculous that we have that many people that are like the computer hackers. It's kind of annoying
Okay, everywhere is the smell of meat
Everywhere the stink of flesh
Buried body wait, I just kill everybody avenues of escape are the new normal. I just killed everybody
galaxies of children who cannot understand that there are colors that are not red
We finally have enough organs for everyone we're choking on them Jesus this game is really fun. I like this game a lot
Alright, let me download coin game. I said by the way, I said download not play. This game is awesome space organ trading simulator
Space warlord trading simulator space warlord organ trading simulator. There we go. I got I wonder what the worst ending is
I could play a little more but it's been four hours if I'm gonna give coin game an hour or two
Then this is probably the time to do it. All right, wake up. Wake up children. Wake up children
Okay, give me a sec. Actually, this is a good probably a good place to go pee and I will play a coin game the new update
What do they add? I guess we'll find out we're back