Is that... is that Freddy Rodriguez? That's Freddy Rodriguez! What the hell is going on?
Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa easy. That's dangerous. Oh shit, he's gonna hatch it. He's gonna hatch it.
Suplex.
That was... that was awesome. I ain't gonna lie. You can't deny that suplexing somebody off a
motorcycle isn't pretty damn cool, okay? Just get these guys out of the way. Get out of my face.
A couple more pieces of health. Nice. Whoa, there's another one up here. If I can get through one a
minute, then I should be fine. Did you see that burger? That was a ridiculous looking burger on
that billboard. It was like six patties on that hamburger. That was insane. Now I want a hamburger.
Great. What the fuck just happened? What? I don't know what... I don't know what happened.
The thing just freaked out and flew off the cliff. Move, move, move, move. I only have 54 seconds.
I only have 54 seconds. Get me up there. Come on. Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
It did it again. It didn't... why is it doing that? Why is it doing that?
What? I'm gonna fail the mission. No, no, I'm back. He's back. You see that? He just teleported from
the right side of the screen. Wow, that was really stupid. I hope you guys got to see that.
That was unbelievable. Thank God, dude. That was ridiculous. Speaking of ridiculous,
the car just got sucked up by a spaceship. They put a tractor beam on that fucking thing.
I got an F. Fuck you with the F. Maybe if your stupid trucks weren't driving off the side of the
road, I wouldn't have to restart the thing three or four goddamn times. You wanna talk about a quick
time? You wanna talk about a quick time? You wanna talk about quick time? Press A, quick time. Press
B, looking for the quick time. Come out at your quick time. Helicopter, don't worry, quick time.
Gonna turn right, looking for the quick time. I ain't seeing more, right? Quick time. Helicopter,
quick time. Come back, quick time. What you wanna do? Wanna go, quick time. Wanna find a way,
do some quick time. Ain't no other way for that quick time. Coming at you, quick time.
Oh, road rash. Whoa. What the hell? Oh, damn. Are we really watching this?
Coming soon to theaters. Cars 3, colon. Motorcycles, a love story. Rated X.
Dude, this guy is just on a rampage right now. Are you serious? What a dick. These innocent people
did nothing wrong and you just caused like a seven car pileup. Just for what? Because you're mad at
her for like being like too pretty or something? Like what's your problem? And now you just blew
up a perfectly good oil tanker. That company's gonna lose out on thousands of dollars.
I know this trick. What, you think I'm stupid? You don't think I've never seen
homing missiles shot at me before? Your buddies have been doing this all game
and look what happened. All your secret agent buddies have been shooting homing,
slow homing missiles at me and look where it got them. You probably should have taken a note
about that before you came after Marie. Marie. You probably should have taken a note before you
came after Marie. Oh, I'm on fire mode. On fire mode. Ooh, counter attack. Hello, sweetheart.
What's going on, Master Chief? You're in the wrong game, Master Chief. Don't you know you
can't fuck with the Batmobile game thing with the flaming wheels from Disney Pixar?
Master Chief and your buddy Boba Fett Chief, you're all a bunch of fucking clowns.
Halo 5 ain't even coming out this year. Haven't you read the fucking news?
Halo 5 ain't gonna be out for like another 10 years. We got the Power Rangers behind us.
We got, who's the Red Power Ranger? Tommy? And the Green Ranger? No, the Green Ranger was Tommy.
And the Red was, what was the Red Power Ranger's name? I don't remember. Henry? All right, well
Henry's dead. Tommy, well, all the Tommy clones are dead now. Hopefully they don't morph into like
Pterodactyls and T-Rexes and shit. One Power Ranger had a terrible, terrible transformation.
Do you remember in the Power Rangers movie, the one Power Ranger that had the frog
and he was pissed? I'd be pissed too. If my power, you know, T-Rex, Pterodactyl, Tiger, Lion, Frog.
Yeah, that would suck. I want to be the Tiger. I don't want to be a frog. What am I talking about?