This is gonna sound weird. Do you ever sit down in your chair, or in your car, and you know nothing has been changed?
You know that you haven't moved the seat, you know that you haven't changed where the wheel is, or where your mouse is, or where your armrests are.
But it doesn't feel correct. It feels like somebody changed everything about this seat, and this has been the same way for probably eight and a half months.
It's freaking me out. Well, it feels like the armrests are too high. I didn't do anything. It's weird.
Maybe I should go up a little? I'm gonna go up. Let's see if this helps.
And now when you adjust to try to get it the way that you want it, the way that you remember it, you'll never get it the same way again.
It's getting shorter. No, I'm saying, like, I need to be up higher. Doesn't matter how long your legs are.
Guys, everybody that goes and gets their hair cut, they pump, pump, pump, pump, they pump you up in that chair. You could be six-five.
Don't matter. Anyways, welcome, everybody. Welcome back. Time to get scared.
It is going to be a continuation of Darkwood for as long as I can tolerate it, I guess.
Should be fun. I'm enjoying it so far. That might change over the next five to seven hours. I don't know.
He's just tolerating it. He's tolerating. Tolerating implies you don't like doing it.
Well, I'm talking about scariness and stress. It's not that I'm tolerating the game.
I'm tolerating what happens when you play a game like this. You get stressed. You get jumpy.
It's not too scary. So tolerating the game. No, the game is good. It's just, all right, if somebody screams in your face,
there's only so many times somebody can scream in your face before you're like, all right, I can't do that anymore.
That person could be an amazing juggler, and they're doing an incredible juggling, and it's the best juggling act you've ever seen.
But every four or five minutes, they just lean over and they scream directly in your face.
You're going to be like, this is great juggling act, but he screams a lot, doesn't he?
Anyways, hopefully this, I have to turn my webcam on. How do I turn off the whole stream?
Because I think I was not, I didn't have any clothes on when I was doing this last.
So, and sometimes this webcam takes a frame of the last thing that I did before I turn off the cam on OBS.
So there's, I have no shirt on for this, and I'm certain of it. So I need to like turn it on without you seeing.
How do I, I think I can do it like this. I think, I hope this works. Please work.
Don't like come up and hold on, I need to see where this is. All right, I almost just did it. Thank God I moved it.
Okay, so now this should be fine because I've just turned it on and turned it off like twice.
Don't be fucking naked. Don't be naked. Don't be naked. Don't be naked. Don't be naked.
Yes, we're good. We're good. I look a little tired today. It's because I had a bad dream last night.
And anytime you have a bad dream, it's like you hadn't slept at all.
All right. Let's see, make sure that's all set. It's a story time. No, this is not a story time dream.
This is just scary and horrible. It's like somebody broke into the house and I was like, like hiding around a corner.
And they were like going through everything and breaking stuff and trying to attack everybody.
And I'm just like, what the fuck do I do? What the fuck do I do? And I grabbed, this is gonna sound crazy.
I don't know why this was here, but I grabbed a music stand, a music stand.
But the thing that you put the, you know, like the notes on, I don't know why that was in my house.
And I had this music stand. I was like, I'm gonna fucking bash this guy's head in. And then I woke up.
I mean, it was just terrifying because I'm playing this. Guys, this is why I don't play. I'm playing a scary game.
That's why I had this dream. Okay. It makes sense. But that was the only thing that was around.
It was, that was it. I had to use it. It's the game. All right. Let's go.
If you don't know, this is obviously Starkwood. Played about six hours of it last night.
You got to be careful when coffee is filled to the brim. And I did it this time. It was me.
I talked a lot of shit about this and I did it. But here's the difference though. It's open.
It's different when you do it to yourself. You know what I mean? When somebody else does it, you can slide it.
All right. Let's go. Is the webcam too big? I don't know. I spilled on my shirt. No, I didn't.
We're on day 11. All right. I got to get ready. I can stall as long as I want.
I don't know why I'm doing this. It's because I know it's about to happen. I have to like concentrate and it's like, it's hard.
Somebody just said to go to the spa. All right. I'm ready. Nice hair.
I know. Everyone talks about my hair. One day I'll have the best hair on Twitch and then nobody will be able to make fun of me ever again.
All right. Let's go. This is a 758 chapter one day 11 difficulty. Pretty hard.
Why did I? I just saw the only thing that was a color and I just almost clicked it. All right. Both headphones going in. I'm going in.
You're playing a challenging and unforgiving game. You will not be led by the hand. Respect the woods. Be patient and focus.
Yeah, I'm going in. This is two headphones. Horror movies have two headphones. It's called normal.
No, but it's not, though, because the game told me that it was very hard to begin with.
So it's already already on hard. The other two difficulties are just harder and hardest. Hard, harder, hardest.
All right. That's good. So we got to the second shelter. Lost. Oh, I died in here. Right. That's the last thing that happened.
Somebody told me to put the bathtub up in the corner. It turned out to be incredibly incorrect.
Where's my backpack? There it is. All right. So now I've got time. What I was going to do today.
Those of you have no idea what this game is. This is Darkwood. It's a game about surviving in a haunted, scary forest.
And you have to go to different hideouts. And I'm at hideout two. And it's scary and it's hard. It's a very hard game.
So you're going to see me probably lose a few times, but it's because it's hard, not because I'm bad at the game.
You know, when you even go to a toy store and there's those things that, you know, I have to I have to annoy everybody as soon as possible.
That's what I have to do on this stream. All right. So the time is frozen right now so I can. Where's the. That's good.
He's just doing the same stream. No, it's callback. All right. I got a lockpick. I have to rearrange this.
I hate this already. What did I do? Gas on the bottom.
Graph from the bottom. Oh, this is so annoying.
What a mess. And there was wood was up here.
Torch is technically made out of wood, but it's going to go my inventory. Shiny stone is technically a metal.
Technically. Well, it's kind of a metal. Wood is going to go here.
Wooden rocks will go here.
There it is. All right. Wood. Wood. Consumables. Recycling will go this way.
Yeah, this is like recycling and just shit that is like miscellaneous.
Drugs and alcohol go up on top of here and only have three stacks.
He's still streaming this. Yeah, I haven't stopped since yesterday. That's why I look a little tired.
I'm just so into it. I'm like looking addicted to it. It's just real fun. I haven't stopped.
And I didn't put that emote. The German sour emote wasn't there at stream start yesterday.
So here you are. I've only got like another six hours of this shit before. It's over 24 hours.
All right. Weapons are going to go up top. This is technically wood.
I don't know why that wasn't just part of the stack in the first place. All right. So drugs, alcohol, fire, drugs.
OK, now keep that together. Shovel is going to go.
OK, fan belt is just miscellaneous, but I don't know.
Guns, weapons are going to go up top because that's obviously important, right?
Still, I need to be able to make that. The small caliber magazine is for the gun.
Craft a shovel. Oh, I need tape and I can do this right now. Tape.
All right. Does this guy have tape? You got tape, right?
Well, how much money do I have? He's got tape. This is awesome. All right. I can actually make the shovel.
I do need to upgrade my workshop to craft this. What are you talking about?
I need to upgrade my work to what? Why? I need to upgrade my workshop.
I need to know. Didn't I just do this? I need another toolbox.
OK, well, shovel materials are going up here. I need the stick.
This will eventually make shovel. I need five toolboxes. That would be horrible if that were true.
Torch. I got to prepare this. Do I have enough? I need five needles.
It's like you pay for a service, right? I paid for the guy who was supposed to deliver my shit here.
And he just threw it on a bag. I had it all alphabetical order.
And he just threw it on the bag and just dropped it in front of my house because I have to do this again now.
All right. Fan belt is probably going to be miscellaneous.
Tire would be miscellaneous. Battery electronics go up here.
All right. This is OK. Shiny stone is not electronics. I'm just going to sell it.
This is miscellaneous to the wood. All right. This looks all right. I'm OK with this.
Weapons, fire, consumables, like the tire. I could put that up there, too.
This is all right. Now, I need to board up a bunch of these windows.
That was what I was going to do last time before extreme fatigue put in after playing this game for six hours.
Now that I'm fresh, I'm awoken. Almost just spilled the coffee completely off my lap.
We're organized. Is my first time playing Darkwood? Yes.
I started it yesterday. It's the second time I've ever technically sat down to play it.
All right, let's go. I need some needles. I have how many traps do I have? Bear trap.
How many windows do we got? What does it take? I need three wood and seven needles.
I'm going to have to go back on a wood hunt. Where's that thing? I can do this. I got some wood here.
How many is this going to make? Wait and get the needles first before he leaves.
How many does he have? Nail. I just got to get a bunch of them. I have to do this. I need it.
Just give me all of them. He's late. I've been streaming for 15 minutes. He's late.
All right. This generator is still on. No, it's not. It is.
God damn it. Let's make some planks. So I got like 20 of these now.
Still frozen time. That's good. All right. I need to get all these boarded up.
But I need to repair this. All right. Let me think about this for a second.
Now, don't build a bathtub. So this is I can't do anything about this.
So they're always going to get into here, right? So if they're always going to get into there,
that means I have to take care of I have to get one spot that I know I'm going to stay in.
Where are the lamps? Build. I'm not building a bathtub.
OK, there's a window. This looks all right. I don't mind this spot.
But then I have to deal with this. What about the bedroom?
This is all right, too. But there's two entry ways. And then there's in this room.
And there's only. Yeah. OK. This is the room right here.
This one. Let's go for it. All right. That's boarded up.
I can go around here, board this one up, too.
I will have two rooms to play with here because then I just have to worry about the up up top here.
Oh, there's bread in here. Nice. Because I could care less if they get in up here.
I just don't want to get in here or here. That means you trap it up.
Let's drag this table. I came prepared today, guys.
You thought I was going to be a clown today. No, not today.
It was that why even drag the table?
This is so much easier to do that like this.
Just push it. All right. So that will block off.
Will it block this whole thing? It will not.
So I need to be aware of that. We've got to have table here.
There's a sofa. Let's move the sofa. I'm thinking maybe a bathtub.
Because then this is good. I'm thinking bathtub right back here, too.
All right. Let's make a bathtub. I'm not going to say it.
I just wanted there to be a mess over here. How am I going to get in?
I will have it so I can move it in a particular way, very, very small, like a puzzle.
So if you see a puzzle for the first time, you don't know the solution to the puzzle.
But if you made the puzzle, if you created the puzzle, you just turn that table 14 degrees clockwise.
And I get in. I am the puzzle maker, not the puzzle taker.
So for instance, it could just be as simple as drag this up like this.
Done. Puzzle's complete. And then I make it through here.
And then I just pull it back down. I don't know. Something like that.
All right. I got two boarded windows. I need my traps.
How many do I have? Zero. I need to make them.
I need to get a door. I can't. How do you mean? I can't make it.
Can you make a door? Can I take the door off from here?
I'll barricade this door. I need more needles. What?
All right. This also has to come into the other room.
I got to get this in here. This is where I'm going to get ready.
If the time is frozen right now. So I got all as much time as I need.
We're going to do this the way that I should have done it in the first place.
And that's just walk into it. I don't, you know, it doesn't need to.
I can, I can do the puzzle maker after it's pulled through.
I got to get this set up. It's important. If I could survive a night here.
And that's the plan. Boarded windows, put traps along.
I'm going to put traps here too. I'll be ready.
There's one lamp. Where's the other ones? There's one in here. That's fine.
Get it away from the windows though. I remember that message from last night.
That's get this away from the windows because the light will shine through.
So we're not going to put it near the windows. Okay. This is new.
We're going to put this in the corner. I need a good lamp placement.
So it doesn't shine completely through these windows.
I'm going to say this corner up here and I'll block it with a sofa.
Sounds good. Right there should be all right. I got one there.
I got one here, maybe a little bit into this.
Maybe up here a little. Still shining through a little bit.
I think it's all right. What about the?
I think that's fine. That should be okay.
Two lamps and a bathtub. They have no chance.
I also have this too. Can I move this?
I can't drag the table. Whatever.
All right. I need to make traps. I need more nails, which I don't have.
All right. Where do I get nails?
No, don't repair the doorway. Where do you get nails?
At the hardware store. I'm talking about. Yeah. Okay.
I have six.
I bought the whole store worth of nails.
Really should repair the door. I need another nail. I don't have any.
I have to just kind of explore and look for some nails.
And wood too, because I'm out of that.
Or am I? That was kind of a waste of money, but it's okay.
I need to repair my board.
Game is quiet.
Oh, shit. Hold on. I'll fix that.
Game's quiet.
All right. Still haven't spent any time.
I need to repair this.
I should have enough, right? I do. All right.
Crude weapon. I've got some gasoline that I'm going to just store.
I don't need it right now.
Get rid of these boards.
I mean, I'll keep the bread on me. I'll keep the torch on me.
I could sell the scrap metal. I could sell the shiny stone.
Yeah, let's do that. Might as well. I heard something.
If you take too long, does like the bubble bobble ghost
come and get you if you take too long here?
Can somebody confirm that with me, please? No. Yes.
All right. Well, I think I'm fine.
All right. Time to go look for wood. I am in the silent forest.
So might as well look for wood. I have to get wood and nails
or I'm guaranteed to lose.
If I go off on a tangent here, stop talking about keyboards.
If I bring up the dream I had last night, I want you to
spam Jerma Sauer in the chat
because I cannot mess around tonight.
I have to go do this right now.
Do not let me talk about anything else besides
did I collect wood or did I collect nails?
All right. I'm going to go up to the camp
because there was still stuff up there that I needed to get and
I'll pick bread. All right. OK.
I don't need this gasoline here. It's wasting inventory space.
How do you do Jerma Sauer? You got to be a subscriber to the channel.
Tier one. And then you do Jerma
lowercase and then uppercase S and then lowercase
hour. But switch the O and the U.
So it's your. But if you say, you know what I mean, you figure it out.
All right. What was I doing? Gasoline.
I got plenty of gas. This is fine. All right. I'm ready.
Wait. I also need a bunch of scrap metal too
because I make a shitload of these. All right. I'm ready. Let's go up to the camp.
I got my board. I remember how to play.
Maybe that's
kind of it. I don't think that's actually true.
And we found wood automatically right up here. Oh, my
God. Thank goodness.
Only one pile. Come on. Make it easy
for me. It took me 40 minutes when I played
yesterday to figure out where the hell this stuff was in the first place.
That's so dark. 8 a.m.
All right. This camp had some stuff. Yeah. There's some rocks
here. I remember I was freaking out. Everyone was telling
me, just go, just go. You can come back. You can come back so I can come back. I'm fine.
Stick here. I might just turn around
immediately and just dump the stuff back in the stash.
Oh, nice. Absolutely beautiful.
Someone's walking around. All right. I'm going to let's
deposit it right now. Oh, OK.
It's just a it's a rock throw. That's a throw. The guy throws rocks.
Come on. Throw a rock. Throw.
That was a pretty good dodge, she asked me.
Wait, he doesn't wait. What? I thought he just threw rocks.
I just got baited.
I thought he just threw rocks. OK, I get a deposit.
It's only been one hour. This is good.
This is my house. Yeah, right. It is.
All right. Get rid of this stuff right now. So we got a
rocks, staff, bottle, rag.
I don't have any healing potions.
I don't have any healing potion drenched gauze.
Meat, match, wire. OK.
I need to make some bandages because I don't have any.
I have two of the big ones, but I'm not going to use those.
That would be a mistake. Take your shirt off.
I unironically banned that person for five minutes.
How do you unironically ban somebody?
Don't you just ban somebody? All right, hold on.
I just want to have bandages with me.
Yes, we're good. I'll keep the bread, too. All right, back out.
Nails. Deposit the nails just in case I die. Nails.
What if I lose? All right.
And this thing's almost broken. All right, back out.
I'm going to explore to the left because there's a wolf's camp.
Piotrek's house is over this way, and there's probably lots of wood and stuff to collect.
Fucking battery in here. The heck.
OK, I also have a gun. I need to get to...
Remember, if you see a toolbox, spam JermaToolbox in the chat.
That's my new emote. Guy right there.
I take it. Of course I do.
I couldn't see it. There he is.
All right. All right. Is he throwing rocks or what?
Is this a rock person? I can't tell.
I think it's a rock person. Yep. I stepped in the poison mushrooms.
Again. Oh, my.
They blend in really well here.
They blend in so well. This is bad.
Silo. Plague doctor here?
I've said it before and I'll say it again. There are only two people
that listen to classical music like this.
That's the dentist and serial killers.
No, I can't turn this off because it's going to be like,
who turned off my gramophone?
I'll endure it for now.
That's what happens when you do stuff like this.
There's a bed over here.
Oh, shit. OK, hold on.
There's a chest. Something good. Something really good.
Dead rat. Why would I have... That's the first time I've seen that.
Dead rat? Check the other side.
All right. I'm going to do it. I guess it's just playing.
I can't turn it off. OK, maybe I'll come back here later.
Wood and sticks.
Nothing else. Right?
Wood and nails. Nothing else. Wood and nails.
All right. Come on. Break it.
Wood and nails. Wood and nails.
I'm supposed to be getting wood and nails. What am I breaking?
Break what? What am I breaking?
Smash it. Smash the gramophone.
You guys are supposed to keep me on the wood and nails only run.
Nowhere it has gone by.
I can only hit something like two or three more times before this is broken.
Keep that in mind. What's this? Corp?
Chicken head. Bear trap. Nice.
Alcohol and a bottle. I'm out of room.
I might have to go back, but I need nails.
Bad. Really badly.
Can I burn this? Damn it.
I have to go back at like 15 and figure out...
There's a tank. He's got me nails in here.
Right? No, this is the silo.
How many are there? Can I throw a bottle at his head?
Wait a minute. I just did.
Oh, this is not good. There's something over here though.
Whoa!
Kill him. Kill him. You do it. You do it.
Get him. Help me, please.
Kill that guy.
Please. All right. One's dead.
I'm trying to line it up. Good.
Okay. Now I gotta go.
I gotta go. I gotta go. I gotta go. I gotta go.
Tank wreck. A wreck of a World War II tank.
That's it? Knife. Don't put the watch away.
Gasoline. Don't need it. Fabric.
Throw away the stones. I don't care. It's fabric.
Battery. Gasoline.
Take the battery. And then...
Get rid of the rag. No. Just make something.
Throw away the dead rats. Do I need them?
Sure I don't need them. Keep them.
It's a dead rat. I know, but what if I need them?
There might be some recipe. I don't need the gasoline. I'm fine.
Okay, I have a knife now. But, okay, where is that beast?
I gotta look at what you have on you. Just a stick. Who cares?
I want that alcohol.
I can take it. Okay. Hold on.
Rag. Stick. Who cares?
I need to go back.
No, where's the wolf? I gotta go to wolf camp.
And buy nails.
No, that's far. How far away is that?
That might be too far away.
16. I need enough time to get back. I'm gonna go for it.
Okay, I have to leave.
I have to leave. I have to leave right now.
Bear traps in this game is like dig... You cannot run in a straight line in this game.
It's like digging down in Minecraft.
I have to go back. I have to deal with it.
I need a pile of wood. I need nails.
I might be able to survive. It's possible.
I just have to really get boarded up and get ready and stab somebody with a knife.
Let me see what I can do here.
Boarded. This is open, but it's okay. They're gonna come through here anyways.
Alright, let me deposit the mushrooms. I still have about...
I have two hours or so to figure this out.
So we've got 40 essence. 40 essence. Nice.
Not bad.
Okay, here we go. Battery.
I still have wood. Chicken head.
Scrap metal. Dead rats. Bear trap. I need that one.
Fabric. Keep the bandages. Actually... No!
Wait, I don't have a well here.
Okay, cool. Lantern.
Should I do this?
Inventory upgrade.
I know I'm doing that one.
Now I want to do bear trap.
I don't have any bookies. Stop. Bear trap. Bear trap.
I want four bear traps. Make advantage.
I still have alcohol. Store it.
Get rid of the wood too. Alright, now I can do this later.
Prepare this.
To me, use this as a melee weapon of throne.
I'm gonna have to just use the knife and get rid of the bottles.
Okay, set these up. Cook the rats.
Cook the rats? Are you serious?
Alright, chicken head rats.
You guys want me to throw those away?
Wow, imagine if I threw those away? How much of a mistake that would be?
Holy god.
I think that's enough. I have a bandage.
Stand next to electricity light.
I'm gonna go for it. Okay, let's do it.
So, I need to turn the generator on. Now.
Generator on. Boink.
Get back over here. This is where we have to figure this out.
Alright, now I need to survive in these two rooms.
Bear trap. Right here.
Okay. Bear trap here, bear trap there.
Good. Alright. In here too?
I need... Why is this wall glowing?
Okay, bear trap here.
You know what? No, no, no. Bear trap.
I don't know. It's gonna have to be like right here.
Yeah, I have to hang out in this room. There's gonna be a bear trap here.
First of all... Ah, I'm running out of time, running out of time. There's no more time left.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Get the bathtub in the... Hurry up. Drag the table.
No, not long ways. I have 30 minutes.
Light. This is a light source. Why am I not being healed?
This is an electricity light source? What? Why?
This is in case somebody gets in here. This is in case somebody gets in this way.
They're boarded though. A little bit of light's bleeding through, but I think it's okay.
They're in the house right now. Okay.
He's in the house. He's in the house right now.
He didn't get... Step on the trap. Don't...
Why is he not getting stuck on the traps?
He's avoiding all of them.
Wait, what? My knife. Huh? Heal.
The trap was underneath the sofa.
Oh, fuck. He's coming in.
Give me the scrap. I don't know what to do. He didn't even step on any of them.
I'm just gonna go like this and just put weight here so he can't open it.
You know what I mean? Like he can't push me over.
They're gonna turn the light off. Wait, are they gonna get doubled?
Are they gonna get doubled? Don't turn the lights off. Both of them.
Nah, I can't take a sip of my coffee yet.
Something else has to go here. That says to be traps.
Furniture is useless. 6 AM. Come on.
God. Oh, God damn it.
Give me a torch. Get out of here.
Back! Press Q to use moth.
Oh. Furniture is absolutely useless.
Get rid of all of this and we're gonna do like three traps here.
They just walk into the traps. Can I pick these up?
This arm. I'm gonna leave them there though.
These are okay. I actually don't mind these where they are. I don't have to go in this room for any reason.
I'm fine.
That was a stress gas that came up.
Okay. Search this already. Let's go back.
Nails. You got nails for me. Yes, you do. I know you do.
But do I want them? I mean, yes, I kind of do.
I kind of need them. Give me all of them.
All these. I'll take the mushroom too.
You know what? No, that's a waste.
Gotta go find one.
And I've already got tape for the shovel, but I need the toolbox.
I need to go back to the wolf. I'm gonna refill everything.
Okay. Let's check this out now.
Now that I have a minute. I might come back and buy the scrap too.
Because I need it for the traps. In fact, I'm just gonna get it now.
Because I know I'm gonna need it.
Let us do a fun little thing here called.
Board up the remaining windows.
Or repair door. You know, this is not a bad idea.
But first.
The furniture is stupid.
I don't even know why I have a bathtub.
It doesn't do anything for me.
Bathtub just gets in the way. And I wasted stuff on this.
Alright. Chair can go over here.
So I got one in front of the window. I want one, two, three here.
Can I make them? I think so.
Back to the workshop for a second.
I don't have anything to cook. No. I almost have another level up though.
Alright. Bear trap. Three, six, nine, twelve.
I can make four of these. One, two, three, four.
Turn off the generator. Thank you.
Thank you for reminding me about the generator.
Appreciate it.
There's a hole in that wall. I can repair that.
I can reinforce this door.
Wooden door. No.
I can't. But only one trap has to go here.
Check this out. Yeah. Okay.
There's only one point of entry here. I'm gonna try it.
Whatever. If it's wrong, it's wrong. If it's wrong, it's wrong.
It's smaller. It's less places to get in.
I'm gonna dismantle all the stuff that I've done.
Now it's too late. I already have this set up.
Now this is alright. It really is just this one point of entry right here.
And that, potentially. Whatever that is.
Why is this counting up? 46, 40. What are you doing?
If I dismantle this trap, can I pick it up?
Or does it turn into scrap? I need to find out. I need to learn on my own.
It's alright. But is it the same amount of scrap?
I need to learn on my own. I have to make mistakes.
Two scrap metal. What does it cost to make one? Two or three.
It's half of what it is. Alright, so I'm gonna...
Shit. Okay, that's fine. Whatever. Don't worry.
I gotta make my mistakes. Let's see how this plays out.
In here. Got this one spot.
The barricade.
I don't have any... How do I not have any logs?
What the hell are you talking about? Why? What are you guys doing?
Why are you guys counting up? Why? What's with the counting?
What happened? I don't understand why this is happening.
Alright, wood. Wooden planks.
Wooden planks.
Any more wooden planks in here?
I'm gonna take the gasoline and dump it.
I'm gonna make another bear trap.
Alright, one, two, three, five bear traps.
I can make another weapon. No, why would I do that?
Make a bandage again? Okay.
Got two lockpicks. Pretty sick.
I got a mushroom. Let's deposit that.
You guys aren't gonna make me put this in subscriber only mode, are you?
It'll get worse.
Don't make me use that power.
Okay, wait, you have a mushroom for sale, don't you? What if I'm lazy?
I'm lazy. Let's level up.
Okay. My...
My blood will hurt enemies.
Once a day for about a minute, I will be able to see all around me.
Once a day, I'll be able to run for a short amount of time without losing stamina.
My vulnerability to poison increases.
My sight will get worse for a short amount of time when I receive damage.
That's not good. This is also not good.
Because I step in these every time.
I don't know what's the right call here. I kinda like this.
When I take damage, I don't know what that means.
I step in poison mushrooms every time they're around.
So I don't know how much worse that's gonna be.
Runner is really good.
Does that just randomly happen?
So randomly, it turns on a super power.
If I can activate that, that's really good.
I like that, because then I can just sprint away from anything.
Yeah, that's this one.
Just don't step in the poison mushrooms, Jeremy. Seriously.
Just don't.
I'm gonna be fine. I have heals. Yeah, I got heals.
It's the goose game.
The sound still resonates inside this mossy bell.
It's a sword. A sword castle.
I want them to think I'm stupid.
Alright, so we've got...
Come on in. Get in line.
Think. I want them to think I'm stupid.
I want that person to not be able to talk for the next eight minutes.
I want that person to not be able to talk for one of the eight deadly sins.
Greed. Gluttony. Lust. Wrath.
What? How is he doing that?
He's pulling his thumb off!
Whoa! Pride, as you just saw.
Lust. Wrath. Sloth.
Greed. Gluttony. Pride. Lust. Sloth. Wrath.
What's that on? Lust. Greed. Gluttony.
I've done this before. Yes, I've done this before. I remember this.
I remember trying to do the seven deadly sins.
Envy. There it is.
What if I don't touch it?
Just prepare the doorway of my dream.
You see there's a line. Where the hell are you going?
Alright, fine.
Was it already on it?
Lockpick. Can I just lockpick?
Do I have to get in line and listen to them talk?
Don't barricade the door.
I remember the lockpick.
An axe and a strange box.
It's covered in scratches.
I have a weapon now.
You suck.
It's a scripted event, guys. That's a script.
I don't suck. I don't suck at reading a script.
What did I just do that for?
I thought this was my inventory.
That sucks. I'm just buying everything.
I was in the middle of doing something.
Oh, wait. It's the wolf man.
The selfish bitch is keeping something that does not belong to her
behind the locked door in her house.
Something I'm after, bring me the key to that door
and I'll tell you where to find the thing you lost.
Is this fair, comrade? A key for a key.
Ha. Good. Now take off. Get to work.
Oh, it's one of these. The wolf grabs the box and starts sniffing it from every angle.
I could swear I've heard this tail moving under his coat.
Interesting. Fine. Me guess now you want to know what's inside.
The northwestern part of the old woods lies a place where you'll find a key to this box.
Northwestern part of the old woods.
Well, mate, I would be careful if I were you.
Trust me, you don't want to open it by yourself.
Bring me the key and don't try to be a wise guy.
You won't know what to do with it.
Looks like no one else will enlighten you. Listen.
The inhabitants of our lovely village hold many, many secrets.
Treasures they do not wish to share with anyone.
They think they're superior because they have human gobs.
They treat us like leopards.
Well, you know what? Fuck them. We're buddies, aren't we?
And them. Oh, they deserve to be punished, mate.
The wolf moves closer to me.
You hear that squealing? It's one of their secrets.
The wolf grins, listening to the distant sound with great relish.
Find that pig shed, mate. Make that squealing stop and the treasure will be yours.
I need that toolbox.
Stay here. Don't leave. Do not leave.
I've got, I've got to do something with you.
Hold on. He likes weapons.
Alright, what about a staff? Meat?
I shouldn't give her the gun, right? It's a handgun. It's worth a lot.
I have 37 matchsticks. Sell the shiny stone.
Oh, shit. I didn't even know I had one.
What's that doing in the consumable, in the alcohol category?
What is that going to put me on? Flare, maybe?
I'm not going to use these flares. You know that. I'm not going to use them.
I'm certain. What's with the big eyes? Scared?
Bad dream. The wolf winks at me, bearing his teeth slightly.
I need 200. So, I'll give you a flare.
60, 70, 80, 95.
And then I want $5 for this staff.
Give me that toolbox. Done deal.
Upgrade the workbench. Let's go. Shovel.
New melee weapon. I can get rid of this stupid board with nails in it.
Finally. There it is.
Thank God. Upgrade item two.
What can I do with this? Light materials.
Attacks use less stamina. Inflict more damage.
Increased durability. I like that.
And sturdy base greatly increased weapon durability.
I need another spade head.
I would say probably this one.
Weapon durability. Sharpened shovel.
What was I going to do?
I don't remember. This is an emergency weapon.
Repair item. No, don't need that anymore.
Torch. What are these bottles for?
I guess I could just throw them around and put glass everywhere.
That's not a bad idea.
I'm going to have a bunch of glass.
What the hell am I going to use this shit for anyways?
I need those boards. I need nails.
Where are my nails? There we go.
I'm going to go turn this wood into more boards.
14. How many do I need? What does it take to barricade a window?
Three. Alright, let's check this out.
I can make a door here, but let's get the windows first.
Seven. I can only do this three times.
Does he have nails? Does the wolf have nails?
I didn't even check. He does.
God damn it. I need all of these.
And we're going to red lobster.
Red lobster? No.
Ugh. Alright, let's board these.
No. What if I just don't give a shit and just board this up?
Like a barricade? No, that's a bad idea.
I have to make it secure.
This is the entryway. Let's board up this.
I'm going to have to do them all.
I actually don't mind sitting in this corner. Oh no.
I didn't see that. This room is not good.
Lobsters aren't even real.
This is alright. So they can only come in through here.
I actually don't like lobster very much. I like crab.
I prefer crab to lobster.
There's a potato in here. Alright, so the only one that needs to be boarded is this one.
And then I have the door there.
So this needs, I need some more wood and a couple more nails.
I can buy that from any of these two people in the house.
Let's go on my stash.
Chicken head. I'm getting rid of these matchsticks.
I don't have anything else that's worth anything.
I just need a little bit more.
The batteries are worth a lot.
But I feel like I'm going to need them eventually for something. Light armor.
A potato? Oh no.
Okay. So that wouldn't work?
I'm just going to sell the potato.
Sell the potato, sell the meat.
And one battery.
That should last me, I think.
Who has the stuff I need?
I know you have wood, so I'm going to take, I'm just going to buy ten wood from you.
Wires too. Just one wire.
Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
He's compulsively buying things. I need to do this though.
Otherwise I'm just dead.
A potato. A battery.
If he's meat. And that's good, right?
Because then I need to buy, what am I buying from you?
What was I doing? Why did I do this? For nails, right?
Okay, nails. So then I don't have to give you the battery.
No, I can keep the potato. And the meat.
What's this, like, up-down thing I'm seeing?
Now that lets me barricade this.
I want to bring, store this.
Glass bottles, because I want to break them.
Let's make another lockpick.
I only have one bandage. I have a couple of these good ones though.
You know what? No. No, not worth it.
Put the leaves back. Put the potato back. Put the boards.
Let's do it.
He's the traitor. What? Okay.
This is an open window. This needs to be boarded.
Boarded. Boarded? All the windows are boarded.
Now, I'm thinking, board up this.
And just be in here.
I think that's a good idea.
I guess it's, why did I...
Why did I board these up?
Just in case. I don't know. What about the lights?
I could put a light on in the corner over here.
And then the other one can just hang out, like, up there.
And I'm going to board this up too, when it becomes night time.
And this, unfortunately. Can I drag this?
Oh, I can drag this though.
At least block up this thing.
You now have one of the best melee weapons in the game, the shovel.
Oh, I know. That's why I built it. It was worth it.
Let's spin this. Can I spin this around?
This ain't going to do anything, but at least it'll be annoying.
It'll at least be irritating.
For somebody, for a second.
Let's spin this around. In here.
And then, so now I just...
Yeah. Right?
And then, sprinkle it here. Right there.
Right there. Yeah. Yeah.
Alright. Good. Don't step in it.
I'm going to put some more here too.
Just in case somebody, you know, comes in here.
He's going to step on it.
I am not really going to come down in this room.
Unless I absolutely have to.
At least that's the theory.
So glass is not a trap. It just hurts. Right?
Okay. Board this up. Do I have enough to do it?
I do. Do it.
And anybody getting through that? Bear trap.
Put the sofa down there. No, put the sofa up here.
No, no, no, no, no. I have to get everything in here too.
Where's the light? I'm going to get the light right now.
Should I just get one? No. The ghosts turn off one.
Hurry. I've got... Time has stopped right now.
I've got plenty of time.
It's seriously faster if I just do it like this.
And the bathtub too. Just so people can stop saying the word bathtub.
This is so far.
Uh oh. Here comes the bubble bobble ghost. Here it comes.
Were you actually serious?
I'll get that new ground I'm dragging over.
Get this in here. Good.
Now let's get the other one. Ice hockey?
Well that would be more like curling.
Curling is lame. It's alright. It's cool.
It's curling the game with the brums.
The guys just go favorishly like brum brum brum brum brum brum brum.
Right? That's kind of cool.
Alright. We can almost be done with this.
Uh. Generator off either.
I should... Can I make these eventually?
Because it's annoying to have to drag them around the whole damn house.
This is almost as boring as this stream.
What's that person's name? Sorry. What's that?
I couldn't hear you over me enjoying the video game.
What's that? I couldn't hear it. What'd you say?
Is somebody up? What? Straight down.
Alright. I'm ready to lock this down.
Tell me his name.
So in theory, this is boarded.
Sofa goes up here at night. Traps go down.
Well I'll have enough time to do that. I have them in my inventory.
I might as well just do them now. At least a couple of them.
Where I know I'm going to put them.
So this is very obvious. This has to go in the corner.
I'm setting up my Animal Crossing house.
Okay? Let me do it.
Maybe right in the middle. I don't... I hate that.
But if they turn it off... No, there's light going through there.
What about over here? Just both corners?
Yeah, right in front of the door. That's fine.
Play Animal Crossing OST. I'm not going to put Animal Crossing OST.
Alright. Bear Trap. In front of this window.
Just don't step in it.
And then eventually I'm going to have one right there and one right there.
You can't see because I'm pointing at the screen.
One right there. When I come in for the night.
We want Animal Crossing. And the Animal Crossing OST is not going to make any sense.
In about three minutes.
So... I thought I stepped on a trap.
Same thing with this one right here.
Both... That is good. That's good. One more here.
And then I have two for the front door.
I am ready to survive. I will live another day.
Because now if they get through this one...
Oh, what's that? Whoopsie.
Where's the actual door? The actual door is right here.
So I want it to be like right here. Right there.
Alright. And then at the end of the day...
Two here. I ain't dying, guys.
I'm not going to lose this one. And I'm not going to move.
So let's get the couch in the right spot.
So I can just kind of push it over when it gets too late.
Good! I'm ready. Let's go. What was I going to do?
I don't know. It's open. I can do whatever I want.
What was the thing that he said? The northwest of somewhere?
Not here. Up here, probably.
It's a pig. Yeah, the pig shed.
Is the pig shed down here?
Like up this way? Pig shed.
He's like, go up in that pig shed. Go to the pig shed.
Chicken Lady is south of the Silent Forest.
Alright. So I'm going to bring a chicken head to the chicken lady, right?
Makes sense, doesn't it?
Oh, I didn't. You're right. I did not go to the wedding.
Too many things to do. Alright, this is fine.
Oh, I'm going to fill the gas up.
I thought I didn't want to go to the wedding. It's just I forgot to go.
Let's fill up the generator. I actually filled this up with the gas.
Might as well. This thing needs it.
That's alright. Put the rest in here.
Okay. Store the traps.
And I'm ready for the adventure to begin.
Wait. Bandage. Keep. Got that.
Put the knife in the second slot. Bear trap can go away for now.
Both bear traps can go away. Nice.
Alright. Looking good. Looking good.
Nails. So I got lockpick. Watch.
Bandage. New weapon. Shovel.
Bingo. I'm ready.
We are going to go left and then we're going to go to this person's house.
Chicken head. Don't forget the chicken head.
Where is it? Chicken head. We're going to the chicken lady's house.
Alright. Here we go. I'm going left and then down.
I got the shovel now. Let's see. What does it do?
Okay. It's like a stab. How long does this take?
Okay. It's a big swing. This game looks pretty cool.
The game is pretty cool. It is pretty cool.
But hold on. How do I do? Was it Q to do the thing?
Is it set? How do I do this?
I get it. Just wanted to know.
So let's go down here. Let's go to Piotrek's house.
Or as far as we can get.
Remember. We're collecting nails too.
Use the UAV. Use your UAV.
Chicken lady. Don't step on mushrooms.
I have a negative now.
Stepping on mushrooms means very bad things happen to me.
There's a moose here somewhere. I don't even want it.
I told you it was right here. I'm not going to fight it.
There's no reason to. Don't step on a mushroom.
There's so many poison mushrooms.
It's just a maze of poison mushrooms. I need to go down, not up.
I don't have a torch. I didn't bring a torch.
The one thing that I forgot to bring.
Damn it. I was so ready for this too.
Where are we at? Alright. We're at Piotrek's house.
Got some barricades.
Somebody in there?
I don't want to if I don't have to.
I'm going in. Junk pile.
A pile of junk sloppily welded together.
This is somebody's base.
Tractor ain't going to stop me from coming in.
There's a heavy smell of gasoline in the air.
This is once a tractor. Now it's a hollow rusty body.
All of its useful mechanical parts have been scavenged.
Alcohol, match, gasoline.
Nobody in here. I need fire.
I can't get through here without fire and I didn't bring...
What about the match stick? Can I throw matches on it?
Can I light a match? Oh yeah I can.
I'm not strong enough.
Alcohol and match.
Throw alcohol and then throw match.
There's gas in here and I'm like
I'm just going to throw matches.
I didn't even realize that. Yeah you're right.
That would be really dumb.
Well I'm going to need to throw a Molotov in here.
Remember this exists. Put gasoline on the gunk.
I have an idea. Does this work?
I thought there was gas in the air.
Yeah.
I didn't have to do that much.
I figured if there was a big fire the whole building would explode.
That's why I tried to go out and do like that GTA mission.
I've got to be ready for this.
Something's probably in here. No it's just a chest.
And some mushrooms.
It's in the crate. Something worth it.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah that's worth it.
And a note. And I cannot decipher any of this shit.
So this is a wheel.
A tire. A toaster.
A rocket ship.
Well they were breathing in gasoline this whole time they were drawing this.
So they take this whole thing with a grain of salt.
Alright well I got the toolbox. That's good. Let's continue.
Nothing else in here. Well I'm like in this little compound area.
This place looks like a scrap metal warehouse.
The walls are covered with fungus and spider webs. It's very stuffy in here.
I'm going to get reed. I know it.
They put my hands up here.
I don't know what kind of defense mechanism that's supposed to be.
But I do it when I get scared every time.
I smell a rosin. What the hell is a rosin?
Batteries and tape. And then a postcard with a portrait of a man.
Someone has pinned a caption on it.
1961 the sky is dark and the earth is blue.
Nebo. Just cream.
Oh that's a different language.
There's also stuff down here. Metal door.
Prepare.
There's a person right here.
Oh there's a person. I didn't hear you come in.
The boy's eyes are wandering around the room.
Wait is this the courier?
Should I show him all the stuff?
One from the spring that fell off recently.
When I was entering the cockpit I hit my head and well it fell off.
I thought I was flying but it was just that lights went off.
Oh this is your blueprint.
These are the blueprints for my space rocket. Almost ready.
I broke down a whole tractor to build it.
But I'm missing several parts. Several very important parts.
For example a shiny little mirror in this rectangular box with wires.
And the boy suddenly becomes lost in thought.
If only I had more tractors. It would definitely go to space.
What can you tell me about the road?
You won't be able to make it home via this road. You should build a rocket instead.
What do you have? Oh containers of gasoline of course.
I just inhale it all day.
I like electronic and mechanical thingies. Foods. All sorts of stuff.
So you like food. Mechanical things. Batteries even.
One would say you like batteries.
Oh you got nails.
Here. You like watches. I'll give you a battery.
What's this? Cable.
Does he have any in particular items that I... what did I just buy?
Okay. You just stole his nails. No I didn't.
I had 50 reputation dollars.
Flashlight. Military flashlight.
And a regular flashlight is too much money.
I'm going to have to come back here with other stuff for you.
You like electronic and mechanical thingies.
Okay. Good to know.
What about gossip?
Suddenly it becomes sad.
Well I know you exist now.
What's in your... is it a bathroom?
You got something over here.
Hold on. It's getting kind of late.
I should probably think about getting at it.
I could open it with a lockpick.
Okay.
I should probably think about getting at it.
I could open it with a lockpick. Is he going to be mad about this?
What do you got in here? And two Molotov cocktails.
Generator. Okay.
How do I look for inventory space? I'm going to have to think about heading back.
I'll give it one more look.
And then it's time to go back.
I'm going to go down. Where's this...
Witch's hut. Whatever it was.
Get out of here.
Don't even... I just need one shot.
Or two.
This reach is amazing. I'm so glad I have this.
And it's pretty durable too.
Alright. Let's go down.
At fifteen or so I've got to turn around.
What the hell is that? Oh shit. There's two.
Oh no. I've got to... okay.
Come here. You don't even know.
What do you got? Wires.
Alcohol. Is somebody still banging?
Who's banging? Who's banging right now?
Holy shit. Holy shit. Holy shit.
Wait, wait, wait. I've got to...
Get rid of the matches.
Get rid of the meat.
Get rid of the stones.
Okay. And battery.
Oh, it's this guy. He's hitting his head against a tree.
Alright. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. Time to go.
Hey. Once a day. Once a day I can do this thing.
That is very useful right now. Once a day.
Hey! Whoa!
Shit. I should have went... What is that? I should have went at fifteen.
Can I do it again? Alright. We're good.
I'm going. I'm going. I got a lot of good stuff.
Two.
Fine. It's fine. Just go.
He's pretty fast though. He's fast. He's kind of fast.
Where the fuck am I? Okay. I'm here.
Where am I? This is not my house. Where's my house?
Poison. Your sight is wrong. Where's my house?
Oh please. Just...
Go. I have... Okay. I've got to remember what I was going to do.
This ain't my house. There it is.
This wood right below my house? I didn't even know that.
Fix this well too. No. I can't. Not yet.
Oh my god.
These were just down here the whole time? Forget it.
Do it tomorrow. I have no time for this shit.
One. Two. Three. Almost eight hundred. Good. Good.
Store this stuff. Bring out the traps.
Store the fabric. The toolbox.
The chicken head.
Let's make another bandage.
Make a torch. Yeah. Yeah.
Make a couple torches because I'm going to need them.
I think. Drugs. Molotov cocktail.
Bullets. Wire. Put just all this stuff. I can figure it out later.
The nails. The machine gun.
The other...
I need more inventory space.
I can have two clips. Gasoline.
Okay. Now what's this? Hotbar upgrade.
I can't do this though.
I can't craft more items of this type so I have to do a hotbar upgrade.
Wait. What about the shovel?
I'm running out of time. Okay.
Just go. Go. Go. Go. I need to repair this. Oh no. What?
What does it take? What is that?
What is that? Super scrap. Scrap?
I don't have that. Okay. I'm in trouble.
Give me the board. I don't want this to break.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Out. Get out. I didn't take any traps.
Where are the traps?
I just put my face in it. I shouldn't have done that.
That was a mistake. I can't move this over. Yeah, I can.
There are traps fucking everywhere.
Got it. Okay. We're good. Let's go.
Electricity. Once a day.
I'm surrounded. There's no gas in the generator? Yeah, there is.
There's plenty. You can't step into one of those if you don't move.
I mean, the theory is to just kind of stand away from...
How come they're not coming over here?
I should have barricaded the door. That's right. You're right.
I was going to do that. Remember I said I was going to do that? It's okay.
I have to pee really bad too. I'm trying to hold it in as long as I can.
No sign of anybody yet.
Can I do it from right here? I can.
No, I'm not doing it. I think that would be a waste.
Because I'm already almost at a good enough time, I think.
Let's do it now. I don't need to do it now.
I got trapped right here.
They're going to push the sofa out of the way, get stuck, and I'm going to kill them in one hit.
Plus, I'm going to be banging on the wall?
That's just asking somebody to come over here.
No, it's good the way it is. There's a gun.
There's no way. It hit the wood.
Okay, get ready.
He's over there.
He's in the other part of the house.
Okay, there he is. There he is.
He's coming over. How much health does he have?
He's almost broken. He's almost broken. He's in. He got in. He's going to get in.
Got you. He's dead. Come to me.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Don't come to you. I need to...
Oh, no, it's open. Go to them.
No, rearm the trap. I don't have any more.
I don't have any more. I got to hit somebody to have a...
Okay, I'm fine. I'm good.
Use the moth. What's that? What's the red?
Oh, right. Day 13. This is the unlucky one.
All right, now I've got some time. We live another day.
This strategy worked out pretty well, but I'm going to board the door next time.
That can stay. I need to reboard this. What do I need?
I need wood, and it's all down there. All right.
I'm going to pee. I have to go to the bathroom now.
I'll be back in like two minutes. Maybe more.
You're back. I'm back.
If Jerma reads this, I'll eat my sock.
I wouldn't do that. How about this?
Go get yourself water.
At least eight ounces.
How does that sound?
What did you say? This wood logs here, too.
Now, let's put this back in.
Make sure I'm in the right place, which I should be.
I've got to get a haircut, too, eventually.
All right. This was a success.
So much, in fact, that I'm going to do it again.
I've got scrap metal.
First things first.
This was untouched, so that's good.
I'm going to put some more gas in here.
Hey, what? What's this shit?
Why is this here?
Why is there corruption all over the place?
All right, you're good. Don't hit the trader.
I'm not going to hit the trader.
Scrap metal weapon part.
I've got plenty of time, so let me go to the workbench.
Let's see what this takes now.
I need to upgrade the workbench. I need a gas canister.
I can make a hot bar upgrade, which is probably for the best.
So I'm going to do it. What's it going to give me?
Another hot bar. That's good. It's just another slot.
I'm going to repair the shovel.
And then I'm going to look at this again.
Durability. I need eight scrap and I need a silencer tube.
Scrap and a silencer. I want increased durability.
Silencer tube. You got one of those?
You do. I will take that. How much scrap do you have?
Three. I'll take it all.
Okay. How many lockpicks do I have? Two. That's fine.
Okay. What do I need? Eight?
Plenty of these. All right. I need to...
The thing about games like this is it's so hard
to just point at the one thing that you want to do
and do it. You just get... What about that?
And what about this? What about this? And what about that one?
Wait, I've got to get nails. Okay, I've got to get nails.
But no way. I've got to get this tire over there. I have to get the tire to make the thing.
But that makes it fun. I really like it. Make the camera bigger.
Is this a one-guy scenario where I'm going to one-guy this?
No, that's a good spot. In fact, it's too bright.
There you go. There. That's better.
But no, I really like that about the game.
I like it so...
There's so many random things to make
and look at and craft, and you only have a certain amount of slots.
It's just managing your
self. But look at all this stuff.
I don't even have the stuff even... Okay, I can make a pistol.
But it's one shot. Hold on. I need the weapon part.
This is what I was talking about.
Now I'm... Okay, I want the...
Now I... All right.
Okay. One at a time.
I need to go back and set the traps back up
over here. So I have...
How many traps do I have? I'm going to bring the gasoline over and I'm going to fill
the gas tank again. The shovel is fixed.
I think I want another torch because this one's almost gone.
Put the glass back here. Oh, that's right.
I was going to make an upgrade for the shovel.
Which is... I need four more scrap.
We're going to go get scrap. Oh, this game's fucking awesome.
Okay. I'm going to sell this battery.
Because I don't want it. All these nails.
I'm going to need these though.
And some boards. Do I have any more? I have two.
Take the potato and just eat it. Box.
Medium caliber bullet.
Okay, I'm going to get another wire. Yes.
I think...
No, no, no. Boards is what I need from you.
No, I don't. Because there's wood down.
All right. Go get wood
from the thing down below you. That's the task I'm doing right now.
Stay frozen. Stay frozen.
Stay frozen. Stay frozen. Stay frozen. Stay frozen. Stay frozen.
It's frozen. Good. Okay. Got the wood. Craft it.
All right. I now have plenty of these.
Board this up again. Bang.
German's not going to answer us about his tears.
So that's done. Now I'm not going to freak out over that.
Now I need to make a bear trap.
I can actually do that later when I come back with more scrap.
This is a scrap run.
Try to find chicken lady.
Which is down here.
I'm going to say it's right here. Find chicken lady and get scrap.
Is this for today? That's what we're doing today.
And re-arrange this ship.
How does that meet in here?
Weapons go up. I'll do this later.
So many random things that I have now.
Aye, aye, aye.
Okay. Scrap metal.
I'm starting to lose my mind because I'm just going over a thousand times.
All right. Scrap metal. Let's put everything in. Keep the potato.
I'll keep this torch because I'll burn these both out.
That's fine. Gasoline can stay over here.
I got plenty. Let's go. I'm ready.
I'm ready for this. Let's go get scrap.
I have to be back here at 15 hours. Chicken head.
Good reminder. Thank you.
Thank you. What happened? Oh, my house is poisoned.
Scrap.
I said I was trying to get scrap.
Use your Molotov. I'm just going to get over there.
I'm going to make another torch anyways.
Okay. Good. Somebody stepped in that last night apparently.
All right. I got a few scrap.
Good. Make another torch. Ignored.
Who am I ignoring?
Who am I ignoring? Us.
Oh, what?
All right. It's time. Scrap run.
Chicken house. No, don't say the word chicken.
Because I can't eat like fried chicken.
And I want like a fried chicken sandwich now. And it's over.
And it's not. I can't do it. I can't have that.
I'm going to have to eat like turkey patties. But those are fine.
All right. Let's go down. Probably animal.
All right. Where is chicken lady?
Big open field here. Wood.
I'll take it. Road to the village?
I can't get into any of this.
Road to the village. Gutted pig.
Is it poison? Where the hell am I going?
Am I going to a new map? I can't do that now.
Shrine. A shiny stone has been pressed into the mud covered head.
Take the stone. This is Indiana Jones type shit.
No. I'm not taking it.
Not yet. I take the stone. All of a sudden a boulder is going to land on me.
I'm going to alert the horde.
What's this? A wagon?
A meat wagon. A dock.
There's something in the water. A phone.
Our woods are so beautiful this time of year.
I can't talk. Where's my meat?
I should get two kilos of meat for this month.
Antec won't save you this time.
You hear me? Give me the fucking meat.
If he ever tries to come back, fucking quack doctor.
Bug. Bag. Doctor bag.
Who are you? I don't know. Get away from me.
Alright, alright, alright. I'm fine, I'm fine.
I don't want to piss off any NPCs. Generators running. Two generators.
Barricaded windows.
Okay, let me look back around.
I'm going to go in this room. Destroyed well.
I can go in this. Pigs in here?
How much gas you got in these? It's a lot.
Alright, so this is nothing I can do here.
What now? Get the fuck away from my home.
There is no more meat.
The sow is starving.
Get or I'll let Antec loose. What is Antec?
Oh my goodness.
Alright, I'm out. Chest. Map.
What a joyous day.
We shall meet again today.
I hope she'll enjoy what I've prepared for her.
She hasn't had an appetite lately, but it's okay.
We have our ways around that, don't we?
She must eat rich meals.
I've dug out something delicious for her today.
My queen. Only I can be close to her. No one else. No one.
No one else will get close to you anymore.
Everything.
I can get you today.
If you're monarchy, if you're hungry,
I shall now, I shall show you something
I've found the way.
Sixteen.
Sixteen. That's probably part one of the code in there.
Time has stood still in here, by the way.
Which is interesting.
There's a guy in there that doesn't want me in there.
People want meat, right?
I'm assuming Antec is the pig.
Like the prize pig.
If I find a long sturdy rope or chain, I should be able to descend it.
What? I can descend into the well?
He's been hiding in his cottage for the last couple of days.
He'll end up like the others.
I'm telling you. He'll run off into the woods and disappear.
So is this supposed to be my village that I've disappeared into the woods?
These people aren't all messed up yet.
The villagers turned their heads away from me.
I don't think I'm welcome here.
Well, I have a shovel, so that don't matter.
I need to get in this room, okay?
Not a very good puzzle. I hate to say. Sorry to tell you.
All it took was me to put weight into it.
Shelf? Nothing?
What the hell is going on?
Why is it doing this?
You gotta pick up the shit before you get in trouble.
I can hear you. Hear you.
Just want to look under your bed and see if you have any coins.
Did I kill this thing?
So, how is he?
He's gonna be fine. Just give him Tylenol.
Okay, I have to go now. Bye.
I'm just slowly trying to go through that.
Time is standing still. I don't want to miss much.
Kind of an empty house.
Nothing. It's just a hotel. Siphon.
Ooh, what's a siphon? What does this do?
This is a whip cream canister. Okay.
Found a whip cream canister.
Nothing in this oven. Chest over here.
I don't need to lock, which is good. Bread and gasoline.
What do you want?
It's quite a wide tunnel. There are finger marks on the ground.
It must have been dug up by using bare hands.
Large hole in the ground. Let me dig in peace.
I gotta shovel too!
Someone's inside this hole. I can barely make out a silhouette.
Looks like a grown man with long disheveled hair.
He's completely covered in mud.
What? Wait, this is my house?
Oh, shit. It is my house.
Is that because I had the shovel?
Oh, that's awesome. Okay, cool.
Go back in? I will. I'm just going to deposit my stuff that I picked up.
Didn't pick up any mushrooms.
I got lots more gasoline, which I'm just going to fill.
This is what we're going to do here.
I'm using both these completely.
Matchsticks, rope, alcohol, shiny stone, scrap metal, battery.
Bread, whatever. I'm out of room.
I'm going to get rid of these gasoline cans and dump them.
We're going to go generator, fill the whole thing.
Just max it out completely.
I'm really enjoying this stream. Hey, thanks. I am too.
This is kind of just a fun game.
Does anything else take gas?
Or should I actually just fill this?
What do I do?
I'm going to put some space let up then.
Go back here.
I don't need to repair anything. I've got another torch.
Anything else I need to bring to that?
I'm going to bring the knife, just in case.
I could probably bring another heal too.
I need some more rags. I'll be alright.
I'm going to heal with the bug thing.
Yeah, I'll be good.
I'll bring two to heal.
I'll bring two.
Let's go back. I have more room in my inventory now.
Where's the Animal Crossing OST?
I don't know. I lost it in the mail.
Creepy Animal Crossing.
Now the time has stopped again.
Shovel, there's my shortcut back, and then there's this person.
I've got another thing to explore.
I really think I'm at the stage of the game now where I probably need to make a gun.
But I know what's going to happen.
I'm going to make a gun, and I'm not going to shoot it one time.
I'm going to wait until the very last boss of the game.
And I'm going to unload the clip on the boss and miss seven or eight of the twelve shots.
I should probably just sell it.
Let's go back down here. Didn't I get a map?
Make a gun. Are you serious?
There's a door for this place.
How do I get in here?
This is one of the only survival horror games that I've played where getting a gun is still scary.
I can see that. Very much so.
Let's go up here first.
It's locked. I could open it with a lockpick.
What was the point of that? Was there actually no point to that?
Or did that give me access to this weird courtyard?
Bread oven.
Don't talk about pizza.
I can't eat that either.
I could open it with a lockpick.
I'm going to use all my lockpicks for this shit?
Dead here. Potato. Liar.
How many dead bodies are in here?
Oh my god.
I got my lockpicks back. Let's go make one.
I need a key. Lockpick, lockpick, lockpick, key.
Well, that sucks.
At least I know this is here.
Smash the door.
He missed something. Did I?
No, I didn't. I got them all.
Smash the door. That's not going to work.
Who the hell are you? I don't know.
A jar filled with cooked meat.
Help yourself, whatever you fancy.
I could open it with a lockpick.
Meat grinder?
Is that what they're eating people? Is that what this is? They're grinding up people.
The pig is just a show. It doesn't actually do anything. It doesn't mean anything.
I'm going to make something with this.
Bandage.
I got to go deposit some stuff.
I need a key.
I'm right here.
Kill this guy. Kill him.
You want me to kill that guy?
He didn't do anything.
He told me I could have whatever I wanted in his house.
That's sort of strange.
I'm alright.
I need to go get rid of this stuff.
I think there's only one more building I didn't check.
I think someone up here. Yeah, I didn't go up here.
There's actually a couple places I haven't been.
This town is huge.
Wait. This is a big-ass town.
Explain the corpses outside of his house.
He's grinding people up and he's feeding them to people.
Yeah? But he gave me three pipes.
And I got two pieces of wire from his house.
I can throw a knife in his head when I get back.
Where's the exit?
I wish I had a map. Where are those little things?
Down here?
Where the hell is that thing? There it is.
Alright, hold on.
I've got to get every item that I can get from here.
Time is freezing through the window.
Did I get anything to cook? What about the meat?
Wait, that meat I could probably cook.
That's unfortunate.
This is where it gets weird.
Because I can't carry any more of this stuff.
It's time to get rid of it. I have to get rid of some things.
I'm going to upgrade this shovel.
I want this to have better durability.
Attack to use less stamina.
More damage? No, more durability.
Is absolutely what I need.
Build gun. I need the weapon parts, which I don't have.
Homemade shotgun. No, I need the weapon parts.
You get that the next day.
What I'm going to do is I'm going to make a lockpick.
Then I'm going to make...
I'm going to upgrade this shovel, which is more durability.
Boom.
I'm going to hold onto it for sharpened.
I can build the homemade shotgun now.
Do I want to do that though? I don't think I want to do that.
Do I want to make this thing with the weapon parts?
No.
That's what I'm saying.
Wood.
I have to get rid of the board with the nails.
Just eat the potato.
Jar of meat. I got these glass bottles.
I'm not doing anything for me.
I'm just going to pretend I filled them with the meat.
Glass bottles. My wardrobe.
Stupid ass thing.
Where's my wardrobe?
This is where I'm going to put bottles.
Bottles are useless. I don't want bottles anymore.
Hold on.
My metal pipes are going in here.
This bone is going to go in here. I'm going to forget this exists.
Anything else I can put items in?
Put bottles in this table.
This is where the tape is going to go.
That's fine.
There's another wardrobe right here.
I'm going to be scattered around everywhere.
Bottles in the wardrobe.
Alcohol in the wardrobe.
Drugs in the wardrobe.
Metal pipe.
Bread in the wardrobe.
Drugs in the wardrobe.
Meat in the wardrobe.
You guys just have to remember where these items are because these don't stack.
Items that do not stack have to come out of here.
They're just taking up huge amounts of space that I could stack items in.
Batteries are going in the wardrobe.
I'm going to eat the potato.
Get this broken glass out of here.
Meat on the bone. I can't sell. There's nobody here.
Close.
Wardrobe. Batteries.
The bell in here too. And the fan belt.
Meat on the bone.
What are you talking about?
Where's the bone? What did I do with the bone?
This is what I was afraid of.
Cook the bone? What are you guys talking about?
The meat bone.
Stick bone.
Meat on the bone.
What are you guys saying to me?
I'm wasting time.
I'm going to make another one of these bandages.
Meat on the bone for fuck's sake.
I don't have scrap.
I have too many things.
Where's the wardrobe?
Now I need to organize this.
Otherwise I'm going to lose my mind.
Board with the nails is getting sold.
Rope.
Gas on the bottom.
Bottles of stuff that are filled is after that.
Empty bottles.
And other things that are not...
Fire related things.
Let's put the matchsticks.
How many potatoes do I have?
Why are these not stacked?
Bone down here.
I only need three of them. We can put that here.
Drugs next. Drugs and healing.
Medicinal stuff.
Drugs and medicinal material.
We're getting there.
Next is electronics part one.
Fire related or fuck's shit idiot meat on bone.
I'm going to freak out.
Do I need 50 matches?
Weapons.
Weapons up here.
That means this.
Bullets.
Wood.
Wood and rocks and shit.
And nails.
And healing and medicinal items.
It's just like doing one of those sliding puzzles.
Material.
Yes, I'm ready.
Okay, now it took me long enough.
Now I have to just go to...
Uh oh.
I have to barricade this.
I need three wood and I need wooden nails.
And scrap. Wooden nails.
And some wood.
Let's barricade this door closed. Turn on the generator and hang out.
It's just like a lot to process.
Generator on. Board up this door.
Did I need anything else?
Well, I'm trapped in here now. Did I need anything else?
The left window.
Meat and bone.
I'm going to take a knife out and I want to break this.
Alright, I'm good. Let's go. Anything else I need to do in the meantime?
I have heals.
I can throw some... Yeah, let's throw some bottles.
I already have some broken here.
Check this out. Let's get it on the ground right here.
Let's do this a couple times. Like right there.
Because there is no... What are we doing?
I don't have a trap right there so this is going to be alright.
Just put a little bit of glass there.
Let's throw a bottle on the ground and break one.
Do I have to pick this up or will it just...
Do I have to actually set this as a trap?
I can leave it. Okay. That's good to know.
I'm going to do the same thing right here. I'm ready.
Bring it on. Meat bone.
Alright, I need you guys to explain to me what the hell this is.
Is this like a meme or something that I'm missing?
Jeff just gave five community subs. We should be focusing on that.
Thank you, Jeff, for the five community subs. Appreciate it.
Use meat on the bone.
I'm going to do that one time and if it doesn't do anything,
I'm not going to stream for two weeks.
Good. Good. Alright, let's go.
It's a win-win. How is that a win-win?
What do you mean? Morty. Morty.
Morty, you put the meat on the bone, Morty. Morty.
Why am I getting minus two?
Somebody in chat wrote that and I was just referencing it.
I just said it.
Alright, pay attention. Pay attention, folks.
We've got an alien coming through.
First alien of the night.
I'm going to throw this knife right between the eyes.
There's no trap here, so I have to do it. I have to throw it right away.
Did he give up? What did he stop for?
He decided to go different. There's two of them.
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh. Fuck. Where's my knife?
Where's the knife?
Shit. I've got to get somebody stuck in a trap.
Oh, no. Don't panic. Don't panic.
Fucking trap.
I threw the knife and it didn't kill him.
It kills everybody in one hit,
but the one guy that comes through the left window
doesn't die in one hit from the knife.
His two friends died in one hit.
Bullshit. Bullshit. Bullshit.
No, no, no, no, no. I need this. I need weapon part.
Here, you can take these potatoes. I'm not going to eat them.
I need to get that weapon part because I want to build a gun.
Quick, use the music stand.
Alright, it's time to make a gun. I'm sick of this.
I get medium caliber bullet,
medium caliber magazine.
Shiny stone. I'm making a gun.
So that I need weapon part. I need 450.
What is this going to get me here?
That's two, three, four, ten.
Alright, now I just need 40 more
and I'm going to make a gosh darn gun.
Why am I selling gun ammo for a gun?
Because I want a pistol.
That's a medium gun. That's a medium sized gun.
So, you can take the bread too. I'm not going to eat it.
Take the board with nails. I'm not going to eat it.
He doesn't have enough room in his inventory.
Wait, you have to hold...
Are you going to have... If I give you bread,
are you going to have it forever?
Oh, this is not good. I have to get him...
What do I give you? Pills? Yeah, okay.
I'm not going to sell the bread then. Yes, I am. Who cares?
What about alcohol? You got alcohol stored there, right?
Okay.
I'm going to go sell you one of my many tubes.
What's in this wardrobe?
No, that's important stuff.
Here we go. You can have a metal... No, I might need that.
You can buy and sell at the same time. Yeah, I know.
I need $450, man. I don't want to buy anything right now.
I need $450 reputation dollars.
Alright, you can have a tube. I've decided.
Do you have bottles? What does he have a stack of?
He has a stack of... Buy the part.
That was the right thing, right? Yeah.
Gun. That's what that person meant when they said
buy and sell at the same time. Sorry.
I'm stupid. I didn't...
I thought you meant like I could... I don't know what the hell I was thinking.
Anyways, it's time to make a pistol.
Small caliber, semi-automatic pistol.
Small caliber magazine, small caliber pistol.
Bingo. Gun with no ammo? I got ammo right here.
I got two clips.
I need another scrap metal. I gotta buy one.
It's loaded. Yeah, that's fine. How many shots does it have?
Where the hell is it?
How many bullets does this have? How do I shoot this...
How do I aim this? I don't want to fire it accidentally.
Okay. So you aim it like that.
How many shots are in it? Okay. I'm ready.
I got my gun for emergency situations. I have a magazine for it.
I need another scrap metal to repair the shovel.
And then I can move on with my day.
What do I need? Ten? Just give me all of them.
Repaired. Good. I have nothing to cook.
I'm gonna go back to the weird house.
This is nice and organized. I need
a gas guzzler. Get rid of this.
Inventory space is increasing, so this is good.
Jar of meat. Jar of meat on bone.
I'm not gonna use that. Meat and bone.
See you guys in two weeks.
I need to make more traps, which I need scrap for that. Of course I do.
Meat, not jar of meat.
Okay. I'm gonna store this.
I have two, three heals. Let's just take them all.
Extra torch.
Anything else to satisfy me?
Yeah. Let's go.
Jar of bone in meat.
Alright. I'm ready.
Repair item. We're good. I'm gonna head back to the town.
And see if I can figure something else out.
I do have to go pick up my items, though.
And the generator has been on the whole time.
Why did everybody not scream at me?
What's up with that, huh?
If you reload, you lose the magazine. Thank you for telling me that.
I would not have known that.
Pretty good. Get rid of this.
Keep the rag in case I need to make another...
No, I'm not gonna need to. Chicken head, keep that.
Watch, keep that. Good to go.
Alright. Off I go.
Let's move. Back to the town.
Scrap metal. Need it. A lot of it.
How do you reload? It's probably R.
So I'm not going to press R.
Alright. There's a spot up here that I didn't check out.
Oh, it's a reference to something else. It's a reference to another game.
Well, this is Darkwood.
This is not that other video game that you're referencing.
Alright, then down here is the... Wait, what's that?
Nobody taught you how to use the door.
It's Chicken Lady.
Alright, show item.
See him? He never came back.
Item found.
These devilish trees have overgrown everything.
It was a long time ago, but you remember it's still my little hand, don't you?
Thank the Lord for our sow.
Poor thing seems sickly, but she has more life in her than the lot of us, if you ask me.
Only thanks to her we got something to put in the pot these days.
Okay, so take this. He went to see this fellaceum. He never came back.
I have to find this doctor.
Holy mother, this creep again. May the devil take him and his blasted violin.
The old lady turns in red and starts to scream.
Devil fucked your mother.
Get away from me house.
Where?
Location already marked Pig Shed.
Why do I not have a map of this place?
These are hens, right?
Oh, another toolbox. I'm not taking... I don't pick up bottles anymore.
Cross covered in mud and sticks.
A wooden cross covered in mud and sticks.
A key.
None of my keys fit.
Tractor, gas, steering wheel.
Doesn't the spaceship guy need a steering wheel?
Ruin. Scorch remains of the wooden hen house structure.
Scorch remains of the wooden hen house structure.
Hello? Basket full of eggs.
Chicken egg.
More chicken eggs. Nice.
A red egg.
That's a red egg. Cool.
I think I got everything.
Wooden chicken egg.
Can I smash this?
It's a metal door. I can't smash a metal door.
What about on the outside?
This is one of those scenarios where you go to your kid's recital.
And it gets introduced as...
And here's little Gary Elbertson.
Oh, that's my son. Come on.
We're practicing. It's my son, yeah.
He's trying. He's practicing a lot.
Lately he's in the garage and...
What the fuck does your kid do, huh?
I bet your kid plays the piano.
That's easy compared to the violin. You don't know shit.
What is going on? I'm sorry, it won't happen again.
Somebody under here? His musician is the car.
It's like that Lindsay Lohan movie.
It's not my fault. I know it doesn't sound too great.
I won't play anymore. I'm sorry.
I know it's under there.
The chicken lady's hut. You're not afraid of her?
You're brave.
Have you seen her? The pretty lady.
She's the most beautiful lady in the world.
I watch her through the cracks in the windows.
She changes when I watch her. She gets more beautiful. I play for her.
I want to be happy because a chicken lady locked her in that room.
She envies her. She won't allow anyone to see her. Even me.
She knows very well that during the last Capala night,
I fished out the pretty lady's wreath from the river.
Yes, sir. The chicken lady knows what it means.
Oh, yes, I'll become the pretty lady's husband.
We will walk hand in hand, sir. I will play for her, sir.
I tried to release her, but the chicken lady,
she chased me off. She always does.
I also look for the second key at Mr. Jan's,
but now he's disappeared. I don't know how to get in his house.
Yes, sir.
Okay, so it was Mr. Jan.
Second key, Mr. Jan's, but he's disappeared.
I don't know how to get into his house.
So kind. So very kind. You're just like him.
My daddy, but my papa has changed, mister.
Just like my mommy. They will not listen to me.
They won't hear how sad I am, sir.
But I am not boring you, sir. Please don't go.
Please. They hear me out. Don't go.
Nervous, grunting, I heard from under the tractor.
Perhaps you could help me. Leave board.
Please find the key, good sir, to the pretty lady's room.
The chicken lady has it. Well, Mr. Jan also has it.
I saw him recently near the well.
He used to play with me. We threw rocks into the well,
and I looked into our reflections while making silly faces.
Do it, or else my face will stay that way.
And now the water in the well is always hazy.
It shows these weird images.
The well is here in the village. Maybe you will find him in there.
He used to hang around often.
He's staring into the well as if looking for something.
I must hide now. I'll hide from the chicken lady,
the chicken lady of that place where they used to keep all the grain
in the southeastern part of the forest.
What about this road?
My mommy once told me this road.
She said people used to travel it.
They would leave their houses and walk it during the night.
I was scared of this story.
I was afraid my mommy would go out too and leave me behind.
Have you heard about the sow?
The villagers keep this sow nearby, the pig shed, they call it.
Mother of all pigs, they say, it's beautiful,
but I've never seen it. They don't allow me near her.
They chase me off. They always chase me off.
He drops his gaze.
Maybe you would be able to see her, mister. If you managed to get inside,
maybe you could take even a wee piece of meat from me.
The guy's asking a lot. I've never eaten a pig and have heard it's very tasty.
Would you take some meat from me?
This person's freaking me out. All right, we've got some info though.
Chicken lady's bad.
I can just break the window.
The barricade's too strong to dismantle.
All right, I've got to get to the well.
The well needs to be repaired though.
Chicken lady's fucked up.
Smash it, you dumb dumb. I want to do it the right way.
I want to do it the correct way. I've got to go up.
Time's still frozen? Yeah, time is frozen forever here somehow.
There's one more house up here.
This is where I was last time.
Woman examine, crate search.
Doll. Don't touch that until I talk.
The woman stares at the ground with a dead look.
I'll trade you half drank gasoline for a doll.
Doll.
Kill the pig.
Another house over here.
Can I get in? Metal door.
No windows.
Metal door locked. I need a key.
Of course I do.
I'm going to head back to...
I got a new thing on my map in that silent forest.
Here is the shrine.
The well was down here?
Where was that well?
Last time I saw him he was down the well.
Well rotting.
I would think that's where he is.
This side.
I still need a key.
I'll probably get it later.
This guy is pissed off.
I need a chain.
I need that.
I think I've exacerbated all options.
It's time.
There's something in here though.
What should I do?
Should I just kill this person?
I feel like I should just smash.
I don't know.
There's no talking.
I can't do it unless I know what's happening.
I can't do it.
I have to come back here with one of those chains.
Sorry guys.
I have to go back to the silent forest and look at that place that he told me to look.
Store these things that I have now.
There's a chain in the village.
Let's do it.
I've got more of these things.
Scary.
Chicken eggs I can just eat them.
Let's store this crap.
Chicken head doesn't do shit.
I'll keep the eggs.
Let's make another bandage.
I was supposed to get a bunch of scrap.
Let's go find that new place that's marked on the map.
There it is.
The day just started.
I'm ready to move.
It's like 8 o'clock in the morning.
I haven't even done anything.
The electronic stuff.
The guy that likes you to give him electronics.
I don't really have any electronics to give this person.
The steering wheel.
I'll bring a couple batteries.
I want to keep the wires though.
I'll give him the steering wheel.
Let's go.
Look at his blueprint.
Tire, steering wheel, battery.
Wait a minute.
Car battery.
Is that the fan belt?
It's somewhere else.
It's over here.
What else does he need?
Fan belt, battery.
This is like a muffler.
What is this?
I can just give it to him now.
Let's go.
I could have saved a little bit of time if I went through the hole.
You're right.
Always get the mushrooms.
Don't forget the pig shit.
There's an elk here.
You're in the way.
This is the weird poison forest.
Just don't step in any poison and I'll be alright.
Metal down here.
I think I already did all this.
I didn't get these.
This is not supposed to be a wood run.
This is supposed to be a scrap metal run.
Don't step on a mushroom.
There's the house.
I have some stuff for you.
I have some materials that you're going to want.
Steering wheel.
A trajectory guidance system.
This will fit perfectly in my rocket.
Have you seen my rocket?
It's almost as pretty as Gargarin's.
Would you bring them to me, the other parts?
I would love to fly to space and into the moon and into Mars and Jupiter and the sun.
I mean, I would land at night.
The boy suddenly looks into my eyes.
Look for old detractors.
We'll find my missing parts there. Tires.
I'm getting 100 space rocket chassis.
Only two more to go. Fan belt.
Hold door frame stabilizer.
A hybrid rocket engine.
Yay, finally, I have everything I need. Go your way now.
Go now, please. I need to install these parts of my beautiful rocket.
And then we off I go.
I'm receiving tons of shit.
I will wave to you when I'm on my way to where no man's been before.
Do you know the doctor?
Beautiful, but I don't see Gargarin in it.
I've never seen a photo without Gargarin in it before.
Gargarin was this cosmonaut, a man who flew to the stars.
I'll reach the stars, too, one day.
Maybe tomorrow, for example. I just need to find the screw for the cover.
Blueprints for the rocket.
Postcard with the portrait of the man. Oh, I have one, too.
I did it. But before you leave, what do you have here?
He has a chain.
Cable. Chain. Couple of wires.
I mean, just clean the guy out. He's gone. Map of the old woods.
I should get this, too. Get the flashlight.
Flashlight, map. Now, what do I have to give you?
Right, I was going to give you nothing.
Get the flashlight. I need 200 reputation with them.
Some of these have to go.
Flashlight's too expensive. I could probably make one of these.
Get the military flashlight.
There's a chain in the village. Are we certain of that?
Yes. You're going to have to point me in the direction where it is.
So now that leaves with...
I have the cable, the military flashlight.
Oh, I was going to give you a couple of batteries. That's what it was.
That's what it was. But I'm going to... No, I don't.
You gave me weapon parts? Wait a minute. Okay, this is important.
I'm going to give you a healer.
Because... And, I don't know, a fucking log.
Don't want that. Normal is better than military.
This is going to be a fight and chat here, I think.
Why is military more expensive?
That seems odd.
Military is brighter but uses way too many batteries.
I'm going to do the regular one.
Did it... Stunt. Stunt.
Buy the nails.
No, I don't want nails. I wish I had enough for this.
Map of the Old Woods.
I want it. I want it. I want it.
I don't care if it sucks. I want it.
How many do I need? 40 more points.
I can do that with a torch.
Sell the batteries? No, now I need the batteries.
Because I have a flashlight now. Here, take a bandage.
60, 70, 80, 92.
No, I need that torch. No, I don't. Here, take this shitty torch.
No. Alright, take it.
Give me it. Done. Okay.
It's been a pleasure. Goodbye.
Now I have to go up to the pig shed.
I think I should go back.
I'm so conflicted on what I want to do right now.
Map of the Woods. Church ruins.
Church ruins? Oh shit, okay.
There's a hydrant up there.
I'm just going to keep doing what I was doing. I'm going to the pig shed.
No, that's too dangerous.
I'm going back.
I'm going back and we're going to take the super runner. Let's do it.
Poison.
I don't even know what I'm doing.
I get very easily overwhelmed in games like these.
Because when you have a finite amount of time to do something,
and the game tells you to do 10 things at the same time,
I get overwhelmed.
It's very simple for me to lose concentration completely.
I really like this game though. It's very fun.
It's very interesting.
So I am in my possession.
I can now upgrade the workbench.
A sickle? I can make armor after this.
Single shot shotgun.
All right. I need more scrap,
which is the point of the entire mission that I went on.
What's going on? I have to make these into wooden planks.
Let's go ahead and deposit them all.
Need more gas in there, but I'll just take them.
Cook the mushrooms that I got.
The flashlight now takes the place of the torch,
so I do not need torches anymore ever again.
Technically.
Make sure I get all the wood out of here so I can compile it wrong.
I have a lot of batteries.
No more wood or wooden planks. Let's go fill this up.
Go get the chain. I'm going to.
I'm going to get the chain.
Get out of here. What are you doing?
Generate this is still fine, but I'll top it off.
All right. Let's put the rest of the wood that's in here.
Bang, bang, bang, bang.
I now have more wood than I know what to do with.
Good. Turn around.
Now I've got to get my wood pile here.
I don't know. Stones. It's time to just remove them completely.
Just get rid of them.
I have no reason to have these stones. Zero.
They don't do a damn thing for me.
They're just here. Weapon parts.
The batteries away. Put the welder away until I can actually use it.
Don't turn that on.
All right. I'm getting rid of the rocks and then I should be good to.
Where are those rocks?
Oh, my God. Give me a break.
It's like a super dog.
Holy shit. He's going to kill me.
Dead huge dog. Cookable meat. What?
All right. I'm going to do the bug thing. Moth thing.
How much is this worth? 60. Nice.
All right. I'm just throw them on the ground.
At this stage of the game.
I'm going to put just throw them over here. If there's any stupid reason why I need them, they're all over here.
If there's a dumb reason for them to be needed.
Build the well. Build the well. Build the well. Build the well.
Build the well. Build the well. Build the well. Build the well. Build the well.
Wait, I just need the chain. OK, build the well.
Build the well. Scrap.
Itchy inside of my ear. That means like a ghost is in the room, right?
I know that means something weird. There's like a ghost in here.
Just like when you sneeze, it means somebody's talking about you.
All right. Build the well. I need to heal.
No, that's if your ears get red. Dumb, dumb.
OK, we're looking for near the chicken lady's hut.
There is a person who is on fire, who is burned.
Where is this person? There's a burnt corpse over here somewhere.
OK, looking for somebody burnt.
Burnt wood logs. I'll take it.
Pig. That's a wrong house.
It's dummy. Dumb, dumb.
This isn't the chicken lady's house. Where is the chicken lady's house?
Down to the right. I hear you.
I haven't even been down here. I see you between the trees.
You will not squeeze between them.
I would use these next words more carefully if I were you.
I didn't even say the line right and I leaned in for it.
Who are you? Get away from me. Get away from me. Get away from me.
That would be very nice. Mushrooms.
Why am I itchy? My eyes are itchy.
My inside of my ear is itchy. My eyes are itchy. What's happening to my body?
Cool. You have fleas in my eyes.
I got fleas in my eyeballs.
Lady's house. I think it's over here. This is it right here.
OK, looking for a burnt thing.
Burnt thing. The tractor.
You. Destroyed well.
Now this ear is itchy. What the fuck is happening?
Go back. Go back. Go back. Go back. Go back.
He's losing it. What?
In the house bottom right.
That person wrote that so fast that half of it was not in caps.
And then they just said, I'm melting. OK, I'll listen to that person.
He said it needs to be done.
It will help, he said. I don't understand.
Note. Burn a mix of herbs in the oven.
Lavage.
Combomile and nettle.
Lounge, chamomile and nettle.
Keep the patient warm twice a day.
One tablespoon of sauerkraut juice by mouth.
Do I have to do that? What a foul stench.
Its arms and legs are bound with a chain.
Bingo. In the oven.
Time to fix the well.
Keep the patient warm. Yeah, that's fucked up.
You're not. He's not under here anymore.
Fix the well. Look at the time.
Yeah, it's frozen. It's fine.
Take a bandage. No, I just need to stay next to a light and do the moth.
All right, can I activate moth and then shine the light in my face?
With a flashlight? I feel like I should be able to do that.
I need a lamp or something.
I'm not going in here.
Use the well, you dipshit.
What's with the light up there? What's with everybody with this well?
By the way, I looked into it.
Full moon is in like two days.
Just saying. I'm going to heal.
There's going to be something down here. Should I get the gun?
I'm going to be ready. This is going to be like a boss fight.
Okay, there's a return to the surface.
Torch and a flare.
It's going to get dark in here.
What the hell is scribbled on the ground?
Is it like a scorpion?
I hear somebody walking around.
Super mushroom. God.
Do I have batteries?
There's a key down here. Just find the key before I run out of power and light.
And I'm going to take out this gun.
If there's a monster down here, this is a gun scenario.
If it is anything besides those guys with the halberds, this is a gun scenario.
This is a gun scenario. Gun, gun scenario.
This is a gun scenario.
No, it's not. This thing is little.
I can't see. I'm going to wait until the turns are going out.
I'm going to bash his fucking head and fuck out of here.
Let's go. Heal.
Where is it? Nice 90s voice actor dub.
Get over here before this burns out.
What the fuck is it?
It's you. The doll. Odd meat.
No, don't throw this. Okay.
Where's this key that exists down here apparently?
And the music's getting louder. Why?
There's so many mushrooms here.
What is this? Return to the... Wait, I made it?
I did it. The hell am I?
This thing breathing? How do I get the hell out of here?
McCull. McCull. K.
A couple of eggs. Plastic chickens.
More eggs. Is it bread?
So many eggs.
Key covered in chicken feces.
Oh shit. Okay.
Where does that key go?
I got the key.
So now I have this chicken key.
Which, yeah, that's the thing that the wolf man wanted.
I know what we're doing tomorrow.
For the music kid.
This is a choice we have to make. I'm not sure what to do.
Nice oblivion NPC face.
I can just open the door. Should I just open the door?
What if I just go in? What if I just go in the room?
It's a little hen with an odd little shrug. I wish I could find a fat little bug.
Upon seeing you, the old lady stops humming. What do you want?
I thought I was going to try to show her the key.
Be like, haha.
I'm going to do the thing. I'm going to give the key to...
I'm going to give the key to the wolf man.
Just look in there first.
Should I not do this?
Go in the room. Are you sure? Alright, I'll do it.
I'm going in. Going in. Going in.
Going in.
He said don't. Wolfman said don't do it.
Wolfman said don't do it.
But what's behind the door? It's up to me now.
I'm not going to do it. I'm going to go give the key to the wolfman.
That doesn't mean I'm not going to bash the old lady's head in.
Kidding.
Friendship with wolfman secured. You can do both?
I don't know how accurate that is though.
Because every time I go towards the door...
The door is hot. There's a fire behind that door.
And it's you guys.
Half of you are in front of the door trying to open it.
And the other half of you are creating heat to not open the door.
So I'm walking up to the door and it's like fucking fire.
Don't open the door!
I'm going to burn my hand! And then everybody behind me is trying to push me to get me to touch the door.
I'm going to burn my hand if I touch the door.
When I walked up to the door it was like a sea of don't.
Don't do it! He said don't do it! Please don't do it!
And then I'm like okay I'm going to back off.
Yeah fucking wuss! You're the biggest piece of shit I've ever met in my life!
And then the fucking door cools down.
And I'm like okay I'll walk towards the door again and it turns red.
Again. I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do. No. I'm not going to do it.
I'm going to go to the wolf. Because the wolf gave me a specific task.
And it was to do this.
Up here. That's what we're doing.
That is the plan. You're going to regret it.
Well then that's my own fault.
Oh god. It's 17.
I didn't get any scrap.
I have a lot of things to cook.
40, 40, 40, 40, 48.
40, 40, 40, 40, 40.
4800 points!
Acid base? Yeah I like it better.
What is this? It's just an eagle eye thing. Who cares?
Acid base. Nothing else I can cook right?
That doesn't matter right now. What matters is you boarding up some doors.
Like right now.
Like why are you still sitting here like this?
I don't know why I'm still standing here. I need to board up doors.
Why am I still sitting here?
Okay. What's this? I still have a trap. This is scrap.
I have no more traps.
Thankfully my shovel is still good.
What about down here? This is alright still? Yep.
Barricade this door. Good.
Good. Broken glass is still there.
Move this sofa just a little bit.
Well I think it matters.
And then I'm going to put a trap on this wall over here. I have a chain trap.
There it is. Get it on here.
Lay it like right here.
Move the trap. What are we talking about?
Here we go. Is he really going to say acid base and not play it?
Yeah I think.
Heals? No.
I'm really prepared here with no heals.
That just means I can't get hit. Wait no I do have a heal.
I've got them off. Play the damn song.
I can't. I cannot alt tab.
No I've got to focus on this and then I've got to give the wolf the key.
Just don't get hit. I know it's not hard.
It actually is kind of hard.
I will make the 16 people that spam this link in chat happy.
I will.
Because I'm a pleaser. I'm a crowd pleaser.
That's what you're going to get. And it's not a crowd pleaser.
There's 4,000 people here and like 20 people want me to play this.
So this is actually not me pleasing the crowd. It's me pleasing a few people.
I'm a crowd pleaser. You're a gaggle pleaser.
Here they come.
This sucks. Does this not do anything?
Front door. I think it's over here again.
That's it. There's no autoplay on by the way.
You know something funny about that video?
One of the recommended videos after that.
In the 9 like Hollywood squares stuff.
You know like the 9 thumbnails.
Is Germacraft episode 1.
What does this mean? What's going on?
Somebody's spawning in here. What do I do about this?
I need some backseat gaming. What is that?
Backseat gaming. What is it? What do I do?
Don't look at it. Backseat gaming.
Don't look into it. Should I get out of the room? Is it going to explode?
Should I get out of the room? Get out of the room.
I want to get out of the room. Yes.
I stepped in the trap.
And then the sofa.
Blocked me from leaving the room.
Can you imagine somebody.
Barricading up themselves in a fucking room.
First of all. Second of all.
Somebody rolls a grenade in the room.
And then the person goes. Let's say there's like 6 or 7 other people in that room.
Hey! Should we run out of the room?
Should we run out of the room? I think we should probably run out of this room.
Let's run out of the room. And then that person sprints.
Directly into a trap that they put up.
They step into a bear trap that they assemble.
And then a fucking monster comes in.
And pushes the sofa directly into them.
And they get locked with the bear trap on their foot.
Still against the wall. Well at least the other 6 or 7 of you could leave.
Like you're just raring to go.
Waiting at the Olympics for the guy to shoot the gun in the air.
To start running into the trap.
At least whoever else is in that room could easily get out.
I put these traps here.
Get out of the fucking room.
My only...the wires.
The copper wires. The fiber optic wires.
That connected from this part of my brain to this part of my brain.
Was just get out as fast as possible.
I don't...what is that thing?
Why did somebody drop like a gas grenade in the room? What is that?
How did this even get over here?
That's what happens when you play Left 4 Dead like that, by the way.
I just did the thing where everybody goes into the bathroom.
And if you've never played Left 4 Dead, that seems like a great idea.
Hey, all of us go in the bathroom.
And then all the special infected.
Just find you.
And the boomers blow up right outside the door.
The smoker is just grabbing people. The tank is getting in there.
Everyone just gets in the bathroom. And then everybody dies.
I admit, what a fun game. Oh, generator.
Well, now I have to make another door.
You have a 9-volt brain. Get out of here.
Okay, so I have...why do I only have five...oh, I died. Right.
So I need another scrap.
And then I can upgrade the workshop again.
This is a scrap day only.
We're going to go talk to the wolf, and it's scrap day only.
Yeah, everybody runs out of ammo.
If you do the bathroom strategy.
And then somebody has to go try to find a weapon.
Okay, here we go.
Scrap only. I'm going to keep the pills.
Deposit the scrap. I'll keep the potatoes.
I will take a couple of batteries with me. Flashlight can stay.
Torch can stay in emergency situations only.
Wood goes back. Bottle goes back.
Potato stays. Let's go.
All right, buddy. I'm going to move out of here.
This is a scrap run. Go to the wolf's camp.
Let's go. Do I have any heals?
You don't? Yes, you do. I'll be fine.
Somebody said I should go do the other stuff in this woods first,
or I lock myself out of it.
I lock myself out of doing this stuff again.
So what were the other quests I had?
I don't remember anything besides the pig farm.
Let's just head over there.
I need to get scrap to upgrade.
And I need it to make traps and everything.
Is there anything else I can do in here?
I feel like this is an important place. Might as well look at it.
There's the gramophone. Oh, he's in here.
The boy stops playing and lowers his head, avoiding my sight.
Have you heard about the sow?
The villagers keep the sow in the nearby pig shed.
They call it the mother of all pigs.
They say it's beautiful, but I've never seen it.
They don't allow me near her. They chase me off. They always chase me off.
Maybe you would be able to see her, mister.
If you manage to get inside, maybe you could take a wee piece of meat from me.
Should I show them? Should I show them the key?
Wait, that... No.
I'll get you some meat. Pig shed.
Let's go.
All right. Proved.
Right when I walked out.
You're just hiding the fact that you're not very good at the violin.
It's an LOL situation.
Is that a big dog? Yeah, this is a meat dog, I think.
Gah!
Yes, yes, I'm wearing a bathing suit.
Okay, it's laundry day.
Fuck. Those dogs suck.
Those dogs are ridiculous. You can't dodge those.
I have to shoot that dog. That is ridiculous.
That's ridiculous. You just suck.
Dodging only goes backwards and it just... That's not... No, no.
The big dogs... No. I am not going to hear that from you guys today.
I'm not going to hear that from you guys today.
That thing was ridiculous.
I ain't going to hear that from you today.
Just kill it. I've worn bathing suits as clothes outside.
You're good. I know.
Wait, am I supposed to be embarrassed at the fact that I'm wearing a bathing suit? They're light.
They're very thin. And they do complete coverage.
What's the problem? I'm incredibly comfortable right now.
Okay, I'm going back.
Can I repair this? I need to repair this.
If this dog is dead, then I'm going to get my shit back.
Those are worse than Dark Souls dogs.
Yeah, they're the mega dogs because they have a thing that they drop that's like a hundred essence.
I'm sorry, I ain't going to have somebody tell me that dying to the mega dog is bad.
It's a mega dog.
And I'm going to hit it in the face. Whatever.
Did that guy just punch that thing and kill it?
He just punched it once. Holy shit, this guy is ridiculous.
That's free antlers for me.
All right, let's go. Poison.
And we go up. I need metal.
Metal. Metal.
Round two, dog. Super dog.
Okay, we've been here. Go up to the pig shed.
Try middle mouse.
I have it on my other mouse, but yeah, I do it sometimes.
It takes way too much stamina for me.
It takes more than half a bar of stamina.
Look at what that...
What are you talking about? All right, here we go.
What is that thing? Bugs? Ooh, there's an egg sack thing here.
Embryo.
Ooh, I remember this shit.
I'm getting some expensive items.
Okay, I'm here. I need to get a piece of meat from the pig.
I did my best.
Squish this between your teeth.
That's disgusting. I don't think I'm going to do that.
Oh, banana cream.
Is this the pig? I can't collect meat. Banana cream pie.
Straight up banana cream pie.
I told you he had it coming.
He loved that pig and she ate him.
She wouldn't have eaten him if some fucker hadn't cut the cables.
How the fuck didn't he get electrocuted?
Who's going to feed it now?
It's the only sow in the village.
It will starve if it dies.
Do you guys care that I'm here?
Who in the flying fuck goes there?
Get out of here or I will break your legs.
All right, good thing I got the gun.
Pitchfork. I'll take it. Don't want that.
This guy took like three full bullets each.
We got it.
There's going to be a huge pig in here.
This is what's happening.
This is going to be a giant pig. It's going to be horrible.
Don't come any closer.
I hit the pig in the face.
I'm sorry.
These things are worth a lot of money.
What? What happened?
Okay.
I don't know. It was attacking me.
It was attacking me.
But I didn't mean to.
What should I do with the skateboard?
I don't have any heels.
Are you eating this pig?
It's late at night.
I have to get out of this.
How do they get in here?
I'm in trouble.
I'm in big trouble.
Get away from me.
I didn't get any scrap.
This is terrible.
I should know that's going to happen by now.
I don't care.
I'm not going to die from that.
I'm here.
Cook. Embryo.
Store all my shit quickly.
I'll figure it out later.
We're good.
Do I eat a potato?
I'm going to use the pitchfork for melee.
Why are these over here?
Couch.
I'm ready for you.
If I don't use the pitchfork,
then I'm going to break the shovel.
What's the swing animation?
That's not very good.
Check the left window.
Why am I moving?
I should not be moving.
I think I'm going to use the gun.
The gun's going to break.
That's what I was thinking.
Here comes our first visitor of the night.
I'm going to stand up here so he gets in the trap.
He actually comes through and lands in the trap.
Is the red durability not ammo?
What are the crows?
Something over here.
Why is it not...
I have two hours.
Take a quick peek.
There's something right behind this door.
I'm safe.
Day 16.
Nice.
Another day.
Now I need to go back to here.
They mentioned the word cable.
I'm going to probably assume that I need to bring the cable.
Now, what exactly do I want to get rid of here?
These pitchforks I don't think I'm going to use.
I might keep one of them though,
just in case I need it for something.
Repair the shovel.
Let me see the upgrade here.
I need three more scrap.
I think he sells them.
Nice.
Go to where the thing was.
Workbench upgrade.
Exploding barrel.
Light armor.
Gas bottle.
Don't I have one of these somewhere?
I think they have one.
I'm going to sell.
I don't have anything to cook, right?
No.
We're going to go for the big pig.
Battery shoes.
What else did I have here?
Take that out now.
Put on some shoes.
This cannot come out now.
I don't have to store this everywhere.
Let's clean this up.
Let's make some molotovs.
I've got plenty of alcohol.
I'm going to make a molotov.
I need rags in the bug shells.
Batteries.
Sell the antlers.
Bring the cable.
Eat it before I run away.
Lockpick. Don't need the tape.
Store the bottle.
Flashlight up here.
Molotov. Antlers. Get rid of them.
Watch. Battery. Shovel that is being depleted.
Torch. Don't need it. I have the light.
I got batteries. Eat that potato.
Cable. The axe needs an axe head
and a stick.
You sell an axe head and I know there's a stick outside.
210. I can't get this right now.
I'm going to bring the pitchfork and use it.
Shovel and if I have to I'll use it.
I don't need the toolbox anymore?
Is the toolbox useless?
Have I sold the toolbox you won't need it anymore? Really?
So this is useless to me?
I'll sell it if that's the case.
Upgrade workshop.
I need a pair of pliers and some wire.
I need to do the pliers before I can do the axe.
I just need scrap metal.
I can't craft it yet.
I don't need to do this yet.
I'm going to make one more lockpick.
I'm going to make a couple bandages.
I'll bring out these pills.
I don't have a reputation with this dude.
Right? Not bad.
Not a bad idea.
What are we doing?
I already have enough tape.
Let's get these rags and let's get a wire.
Now I need another wire.
I need both your wires because I want another lockpick.
I'm probably going to need it.
Three molotovs, which will go down here.
Can I only stack these in twos? Why?
Battery for the light? How do I use this?
Will it just automatically consume it from my inventory? Maybe.
Alright, I'm ready. Let's go try to do something with that.
I got the cable here. Let's do something with the pig.
Here we go. All the way to the left. Let's do it.
And then it's time to give the key to the wolf.
Let's go. Let's eat potato and run.
What a good use of the potato.
Walking through this stupid poison thing.
I'm just going to eat another one too. Cover more ground.
How do I like the game so far? I think it's great. It's very fun.
I've not decided that it was time to stop playing it.
Does anybody know?
I'm sure a lot of people here have already played this.
Hold on. I need to concentrate here.
How far am I in the game?
Oh, shit.
Everybody quiet. Everybody don't move.
That thing sucks.
Use gun? Not unless I'm absolutely necessary.
How much? One of my halfway.
That's cool. Here we are again.
Now I need to get back around and then I've got a cable now.
I'm a 2% Andy.
What?
I have to be ready for this.
I'm going to go up here and through this.
I'm still on the starting island?
Thanks for ruining the whole game for me.
Let me get this right.
I have the pitchfork still.
Get out of the way.
Got it. Eat?
What do I do with the cable?
How do I get out there?
How do I get to the cable?
I have to go all the way out and all the way around.
Eat another potato.
Still on the starting planet.
That is pretty funny.
Cut cables.
Hold on.
What the hell is in here?
Why do I have my Molotov cocktails out?
Lever. I need to turn the power on to use the lever.
That connects to that.
Search the chair.
Let's zap everything.
Let's electrify everybody.
Turn the power on.
Am I stuck in his head?
Let's turn it on.
It looks like a president.
Chill. It's just a game.
It's hard to chill when there's scary shit everywhere.
Some of them run through the door to the outside.
There's a lever and a red button on the panel.
The motion range of the lever is limited by a provisionally attached plate.
The node is glued to the casing.
The lock is set to a voltage that paralyzes the sow for a moment.
Around 15 seconds.
The lever operator positions it in the middle.
The feeder gives a sound signal.
The operator then pushes the button and the feeder feeds the sow.
Repeat until the feeding is complete.
Remember the sows are common good. Do not remove the lock.
So it paralyzes for 15 seconds.
Position the lever to the middle.
The lever is positioned in the middle.
Then I push the button.
It paralyzes for 15 seconds.
Should I kill it?
Then I feed the sow.
Then I have to run over there.
Come on.
I was just being tortured and shit.
What do you want me to do?
I just caused a famine.
Grow soybeans. Plant some corn on the ground.
Get some fresh lettuce.
You'll be fine.
It's time for my piggies to go to bed.
The great big mother piggy has said.
I will count them first to see if all my piggies come back to me.
One little piggy, two little piggies, three little piggies.
99 gg.
16 gg.
1699 is the password for the thing that's over there.
And I got a single shotgun.
Is there anything I can do with the pig?
I don't think there's anything else I can do here.
Battery's dead.
So now I'm going to do 1699.
On the thing that was locked over here, whatever it was.
I can reload on the flashlight.
Where was that thing?
Where was the 1699 thing?
It was down here, like a box or something over here.
Where was it?
I gotta go. It's late.
I'm going back. I'm going. Activate the super run.
Get out of the way.
Activate super frog.
I still have to go to the wolf too.
Bye.
Will you step in this so I can get free antlers?
I'm going home. I'm almost there.
I know it's past my bedtime. I'm going. I'm going to make it.
Another day. Let's make this quick.
I was supposed to get scrap metal.
And I didn't do it.
What's wrong with me?
This gun needs to...I'm going to have to put some stuff in a container.
Molotovs, pills, the...
Where's the other pitchfork? It's gone.
It's gone. I can't put the flares away either.
I have to start throwing shit in random boxes.
Don't sit at the table. I want the wardrobe.
No, keep those in...no.
Alright, alright. Pills, right?
Yes, I do. Pills...um...okay.
Good. Go.
I heard this treatment was funny. I'm disappointed. Minus two.
How did you know about minus two? If you just heard about me
and you came here for the first time, how would you know that?
Liar. Spot the liar!
Alright. These are still boarded.
I can't barricade this so people do...
I just have to wear the nails, wear the nails, wear the nails, nails.
This is almost done. I don't have any more traps left.
I should be okay. We're going with the...
I have the guns still.
I'm not going to need the flashlight. I'm going to put the pills here.
Or no. Yeah, that's fine.
Let's go, motherfuckers. What would I rate this game out of ten?
Three? Oh shit, heal.
I used the moth already. I have to just deal with it.
Zip your fly up. Oh shit, thanks.
Appreciate that. Thank you.
What door are they even in?
I think they're on the other side.
Bathing suits don't have flies.
I'm actually pretty uncomfortable. I'm not going to move.
Hey, why can't I see myself on your forehead? Don't yawn.
You can? Well, that's because
I've been playing a scary game and I've been sitting in front of the computer
for five hours and I've just peed.
So I'm sorry I haven't had time to be in the washroom
and like pat, pat, pat, pat, pat and like powder
in my face and put like cleanser on it and everything.
I'm playing Darkwood.
What the fuck? He can attack.
What's he doing?
He just got killed by a...
No!
He jumped in.
Give me the gun.
I can't see. I can't see.
Move. Why can't I move?
Oh, that sucked. Those big dogs die in one bullet.
That's really good to know.
Reload the gun? No, I don't want to waste a clip.
I think this is one of those games where when you reload, it just...
Come on in. Let's go.
Get out! When I missed him with the first swing and then he like went around
and I swung this way somehow
because he wrapped around me.
Kim probably thinks it's a home intruder here.
Get out of my room!
Like I'm being injured.
Okay, I can do the meat. Please.
794. I need to...
I need to steal. Let's go.
6. Let's go.
Go open 16GG.
Give me more magazines? You do. Give me one.
Let's go. I'm out. Wait. I'm out.
Let's do it. Wait. Yes, I'm fine.
I'm going to have to seldomly use this weapon.
Nice gamer slouch. Thanks, man.
Scrap! It'll have to do. I have a gun.
My whole body is itchy.
You want meat? I didn't get it though, did I?
I killed the pig. Where the hell are you?
He stops playing low as his head.
Show item. No. Gossip.
I saw the villagers dragging a cart with a dead sow,
the one they called the mother of all pigs.
It wasn't as beautiful as they said, nowhere near the pretty lady.
And that piggy, it was a bit similar to me.
The boy sniffles and rubs the mask with his deformed hand.
I've been crying after her a lot.
I saw them trying to cut through the wall of trees.
Do you think it's even possible, sir?
Mommy told me once that the woods are never ending.
And there's nothing on the other side.
What's the grand plan?
I don't know. That pig did not look well.
It was really awful, actually.
I'm going to put the eggs up here in place of the shovel for now.
I'm just running. Eat.
Eat. All right, keep going.
Almost there, wolf man.
And the pig place.
I need to find that. I need to find out what's going on in the cellar.
It was like a panther. What the hell was that?
Okay. That was a nice reference to a show.
I mean, a little bit, maybe. All right, let's get in here.
Where is this?
It was like over here.
Well, they took the pig out, right?
It's in here.
No. What? Where is it?
Where the hell is this thing? Oh, it's in the town.
There's a workbench in here.
Wait a minute. Is there an oven in here?
It's that door right there. That's the one. No.
Where's the oven? Is there an oven? This looks like a hideout.
I don't know. I guess I could turn the generator on, but there's no gas.
I guess there is.
I don't know. Let's go to where the pig was.
Go to the wolf man. Well, they took the giant pig out of here.
I kind of want to see what's in the spot that it was in.
What the fuck? Oh, egg. I'm going to shoot him.
I'm going to shoot him.
Why did I take the melee weapon off the bar?
Well, it's because I was just going to run
and just eat the eggs as I ran.
The guy on the cover art is dead.
That's what was on the cover art? Interesting.
What is in here?
Oh, the pigs are dead. No, they're not. They're all alive, actually.
So they took the pig out.
What's here instead?
Oh, come on. There's no item here.
Really? That sucks.
I really thought there's going to be something in here.
Check the generator room. Yeah, I will.
I'm going to go all the way out for that.
I'm going to go all the way out, all the way around to go to the generator room.
I don't need to eat that yet. Okay.
Through here, right? All right.
Is there anything else in here? Is the lever?
Dead villager? No, you didn't have anything on you?
Lamp. Talk to the mirror.
All right, you kind of losing it.
You are one ugly bastard.
I guess you got what you deserved.
Yeah, whatever. Stick it up your ass, Humpty Dumpty.
Right here. Right here.
What am I doing?
Wolf, please don't tell me I have to go all the way around.
Please don't tell me I have to go all the way around.
Peasant here looking good today? Thanks.
We are almost there. Top right.
So Key is going to go to the wolf.
And hopefully I get a reward.
This is... You guys cool?
You guys know each other?
16GG. You guys fucking know each other or what?
I didn't do anything.
Yes, show item.
Here is the key covered in chicken feces.
As I produce the key, the wolf's pupils widen with excitement.
Well, mate, I didn't think you could succeed.
I'm impressed. Time for your reward.
You'll find that quick thief here.
You'll find that quack thief here.
Buddy locked himself away from the world and he won't let anybody in.
This information will be of any use to you, meaty.
What the fuck are you looking at? I promised that I'd tell you where to find him.
And I did.
Did I tell you you'll be able to get there? That's something else, isn't it?
He laughs.
Now get out of my sight, meat. I have important business to attend to.
If you're interested in continuing our wonderful relationship, look for me in the northeastern edge of the old woods.
I predict a tasty future together.
Sinks his hands into the deep pockets of his coat.
Could you deliver this to that insane old bitch as a way of thank you for her beautiful sister?
The wolf throws the head of a chicken under my feet.
As I lift my gaze, I realize the wolf is gone.
What are these codes?
What are the codes? You have these two codes, these crates here with codes on them.
Those are backer rewards.
Oh, okay.
Well, I gotta go this way.
Go back and give this to the old bitch.
Apparently is what he said.
I'm going to go back and talk to the old lady.
15 o'clock. Yep. I gotta go.
I want those crates.
Can I retroactively contribute to the Kickstarter?
What the fuck is happening? I'm going to die out here.
Scrap. Get me the fuck out of these woods.
Why does it have to go all the way up and around?
This is unnatural walling that you're doing.
This is the only place to go here.
This is unnatural walling, and it's preventing me from playing the game.
I have to take this thing.
What the hell am I? I gotta go down and then right.
Blood. Oh, that's why.
Fuckers, I need to get out of here.
Tab four!
I had to shoot him.
Hold on, guys. Let me hit tab.
Tab. It takes like four and a half seconds.
What the hell even is?
It's right there. I got time. Just go get it.
I will shoot a motherfucker if they come near me.
Stop hitting.
I'm switching them. Tab is map.
M is inventory.
Just give me my inventory. It's right here.
I just hit M to look at the map.
It's right here. Get off.
Give me my stuff.
I need audio. Why is this taking so long?
Where's my stuff?
Where's my bag of stuff?
Shit.
Actual shit. Not good.
Actually shit.
Oh shit.
I just hit M.
I'm furious.
I had it on me too. I'm fucking mad as hell.
Let me in the door. What?
That takes you forever to do anything.
I could be over that in a second. Way quicker than that.
Wood. I need wood and nails.
Where the fuck are they?
I had like a thousand of them. I don't have anymore.
I'm going to actually get mad and fucking smash this keyboard into the wall.
I'm going to just resby it.
Do it.
This guy's made it a quicksand.
I've been doing drugs all day and I can't speed it up.
I'm using the gun. It's a failed experiment.
I'm going to use the gun. Check the gas. Uh oh.
Is that going to last?
What are you talking about? The flash was off.
He's so mad.
I wish I could make boots to not step on the poison.
It's hard to see. It's embedded into the ground.
I'm going to step in a bear trap. Who's putting the bear traps out there?
Turn the lights off in your room for maximum immersion.
Don't look at it, right? I don't know where it is.
This isn't the gas, is it?
Thank God nobody's showed up yet.
No, I'm not turning my lights off. Not right now.
Why did I shoot the gun?
It was moving around. It looked like it was going to explode, so I don't know. I had to shoot it.
Almost there.
I can make the light armor. No, I need scrap metal.
Dude, I don't even know where to get scrap metal. I have to buy it from the vendors.
I've got plenty of gas.
Thank goodness.
All it was was a bug. One beetle attacked my house today.
I'm okay with that.
Did I loot the insect? Yeah, I did.
I got the shell.
150 rep.
Let's get the hell out of here.
I'm going to dismantle the window.
I want scrap from you. All of it.
I will do that.
Now I need to repair the shovel.
I also need to...
I need two rags.
I don't have one rag.
Cool. How do I put it on?
You are wearing armor. It's that simple.
I'm good to go. Get rid of the shiny stone.
Keep the pills. Get rid of these containers.
Keep the lock picks.
You got anything else for me?
I'm going to refill the generator.
I'm going to forget.
That's a guarantee.
What are we going to do?
We are going to probably go back to the village and talk to the old lady.
Give her the chicken head.
Let's complete that quest line.
How do you beat this game?
You have to leave with a special key that I don't have.
You get a key and you can leave.
I think that's what happens.
I think I'm good to go.
I have my pills. Got a gun. My flashlight.
I'm going to replace the flashlight.
I need another slot.
Let's go to the village.
I have no idea how this is going to happen.
The village is on fire.
That's the pig.
This place is kind of in shambles.
It's your fault.
Old lady.
That's probably something to do there.
I'm going to end up killing that thing.
You're a boomer.
Just hit it with a stick.
Where's the old lady's house?
Who's this?
Is that the doctor? No?
Everyone's getting sick.
We're never going to make it.
These woods have no end.
We'll just starve here.
My hands are killing me.
It's your turn now.
He's deaf all of a sudden.
He has an axe.
He'll drop this, right?
He has a better weapon than me.
He'll probably turn in one shot.
I have a gun.
Why would I use this when I have a gun?
I want that axe. If he drops the axe, I'm doing it.
That's 450 bucks that I don't have to spend.
I'm meeting people in this village.
We're all so innocent.
Where's the witch's house?
Is it blocked off now or am I going the wrong way?
I shot a guy who's eaten probably five people.
To take his axe.
Wasn't there something down here?
Didn't this guy have a box that I couldn't open?
No. Where am I thinking that was?
I thought he did. Where is it?
I've already searched all these. There's not one in here.
I don't know. I need a key.
Inside the house.
The door is locked from the outside and it's locked from the inside.
Why do you have to block me off?
I just want to go that way.
What? Quit eating people.
Killing people. What are you talking about?
Zero. I've had zero people for breakfast.
Why have you forsaken us?
I'm taking the jewel too. No I'm not.
What have we done to have wronged you?
They're eating the pigs.
I thought they were eating people. And the pig.
I thought it was double food source.
One guy was eating people.
They feed people. It's all fucked up.
Let's go in here.
No witnesses. That's not how this works.
This is not even the right house.
I wish I had a map of this place.
This is her secret house with the key in it.
I wish I had a map. It helps to have a map.
I know. And I wish I had one. But time is frozen.
Is it over here?
This is a box on the ground. That's the doll.
Northeast.
All the way to the left. That's where I'm going now.
It's a chest. I'm not going to kill the mayor.
I'm not going to kill the mayor.
This is not it, right?
Where is this old motherfucker's house?
Up. Every house is just the same house.
It's a square.
Why can't I get a map for this stupid village?
I can't get a map of the silent forest, but I can't get a map of the village
with people in it that live here?
Nobody drew a map of this place?
I'll take some rope.
And I'll take the photo.
There it is. Shotgun. Memories.
Now that I have that,
I want to go to the old lady's house.
In this gigantic Disneyland maze.
That wasn't me. That was in the game.
Now I'll go right. Go left.
It's that house right there.
No, it's not. It's not this one.
Because it's the one with the broom down here.
I'm going to scream into the mic.
Who is this? Oh, that's the person that I shot.
Go left? I can't go left. This is an unnatural wall.
There is no left.
Wasn't she to the right?
This is the house with the person that's lying on the ground here.
She's to the right. She's actually to the right.
There's nothing over here left. The person lying down on the ground over there is left.
There's the well. Might as well kill that person too.
No. Okay.
This is the hole to go back to the house.
They're burning the pig over here.
Up here is the guy that's eating people.
That shit fucked me up. That's the problem.
That was the problem right there, guys.
That's the issue. I would have found this like 13 minutes ago.
Do you understand?
The burning pig surrounded by burnt trees.
It kept me out.
Look. You don't even need to tell you.
Hey. Look at this. Just give me a fucking map.
Lost in the Disneyland parking lot. Yes.
Except for everything else in the whole game.
Except for the one place that requires one to see points of interest on it.
Did you see the chicken head yet?
Mister, have mercy upon me and find her.
Mother Mary, I don't know what I'm going to do without her. I'll buy myself.
He parked in the Donald Duck section.
Yeah, that shit sucks because it's like Donald Duck A2.
Donald Duck A1. Donald Duck A.
And it goes from A all the way to like F.
I don't know. I think I've hit Goofy F6.
The McDonald Duck B622.
What do you want me to do?
Your mother is your mother. Oh, the pig, right.
Okay. Let's gossip for a second.
We already saw this.
Show item.
Jesus Almighty, my little darling, what have they done to you?
This is a bad sign. Mister, a bad sign. What will happen now?
Military flashlight.
A rag and pills.
A sheet and a few pairs of worn trousers.
Well, you ain't here anymore. Sheets.
A pile of crumbled pillows and pillowcases. Looks like someone has slept here.
A wedding ring. Thank you.
Okay. Nice.
Okay.
I wish I could find a fat little bug upon seeing you.
All right. Well, I think I did that.
I've got the shotgun.
Pig is gone.
And now I have the new area up top to go up to.
Kill her. Why would you write that?
Why would you write that? Why would you write Banana Cream Pie?
Completely without any reason to write it.
You just wrote it and I've read it. Why would you write that?
Why would you do this to me? You're a coward.
You know I'm on a diet right now. See, this shit fucked me all up.
Because I couldn't go around it. I can't come over here.
I come over here, right? I typically knew the witch was over on the right.
All right. Here we are. I just got out. Oh, this is about...
This fucking giant pig here. Oh, shit.
This is just here now. I can't go around this.
There's like a bunch of stuff here. Where's that witch?
And then I went down this way. I thought I had to go that way.
That's my explanation. If you don't like that, then...
Blame the unnatural walling that goes down in a straight line past the pig.
Why can't I just walk right over here? All right, I'm done.
Where am I going? Homemade shotgun.
I don't have any... How many shells do I have?
The mayor. The mayor, right.
Where's the mayor's house? It says useless after...
So I can shoot that one time. Buffalo chicken pizza.
You guys are cruel. You guys are cruel.
Garlic bread. I can't eat that either. I can eat lettuce.
Lettuce. Crab meat.
Turkey patties. Plain without seasoning.
Some vegetables. Dammit. All right.
Where's this guy's house? Mayor's house.
Not over here. All right.
From where I'm standing right now, where should I go to the mayor's house?
Up. Perfectly cooked and seasoned sirloin steak.
See, unfortunately for you, I don't really like steak.
So that doesn't really do it for me.
Let's buy that bridge. Not this way.
Mayor. No, I don't like...
I don't really like steak. I just don't.
I like... Red meat is great.
I think I like hamburgers. I like corned beef.
I'm a huge pastrami fan.
Pastrami is seriously one of my favorite...
kind of go to the deli.
Get away from me. What are you talking about? What's wrong with you?
Are you the mayor? Where's the mayor?
Just checking it out.
Sliced or shaved. Shaved pastrami.
I need to stop talking about this.
Where do I just go? With cheese. Yeah.
With a slice of Swiss cheese on it. Maybe a little bit of mustard.
For sure. It's good stuff.
Okay. So here is a house.
This is not the mayor's house. It's just a house over here.
South of bridge then immediate left.
The mayor house is a house with a generator.
This is the only structure that's over here.
This is the only structure that's over here. Is it this one right here?
Where's the mayor? The mayor wants to see you.
I don't know what house he lives in. By the way, he's in the cellar.
Oh, I shot the guy immediately. Yeah, I'm sorry. That's right.
He would have told me. I shot him the second
he said go to the mayor's house.
I don't know where the mayor's house is,
but the guy that was going to give me the information,
I killed him immediately.
I need to apologize for this.
Because people would have told me what to do. Probably, right?
I have to say sorry about that one.
Hey mayor, let's make some legislature.
Give me plus two, plus two. Please, please God, please, please God, please God.
Alright, where is he? Come here for a second.
It's him. He's the one who killed our sow. Unleash!
Antec!
Which one of you is the mayor?
Antec was pretty bad.
I was thinking it was going to be bigger.
It was just a guy with a headcrab on his head.
Was this the mayor? Oh, shit.
Oh, you're going to find out what you fucking cellar, mate.
Oh, this is bad. All this stuff is important.
The rope. The nails. The wood.
The dead meat is useless. Who cares?
I have nothing else on these guys. I'm just a pitchfork I don't want.
Odd meat and another wire.
Damn it. I can make some toothpicks that open doors.
Give me some room.
Yes, good.
Oh mayor, where are you?
I think I killed the mayor.
I'm mad that I killed that person.
I preliminarily eliminated another enemy.
Why can I not leave?
It's good to go. Nice.
I'm done with this town. You searched the villager on accident and not the chomper.
What?
Alright, so this village is done. Did what I can here.
Leave the potato. I don't care. I got a lot of shit now.
I got a military flashlight.
Go back and then...
What time is it? You searched the chomper on accident.
Alright, now I know where to go.
You have the whole city. The city is yours.
There's the well and now...
This way. See? I got here immediately.
So, what do you think we're doing tomorrow?
Now this, I have...
Why is there blood everywhere? Why is there a bunch of pig heads in here?
Why? They know where I live?
It's kind of creepy.
So, I have like six or seven horror games that I'm going to play.
Over the next few weeks.
I kind of want to see this through.
Do you think whoever has played this game that I could beat this game
in another six to seven hours?
Maybe. No. Absolutely. Definitely. No.
Almost.
Absolutely not. Okay. Well.
Maybe. I didn't get anything down there.
Rope. I have this axe head.
These have to go. I'm not going to ever use them.
The three matchsticks are going to go.
The three pieces of bread.
I don't understand what I do with the meat though.
The bone is going to stay.
I have these two toolboxes that I'm thinking of getting rid of.
I have 50 nails.
Get rid of the potato. Put the rag in here.
Get the flashlight in here.
The shotgun in here.
The alcohol. The rope.
The molotovs. Get this out of here.
Get this out of here. Unnecessary.
I'm just going to throw it on the ground.
All this shit is out of here.
Well. Let me ask you this.
So if tomorrow I played something else.
And then the next day I went back to this.
Break it up a little bit.
You're not going to play this again if I do that.
Do I need to break it up or do we just play it?
Change the pace and then let's play it.
Let's get it done. Yeah. Let's just finish it tomorrow.
You're never going to finish it. You're not going to finish it tomorrow.
There's like 12 hours left.
Well. Alright we're going to break it up.
No we're not. I don't know. I don't know. We'll see tomorrow.
I have the super spooky jumpscare mansion HD to play.
I want to do that. You're weak.
What if we do that tomorrow?
And then I think that game is only 3 or 4 hours long.
So if we do that tomorrow.
And then just move on to this.
Play this for like another couple hours.
That sounds fun. Let's do that.
We'll play this tomorrow after that for a while.
What game am I playing tomorrow? Jumpscare Mansion.
I think that's what it's called. Something like that.
Like the spooky jumpscare mansion.
But I'm too far into this I think to just give up on it now.
So we're going to do this again.
Maybe 2 or 3 hours of this.
And then the next day play this again.
Because I did say I wanted to do 4 days in a row.
I think I'm going to call it here.
The exact like 6 hour mark I think is like a perfect time for a game like this for me.
It's enough for me to get over the stress.
So that tomorrow we'll do the spooky mansion and then come back to this for like a few hours.
Time is passing in game? That's alright.
Okay I was going to throw this stuff away.
Well let me finish. Let me get through this last night.
So I can sell this crap. That sounds like a good idea.
I'm going to get rid of these bottles.
Yeah I'm going to sell all this junk. Red, shiny stone.
Okay I have the shovel. Alright well I'm going to get through this.
And then I'm going to clean up the inventory so it's ready to go for tomorrow.
So in the meantime I'm going to get my lost stuff that's over here.
Let's go. He's never going to finish this game.
I might. I'm willing to give this at least another 1 or 2 solid.
At least 4 to 7 hours of game.
I'm too far into this to not.
I'm like 60-70% of the way through this game.
Okay here we are. Lost inventory is right here somewhere.
There it is. Good.
Alright I got it.
We'll close out this last night.
Is it chapter 2? Yeah I would assume.
You don't start a game that says welcome to chapter 1 and there's no chapter 2.
This shit just got to make it to tomorrow.
I'm going to sell the flares.
I don't care about them really at all.
Get rid of these bottles.
I'm 14 hours into this game.
I've not seen one use of the bottle besides to break and put glass on the ground.
You don't put shit in it. You don't put.
I don't want them anymore.
These jars of meat don't do anything either.
Make molotovs.
You have to use gas for this.
And rags.
Rags make bandages which are more important.
I'm just going to sell them all.
I'm going to recycle all these bottles.
In the meantime the final thing I'm going to do.
I'm going to go to the right because somehow I have not been over there.
I don't know how.
The lantern is really important later.
Yeah. I'll make the lantern later.
Have I not been over here? Is there nothing over here at all?
Doesn't look like it.
No. There is something over here.
Shrine.
What is this?
Shrine? Not going to get me this time.
Just kind of there.
Hey!
They're worth nine.
Where's the shiny stone?
Grab it.
Where the hell is that?
Where are you?
What? I don't want to die out here.
Let's go back.
Acid blood is paying off.
Now it actually is really, really good.
My house is starting to get taken over by this slime.
What have we got?
Deposit. Last one more night. Rearrange the inventory and then we can get out of here.
Didn't I just say I was done?
Yeah. I will be.
I want to get a good fresh save point.
Let's refill that.
I have a lot of lockpicks too.
That's good. I'm ready.
I'm going to use my heal.
I've got some time here.
I could go for some nice crunchy iceberg lettuce. That doesn't sound good.
No, it doesn't. Actually, it sounds terrible.
That's the real stuff coming out right there. Can't pretend on that one.
I need to board up this stuff one more time.
And a few nails.
A couple more nails.
A couple more at the fence.
That's barricaded. This is not.
This has plenty of gas. Yes.
This is okay, but not great.
You could have finished the game already if you didn't spend half the day inside your safe house.
You know, you're right.
That's true.
It's okay if I go out there.
That's actually true. I would have 50% more game time outside.
Or 100%.
I want this in front of the store.
Don't turn it on yet. These glass bottles.
This reminds me when I used to pick up plates in Fallout.
I just have 16 pounds or 20 pounds of silverware on me.
I get these out of here.
Cover the floor in glass.
This is the smartest thing I've heard all day.
Now I actually can't move. Put the glass outside the window.
I'll be fine. I gotta go.
Heals. Right, I'm gonna do this.
This doesn't do damage to me. Alright, that's good.
Hide in the corner.
This has been okay so far. I had that one dog problem.
Where the dogs would just jump in and out of the windows really quickly.
But I'm alright.
What about the band sheet?
Yeah, but that was once.
What currency is this? What do you mean, currency?
Someone just said I look like Michael Jackson.
Do people just write random words and press enter?
I don't look like Michael Jackson, okay?
Whatever.
Banana cream pie.
That's so mean.
Alright, this is where they come in.
21. I'm not in here.
Just don't move, don't move, don't move.
Oh god, take out the gun.
Where is he?
Don't move. Did he hear the gunshots and came around this way?
No, no, no, no, no.
Is this one of the...is that it?
Take it down! Take the window down!
Oh god.
What's that? What's that mean?
It's gonna leave my house. What the hell?
Get the sunlight out, please!
Well, that was annoying.
Okay, so let me do this real quick and then we can get out of here.
I have nothing to cook. I have a lot of things to sell you.
I have a lot of junk that I want to get rid of.
All the bottles. This is not like Fallout where he's gonna run out of money, right?
Shiny stone, shiny stone.
Take it all. I don't have enough room in his inventory.
Okay, what about a fabric?
Buy the mushroom and the fabric.
Because that's just a guarantee just I can upgrade something.
Get the metal. Where's your metal? There it is.
I got so much money with this dude.
Buy the rags. Buy the wire, always.
I'm also going to buy
And a fabric.
And then you're gonna take these matchsticks because they're stupid.
These flares because they're dumb.
The bread because you're hungry.
And the meat because you want something more than bread.
Let's do this.
I cannot craft any more of those so I'm gonna do another hotbar.
It's just an extra inventory slot.
Now, let's clean up the inventory.
The shovel, which is less stamina.
Tax use less stamina or should I just wait until I can get that?
I think I'm gonna do that.
I also can repair the armor.
This item cannot be repaired. The armor is not repairable.
Okay, interesting. Good to know.
Let's clean up the inventory. Bandage.
Lockpick. I got too many of these.
Hook the mushroom. Alright, here we go.
Can we confirm that these are useless?
Somebody that's played this like 4000 hours of this game.
Do I actually need this for anything? Just get rid of them.
You're good to sell them. Alright, I'm just gonna sell them.
I don't know if the wedding ring is needed for anything.
I have three lunchboxes. I don't know why I have this many.
That helps free up some room. So does this.
Meat. It's a chicken head I feel like at some point.
Maybe it would be useful? I don't know for what though.
Torch. Alright, let's get rid of these.
I really hope I don't need these for upgrades or anything.
Because I can't get them anywhere.
You need the boxes for upgrading the workbench.
You need them, you need them, you need them.
Well, shit. Oh, that's right.
The other workbenches though. Don't I have to do the other ones?
I already have them though. Is it already there?
There are more workbenches. They all have the same level.
They're global. Okay, okay.
So you can't take all this so I'm gonna do...
I could just get some more pills.
Get a red egg and cook it.
Make the axe. I can't make the axe until I upgrade the bench one more time.
So I cannot do that.
Hundred essence. Okay, organization time.
Gasoline. Which is something I kinda need to pay attention to.
Alcohol and gasoline can stay down here.
I'll craft like a super bandage.
There we go. And that looks good.
Three of those. So we got alcohol.
Miscellaneous junk. Weapons up here.
What's this mirror for?
Weapon part. Get the rag out of there.
Scrap metal come down here.
I'm gonna classify that as a weapon.
Technically, kind of. Chicken head's not a weapon.
Weapon part.
This bone seems kind of useless.
All those other stuff we'll put down there. Molotovs.
There's gonna be a drug category here.
Drugs and medicine will go down here.
Materials here.
Wood and other materials here.
Miscellaneous junk.
This shit is just junk, man.
Weapon parts.
Matchsticks. That can stay down here.
I wish I could put these in more than one stack.
Or more than, you know, two, three.
That's alright. Scrap metal.
Wood. Weapon parts can stay up here.
Axe. Shotgun for the axe.
Welder. Whatever. You can spray somebody in the face with it and hurt them.
Chicken head's gonna come down here.
Batteries are gonna go this way.
Other miscellaneous parts like wires and shit.
Everything that I don't know what the hell to do with is gonna go up here.
So I don't know what any of these are really supposed to be for.
I know the chicken egg is technically, it's like a healing item. Technically.
I'm good.
Feels good. Lockpicks up here. The nails.
Wood. We can turn this wood into new planks and put them over here.
Alright. Done.
We're organized.
Way more than I was before. Now.
Let's do this. Gasoline.
I'm gonna buy another, no I'm not. Not yet.
Let's do another tank.
My gasoline supply is starting to deplete.
More hotbar is very, very useful too.
I like it. This is a mod for don't starve.
Yes. That looks good.
Look it up. There we go.
I hate the one stack of shit.
Wood. This part, the metal shit can go up here.
Alright. I'm fine with this.
Nothing needs to be repaired or upgraded.
I can make traps if I wanted to, but no.
I'm not going to.
Anything else I want to get from you before I stop this? I don't think so.
Long barrel. We're good. Game is saved.
Got it.
And that is where we are going to call it a night.
We'll be ready for it tomorrow.
Tomorrow we're going to start with that jumpscare mansion.
And then from there we're going to try this again.
For a couple hours. And then we'll see what we want to do the night after that.
I'm into it. I think this is fun. I'm into it.
Hey. Don't mind me.
Just Jerebo985 continuing to be the person that's to give the most gifted subs ever apparently.
I still don't understand why this doesn't work.
Session top subgifter.
This just does not work.
I'm going to put it on weekly for now.
Because that seems to work, but that doesn't make any sense either.
Session top cheer.
How about weekly top cheer? Doesn't make any sense.
Streamlabs OBS. Not impressed.
This is apparently weekly.
This is all wrong.
This is the most recent cheer.
Unless I can find out a way why session top all these things that are sessions just do not work.
How about recent follower?
This is the most recent follower.
Hey comrade. Thanks for the recent follow. Appreciate it.
Welcome to the channel.
Alright guys. I will see you tomorrow. Take care.
We'll do the bits. Speaking of those things.
That's sad.
Why isn't the movie playing? Because the movie's over.
I'm going to start doing all my streams just inside of this theater.
On the screen.
So now onto my personal least favorite souls game.
Bloodborne.
Wait a minute. What are you talking about?
Souls game is Bloodborne.
Oh no. Alright. I would disagree with you.
But I mean that's alright.
Good luck for the rest of that.
Also most of the DLC has been completed in Dark Souls 1 and 2.
What is Darkwood about? I've never heard of it before. It looks interesting.
It is a game about living.
Surviving in the forest.
And there are cannibals that are eating people.
You may attack some of them.
And they've been eating people.
So that's why you did that. And that's why you decided that was a good idea.
But it's kind of just like a trippy you're in the woods.
And there's like a lot of psychological things happening.
And you have to be careful because at night time people come and try to kill you.
They may have been eating people.
Which is what I thought. That they were all part of the same kind of cult of sickos.
And I may have dropped a couple of them.
But that's on me.
Why are you in the woods? I don't know. That's a good question.
But good luck with the rest of your run, Spooky Spitfire. Thanks for the 250.
Hey broluck, thanks for the 500 bits. Hello Mr. Streamer Man.
Here's the 500 bits I owe you to keep my family safe.
Why do people keep doing this? I'm so sorry it's late but you're a reasonable person.
I'm sure you understand. Please let me just see them.
Why do people do this?
Hey white fox, thanks for the 300 bits. Hey man, love the streams.
Huh? Great stuff. Bearded dragons make great pets.
My brother's fraternity had one for three years and loved him to death.
Just made a weird pet purchase myself.
These are blue death feigning beetles.
Also known as desert iron clad beetles.
And they're pets. Wait, what?
The title of this video is Jerma Eats Ass.
This is supposed to be back here!
Signed to confirm my age! What?
The title of this video is Jerma Eats Ass.
I can't watch it on stream through the browser source.
Well here, if anyone wants to see this...
These things are ridiculous looking though. I couldn't do it.
Ah! He forgot his password.
I am... I've had it set up so I can watch them behind here.
They're big and they're huge and they're going to go...
They're going to crawl in my mouth and lay eggs in my mouth and down my throat.
They're actually not kind of cool looking though.
I'm eating.
Oh, sorry guys. Let me watch the stream.
And talk about all these things that the guy that I'm watching can't eat.
Banana cream pie, pizza, go get a banana cream pie.
Sorry, I said a bug was going to lay eggs down my throat and ruin your meal.
Oh, boo hoo.
I saw at least 200 banana cream pies in chat.
And if you want to see more of these videos,
And if you happen to be one of those people that did not say banana cream pie and you were eating now,
I'm sorry. I do apologize.
But there's been a war going on here for the last like hour and 45 minutes.
I'm really sorry.
But yeah, bearded dragons are cool.
I'm still contemplating if I'm going to get one or not.
Trying to figure out exactly how that would work.
But they seem really fun. Seem like really interesting pets.
Iron clad beetles.
That's a really interesting hobby, though, to collect stuff like that and have pets like that.
To pets, as you say.
Thank you for the 300 bits.
Thank you, the wild ald, the wild ald, for the thousand bits.
Try not to look at chat. Best part of this game is figuring it out.
Yeah, it's true.
But if I get stuck in the village, I need you to tell me where the mayor's house is.
Otherwise, I'm going to be walking in a circle for 30 straight minutes.
And I don't want to do that.
I did say that backseating was okay for the streams.
Just because it's one of those...
It's one of those wiki games where this stuff you just kind of...
If you don't know, then you just might be in trouble.
Is that incorrect? Is it not?
Like if I sold something that was wrong,
then later on I could use it for something else.
This is 100% a game I would play with like 10 wiki tabs open.
The game even says in the beginning,
open up a wiki tab to help you,
because it's not going to hold your hand, but a wiki will.
That was part of the fine print at the bottom.
No, backseating is okay for these streams.
Just because I sometimes, especially with a game like this,
I do run into a wall a few times and I need to be nudged in the right direction.
So it's all good.
But the wild ald said,
1,000 bits in a row.
So that's 2,000 bits from the wild ald.
They say, this is my jam. I believe it was acid bass.
It's a great song.
I think I got it all.
Strength, intelligence, agility, friendship.
You know, I'm very much a friendship kind of person.
I can read at at least the 9th or 10th grade level.
It's probably me.
Devakitty, thanks for the 250.
Jerma, the big dogs are easy enough. You just need to stop losing your cool.
Whenever you miss any attack, you instantly get as tilted
as the fucking leaning tower of pizza.
Pizza.
Not pizza.
I know, but that's why I need you guys to backseat and help me sometimes.
Because, I don't know, I just...
Pizza's on the mind.
Banana cream pizza.
I wonder if I could make like a low FODMAP pizza.
It would have to be with like a fake crust.
Not real pizza crust.
A sauce that didn't have any garlic in it.
And just cheddar cheese all over it. It would be gross.
Nevermind.
Spooky Spitfire says, thanks for 250.
They say, Jerma, why aren't you able to eat anything?
I've been on a low FODMAP diet because
I've been having some annoying symptoms that won't go away.
And they may or may not even be related to my
intestinal irritable bowel disease.
We don't know.
I may have developed more stuff since cresting over like 32, 33 years old.
I have no idea.
So we're doing a low FODMAP diet for like a few weeks.
And we're gonna see what happens.
I don't think I want to do that.
Yeah, FODMAP. Essentially it is a fermentable carbohydrate
from my understanding that is in fructose.
High fructose corn syrup is, I may as well be drinking poison
if I have a FODMAP intolerance.
Also, garlic and onions are absolute zero.
Cannot have them ever. And that's the worst part.
Garlic is in everything. Onion is in everything.
Even if it's not physically on your plate, it is somehow in a seasoning blend.
That's why I can't really eat out right now.
Onion and garlic are, garlic is seriously one of my favorite foods on Earth.
So unfortunate. Can't eat garlic.
It is an incredibly concentrated place where FODMAPs come from.
Time just to, I can eat lettuce and meat.
It's kind of like a low carb diet, but you're not allowed to have onions and garlic.
So a lot of bread is off the table.
A lot of dairy is off the table.
A lot of, I can be one of those people that eats
a hamburger with a fork and a knife.
I can have a patty and cheese with like mayo on it.
And maybe a little bit of mustard and eat it with a fork and a knife.
It's kind of like a low carb, no bread sort of thing.
And no garlic and no onions. And no fructose. No fructose corn syrup.
I can eat sugar though, so that's okay. So we'll see what happens.
I'm gonna let my doctor help me out here and we'll see what he does.
Hey, let's put the credits on the screen.
Thank you everybody. All the subs.
We'll see you tomorrow. Here they come.
And sign in to confirm your age needs to get off the screen as well.
Because that's, well I don't know why that's still here. This movie sucks.
But anyways, thank you CVFD721.
Thank you CVFD.
For 2500 bits.
$25 total here from CVFD.
They say, yo Jerma, just want to say thank you for helping me and plenty of others
get through the monotonous grind of work.
I feel pretty good. I feel pretty good.
But thank you so much for the 2500 bits.
If you got me on at work, just don't get fired.
Because I've said like I shit in my diaper and stuff before.
Just make sure you have headphones in. Don't accidentally have your chair get caught
and pull the headphones out and it's like I shit in a diaper.
And then all of a sudden all your coworkers are looking at you.
I've said that exact phrase probably 6 or 7 times.
So at that point I've said on stream and on camera
16 to 17 billion words.
So how many words are in I just shit in a...
I just shit in a diaper. 6.
So 6, 12, 18, 24, 32.
So you're talking about there's a chance.
Maybe like 42, 45 out of 17 or 18 billion.
So it's still possible. Be careful.
Apple Shift, thanks for the 250.
Hey, since Halloween is around the corner, do you believe in ghosts? If so, have you ever seen one?
I do not believe in ghosts.
Or what most people think of when they think of a ghost.
I remember watching somebody talk about this before.
I think there was like a comedian or somebody that talked about this.
But it's true. If there were ghosts, where are they all going to go?
You know how many hundreds and hundreds of millions of people
that have passed away?
There are billions of people that have probably died.
Are they just walking around in your house?
Walking around as a ghost?
That would mean that not everyone becomes a ghost.
Well, why do you become a ghost?
What makes you allowed to be a ghost?
They watch over you.
Let's just say like my great-great-grand-papa is watching over me right now.
Is his great-great-great-grand-papa watching over him too?
Like in the same spot?
Making sure he doesn't screw up?
No, he went to the afterlife.
How long do you have to watch somebody before you get to go?
Is that part of the criteria? You have to watch for like 20 years?
You have to tag out. You have to tag out.
I don't want to do that.
That does not sound like a great time to me.
So my great-grand-child, I'm sitting there to watch him?
What about like 2.30 in the morning when they're in the bathroom
eating boogers and they're like 40?
Do I have to watch that?
Do I have to watch every time that my great-great-great-grand-nephew
the grandson goes to the bathroom?
Do I just not? No, no, no.
He's like taking a dump down there. I clock out.
Alright, I'm going to clock out for like 10 minutes.
You only get one break or two breaks during the day.
You come back and they're still taking a shit.
You're like, god damn it.
You have to go sleep?
You have to go to bed. You don't sleep?
You have to watch that person sleeping all night.
Got news for you. There ain't no Nintendo Switch up there.
It's you and binoculars looking at your great-great-grandson sleeping.
You don't get to go to sleep?
Oh, and he's watching over me.
You hear like a gust of wind.
That was him. He's telling me something.
I heard the wind gust at the door at the bathroom.
Yeah, it's called get out of the bathroom. I'm trying to get you to do something else.
You know those house noises you hear that are like...
That's your great-great-grandfather trying to get you to do something else.
Because you're boring the shit out of him.
What kind of house do you live in?
You know, there's lightning outside.
That's somebody's great-great-great-grandfather annoyed
that they've been in the bathroom for too long.
Okay, we have to move on.
It's gone. It's gone. It went there.
I was trying to avoid it, but it went there. I gotta move on.
The great-great-great-grandfather won't even understand what a phone is.
You're like, no one's gonna tell them.
Who's gonna tell them what a phone is?
Imagine like your great-great-great-great caveman grandfather.
No, he's gonna be swinging his club around up there
trying to like hit your great-great-great like
one grandfather with like a club.
This gets chaos up there. You don't know what a phone is.
They all have to teach each other everything again.
You have to teach the great-great-great caveman grandfather
all of human history for them to understand.
And then you need to be taught by the person
in front of you a generation what television is.
I do not envy that situation.
Constant conflict up in guardian ghost land.
What is cloud gaming?
Cloud gaming? What cloud gaming?
Me hit rabbit in head with club.
Okay. Did you spin that guy around
and like make him walk in another direction?
Just go that way for like 400,000 miles
because distance is completely relative.
It does not even exist.
You could have great-great-great-great-great caveman.
I'm not gonna add very much to the conversation,
so just point him in a direction and tell him to walk
and tell him that there's like a nice, crunchy rabbit
like 200 million miles that way.
At least he'll get some peace and quiet for a while.
You assume he can understand.
Well, at some point, this has got to be like a mutiny.
They've got to get rid of him.
I would assume they have some type of hierarchy.
The caveman is gonna be the first one,
so there's gonna be like an uprising,
and they'll just find a way to get rid of him.
It would be the oldest. That's exactly what I'm saying.
They would not have any time at all to watch over you
because great-great-great caveman grandfather
is gonna tell everybody they need to find pebbles
and trade teeth and stuff, and they're not gonna have time
to watch you go to the bathroom and kill him again.
They kill him again, and he goes up another level.
It's like Inception. He goes up another level.
They're killing each other up there.
What? Getting even stronger.
Anyways, thank you to Cyrus Dexter
for the 251 bits. Appreciate it.
And Apple Shift, thanks for the 250.
And no, I do not believe in ghosts in the traditional sense.
I mean, could there be such thing as like a spirit
or a soul or something that electromagnetically
is still around after a while and maybe like after a while?
I don't know, guys. I'm of the opinion that it's possible
that when you die, you know, when you dream,
your brain activity slows down, right, to a point
where I might think about this.
If your brain activity slows down to a point
where it's so slow and you're shutting down,
10 minutes in real life might be like 6,000 years.
You might live like 50,000 more lifetimes
in like a dream world because your brain is slowing down so much.
That might happen. This is a Black Mirror episode.
I don't know. I don't know.
What if your head is destroyed? That's the thing.
Time is relative to when that person is experiencing time.
Because, well, let's say you go have surgery, right?
When you go get put under by, you know, the anesthesiologist,
oh, hey, okay, it's time for me to do this.
I just woke up. 12 hours may have gone by.
Time is relative to who is experiencing it.
So who's to say that if your brain activity slows down,
10 minutes could be just 10 hours to you.
So by the time that they actually bring you to where,
a funeral home or crematorium,
you're talking about it could be like a couple of days,
which could be 200 to 300 years.
I'm going right for the caveman, I'll tell you.
I'm sprinting at caveman.
I'm going to be the new king up there.
It's going to be hard though because there's going to be
like 5,000 other people there.
Just like, it's going to be like a train.
You're going to be like on a train.
I'm going to be the king of ghost land. Yes, you'll see.
Banana, banana.
I have to go. Banana crematorium pie.
Nice, okay.
Thank you archive.png for the thousand bits.
They say, hey, Jerma, I've been starting making an archive
of your streams, which has the chat in view.
I've got 16 full streams with the chat up so far.
Right now, these archives aren't worth that much to anyone,
but I think there might be a lot of people who are glad
they can watch old Jerma streams and see the chat in the future.
Gives you an additional perspective on the streams at least.
You can find this archive by searching it on YouTube
and by sorting by date, by the way.
There is a channel that archives every stream I've ever done,
but they don't do the chat on it.
He's going to take it down.
I think you overestimate how much I care about that.
There is an archive channel that actually does that,
but not with the chat, I don't think.
There is a Jerma Streams archive.
Mean to him? What? No.
I'm just, I'm saying that I'm, that doesn't bother me.
It's not like a, wait, hold on a minute.
You're taking my content
and you're putting it up on your channel?
I'll take it down. They're monopolizing my humor.
They're monopolizing off of my humor.
More of my royalties!
Because I know what YouTube pays.
If I was to really go after somebody
for potentially making, like,
let's say a video like that got, like,
five to, like, three, four, five thousand views,
am I really going to go after somebody
for, like, fucking three dollars?
Probably. Yes. Yes.
That's McChicken money.
That's one of the, like, the whole, well,
copyright infringement and copy striking
and content ID and stuff.
It's like, really, do you, like,
that seems like way too much effort to
try to spend, like, sixty days
to make, like, twelve dollars.
YouTube does not pay what it used to.
Depends on the context.
Okay, right. So, let me give you an example.
If somebody were to make a video of my voice
doing something terrible, or
making it look like I did something
or said something that I didn't do that was incredibly awful,
like, actually crossing the line for something,
like, truly crossing the line, and you all know
what the things I could be referring to.
And that video had a shitload of views.
It would be like, okay, what do I do here?
Deep fake of you eating boogers.
But, no, if, if, let's put it this way,
if somebody were to ever make a video
about, like, my stream or something,
or me, or, like, you,
look, this, I have no leg to stand on here.
I, I put out into the wild
six straight hours of green screen footage.
Am I, you're gonna, I think I'm gonna, I'm gonna
copyright strike people?
It's over, at this point.
I royalty free threw out
a half a day's worth of green screen stuff
which, by the way, I guess I'll announce it right now.
I'm gonna get back in front of that screen very soon.
We're gonna do, we're gonna do part two.
Too much interesting stuff has come out of that
that it would be a shame if I didn't add DLC, right?
Free DLC, by the way.
It's just gonna put it up again.
So we'll do, after Halloween,
we will compile some more stuff
that you guys want me to do
in front of that screen, and I'll do another, like,
four, five, six hours in front of the green screen.
But no, I've, that doesn't, I don't,
that does not bother me. I don't, that doesn't,
I don't get into that.
If you want to make a video or something
on something that I've done or said
or you want to use green screen footage,
that's your shit. Like, I don't,
that doesn't bother me. It's not like, oh, well,
hold on a minute, dear.
I don't want you to use that JoJo dance
in that video.
But, that kind of
goes all around in a circle there.
No, I have an
archive channel. I don't have one,
but I have, like, a sort of unofficially
yesed
on an archive channel.
If they don't do chat, maybe
it'll be worth seeing if
people really want that that badly
or should the streams on that
archive stay that way? We want
chat. We want it.
Well, let me
ask a question or two.
Am I gonna stream
the entire green screen? Yeah.
Like we did last time.
The exact same thing we did last time, but just a bunch
of new actions. Thank you,
Produce, Produces
San, or Produce
Sasan. Thanks for the thousand bits.
I'm not kidding. You, the
first stream I ever saw of yours was the carnival stream,
so I'm relatively new. Welcome,
first of all, if you're still here. But I've known
about you for a while thanks to Joel and Vinny.
You three have been keeping me going these past couple
months. It's been rough trying to figure out where I
am in life, but you making me laugh is
more than enough to let me know it's gonna be alright.
Thank you for even stopping by this channel.
The other two people that you
mentioned there are absolutely fantastic
streamers. They're
some of the best, I would say.
So thank you for even putting me into that
category with those two.
I'm glad you found the stream. Hopefully you have
fun here. Hopefully you have
enough laughs, enough
chill time here is really all
I want. So thank you.
And say hello to Vinny and Joel
for me. Next time you see them.
Phylacter Lich just gave
five thousand bits right now.
Fifty dollars Phylacter Lich.
Jerma, watch this video.
What's the over under that this is a
Jimmy Neutron video?
Fifty-fifty. This is a Source
Filmmaker video.
I should watch this video. What is
this? This Wonderwall?
I'm not old enough to watch this
video.
Fucking god.
...
Is this
the...
Can this get picked up by
the Content ID system on Twitch
because it's so fucked up?
Archive it quick before it gets muted!
Full house?
Nice.
Somebody said I missed the best part, so I went back to see the best part.
Oh, here's the link if you want to watch it. Trying to stay within terms of service.
Yeah, I'm trying to st- I'm trying. I am.
Dr. McNinja, thanks for the five community subs. Appreciate that. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Right at the end here.
Devikitty also gave 250. Hope that ancestors don't look over me when they're dead. I don't want some old fuck watching me
hanging out somewhere.
What if when you die you become a Twitch shatterer? Mugga ass.
And then dorkcube. Thanks dorkcube for the 250. I post this in the game recommendation channel,
but I wanted to send this directly to you.
Murder by numbers a murder mystery pick-ross game by the maker of Hatipful
Boyfriend. I do check the recommended every pretty much every two days and see what everybody has written. I will check this out, though.
The balacuola just came in with thousand bits. Hey, Jerma, watch this. They forgot the link. This is not how this works.
Okay. Well, I expect it. Nice.
Thank you for the $15.
What the hell. Okay. All right, I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Starting pretty much around the same time. We're gonna start with that jumpscare mansion game and however long I can stand that game,
we're gonna move on to
Darkwood again. Take care. Good night. Goodbye.
Why did I do that? I didn't even do change the scenes. I am so stupid. I'm terrible at this.
I gotta get better at that.
Anyways, good night. See you tomorrow guys. Take care. I just love you.