Okay, hi. So, I just wrote www.tv.tv. Oops. Hold on. Let me fix this.
www.tv.com. Whoever owns that domain, congratulations for the 500 trillion dollars
it took for somebody to buy that domain from you. What a shitty domain, too. Who cares?
Nobody's going to tv.com for any reason. The value of that domain was probably 50 million dollars.
In 2000. Not anymore. They sat on that for way too long if you didn't get rid of it.
Are you high? No. All right, let me just, let me tweet this. Hold on.
All right. Yakuza minigames. Pogchamp. All right, let's go.
How you doing? How's everybody doing today? Are we doing good? What are we looking at here?
All right, there's an image already. Get well. Oh, look at this. Really? Oh. Get well. Wish you
best soon. I'm going to put this on stream. This is cute. Well, thanks, guys. This is cute stuff.
I love the cute stuff. You see, this is a little get well card. Look at this. I don't deserve this.
Oh, this is cool. I thought that was a dick over there in the left. I'm not going to lie. I thought
that was just like a sagging dick with like one big ball, but it's a happy face. Don't be sexual.
Stop being sexual. I'm sorry, but I mean, you know what I'm saying? It's a little bit more
mature recently over the last few months, if you know what I'm saying. What does that say?
What does this say? Pog? Ipo happy. Oh, they're all... It's awesome. Thank you.
We're going to play more Yakuza and sorry if I sound sick. The thing happened where I got better.
I felt really fine last night and into this morning and I took a shower and then it got worse
and then it got better and then it got worse again. So don't mind me if I mute the microphone
sometimes and just like... It's probably going to happen. By the way, I just want to make sure
everybody knows this. If you weren't here the other day, I'm negative for COVID. I took a test
because, you know, if you're coughing, stuffy nose, headache, flu-like symptoms, it's like,
okay, I probably should get on top of this. No COVID. So that's pretty good, right? I'm happy
about that. So we'll just see how it goes. Odd bless. Yeah, I know, right? Yeah, we're going to
pick up right where we left off in Yakuza. I was in the middle of getting a potential bowling
girlfriend. So that's exciting. Very exciting stuff. I don't care about the story. I don't
care about the combat. I care about the bowling girlfriend. That's it. That's why I'm playing this
game a second time. Remember, do you like Yakuza? Yeah, it's pretty good. Why are you playing it
again? Well, you know... I require only one thing, okay? From in like a female interest.
And you want to come over and just like play Diablo 2 for like four hours or so and then
just like hang out, you know, whatever. That's all I require. That's the only thing I need.
That's it. Yeah, I heard about Vinny. That sucks. He'll be back though. He'll be back stronger than
ever. He'll be fine. He got a suspension. Yeah. He's showing potential nudity on stream. He'll be
back. I look forward to the next stream, Vinny. How could you not look forward to a Vinny stream?
They're all good. All right, let's go. He's not here. Well, he doesn't have to be here.
I like looked at like the viewer list. Is Vinny here? Oh, Vinny's awesome. He'll be back.
And I, how can I, why can this not work? No camera, right? No camera? Because I'm
naked. I'm not actually naked. I just don't have a top on because like fuck tops, right?
I wear bottoms. I don't wear tops. What the hell am I doing? Uh, what? Hello? Video game?
Video game? Um, I'd like to. All right, let's get back into Yakuza. I want to do mini games. I don't
really care about playing the game. Oh, if you missed it, we got a couple of dragons last time.
A couple of lizards. Uh, where's the health one? Oh, here we go. So I can send these to my item box,
right? How do I do that? Opponents? What the hell is all this? This is not bowling. Valuables.
Go to club sunshine. Hold on. I will. What was the next thing I had to do?
Wasn't it just have fun a bunch of times? Enjoy erotic videos. All right. Is this actually erotic
videos? What am I going to get banned? It's like, Oh, Vinnie got banned earlier for like nudity.
Like here. Am I going to, should I get banned too? Do I do it? What is going on with my controller?
Stop. What happened? Why does this thing suck? Oh, hold on. Can I ask you a few questions? All
right. We got stop, stop by a police officer. Stop and search, huh? This is the music. What's
your name and what do you do for a living? The name's Kiru. I'm in a hurry here and I'm also in
a hurry to read the fact that we've got five community subs from head full of crap. Thank you.
Head full of crap. Appreciate that. Excellent. Well, we've had some trouble around these parts.
Just to be sure. Would you mind if I checked your belongings? My thing's going to do with any trouble
around here. Relax. It's just a precaution. Can you show me what you're carrying?
All right. Is it more embarrassing to have a bunch of like lizard toys or Coke?
From the, you know what I mean? Like, why do you have like four lizard toys?
Okay. You win. What should I hand over? I mean, should I give them the lizard toy? All right. Here.
How about this? This is what I have. Hmm. This is about as safe as it gets. It doesn't look like
you're carrying anything dangerous here. Take this back. I got nothing to hide. Did he expect
me to hand him a gun or something? He didn't search me. He just said, hey, could you present
me with something? What? I could have had, what am I going to hand him the drugs in my pocket?
Thank you for your cooperation. Give me a break. Cops like you are always abusing your power.
You never stop to think about how much of an inconvenience this is for regular citizens.
Well, that may be so for other police officers. Not for me though. I'm only doing this because
it's all good. It's all I'm good for. Huh? What do you mean? Oh, never mind about me.
I'm the one asking the questions here. Huh? It doesn't make sense. I was sure you had something
big on you. I've got a nose for these things. Well, I guess your nose failed you this time.
By the way, is your nose broken? No. What the fuck? My sixth sense tells me I'll find something huge
if I dig deep enough. I don't know what to say. Why does that keep happening? I'm a pro at
stopping searches until I'm sure you're not a threat. I'm going to keep questioning you, okay?
Not okay. Oh, come on, Kiryu-san. Be a good sport. It won't take long. I just want to be sure.
I give up. Fine. Have it your way. Just keep it short. I mean, we'll keep it really short.
I'm trying to get into the porn theater. Come on. All right. Thank you. My name is Officer
Kikuchi. I'll see you around. Oh, I'm a friendship with Officer Kikuchi.
You got to know Officer Stop and Search Kikuchi. Interacting with him will gradually fill the
friendship gauge. You can check the status of this gauge at any time in the pause menu.
Build your friendship with Officer Kikuchi and see what happens. No, I don't think I will.
All right, porn theater. Do you bowl? If you bowl, then you and I are going to be good friends.
No, I'm not. Is this bad? You're going to watch Attack on Titan? Oh, shit. That's right. It comes
back. That's right. Isn't it like, yeah, maybe. Is it okay? At Gandhara, you can watch videos of
varied cast of gorgeous girls. As you meet these women out in the city under certain conditions,
new video content will be available. Search every corner of town to find your dream girl.
Hey, S. Ducks, thanks for the ten committed subs. That's a lot of money. Thank you. We charge
eight hundred dollars for one view. You're gonna actually stop Omega Lo. All right, I'm gone.
You're gonna get banned. Okay, I'm not gonna get banned. No, I'm not gonna get banned. I'm not
gonna see anything. All right, let's go. What's next on the list of things to do? It's soft core
porn. Okay. Well, you said the word porn. No, no, no, dude, don't worry. It's okay. It's soft core
porn. It's you said porn. Oh, shit. It's got histamine. Wait, because I bumped into him.
Nice. You can skip it if you have to. Yeah, let me skip it. Violence good, boobies bad. Hey,
I don't make the rules. All right, I just have to live by them. Yes, I know. I understand. I can
gouge a guy's eyes out with a knife in a horror game and pulls eyes out and eat him and squishes
blood will shoot out of the sides of my mouth and then I can like throw that guy off a cliff
and watch his body fucking roll and smash into rocks and his head smashes on the rock and the
back of his head explodes and then I climb down there like Gollum and I eat his brains and then
shit on him. But if like a nipple shows up on I got in trouble. I know I get it. I understand.
Look, I don't make the rules. Oh, wait, it's this guy again. I just walked around the circle.
What should I hand over? Oh, how about um, no, I don't want to give him my rare toys.
I don't have a gun. Oh, here. Oh, this looks really dangerous. What do you use this for?
It's not dangerous at all. Everyone carries around that sort of thing.
No, they don't. I'm beginning to suspect you might be a threat to public safety.
Kira-san, tell me what it's for. It's complicated. It is a very specific use.
And what would that be? You know, it's a little embarrassing so I didn't want to have to say it.
It's actually for. Yes. What happened? What are they doing? I've never heard about that before.
I guess I've led a sheltered life. What is that implying? I've used a gun?
I still get the feeling you're not being completely honest.
But you can go. Are we not friends? Oh, no, we're not friends.
All right, what am I supposed to be doing? I gotta go to the store.
I gotta buy some stuff. All right, let's go to the drugstore. Oh, shit.
I'm gonna go beast mode on this one. What's the graph for beast mode again? Holy shit.
That was awesome. You're not under any circumstances play Mahjong.
I'm going to. Unlike a lot of probably streamers that you've seen play this game,
I know how to play Mahjong. I used to play it back in like 1996 on my old Windows 95 PC.
I know how to play Mahjong. Oh, why would I not play it?
Oh, this gives me a health boost. I'll take it.
The different Mahjong. I mean different. It's not the same Mahjong. What? It's different,
like solitaire different to what? Why would they do that? I only know how to play Mahjong classic.
What's that? What am I actually? How am I supposed to? How do I progress the game?
Can I pick him up off the ground? I can. What the fuck? I can pick him up by the legs.
And I can do like a bam bam. Oh, shit. Hold on. All right. If you see a guy walking at you with
a bike, I think you turn around and run. Because regardless of this person is strong,
it doesn't matter how tough this guy is. They're holding a bike in their hands in the air.
Oh, shit. Go back to the videos. You're a coward. Coward? Coward? You're saying I'm a coward?
What's what's what are we doing? What's what's this? What's going on here? Wait.
I like beast mode, but brawler is probably my favorite. Okay, I got four, three million.
Okay, hold on. A mighty knee strike. Old Y. Okay, that's cool. Max health. I'll take it. Yeah,
too bad. Max health. Go back to when I where I learned beast style.
Beast is the best. Beast is the best. 5% completion. Oh, my goodness. Wait, where's
the bowling alley? I want to go bowl. I go back to where I learned beast mode. I don't know what
that was. Best automatically picks up beast, picks up heavy items in the bowling alley.
Is it near the bowling alley? This is over here. Okay, I'll go to bowling alley. Yeah,
I'm not opening any links for at least the next 30 to 40 minutes. Understand? No links for 40 to
30 to 40 minutes. Beast mode is really fun. It's a big cleave. It's too slow, though.
It's back against the big bar. Oh, my goodness. That was horrible.
Oh, fuck. I'm sorry.
That's instantly dead. There's so many instant kill moves here. All right, bowling alley. Let's
go. And I'm gonna go visit my bowling alley and my bowling alley friend. Okay, so by the bowling
alley. This is where we did the advice for the band. Let me just see how she's doing. You know,
let me just check in on her. Wrong way. Let me see how she's doing. Okay, I got to act natural.
I came here specifically because I wanted to see her, right? I only came here to see her. But
what do we have on the street here? We have a drugstore. We have a video store. Okay,
I got to go into the video store. I got to go to the drugstore. I got to make sure I have a
bag that has the drugstore's name on it, right? Like, okay, CVS. I have a CVS bag and I'm holding
it with the logo out. Just get a fucking coconut water. Who cares? I got to walk in here with the
CVS bag facing her. Hey, what the fuck? What is going on here? Oh, yeah, I'm CVS. Yeah,
I was getting coconut water. I was on my break and just popping in. You're a serial killer. What?
What are you talking about? No, not. Oh, CVS. What? That's Dennis. What do you mean,
Dennis? And then I tap on the ... No, excuse me. Hold on a minute. Me and her are in a very, very ...
We're talking and we're hanging out. She's like, come back and see me. Come back and see me,
right? But I got to make it ... Look, I went to CVS, right? Come on. She wanted me. She told me to
come back five times. She's like, come back and see me. Come back and see me. I'm going to come
back and see you, but I went to CVS first, right? I just slam dunk you in fucking bowling.
Oh, yeah. I got time for a game. Oh, you're on break from work. You just went to CVS,
but you got time for a game? I mean, yeah, I do. Of course I do.
Where do you work? Oh, I mean, in here and there. A job. A lot of jobs, you know.
I'm on break. I'm on break for four hours. She's going to tell me to come back tomorrow. She's
going to say, hey, come back and see me tomorrow. And we're like, oh, yeah. You know, if I'm in the
area, I'm going to show up with like a bag of ... With a bag of like takeout. With a bunch of
food in my mouth. I was just getting takeout down street. I'm in the area. You wanted a baseball?
Ooh, that was bad. She's trying. Yeah. No. Okay. Excuse me. Me and her,
I've made it very clear that we're like trying ... We're like, want to talk to each other.
Let her win. Should I? All right. Is it too obvious if I just do this?
No, she'll think you're weak. She laughed. Yeah. Stop saying simp. I didn't say simp. You did. Who
is doing that? Stop saying that. God, she sucks. You have to rush her. No, I'm not going to just ...
I want it to be like fun. I just want to have fun. It's a close game. Oh, yeah. Let's go.
I can't wait till she shows up at like my work with like a bag of Doritos with like
the Doritos logo facing out. Sponsored. No. How would you be sponsored in like
just a regular day to day? What? A sponsored date? I think at that point, why do I feel like some
influencers do that? I just want to make sure ... Are you okay with that? This is a sponsored
date. Are you okay with me having like different logos, all these different toys and stuff around
the dinner table? I got sponsored by Hasbro. I have to like always carry around the toys with me.
Do you have to do that here? Yeah. It's part of the contract. Even when there's no cameras on?
Yeah. How will they know if you don't? Manly voice. My manly voice is like this. Okay. Did I
start talking like this more often? I'm not going to look at chat, but what I want someone to do
is I want them to count how many times the word stop in all capitals has been spammed.
I'm not going to keep track. I'm not going to look. I'm going to say two or 3000 times.
Something like that. I don't know. Whatever. I don't care. You think I care about that?
No. Why would I even look? I don't care. And time. Okay. How many times it was said?
Oh, an event is scheduled to take place at Mock Bowl. Your friendship with Emery will not increase
until then. You need to make progress with Kamarucha Real Estate Royale for the next event to start.
Unlocked as you... All right. Let's go. Okay. I got to go to the Real Estate Royale.
How do I do this shit? It's not unlocked. It's chapter five. Are you kidding me? It's like
chapter two right now. All right. How do I progress the story? Turn around. Do the story,
you cuck. Really? You're going to call me... Really? Well, now you're in big trouble. Now
you've lost a little bit of privileges here. I wish I could... You know what? You know what
I wish you could do on Twitch? I don't want to ban you. I don't want to ban you. I want to like
make it so you can't write the word cuck on this stream for like an hour. So you'll be like,
oh, whatever you say, cuck. Wait, it didn't work. I just blacked it out. Why? No, I want to say that
word. I want to just remove words from your vocabulary like that. You know what I mean?
You're not banned. You can stay. You can't say that anymore. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, ladies.
Ladies, I'm sorry. You can just blacklist the word yourself. Oh yeah, I can do that. No,
but I just want to make sure that person can't say it. And everybody else can spam it, but they can't.
All right, how do I play the game? How do I progress the story down the alley?
Oh shit, this is Yakuza. All right, let's bike somebody in the head. Come on. Come on. Come on.
All right. And you missed. Can I throw him up the stairs? No. Imagine getting thrown.
How do you go up the stairs instead of down the stairs? That would be worse than falling down the
stairs. Hey there, buddy. Been looking for you. You again. Got a lot of nerves showing up now.
What do you want? I think it's pretty clear what I want. Time to pay your protection money, pal.
If you're doing business in Komurocho, you're doing business with us.
The hell with that. It's not protection money if I don't show up to actually protect me when I need
it. And you have the gall to ask me for more? When you need it? What are you talking about?
I'm talking about Tachibana real estate. When they came and chased me out,
you people were nowhere in sight. Some protection. Tachibana? What? Oh, Tachibana real estate. Yeah.
They're, uh, look, it's complicated. Complicated my ass. You got scared and ran away.
What could be simpler? Scared? What? What do you think? Thanks to you, I had to relocate.
Now I'm scrambling to get new customers to make up for all these ones I lost
and pay you even if I wanted to. I think you better keep that attitude in check, asshole.
Mind if I cut in? Huh? What do you want? Who are you? What family are you with?
I'm not in anybody's family. Pipe down. It's this guy I'm talking to. So he said it's a four kids
dub. Excuse me? What do you want from me? You say you opened shop here because Tachibana
real estate forced you out at your last location. Is that right? Oh, I see what this is. You're
trying to be this guy's new muscle. Oh, hell no. What? Our family's handled this cafe's protection
for 30 years. You try to swoop in on our turf, it'll mean war. Look, looks like you might need
some convincing to stay quiet while I speak to the owner here. Shut your mouth and try me. I'll kill
you. Go, go, go. Hey, Rainbow, thanks for the vibe. Give you a dirty job. Ooh. God, you just got
triple quadruple summers off him. Saying words to make the YouTube video more funny.
Saying words that are out of context to make the YouTube video funnier.
You've just got Slam-a-lam-a-ding-dong on your skull, Camarito. Say hello for the glass, ass.
Let's do it again on his little mouth. This time hit him right in the mouth.
You're my favorite YouTuber. Hey, thanks. Appreciate that. Thank you. I'm serious.
Ned Flanders? What the hell? I'm not losing to some kid. You just did. Now get lost and don't show
your face around this guy's shop again. Damn it. This ain't over. Why do we all, why do we talk the
same? God doesn't even realize. We all talk like this. You know what I mean? What the fuck is he
talking about? We can finally talk in peace. So, what in the end are you just talking in this place
as this guy squeezed me for protection, huh? Can you just leave me alone? I already said it wasn't
like that. I'm not even Yakuza. I'd just really like to talk for a minute. Talk about what? Not you
bound in real estate. Doing a little investigation. And I'd like to tell me if you know anything.
Anything's fine. What I know isn't a hell of a lot. Besides, I'd prefer never to deal with
those guys again. They're terrifying. Terrifying how? Too much CVT. Stop doing the H1, Z1 voice?
I'm doing the, I'm a, I'm like a character in a television show that's animated and full of
people. Ask me for the play, kid. Hey, thanks for the five community subs. Appreciate it.
You know, I haven't said that in probably seven years. PBS four kids animated voice. Well, let
me pay attention. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. Leave me alone. Leave me alone. Where would I go if I
want to meet the guy from Tachibana's office who paid you that visit? Probably still there,
finishing what they started. Still where? Fuck, I'm still doing it. I'm sick though. It's my
excuse to talk like this because like I can do it today. I can't do it any other day because I'm not
sick. Ooh, okay. They drove most of the tenants out. The place is practically empty. And he's still
there. Probably. They're making him all kinds of sweet deals, but he turned down every last one.
He's still there now. Tachibana's boys will be too. Go have a look if you really want to get
mixed up with them. Okay, thanks. Appreciate it. Tachibana's been running tenants out of the Hakua
building on Shichifuku Street. It's worth checking out. Thanks for the info. I just turned,
I turned and not paying attention, just turned and just hit my head square into this thing
and fall flat on my back and in a coma for the rest of the game. I've literally done that. I've
too. How many times have you guys in your own house somehow taken a corner too sharply
and just your shoulder just smashes into the corner like of the doorway? Yeah, it happens. It sucks.
But then you get really annoyed with yourself because you're like I live here. How do I not
know how to do these corners correctly? Oh my God. Hard door, hard door, hard door.
All right, come here. Hard door. Beast car door. All right, let him go. Come here. I got like stuck
on the whatever. I grabbed him over here and I couldn't like push him back and then he got away.
And then like my controller got like locked. You get this. This is a game where you get like stuck
on stuff. Notice that it's very, it's very like clingy. And here we go.
No sticky keys? No. What if I need them? Hmm. Here we go. I can like, I can mute the microphone
and cough like 10 minutes straight. I'll be right back. Okay, hi. Okay, who's in here? I get some
story. I run the place. Wait, is this the bathroom? Why is he like opening the door like he's sitting
on the toilet? Like get out here. I'll drop you out of the building. Okay, I'll take care of that.
What is this? Hold on here. I don't even know why I'm laughing. It doesn't make any sense.
Off your phone? I'm not on my phone.
I don't want to rate Twitter. Like I don't want to rate the app. Like fuck off.
It's been like seven years since I've owned this. Like if I haven't done it yet, I'm not going to.
Streaming, shouting, pissing the halls.
Can't put the phone down to stream. Yes, I just did. I just have to check my notifications, man.
Oh, I can't wait to drag somebody's head across that bar.
He just opened that like there was a bee in his room. He just like just opened a door and run.
Eventually, maybe he'll leave.
So
Irma hair? Not anymore.
It's like the exact same haircut I had like a year ago.
Oh shit.
How much is that?
Oh shit, he's giving it back.
Oh shit.
Another two million. It's like Oprah. He's just going to be like are we going to get cars too?
Oh, it's the money that you lost at baseball.
Wait, was it a debate?
Wasn't even real.
I have 20 million dollars in brawler. What are you a rush guy looks like.
He pushes me really fucking hard.
Russia's op was fucked. So I picked the wrong one.
Fetish stream.
Sorry, I laughed when he left.
But I'm I like brawler mode.
Oh shit, this is ugly.
Guys, hold on. I play in the bathtub. I was just rinsing my hair.
I just said I've had the conditioner in for the last 51 minutes.
I'm just shaking up a drink. I have a little drink here. I have like a little. I need to get. I don't know. Whatever. Don't leave me alone. Watch the game. I'm coughing.
Okay, I'm trying to be cool.
How did I do that? I just like shook up a drink and got like embarrassed that you heard it.
Let me pay attention. Hold on. Leave me alone. You're gonna be in big trouble.
Close chat during Kai Canyon.
I read what somebody said.
Okay, real estate company willing to make an enemy of the.
Of the Tojo clan, the owner of Cafe Blend may have been right about them being worse than the Yakuza.
I want a bit more info. Hopefully I can track down those other homeless guys in this neighborhood.
Usually see them hanging around Park Boulevard and maybe I'll start there.
Find the homeless men flat on back.
Old material. It was like 20 minutes ago.
It's not old material if it happens in the same stream. It's a closed environment here.
Get me this. Nice heat mode.
Fuck, that happened so quickly. I don't even know what's going to happen. Use the railing.
All right, let's go. Come here. Did it work?
Yeah, come here. Yeah. Corner of the railing. Holy shit, that was a cool move.
He's crazy strong. I am. Hey, I have to ask you guys a couple of questions.
If I did, I'd be doing them myself. Speaking of, I hear Saku-san just got back from that
gig for a touch about real estate. Serious? Lucky bastard. You think he'd cut me in on
some of that if I asked him? Who knows? Can't hurt to ask. I guess he's probably over at
Public Park 3 with his buddies. I just had like a funnel in my ear leaning.
Hmm. Stop eating spaghetti in the bathtub. Why would I eat spaghetti in the bathtub?
It's me. Yeah, it's me. What do you want?
Oh, come on. Who am I? Hey! Oh shit, I thought this guy was attacking me.
Like, come on, dude. Please. You're too close to the fight.
You eat spaghetti in the bathtub? I don't. I feel like that's like a weird YouTube video
you watched where it was like I made a bathtub with spaghetti sauce and like ate spaghetti
in the bathtub with this with the tomato sauce or something. Oh, not this guy again.
No, just get away from me. Here. Look, I have a- here, look. Isn't this cute? You made that
video. No, I didn't. I made a video where like- I made a video where I sat on a gun in the bath.
Different. This is about as safe as it gets. It doesn't look like you're carrying anything
dangerous. In the bathtub when I have like the TF2 video. How many- wait, how many of you guys
have like never seen any of my videos before? What's like the over-under of how many people
are here? You made videos? Tons of them. Hundreds of them, dude. Kicked somebody's bike. Sorry.
Come here. Come here. He did- he went- he hit his head on something. Why did he hit his head on?
I just unplugged that guy from his internet. Somebody's pulled the ethernet cable out when
he ran at me. Actually, I gotta save the game. Geez. Do the RC car racing? Ending machine. Yes,
sure. You pay 10,000 yen. Inokitake. Cool. I ate it? Inokitake mushrooms are recommended by
mushroom suppliers. Cool. All right, I used it. I have to- where's my item box? Get rid of this
stuff. What is this? Tissues? All right, where's this pocket racing game you're talking about?
Do pocket racers? Is there a drug store in here? Sorry. I'll take a beef bottle down here.
The north top left of the map? Okay. You just ate mushrooms, now you want more drugs. Yeah,
whatever. Okay, north- north left. North left of map. Batting center. Disco. I don't have it. I
don't think I have it unlocked. No, I don't- I don't have that yet. You think if you made the
exact same sound as the person that just got bumped, if it was like somebody running down the
street they bumped into you and the person went, oh yowzers! And then they bumped into you and you
went, oh yowzers! You think you'd look at each other? Be like, dude, you- you're- do you want
to hang out? I feel like we kind of get each other somehow.
Was this supposed to be a sweet little year-end bonus this calls for toast?
Yeah, we deserve to forget all the bad crap for one day. Let's live it up. Eat your shit together.
Stop eating a candlelit dinner in the bathtub. Do not tell me how to live my life. I can do
whatever I want. I can do whatever the fuck I want. I can eat a candlelit dinner in the bathtub if I
feel like it. How is that hurting you? How does that hurt you? How does that hurt you? In no way
does it affect you. You can do whatever the fuck I want. What? Hmm. If only I had some booze that
thought right out. If you're that eager to chat, buy us around. Sure, let's go. Let's do it.
Put the fuck up with dumbass boys references.
Hold on a second, folks. Ladies and gentlemen, um, you don't- that's a good show.
If you haven't seen the boys yet, fucking watch it. Like, it's a really cool- it's a good show.
It's based on a- I mean, no, no, it's not a good show. I don't like that show. I don't like the
boys. Well, I do. Comics are good, too. Yeah, I might read them. Great acting. It's like,
it's really, really all over the place. It's really, like, dark and gritty and- yeah,
oh, you said the Reddit word. It's like, dark and gritty show. Excuse me. Excuse me.
No, it's actually- well, jokes aside, it's a really good show. It's just fun to watch.
Um, Anthony Starr better get the, uh, like, an Emmy because, like, he's fucking fantastic.
Anthony Starr? Yeah, he's fantastic. He's really fun to watch. I'm being dead serious. All right,
we gotta bring him some booze. Do I have- can I just buy booze? This is a bit. Don't fall for it.
It's not a bit. All right, let's go. Let's go. Beer's easy. They sell it everywhere. Let's go get a
bunch of beer. Okay, uh, soba noodles burger shop? Wait, there's a- this- wait,
there's cheeseburgers in the game. Hold on, I didn't even see that. Talk to all of them.
All right, so you want a beer. You want a beer? What do you want? Uh, sweet potato sochu mood.
Somebody write that down. Potato sochu. Sweet potato sochu is the only sochu worth drinking.
You're one of those kids who only drinks beer. You gotta expand your horizons. You'll never get
a woman. All right, so we're getting a coke for you. Something like sake to warm you up
in the winter. Sake is that- what was that blinking over there? What was that? Check that out.
All right, yeah, I like sake. Warm sake is good. Okay, hot sake. What do you want? Champagne.
Ensy, okay. Christmas. Probably have some at Don Quixoto. Okay. You guys writing these down?
Ehehe. Ehehe. Didn't expect a free drink. Life's just great. Well, I'm a whiskey hound.
Okay. Make sure it's scotch. What does it mean? My girlfriend are watching and we want to hear
the Dutch voice. Like your anniversary or something? Is it- okay, if it's your anniversary, then
if it is, okay. Well, listen to me, Arthur. Arthur, you have to get on that train and start up a fight
with those bandits before I can get on to that train with you. Happy anniversary, guys. You got
the- no, wait, hold on, I screwed up my thing. Yeah, I'm not gonna say Goku at the end of every
one of those, man. All right, so we need champagne. Let's get this right. We need potato, drink,
champagne, scotch, beer. What was the last one? Potato drink, scotch, champagne, beer,
sake. Okay, easy. I can't just go into the- no!
I gotta get on that train so I can get on the train, Arthur, so I can get on the train with you.
Really, really reaching deep into the- hold on, I gotta call in this guy.
Giant traffic cone. Pog. I want to go to the burger place first. Do they actually have cheeseburgers?
Oh, will this be for here to go? This is for here. Free smile? What? All right, a smile burger,
smile cheeseburger with fries, teriyaki smile burger, a king smile burger. This is like a big
mac. Una burger, a smile shake. I want the smile cheeseburger set. I'm so hungry, I'm eating my
hands in anticipation. All right, what about the smile? Free smile. I have a free smile. Here it
comes. Oh, I thought the smile was like the name of the drink. Excuse me, can I have a free drink?
You don't sell alcohol here, I'm leaving. This is a real thing, you can ask for a smile in Japanese
McDonald's. What? That's- you can? Okay, I need to get a beer, open noodles. Oh, drinks, okay.
Let's go up and left. So you just go- excuse me, I'd like a smile- what if you don't order anything?
I think that's kind of fucked up. You should have to- you should have to at least have to order food.
Otherwise, there'd be a line out the door like, can I have a smile? Sure, thanks for taking up
a fucking space in line, dickhead. Like, imagine like the- you're like in a rush, you're in a hurry,
and like the four or five people in front of you are ordering smiles for free. It's like,
okay, that's very cute. Get the fuck out of my way. I would like to order a meal, please.
I'm- I'm gonna pay- I'm gonna be ordering food. Oh, this is beer, right? Enjoy the moment with
full body flavor. All right, so we need this as draft. This beer tastes incredible. In which
takoyaki would you like? What? Do I have to buy food with this? Takoyaki and egg. I'm too full
for this. No, I can't eat. What if I don't want this? No, I don't want to drink the guy's beer.
Wait, what? Okay, well that was not right. I go up with like five empty containers, shit face.
Did you get our orders? I sure did. Okay, you're all shit. Okay, come on. You know, do you sell
beer here? Just show up with five cartons of milk. Oolong tea. Wait, whiskey. Is it scotch?
Oh, sweet potato. That's expensive. This is $1,800. Oh, friendship. Hold on a minute.
Hold on a minute. Excuse me. You seem a little tense. I just started working here, so
this takes a while to get used to it and learn about all the different products. Well, good luck.
Thank you, sir. How much kinder than you look. I am? What kind of look do I have then?
I'm sorry. Don't worry about it. It's fine. My name is Miho. If you come here often,
we'll be seeing each other a lot. So I thought I should introduce myself.
Nice to meet you, Miho. I'm Kiro. Okay, new contact. This could be the beginning of a
friendship with Miho. All right. You're cheating on bowling girl. No, here, I'm going to buy stuff
from here to talk to this girl. I'm going to bring the bag of this logo with this brand on it
to the bowling alley. Psycho. All right, what else do they have? Delete System 32. That's not even
like, why are you even saying that anymore? It's been like 10 years since somebody did that.
You got like, okay, somebody got one person to do that like 15 years ago and people still say that.
Does this count as scotch? Get the malt. Okay, this is beer. Wait, I just have to buy things
from here and we can, all right, sure. Here. I'd like a couple more things too. I'd like some ramen.
Cool. I'd like, that's what I want from here. Every time I buy something, you like it. I'll
take a seaweed rice ball. Cool. Okay. I'll also have a, you know, hey, I'll take a couple of,
these are expensive so I can show you that I got a little bit of cash. I'll take two of those.
Okay. Also, I'll take some health potion. I'm going to buy one at a time because it makes you
happy when I buy one item at a time and I need help anyways.
Okay, so I have a, this is a separate trip. Oh, no, that won't work. Oh, Kirsten, hello.
Oh, sorry. Thank you for shopping with us. Looks like she's got something on her mind.
Something wrong? You look a little out of it. Oh, do I really?
I'm so sorry. I shouldn't have let that show, but you're right. Something's been on my mind all day.
What's that? Head office gave me an assignment of sorts. An assignment, huh? We have lots of
competition here from the M store chain and others. Our stores are all very similar,
don't you think? But think of it, I guess there's not much of a difference between your store.
That's why the head office asked employees from various branches to come up with ideas that would
set Poppo stores apart from others. That's why you're lost in thought. Okay. I don't want to
suggest something random that would only grab the customer's attention for five minutes.
Silly me, I should ask customers for their opinions. Do you have a few minutes?
No, of course I do. Great. So, Kirsten, is there something, is there anything that you would,
God damn it. Okay. Is there anything that you would like? Oh, man. Is there anything
you would like our store to introduce? Let me think. What would I want at a convenience store?
I would want sofas, luxury brand goods, also delivery service. How about delivery?
That would be pretty good, right? Let's do delivery.
If stores all across Japan, you could use that to offer a delivery service. Oh my gosh,
that's a good idea. Why go to the post office or arrange a curry if you could mail or pick up
parcels at the same store you do your shopping in. Oh, I got it wrong. I thought they were going to
be delivering food and like sprites and stuff to people, not like actually do like mail,
like handle mail. Okay. It still worked. You could also offer a range of discounts
to further entice the customers. Your idea is going to be a winner. You must be a business
genius. Okay. All right. Friendship ended with bowling girl. Now store girl is my best friend.
Good one. Oh, more friendship, friendship, friendship again.
And he bought the whiskey. Almost there. Oh, I shared your suggestions about offering parcel
delivery service with that office and they jumped on the idea. I even got a raise thanks to that.
Hey, that's great. But it was your idea to begin with. So I owe you a big thank you.
I got you this. Hope y'all like it. You got a berserker charm. Oh shit. This is going to be a
new hot snack here available soon. Nice. Yeah. Congratulations. We're starting to sell this
today. Can you guess what it is? Let me give you a hint. It's delicious by itself or with soy sauce
or mustard. It's a specialty from the Nagoya area. It goes well with soy sauce and mustard.
It must be hot miso soup, steamed pork buns. It goes well with soy sauce and mustard. That's
steamed pork buns. It has to be. Wait, is it cutlets? Miso cutlets with pork buns.
Probably pork, right? Mustard? Pork and mustard. They go together really well. Did I just get a
Dan's game for saying pork and mustard? It's cutlets. Dude, it's no, it's not. It's another
no, no. Cutlets. It's literally cutlets. They go together great. Don't listen to chat. Yeah,
I know. What's going on here? Cutlets is the right answer. If you're wrong, I'm going to be pissed
off the rest of the stream. Bingo. So starting today, we'll be selling yummy miso cutlets.
Yay. Gabby J. Yay. Yay. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Where? What happened? Can't wait to try one. I really like them too. And the reward for guessing
correctly is our brand new miso cutlet lunch set. And it's only a two star. Gross. Yeah.
You give me too much credit. Besides, look at you. You become a model employee
and you're excellent at customer service as well. You think so? Well, I guess I'm not as nervous
around customers anymore. Not only that, but the head office likes your ideas too. Who knows,
you could be the manager of this store soon. Oh, no way. I have so much more to learn before
I can even start thinking about that. But if I am getting better at my job, I have to thank you for
that. How so? You were so scary looking. Hold on. You were so scary looking that I was terrified of
you at first, but we managed to become friends. Since then, I don't get jittery around other
people anymore. Oh, I'm pretty good at doing that shit. Only friends? Yeah, whatever. I'm not that
scary, am I? Well, hee hee heart face. And there it is. And there it is. And we got a heart. We
just got a heart. Okay. Just got one. I hope I can return the favor by making Poppo your favorite
store. Please keep shopping with us. Oh, hey, it's me again. I'm here to buy things to make you
happy. I can't carry it. I have a backpack and two duffel bags and grocery bags on both arms. And
I'm just stumbling in here. Hey, hey, I'll take like a couple of Slim Jims. Can you just put them
in my mouth? I'll open in my mouth. God damn it. All right, I'll be back. I've got to relieve
myself of stuff so I can go back and buy stuff to make that girl happy. Here, take this. Here,
take your beer. Oh, perfect. You're a decent guy for a kid your age. Kid one? How old am I?
How old is Kiryu? 20? He's 20 years old. Damn. All right, what did you want? No, not you.
What should I hand over? Here's the sweet potato soju. Enjoy it. How the fuck am I as old as Kiryu?
I don't know. You get the wrong attitude, kid. When an elder offers you a drink, you drink it.
Doesn't matter if you're a featherweight. That's the rules you want to get ahead.
Back when I was a businessman. Oh, whatever. You wanted the scotch, right? I'm really particular
about my whiskey. Oh, I didn't get scotch? That was just regular whiskey? Oh, shit.
You want... I'll have something else. Sake, right? All right, I don't have it. All right,
where can I get it? This is... Here's the drink place. Beef bowl restaurant. Bowl? Bowling?
Bowl? This is the person I'm going to talk to? Oppo? Don? There we go. Don Kyoto. All right,
we're going to be going right and then right. Oh, we got Yakuza. Did I say Kyoto? Kyoto?
Kyoto? Kiyotio? What do you say it? Kiyoti? Kiyoto? Kihote? Kiyotio? Kiyoto? Kiyoxio?
That's Spanish. What? What do you mean that's Spanish? Don Kyoto? It's not Spanish? Oh, it is.
Don Kiyote? Don Kyoto? The plot revolves around the adventures of a noble from
La Mancha named Alsano Kizano who reads so many chivalry romances that he loses his mind and
becomes a knight. Thanks literature. Okay, let's play the video game. Shut up. N.A. education. I
haven't been in a school desk in 20 fucking years. Give me a break. Give me the truck.
Beast mode. Beast mode. Can I pick up the truck in beast mode? Nice. You dropped out at 15.
No, I didn't. I'm just saying it's been a while. What's going on here? Oh shit. All these people
are waiting for smiles. Look, I'm just going to, I'm going to just walk by all these people
starting at the bottom with a huge toothy smile and just walk backwards looking at everybody
directly in their eyes and go, thank you. Thank you. Goodbye. All of you. Goodbye. Thank you.
And then get right in front of them, get in the right, get to the front of the fucking line.
I snuck off from work for this. If my manager finds out before I get back, I'm so dead.
Hey kid. Oh, yes. What's going on? Why are all these people here? Did you want one too?
I'm really sorry, but they said I'll get the last one in stock. What are you talking about?
Aren't you lining up for an Aura Q3? Aura Q3? Is that some kind of secret code?
No, it's an Aura Q3. The newest game in the Aura Cure series. Aura Q3 short for Aura Cure 3,
quest for the quantum quill. I can't wait to read the instruction manual on my way home.
Never heard of it. People are actually lining up to buy a video game. What an amazing world we live
in. Yeah, it's the most popular game in Japan right now. I went looking for it with Papa.
They were sold out everywhere. Then my friend told me this place was getting a new batch today.
So I grabbed my allowance and ran all the way here. They got any 3080s in there?
I made it just in time and got the last reservation ticket. I'm so happy. It's
going to be the best game ever made. Times are strange if it's this hard to buy a toy.
Sorry to bug you, kid. Thanks for the info. Bye, mister. I snuck off from work. Yeah,
we already talked to you. No cutting in line, pal. You have to play by the rules
and get in the back like everyone else. I'm so glad I lined up first thing this morning.
I'm going to be the first one to get it. I just went in. Wait, does this move not know
the store is open? I'll take a Aura Q3, please. Oh, damn it. I can't just buy one. Pires? Comfy
souls. Yeah, give me one of those. Okay. What else you got? Leather belt. Protective amulet.
Baseball shirt. Binding. Table, salt, coin, and gun. Okay. Gentleman's umbrella. Lumber.
Pocket tissues. Gold champagne. All right. Wait, did he want the good stuff?
Just we can just get the shitty stuff, right? Hold on. Oh, dude. Force drink, force stamp,
leather belt. Oh, dude. Force drink, force stamp, leather belt. Oh, dude. Force drink,
force stamp, leather belt. Okay. Just regular champagne, right? It's a really old meme. Yeah.
Sorry, I was on the internet like fucking 15 years ago. Got to be gold. That's too much money.
Zoomers don't get it. Oh, dude. Zoomers don't get it. Vintage. What else can I do here? Wait,
should I get the Mountain Dew? Oh, enjoying her nice Mountain Dew. Didn't we have a whole entire
stream where I got like the Mandela effect where like I said Tom Green did that and we couldn't
find it or something? Wait, 7-up? Why are these in the game? The actual brands? That's kind of weird.
Why are they just getting Mountain Dew? I'm just getting Mountain Dew. There's a ton of brands in
the Yakuza games. How do they do that without getting in trouble? All right. This is where I
go. Hey, do you guys sell cardboard boxes here? Yeah. Can I get like a couple of cardboard boxes,
like two or three cardboard boxes, just kind of like large squares? They're like, I guess. I mean,
that'll be like $3. Thank you. Thank you. And I buy the cardboard boxes and I just kind of get
them up from holding empty cardboard boxes. And I open the door to leave the store here and I go
like this. I start like out of running. Just run by the line. Hmm. Is that? Game over, loser.
What? Hey, the kid that was lining up for the game, right? Did you manage to get it? Oh, Mr.
What's the matter? It's my brand new video game. That guy stole it. What? You mean that high school
kid just stole it? Oh, he just ran up and yelled at me to hand it over. He took my
RQ3. I spent all morning waiting in line too. I saved up my allowance for a really, really long
time to get it. He stole from a kid. He deserved the strongest punishment. I'll get it. I'm going
to go get it. Here, kid. I'm going to go get that, but I can't promise that I won't smash it over his
head. I'm going to be in beast mode. It's going to be hard for me to control my emotions,
but I will get revenge for you. I promise. Hey kid, what's your name? It's it's Akio. Akio got it.
Hang tight. I'll get your game back. You will? So there's no need to cry. Mr. Okay. I won't cry
anymore. Good. That's showing some spine, little man. I like that. Leave it to me. Yay. Thank you,
mister. At high school. Oh, he's in high school. Oh, right. No, I'm not going to smash it over his
forget everything I just said. All right. Where is he? You get that back right now. Isn't that
later freak? Wait, did he just steal it from the high school kid?
They're just playing like steal the PlayStation five tag. No fair. That's the kid who took Akio's
game. Hey, you have that game. Don't you? What's it to you? My adventure just came to an abrupt end.
So leave me alone. Who can do I'll take back that our Akira you took from Akira.
RQ three. That's the last thing I want to hear about right now. Forget it. I'm going to grind
your ass just for the experience. What? Okay, I got a trash can in the head. Get the fuck over
here, dude. Put his head in the trash can. All this over a video game. What is that? Can this
kid in high school? What the hell am I doing? Mr. That run was I just caught the guy who took
your RQ. Oh, yay. Okay, give Akira his Akira back. Man, I don't have it. Give it up already.
If you don't want another beating handed over and get a job next time you want a video game.
I told you I don't have it. I got robbed by a better thief than me.
You were robbed who? Yeah, this jerk from a street gang busted out his dagger of stealing
and made me give it to him. Oh, a dagger for strength for stamp dagger of healing.
Dagger of stealing. I mean, yeah, lame. I could be leveling up but my our Q3 is probably going
to be some dude's not even a fan of the Q3. Dagger of healing. No, no, trust me. Trust me.
When I stab you with this dagger in the stomach, you're going to feel your diarrhea is going to
go away tomorrow morning. I promise. That wasn't yours. You rob a little kid and then turn around
and cry like a baby when you get mugged. How pathetic is that? You haven't learned your
lesson yet. You bunk. No, I'm already out of lives. Sorry, man. I'm out of here.
Didn't I just kick this guy's head into the wall as hard as I could? Being able to make like joky
video game references after all of your teeth are gone and you need like four hours of surgery to
fix your skull. Like, I mean, that's just I mean, come on. What's going on here?
All right, I'll get it back. The kid stole and stole it by some other stole somebody
and that guy went off this way. I swear to god if this guy gets robbed. Oh my god.
Oh my god. Okay. Hey, you're the guy that stole the PlayStation from the kid that stole it from
Accio. Who the hell is Accio and what if they did? I saw my chance and I took it. Yeah.
No, you robbed the kid who robbed Accio of his Arakura.
I don't get it. Forget it. Just give back the Arakura cartridge you stole.
Ara Q3, Ara Q3. I don't want to hear another word about Ara Q3. I'm gonna stomp you. Oh, nice.
Take him up by his legs and smash his head somewhere.
Fuck, I pressed the wrong button. Get up. Oh, I got a scratch on my arm.
There's a lady that walked on stage and she had like the arms that came in. She like did that
walk. It's a meme. The politician. Some EU politician. Theresa May. Yeah. All right.
He's doing like the Theresa May walk. All right. Give the Arakura. Sorry, pal, but your game got
pinched. I'm not playing around. Give the kid his game or you can suffer. Me. Suffer me now. I'm
serious. It's really gone. Some a-hole got the jump on me. You carry around a knife. You rob
kids and stuff and you stab people, but you won't say asshole, but you'll kill people.
Remember how we talked about earlier? You can gouge somebody's eyes out with a fucking stick.
But like saying the word fuck on TV, we're seeing it's coming full circle.
Professionals have standards. Remember your nephews are watching. My nephews are not watching
Yakuza. This hard ass held me up at gunpoint. That guy that was just here. What a shitty day.
That guy jacked my Ara Q3. That wasn't yours. You steal from a kid then cry like a baby when
you get mugged. I'm seeing a pathetic pattern here. If this isn't getting through to you,
how about we go another round? No. No. If I'm good, I'm sorry. My Ara Q3. Don't worry. I promise I'll
hunt it down. At this point, at this point, I'm going to be like, son, just give me one second.
Do you ever heard of eBay? Here, I'll get one for you. What's your address? Well, the thug who took
Akio's Ara Q3 from the kid who stole it in the first place ended up having it taken by some
hard ass Yakuza who went up towards the Taihei Boulevard. Let's go. It's 1988. Oh, internet
didn't exist. Well, I would just go buy one. I would just, okay, here's what I would do. Yeah,
sure. eBay didn't exist. I would stand on the corner, like right here, wherever that game store
was. And I would just go, ladies and gentlemen, may I have your attention for one moment?
If anyone has recently purchased the Ara Q3 system, I am willing to pay 20% more than what
you paid for it. I currently have $500 cash in my pocket, and I'll do it. We will do a transaction
right now. Spread the word. I'll be here every afternoon from 2pm to 4pm Pacific.
And I would just go, I never wait till somebody showed up. You get robbed. Oh, yeah. What about
that one? Yeah. Yeah. You're gonna come rob me? Oh, excuse me. Where is it going? Sold out. Yeah,
that's why I'd be announcing it on the corner. If you're more comfortable with getting a check,
I have those too. You're finally mine Ara Q3. My quest is complete. A game you got there.
You stole it. Oh, you see this Ara Cura belongs to us. Bwa ha ha. So if you want to live, get off my
street. Listen, don't bother looking for a place that's still selling Ara Q3. Just find a fool who
bought one and take it. Villains. Every last one. What's this world coming to? Bah. What'd you say,
boy? That Ara Cura, you're, I'm taking it from you. What's that? Take it back. So listen up, boy.
Pornography starring your mother. Don't act like it was your game to start with. Huh? Shut up,
it's complicated. I see you're an Ara Q3 hunter too then. Playtime is over. I'm not holding back.
And he has a gun. He just aims it up, excuse me, right in the forehead. Can he kill me?
Don't even let him shoot it. Why is he hitting me? You have a gun. He's using it as a melee weapon.
This cannot be. I'll be taking that Ara Q3 with me. Hold on, please. I need that. Give it back. Come
on. Give it back? This was never yours to begin with. Bella, I'm begging you, please. My little
boy's been really looking forward to playing it. Your son? Uh, yeah. My old lady left me and took
the boy with her. He's been wanting Ara Q3. Wait a minute, is this the, is the kid's dad?
We were looking everywhere, but there ain't none for sale anywhere. I just wanted my boy to be
happy. I'm begging you. You gotta let me have it, please. Uh, I can't do that. You probably don't
know this, but a little kid saved up his allowance and went through a lot of trouble to buy the last
one. Huh? I didn't stick up a little kid. I just took it off some worthless goon. That's right,
you got the game from a punk, but that game belonged to a little kid first. Long story short,
you took Ara Q3 from a wannabe punk who took it from a high school bully who took it from the last
boy in line who bought it in the first place. And head hurts just thinking about it, but all right,
so that's what happened. And I came to get it back for the little kid. It's gonna, going back to the
rightful owner. I'm sorry. It's gonna be the kid's dad. Bella, I'm the fool here. Give it back to that
kid for me. Damn, I was about to make someone's kid cry for the sake of my own. What kind of monster
have I become? I thought I could make my boy happy with something I stole from someone else.
I was wrong. Am I supposed to be a good dad to my boy? Do Akio like this? Yeah. I guess you better
think about it. Wait, what? Who? Oh, hi, mister. Perfect timing, Akio. I got your Ara Q3 back.
Oh, really? Yippee. Oh, Akio, it's you. Oh, my boy. Oh, hi, papa.
Papa? You guys are related? That's right. Are you friends with papa, mister?
Uh, yeah, you might say that. Simpson's episode. Wait, buddy, that little kid you were telling me
about, that was his. Yeah, that seems to be how this is shaking up. Why, Akio? Why didn't you say
anything to your papa? All you had to do was ask. I could have given you the money to buy Ara Q3
any time you smashed his dad's brain into the pavement in front of him. Hey,
Jerma sucks. Thanks for the 10 community subs. I beg to differ because mama always gets mad at
you, papa, for spending money on golfing and go-karts and board games. And I didn't want
mama to get mad at you even more for spending all your money again, papa. So I tried to buy it myself.
Akio, I just like did a huge burp. I'm sorry. Did you guys hear that? I hope you didn't.
That just hurt. It came out of my nostrils. I just leaned back and went,
and it came out of my eyes. It went through my sinuses. That hurt. I'm sorry. Mr. Papa looks
kind of scary, but he's a really, really nice man once you get to know him. Ew. Don't share that. I
share everything. He took me to a bunch of game stores just the other day. He's not living with
mama and me now. I think he's lonely. Please stay friends with him, okay? Actually, Akio,
your papa helped me get your RQ3 back. Yeah, that's right. He did. And his dad smiles,
a big smile, which just bruises all over his face and like four of his teeth fall out and like
bloods all over his mouth. Really? Thank you, papa. I did in a way. I don't want to see you crying
again. Nice Looney Tunes joke. Yeah. I think that actually happens like every three episodes.
How many times has Davy Duck's teeth fallen out of his mouth after getting like smashed in the head
with a board? I don't want to see you crying. Be careful going home with your game. Yep. Got it.
Thank you, mister. Hey, mister. Thanks. This is to apologize or to thank you for teaching this fool a
lesson. Maybe whatever. I want you to have it. Got a sunburst. Holy shit. What was that? Is that a
katana? A sword? I now want to be a good dad all the time, not just in front of Akio.
You don't want to do anything that'll make kids sad, no matter whose kids they are.
Yeah, you got that right. Papa, this is too hard for me all by myself. Let's go to mama's house
and play RQ3 to go. Oh, my heart is exploding. Oh, without the expert advice, without my expert
advice, we'll be making a beeline to that nasty demon lord in no time. That's how a game should
be played. There it is. That was very, I loved that. That was wonderful. That was wonderful.
I got a sword out of it, too. All right. What was I doing? Oh, yeah. I need to give shampoo.
Do I, where do I get the champagne? I have, uh, what did I get? Did I get a golden champagne?
Where is it? You didn't buy it. What? I didn't buy it? Really? I thought I bought it. Oh, come on.
Really? All right. Well, I did that quest. That was cool. So let's be going to go straight and
then go right and then right. Sorry. I don't want to be like a coughing Andy.
Yeah, I want to make sure I said this again. For those of you that don't, I'm sick. I'm a little
sick. Just trying to stream around being sick. I was tested for COVID. I'm negative for COVID.
So I just want to make that clear. For those of you that might be concerned,
I haven't tested. I'm negative. Uh, where is this place? It's right here, right? Wrong side.
Wrong side. Wrong side. Wrong side. Wrong side. Okay. Give me something, please.
Okay. I have. So do I actually have to buy the gold one?
Dear Jerma, sorry for being, what? How's this coffee cost? Hold on. Dear Jerma, sorry for
being off topic, but upon reviewing a recent VOD, I noticed a peculiar claim you made.
You claim that you rubbed your body wash on your chest to build up a good lather, which you could
then use on other parts of the body. The ability to build lather is determined by surface area,
meaning you must have significant surface area already on your chest. The only explanation for
the, this would be a large amount of chest hair. Um, no, that's not accurate. I don't have like a
lot of chest hair. No, I don't have a lot of chest hair. I really don't. I have, they kind of sprout
up a little bit and I just go and I just pull them with like a pair of tweezers. Cause nobody
wants to have like eight chest hairs, right? Like, no, get rid of them. I have like 12, eight to
12 chest hairs and I just kind of look in the mirror and I go and just pull them. My eyebrows,
I do, well, I pluck my eyebrows. I pluck my chest hairs. I clean up, right? I do some little,
I clean up. I make sure I'm, you know, look, make sure I look okay. Yeah, I, sorry. I, oh, sorry.
I take care of, I take care of my hair. I don't want it to go out of control. You know, you do
everything. Sometimes I let it go for a little while and you get, you know, you clean it up.
You know, I don't want to have like the, I have this wild hair, wild everywhere. Next topic. Oh,
I don't mind. I sometimes, I mean, you gotta clean up a little. You're like Patrick Bateman.
I'm not like Patrick Bateman. All right. Do you have the other thing too? Cause I like pluck my
eyebrows. I like get my eyebrows done. Cause I, I, I, I get like my hands and feet done too.
Is that, you don't, we think that's weird too. You don't, you think that's odd. Get over it.
I can't buy anything else from her. Yeah. That's self care. Oh yeah. It's yeah. Come on. Good
boy. That's hey. I thought, yeah, of course. I'm just doing a little, you do a little, you know,
TLC. Uh, okay. I'm going to give the champagne to the guy. THC.
Chest hair is gross. I don't have chest hair. Didn't I just sprint? Why is it? Oh, okay. I
pluck my nose here. Yeah. I got to take care of those too. But be careful. Be careful. I'm
going to give you guys some tips here. If you're going to take care of your nose hairs,
just, just trim them down to like the edge of where your, your nostrils are.
Cause you can end up with a problem. I've had this happen before. This is not a joke.
If you do, if you go too far in and you trim too much, you can actually get an ingrown hair
in your nose. And, and I've had, this has happened to me twice. I have trimmed my nose hairs to a
point where I got an ingrown in my nose and this shit came out the other side of my nose.
It was so painful. I had an ingrown inside of my nose and it grew. It went out the front of my
nose and I had to pull it out. It was horrible. It was horrible. Please, please. If you're going
to trim your nose hairs, do it just to the edge of where your nose hairs are about to touch your
nostrils. Please don't go just you'll end up like me. It was awful. It's happened twice. Please.
I'm just trying to help you guys, trying to help you out. I don't pluck my nose hairs either. No,
I don't do that either. That same thing can happen. You do, you trim, just trim so they don't like,
like all coming out. Then you can't see them. You know, it's fine. I'm giving you tips.
Guess what? My tips, I'm going to give them to you. Nobody asked. Did nobody ask? Did nobody ask
this? Why do we start talking about this? How about this? No, no, no, no, no, no, no. You ain't
going to get those tips. Nope. I'm not going to say that one. Where do I get the scotch?
And you want sake. Where do I get the sake? Just one, please. We need to know.
Please just tell us. Please give us a secret. I'm not going to take tissues from some random
person on the street. Just one tip. One, please. No, sorry. I don't give those out. I don't give
those away. Get over here. Body slam. All right. I'll go rush mode. One person in chat is going
to freak out. They're going to be like, finally. Okay. I'm going to save the game. I'm going to
go to the next mission. Oh no, I need sake. What does, what does nani mean? I hear like,
nani means what? Nani, nani, nani means what? Like what? Like what? Nani. Okay.
All right. We're going to go. Somebody said north for the drinks. Meaning store up here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, what? Wait, wait, what? I'll get it. Wait, wait, what?
How do you do rush with them? Yeah. No, no, no. Sorry. Excuse me. That one sucks.
I'm going to my try and prove. This one sucks too. Beast mode only.
This one's bad too. What's the, what's the fourth one called? You just suck.
Sorry. I have to text somebody. Sorry. Sorry. I'm texting right now.
Just temp. Just texting someone really quickly. Hold on. It's important. Okay. We need boos.
Booze. Booze. Boohoo. Boohoo. Boohoo. Boohoo. Boohoo so sad. Boohoo. Boohoo.
Out of our way. I've got booze just so wait where's the girl? Oh, wrong store.
What? Was Trump? Trump? That was maybe. Oh, it's me. Donald Trump boohoo. It
It kind of is in a sort of a way I can't carry anymore.
Oh my gosh, drink something in front of them.
Just eat this and drink, just drink the Mountain Dew.
That was a scuffed impression.
That wasn't a real impression.
You want me to do my real Trump?
Okay.
Let me just say I'm going for a full Donald Trump now.
Do not, hold on.
Don't, don't, don't, it's Otto.
Hi everyone, it's me, Otto.
It's me, Otto Trump.
It's my next video.
Cursed.
Oh, what's this?
Ooh, what's this?
What's this?
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
That is sucky.
You can't LUL in minus two.
You can't do that.
That's not fair.
That's not fair to me.
You can't do that.
And I will get, you will be timed out
if you do something like that
because you're just, you're fucking up my market.
All right, where's the, now where's the scotch?
I need scotch.
Did it say where I could get it?
This is the only store up here.
You didn't buy the sake.
What?
How is that possible?
That's not even possible.
I, you watched me buy it.
I bought it.
What?
Oh, dump it.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Sake.
Thank you.
Yes.
This dude's eating chest hairs.
You're gross.
So where's the scotch?
Every goddamn time.
It's sake, not sake.
Oh, okay.
Sorry.
So I'm saying with a slight different accent.
You gotta go to Papa Showa Street.
How am I supposed to know where that is?
It's sake, not sake.
Sake, sake.
Oh my God.
You said sake, not sake.
Get him.
What is it?
Oh.
Where do I buy it?
Somebody just tell me.
Just give me the tips.
I don't care.
You guys want like sex tips?
Then you better tell me where to buy the scotch.
Huh?
Someone tell him quick.
Southeast Popo store for scotch.
Yeah, I got your attention.
Got your attention.
It's the Southwest.
Okay.
Southeast Popo store.
Hmm.
Okay.
Let's go.
Tell him please, please.
Give him exact directions.
Oh shit, I gotta go this way.
Please, quick.
Give some tips.
Please.
Please hurry.
Hurry.
Give the tip, please.
Let's go.
One, two, three.
That's a lot of blood.
Quick.
She's here.
I need advice.
But like you're sitting there like,
oh my God, I don't know what to do.
Derma.
Like you just ran in the bathroom.
Like you're like, they're like,
oh yeah, you know, I'm,
if you wanna like, you know, fool around a little,
I'm here and I'm like, I'm lying on your bed.
Okay.
Yeah.
What a second.
You sprint in the bathroom, get on Twitch.
Derma, Derma, Derma, Derma, Derma, Derma, Derma.
Derma, what do I do?
I can't help you.
Oh, casino.
Wait, I got sidetracked.
It's down.
Okay, down here.
You promised.
Okay, here you go.
Here's a tip for you.
Just relax, relax, relax.
You're gonna, what you're gonna do is you're gonna,
you're in the bathroom.
Just chill, chill.
It's gonna be fine.
Just relax, be comfortable.
You're gonna look in the mirror.
You're gonna get a bunch of water in your hands like this.
Water, water.
They go to the sink.
Tons of water.
Throw it in your face.
Water, water, water.
All in your hair too.
Slick your hair back.
Make sure there's water like dripping down
from your head and face and stuff.
So you're covered in water and you're like,
okay, it'll be nice, it's cooling you off a little.
Then I want you to do,
is I want you to just get some,
we'll get a moisturizer.
Dry your hands, get a moisturizer.
Get moisturizer like all over your hands
and all over your arms and wrists and neck and face
and like just tons of it, like a lot of it.
Like if you have like the big tub of it.
Just make sure it's like all over you
so you can like get like moisturizer
and be comfortable and calm.
Then what I want you to do is I want you to,
I want you to just slowly open the door
and I want you to start singing.
I want you to go.
Hello, my love.
I am here to have some fun with you
and me.
We'll see our destiny while we're in love.
And let me know how it goes.
And then what you're gonna do is you're gonna crouch down.
You're gonna start running around the room as a dog
on all fours, just going like.
Woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof.
And do your best Scooby-Doo impression and go,
I'm ready.
Remember this 8,000 people watching.
Oh shit, that's right.
Sometimes I forget that it's not like three people here.
Just like in a Skype call.
I seriously forget that sometimes.
I forget it's not just like me, boo, stealth and star.
Just like in italics.
Oops.
Oh, whatever.
All right, I gotta go in here.
Oh shit.
And make sure, no, I'm done, I'm done.
This is gonna escalate.
I'm gonna escalate this until like
a bunch of people will fucking leave.
Okay, we're gonna just, what am I buying?
Scotch.
Did I not buy it?
I bought it, right?
I can't, I'm not doing it anymore.
We're playing Yakuza.
You fucking drank it.
I bought another one, I'm fine.
They know we're gonna leave.
Hey, you had to click the mature,
listen, you clicked the mature audience filter before.
This is a mature screen.
We talk about mature topics sometimes.
Oh, nice dodge, dude.
He almost just kicked his friend in the face.
He just kicked me right in the groin.
I wanna do it to the pole.
I wanna smash him on the pole so bad.
Why won't that work?
Oh, I got him from behind?
Into the pole.
Smash his face into, no.
Stop it, stop it.
Dead.
I have to return these items to these people.
Where are the tips?
I already gave them.
I'm stuck, you get stuck in Yakuza.
Get over here.
Right in the face.
Oh, goodbye.
Goodbye.
Go read an analog clock.
Why do I feel like that?
Okay, I know what you're saying,
but why do I feel like that's like a boomer reference
or something?
Like, okay, boomer, why don't you go read an analog clock
and you're studying.
Okay, here's your sake.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, didn't mean to.
I'm gonna say sake.
Sorry.
What?
Oh, no, it's the other guy.
Got your scotch whiskey.
I got your scotch here.
Scotch whiskey.
Oh, booze really is the water of life.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm looking like sniffily.
I know people hate that shit
and I know I'm like streaming sick and I'm sorry
and I'll talk, I'll take tomorrow off, I promise.
I heard you've worked at the Chibana real estate company.
Ugh.
Yeah, I've been sitting in the same place all day.
Don't you fucking dare.
I'm just a simple part-time job.
I need a doctor's note.
I just got my first check and I got a second one.
I'm gonna sit in a different place tomorrow.
You've been doing this all this time, right?
I've seen it too, so I know.
I'm going to the doctor's office.
Yeah, I need a doctor's note.
You know that?
You need a doctor's note for work?
Um, I mean, kinda.
Should I call it that?
What are you talking about?
Oh, I make like jokey pretend sex tips
to like a bunch of people on the internet.
And then I play a video game in the background.
Sure, I guess that could be work.
Pretend, pretend?
Oh, that was real?
I just can tell the doctor that
so he doesn't think I'm weird, right?
And he leans in and goes,
by the way, you're talking about sex tips.
What are they?
I gotta spice things up with me and my life.
What would you suggest?
Oh, that's Champion Street, right?
I see you're doing well.
That area is now the mecca of self-reliance.
It's just a small bar.
Bro.
And the camera pans back, coming out of the office,
and I'm like, hey, you ever seen Scooby-Doo?
And then they are like the clapping,
the studio audience is clapping and laughing,
and then we fade out to the credits.
That area is not only for the Tachibana people,
but also for the people of the Tojo Clan.
If a yakuza like you goes there,
the people there will hate you.
I see.
That's helpful.
Thank you.
Made by Dick Wolf.
The Champion District.
That may be my ticket to bumping into Tachibana's boys again.
It's the tweet.
All I need is the tweet.
I don't care about anything else.
I got the tweet.
I got the lore tweet.
Ooh, hold on.
Is that you, boy?
Isn't it over here?
Oh, it's Glockus.
Perfect timing.
There's something I need to talk to you about.
I'll wait for you back here.
Do I care about what he has to say right now?
Look, I heard you're giving out sex tips.
We're in an alley, nobody can hear us.
Give me a good one.
We're the only way somewhere, boy.
Sorry to hold you up.
Yeah, you wanna talk?
That's right, tell me.
Have you been training?
Yeah, here and there.
Good, because I have something I'd like to ask you to do.
If you're willing, that is.
What's with the hesitation?
That's not like you.
Truth is, I've got debt collectors on me tail.
Scary ones.
Yeah, I gather you've been running since we met.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Those two-bit jokers are nickel and dime stuff.
I'm talking tunas.
Famous, and I mean that in the global sense.
And now they're here in Japan.
Hot on my tail.
Blond, did you seriously try to escape
your mountain of debt by fleeing to Japan?
Yes, and this time, they may be no going back.
I think there's a price on my head.
I guess it's too late to pay the money back then.
What are you going to do, Bacchus?
Well, I was hoping I could get you to be my bodyguard.
Figured as much.
Unfortunately, I've already got enough trouble on my plate.
Believe me, you'd probably be in a worse danger
with me around anyways.
Oh, no, that's in no way to have a part, please.
Sure, I can't pay retainer, but if you protect me,
I'll teach you some of my top shelf moves.
They're good stuff.
Ooh, wait, what?
We're going to get tips?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on, hold on, hold on,
wait, wait, wait, wait, you're going to flip this on me?
I got, are these moves better than my moves?
Damn straight, they are.
That'll do you right in a tight fight, me boy.
Oh, okay.
Are you Bacchus?
I think they found me, boy.
This is the big scary debt collector, huh?
I'm here for your head.
Just doing my job.
So don't hold it against me.
Nanny?
Debt collector, huh?
More like Hitman.
Oh, you're looking forward to that one too.
Did you hear that the PSVR is the only version it'll be on?
And it's only going to be on the PS4 version of Hitman 3?
That immediately deduces a full retrograde
from that fucking game.
I can't believe it either.
It's a stupid decision.
Please help me.
I guess I don't have much of a choice if I left you here.
I'd be putting a bullet in your head myself.
Stand back, get out of here.
No, settle down.
All right, actually delete that one.
Delete that one.
For real, delete it.
Delete it.
You're protecting this guy?
For now, I don't especially feel like watching him die.
I see, fine.
There may be not a price on your head,
but I'll see if I can swing a bonus afterwards.
Crack knuckle, crack knuckle, crack knuckle, crack knuckle,
crack knuckle, crack crack.
Here we go.
Way ahead of you, old man.
Mysterious Hitman.
Come on.
Oh, that's all it takes.
You just have to shoot you for real.
Don't shoot me with that.
Get off me.
Oh.
Give me this.
Oh shit.
Get off.
What's that, nails?
Wait.
Use the sword.
Gah.
I'm letting you live.
You go back and tell whoever ordered the hit
to forget about Bacchus.
You hear me?
There'll be others on this trail soon enough.
They'll get what's coming to him.
This is the worst Yakuza dub.
You think so?
All right, that's a one guy moment.
I'm fucking gonna actually try really hard here.
There'll be others on this trail soon enough.
You'll get what's coming to him.
Hold on, you stay right fucking there.
Don't leave the stream.
I saw your name.
Sorry, boy.
Why the apology?
I told you to watch out for a knife in your ribs.
Hey, you, hold on.
Now you're in my head.
I told you.
I told you to watch out for a knife in your ribs.
And here I am putting you in danger myself.
Don't worry about that.
I'd rather hear more about the offer you made earlier.
This is bad.
You said you'd teach me some new moves.
Better make it quick though
before the next Hitman gets here.
You sure about this, boy?
I don't have much of a choice.
Like that person's in my head now.
I can just see this is the worst dub ever.
It's just flashing in front of my head.
I don't have much choice.
Like I said, I've got my own problems.
So a few extra survival skills would come in handy.
All right, then let me fill you in on some moves
that'll send those Hitman reeling.
Hey, boy.
You ready to learn my moves?
These are the moves I can teach you, boy.
What's the, yeah, what's the key to brawling?
Yes.
Okay.
The most important thing in a fight is tenacity.
That's the secret.
Sounds pretty simple for a secret.
Though I guess in a fight, simplicity is best.
Brawling comes down to spirit in the end.
So I'm going to teach you a move that harnesses that power.
I call it spirit fire.
Spirit fire?
Interesting.
So you use the force of an enemy's blow
to strike them back with twice the power?
Yes.
I'm sure you'll be able to make use of it.
Hey, you're Bacchus, right?
Oh, another guy.
It's one of those Japanese hooligans.
You call yourself an assassin?
You look about as pro as some sorry street punk.
I don't really know what's going on here,
but I just got paid a fortune up front
by some guy in chat, a one guy.
I get the rest once the job's done.
Oh, so he's a street fighter on a freelance job.
He doesn't look so tough.
Shut it.
I may not look like much, but I've never lost a fight.
Time to earn this cash.
Please don't smash my head over and over again into the wall.
Please don't use a bike on me
and smash the bike over my head and get a million dollars.
Don't kick me in the head while I'm on the ground
and crush my head.
Let's go, you fucking loser.
I think you've got the tenacity to win.
This is the perfect chance, boy.
Yeah.
Time to try out that move I just learned.
What?
You want some first, do you?
All right, open up, sir, I'll serve you your tea.
Oops, I just skipped it.
Holy shit, what, I have a gun too?
Wait, what, I have a weapon?
You can charge up a counterattack.
The attack's more powerful and likely to knock the opponent.
Start.
Hold down X or Y after being attacked.
Okay.
Defeat the Hitman, targeting Bacchus.
Use your brawler style of moves to take out the assassin.
What, I'm trying to counterattack.
I want to do the thing that just toppled.
You want to do that?
Throw him into the trash.
Oh, just, can I just shoot him?
Oh, dog, dog, dog.
Right face.
Yeah, all right, let's go.
Should have saved up, that was a mistake.
Holy shit, that dodge though.
I'm gonna die, wait.
Step on his head.
Run, run, run, run, kick.
Tried to grab me, didn't you?
Nope.
Over here.
I might have no more drink.
Happy holidays, happy holidays to you too.
Boy wins.
Hey.
Yeah?
What?
What did the guy that paid you look like?
It was dark, I didn't get a good look at their face.
From the way they talked, I guess they were foreign.
Was it me?
Of course not, yeah, it was him.
It was, oh, did you guys hear that?
There was like a person talking out of my throat.
It was like, no, it wasn't.
Nope.
Did anybody hear that?
Maybe my noise gate didn't pick it up.
I went, oh, blah, blah, blah.
Nope.
Oh, I hope it got picked up, it was weird.
I was about to cough.
You stop getting CBD injections.
It was Jerma's tapeworm.
Oh.
Jerma, is chat your little pogchamp?
Yeah, I don't know, sure.
Looks like you handled this one no problem.
We better hope they're all like this.
All right, I'm injured, I need to drink.
I need to drink.
Okay, I feel better.
Four million, was that four million off the debt if I...
Four million off the debt to improv an apology video
for showing your genitals on stream.
No, that's not enough.
Okay, let me do the story mission.
I've been playing for like three hours
and I don't think I've done anything.
These people are chasing me.
I don't wanna fight them, I just wanna...
Wait, how much money do I have?
Oh, shit, hold on.
I need to do this.
Not enough.
Wait, what about these?
Two million, reduce the damage you take
when thrown by an enemy.
It's only two million.
Reduce the rate that the heat gauge drops down over time.
What about beast?
Increase the power of your regular attacks
and heat actions in beast style.
It's a no-brainer.
Go to the shrine.
Boost max health, yeah, of course.
What else we got?
Charge forward while keeping your guard up.
You won't be staggered by attacks
below a certain power level.
Okay, what up here?
This is kinda good.
What's after that?
This connects it.
I wanna see what's over here.
Boost the power of your attacks when in heat mode.
Yeah.
Did I just unlock this thing over here?
You are less likely to falter during a rush combo
when in heat mode.
400 million dollars!
We have a confirmed offer.
We have an offer here, hold on.
Confirmed offer, wait, wait, wait.
What is it?
Do offer, read to us green eggs and ham
without fucking up once.
Remove 75 million.
Without fucking up once?
Is that a deal?
Okay.
I don't have green eggs and ham.
I don't own it.
Okay, I got it.
No, I got it, okay.
Green eggs and ham.
I am Sam.
Sam I am.
That's Sam I am.
I do not like that Sam I am.
Do would you like green eggs and ham?
I do not like them, Sam I am.
I do not like green eggs and ham.
Would you like them here or there?
Wait, show it?
Okay, here.
All right, all right, all right, I'll do it.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Hold on, I was even in the middle of something.
Okay, where is it?
You can't see it.
I love how there's an anti-aliasing here.
Can you not see it?
Is it too much text here?
I'll take a screenshot, hold on.
I have it in a text file.
You shouldn't be able to see it.
How come the, huh, that's weird.
Read it faster.
Don't get relief, have it.
Wait, what?
How come I can't get this to show?
I'll just have to take a screenshot.
It's a long book, man.
Okay, can you see if I do this?
I'm just trying to put the text on the screen.
Okay, hold on.
Is it showing up yet?
Anybody see it?
Not showing up at all.
You can't even see it at all.
No, you can't see it.
All right, so I'm using Streamlabs OBS for the last time.
It's literally the last day I'm gonna use it.
I'm uninstalling this shit
as soon as I get off the fucking stream.
Okay, hold on.
You said that last year.
I know.
I'm gonna put, hold on.
Let me just paste it and just, hold on, here.
Just, we're gonna look at some art for a second.
I'll be right back.
And plus I should piss too.
I'll get this ready.
Let's take a look at some artwork.
I'm gonna go pee.
I'm gonna get this ready and I'll do it.
Be right back.
Okay, I am back.
Let's get some, I would say music,
but can I get royalty-free cartoon music?
Background cartoon music, royalty-free.
No copyright cartoon music.
Let's see if this is good.
No copyright cartoon background music.
This is called Cartoon Pizza.
Cartoon pizza, pizza music?
Hold on.
No copyright cartoon animation background music.
Okay, that's right.
It's gonna be hard with this music in the background though.
Look at that, that looks good.
Jeremiah Hades and Otto Cerberus.
All right, give me a sec.
Let me try to get this over.
That's really good.
Boppities, what the hell is Boppities?
Boppities, that's not even a real person.
It's not.
Very good.
Very good shit.
All right, let me see.
I gotta capture this window.
Let's go back to here.
And I'm gonna, what is this an image of?
All right, I'm just gonna put this on the screen
because I don't, whatever.
I gotta hide the window for a sec, okay?
Just look at that for a minute.
Where is it?
I'm going to try to read
the entirety of Green Eggs and Ham.
I'm gonna try.
I have it here.
I just like, I just, I was there, I'm gonna try.
I'm gonna go for it.
Let's see if I can get it.
Okay, here we go.
Green Eggs and Ham by Dr. Seuss.
This is 75 million if I get it right.
Okay, I'm ready.
Ready?
Oh, hello.
Retail readings with me, Jeremy.
Today we're gonna be reading Green Eggs and Ham.
Oh, it's so wonderful.
Here we go.
I am Sam.
Sam I am.
That's Sam I am.
I do not like that Sam I am.
Do would you like Green Eggs and Ham?
I do not like them, Sam I am.
I do not like Green Eggs and Ham.
Would you like them here or there?
I would not like them here or there.
I would not like them anywhere.
I do not like Green Eggs and Ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
Would you like them in a house?
Would you like them with a mouse?
I do not like them in a house.
I do not like them with a mouse.
I do not like them here or there.
I do not like them anywhere.
I do not like Green Eggs and Ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
Would you eat them in a box?
Would you eat them with a fox?
Not in a box.
Not with a fox.
Not in a house.
Not with a mouse.
I would eat.
Ah!
Hello, everyone.
And welcome back to Fairy Tales with Jeremy Albertson.
Ugh!
I am Sam.
Sam, do it again.
Do it again, do it again, do it again.
I can do this.
Hello, children.
And welcome to Fairy Tales with Jeremy Alberton.
Today we're gonna be reading Green Eggs and Ham.
Ugh!
I am Sam.
Sam I am.
That's Sam I am, that's Sam I am.
I do not like that Sam I am.
Do would you like Green Eggs and Ham?
Why is it do would you like?
That's wrong.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to reading children's stories from Dr. Schway's.
Here we go.
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three,
one, two, three, one, two, three.
I am Sam.
Sam I am.
That's Sam I am, that's Sam I am.
I do not like that Sam I am.
Would you like Green Eggs and Ham?
I do not like them, Sam I am.
I do not like Green Eggs and Ham.
Would you like them here or there?
I would not like them here or there.
I would not like them anywhere.
I do not like Green Eggs and Ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
And would you like them in a house?
Would you like them with a mouse?
I do not like them in a house.
I do not like them with a mouse.
I do not like them here or there.
I do not like them anywhere.
I do not like Green Eggs and Ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
Would you eat them in a box?
Would you eat them with a fox?
Not in a box, not with a fox,
not in a house, not with a mouse.
I would not eat them here or there.
I would not eat them anywhere.
I would not eat Green Eggs and Ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
Would you, could you in a car?
Eat them, eat them, here they are.
I would not, could not in a car.
You may like them, you will see.
You may like them in a tree.
I would not, could not in a tree.
Not in a car, you let me be.
I do not like them in a box.
I do not like them with a fox.
I do not like them in a house.
I do not like them with a mouse.
I do not like them here or there.
I do not like them anywhere.
I do not like Green Eggs and Ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
A train, a train, a train, a train.
Could you, would you on a train?
Not on a train, not in a tree.
Not in a car, Sam let me be.
I would not, could not in a box.
I would not, could not with a fox.
I will not eat them in a house.
I will not eat them here or there.
I will not eat them anywhere.
I do not eat Green Eggs and Ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
Say in the dark, here in the dark.
Would you, could you in the dark?
I would not, I could not in the dark.
Would you, could you in the rain?
I would not, could not in the rain.
Not in the dark, not in a train.
Not in a car, not in a tree.
I do not like them, Sam you see.
Not in a house, not in a box.
Not with a mouse, not with a fox.
I will not eat them here or there.
I do not like them anywhere.
You do not like Green Eggs and Ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
Could you, would you with a goat?
I would not, could not with a goat.
Would you, could you on a boat?
I could not, would not on a boat.
I will not, I will not with a goat.
I will not eat them in the rain.
Not in the dark, not in a tree.
Not in a car, you let me be.
I do not like them in a box.
I do not like them with a fox.
I will not eat them in a house.
I do not like them with a mouse.
I do not like them here or there.
I do not like them anywhere.
I do not like Green Eggs and Ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
You do not like them.
You saw.
Hello everyone.
Today, we're going to be reading from a,
I'm gonna do it very slowly.
I am Sam.
I am Sam, Sam I am.
That's Sam I am, that's Sam I am.
I do not like that, Sam I am.
Would you like Green Eggs and Ham?
I do not like them, Sam I am.
I do not like Green Eggs and Ham.
Would you like them here or there?
I would not like them here or there.
I would not like them anywhere.
I do not like Green Eggs and Ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
Would you like them in a house?
Would you like them with a mouse?
I do not like them in a house.
I do not like them with a mouse.
I do not like them here or there.
I do not like them anywhere.
I do not like Green Eggs and Ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
Would you eat them in a box?
Would you eat them with a fox?
Not in a box, not with a fox.
Not in a house, not with a mouse.
I would not eat them here or there.
I would not eat them anywhere.
I would not eat Green Eggs and Ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
Would you, could you in a car?
Eat them, eat them, here they are.
I would not, could not in a car.
You may like them, you will see.
You may like them in a tree.
I would not, could not in a tree.
Not in a car, you let me be.
I do not like them in a box.
I do not like them with a fox.
I do not like them in a house.
I do not like them with a mouse.
I do not like them here or there.
I do not like them anywhere.
I do not like Green Eggs and Ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
A train, a train, a train, a train.
Could you, would you on a train?
Not on a train, fucking there's no A.
This is, there's misspelling in this.
There's misspellings from this.
It's not on a, it is not on a train.
Not in a car, Sam let me be.
I would not, could not in a box.
I would not, could not with a fox.
I will not eat them in a house.
I will not eat them here or there.
I will not eat them anywhere.
I do not eat Green Eggs and Ham.
I do not like them, Sam I am.
Say in the dark, this is unfair.
Here in the dark, would you, could you in the dark?
I would not, could not in the dark.
Would you, could you in the rain?
I would not, could not in the rain.
Not in the dark, not on a train.
Not in a car, not in a tree.
I do not like them, Sam you see.
Not in a house, not in a box.
Not with a mouse, not with a fox.
I will not eat them here or there.
I do not like them, Sam, anywhere.
Oh wow, just a little bit of actor ad libbing.
You do not like Green Eggs and Ham?
I do not like them, Sam I am.
Could you, would you with a goat?
I would not, could not with a goat.
Would you, could you on a boat?
I could not, would not on a boat.
I will not, will not with a goat.
I will not eat them in the rain.
I will not eat them in the dark, not in a tree.
Not in a car.
Would you let me be?
I do not like them in a box.
I do not like them with a fox.
I will not eat them in a house.
I do not like them with a mouse.
I do not like them here or there.
I do not like them anywhere.
I do not like Green Eggs and Ham.
I don't like them, Sam I am.
You don't like them, so you say?
Try them, try them and you may.
Try them and you may, I say.
Sam, if you let me be, I will try them.
You will see.
I say, the Green Eggs and Ham.
I do, I like them, Sam I am.
And I would eat them in a boat.
I would eat them with a goat.
I would eat them in the barn.
I would eat them in the dark and on a train.
And in a car and in a tree.
They're so good, you see.
They're so good.
So I will eat them in a box
and I will eat them with a fox
and I will eat them in a house
and I will eat them with a mouse
and I will eat them here and there.
I say I will eat them anywhere.
So you like Green Eggs and Ham.
Thank you, thank you, Sam I am.
I'm gonna go back to play Yakuza now.
There were misspellings in this
and it fucked me up.
That's not fair.
Is it corporate video background music?
Okay everybody, get set, get ready.
Here comes our five annual company meeting.
We all got matching t-shirts.
The CEO is here.
He's gonna get on stage.
He's gonna have quick and bright white fucking teeth.
He just got him cleaned.
And he just got him polished for this event.
He can't wait to make you feel
like you're one of the company members.
Oh here he is.
Dan Stevenson.
A guy that makes 2.7 million dollars a year.
He loves the fact that you're here.
And by the way, we haven't increased our wages
for this company in probably six years.
Come on in, put your t-shirts on
and get excited for Dan Stevenson.
Get him on stage.
Yeah, ooh, here he comes.
Yeah, woo hoo, yeah.
Everybody, welcome to the self, self-fear realty group.
I love all of you so much.
Thank you, and thank you, and thank you, and thank you.
Self-fear realty group.
What is happening, I don't know.
I kinda lost track, I kinda lost control.
All right, whatever, I lost.
Whoa, whoa, who is this?
And who is this, look at that open mouth.
Look like a fucking idiot.
It was making me laugh because I was doing the John Oliver,
I kept seeing John Oliver in chat.
I do not like them at the most.
I do not like them here or there.
I was gonna start laughing.
Ugh, whatever else can play Yakuza, fuck it.
Did you fix your Joker impression yet?
Joker, what do you mean fix my Joker impression?
It's perfect.
I definitely, I feel like he would do that too.
Don't you feel like that in like an episode
of the John Oliver show, for Christmas this year,
he's going to read the entire greetings that I have.
Read more Dr. Seuss books, no.
All right, can I get five million off the debt for that?
If you're good at something,
never do it for free, Samayam.
By the way, why does Samayam give two shits
about what I like to eat for food?
You want to think about that?
No, you have to eat this, eat it.
I don't want it, I don't really like seafood.
No, no, no, dude, just trust me, trust me.
Just eat it, you'll love it.
I don't want it, I don't want to do that.
Stop telling me to eat foods you like.
You're missing the point, I know, try new things.
What are you doing?
You're gonna look, you're gonna link, link, link, link,
link, link, link, link, link.
What is the link?
I do not like that man, Ted Cruz.
I do not like his far right views.
I do not like his stupid chin.
I do not like his smarmy grin.
I do not like him with a beard.
I do not like him freshly sheared.
I do not like Ted Cruz at all.
That man, Ted Cruz, can suck my balls.
I don't like that man.
I do not like Ted Cruz, I don't.
What does he want?
Oh, here, take a tissue.
I can't believe it, you already did it, whatever.
Ooh, we're friends.
All right, can I please,
I just want to do a story mission for once.
Well, here's the champion district.
Excuse me, do you guys know what the champion is?
He doesn't deserve money off, what's this poll?
We got a poll, hold on.
Chat thinks you deserve 250 million off the debt for that.
Wait a minute, does German deserve 250 million off?
Oh shit, oh man, this is a vote going on right now.
Holy shit, this is 250 mil, that's coming off.
It's 71% saying yes.
The original offer was 75 for no mistakes.
Hey, I'm not keeping the books here,
I'm just the one that has to pay.
All right, that's pretty unanimous.
Fraud, fraud, rigged, stop, stop the count.
I do not like them.
All right, I'm gonna leave it up to you guys,
but that's pretty clear that it's 250 million.
Mash his head down, I want money.
Oh, links, oh, links.
Uh-oh, this, I mean, all right, no more links after this.
I'm done clicking links after this,
I wanna play Yakuza.
No mistakes, farting and screaming, one billion off.
One fish, two fish, red fish, blue fish.
No mistakes, farting and screaming
by reading one fish, two fish.
Oh my god, that's gonna be impossible.
I don't think I'm gonna be able to do that.
I don't think I can do it.
Okay, I'm gonna go for it.
One fish, two fish, red fish, blue fish.
Black fish, blue fish, old fish, new fish.
This one has a little car.
This one has a little star.
Say, what a lot of fish there are.
Yes, some are red, some are blue.
Some are old and some are new.
Some are sad and I can't, oh, I can't, I can't.
I don't care, I'm done.
I can't do that.
Once the lady screamed, it's like, I can't.
You lost, friend.
Why are you here?
There's no place in this name.
I serve a yakuza like you.
Two billion with a face cam, I can't do that.
I know, I gotta do things I know I can do.
No, I can't do it, I can't.
I can't.
That's a long book, that's like a 10 minute read.
I'm not gonna be able to do that.
No, I plan on doing soon anyways.
I wanna do like a laugh you lose thing on Twitch.
People do it and it's like just fun.
I wanna do it, I've done it like weirdly before.
No emotion, right, don't laugh for like subs and stuff.
I wanna do that like for real for the whole stream.
We'll set that up for like in like a week or two or something.
That would be fun.
Sound better today?
I might sound better, but I'm still coughing.
And you just like brought it up to the house like, hey.
I have a dry cough today, being annoying.
I think it's because my nasal turp is being annoying.
I'm definitely getting over it though.
Maybe like another day or two.
Baseball bat, I wanna end it with a, come on.
Holy shit, oh my God, am I gonna like execute this guy?
Holy shit.
Did I get my results?
Yeah, I am negative for COVID-19.
So that's good.
It's probably just like a cold.
Is there gonna be stakes for a laugh you lose?
Oh, of course there are always stakes here.
Always high stakes here.
Yeah.
Yeah, we'll do webcam.
I'll make sure the cam's on.
It's this guy again.
You guys have to be able to verify it or not.
I can't just like sit here with the mic muted.
I don't know.
Can you please stop this yakuza bit
and go back to the Dr. Seuss stream?
No, not today.
What did he say?
Come to the place.
I'm just reading chat right now.
I gotta pay attention to the game.
Why did it change from the attitude of the other players
Why did it change from the attitude of the other place?
Just play the OG Diablo already, man.
I know you want to.
I'm not trying to be arrogant.
But, you know, you're a Diablo.
You're the one who rules.
I play Diablo too with somebody, and just like chill.
I'm a
D2 and chill.
Stop it.
I'm trying to read the video.
All right.
I didn't even to read it.
What?
Did we get a TLDR tweet?
Come on.
No TLDR lore tweet.
Hmm.
Not good.
Are you bored?
No, of course not.
Save it though.
I'm not bored.
Hey, chef.
Thanks for the five community subs, chef piece.
Thank you.
How many times have I saved the game?
Trying just to fast track the story.
Almost several P would like to have a world with you in the discord.
But somebody wants to have a word with me in the discord, so I have to just like go
in there and just listen to them.
What?
Several people want to have a word with me in the discord.
I wonder how loud the screams are going to be when I go into voice one.
I wonder how loud it's going to be when I hurt myself.
My ears going into voice one in the discord.
That Oda guy said if I wait in the penthouse here, he'll show up.
Let's go.
You just ruined the discord.
Well, sorry.
I ain't going in there.
The fight.
If it's a fight you're looking for, it's a fight you'll get.
The next chapter is on Jima.
Is that a different city or something?
With new minigames?
I'm just trying to get through the story to play more minigames.
That's all I care about.
A young thug would come barging in and I would greet him with gentle bruising.
Oda?
Oh, it was that jerk with the germa hair.
Shit, I'm sorry.
I'm like doing this a lot off.
I'm trying to mute.
It's like 500 people in voice one.
What are you just trying to do?
Break the server?
Don't do that.
I'm sure you're all singing your own songs that you have on Spotify.
Oh, by the way, somebody said, hey, dude, do the Spotify thing where you like say what
you've been listening to on Spotify.
I don't even have Spotify installed on any device.
I've never listened to Spotify for one day.
Oh, bonus.
Lightly fast.
No, no, no, no, no, don't do that.
I want to hit somebody with it.
Oh, right in the table.
Into the table.
Come on, get over here.
Table, table, table, table.
Come on, WWF.
No.
I want to WWF into the table.
Holy shit, I'm going to sofa somebody in the head.
Nice.
Can I pick up the whole sofa with beast mode?
What the fuck?
What is this?
What?
Holy shit, I have a sword.
You absolutely can pick up the sofa.
I can pick up the sofa, can I?
I don't think I can.
Come here.
It was the table.
Pepe D.
What's Pepe D?
I can't see it.
Discord is omega fucked and it's your fault.
I apologize to all the Discord mods that are on Discord right now.
Scrambling.
I'm sorry.
I'm just sitting over here Pepe D-ing.
There you're pretty good in a fight.
But good enough to merit President Tachibana personally recruiting you?
I just don't know.
You'll have to fight me and throw me through this window.
Guaranteed and I'll fall onto the street and die.
What weapon is that?
He's holding that backwards.
Hold it like with the hammer pointing out.
Use the hammer side.
It's a good match.
We don't need to fight each other.
Come at me with that intention!
Take this.
Now use the sword.
Let's go!
Sunburst.
This thing is insane.
Now we're going to go beast mode.
Table smash.
He's got burst.
Stay away.
Let me dodge.
Let's go through the window.
I'm going to throw him in the window?
Heal.
Fuck.
Wait.
I got heat.
I'm ready.
I want to throw him out the fucking window.
Go out the fucking window!
Do a heat move with the sword.
Got it.
God damn it.
I don't give a shit.
Whatever.
I'm just going to do all the drugs.
I got heat.
I don't even care.
I just want to play the casino game.
I don't care.
Just kill him.
Slash him once.
I don't care.
All this is just to get to the casino and go to the slot machine.
I don't give a shit about anything else that's going on.
There are no slot machines.
Why did I spend all this time playing this?
This dude's kind of cringe.
Hey, boss.
What's going on?
You tried to test me on Oda, didn't you?
Sword's really good, though.
It does a lot of damage.
Yeah.
Oda-san is an irreplaceable one-armed man to me.
That's why we needed to take his understanding in order to welcome you into our lives.
That's right.
I've been thinking of myself as a fool.
I thought you guys could have trusted me until now.
Tachibana.
It's about time.
Show me what you've been up to all this time.
Why did you come all the way here?
What's the reason for that?
Isn't that nice?
But before that,
What do you think of this town called Kamurocho?
Kamurocho?
I don't know.
I don't even care.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm Kiryu-san.
This town is said to be the feeding ground of the Tojo Clan.
People and money gathered in this town, colored by neon, all night long.
The sweet juice from there can be sucked up by the Tojo Clan.
What are you talking about?
This town is said to be the shining light of the Tojo Clan.
I am the one who opens the casernas.
Just like this.
Play Ellen Degeneres' slots.
I won like $200 on an Ellen Degeneres slot one time.
I think it was like $300 actually.
What the hell is he doing?
What?
Why does the guy have magneto powers?
Money is power.
I want to see how far my power can reach the Tojo Clan.
But I still have a long way to go.
Oh, it's scripted.
Let's see.
He told all the people to turn the lights off for five seconds just to give me a point.
To give me a point.
I must play pocket racing.
Once I get to the new city, I'm just going to play the minigames and then turn the stream off.
I'm going to play the minigames for like two hours.
What?
That's my friend.
That's the guy that I know.
That's the person that's my friend.
The secret.
I'm the secret.
I feel like I'm jumping in halfway through a movie that I have not seen any of.
And I've been here the whole time.
Hey, what are you watching, man?
Oh, this is the cool movie called Yakuza Zero.
Oh, let's sit down and just watch it.
Whatever.
Who's this guy?
Who's that guy?
What city are they in?
I don't know, man.
You got to just jump in.
Just chill.
Are you playing a game you don't care about?
I care very much about this game and all the fun stuff to do in it.
I care about this game.
I think it's really good.
I like I really like this game.
I love the little side campaigns like the fun stuff and like the minigames and like the fighting.
I like this game.
Stop.
Name five characters to erase a bunch of debt.
Name five characters to erase.
How much?
All right.
Kiryu.
Kachibana.
Kazama.
Kuze.
And...
Who's the fifth?
Okay.
Kachibana.
Kiryu.
Kazama.
And...
Kuze.
And Dojima.
Dojima.
I got it.
Oda.
Right.
The guy I just beat.
Dojima.
Dojima is one.
Dojima is the family.
Yeah.
All of them.
All the whole family.
The Dojimas.
Technically counts.
God damn it.
Why?
I really do like the game though.
It's like fun.
As much as I'm not like paying attention.
I know.
But like...
I can't.
It's hard to pay attention.
I need like action.
I need like stuff to happen like right now.
You know what I mean?
I like it though.
I do.
All right.
We now have a new ally in Kachibana.
After two, the real estate broker in the shadows.
Bonus of three million yen.
There we go.
Twenty-two million yen.
Worth twenty times.
Diet member's salary.
climax battle has opened.
Go.
Please pay attention to Mojima at least.
I'm gonna.
Crab.
Giant enemy crab.
There it is.
The Grand Cabaret Casino.
I can go play the Ellen DeGeneres machine.
And watch her go like this.
I'm dancing.
Don't you want to dance with me?
Come dance with me.
Dancing.
Oh wow.
Can't wait to see how much money you win here.
This one's gonna be wild.
Come dance with me.
And then her face fills up like four slots.
And like you get that they're all wild.
I'm paying attention.
I'm paying attention right now.
Dinner.
Drinks.
Waiters.
Theater.
Money.
Watermelon.
Melons.
Ice cubes.
Lady.
Uh.
I'm.
Whatever.
Whatever that was.
Tie on his head.
And.
Money.
Dress.
Roof case.
Tie.
Brown suit.
Green suit.
Riddler.
They're in Tokyo.
No they're not in Tokyo.
I'm paying attention.
Okay we're on vacation.
Backyard.
Rikuzo here.
When we're in our hotel.
Okay.
I'm paying attention.
You had no idea.
in those briefcases, how do you fit in there? you can't really fit much in there
destroy dude thanks for the six subs appreciate it hot towel oh i love hot towels
oh
like i'm in his ear
after you take that shot open mouth wide show her all your teeth do it do it do it
don't order that shit don't order that shit order the whiskey
no no no you're fucking with yourself
no no don't cut him off cut him off say say whiskey thank you good good good good good
don't
make sure he takes the bill very good very good
get three bottles and take two of them i want one it's hard to get um that kind of japanese whiskey
take one for me please
go to the customs please
don't drink too much though you've been drinking a lot
you're doing good you're doing all right less less way less
way less are you are you still in your ear hello
oh it's a different guy
i thought it was like a guy that we cut and it was like he was going wild
uh
me
kick this guy's ass what the fuck
i
smash his saxophone over that guy's head guy in the front row
smash it over the fucking head
Him. It's him.
He's gonna kill this guy.
Oh, this is Majima. I thought Majima was like a city or something.
This is, it's the guy.
You're like, wait till you get to Majima, you're gonna love it at Majima.
Hmm.
Oh. Oh, shit.
Oh, man.
Now you've gone and done it. Now you've done it.
Oh, nice try.
Boy.
As you get your ass kicked to a beat at a club, you're never gonna let that one down.
Okay, wait what?
I can't, don't, don't hit him.
Wrong courage. Don't punch him. Don't hit him.
Avoid the customer's attacks.
avoid the customers attacks but I'm playing the first law of management
customers King even if punched or kicked prysel is out of the question for now
watch for the customer to make a move and then evade their attacks using a
really okay oh it hurt okay second law of management
customers King even in the worst of times you must never forget to provide
only the finest service patients shall be rewarded as now it is time to show
all your customers the ultimate in hospitality that's why in front of an
attacking customer with the heat gauge at third bar what is going on what this
is so bizarre would you like a towel sir okay
the customer always comes first
did I hurt him
this justice non-violent justice
I was saying to like smash the fucking saxophone over his head we're very
different I guess
sake no seki de no shittai wa sake de sosoide
what the hell
we got dirt
okan no minasama ni mo kawarazu konoba
watashi no wakamama desu
everyone's okay with it he's gonna buy the way to get him to spend more money
thank you very much
spin minasama ika ga deshoka drive played from this guy from the beginning
can I play yakuza colon mojima
minasama no kandai no kokorozukai kuchoudai ita shimasu
yuuki aru go handan wo nasareta
round of applause oh yeah
that was awesome
so do we just take control now are we like in a different place I guess kind
of huh it's a parallel campaign oh cool well is it like GTA can I never play as
the other guy again and I go through like the entire entire story is just one
character and just never plays the other one what's going on what is happening
here holy shit I love mojima that was a lit cigarette and he just dropped the
lit cigarette on the ground he just showed behind the curtain
yes
gets a bonus tonight nothing kills
it's the staff members
sonic
May as well go see her now and get this over with. She's probably in the dressing room.
Alright, cool. And there's like an S here? Save point.
Oh, nice. How much money do I have in my bank account on this guy?
30,000 yen? What? I managed like a big hotel casino entertainment venue. I only got 30,000 yen in my pocket?
Should be four zeros added to that.
Alright, dressing room. Where's the dressing room?
Wait, wait, wait. Let's talk to these guys.
Let's see how they're doing.
Can I talk?
What an incredible spot. I had no idea Sotenbori was hiding such a gem.
I've been making this my regular spot whenever I'm in town.
I mean, I'm just like, look. Oh, he's paying attention now. He like wants to talk to everybody.
He's in like the casino. He's in like the fucking hotel. Like, let's go. Welcome to Vegas.
Whatever. Alright. It's interesting to me. I like it.
Where are the dressing rooms though? Just walk around?
I'm gonna go down.
Got a minute.
Oh, sorry about that. What can I do for you?
Can you call Kane for me? I need to talk to her.
Yes, sir. Of course.
This deal is spacing out on the clock.
Hi, sir. Nice work out there tonight.
Thanks, Kane-chan.
So, you wanted to talk to me?
She said she was locking horns with Sakurako.
Hmm. Where do I start?
Hmm. Alright. Do we lay down the law?
I think not. I think we'd be like, hey.
Let's talk for a minute here.
Yeah, you're really smoking tonight, babe.
I thought some new idol singer wandered in.
Oh, you. That kind of flattery won't get anybody but paying customers anywhere, sir.
What? Is that wrong?
That right? I take it back then.
What? So it was just flattery, huh?
You wound me, boss.
Aw, come on. You know I can't tell a lie.
Here, I'll buy you dinner sometime soon. You forgive me?
Really? Oh, I'd love you, sir.
This is idiotic. Time to get to the point.
It's been about a month since you came on here.
Yeah? How's it going? Think you can make a real go of it at the Grand?
Oh, I think so. The hall is much bigger than the last club I worked at, so it was pretty daunting at first, but I'm totally used to it now.
And more and more and more customers are coming here specifically to see me.
Yeah? That's great to hear.
Not surprising from the number one gal from one of the oldest cabarets in the Kita area.
I guess I was imagining things then.
Hmm? What do you mean?
Oh, see, the one month mark's actually when I see that most girls up and leave.
I was a little worried you might be getting the itch too.
Oh, have no fear of that. I wouldn't dream of quitting now.
That hag Sakurako's been trying to play the seniority card on me, but I don't even notice her.
Damn, girl. Hag? This is pretty serious.
Aw, don't be like that. Sakurako's a vet here. She looks after the other girls too. Most love that about her.
Try to get along, yeah?
Oh, I hate nosy types like that. And she's got a whole entourage.
Whatever, soon I'll have my own clique and I won't have to deal with them.
Does she even realize she's getting lectured here?
Dan says adored this one.
She's even giving me a little too.
All right, we're gonna go more direct.
Direct. Better make it loud and clear for her.
That ain't right.
What kind of a champ?
You gotta learn to read the room.
Huh?
Doesn't matter how good you are at your job or how popular you get.
You've snubbed your seniors like that and you'll wake up one day with nothing but enemies here.
Fine by me, not like I do the job to make friends with the other girls.
Really? That the best you can do? I'm disappointed. I doubt you'll be around here long enough to make those enemies, then.
Wait, what's that supposed to mean? Is there a problem with my work?
Nailed it. She's the competitive type. With her pride on the hook, she'll take the bait.
Look, I ain't asking you to be friends with Sakuro-chan. In fact, you two make much better rivals.
Rivals? Yeah. Well, not the kind that shanks the other in the back.
Compete. Puss each other. Get better. You'll bring up all the other girls with you.
Stop the accent. What? You don't like it? You guys don't like the accent?
You guys don't like it? You don't like it? You don't like it?
Right now. Right now. You're just tripping over each other.
And that makes it harder for everybody around you to step up.
Customers may love a gal like that, but I got no use for them here.
The grand needs girls who are popular with the guys and the girls.
The guys and the girls?
Thing is, I know you could be that girl.
Kanae-chan, that's the only reason I'm coming down on you about it. I like this.
You really think I'm... I'm sorry, sir. I was acting like a spoiled brat.
I work on being that girl. I'm being more considerate. Please, give me the chance.
There, see? You do get it. I knew you were a keeper.
I knew you were a keeper, kid.
And I hope you'll keep helping me improve when I need it.
Matthew McConaughey.
Ah, finally. Took long enough.
Shit.
And wait. What was that waiter's deal?
Can't have him zoning out on me like that.
Better go have a chat.
This car goes fast, but it's safe, too.
Know what I'm saying?
When you drive a Lincoln, sophistication is key.
Okay, cool. That worked.
What else can I do? I'm gonna talk to this guy.
Quit while you're ahead.
Why the long face? Need to use facilities?
Sir, no, no. I got a letter from my little sister back home.
Yeah? What's the word?
My father's sick, unfortunately.
The doc says he needs to be hospitalized, but the procedure they want to do runs 500,000.
But I ain't got that kind of cash.
Sorry to hear that.
You try asking the floor manager for advance?
Another emergency a while back already forced me to ask for one.
I'm afraid if I ask again, I'll get canned.
Especially for so much.
You in the habit of breaking mirrors, kid?
Here, I'll spot you.
What? But sir, I can't.
Don't sweat it. You can always replace money.
Saying can be said about people. Once they're gone, that's it.
Sir, as I recall, you ain't been back home in a while.
Yeah? Take a few days off, too. Go visit your pops.
Gosh. Thank you, sir.
Only thing that matters right now is keeping this place running smooth.
I'll throw as much money at it as I need to.
I'm having fun. I don't care.
Looks like that's it for my staff troubles.
It's about time I checked in out of the hole.
See what's going on outside.
Ban that person for a day!
One of the customers is placing insane orders now that he knows he isn't paying for it.
He went down the line of our top vintage wines to start,
and he started on our best whiskeys and brandies.
Well, I mean, when you hear the words,
this guy's gonna pay for every drink, it's like,
okay, let's go to the bottom of the wine list.
Let's turn the page three times.
We're gonna go to the bottom.
Start at the priciest and work your way down the list, huh?
Guys, this is the only way he's going to read and comprehend the story.
Well, somebody gets it, but, okay.
Start at the priciest.
Shit.
Now, I haven't been paying attention.
I haven't been paying attention. I haven't read anything.
I haven't comprehended a word.
Right this way.
Fine, just do the accent.
Oh, goddammit.
We have to dodge this guy, too.
He's already such a dick.
Don't you think he'd be like, oh, my god, I'm doing all this expensive stuff.
Don't you think he'd be like, oh, my god, I'm doing all this expensive shit.
Yeah, what can I do for you?
All right, I'll cool it. I'll cool it.
I won't order anymore. I'm sorry.
I've got a little ahead of myself.
I have to be his dick.
I don't know. I thought I was going to microwave the cigarettes.
I've got to reheat these cigarettes.
They're getting cold.
Oh, that's not even a microwave.
It's a hot towel bin.
You get a raid?
Who raided?
Raid? I don't see a raid.
Where? Where? I don't see one.
I don't see a raid. Who raided?
Is it your raid? I don't see it anywhere.
Whoever raided it, he did.
What's up? Thanks.
I don't see it anywhere.
What happened?
Oh.
I'm sorry.
What's up?
I don't see a raid.
I did not expect that.
It's a shame.
You, who on the outside is jealous of others,
is all alone, in this town in search of something else.
People who call themselves happy are all doing the same as you.
Isn't the weather hot today?
I feel like I saw you in your dimples.
But, well.
This is the situation you're into, no?
Oh, this is punishment back in the Yakuza
Retainer to the fifth only Alliance chairman there was a lot I couldn't read it all
Anta New York, I don't need to know
This month I'm going to sell
This month's take is that I can keep a case you'll have your 100 million by next month
Oh, that's amazing
Don't be stupid
If you get it, I'll tell Shimano's dad that I can go back to the Gokudo
I haven't forgotten my promise
Well, did you make that promise?
I'm not going to be able to make a joke out of this
No, you can't
I'll give you another 500 million
If you do that, I'll listen to you
That's bullshit
You weasley rat bastard
Oh, no, I can't do that
Shit
What? You're not going to hit me?
Well, I can't do it, but
I thought he was going to do it
If you do that
You're going to go back to that dark place
I don't want that
Oh shit
This is the way you want to go back to the world
Yakuza is like you
It's easy to let go
Oh, you fuckers
What do you think?
I think you should take revenge
I'll make a lot of money
If I do it to go back to Gokudo, I'll do anything
Oh, you're in the same debt pit as Mojima
I like Mojima
He's
2 billion, 3 billion, 4 billion
Add another 500 to the debt
Yeah
How much are you getting paid to play this game?
I don't know how much you guys gave me today
How about zero?
What about her?
Yeah, what's his deal?
Hey, what?
Oh, no
They're separating us
I'll do my best not to lose the deal
I have to earn 500,000 yen after all
That's not good
Pardon me, sir
I just got a call from Noriko-chan saying she's jumping ship to a different club
Yeah, I just found out
Did you know?
Why are you so sudden?
If Noriko-chan is gone, it will have a big impact on the sales
I know
But it's the owner's decision
There's nothing we can do about it
Is that so?
But what should we do from now on?
Damn it
There's no time to get depressed
Look at that, what about it?
Who's the hottest hostess in town that we don't already have?
A hostess from somewhere else?
If it's a girl from somewhere else, that's right
Nozomi-chan from Odyssey is the clear winner
She's a big part of why they're the strongest rival
I see
Yeah?
Well then
Well then, I guess I'll be heading out
I guess I'll be heading out
Not too soon though
Hey, Shion!
Where are you going?
See you around, kid
Of course I will
I'm going to take Nozomi out of our house
I'm going to be poaching Nozomi to come to our floor
Taking out the number one rival?
Isn't that bad?
How are we supposed to do that?
The world at night is full of evil
If we fall here, we'll be crushed
The strong eat the weak
We true
And the grand will come crumbling down in days
My job is to do what it takes
To...
Can you run back the prompter?
I'll get it again, don't worry
I promise
Alright, we gotta go get that other girl to come over here
And do...
And be at our hotel
Netflix dub
Do karaoke?
I did karaoke
I wanna go check out the town
Do I have access to the town now?
You know what a cabaret is?
Yeah
It's a...
It's like a performance
It's a short performance of music and theater and dance
Like a bunch of dancing and singing and performances
Go to Odyssey
Ooh, okay, we have a town here
Oh, look at this
Okay, what's this?
Shot bar
Bart with darts and pool
There's the cabaret
There's...
Oh, and the arcade
Alright, we'll go to the bars with darts and pool
Let's go
You there
Huh?
You are the master of the Hell House, the Grand, yes?
Yeah
Yeah, that's me
I knew it
Even the way you walk is refined
Guarded, you have no blind spot
Despite appearances
I'm sorry, sir, have we met before?
My name is Sumotaro Komike
Heir to a certain form of martial arts in its present master
Martial arts?
Yes, but lately I've felt my technique slipping
My edge has been dulled
So I left the lights of Tokyo in order to train
Yet even here I find this age of excess
Gluttons and fools gorging on carnal pleasures
Nobody hungers anymore
Then I heard talk of a lounge called the Grand
They said it was the home of a most interesting man
Pardon my answer
But have you visited our establishment before?
What kind of question is that?
Guttling booze with painted ladies hanging all over you
Bah! Wanted excess
Of course I haven't been there
Well, then why the hell am I doing song and dance if you ain't accustomed?
Besides, that's a washed-up martial art as well with me
That hungry air about you
It is far beyond the men I've fought in recent years
Would you do me the honor?
What honor would that be?
Want me to fight you?
Precisely
A deeper strength sleeps within you
I refuse to let it lie dormant and unused any longer
What?
You okay upstairs, pal?
You don't earn me skinny hands profit
Busy gal
Busy guy
Hide behind your merchant's guise all you like
I know money isn't what feeds that hunger
Whatever honest life you make
A show of living I can see the demon gnawing at you inside
Hmm
There's only one way to appease the demon, son
Face the strong in combat
And set loose those fighting instincts struggling to burst free
And you're telling me you're that strong guy?
Oh, as it happens, I am
Now do you see a reason to face me?
Not that it will stay any...
It won't be very easy for you
There's no talking sense to you, is there?
Fine
You win
I was just thinking it had been a while since I really cut loose
Not here though
Somewhere
Not here
Hmm, if you insist
Who talks like that?
Me
This place should work
Hmm, you are awfully...
It's a different guy
You are... It's the same person
You are awfully unhesitant to agree...
I wasn't paying attention
In agreeing to this, I am starting to think you keep the true extent of your strength hidden away
You must have your reasons, I know I have mine
For the fist is like the sword
Leave it in its sheath to rust
And you will not be able to draw it when it is needed
What say you?
Do you feel an urge to shrug off your restraints
And fight to the full extent of your abilities for a change?
You're offering?
I'm game
Not too big on the idea of opening up a can
Of a creaky old guy like you
Though
Fuck
No, cast aside such worries
He even doddled to the edge left
And these should prove sufficient to handle a pup like you
Show me everything you've got
He's throwing
Alright, I'm done
A thug style incorporates a number of merciless attacks
One of these is the eye pope
You land an eye poke attack
The enemy will turn their back to you in pain
Eye poke?
Holy shit, I just dropped him
One of the special moves of the thug style
Is a heat action called the essence of choking
This heat action triggers when an enemy attacks you
Or when you just circle behind them
Okay
The heat gauge at third press Y when an enemy attacks
Yeah, we've seen this
Oh my god, I just broke that fucking old dude's neck
Defeat him
And run at me, run at me
Come on, come get me
He'll snap his neck
The essence of murder
Holy shit
Dropping frames?
Am I?
Oh, I did drop some
We good?
Yeah, the internet's been a little weird here
The last couple of nights
I've had like small internet hiccups
Over the last like maybe two nights
No, it should be good
I mean, I haven't had internet problems in like a year
I mean, I'm on fiber
I have a thousand thousand
But sometimes I'm sure it can happen
I don't have my VPN on right now
But yeah, the last two nights
After like 8 o'clock at night
For some reason it's gotten like a little weird
I'll give him a call
See if anything's going on
Is it still dropping frames?
Oh, it is, yeah
Oh shit, it is, yeah
It is happening
It might be doing like maintenance or something
A few nights
Because it's been like the same time every night
I'll give him a call
See what's going on
Yeah, it's been like 8 months since there's been any internet problems
It's been perfect
I've had almost zero problems at all
But yeah, I'm definitely dropping a shitload of frames so I can see it
Hold on, one sec
Let me just see what happens when I do this
Let's find out
Sorry about that
They're trying to block Majima
Yeah, this is the second night in a row
Oh yeah, no, this is bad
This is terrible
Terrible, terrible
I'm getting like 8 megabits down
And I have a thousand down
Literally like an hour ago, this was a thousand
Oh yeah, this is not good, something's wrong
I think they're doing maintenance or something
Your VPN? I don't have a VPN turned on right now
Facecam react
It's been the exact same time
Two days in a row
I think it looks like it's evening out a little bit
Sorry about that, it's going to be like that probably till I end
Alright, dude, come at me
Lime, well fiber is
It's fiber
The way that fiber works, you don't share it
It's not cable
So that's why when something like this happens
It's like they're doing something
I was on cable, if you remember
A year or two ago, a couple years ago, I was on cable
I've been on cable forever
You still share the line though
From my understanding, you don't share
A node with a fiber
With actual fiber line
Like a true fiber connection
Fiber to the house is not
A shared line with your neighborhood
Is this still happening?
Oh, a node
I'll do karaoke
Is it good now? Is it better?
Alright, I'm going to do
I want to do
Mahjong, mahjong, mahjong, mahjong
Go, go, go, go, go, go
Let's go
At Mahjong Jambalaya, you can play at tables
With varying rates or participate in ranked matches
The tables are beginning, low, right, intermediate
High, advanced and high
The price to play and the strength of the opponents
Vary depending on the table
Ooh, alright, let's go
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Oh, I don't have any money
I don't have any money
Sorry, I don't have any money
Going to the casino
Alright, I'm ready to play at the casino
Okay, sir, what's your bet?
I don't have any money, I just wanted to come in
And play
What's over here? This is Mahjong
Darts, did you just stop me?
Don't stop me, I want to go play darts
What can I get you?
You can get me
None of this
I want to play darts
Wasn't this a dart place?
Dying again? Fuck
No
Shit, it is
I got to call them
I got to call it here
Fuck
Sorry guys
I'm going to call the internet company
It's just not supposed to be happening
And by the way, this is the
First problem in like a year
It's been rock solid
So, something's going on
Let me just figure out what it is
So I'll be back
Tomorrow
If I
Kind of cold gets worse
I might take tomorrow and just not stream
Save the game, I will
I think doing like the voices may have
Caused a little bit more of a problem
But I got to call
And see what's going on, because this is definitely not supposed to be happening
I had a lot of fun though
I'm going to play it again
When I come back, if it's not tomorrow
Then listen to me
Okay, when I come back tomorrow, we're going to have so much fun
If I shouldn't have done so many
Of those throat things
Where the sound comes out
If I'm not live tomorrow, I'll see you guys
The day after that, which would be
Saturday
So, plan on Saturday, I might turn it on tomorrow
But I'm going to call the internet company right now
And see what the hell is going on
But that is going to end this stream
We'll do Yakuza again
I like it, I wouldn't stream the game
Three times in a row if I didn't like it
I'll see you guys either tomorrow or Saturday
Have a great rest of your night
Thanks for watching everybody
Sorry, we're kind of ending like half hour 45 minutes early
I didn't want to end right now, but you've got to catch it
And make sure nothing's going on that I have to fix or something
I'll see you guys soon
Let's do the ending credits here
Here come the subs
Thanks everybody for subbing as always
Really appreciate it
Saving the game, you can even hear it, trust me
You can hear me saving
See, I just shoved the guy
I just pushed the guy like into the street
Here we go
Okay
Alrighty, raid, raid, raid
Who's streaming, let's see
Who's live right now
We have
Uhhhh
Alright, we're going to raid Neander's
Raid Vinny
Vinny's, what do you mean Vinny
Vinny's not live
Hey, I
I'm a Neanderth supporter
Yeah, let's go raid Neanderth
I never catch her live
Neanderth is a Vtuber
She's very funny
Am I a Neanderthal?
Of course I am
Look at me
What's she doing, playing away out
That'll be interesting
I'll see you guys later
I'm going to go drink some hot tea
Go tell Neanderth I said hello
You're going to be there in a second
I'll see you guys later
Take care, goodbye
If I don't see you tomorrow, I'll see you Saturday
Go, go, go, go
Raid, raid, raid, raid, raid
Everybody raid
Raid, raid, raid, raid
Raid, raid, raid
Get that up to 5k
Or I'm not pressing it
Go, go, go, go
Get that up to 5k
People are leaving it
No, get that shit up to 5k
We're going with a 5k raid
Get on there
49, let's go
49, 49, 49, 49
Come on, stop leaving
Join it, don't leave it
No, no, stop it, stop fighting
Just join it
You only got like 10 more seconds before you
You better get that to 5k or I'm going to be real mad
5k, you only got like 15 more seconds
Go, go, go, go, go
5k, 5k, 5k, 5k
You're almost there, you got it
Come on, do it
You gotta give me that 5k
You got like 5 seconds
Get up there, get up there
Come on, it's so close
It's right there
Oh no
Yeah, I'll see you later