Hi guys, welcome back. Those of you that joined us yesterday, we're going to be continuing. Sit down, sit down. Someone's standing on their desk back there. Get sit down. Calling your fucking mom to tell her about all the things you do wrong here in this room. I'm going to do item shop again. Reset here. Receipt here. Part two. I'm having a lot of fun. We are our newest hurdle we have to climb up here is
$200,000. I don't know. I almost didn't do the last one. $80,000 seems very difficult to go over. I'm going to do my best to try to get past $200,000. But anyways, relax, stretch your legs out. Stretch your back out. We'll be going very shortly. See you in two seconds. Mouse off screen. I already know. So here I freaked out. And this is a day. Imagine you can do this to shit in real life.
Wait, my bills are due. My bills are due on the 21st. Hold on. Let me go through the whole day and try to make as much money and try to like sell stuff as fast as I possibly can. And then did I do it tomorrow? If only that were possible. IRL or in the game? Well, I mean like IRL. You could do that in real life. Well, the idea is you try to pay your bills on time and not have a fantasy of freezing time to be able to pay your bills in one day.
Anyways, procrastination. That's not that that's really bad procrastination. I understand like not brushing your teeth for a day and like waiting until 730 p.m. before you like fuck. I probably should brush my teeth. That's procrastination. Waiting until 1159 the day before your bills are due. That's irresponsibility. Let's just come on. Let's just call it. Come on. Anyway, here's our shop.
You see on the 29th, we owe $200,000. We got a long way to go. So what the hell? What was the last thing I did? Let's see. Yes. And those look, we have a whole new slew of people that are going to come to the stream. And we I know it is an animated Japanese style television game. But just give it a minute. Because I know you just heard that. You heard that sound and you were just like, I'm out of here. But just wait. This game is very fun. Just give it a minute.
We gave it a few minutes yesterday. We gave it actually seven and a half hours yesterday. It was worth it. Turn the voice off. I'm gonna get shit for this. But I turned. I turned the voice down since yesterday. I didn't think anybody was gonna notice and you probably wouldn't have noticed except for somebody said that they could hear it. That's all right. That's a decent level. Oh, god damn it. There. That's better. All right. See, you're fine. Anyways, we're
the whole point of this game. If you weren't here yesterday is you got to buy high sell low. You got to bind items. You got to put them in your store and then people buy them and you got to haggle with them. So what's what was the last thing that happened here? We just got the new day here. I'm gonna put the wooden chess piece here. Wait, wait, I just I just didn't get a really expensive fucking item. I did right here. $15,000. There was other things. All right, all this shit. I want to hear the voices. I did. They're fine. I turned it back up.
Necklace. All right, I think I'm ready to I can't I couldn't I can't craft anything else. All right, I'm gonna hold on to this shit. Here we go. Time to open the store. Oh, charm. Welcome. Hey, girl. Heaven. Are you ever not bright and happy? Nope. A bright and happy welcome is a key to sales. Good products is a key to sales. I got a present for you. Oh, shit. We just got a new fucking hero card. Wait, there's a 60 second slow mode on right now.
That's pretty slow. Hold on. Wait, let me fix it. How about uh, how about uh, 15? 20? What did I just do? Oh shit. I did something wrong. I think I just broke it. Uh oh. Uh oh. Uh oh.
Uh oh. There is now no slow mode. And we got 10 seconds slow mode. We got it. I think. Yeah, I think I like turned it off. All right, we're good. We're good. We got a card. I was wondering why I didn't see any POG champs over here. We got a fucking R2D2 card and I looked over and I didn't see any POG champs. I was like, what's going on here? There's gonna be like 2000 of them. Damn straight. If you ever need the help of a professional Burke such as myself, give me a look. Going to negative slow mode. You can't do that.
So are we, are we dumping uh, this dude in here right now? What's his name? Louie? Do a six hour slow mode. You know, I thought about doing a stream before of having a permanent slow mode, like 12 hours or something. So you get to say one thing in chat and you better make it come. Do it. Do it. No, that has to be something that's planned. Not during recetteer and item shops. Actually, that's a pretty great time to do it. No, it's not. I want to get. No, no. I want real feedback of stuff.
I'm selling and buying. Well, receipts been good to me. Consider it my way of paying guys back. All right, we got a new card. By the way, for those of you that weren't here yesterday, when you get a card from somebody, it means that they had to buy them for everybody in the class because so everybody gets a valentine in the class. So you have like 20 cards and you have to hand them out to everybody. Even if you might not want to hand them out to everybody, your mother still tells you to do that. And you're like, ah, I guess come on.
I didn't get one. I only wanted to get my valentine to like my two friends in the class so we could like make jokes on the cards. I couldn't make jokes. Are you really just some random dispassionate loan shark? You should have undid slow mode to max out the minus twos. Yeah, hold on a minute. That's bullshit.
10 seconds slow mode. Usually it's like 20 to 30 seconds slow mode. I'm getting dumped here. This is fucking market manipulation at its finest. Anyways, let's go.
I've been wondering if all you're really after is getting that loan repaid. Wouldn't it not be a lot easier to steal the house and cash out? Nothing's stopping you after all except for one thing, the law.
That is not it at all. As an agent of Terme, I take a little bit of friendly advice. The harder you try to spin some elaborate tale, the worse it ends up being when the web comes apart at the end.
Not that I have any room to lecture on anyone on that front. So sticking to your guns just a loan shark then? Unbelievable! Did you give her your card just to ask me that? Maybe I did. Guess I've been a bit of a busybody, eh?
Everyone who comes through that door is like that. That girl. Something about her inspires people to care. I suppose she does that. Are you going to buy something or what? Well then let me know if you need my help. Hey, thanks again.
So thank you for all that. I appreciate the card. Now let's sell something. What can I help you with? I want some food. I got plenty of food. Ooh, holy shit, I got honey. No, no, no, no. This girl's cheap. She won't spend $2,300 on that.
Let's go the, let's go the egg toast. $600. That's too much, right? You don't pay over it for anything. She never pays more than like 99% over. She's back again. Alright, I want the fish too. No, no, no. She wants to sell this to me.
45% of base, take it or lose. Yes, I'm not going anywhere. Avocado toast. Stop letting her do this. Alright, Miss Capitalist, in two days I want you to get two scarves for me. I don't know if I can do that. I have to buy them. No, there we go.
I put an order for, uh oh. Probably should have checked that before we started. Should I reload? Yeah, but then we have to do that whole scene again. I would have done, but hold on, this guy's, are we going to get this, this guy's about to drop 15 grand. Should I reset it?
No, that's my own fault. I fucked that up. I need to be a better store owner. Um, this is a big sale here though. We have like 20, 20,000? No, he's not going to pay 200% for this. I'm going to start at 21. Alright, I got to go down.
Shit, uh, 19, 19.5? No, no, it's got to be like 18. Got it. There it goes. Uh, I sold it. Could use a treasure. Do I have any treasure? Eh. I mean, could I just, this is technically a treasure, isn't it? Could I be like, what can I interest you in one of these?
I guess you have to get a statue. 128. It's not under the treasure tab. It's not a treasure. I see, I see. Makes sense. You have a bracelet. I do. I have a really good bracelet actually, don't I? You're not going to, no. She's not going to pay 2600 bucks for this.
28. Ah, why did I even try to sell it to you? 25, 26. She does, she doesn't, she never buys anything. Alright, I need to, I got to take some stock here. Hold on. What do we have for orders? So tomorrow, I need two weapons and two foodstuffs by tomorrow.
What do I, I need weapons. Alright, let's go get some weapons. If I was an item in this game, I'd be under the treasure tab. Oh, what? That was so cute. Thank you. Alright, hold on. Let's go to fusion. I need a staff. Alright, bat wings. Backscratcher and impetition staff. I don't have any free honey. I only have one. Can't do that anymore. What else have we got here?
Ooh, the price is currently down on this, but I do have a charred lizard. I have a shell necklace. I could get a shell necklace right now. It's from the other store, right? Let's do it. Wait, wait, wait. I need, no, no, no. I need, no, you're right. I need this for the dude. Fuck. It's alright. I need two weapons then.
I'm going to say, um, let's go with the expensive shit. Let's go with the thief's knife and steel sword. I'm going to make cash tonight. And then I need two foodstuffs. I think I already have it. Let's go to the pub. Sit down and find out what we need to do.
Ah, she's drunk. Ah, silly fairy. You can't schtick a person in a cup. Maybe I could stuff you into one though. Hee-tee-hee. You aren't shumadish. Are you drunk or are you doing a Sean Connery impression? I don't understand.
I believe I shall pass. Oh, well, you're lost then. You're schtick in the mud. Maybe Rosetta wants shum.
What is this? Stop clinging to her for heaven's sake. I swear for professional Burke. You could not hold your liquor at all.
What, you again? I told you no.
What is?
Come on, can't a guy get a break? Cut me just a little slack here.
Not just no, but hell no. Do you have any idea how long your tab already is? You'll drink me out of a business at this rate.
A son of a... All right, all right. I can take a hint. I'll call it for the day.
Who's that guy? Oh, what an argument.
Oh, him? That happens all the time. That guy keeps putting stuff on his tab and doesn't pay up, so he keeps getting chased out.
I think he even has Louis beat when he comes to be... What? Oh, okay, hold on. I think he even has Louis beat when it comes to being poor.
Well, either way, why don't worry too much about it.
The unwise use of money is the human trade, which I find the most perplexing by far.
Unwise-ish of... Well, anyway, come on, Rosetta. Your big sis wants to introduce you to a man named Jack.
Oh, absolutely not.
The plaza in the evening feels kind of lonely. It makes you think it's really time to go home now.
You really think it has that effect? I don't feel... Oh, it does.
Oh, the smell of the evening... I thought that said piss. It makes it even lonelier.
Well, as a fairy, I cannot pretend to understand how smell could make you lonely.
But our dinner tonight is going to be salted porridge. It certainly will not be pie.
Salted porridge? That's like the default gross food, isn't it?
That's the stuff that comes out of an ice cream scoop in every movie.
Oh, man, now I really feel lonely for some reason.
College life dinner. No, they don't serve that in college dining halls.
You don't line up and have them hand out your tray and somebody dumps porridge onto the tray.
That's not a school I don't think I want to be at.
What? What school did you go to where they did a line of porridge? Like Oliver Twist?
All right, let's go. I need to make some money here.
So I need... What do they want?
I needed two weapons, which I have, and then two foodstuffs, right?
I think I already have that. I do. I have two pieces of food, don't I? Yeah, I do.
Not even 9%. Scaves? What's a scave? Scarves.
Sca... How do you say scarves? Scarves? I thought scarves.
It's got staff and stave. That's what screws me up. Why? Staff, stave.
Scarf, scaves. I could just do two shitty ones. Yeah, let's get the expensive one.
All right, I'm ready. Am I enjoying the game? I think the game's great.
I want... Let's put the helm out there. I have enough food, right? Yeah, I do.
Oh, hey, welcome. Hey, Rosette, listen to this. Why do you... Are you still, like, drunk?
It's been, like, fucking 12 hours. What is it? And are you okay? You seem a little different.
So, I got a message from the guild today.
They totally found a new dungeon with Shumshishish.
Nobody does that when they're drunk. I don't know why everybody decided to take
that one old Looney Tunes cartoon of the mouse, going like...
Everybody just copied it. That doesn't happen. Really, really super, really.
Everyone is calling it the Amber Garden.
Boy, I hope it's that kind of amber.
There's a line here I'm crossing where I'm starting to turn into Little Nicky.
Oh, what was I talking about? Oh, yeah, so if you get the chance, we should totally go.
I mean, who knows what kind of items we could find. Yeah, items. Yeah, that's true.
Well, then, back to the pub with me. Fwoosh. Oh, the Joker.
Yeah, that could be the Joker, too. A new dungeon, huh?
Ooh, unlocked. Start buying shit.
Candy Apple. 2000. Back. You want the helm.
Now that, I'm sorry, but that's 2300. Make it a little cheaper.
That's a very rare item. It's a warrior's helm. Thank you.
Yeah, I sold the warrior's helm. Looking for something?
Oh, the more I look at this, the more I just need to have it. What's your toll in filthy...
Do you buy stuff or are you cheap or what?
A little less. 720.
Oh, fuck off. Egg. Pick this one. What do you mean egg?
This guy's getting ready to fight. All right, well, hold on.
He's either getting ready to fight or play a game of hockey.
These items could be used for hockey as well. That makes sense.
All right, let's do 1000. Same thing.
Two food stuffs. Oh, wait. Yes, I can do two food stuffs in two days.
Here's the end of the day. He's ready to go fight Grandma's ghost.
Hey, can you turn her voice off and also the game, please?
That's just not going to happen.
News! The price of daggers has increased. Ooh.
The price of daggers has increased. And I got two. This is going to be insane.
Hold on. I need to... I'm going to sell these on the floor.
Somebody wants... Hold on. I'm buying some stupid shitty item.
Wait, what?
I have a little problem, but I need your help where...
We automatically refuse to place horse heads in anyone's bed.
I would like a fucking, like, nine-year-old know what that is.
Oh, no, nothing like that. Actually, I have a package that needs to be delivered to the orphanage near the town square.
You've seen it, right? I'm a bit busy right now, so...
Oh, yeah, sure. We can do that.
Thanks, girls. This will help me out.
All right, then. Package acquired. Charge forth.
Indeed, not a bad idea.
The merchant's guilt has been generous to us in the past, so getting them into our pocket now will only help us down the road.
In you are now. Wait. Wait a minute.
For the orphans. Let's go!
Now hold on a second here, girls.
Thank you. I hope everyone enjoys the package.
Delivery successful. Forward to Janus.
Now hold on a minute here, girls.
Well, I'm glad we were able to... By the way, yeah, I did read that out loud.
Well, I am glad we were able to get that done with quickly.
I'll say, everyone seemed to like the package.
Although, what do you think they'll do with, I mean, just the...
Honestly, I would rather not think of it. What's in the package?
Blasted Guild Master, I think I would have preferred the horse head.
Well, either way, we pulled it off. Back to the shop.
Is the shop gonna be, like, on fire or something? I don't understand.
What's up?
It may be nothing. Over there, however, is that not...
It's the man with the huge bar bill, isn't it?
Yes, but why on earth is he hiding behind a wall?
Hey, yeah, that's suspicious.
The four...
Yay!
Wait, receipt!
Hold it! You there!
Seize whatever vaguely sneaky thing you're doing at once!
Whoa!
This is an orphanage. What are you doing here, appearing at it like that?
What? Mind telling me who you are?
My name is Receit. I run the item shop, Receit, on the hill.
I was on my way home from delivering a package, and I saw you being off-neeking!
Oh, you're the one who runs that whole...
Pretty impressive at your age.
We seem to have gotten off to a bad start.
Name's Elan.
In the strictest terms, I guess you could call me an adventurer.
I kind of owe something to this orphanage, so I stop by Elan.
Why all the sneakification and peering then?
I wasn't peering, really. I was more gazing at...
I guess with guilt.
What? What are you...?
Times have been a little hard lately. You know how it can be.
I can't afford to buy the kids who live their traits anymore.
So I think to myself, it'd just be better if I didn't show up at all.
But still...
Oh, I see. I'm sorry I was angry at you, but...
Hey! Oh, it's Elan! Elan's here! He's got treats!
Oh, shit! Oh, hell's bells!
Now they've seen me. Let me... little girl... Do you have any treats?
Gotta let them down and go in empty-handed, I guess.
It'll be okay.
Huh?
Look at them. The kids appreciate you, not the gifts.
Yeah, kind of weird for a merchant to say you don't need gifts, I guess.
But it's true, really. Go on, they're waiting.
Little miss.
Come play with us, Elan. I'm gonna be the guard, okay? You're the thief.
Aye.
You're fans await, Mr. Elan. Good luck.
Oh, maybe you should go easy on the alcohol, too.
For their sake.
She sure told me!
Reset of Resetti!
Huh.
Go easy on the alcohol.
Was it my imagination, or was that a fairy giving me a hell of an evil eye just now?
That's not the correct voice for that guy. It's gotta be lighter.
I guess that's the wrong voice.
Hi, are you okay, miss? You look kinda down.
Oh, Resett, I'm tired for some reason. I wonder if I'm starting to get old and slow.
If you're tired, it can help to eat something sweet.
Don't do that.
Sugar stimulates your parasympathetic nervous system and energizes you.
That sounds like big company propaganda is what that sounds like, little miss.
I don't know where you got that bullshit from.
Anyway, you should go eat something sweet. Like, for example, candy or canned peaches.
We have a lot of sweet stuff to choose from.
That does sound good. Maybe I'll have some chocolate cake.
Thanks for the advice, you two.
Oh, cake. Now I'm jealous. Business opportunity.
Imagine going to the doctor and being like, yeah, something's wrong.
I'm really fucking tired all the time.
I kinda feel like shit. I'm sleepy in the morning. I don't have really any energy.
I'm a little bit down.
Oh, well, you should eat just a cake.
What?
Yeah, just eat a cake. See you in a few months when you come back for something else.
You don't think I should probably start exercising?
No, just eat candy out of a jar.
That's the kind of scenario where all of a sudden they've done comedy routines where then that doctor is arrested.
And it's like, holy shit, that guy's pretending to be the doctor.
And the real doctor is in the back, tied up or something.
They've done that before, right?
Alright, let me see. What do I have to do today?
Today is two weapons, two food stuffs.
I have the scarves. I have all the food. I have everything I need.
I got everything I need.
Oh, but wait, wait, wait. Not quite true, though. Hold on.
I want to put these out on the floor because I can sell them for way, way more than they're worth.
And then I'm going to get two shitty weapons and then overprice the fuck out of them when they come in to buy them.
Or should I overprice the fuck out of these in the order?
I wonder. Alright, I'll put them in the order.
Let's get the necklace out there. What else do I got?
Nobody buys the rings.
Alright, that seems good.
Let me just make sure I got plenty of food.
I got the two weapons. I'm ready to go.
Let's get an orange up there, too.
Here we go.
Oh, hello there, receipt. Still manning the store, as always, I see.
Hi, Aluette. You look like you're in a good...
That was fucking loud.
I don't know why. That just scared the shit out of me.
But anyways, thank you.
I thought that was in the game.
That was fifty dollars.
And that was...
Iniuria Palace.
For fifty bucks.
Thank you so much.
They say, hey, Jerma, love you a lot.
Thank you for all the years of helping me get through tough shit with laughter.
Show love a thousand five times.
Thank you so much for the fifty dollars.
Much love to you. That's fucking a lot of money. Thank you.
And not to derail this, but somebody just said they went to...
I'm not even going to say it.
Because that's going to derail the whole stream for like the rest of the night.
I am. Father and I are going on an excursion to eat foie gras in a bit.
What's a foie gras?
It sounds kind of mean.
What? You don't know what foie gras is?
Poverty is a curse.
Auteer, help me out over here.
Yes, very well.
Foie gras is a food made from goose liver and is generally considered to be a high class dish,
due in part to what is involved in creating it.
By overfeeding the geese, excess fat accumulates in the liver, significantly changing the taste.
The process is lengthy, naturally, as a dish that is typically sauteed and then eaten.
Okay, is it yummy though?
Naturally, it's a delicacy of the upper crust after all.
It utterly lacks any texture.
It's strangely meaty and oily.
It's truly the ultimate in rare tastes.
But it's yummy, right?
Of course it is. Silly plebeian.
Why can't we just eat shit?
We're going to find all these fucked up ways to make food.
How bored are we as a society?
Oh, hi, welcome.
Do you have a hat?
I actually don't have any hats.
Society.
No, I'm sorry the word society has taken on this like meme terminology now.
If you say the word society, it's like, oh, he said society.
He said society.
He said it.
I don't have any hats.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
If you don't have any, you don't.
Hi there.
Oh, do you want to sell you this bread?
31 cents.
It's bread.
I don't want to buy you bread.
Oh, here we go.
Okay.
So we got an opportunity to make 10 grand.
150, 15,000.
50K.
That's not going to fly.
No, that no way.
I'll start at 150.
Whoops.
No, not one, two, three, four.
How about one, two, three, four, five?
I think I could do 150.
That's a, come on.
That's 150 percent.
She will back out immediately if it's too high.
That's right.
That's a really good price for that ring.
I got that ring for like six grand.
Hey, do you have my food stuff?
I do.
Let's see.
How can I get the maximum amount of money from you?
I'm going to hold on to the honey because I feel like I'm going to need it in some recipe
somewhere.
Candy, apple, and then a beef brain.
Perfect.
That'll be 6,000.
I wonder if you'll do it.
Slightly, I want a slightly better deal.
54, 5,000.
Yes.
Inching close to 200k.
We have another delivery.
It's the weapons, right?
Do you want a yam?
I will take that yam for like 600 bucks.
No, that's insulting.
700.
I'm getting, you're getting scammed.
I'm not getting scammed.
All right.
Weapons.
Thief's knife and craft is knife.
And this is where we get, this is where we get to be a really bad person because
these things are in hot demand right now and it's an order.
So I'm thinking like, I'm thinking like 15,000 dollars.
14,000, I think.
All right.
Okay.
12,000.
Fuck.
No.
Those items are in fucking hot demand.
In your palace gave another 50 bucks.
You butchered my name.
So here's money to go back to school.
I am so bad with names.
Thank you for the hundred dollars though, dude, for real.
That's a shitload of money.
Thank you.
I want a hat.
I don't have hats.
What's that robots deal?
He's usually 250 to 300.
Oh, that's not good.
Get him off.
Usually 250 to 300 is percent works when it's a red item.
Looks like I'm just going to sell them.
Accessories are down.
Get that shit out of here.
Out here.
I got somebody wanted scarves today, right?
Shoes out here.
I need to go on an adventure.
Yeah.
Let me fill that order.
Let me hold on.
Let's get some powerful antioxidants out here or whatever this is.
Keep the bat wings.
Bake DM up there.
No, no, no.
Get the bake DM and get the fish up there too.
Let's be like a, let's be a grocery store for a little while.
Sword out there.
Yeah.
Get the sword out there too.
Who gives a shit?
Who cares?
All right.
I'm going to go after this.
After today, I'm going to the dungeon.
I can do the new carpet now.
Let's go.
Can I help you?
I'd like to buy some food.
I got you.
I got a bake DM right there.
2,600.
That's too expensive.
2,400.
Jerma's Grocery and Swords.
Yeah.
When she died, my grandmother told me to sell this if I ever got into trouble.
Oh, I just insulted your entire family.
Oh, I was looking for one of these.
Where are you now?
I think I can get away with like 200 and 200 percent, two or five.
He's broke, but I think it'll work.
75 maybe.
72.
No, 7,000.
Got it.
What can I get you?
Can I get you to buy this?
100 bucks.
Just scamming the elderly.
Here we go.
That price isn't right.
1,200.
Take it or leave it.
Give it to the Twix kids.
Oh, here we go.
It pains me to part with this.
It's just a piece of candy.
The price is wrong.
Ooh.
Ah, little lady, how much is this crafter's knife?
Well, that would be 3,500 dollars.
That'll do.
Money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money.
I'm sorry.
Stop.
Stop it.
I'm all right.
When is that person coming in for their delivery?
Tomorrow.
All right.
I need to go kill the slime like a bunch of times.
Two scarves, two food stuffs.
What else can I put out here?
I'm going to put the shark fin out here.
Before we close, let's get some more.
Make sure I got two food stuffs for tomorrow so I'm not putting out any food.
Should I sell the carpets?
I'm not going to use them, am I?
I don't want to get rid of any of these materials unless it's for this.
You know what I mean?
I have a bunch of them, but I feel like I'm going to need them to be out there or whatever.
Ooh.
Yo.
You doing okay, Reset?
Oh, Elan.
Welcome.
You finally came.
Well, I can't afford anything expensive, but I thought I'd drop by.
That's fine.
Looking is free.
You're all right, Reset.
Huh.
Ooh.
Uh.
Oh, I guess that you two haven't met.
This is Tyr.
She's my business partner here in the store.
Tyr, this is Elan.
An adventurer.
For the record, we do not accept payments on tab.
Notice me in the pub, I guess.
Don't worry.
I'll pay straight here when I'm here.
There's $50 for you.
By Inuria Palace.
I'm just going to call you The Palace.
That's $150 from The Palace.
Thank you for the huge amount of money.
They say do a Mr. Krabs impression when scamming the elderly, I beg you.
All right.
I can't.
Spongebob.
I can't do Krabs.
That's a really talented actor.
I can't do it.
All right.
We're ears.
Nope.
Not going to happen.
I tried, but thank you so much.
So bad.
It's all right.
Some people you can't emulate.
You understand?
There are some actors and some voice over artists that you can not emulate.
They'll know.
They'll never be another one that can do that way.
You at least got to try to laugh.
You have to admit that there are some things that you can't do.
Right.
There are some things you just cannot do.
I'm looking for some food.
What happened to the guy?
Oh, I was gone.
Let's get you.
How about some candy?
Those who can't do teach.
All right.
Well, you can't.
Hold on a second here.
I'm not like a fucking eighth grade football coach, guys.
Like, what are you talking about?
No, I'm not.
How?
What are you talking about?
And even if I was, you got a problem with the eighth grade football coach?
Those who can't do teach and those that can't teach, teach P.E.
You guys are fucking mean.
Oh, candy.
The price isn't right at all.
Fine.
Chat is filled with evil sludge.
Yeah.
Can we can we like spray this chat with the Ghostbusters 2 fucking nice slime?
You guys need you guys need to be able to get like fucking slime.
But I like that pink slime and Ghostbusters 2.
Found an apple while cleaning the cellar.
That's not worth anything.
Oh, sandals.
Thousand bucks.
That should be good.
Two hundred year old relic apple.
Can I help you?
I'd like you to buy this, but well, I want a good price.
What an awful negotiator.
You just nervously came in here with a Jolly Rancher and put it on the counter.
Um, I want you to buy this from me.
Uh, please.
You don't have to if you don't want to though.
Like, you know, you don't have to if you don't want to.
But can you buy from me, please?
Good night.
Exceeded expectations.
Okay, we got we have plenty of time.
I'm what about fifty five thousand?
Long swords has increased.
Damn it.
Speaking of like our like alignment here, we are up in light and plain.
Centrist.
All right.
No support.
What?
Where was Benjamin Franklin on like the political alignment chart?
That's where I want to be.
He was a chaotic neutral.
Franklin was chaotic.
Good.
It's important.
Let me see this.
What's my alignment?
Ah, good try.
I was about to be like, well, you know, if I were for me.
Oh, good try.
You almost had it.
Almost.
It was close.
And by the way, I just want to make sure I go like this because somebody will like clip
like a frame and be like, oh, when he said that, he froze like right here.
You don't fucking have any idea what the fuck I am.
I'm sorry.
I'm a wreck.
I'm uncontrollable.
You have no idea where I could end up.
I'm just going to X.
It's so bad.
That would have been so bad.
I haven't saved it.
You don't know what I am.
OK.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Tell me.
Yeah.
You tell me.
You don't have a discipline.
I'm a disciplined emotional.
That is what I am.
We've already that we came to the term determination of that long time ago.
All right.
Let's go.
I want to go level up.
I got plenty of time.
Actually, no, I don't.
Oh, they're closed today.
How could you be closed today?
I got to make some big sales.
I have a couple of big things coming up today.
Right.
Two scarves and two food stuffs.
Both today.
I got both of those things.
Let me just load it up.
I got to go.
Hold on.
I got to buy some stuff.
First of all, let's do the event.
Where is she?
There she is.
Miss receipt.
Oh, hi there.
So I want to thank you.
Miss receipt.
Thank me for what?
You helped me with my doll and found my hairpin.
Remember?
Oh, no, no, no.
OK.
No.
Thanks.
Necessary.
Right.
You seem rather pleased with yourself.
Regardless.
Is it showing?
OK.
Then I'm going to start.
Don't move.
OK?
Start what?
I'm going to draw a portrait of you.
Of course.
Now don't move.
Just a couple of quick questions.
Where do you sit on the political alignment chart?
Well, I sit...
Oh.
Almost.
Can I move yet?
Not yet.
Give me just a few more minutes.
OK.
Really?
Can I move yet?
She's definitely going like this with her teeth clenched.
OK.
Really?
Can I move yet?
OK.
Really?
Can I move yet?
Just a little bit more.
And...
Done.
Phew.
Being a model is hard.
My legs feel like tent poles.
So let's see it.
Come on.
Here you go.
This is me.
I didn't think my nose.
Huh.
Oh, where am I in this picture?
Oh, you're right here, Ms. Fairy.
But that is...
Is that not a dragonfly?
Hee-hee.
You're really good.
Hee-hee-hee.
That was an ee-hee.
I haven't seen that in a long time.
I really think...
I really like this.
Thank you.
Thanks, Mr. Reset.
Bye-bye.
Do I really look that much like a dragonfly?
Oh.
I can't believe it.
OK.
Let's go.
I want to buy some shit.
I need to sell this.
I have to start making money.
I'm going to buy parade armor.
And let's get the spiked armband.
Popular.
Let's get some charms.
No, no.
These things suck.
Composite bow.
Practice lands.
I need high-paying items.
I...
I can do that.
I need to get into that dungeon.
All right.
No matter what, tomorrow I'm getting a dungeon.
Let's get these products up here.
I need to make money.
Forty-two hundred.
That's worth so much.
I just have to keep doing that.
Foodstuff is today.
All right.
OK.
Open the damn store.
And came by to sell this.
There's something I've noticed about the citizens in this game.
All they have, they just come in with random food they find in their house on the ground.
Nobody ever comes in here with a necklace that's worth any money.
They just come in with fucking yams and apples and bread.
I would be more inclined to be happy about this if they was...
Hey, I found this.
Oh, I was in my grandmother's closet today.
And after she died and we found some parade armor.
I would buy that.
I'd be happy to do a decent price.
OK.
Well, that's a...
Let's do forty-seven hundred.
These guys just...
I'm having a collection of expensive items.
I do have the foodstuff that you asked for.
Just stay right there, sir.
I got baked E.M.
And...
Fish.
Let's do one twenty.
Thank you.
Somebody buy the parade armor.
Oh, here comes the rich girl.
Oh, the scarves, right.
Three thousand and fifty.
Overcharge.
Let's do one forty...
Forty-five hundred?
That's a hundred and forty-seven percent.
Forty-six?
Do two hundred percent.
Really?
I don't know if that's gonna happen.
That's ridiculous.
She's not...
She's gonna walk out.
I'm gonna say forty-six hundred.
She didn't like that.
She hated that, by the way.
You guys want me to start at two hundred percent?
She hated that.
I have to do like forty-two hundred now.
I have to sell it.
I'm up against the clock.
Somebody buy the parade armor.
I'd like some food.
Fuck.
Oh, come on, man.
Did you spend all your money?
What did you spend your money on?
Somebody buy the parade armor.
Help a poor lost Burke find a weapon.
I can do that.
And it's gonna be really expensive.
Ah!
Fuck you!
That wasn't even fucking...
Come on!
Are you serious?
That was so...
That was reasonable for a high-demand item.
Curse at your customers?
Why not?
I'm up against the clock again.
It's happening again.
Let's go to the pub.
Oh, charm hello again.
Here we go again.
Oh, hello.
Hello, receipt.
Tears here, too.
Well, you have my deepest apologies for my continued existence.
Oh, I can't take receipt home with me if you're here.
What?
I cannot let you do anything of that.
So I'm kidding.
Yeesh.
Guys, this is serious.
Somebody call the police.
Especially when you...
I kind of wish I didn't go into the fucking pub
because with that, I don't...
Okay.
Well, first of all, let's go back to the store.
I'm just gonna sell what I have
and hopefully somebody buys it.
And then tomorrow we go...
to you-know-where.
Murph!
Oh, shit.
Have you completed my order yet?
Well, no, no, I don't have it.
I don't have it, I don't have it, I don't have it.
Well, nothing for it.
And to be fair, some of those items are a bear.
The slime livers from normal slimes are too small for starters.
I need something from one that's bigger.
Batwing shouldn't be too hard if you've hunt the eyeball bats, though.
I've also heard that it knows a giant meister found of charred lizards.
All right, I did this already.
Get out of here.
There it is.
All right, here we go.
I'm gonna say...
Let's do 68.
65, come on.
All right, 62.
And then there's a bow.
35.
A bow.
I need a hundred and fucking 30,000 more dollars.
I gotta get into that new dungeon.
No, I don't...
I guess a 24.
25.
The dungeon's gonna save me, isn't it?
Hey.
Hey, it's me again.
I decided to come by and sell you another yam that I come by and try to sell you every day.
Candy apples.
I love candy apples.
All right, time for the dungeon.
That's $17,000 a day.
All right, here we go.
The price of metal items has increased.
The price of daggers has normalized.
Do I have anything like that?
No.
All right.
Let's...
I need to go into the new dungeon.
We gotta get some new stuff.
So by tomorrow, I need two food stuffs.
I gotta...
Fuck.
I need a big item.
All right, we got a level eight.
I'm gonna stay with tried and true here.
We're going with Louis.
Let's get a couple of pieces of bread.
This is uncharted territory here.
Here we go.
Amber Garden.
You want...
We demand charm.
Not when I need $140,000.
Take charm.
I need...
She's level eight.
She's got a rusty dagger.
Buy a better one.
No.
Will she use...
This is gonna be a mistake, ain't it?
No.
I'm sorry, guys.
I'm taking Louis.
No.
I will take charm when it's not absolutely necessary that I have to clear this.
I don't...
I don't even know what...
Okay, I need these guys.
By the way, she said, are you okay?
I can speak Japanese.
You learned that yesterday.
So?
If I learned a language yesterday, would that be a problem?
What is that?
That's like a new enemy.
Ow.
Ooh, hat.
It's a cloth hat.
Come on.
Oh, some kind of new enemy.
Ow.
Fun fact, the items in the dungeon suck.
But I need to get the materials to be able to make cool items.
These guys are supposed to drop them.
Those are the gnolls, right?
Nothing over there?
Same old enemies in new dungeon.
B, W, L.
Shit.
Are you alright?
What does that mean?
That means, are you...
Are you good?
Is are you alright?
And then she goes, are you good?
Are you hurt?
Nice battling.
I think I have as many of those as I need.
Wait.
Say W again.
That's really nice.
W.
Watch out for the hand.
Ooh, what's that, gunpowder?
I probably can use that in something.
New item.
Is the next room going to be in JST instead of PST?
Oh, is that supposed to be Japanese Standard Time?
Is that what it's actually called?
It's not Japanese Standard Time, is it?
Movement speed increased for everyone.
What?
I actually, can I keep this on permanently?
Hey, I want this on forever.
That's not a detriment to what I'm doing.
That's a positive.
I definitely have five bad ones.
Mystery item.
Come here.
No, I'm not alright.
I just had a bomb explode in my face.
These, they drop the bread.
I don't even want it.
Yeah, I'm just going to eat it right now.
Say, what's that one?
Daijou B.
What's B?
Are you alright?
Ooh, an apple.
First time I've seen that.
It's an accent.
Oh, okay.
Hey, that's good to know.
Alright, cool.
Hitchy eye, hold on.
Shit.
Toothpicks?
What the fuck am I going to do with these?
One last spot I didn't see down here.
Something good.
That's wood.
Get those George Washington teeth out of here.
I don't even want them.
What are we on?
Second floor Amber Garden?
We could just skip to the latino.
And then I have to do the slime thing.
Is that going to waste so much time?
I can't even get that guy's order.
It's going to be so...
It's going to take forever.
Forget about the slime liver.
Like, I need it though.
I'm going to do some fusion.
I'm going to make some money.
How much?
I have 70,000.
I need 200.
I don't think it will take too long.
Let's get rid of the bread.
Bread is worthless.
Alright, here we go.
Did these guys drop new stuff?
Gunpowder.
Dammit.
I don't think the null has dropped.
One of the items that I need from the null.
Has it?
All they drop is chestnuts.
Magical Staff?
It's the charred lizard.
I only have one.
Watch out.
He's going to explode.
Don't blow up.
These levels are bigger.
One chain.
So, somebody was saying, if I kill the same enemy in a row, just ignore everything else
and just kill the enemy that I need to kill, there's a higher chance that it will drop
the thing that I want it to drop?
So, just run around and only kill the nulls.
Well, except.
Apparently.
So it seems.
Huh.
Alright.
News.
Adventurer attack power doubled.
Well, that's pretty convenient.
Maybe I shouldn't leave.
What's that?
Rusty?
Okay.
Inkwell.
That's a part of a recipe.
Don't ever leave.
Yeah.
I'm just going to keep going down.
Why would I leave?
That felt pretty good.
Watch this.
Ready?
Three, four.
Two chain.
I can see the shadows.
Ow.
No.
Don't.
Come on.
What's that?
A jacket?
I love a windbreaker.
The windbreaker is stupid.
Everything's stupid.
You're stupid.
I'm not stupid.
This is level 18.
Ah.
Honey.
I think I need three honeys, right?
This is where it gets fucked up.
Alright.
I need three honeys.
Let's eat the cherry.
I'm almost going to have enough to make a bunch of stuff.
Snow.
Come on.
This is the cherry, but I need a big of bags.
I can just get rid of the bread.
I'm at that point where I have to start eliminating the least expensive thing here.
God damn it.
Is that a good thing or a bad thing?
It's a bad thing.
Does the candy restore its SP?
I'm curious to see how close I am to two or three cubes.
I'm going to miss this double damage when it's gone on the next floor.
It even does lead.
Can I dash by double tapping?
No.
You're on a fixed speed.
Chest.
Whoa.
Gunpowder.
Good.
Can you make a gun or explosives or something?
I'm almost level 19, so I'm going to get, mm, 1200.
That's pretty good.
This thing's a piece of crap, but I can sell it for something stupid.
How much is the windbreaker?
500.
Let's get rid of the chest nut.
What is this game?
This is called Risseteer and Item Shops Tale.
I could be saying that wrong.
I've probably been risk pronouncing this the whole entire game, so it wouldn't surprise me.
Is it on sale for $5?
I'll go get it.
This is what, is it $4.99?
Just go buy it.
Why would you not?
I mean, you have to gauge.
All right.
What is the boss?
Sometimes you have to gauge the value of something based on if it's more money for you to go
get like a double cheeseburger from McDonald's.
Oh, shit.
This guy's kind of.
Uh-oh.
Oh, shit.
I got to eat food and eat the apple.
Don't do it.
Shit.
Do I know what can't?
All right.
Calm down.
Shit.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
I freaked out.
No chest or anything.
Should I just keep going?
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not going.
I can't.
I have to sell stuff.
I need money.
I'm not going.
Fusions.
Rank one staff.
I need a back scratcher.
Where the hell can I get a back scratcher?
Didn't I have one?
Hat?
I need some.
Okay.
Can I craft a back?
I can make one.
I can make another one of these.
Toothpicks.
This is like $15,000 to $16,000.
So, but I can't because I need to give that to the dude.
All right.
So, I need fur balls.
I can get the...
So, can I...
Can I buy a back scratcher?
This is probably going to be worth a lot of money.
Back scratcher.
Where am I going to get a back scratcher?
Well, there's the...
Yeah, I can get this, but I still need the fur.
So, I can go back and go get like the fur from the first few floors.
Floors 11 to 15?
Yeah.
So, let me get this.
I need a back scratcher and I need three fur balls.
All right.
I can't do this today, but might as well just do this event because it's flashing.
Fur balls are easy.
Yeah.
I heard there's a girl here who's been handing out advice to people lately.
Advice?
Well, that would not be very surprising for a fortune teller as such, but here in the
pub, apparently she can clear up any problem you have in seconds.
Kind of wonder who it is.
Oh, it's me.
Haha.
I wish I got...
Why this...
It was happening.
All right.
Slow down World of Warcraft filter when you take three drinks.
Oh, excuse me.
Yeah.
You have to be...
Will you hear me out?
Oh, yes.
I'll listen.
Go ahead.
My wife terrifies me so much at this point that I can't even look at alcohol without
feeling guilty.
Help.
Ah, women are easy to handle.
I should know, right?
Just do little things that keep her happy.
They'll solve your problems.
Yeah.
Aha.
Oh, that makes sense.
I'll try that out.
Thanks.
I mean, a lot of people like that lately.
Wonder why.
I didn't lose a slice for that one.
Did I?
All right.
What do I got?
One fucking 30,000.
I feel like I still have a lot of stuff on sale.
Didn't I?
No.
Somebody already bought this.
All right.
Let's do it.
Get the sword up there.
Let's get...
Oh, I need all this.
I gotta...
I have to start to sell these rings.
The same shit happened last time.
I have to sell them.
Oh, I am in a lot of trouble.
I'm not going to save over that.
I'm saving down here.
Just in case there's a disaster.
I'm gonna...
I gotta put them out.
I have to make some money here.
Don't sell the rings.
They're not...
No, they're not half price.
Sell the honey?
No, I need the honey for a fusion.
And then I gotta go back and get fur and then I gotta get a back scratcher.
They're not...
The half price.
Yeah, but I got them for like 5,000.
I can only really afford this.
I can afford to do this for like one more day.
I need the batlings for the fusion.
I could put like anti-venom out here.
You have to hold and have faith.
Toothpicks of worth, nothing, gunpowder is part of...
No, I can't.
Who's coming in today?
Anybody coming in at the end of the day?
Tomorrow, two food steps.
Okay.
No, I need all this shit.
I can put the armband up here.
Buy more rings?
Do not give me ideas like that.
There's a lot of good memories tied to this.
Is there a way I can put like a sign on the door that says, I don't want your stuff?
There's a lot of good memories tied to this cherry.
Okay, so...
This sells for 400.
When she died, my grandmother told me to sell this if I ever got into trouble.
I'm sorry.
Now I actually am getting scammed.
There we go.
140.
It is that much.
Once I get these diffusions, I'll have a ton of money.
All right, I want the windbreaker.
120.
I just need the right fusion.
I really, really need two hats.
I need them in two days.
I can do that.
Accept defeat.
No, I'm not going to accept defeat.
I have two or three fusions and those items are going to be worth like 20 to 30 thousand
dollars each.
I'm not going to...
I'll be fine.
The chilly season is here.
Those sensitive to cold should bundle up.
The price of accessories has normalized.
All right.
You know what that means, right?
That means it's time to sell the...
See, they were 50% off.
Let's get that bracelet up here.
All right.
Let's get some of these necklaces.
Make the fusion cape with the inkwell.
Well, if I do that, then I lose out on this dude's order.
But all right, I have to adventure.
Let me see exactly what I need.
There.
Just the good shit.
So I need to do...
I could just open the store now or should I go...
Let me see.
If I lose a slice of time.
How many days do I have?
It's like three days.
I'm going to lose.
It's you again.
I don't have your order.
I'm sorry.
Bingo.
I'm going 3,400.
Just a little bit less.
3,300.
Take it.
Treasures.
Buy them.
Don't want...
I hope you don't want something in the window.
Go away.
I don't want to buy anymore stuff from you.
Please.
It's 600.
That's it.
Mommy would get mad.
I've come to get my food stuffs.
Oh shit.
I got it.
Okay.
Baked yam and a cherry.
130.
130%.
A little bit less.
One...
All right.
3,600.
Somebody buy the rings.
What can I get you?
The adventurer is coming in to get the chocolate.
I don't know what this guy's deal is.
Somebody buy a ring.
I can always rely on you to come in here and just be an absolute moron.
6,000.
7,000.
6,200.
All right.
Ah.
Dammit.
I'm in a lot of trouble here.
Okay.
I can't afford to...
I have to do the adventuring.
I need to go find these items.
So let me see what I gotta do here.
Merchant skill fusion.
I need...
What do I need?
A backscratcher.
Three fur balls.
Okay.
Should I just make this stupid thing?
And that guy will...
That guy will forever.
He's gonna just keep coming to the store.
I can get another...
Was it?
Just do it.
Fuck the Redditor.
What do you mean the Redditor?
I'm doing it.
I have to.
I'm gonna lose.
I need to make money.
Three fur balls.
One cloth cape.
Let me get the cloth cape.
I'm gonna do...
I'm gonna pull this out of my ass.
10,000.
I'm not gonna be able to make this one, unfortunately.
Not yet.
But I will be able to do this one.
Three fur balls.
Now where am I...
What's the absolute best way to get those?
Or one more honey.
One honey.
One backscratcher.
The rabbits.
Three fur balls.
One backscratcher.
One honey.
I'm going for it.
Jade Way.
And it was...
What?
Floral, like, 6-10?
Floral, 11-15?
The rabbits were in the very beginning, weren't they?
Just do them all.
I'm gonna have to do a full tour.
Yeah.
I'm going.
Let's start at the very beginning.
Welcome to hell.
I need rabbits.
Oh, there's this person again.
Can you accidentally drop 50,000 dollars?
Hi again.
Oh my, hello.
Have we met somewhere?
Uh, yeah.
In a way, that's given me a whole lot of deja vu.
Is that right?
I'm sorry that I don't remember.
I take it you are again here by mistake while attempting to get home.
I'm not quite sure I...
Wait, am I...
I'm somewhat not surprised that you did not realize where you were.
I was just heading home from the market with dinner.
See, I even have my scallions with me.
Scallions, I think I could use those.
Those look great, so perfectly green and tasty.
Ah, it was quite a good purchase.
Thank you for buying those for us.
Wait, I was buying them for you?
Yes, you were.
Of course you were.
I think something more than your sense of direction is off.
I think I'll have sukiyaki for dinner tonight.
Sukiyaki?
I don't know what that is, but it sounds good.
Can we fix sukiyami for dinner tonight?
Grain porridge.
Ever.
And.
And on.
Aww.
I enjoy your company, you two.
I must get home, however.
Stay safe.
Raincoat.
I'm not picking up any of this shit.
I gotta find rabbits and chain them together.
Alright, where are the rabbits?
Only kill rabbits.
Rabbit!
More rabbits!
Where are they?
I know there's more rabbits.
Come on.
If I sell all these items that I make right now, that's like 45-50 thousand dollars.
I'll...
It'll be close, but I'll get there.
No more rabbits up here?
Oh, give me a break.
It's wabbit season.
No, no more of these coats.
Duck season.
Wabbit season.
What a classic cartoon comedy.
Debt season.
No.
I'm not gonna leave.
Because, look, they just respawn.
I'm just gonna just...
I'm just gonna game this completely.
I'm just gonna walk around the circle until I chain like 30 of them together.
This is gonna be one rider.
Dammit.
I need...
I still need 120 thousand.
I could...
Look, if I liquidate my entire inventory, I'll be able to do it.
That strategy's not gonna work.
Let's go.
Rabbits.
Oh, a lot of them.
Come on.
Yes!
Alright.
I need two more of these.
I do have 15 floors to work with.
That's true.
Rabbit, rabbit, rabbit, rabbit, rabbit, rabbit.
Hey, did you guys know that if you wake up on the first day of spring and say rabbit,
rabbit, it gives you good luck forever?
That's not bullshit.
Like, that's an actual, like, folk tale thing.
That's not...
That wasn't a joke.
I was actually saying that.
Like, that's a...
Just a perception of something that was told.
Alright, well, I'm out of...
I'm out of things to hit.
Let me try to get some more items.
Was that on your Facebook page?
No, actually, it was on, like, Nickelodeon one time.
It was one of the in-between advertisements for, like, Doug to Ren and Stimpy.
I actually think, like, Stick Stickly said it.
Ooh, gimme...
Ready?
How is that not a chain?
Alright.
I want more, and I can make it.
A lot of gnolls.
Nobody dropped anything.
Dammit.
If you crit, it should be a guaranteed item.
I think I came back up here.
Done.
But that doesn't mean we are done, because I still need a backscratcher and I still need
honey.
Not even chaining Omega Lol, and I still did it.
Slime liver.
Wait, any more of these guys?
Just a pendant.
Looks like the backscratcher are from chests or the rat boss.
That doesn't leave me with very many options, does it?
You can still get higher grade furball, yeah.
What were the other items that I needed from, um...
Furball.
The honey drops from another lizard, too, yeah.
Thanks for the boost, I'll take it.
Honey drops from the bees, I'm assuming, right?
Lizards.
Backscratcher in here, come on.
The honey is really, really expensive, too, so whatever I get out of it, it better be
good.
Whatever the crafting is.
Backscratcher.
What?
Is it corn?
Is it corn on the cob?
I'm gonna wrap it down here.
That's what's killed us.
Alright, let's see if I can get the big slime.
Drop it.
What?
What was that hitbox?
Give it to me.
Is that it?
I think that's it.
Is that...
Slime Lover!
I got it!
Okay, okay, I got it, I got it, I got it.
I wonder how much that sells for, just normally.
I'm so happy that I got that.
You are a winner, so far.
I'm trying to go too fast.
Save it for the Redditor.
Why do you guys keep calling that guy a Redditor?
Is that just going way over my head?
Why is he a Redditor?
He feels like a Redditor.
I don't know what that means.
This is worth 6,300 bucks.
I didn't know that you could classify somebody like that.
That's not a bad...
That's a long go.
I'm getting some good items down here.
I don't want that.
Backscratcher.
Damn it.
That's because you don't identify as a Redditor.
You don't understand.
No, I don't.
I don't understand.
Bingo!
And you didn't think I was going to get to 200,000.
I still don't.
But anyways, what I was trying to say is...
How does...
I don't know how you identify yourself as reading the news from a website.
I don't understand.
News.
He only reads the news.
I don't know.
What do you do on Reddit?
Besides read the news.
Boots!
Any more rabbits?
Who the fuck?
What are you guys doing down here?
Oh, receipt!
What a coincidence meeting you here.
I identify as a Wall Street Journaler.
How are you, Alouette?
Oh, you're dungeon crawling as well, I see.
And with such a seedy-looking adventurer.
My adventurer friend isn't seedy-looking, and we did this joke already.
Self-aware.
I like it.
I suppose a seedy adventurer is appropriate for a seedy merchant.
Anyone else feel like that was backwards?
That if you play that in reverse, it'll sound like a regular laugh?
That's how they do that, right?
Well, come on, everyone.
Don't bother picking up the inexpensive garbage.
Only the best for us.
It would be so funny if this thing just grabbed her and punched her in the face.
You have like four adventurers!
That's stupid.
That's not fair.
Damn it!
He knew.
Well, any more of those gnolls?
No.
Might as well get a double.
You'll never understand the struggles of a Redditor.
Go back to 4chan.
Floor 8.
Let's go.
What'd she say?
I need my, like, I need my, like, Redditors to translate that.
Ooh, a sack of gold!
Nut mix.
Did I invest in Bitcoin?
I don't, I don't even know what that is.
I've heard of that before.
Just get out of my way, thing.
I do like this little item run, though.
I know that it was, it was like, it was like a scam, right?
That's all I, all I remember.
It was like a scam or something, right?
That's what somebody in the office told me.
I need to get rid of something.
What do I get rid of?
Everything I have?
The raincoats?
The raincoats are shitty.
I have, I need the fur balls.
The insect traps.
The nut mix is a thousand.
I'm just gonna eat the chocolate.
Backscratcher.
I mean, that's still pretty good.
I have one extra, but what if I need it?
Why is Dermis such a Redditor?
It's freaking me out.
I don't even know what you're talking about!
This is so over my head, it's freaking me out.
Why do you eat like a Redditor?
No, I don't want this.
I have one extra fur ball, but I'm probably gonna need it if I wanted to ever do this
again.
Should I?
Get rid of this charm.
Backscratcher.
Fuck.
Please do the nice girl laugh.
Get rid of the shitty fur ball, but I might need it.
If I get enough of those fur balls, I can make two.
Count them.
Two!
Triple kill.
I need a lizard too.
Lizard.
No lizard.
Bullshit.
I don't want the cherry.
Maybe I'll get it from the rat.
Can't carry anymore.
Wooden shield.
Garbage.
Raincoat.
Bra.
I don't need a bra.
I'm gonna throw it away.
Alright, I'll get rid of one fur ball.
And the bra.
It's 800 bucks though.
I can't.
I need...
Here we go.
Backscratcher from the rat.
Here comes Ratwheel.
Oops, I forgot you could do that.
Eat.
Oh, that is a heal.
I'm not sure I contemplated if that was gonna be a heal.
Eat one.
Eat it.
Stop making me contemplate.
Alright, backscratcher do it.
Come on please.
I need this.
Well, I got...
Okay.
I need to get another child.
So, what was the last thing I needed for that stupid order?
I needed the lizard.
I needed the batwing.
I got it.
It's probably gonna be a shitload of money, isn't it?
Okay, it may be time to call it a day here.
Because I'm running out of room.
Yeah, it's time to go.
No, not the stream.
I'm talking about the run.
Yeah, I gotta go back.
I gotta...
Here.
You know what I'm saying?
This is my last shot these next couple days.
Alright, news.
The price of food has decreased.
The price of swords has normalized.
Whatever.
So, fusion time.
I have 48 hours.
Time for fusion.
First of all, the dude's gonna come back.
I have it all.
And then I need two hats for today as well.
Here we go.
Fusion.
Rank 1 staff.
I don't have the back scratcher required, but I have the other stuff.
I need a sturdy glove.
So, that's one there.
Okay.
Ready?
This took a long time to make.
It's a, like, Fourth of July hat, and it's 3,800 bucks.
Wonderful.
Okay.
That...
I need a sturdy glove.
Shit, better be worth it.
Like, 15, at least.
No.
3850.
That's nothing.
Shit.
I'm in trouble now.
I could have just sold the three honey for, like, 8,060.
It's gonna be close.
Just put the most, just put only expensive shit up here.
Nothing else.
But what if he comes back?
Okay.
If he comes back, what if he gives me a ton of money?
What if he's, like, a trillionaire or something?
Alright, here we go.
I only have the expensive shit up.
I need, I need these two hats, because I'm gonna, this is gonna be an extremely expensive
two hats for that lady.
I don't want to put them out.
There's a lady coming in today that wants two hats.
Let's go.
Welcome to...
Oh, right.
There is!
Okay.
Like, 50 grand.
Did you finally manage to get my order?
I did.
Is your last supposed to creep out the customers?
Or is that just money?
Give me some money.
Look, and you got, like, a prince cape on.
You have, like, an outfit on.
You have a big collar.
You're like Dracula or you're a prince that has a lot of money.
Either one.
Dracula also probably has a lot of money.
What are the name of...
Duh-duh-duh.
Have you no shame?
You're not happy?
Given how long I had to wait for this.
Well, whatever.
I did put in the order.
And I, sorry.
And I do still need these.
So I'll go ahead and take them now.
Here's the fee.
Thank the owner for me.
Despite the delay, I do appreciate the help.
How much money is it?
I told you I am the owner.
I don't care how much money.
You really don't know when to give up on a prank, do you?
In any event, you do need to learn to deal with customers better.
I'll be coming in here more often from now on, so expect good service.
What's the fee?
I can deal with normal customers just fine.
Thank you.
What was it?
That was it?
3,800.
That's it?
That's it.
It's over.
I lose.
I was really riding on that being at least 20.
Okay.
34,000.
It's in high demand.
It's a hot item.
I can't charge $120,000.
I have to sell it.
2,900.
2,800.
I need to sell things.
Somebody buy one of the 15, $20,000 items.
Can I get a book?
I don't have any books.
Go home.
Grandpa.
Grandpa wants to buy a treasure.
No, this one on the table.
This one on the table.
This one's sitting right over there.
Can I just use a ring?
I think this is what you're looking for.
Not what I wanted.
The hats.
I'm so fucked.
It's not going to happen.
13,000.
14,000.
13.
Fuck.
I'm only $100,000 away.
God damn it.
Somebody buy this shit.
Somebody buy it now.
I have expensive items.
Okay.
I can do that.
7,500.
That's 220.
Higher than 220?
8,000?
I can do it.
I can do this.
Come on.
Piece of armor.
I mean, that's technically armor, isn't it?
The power glove is armor.
This is armor.
The cape is armor.
$15,000.
It's armor.
It's not armor.
You guys lied.
I don't want to spend fucking $1,000.
Go home.
I need to open this door again.
Somebody just take a ring or the power glove.
Wait a minute.
It's the prince.
Hey, it came by to sell this to you.
No, not you two.
Somebody poisoned you out there and now you're part of like the yam.
The scams.
Here we go.
This is the day where everyone's going to die.
I don't want this.
Please.
Just somebody buy something.
I don't want to buy your things.
I want you to buy my things.
I have to open the store again.
Put out food.
Put the cape out.
All this shit is already here.
No, the food is...
I'm going to put the boots out.
I'll put the chest out.
Let's go.
Here are the boots.
I'll do 120.
Cape.
All right.
We got a big sale here, except it's this cheap lady, 18,000.
She's not going to buy it.
She's going to walk out.
I cannot afford this lady to walk out right now.
I'm going to say 18,5 or 20.
No, no, no, no.
That's too high.
She'll...
She always says no.
She's going to say no.
She's not going to back down.
I have to do 18.
Otherwise I lose.
In fact, we're doing 17,9 or 17, like five.
Yeah.
I can't afford to lose this.
So I have to sell this.
Come on.
I can do this.
I have one more day.
I just have to make a little bit more money and I'm done.
I just have to make like 60,000.
The price of precious metals has decreased.
Get the staff up here.
There's no way I'm going to have 75,000 in one day, but there is a way, and that is I
liquidate everything I own at the store downstream.
It might happen.
It's today.
It's at the end of the day today.
I have three save files that are all like 30 minutes apart.
This is like an hour apart from this.
Let's hold on.
Let's just see what happens here.
I'm okay with liquidating stuff if it means to stay alive.
I think if I liquidate everything, I'll be able to stay alive.
I'm going to try it.
Fill the counters.
I'm going to...
What do I have here?
I don't want to sell the foods.
No, we'll put a baked yam out there.
All right.
Let's go.
Grandpa wants the boots.
Bring it down a little bit.
I can do that for you.
2,000.
Come on.
Big item up top.
This is a present from my brother.
You ne...
Okay.
You never buy.
1,850.
Hot items.
Hot.
All right.
He's going to get a hot item.
Oh, no.
Stop selling me food.
Of course, the girl that doesn't want to pay more than 110%.
Come on.
He always...
This guy is so dumb.
He always buys the most expensive shit in the store.
I need two cold weather clothes in two days.
Come on.
No.
Come on, old man.
You want us to buy some candy?
We're going to have to do some liquidation.
Put the rings in the window.
I've got these awesome things in the window already.
You know, and only...
People only buy candy.
No, I don't want to put on a bunch of cheap shit.
I'm going to go...
We're going with this.
There we go.
All right.
7500.
It's that much.
You can't bring it down at all.
I can do 7200.
No.
7000.
Come on.
Buy the cloak.
Oh, I was looking for this.
I don't want some fucking...
No.
I don't want it.
Oh, it was so cheap.
Somebody buy an expensive thing.
Looking for a treasure.
I don't have treasures here.
Here, have an unthankful statue.
At least I'll be able to sell it.
Mommy told me to buy this.
This girl.
I have to get it off the counter.
You've got to be kidding me.
This is a racket right now.
Unbelievable.
It is getting dumb.
I'm in so much trouble.
The price of a heavy armor has decreased.
Flee the country.
Just get on a plane.
It's still possible.
It is.
I have to sell this stuff.
Get the...
Put the ring up here.
Where's my expensive ring?
7000.
How much is this one?
Get the food off the shelves.
Is it possible that I just only have the stuff in the window?
This is what's in here.
And then I can liquidate some stuff.
Sell everything in the market.
That's why I have that save point.
I'll have some of these out.
I have to make the money.
Let's have a little candy counter here.
Food counter.
Let's just go.
Open.
You actually want the ring.
Holy shit.
Okay.
She's not going to buy...
I have to start at base.
She's not...
Alright.
Come on.
I can still do it.
Somebody buy that cape.
Rich girl.
Rich girl wants to sell me an apple.
Doesn't ever want to buy anything.
Come on.
Can I get a book?
I don't have any books.
I just need like a few more sales and I will be able to get there.
Come on.
Prints.
Two weapons and I want them in three days.
Sure.
Oh fuck.
I forgot about the guy that wanted stuff in two days.
What did he want?
Okay.
In two days.
Too cold weather.
This is it.
This is how possible I was.
I might as well just accept my fate right now.
But hold on.
We don't even know what happens.
What happens?
What now?
I'm afraid this amount of money is insufficient.
I'm sorry, but as an agent of Termi Finance, I must now seize this house in order to repay
the outstanding debt.
And so the cute, courageous little heroine was crushed by the cruel bitterness of reality.
Wow.
Why did it have to end in a box?
This is a dream, right?
This must be a joke.
If I did not know any better, I'd say you were in a coma.
Huh?
I'm asleep.
Hmm.
Tira was just a dream, I guess.
That dream seems so real, though.
I thought, I mean, I liked, uh...
Hmm.
Pillow.
Would you wake up, please?
I didn't shoot the sheriff, I swear.
Oh, Tira.
Morning.
You're still half asleep, I suspect.
Reset, you are the proprietor of an item shop.
Now, you must learn to be responsible and not sleep the day away.
You're right.
I...
I don't remember.
You can't seemingly be awake and asleep at the same time.
It'd be a wonder if it did not fill me with blind, hopeless terror.
Yesterday, we paid our respects at the Merchants Guild and then briefly opened shop.
Have you already forgotten?
What do you mean, paid?
Is Lily dead?
From this day forth, we are now in business properly.
The way this is going, though, I fear for the future.
That's right.
We're in business.
By the name of heaven, are you smiling so much?
Oh, no reason.
I just think I saw something nice in my dreams.
Tira, let's give it our all.
Well, if you really are dedicated to making this work, wash yourself and meet me downstairs.
What day is it?
What?
You...
So, I have an item shop and stuff and it's all cool and awesome.
So, what do I do now?
What?
Why am I getting this all over again?
Okay, we did this already.
You keep your levels and your stuff, but you don't keep money.
Oh, so you're supposed to lose.
Safe's coming, buy everything.
Did it go drop like $150,000?
Well, I'll at least be able to pay off the debt.
What about, like, event...
Hold on.
This is...
What about adventure guild shit?
Hold...
Wait a minute.
This is important.
Oh, shit.
I got to do this all over again?
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
I just want to see what happens.
Let me just see.
Let me check something here real quick.
I just want to see if this is possible.
Right here.
I just want to check something.
You keep everything but money.
I just...
I just want to see if this is possible.
Just out of curiosity.
No.
No, it's not even close.
Fuck.
Well, we're going to have to do it.
And I'm done.
I'm going to be ready this time.
God damn it.
$200,000.
I didn't even...
I couldn't even get it.
Open the store.
End the...
Let's go.
We're going to...
I'm not going to change the past.
Go back a few days?
Buy stuff?
Buy...
But that's cheating.
Who cares if it's cheating?
You want a bracelet?
Hold on.
I don't have any bracelets.
Am I above cheating?
I'll buy a few things, okay?
Watch me actually do it this time, somehow.
The interest rates on these loans are cheating.
Yeah, that's true.
I will buy...
How about this?
I'm going to go buy the most expensive weapons.
Oh, your mom told you to come sell this.
No, thanks.
Yeah, that is tactical gaming.
You're right.
Get out of here.
The game's designed to kick this shit out of you in your first run.
You're supposed to optimize for the second run.
Okay.
The price of weapons has decreased.
And look at that, guys.
I waited a day and I'm going to nail it now.
I'm going to go buy up all the expensive fucking weapons.
Keep all this shit.
Steel sword.
Buy it.
Thief's knife.
Pretty wand.
Buy it.
Composite bow.
Practiced lance.
Get it.
Gloves.
Dirty.
Buy it.
Clothes.
Tough clothes.
Get it.
Spiked armband.
Sure.
Big shield.
I'll take it.
Warm hat.
Give it to me.
Parade hat.
I'll take that one.
Popular charm.
Yep.
Now that I have all that stuff.
What's the most expensive secondary thing I can buy right now?
$784.
$1000.
$350.
$700.
$560.
$1000.
$450.
$840.
All right.
I'm going to buy 10 iron armors.
Buy 100 capes.
No, the capes aren't on sale.
Charms.
No.
Yeah.
Buy like five of these.
And I'm going to, yeah.
I'll get food too.
All right.
I'm good.
Markets.
Shit.
It's all right.
It's okay.
It's fine.
I'm just going to buy the cheap.
Like buy the diversify my portfolio.
I'm doing fine.
I got 10 of these.
10.
Cloth, robe.
Don't need these.
How many chest pieces do I have?
20 iron armors.
These are bracelets.
So like just get a bunch of these too.
I got 10 shields.
Give me four more hats.
Five more of these.
I got 15 charms.
10 long swords.
I got plenty of those.
I got plenty of bows.
Let's get some some knives and plenty of this stuff.
Windbreaker get like just fucking 10 of them and the rest and cloth robes.
All right.
i i now i'm going to destroy this game i've been told this is a feature and i'm i'm ready to go
good night good night 124 000 dollars the speed run of this game is under an hour
691 dollars out of 200 000 look at all this inventory i have now i'm gonna have so much
money i'm gonna be able to just blow through this and i can skip all these events because
you've already seen it i'm awake here we are day two loop three incoming i have wade no i'll be
ready for loop three ain't gonna happen but i'll tell you what is gonna happen i am gonna go pee
because it's been about three hours and i haven't gone to the bathroom and you know what that means
i'll be right back this game's got me just sucked in it just does all right so what i wanna we're
accepting our fate i'm replacing the original save file i've accepted the fate all right so
let me take a look at my items here yeah i got so much shit this is gonna be awesome i'm you know
i'm gonna leave it leave the cape let's put some swords up here no no no just sell this stuff
let's go move tables they work block the door all right let's get something good up here
let's get what do i want up there popular charm i think may speak with you
what do you want is this is this more tutorial shit yeah we already know this
make the whole shop long swords no because if i'm not gonna do that's a that's i mean that's a
pretty funny thing but once weapons become valuable we make five thousand dollars a pop
yeah i'm not gonna put any of these relief any of these out i'll put some robes out here maybe
a couple of cloth robe maybe some iron armor and uh maybe a shield i'm ready let's make some cash
i'd like a treasure please do i have any of those i don't have any treasures come on i don't
no treasure sorry tell him a ring he got really mad last time i did that bracelet i got lots of
those do you want i'm gonna uh no take it i'll take a iron one you're a pain in the ass so
we'll do 690 did i pay the 200 000 back i did not uh in fact i had to restart what happens is when
you lose in this game you start from the beginning we keep all your stuff i have hats warm hat no
cloth hat i'll sell the other ones much more 900 what the hell is that i think you'll like this
teacher's pole oh i'll take it i'll give you two grand for that
all right okay all right i'll give you 20 i want this i'll give you 3000 for it people are posting
important tips you're missing in the corners what do you mean in the corners don't haggle it
ruins your combo well i also want money let's put that pole right out six thousand combo is
more important go recruit louis hold on don't listen to these idiots haggle from max cash
if you get someone to buy it on the first try builds a combo high combos give more experience
all right my wife asked me to get a weapon i can help you out here that's it how much
so when you say don't haggle you talk about just sell it for 1200 what do you mean just make sure
that they take it first try make sure it's first try okay i mean this guy this is he'll take it
at 1400 make sure they take it first try i'll go for it i want to get two food stuffs and i
want them in two days i can do that go to walmart and stream this experience
we need there it is been looking for one of these now do i care about the combo right now
or do i want like 20 grand i think i think a first try would be like 18 20 i think it's too much
i'm thinking 18 will do it 18 will do it yep keep the combo going back and i want this cloth robe
i think in 12 yeah 1200 will do it yeah more combos i'm doing pretty good
oh all right this is a present 3200 this girl always i gotta keep it under like 110 i'll say
106 yeah 106 what does near pin mean near pin near perfect or something
and so it's near their perfect ideal price i see okay so let's see this guy i'll do 120
118 1420 guys i already have enough to pay off the debt next week i need to get rid of these rings
let's get the ring let's try to make as much money as i can up front because something that
i've learned since we've started this these rings never ever ever ever ever have increased in price
they've only decreased in price the food corner i'm gonna keep the nut mix cloth robe and let's
get the uh let's get a chess piece of fruit tomorrow i will take louie into the dungeon
all right there we go wooden chess piece we'll do 118 reasonable wants to sell the candy
so the same rules apply then so i have to buy this to keep the combo going right so you don't
want to haggle with this i need to make sure that they that i do this same rule applies i'll do let's
do 50 50 percent of base reasonable good i would very much like to place an order for two treasures
yes i can do that i'll just go buy them hydrate i got them good i got a coca-cola classic right
in front of me and i drank a water downstairs all right 110 can't haggle too much really that'll
be fine oh that was near perfect she wants the ring 108 i feel like she probably wants to buy
this for like 90 i'll do 105 buy the other rings yeah the yam is for sale 2400 never thought about
putting something like this in the store no i've never thought about it never thought about putting
an apple in the store you're the first person to think that can i buy this all right 104 that's a
near perfect level 11 i think i'm getting the hang of this when's the debt due i got look at
what's telling me for the debt all right what uh hold on in two days i need two food stuffs and
two treasures and everything's closed but it's being a food let's get a charm up there
some chocolate in here a piece of candy let's do uh cherry put a cherry over here and a cherry
we'll get the apple over there too all right sounds pretty good let's go okay 114 sounds pretty good
at level 12 i can expand the store oh shit are you serious finally finally people are buying these
things took long enough where'd you guys get the money 7500 i you want both rings i think i can
get away with 110 9000 i think i can get away with it yep finally cleaning up my ring inventory
now i'm ahead of the game
i have a moment anything new concerning the debt if his dad couldn't do a repayment
we already seen this yeah we've seen it already all right what's next
today is oh the guild is closed today isn't it the guild is closed oh is it tomorrow
let's get that out of the way though i'm cheating well wasn't i told that this this was like a
tactical video game strategy no it's over all right let's go get this out of the way skip this
there he is yep uh let's do it put the steel sword in his inventory so we do this quickly
spoken like a true redditor whatever
we just need to get to the end i don't need any other stuff because this is all just
shit we've already seen plus i keep the levels too that's a good thing and i keep the moves
i've literally rewinded time this wasn't supposed to happen yeah but that you're supposed to try
this is what i this everybody told me that this is like the way you do it that's the way i did it
all right here we go the letter the name of the game is literally resetter
okay thanks for the card louis there's the door let's go what happens at the chapel finance come
yeah we already did this we've already seen it all okay i'm gonna hold on to the weapons
i do i can do one more day here though uh let's put the windbreaker up here sell an armor piece too
oh it's this guy do i have to go get all that shit again for him dev in the chat i don't believe
that to be so why would a dev be in the chat right now guys dev all right i got
this game came out like 10 years ago do you really think the dev is just hanging around twitch chats
now still you can do 120 now 115 what the hell is this golden pedestal i want it i think uh 48
percent is reasonable or 50 so something i'm realizing even if i didn't do the mr rissetti
thing i'm getting more offers to have huge money that that that thing's like 20 grand
it's like day three i'm getting it would have been essentially the same it's the level okay
i see based on merchant level i see all right let's go uh how much do you want this for how about one
one one one all right time for bed i lost money today but it's okay that's why combos are king
i'm assuming that there's going to be a situation so look ready 200 000 was the wall then like a
million is going to be the wall does this just keep going to like 10 fucking million dollars
and i'm gonna have to like reset and do like kind of prestige again interesting whatever that is
all right so uh i have my orders here it's the atmosphere of the store it's all right merchant
level more items at this level even more items can be found at the guild and in the market
and then the store expands coming up next all right so um let me go take a look at that have
i even looked i don't think i've even looked in the stores yet what the fuck is this magnet necklace
i mean yeah give it to me old cape fleece muffler 80 400 hard boots meditation ring no no rings
golden scales 17 000 wait when's the day when do i owe the money soon right i'm gonna make it all
back it's gonna be huge sales old vendor an old refurbished vending machine still usable although
it's cooling unit 21 000 but a vending machine okay this is fun it's not today it's not today
he would break check this out though look at this where is it i'm gonna put it up here like didn't
that person want two treasures who wanted treasures because i'm gonna make like fucking
50 000 somebody wanted two treasures today two treasures oh you got it i'm gonna make a ton of
money watch out let's get um get the fleece muffler up there magnet necklace don't put them
what do you mean i have two of these don't put me don't put them on i have two of those
hey hey hey hey hey hey easy look uh let's put out put some boots out here too and try out there
all right let's go oh what's up with these fucking redditors the order i made the treasures did it
come in oh it did it sure did 25 400 and 14 900 is this what you're looking for yeah oh it is
that's 40 40 42 000 she's she's on the cheap side but i think i can do 43 000 maybe 44 000
that's 109 44 400
44 5 what a fucking sale i felt good oh and you want the magnet necklace too
this is what it feels like to be a fucking trillionaire what can i get you i asked for
some food stuff so yeah i got it uh chocolate and a cherry yes that sounds good you uh let's do
104 for you near perfect anybody else oh man louis that's so good for you
look at how much better that is 1390
charm grandpa has money we'll do 121 shit i broke the chain there
i'd like a treasure oh you want a treasure huh
so that'll be 17 000 please it's back armor we'll do 20 226 vending machine incoming yep
schedule maintenance yeah we've already seen this uh i'm buying the vending machine
is something wrong ma'am oh just wondering what to do for dinner tonight we have already seen this
oh cute carpet fancy carpet hold on ruins wallpaper the eyes on this wallpaper are always
watching you no matter where you go why would i want scary wallpaper ruins a heretic wallpaper
all right i just bought the vending machine i got it oh that's enough come here scary walls
with cute carpet can i put the vending machine in here this is going to be a confusing store
can i sell the vending machine i can take a 30 000 of the vending machine vending machine
cannot be placed at our level oh fuck all right that's fine let me sell the wallpaper yeah sell
the resort wallpaper no no no what if i need it what if i want it i might want to do it again
i might want to use it the old cape up there a nice charm up here and parade no no no no no
when do i tell there's an actual spike in sales here
um there are eyes on the walls yes there are let's get rid of the wood no i can no i don't know
i'm i'm hoarding too many things windbreaker that's fine that's enough it's a salmon max carpet
95 set up the vending machine i don't think i can charm
i gotta keep that i gotta get to 12 so i can get a bigger store and then i'll have a ton of
inventory oh nice deck him out i'm not scamming him i'm doing i'm doing very well this time
it's the windbreaker 1 15 for 580 that's a fair price
now i got plenty of money about you know you've got to spend money to make money
what's the day you have four days i need to have 10 000
let's actually i'm going down i'm going down let's go adventure for a second here
steel sword iron yeah all right let's go no you don't i gotta start the whole thing over no i
don't wait what i have to go unlock charm charm unlocks the other one so we have to go to this
we have to go to the pub where did i meet her the first time yeah i've already done this
gotta yeah have to do the town events oh she's yeah she's the boss she is the boss
right so she's down here 11 to 15 and i still have to get the stuff for uh why i guess yeah all
right well what do i need for um let's just go unlock she's the boss of this gym i'm not
gonna pick it up unless it's worth picking up or if it's honey
me
i need you
no he doesn't know he doesn't know about gotchi i don't i know it's an emote these guys have eyes
please nothing now nah let's just make these that happen
i'd like to buy salmon max season three but uh 2000 picks please
i say yeah i'm gonna have to haggle with you here
maybe a little more than that i think it's gonna be a little more than that
that
you know how data and things that are saved forever are interesting you know right i think
i've said that like it's just something that i say i don't know why i even when like the camera is
off i say that all the fucking time you know kim will will be able to tell you a story of how
um i think i've already told this story but sometimes i just get on something i just don't
get off after we watched infinity war i was just doing Thanos quotes alone i was making like
sandwiches and just be just would just talk as Thanos and say the same like four lines over and
over again i would just do it i don't know why because it just i i don't know it's just something
that i do sometimes but the reason why i bring this up is because i i've said that on stream so
many times you could probably make like a four or five minute video compilation of me doing
that game of thrones guy you probably could i've said it so many times
look what i'm doing it again
talk about the pizza hut instructional video instead why would i do that all right we just
talked about that yesterday what's my favorite show i've ever seen that's tough that's a tough
that's i don't know i've seen a lot of good shows
what's your favorite ice cream well uh oh free iron armor there's this ice cream that sells
i hate the name sherbert by the way i'm of the opinion if sherbert wasn't called sherbert most
people would think it was good
oh you guys want something to something for dessert yeah what do you want ice cream ice cream would
you want some sherbert no shut up mom i call it sorbet or sherbert is not a sorbet they're
two different things let's not have a jelly and jam conversation again sherbert is not
sorbet do you want are we doing this again they're not the same thing i'm not going to
get in there sherbert is not so big holy fuck we're not doing it again i'm not doing it again
sherbert is fruit juice and milk sorbet okay um you got i almost just fucking ended the
fucking stream by no by exiting this
it's too easy what are those goggles it's too easy end of the stream argument
and sure but still though nobody gets i like sherbert but nobody ever has it okay there are
there are 40 almost 4200 people here does anyone here and i mean let you be honest does any single
person here have sherbert in their freezer right now i bet you it's zero there's the honey
i and i like it i love it but why is it like less than
0.5 percent of all people have sherbert i have orange swirl sherbert we are the one guy
they serve sherbert in school in plastic cups that's so weird i'm eating it right now
i don't believe it but whatever come here
here
i love this i love this i love this i love this i love this i love this i don't love this
stop stop it seriously i haven't had sherbert since the fifth grade yes for some reason the
only time people decide to buy sherbert is to have an option at a birthday party strange that's also
one of the only places that you see elio's pizza is that a birthday party here we go
that stuff is really good too elio's pizza is really good all right here we go time for the
fight hey look at me come on down the only problem with elio's pizza is after you eat elio's pizza
you do damage to your mouth real damage every single bite i've ever taken from an elio's pizza
did like two to three week long damage to my mouth because it's it's so hot on top and it's
like lava in the middle that no matter what you can sit there and yeah if you don't let it cool
for like 20 minutes you like flakes are coming off of your mouth for like four days all right
i'm gonna lose it's the only piece of it that's ever happened to me before hold on i got a book
remember that joke from yesterday all right booze of the world and oh there's that vase
okay got charm very good let's go to the pub let's see where she is skip it town square skip it
we've seen it down out ohio was it ohio how do you do it ohio
ohio how do you do it ohio means good morning ohio ohio good morning i like i'm learning
another language ohio so how could i go wow this is cool all right now uh let's go to fusion
rank one staff i need the back scratcher i need i've already done all this rank one shirt though
need some more fur balls rank one helm i need the slime liva but i need to do
first and foremost let's do this event skip it by the way
wait have i seen this are we gonna play doki doki literature club no i i refuse to play that game
no i've seen this yet booze of the world is worth a lot of money all right hams let's get some uh let's
get a few ham sandwiches people looking for food shortcake let's get like a cake some tuna
all right stop now that's enough you got a zero anime game policy you broke it
no listen this is important because what's gonna happen first i'm gonna sneeze in your face
second after i do that i was i never said that i talked about it yesterday i was i was so bombarded
with the quotation marks play doki doki literature club end quotation marks that i had to ban all
anime from the stream that was a last that was a last resort measure play doki when are you going
to do doki doki literature club and at this point it's been said so many times i already know what
happens in the game i know it's not like a game that you play and oh here it is here's this regular
game i know that like fucking i know so i know i already know so my surprise has been ruined
no i didn't get spoiled i just know there's no reason why anyone would ever tell you to
do that so many times that's like desperately trying to get me to shake your hand with a hand
buzzer in it hey dude uh you want to shake my hand why do i want to shake your hand right now
i know you like hate shaking hands but like shake my hand no um i've been here for like two hours
i don't need to shake your hand just do it man no i'm not i don't want to shake your hand and you
call me like two days later hey dude i'm not gonna come over tonight um can we like shake hands when
i get there um i don't i guess maybe i don't know why why do you want to do that so bad
just just because i like i'm like i don't know scrap that's dog shit well like you got like joke
gum you know the gum that like turns your mouth blue and shit it's like a joke prank gum i'm not
i wasn't gonna let you guys prank gumby i think it's time to put out a uh hmm oh the vase all
right booze of the world i think i'm gonna hang on to that are you excited for your doki doki
literature no let's put the ham sandwich that's an important item let's get the egg toast and
let's get the shortcake out there too you there we go don't don't hold on they don't have to do
something here and here like here's the worst part about what i just said like to not to keep like
beating on this but this is the end point here eventually when you tell me to shake your hands
so many times and you call me and you leave voicemails and you fucking text me i i'm gonna
start to look at your hand and i see that there's a buzzer there and i just pretend that i don't see
the buzzer because i know you really want to like get this i realize what you're doing and then
finally like a week goes by and i you still have the buzzer in your hand and i'm just like hey
let's shake hands dude and you brought the fuck drop the fuck up what'd you say dude hold on you
want to what do you want to do i think i want to shake your hand man it's been a while since we've
shaken hands holy fucking you like hey hey put it there and i go ah
eventually that's kind of how that plays out so i know the the outcome there you just promised
you're gonna play it all right we've already seen this hey welcome hey i want a weapon i can do that
what do you want a cheap weapon do you want to lance how about a lance thief's knife
oh that's better yes it is what do i want for it i'll give it to you for 111
3800 you don't have 100 really 102 what not if i want to what did you want to do for like 95
a durian uh i'll take it that sounds pretty cool i'll give it to you for 40 percent all right 50
percent you got me 55 percent you got me ham sandwich this will do 117 that's your fine
ham sandwich somebody buy the vase charm one one oh seven near perfect is that sandwich fresh
it better be how do i shake my hand a weapon all right i could sell you a i don't want to do the
the expensive ones you have a crafty one oh seven perfect near perfect remember the car tuna
sandwich it wasn't a tuna sandwich it was a turkey sandwich little lady i'd like to get two
hats if i come pick them up in three days or you have them for me and by the way put her there
go home grandpa how many times do i have to teach you a lesson old man what this is how you run a
joke into the ground like asking somebody to play the same thing hundreds and hundreds of
fucking times is that what it's like tough clothes for the tough crowd that comes in
bright and happy welcome is the key all right yeah we've already seen this
there it is i got the card thank you tough clothes uh let's do 103 i didn't get to level 12 this is
important you want a weapon how about a how about a magician staff you look like you could be a
pretty good wizard no no no 108 oh man can i get you to buy this from me it's this golden scales
all right yeah i'll get it i'll take it off you 48 percent we do 48 no i need this part of the
combo it's worth buying 51 you're gonna you'll take it yep piece of armor let me deck you out
because you're gonna be what's parade armor is not stronger than iron armor right she needs to use
a thief armor robes breastplate shell i mean this is probably gonna be pretty good that's really
good all right that's nice now i don't want to i think it's gonna do it at base i don't have
that much money god damn it really i want you to have this on 78 i wanted to wear it so
uh windbreaker cool 108 level 12 level 12 yes we're good hmm you do 48 49
he's addicted to the game i really am it's just i want to see how it plays out
can i have a few strands of your hair i don't think that's gonna happen
because what are you gonna do with with that hair i feel like you're gonna make a clone or
something nobody asks for a strand of hair unless they're doing you putting it like in a tube
and shaking it up with like hydrochloric acid to make like another person
oh my god tomorrow what items do i want to put up here weirdly enough there's been no
i'll put the durian up here we're a sandwich and durian store now
hey reset let's just that's drunk again so found the new dungeon that's all we need to know the new
place is now open i would like a treasure do i have any treasures yes i do 25 000 i'll do 105
27 000 should be reasonable near perfect yeah i'll do the uh the expansion tomorrow
all right somebody wants the durian 112 9 000 weapon uh let's do longbow just underneath
oh the pole you want wait you have one of these why are we the only two people in the world that
has one did you look in the window to see if we had one of these and just what is this a copy
is this like a fake got donated to me by a rich old man he kind of wants it back how much will
you take for it that combo meter rolling all right now we're gonna expand the store
does it cost any money if i had a tiny clone of myself would i torture it um that might be
i mean it's very possible that could be the worst chat message i've read in 2019
it's pretty close i don't even know why you even asked that oh all right so let's expand the store
change flooring chain open store move tables is there a way to do this at this level you may
expand the store giving you more room for counters and items so how do i do it no i would not do that
expansion ten thousand dollars to expand yeah all right cool so what does that do
i've seen this already i feel like i should go do an adventure if i'm already out here
she has a shitty dagger but i kind of want to see what she does let's do the amber garden
for six to ten let's see if we don't let's see if we die let's go be careful well faster what does
her move clone she can run she can run can't she all right wow that's worth it that's pretty
great actually fuck louis that's pretty cool that i can just like hang back and have my clone attack
things oh can i put this on right now although this i need to level up
she's weak as hell right now pumpkins new enemy what do they do they are they thwomps
thwomp i knew they were thwomps i just didn't know when
so
land on the shadow that's so great i love the run
no no no no no don't die don't die
the one b it cannot end this let me heal i have any heal i don't have any food to eat
i gotta be really careful now
it's not food
it's not food i'll be oh shit come on you need to level up it's just a slime just be careful
if i level up i get everything back
food what the hell was that oh what the fuck just happened that just scared the shit i heard like
the explosion behind me he's dead we book it back home normally we would not be able to bring any
items with us loot or otherwise but thanks to the special little box the guild gave us we can bring
back at least one item she was drunk when we came down here this is not my fault victory lap and
let's see what's that that's another adventure over here right holy shit look at this this place
is huge um all right good morning you're aware that today is the first day of collections i have
it so i can buy more room right actually now i have it over here already so there's there's
more over here do i have any more treasures or anything charms helms necklaces treasures
yep let's get these out there i got two poles keep one of them just in case i need it for
something boots out who's the world keep it ham sandwich now let's put the food items in the
middle that makes the most sense uh cherry over here is going to be armor the treasures are in
the window armor and armor is going to be on the left let's do a warrior's helm up here too
common shield and iron iron band weapons will be on the right i'm thinking let's get a spear out
here counter counter counter counter counter counter counter counter counter counter counter
wait vending machine hold on what's this vending machine cannot be placed at our level counter
counter counter legendary counter wait what do you want to do with this move tables place that
how do i place the counter i don't think this way i can place it unless i can do with the fairy
no i can't place it move the table it's fine i i'm re-centering it everyone relax okay let's
get the couple of uh get a bow out here for staff and a craft this knife ready for business
open the store hydrate sure you want a cherry there you go i can change the counter's level
14 oh okay there we go nice necklace good deal do you get more customers take that helm for
i'll give it to you for 110 i want to buy a hat i think i have a couple of those you can take
warm hat i'm gonna know i feel like i'll need that for something eventually
vending machine does things i just can't use it at this level all right i think i'm gonna
let's try that doing that again this time i'm gonna bring a couple of food items i have enough
for the dead let's go i'm gonna try this again rusty dagger we're gonna change that
i'm gonna give you the thief's knife i'm gonna bring food this time let's bring a couple of
apples and let's bring uh candy bring two candies here we go all right i can do this let's go armor
doesn't you have new armor attack power doubled for everyone didn't she just buy it
now what a better item you're doing so much better no i want to explore
oops ah i missed
i'll take the apple oh i just got creamed i got creamed right there that was not fair
it's this fucking goddamn ice bullshit man like this mario maker ice level shit god damn it and
i can only take one thing with me i'm so upset right now i got the rocks came down to hit me i
got double hit there ice level mario maker dog shit and i get in debt i can't take her in there
i have to go to the other one quests i got quite yeah louis we don't even care about you anymore
although i should because you're 10 times better i didn't die with louis one time even when he was
level one did we see this you want a quest reward i feel like we haven't seen this louis you remind
me of papa louis not gonna die i will keep louis alive at all costs first debt all right i'm ready
to go next is what is it uh 50 i did three right oh it's her it's oh ho ho ho i kind of want to
hear it though that's anybody else want to hear it good now next 30 000 do uh now i'm not gonna
mess around here i got plenty of money any more food items i can't believe i lost all that food
toothpicks cherry let's go oh hello there it's me eight hours of exposition that we're missing
but it's all good because we've already seen it save yeah i'm going for it 120
no 119 i can auto skip red text maybe i'll turn that on ham sandwich 114 hard boots she's rich
right i can do a little bit higher of a margin here 126 maybe like 55 or 54 i'll keep it under 130
got it oh fuck do i have the hats yeah i do i do have the hats that you were looking for
i want to keep the warm hat though 118 good keep the combo going i can go high with oh ho ho
yeah now uh i'm gonna do it again okay i'm not gonna screw this up this time
she already has a better uh chest plate on doesn't she iron armband i'm gonna give you a hat let's
take an apple and that's it by the way we're gonna go to floor one two five i can do this
attack power doubled for everyone again all right now i'm paranoid i'm actually paranoid i'm like
freaking out what what just happened did i just run into the wall what oh my god
why did i fall down why did i fall down what made me fall oh i didn't even fuck it up that time i
apparently ran my face into the railing that sucks that's three strikes man the innings over
that's out number three the booze i like booze all right stuff there's a brand of stuff called
points she what happened i'm not sharing info with us show folks found out the punches
rice bae she are you listening to a word i'm saying hey that's how term is i guess if you
dash into walls she knocks herself down i did not know that i like you who cares all i care about is
the money i have plenty of it right now here we go candy has increased who cares yeah i saw i know
the news all right um this is the last time i'm going to try doing this shit i have to pull her
all the way back i can't do the okay there's level nine i'm just gonna kill the rat and then
i could take after like level 12 or something
just wanted to test the theory because i didn't believe them
for a second i thought there was a glitch i don't even want
okay so far so good
okay
faster than rabbits that's good this is awesome sauce hey thanks
people still use that word
i'm a little 10 all right we're going we're going we're going looking up things looking good
next floor i'm just trying to get exp so what's the point of me running by enemies right
all right anybody what does she say there
i'm like hoarding these nut mixes for some reason i'm not entirely sure why i'm doing that
i wonder if you uh level up get something to level 10 maybe something like that
possibly
level 10 all right i got something new what's that fire let's see what this does
okay you dash through people what's that focus staff
doesn't do that much damage but it's you can i guess you can travel through people really fast
fast it's not bad
another uh dagger
the apple good
uh it's all right it's not the greatest it's not the worst
oh no fuck this i'm leaving
scrap metal
fucking addicted to this game
it's clear at this point
do the weapons degrade i don't i don't think they do
uh no now we got raided by john oh right okay so we got pretend raided
i'm looking over like john raid john raid he's like i don't know what do i know what john
oh shit don't kill me he didn't run with the joke yeah i'll go i don't know we were doing one
i was actually trying to think in my head who do i know that is john
i'm gonna eat something here i'm level 11
i don't want to die with rat so i could actually start to be careful
oh
i think i confused these things now i should have enough right
really close to enough all right i got a few levels uh i might as well check
it's pretty useful
i can eat this bread shit well have i picked up that many things i have picked up a lot of
stuff huh damn all right what about i'm gonna throw away just eat the apple or throw away the
staff sucks shroom sucks i'm just gonna eat this right now we'll close
how am i halfway to 12 no i don't want that thing
timing was off but sorry all right let's go i didn't know you were here
are you worried about not collecting two hundred thousand dollars well not yet
i got like a month to figure that out don't eat that one
i thought it was dead there you go eat consume
boom eat eat eat eat eat my child
get it all right backscratcher please so i can get the item i'll take that though that's good
throw away some piece of shit uh i'm gonna throw away i can't throw away your stuff can i
no this thing sucks get rid of it charred lizard and that's it
into her cups again this is we've seen this already we've seen this already i believe as well
did the boss rush for the items let me take inventory first let's go see what do i got
i have plenty of good stuff here i just want to get rid of this thing it's
worthless last little uh shop before we go to bed welcome candy apple need two food
stuffs and i'm gonna need them in two days i accept your challenge did i just buy that
you can afford that i saw the heart that was good
one thousand yeah i haven't saved in a long time that's a good yeah good call
oh dear we need a ring at home you see the one time that i don't have rings really you want rings
now where were you when i had eight of them there's nothing to be done oh goodbye the vending
machine something warm uh thick robe raincoat i would say a thick robe the warm hat nice time for
bed so i got as long as i keep myself what here's the plan i have to stay 100 over the debt
so if the debt is 30 i need to always be at 60 000 get the daggers off the menu
just get rid of the staff i don't want it what food do i have the candy out
candy apple candy apple let's go oh yeah two food stuffs i need a lot of food
i gotta check those orders because i need all right long sword i think that's actually worse
than the thing you have right now give him two day old cheeseburgers as long if i as long as i get
over the 200 000 debt tonight i'll be happy oh 115 69 now 7000 reasonable enough why am i selling
so low because i want to try to string together perfect combos because that's how you get levels
you need a treasure i got and i just get one right here 21 4000 i could probably do 25 on this
24 24 000 do it yes how's my alignment doing we're down in dark and plain but i got like the cute
thing down there what's next store expansion fusion rank 2 is coming up after this it's the
yeah that's all right though i feel like i want at least one of these because it's probably used
for a recipe speaking of recipes where's my orders get over here we got tomorrow is two food stuffs
i have the charred lizard i have the bat wings i need the slime liver let's go get that let's go
boss rush it's closed never mind there's nothing i can't i don't think i can do here oh you two your
timing is great i have a little problem that i need your help with uh is this the fusion thing
package that needs to be delivered to the orphanage yeah we've i'm remembering this
yeah let's go and then there's a dead guy yeah all right yep yep yep yep yep yep yep this is
that way unlock the third guy this is elan right okay elan there he is there he is all right he's
now available for us to talk to let's open the store again where did this stuff there we go
open it up slime liver yeah save save save you're right 10 and a half hours it's been a while since
i put 10 plus hours into a game that was the same game buy a new floor i will after this
there it is windbreaker so that's probably gonna be perfect yep so every time i do a near perfect i
gain reputation with that person am i going to be finishing the game today yeah maybe it depends
this game has 30 more hours in it
uh i want this watermelon 40 50 50 we'll see what after i get over 200 000 let's see what it says
well everybody wants food i need more food all right there's the candy apple
no 112 hungry for some reason i don't know why i'm still 13 fusion level two will get us some
ridiculous expensive items oh here we go i can i'm gonna do i'm gonna be i'm gonna be normal though
let's do one six let 175 525 yeah let's be reasonable 13 120 he'll do it mother-in-law
uh selling an apple always do 50 with food that really does work have i started haggling in real
life and this game's getting to me i'm doing i'm like trying to i was at the drive-through last
night telling the guy to put like three extra fries in the bag hey i'm gonna buy a 10-piece
nugget but you're gonna put 15 in what oh just kidding and he puts in eight okay what do i need
new floor everyone's like new floor new this floor sucks right so okay i'll get a new floor
i need more food what i have for food right now apple watermelon honey i gotta buy some more
food so i'm gonna do this uh tomorrow more markets close right now so i'm gonna we'll just do well
let's just open the store just get rid of the inventory it's the good day right you haven't
completed my order i will i will i will i'm gonna get the slime liver that's all i need
oh he wants the statue i'll try to get money out of this one let's go with 126 i'm so good
at pricing stuff i'm so good at it over 100 000 oh the peach tin i have to get more food
otherwise this six orders i need one we'll do 130 what does it like to work with derma
what's it like to work with me um i don't know probably pretty good work for me or work with me
long swords guys this is uh this is what we this is why we were keeping all these
it's long sword day i'm gonna keep the steel sword because i want louis to have it and it's food
stuff day too all right let's go buy some food some good food i could do ham sandwiches how much is ham
sandwich 23 what's more expensive than that 24 shortcake just buy like six shortcakes check this
this is a little girl you fix the stuff your doll you fix the doll here we go now
oh let's get some stuff out here i wish i could put this out i wish i could do anything with this
right now but i can't i get the watermelon out here it's a sword day so i don't want to
put that much more stuff out let's go there we go first long sword we're gonna do maybe should
i do just 2000 for all of them either 2000 or i don't know if i want to do 200 175 i think it's
fine yeah she's cheap she's cheap i'll also take one of those long swords now you on the other hand
i know you're good for it 2400 i do have the things uh you asked for i have two cakes for you
3500 3500 oh yeah seven grand base i could probably do 8000 though yep sword
cherries no i don't want to whatever i have i'm gonna keep it i gotta keep it going
yam uh you want to sell a yam i'll take it dark plane is the best atmosphere you can get to get
old men to come in the store really why any chance i could turn this into some money
i'll take it for 50% thankfully the swords are doing well
i'm a 40 what do i do at 14 i got something else right 14 is change counters finally and i
can do the vending machine next fusion rank two oh okay hold on i can do counters change tables
legendary counters legendary super counter lineup items use it as a desk
these just look like cardboard this looks like shit these look way way worse i need a new floor
too yeah let's go get a new floor flooring brick floor ruins floor bamboo mat red floor leaf floor
earthen floor quality plank floor arranged and pleasing patterns hard to clean though
46 000 dollars that's so much money i'm gonna go with leaf counters legend barrel counter
draped counters legendary counter looks stupid draped counter the walls i don't like the
the heretic walls how about like stone just like a nice stone fake stone versus stone why would
fake stone be more expensive than real stone i'll leave it as is let's just go back uh-huh
yeah we saw this already let's make our home look nice so let's change the flooring
this is ugly this is really ugly i like these the resort walls are so much nicer looking than that
this though i need a different carpet though this is yeah that's horrible dark and gaudy
it's a goth store well not quite all right let's do oh i want to fusion i want to see the fusion
stuff there's a new rank two fusions power glove rank one rank two i don't even know what the
hell this stuff is i need to find it first 20 apples oh jeez this is oh jeez rick did i
really just do oh jeez oh jeez i can't believe i just did that i did an oh jeez no i can't do
any of these you know the funniest thing in the world is if you if you just say the word
rick and morty somebody tries to eat your fucking eyes with a knife all you have to say that you
just have to say the word like morty and it's just it's game over oh i can do this no i gotta
unlock the sam's hat oh that i remember i remember this one why is that that's like a horrible thing
to hear it's like a certain frequency on the radio that you get to and it's like ear piercing
and like you guys cover your ears and you move around you're in pain it's a dumb tv show
men of character are currently seeking out rusty daggers price of candy is normalized finally took
like three weeks men of character all right we're we're two days i got there i got plenty of money
i need to go deeper into the dungeon put it to get a new floor i like this floor it's not that bad
you'll get used to it you'll like it right okay dungeon let's go to dungeon
adventurer's guild bring a thieves knife with you i'm gonna bring some food too do i have any food
yes i do i have apples apple cherry okay i'm going to do this this time i'm gonna do it
i'm ready amber garden floor six to ten it's equipped right let me make sure it is it is
all right let's go
i ain't gonna blow it this time i'll probably get to level 12 before i go down a floor and then
we're looking for cool items unidentified stuff we haven't seen before that's just a hack i don't
want that these guys are the worst because i gotta get close
oh
motherfucker doing better than last time
pumpkins really whoa gaseous grass
that's new i dropped some frames it's all right it's oh
slime liver or slime fluid i don't know what happened there but i apparently i
critical strikes counter-attack oh it's over i can't do it i can't do it like this
i can't do it like this give me give me the exit quick before this gets any worse watch out for
that fish that's just chasing me fuck it's gonna hit me all right give me the next floor
it's probably gonna be a boss too i'm gonna get destroyed
nice battling
use the d-pad for the parry
these pumpkins suck something just dropped though was that herb seed
drop on the shadow
i'm getting new items though that's good oh fuck i have to eat something
don't just don't blow just eat i have that's why i brought them that's why i brought the apples
all right i'm fine
oh
orange nice okay almost level 13
and then i get full health and full mana easy easy easy easy
just kill this idiot kill this guy and then i level up we're good we're good we're good
it's wooden i don't really want it i got a lot of stuff to throw away and a lot of junk
well a lot of stuff is junk you serious
don't run into the wall don't run into this guy either
i had to dodge this thing all right almost done right floor seven i'm not quite
take it so i can eat it
the pumpkins have a shitload of experience
i still need this lime liver i gotta go back and do it again there's too much there's so much to do
it's a little time in the day attack power doubled for everybody that's bad
that means if i get hit like twice i die
i can't i don't that was off screen that's some off-screen bullshit all right this same
shit happened to me last time i'm not gonna let that happen again he's losing he's losing
it he's losing it no i'm good let me get to 14 what level is um
louis like 18 or 19 right something like that 20 20 right right right
by the way if i get hit by that it would have killed me instantly so good thing i
didn't get hit by it just eat the bread
70 damage that's pretty good uh i think i can get to 13 14 on the same floor
floor
almost probably get it here thanks to the free exp got it all right let's go just go
news defense power doubled for everyone all right so i got one more floor and then we're
probably gonna see a boss uh do i just go down i wonder if i should just try to fight the boss
with the items that i have yeah this is gonna be hell was this a cube eternal ice i don't want
to lose that that seems like a really good item i just got like the tesseract i don't think i'm
gonna lose it although i probably might i might be able to get to 15
it's very i don't know it might not be worth the risk i'll try everything takes forever to kill
i don't think that means more experience that just means harder to kill
okay
nice oh all right not bad i think i'm just gonna go
i think that's what's gonna happen i got pretty much full health on everything full
i want to deal with the defense shit after these guys i'm gonna go through
let's see what it is uh no no no no no no no no get get the that's what i'm here for i'm here
for the to level her up i'd be breaking the rule that's what i'm doing here
seven seven ten ten slime fluid i want to throw away
this stupid red coat fall fall fall please
okay of course you wait that long thanks appreciate it that was great
okay 15 before i do the boss please i can do it there's like enough uh spawned enemies
all right don't be stupid here
all right that's the best thing i found so far and with this deep down
let's get the respawn this should level me up although it might not it is pumpkin so it
works a lot all pumpkins no
don't even pick it up not even worth it
i'm gonna get hit every single time by these dumb thing
so close get rid of this shitty slime fluid
gaseous grass again all right let's get back
15 there it is no time like the present the insect king probably gonna hit right in the eye
okay hold on fuck oh my god bad
i gotta yeah i gotta use the d-pad for this shit
fuck oh my god i'm getting stuck
fuck
greedy
you drop something what is this it's like a note tough shell
are we gonna need that for something yeah that's enough it's time to get up
keep going on no balls i'm not gonna keep going down there what are you crazy
where is it tough shell all right let me let me see here fusion rank one bow
i wonder if this is worth doing what about i wonder what rank two bow is
i could do a maiden's bracelet but no rank one helm i can do this not quite
muffler rank two bow is no i'll do the rank one bow weapons are always worth more
long glowing herb seed yeah 6500 not bad not very good either though i'm also going to
go back to here long sword still expensive yes there all right i'm gonna put the long
swords in the window i'll fix it in a minute don't worry that's fine i'm gonna put the steel
sword up here might as well just do it somebody eventually is gonna want to use this right
let's get some cakes over here yam candy apple your store is disgusting my store is just fine
wait no no no no get these i i i'm take these off i have these cakes for a very specific reason
they have to go in the food bucket thing hold the books hold uh this hold that put some charms up
maybe all right whatever let's go i do have the food that's why i took these off because look at
that expensive shit i'll do it uh 8100 i didn't know the germa was a genius like me there we go
steel sword let's do two two ten ring i still don't have any rings i just go buy one she's
gonna come back and want one right there goes the combo uh this she's cheap so we're gonna do 175
oh sell this i'll take it see if i can get it for 46 oh kids genius these i made out really well
with these 82 i mean that's i did really well already on the way to the 80 000 first person
come for the watermelon you usually you don't uh it's hard to sell i don't think i think i'm
gonna stay around 2500 what is pi to 300 digits if you're such a if a genius 3.146
four one two two four three four six one one eight eight two two seven seven two four four nine
nine nine four four three three two six seven four three four two one zero what increased weapons
what weapons increased all weapons have increased this is what we waited for here we go guys check
it watch this we are now a weapons only store and i'm talking expensive weapons what's the most
expensive should i got pretty wand this rosebud bow practice lance i could do the thief's knife
sturdy glove no no no no thief's knife no this magician staff i want her to buy this thief's
knife so i'm gonna get out of the window we're gonna have let's have like food over here too
i'm all right with the food being there let's go germa's weapon buy back emplorium i'll take
that at value one oh one oh three i got the heart i got a perfect sale too this is what happens when
you offer food two foodstuffs i'm again i'm just gonna go buy the cakes just buy the cakes and
sell them at times two easy that's it how what oh what's this guy again i need two foodstuffs if
i return and no everyone just should i just i'm just gonna go buy like 30 cakes nobody wants
weapons there it is i have to do this at like 160 or 170 though she won't buy it if it's over like
180 i'll try 180 i mean this is that's 12 000 she won't do it i'll do 12 5 but she's not going to
do it oh we fucked she actually did all right that's not a bad sale i need a new piece of armor
i could do gloves or i could do iron armor but you can't wear that right i'm just gonna sell her the
gloves i mean like times two wait what what what's wrong gloves are armor i thought it has to be a
breastplate gloves are a weapon are you really asking me if i have a weapon that's all that's
in here all right what's the most expensive thing i have bow practice lance is probably the most
expensive thing perfect how much that'll be 990 9200 pretty good day so far
i'm gonna get i'm gonna get ballsy here 225 that's a much better day a much better hour
get this off um any more expensive stuff put the parade armor up there someone will buy it
although i've been holding on to these because at some point they'll be worth more
now i'll take that off not worth it put iron armor up there sturdy glove
deposit bow that looks good too come on in hey miss i need two food stuffs if i return in three days
food orders here oh look at that crafter's knife don't have to keep bringing it with me
i want you to have this though so i'm gonna do 185 uh this is a present from mommy
okay perfect okay you want the power glove 190 all right look i'm looking by money this time
how much for the armor 120 2,300 somebody buy that wand all right composite bow we're doing
6,400 perfect you want to pay 220 percent all right i'll take it the price of sweets has
increased the price of swords has normalized okay so all the swords are normal now everything else
is still there so get but weapons are all still it's still a weapon sweets all right i have
oh wait a minute i should have bought it i should have bought the cakes
oh i can still buy the cakes is it too late no it's too late all right while there's still
time i'm gonna put i'm gonna sell more weapons sell the long sword while swords are still expensive
i know the the market's closed cake the cakes are closed the store's closed it's closed
i can't do it it's closed i have toothpicks out here go to 14
tomorrow morning yeah i'm gonna buy as many cakes as many sweets as i can purchase there we go
let's see if you'll do 206 finally got rid of that one iron spear you'll do two yeah you'll do
four thousand yeah you're a sucker you'll do two thousand oh these things are holy shit all right
hold on this is currently in a in a buyer market right now a seller's market right now um 65 62
percent i could i could hold on 75 percent if he might just walk out though i can double that so
i'm gonna do i'm gonna do i'm gonna just buy it i'm gonna do 87 75 percent see all right no i got i
i'm gonna i'm gonna buy it at a premium i don't i'm gonna buy it at a premium i know i need to
have that i can sell that for 20 000 right now i don't tell me the haggling is wrong unless
tomorrow if we wake up in the morning and sweets are down then that was a really really big mistake
then i will agree with you but hold up yeah hold on here we go let's load up on fucking sweets
look at this okay okay okay okay slow down
i'm buying the ring for that lady all right and okay all right all right let's get out let's go
stop it you're i'm not out of control i'm fine because check it watch this check this out
no get the durian up here i want to show you guys what i was doing
i gotta slow down slow durian cakes peach tin put it everywhere peach tin
that can be the weapons table that's fine baked yam candy apples baked yam
how is that a sweet isn't that a fish here we go murph oh it's this guy bye i don't suppose you
have a scarf oh i think i do sorry dude there it is no this is my market get out of here with this
i don't want no i know that those are worth a lot more we i'll give you 50 for that apple no yeah
whatever i know what you're doing because that's what i'm doing everybody knows we all subscribe
to the same newsletter i don't know if i buy it everyone's selling uh all right eight i'll give
me eight thousand for it all right that's what it's worth i'm putting it up tomorrow somebody buy it
oh hi how much for this my first cake sale to 7500 i was looking for this more cakes let's
let's put 228 now 225 all right now put the housewives with new money management skills
are on a precious metals vendor price of weapons has normalized okay as long as sweets are still
expensive i'm i'm the durian guy engaged in plebeian labor as always you're going somewhere
again indeed i am father i have to have some truffles puffles and you don't even know what a
truffle is it's to be expected of a popper i suppose how distressing well then this time i
shall instruct you personally truff k as this dr steve rule truffle truffle truffle or truff k
oh yes you should be thankful anyway listen well truffles are mushrooms
reset what do you want a mushroom or not yes that's it so mushrooms okay thanks alouette i
feel smarter already all right well then pardon pardon moi that was the most awkward conversation
i think we've had in the game so far maybe i'm too used to tears long explanation of things
i like some clothes got a windbreaker right here for you that's it that's the one
six hundred dollars please all right he talked all that shit about the mushrooms
245 enjoy your truffles i can probably buy some now too this here we go this is what i did this for
six seventeen thousand dollars that's why i bought these that's i've already paid for both of them
twice oh yeah yeah yeah yeah i'll take i can take that 10 grand somebody buy that the durian
no i know what these are worth i'll give you 100 i'll give you i'll give you 800 for it
oh no mommy asked me to sell this you little shit durian i need to get a ring
that's why i bought the ring that'll be fine 12 000 no because it was blue
okay we all get the same investor newsletters i need two metal things everyone's losing
faith in the sweets market this is not good the price of armor has decreased
the price of sweets has normalized it's all right i made i made 17 grand i can still sell this with
like seven i can still sell this it's all right i got plenty of peach tits that i can
i got fucked by this market i just i'll be real you guys everyone was buying it's all right i can
what is expensive now nothing get the vase back up here get a couple of weapons maybe get a couple
of weapons no no i'll put a long sword up there why not then let's uh yeah no just get in here i
somebody will buy it come on i like something metal is iron is iron made out of metal iron is
metal right yes right no it's not so what's what what are they but i mean what do they classify
as metal in this game is wood made out of metal i'm kidding magnet that's a that's metal a magnet
it's a metal a ring is made out of metal i just don't know if this game like does this game like
qualify what is what is it quantifying rings and gold are not metal in this game
so the vending machine okay here this is made out of metal is it it could be
oh durian i'm at least gonna make back what i said 120 what do you mean what the heck too much
9 000 what the fuck it's all coming down i think this is my cell i really need a treasure
i got just the thing take this 22 000 dollars please it's perfect all right don't blow this
20 no 22 500 we're back you can dump the ashes if you want oh my god that was terrible
is the ring did i already get rid of the ring there it is okay now this is the problem i have
to sell this for a little bit lower because it's a shitty market for rings i bought this for how
much did i buy this for i bought it for 6 000 so let me get 80 90 oh come on a thousand more
than i would i bought it for you've got to be kidding me can i make 200 bucks here i made
500 bucks i lost the combo i got plenty of money next one's 80 so that means by the time
that the payment comes around i need 160 000 i want to be times two in front of this
i'm ready oh yeah it's the robot all right i think durian can stay up there
we're in a shit market right now all right now i'm gonna go down i'm gonna attack
hold on do a thing i overheard some of the customers discussing rumor about someone near
the fountain attempting to sell overpriced items like what paintings and other objects
to art with hard to define value seemingly even then though the offer prices were apparently
absurd let there be a lesson always try to keep our prices realistic or people who begin to spread
rumors about us yeah art's tough to sell though indeed we should always be careful in stocking
paintings and the like new character hey you there uh can we help you you two look like you
have good taste tell me what do you think of these they're pictures postcards oh the sea these are
quite well drawn to be honest aren't they that wouldn't you love having a few of these on hand
at all time but i don't i don't think they match my stamps or anything i own now that i think
about it nonsense they'll look perfect with any stamp in the world or you could pin them up on
your wall use them as pictures or perhaps i could interest you in something else i'm sure i have
something you'll just adore i don't know i don't know what's the asking price for one of these
postcards 500 000 might suggest we return home now wait wait wait wait i'll make a wonderful
heirloom and the price will only go up you know it's an investment really somehow i doubt that
wait please wait you've got it all wrong it's an adventure it's a leonardo adventure ah why the
hell is that old urea charm hauling them in i totally have that little airheaded brat figured
for easy mark too friggin fairy and now i'm all worn out too and there's some rich foolish
adventurer out there with more money that good sense i'm dying here cool that old guy gives
really big bonuses so what to do for lunch hey you there mr cool swordsman hi hello are you talking
to me you bet i am listen i've got an offer for you that's a big eat heat when i was little i
used to come here a lot really i must have been you do not strike me as the very did this i feel
like the church has no purpose maybe later all right let's go level 15 shell chest piece i want
no no no no no no i'm gonna get i'm just gonna get you a good weapon what is this shit knight's
blade uh pure edge i'm just gonna give it to you i just i want it this is expensive stuff sand charm
these are uh silver helm these are priced pretty well scale hat get it knight shield these are all
cheap big shield strong arm band just buy up some stuff but not that much silver arm but this is
crazy steel breastplate get it wizard rope get it okay style that's enough that's enough still
close one more silver gauntlet last one that's it that's it no i did which was so cheap i had to
have i unlocked any other rank two things rank one helm rank one muffler rank two sword no
rank two dagger i have the pure edge still don't know what this stuff is gunpowder red oil
look at how much gunpowder that is now this is important i need to do this shit take this
take the breastplate the strong arm band all right and that's good
i'm going for it floor 11 to 15 if i die here this is a huge problem food food right i didn't take
any food thank you for stopping me we're gonna take a cherry we're gonna take
a chocolate bar we're gonna take some walnut bread i'm gonna take the apple i'm taking a
lot of items but it's very important that i don't lose save the game you know that's even smarter
holy shit that would have been horrible i get too into it and i get i get too into it what else do
i want anything apple cherry walnut bread and the candy all right here we go floor 11 to 15 i'm
ready equip the items everything equipped just double check i got good shit oh god okay i already
took too much damage cloak i'm gonna do just do it slow there's no reason to go fast
this ain't a speed run this is a regular run
i want to try to get to 16 games done normally that's right
games done at your leisure
not here oh that would have been big would have hit me
oh
nice double crit oh that's a triple crit right there oh it felt pretty good
i still got hit it's all right that armor is really really good
game's done with pizzazz i like that that's good
ow i gotta do boss rush to get the slime liver and then what
oh that'll get me in a pretty decent spot right this feels bigger than the other ones
it very well maybe oh shit just give me the exit
i'm fine just get me out of here 12
oh you can wrap that around them that's pretty cool a big swing radius
chat is so predictable are they what do they say i'm not looking at it right now
turn the lookout oh no
well that's a like ten thousand dollars right there
he's wearing earpods
that really is that i don't think that level would not be funny ow what's this water crystal
slime fluid no i don't need that shit
oh parade helm all right this is worth money
17 almost what's that i can work with it
the exp sound is driving me insane this is kind of grating isn't it
what is hitting me what the hell was that
so is there i'm gonna assume this probably only 15
total whoa that's what happens when you look at chat glad i only took
a small amount of damage because that would have been bad trying to go too fast i have a lot of
confidence right now which is bad you never want to feel confident in a game like this you always
want to be nervous fighting your nails and scared up around every single corner
fish cookie it'll be funny if he walked off the edge ha ha i would donate two thousand bits
you can't even walk off the edge i'm stuck here you can't walk off the edge it doesn't work like
that
what time is it right now we're getting to those late hours aren't we
around what midnight eastern i'm still good to go i'm in this for the long haul tonight
i need to know
i just need to know what happens after 200 i just took 55 damage without just have
i know i'm about to level up but i'm scared to get like double tap and die
i'll forget it
i'm gonna hydrate and eat i've already eaten tonight
so right before the stream started i ate a full meal so i'll be good for a little while
i'll be good for like another few hours
pretty good i'm just gonna go i'll try to get to the boss
that's the next floor
and then it's all about the slime i'm gonna just do boss rush get the slime
if i can progress that part of the game
all right so now they're pretty much the same level one more okay uh no not yet
i can probably get to 19 before fighting the boss
he's so addicted well yeah come on
it was last time i was addicted to a game and i wanted to do it for like more than a couple
streams
don't let him play animal crossing yeah but that's just as fun i am a sucker for games with
just slow drip trickling upgrades that's just does it doesn't fool me the gauntlet nobody here
but us what do you mean the gauntlet
holy shit okay this is not a boss i just dump a bunch of enemies at you my god
pretty good move to have here though more it is called the gauntlet yeah oh fuck
too many too many
explosion watch it uh oh
what's that fruit grapes i can't carry any more i gotta wait till after this is over
tons of bat wings
okay there's more of this shit down here uh i might level up
bat wings are not that important but oh jesus oh no there's four of them i'm gonna heal
holy shit they're gonna explode on me one of once one of them dies then they explode and it causes a
huge problem oh shit like that thank god did it all right so this gunpowder
no no i don't need the bat wings i don't know i don't need them but they might be worth more
than this shit that i have okay like a piece of candy is not worth it rusty dagger just throw it
away slime fluid get rid of this walnut bread just eat it
no other items or anything where did the door open probably back here yeah that's i'm pulling out
there it is i can't risk it i have two the items i have it too good
i gotta pee again so it's been three hours i heard this girl has been handing out advice
to people lately yeah and here's the that dude right town square we're gonna see that guy again
good evening you're leaving stroll goodbye good night how did i lose fifty thousand dollars what
did i do the price of long swords has increased the price of accessories has normalized all right
hire an adventurer at the adventurer's guild yes i know that long swords steel sword get it out
there what else is there with money i'm gonna pee yeah i gotta pee all right i'm gonna pee
back to it what are you guys doing i didn't i didn't know that we will be in late night jerks
all right i got a bunch of new stuff in fact i want to sell this stuff first don't have five
orders right due date passed i was i in the dungeon whatever a bunch of food stuff and two metal
things by tomorrow so i need two food stuffs four i got all i have a lot of that shit
i heard you screaming in the bathroom is everything all right yeah everything's fine
i'll be all right i'm the guy who ordered food stuffs i mean okay but you could be a little more
specific tell him the durian no someone will buy that durian you weren't here the day i came to
get my order that's bad business missy all right 200 208 i want to get the little 15
here we go 10109 fuck did what no was that a buy that was a buy wasn't it no it wasn't
no okay this is a buy it was a sell hey look at that told you it was worth holding on to the durian
12 000 price gouger combo come on 15 almost there one more sale run an errand
110 what do i get at 15 the vending machine do you have my food stuffs
i do welcome back let me get rid of these peach tins that i bought too many of during the boom
i'm 26 you'll do it nice all right now let's put the vending machine in a moment if you will
no quite well i simply thought it was time to explain how to place and use vending machines
vending machines allow you to sell a larger volume of items in a shorter amount of time
compared to handling each customer yourself okay to place a vending machine choose the vending
machine from the item placement menu at the counter as if it were a normal item the counter
will become that vending machine and after i put it down it just starts selling stuff
no you'll have to keep the machine stocked yourself there is a limit to how much you can
place in a vending machine as well so be mindful of what you put inside okay there's a downside
however because the vending machine is automatic the price of an item sold from a vending machine
can not be negotiated items will sell for their base price keep that in mind all right it is a
drawback the extra volume can often make up for the lower price however so far cheap items a
vending machine is helpful i'm just gonna get like four of them finally remember that we cannot sell
off the machines ourselves if you wish to dispose of a machine we must sell it back to the merchant
skilled or market at a steep loss keep that in mind if you decide to invest in one all right
well let's get it over here what should i put in it i think i think i want it like right here right
in the front door right there or right here right at the end i think right in the front door peach
tins yams uh i think i could probably just stock up on peach tin i'm gonna put it right here
where is it old vendor whoa it's the whole thing what uh okay is it two this is like the apple
machine and like chocolate and fish do cheap stuff cheap shit well what if it just automatically
sells these for me i think that's worth it for me peach tins won't sell in there what about like
raincoats this is for getting rid of just cheap shit all right well i don't really have that much
cheap shit i mean unthankful statue i got like slime fluids i got a bunch of shitty slime
and anti-venom toothpicks all right it's a toothpick machine this is dumb done stocking
who the hell is gonna buy that shit let's get i want to keep pure edge oh there's no booming
markets right now so yeah there's no booming markets markets are boring today i have so many
anti-venom i'm gonna have to put i'm gonna stock that machine with any venom go back
an adventure i could do that what i got i got what's today i got i got plenty of time i have
plenty of money oh here he is you're doing okay oh elon welcome you finally came well i can't
afford anything expensive but i thought i'd drop by to give you my card you're all right
should we test this guy out i guess you two haven't met this is tier she's my business
partner here at the store here this is elon an adventurer for the record we do not accept
payments on tab yep yep yep give me the card right oh no he doesn't do it yet i don't think
he even did it i'm not sure he did it i need two metal things oh somebody bought something mommy
asked me to sell this what do you mean really that cheap you're getting you're getting what i pay
little lady you got some food i do i do i have some peach tins another sale of slime
dump all my peach tins just get rid of these dumb things
oh rich girl i've been enjoying this a lot more than i thought i would
now that makes two of us this item is for sale it is 17 oh shit i just broke my record
i think it's time to go deeper down into the dungeon that's 92 uh slices right i don't think
i can do it anymore now i can a little 19 yeah let's go down let's keep going and what's that
new steel breastplate bring a little bit of food i'll bring the fish i'll bring oh so i got i got
some bread right cherries bread all right that's good well 16 to 20 12 hours damn it i'm so glad i
have you guys here to yell at me here we go i need the slime boss i need the slime after this
this is definitely the end of the garden sp consumption halved let's go
oh that wasn't cool wasn't cool
cool
third move yep you turn to a spider what is this oh it's the spider web that's the move that she
used on us when we first found her
i don't think blended in with the background come on
so
i can have more than one clone yeah just for some reason my brain just doesn't click and do it
i don't know why
yeah that's really cool
how many can i have i can have as many as i want
what's which one's the real one
that's overpowered well i also have half consumption of mp sp whatever magic power
special power whatever you want to call it
don't want those
rings
looking over at you guys seeing what everybody was saying why am i talking an end of the stream
voice well it's getting late i'm kind of just chilling and playing at this point
i'm just kind of having fun plus uh there's not much to really say when you're doing this part
just kind of kill stuff
you put yourself in low power mode yeah this is low this is low battery mode
like i was doing too many voices making too many fucking like 90s movie references so you
you turned me down i was at like 19 percent you were like holy shit he's gonna he's gonna die
there she is again this is the second time we've run into her down here
what a coincidence oh how are you oh he went oh no no no no we've yeah we've already done this
have a nice life bye your own worst enemy jeremy
nobody else
don't sell weapons in your store
adventurers will ask for weapons yeah i've noticed that too they kind of just come in
and they say hey do you have this don't forget it actually you know
it's free experience why not take it right
worthless yeah and i can't just lend them the weapons too but in a perfect world they come in
and ask for it or they want to buy it so then not only do you don't have to equip it on every time
but they also pay you for it it is a perfect scenario there
don't blow up on me
17 this is 18
that's pretty brutal put on a christmas ost no no christmas song
look it's already getting late for people you i don't i don't want to put people to sleep
if people let's just relax and right now i'm like yeah you know just relax
you want me to like put people to bed
so
i'd rather you do the thing where your eyes close and then your like face goes forward
and your ipad hits you in the chest and you catch yourself really quick
you fall asleep for like 0.3 seconds in your eyes you rip your eyes open you sit back up
i'd rather you do that
if i start playing christmas music you're all you're all gonna be gone
what if i turn on christmas music and people just got like lit the fuck up
it's possible just play the muppets christmas carol entire ost people get
started losing their minds in here
oh shit no i don't know why i just started talking about it and then i just started to go
like sleepy why did that happen no no it's only like six hours at 15 everything's fine
fine
no it's not time yet it's not time it's not my time for bed jeremy go to bed no
i need to stay can i stay for like another hour please mom trash
okay five more minutes five more minutes oh cool she comes back like 45 minutes later
okay i it's been it's been five minutes no come on please i even gave you some extra time there
no i didn't you didn't you gave me like like five yeah it was only 10 minutes
i gotta pay attention it's a crab oh fuck i'm gonna have to knock shit into him
aren't i i'm gonna have to explode things on him i guarantee it yep and then here we go
oh fuck what have i done i just freaked out
all right freeze him come over here over here come on step step step step step okay
that's broken that's absolutely broken i just hit him with like nine people oh a cube
eat the candy yeah just get rid of the candy tough stone nice try try keep going no
not worth it i don't want to lose the weapon pretty good day yeah i gotta spend i gotta make
some money because this is where it absolutely it just it derails if i don't have at least like
two or three hundred thousand dollars soon here peach tins are falling rapidly really i know what
i'm doing oh fuck just buy all the ham sandwiches i can afford all right that's i don't need any more
than that let's see the uh whatever this is gonna be this is the oh you throw fountain you throw
money in the fountain why sell some shit he's a night 10 000 silver gauntlet yeah i get it up
there or maybe i should just know maybe i should hold on to this that might go way up soon armor
everything's all down i mean the markets like actually kind of suck yeah swords are still all
right hold on can i no i need i gotta make some money i gotta have a sale here let's put the
sandals up there restock this stuff put some slime fluid in here maybe this is junk just put it in
here rusty dagger i don't want it slime fluid slime fluid all right let's get some sales here
have you heard heard about what a while ago there was a coup d'etat in a certain kingdom
what aren't you interested even a little bit oh whatever anyway the king of that land was
actually pretty popular so many people have speculated that the coup was orchestrated by
a rival kingdom and out the people now here's where it gets interesting that king had a daughter and
after the coup she just disappeared the nobility of that realm are searching for her in order to
raise her up as their new queen and seize control again it's me they're quite desperate that kingdom's
troubles are just starting mark my words is that so you really aren't interested in this at all are
you why don't you care well it just feels like it's so far away you know like it could never be me
you're not talking about me it's above the clouds or something why should it matter to me i just own
a store and i've debt this is why you'll always be small time what's my being short got to do with
this listen reset a good merchant knows how to gather information from around the world
understand what it means and put it to good use even things that seem trivial can be important
in the long run therefore the best merchants make it to their job they get the job to gather from
across the news in the world they go to all the reddits every one of them they go to reddit news
they go to reddit interesting gifts they go to reddit earth they go to they get they get their
news and they get their information from all over the world okay i guess that makes sense thanks
one last thing speaking of markets that kingdom is known above all else for their very popular
liquor no i need to be going pardon me all right bye princesses and liquor
answer a question for me oh welcome what's up you wouldn't happen to have a street date for the
newest issue of booze of the world would you who's the world comes out every 25th do you want me to
keep a copy for you now i'll just stop and pick it up when i can i have it i own that i need to get
some food my grandchild wants me to get food food is even bad i'm gonna have to give you something
crappy yeah take the peach tin and i know you're gonna i it's a how can i 100 just take it i know
i knew it just just take it from me i don't want to fuck can i purchase this yes you can
powerful anti-venom i have to put those in the machine came by to sell this well i too can play
this game so 100 oh all right don't mess this up 8800 no 8700 good is anyone buying from the
venue uh yeah people are buying from the vending machines that was so cheap that was you pretty
much just threw it in the trash i'm the guy who ordered metal things oh whoops uh you want should
i give him the two swords is this charm made out of metal just take the swords no i want this to be
first spit in his face what's wrong with you 238 he'll do it yes that's a big sale aren't i proud
that i come to shop here is this worth it 200 for this rich girl for 16 grand worth a shot
it was worth a shot 150 i'm losing my combo here
yes i'll buy a candy apple or penny on the dollar
somebody bought something how close am i all right 80 000 i'm not at my 160 000 that i wanted to be
that's not good let me go to the fusion store i gotta be getting close to do something cool here
right i need to do the all right wait wait wait rank two sword gunpowder no i don't know
any of this tough stone and then this armor here no don't know any of these items yet
i could do rank one shoe that's what let me do this one leather boots you don't sell boots
how do you not sell boots you sell everything you sell gloves you sell everything else why do
you not have boots leather boots let's try it rank one shoes watercrestal leather boots do it
good 6800 rank one muffler takes way too much romantics cape don't have it
this is worth a lot but i need it rank one helm all right thankful statue slime liver
i'm gonna go get two of these slime livers right now no and tomorrow i will i'm gonna put those on
the on sale though yeah where they at mermaid shoes pretty good deal here 9800 how are these
looking i have so many bat wings that i don't think i don't care if i get you know base value
for this i'm not gonna put them out all right what any more expensive stuff i got keep these
she wants that book i don't want to sell the knife i'll put this up all this stuff is too cheap put
a charm a couple of charms i got one more shot here to make some money chat has spoken what do
you mean thief's knife um i mean it's just better than what you have i want you to have this so i
want to wait good see that's what i'm talking about making monkey noises no it's like one o'clock
in the morning eastern i know it's only 10 p.m pacific but that doesn't matter i already did a
monkey i've done a monkey noise today rewind of like two hours i already did it i already did a
monkey today something sweet i've got sweetness yam is sweet right the price is down though all this
shit is done something sweet you want a ham sandwich the price is way down 26 grand
all right here comes the ever looming the price of precious metals has increased
the price of pieces of armor has normalized a few more days and then we get to the hard part
and as long as i do that i'll be happy and i can save the game right now in a decent spot
i'm not going to do a monkey sound i need to do slime livers oh these are red these are red
very cool all right i can make some money with those all right i just need to do um what is it
boss rush just do boss rush like five times i need to kill everything do a slime noise
to that see that i can do there
die die all right slime did i get it i did perfect slime literally two of these
i just leave no i have a back scratcher is important too
yes i understand i'm doing this very very poorly
it doesn't matter this is the easy stuff
okay
just eat one broke the mushroom yes i did he's just clubbing me
back scratcher did i watch stranger things i've never seen a stranger thing so no i've not seen
one episode all right don't lose here don't be stupid
don't you fucking dare lose
no stranger things is bad i've i've never seen stranger things so i i've heard it was a pretty
good show but i don't know apart i need one more
bounce bounce
bounce
there it is all right i got two cool just what i wanted
let's see if i can get the back scratcher somebody on the internet told you something
is bad did you just take their word for it no i i know the show is supposed to be good
i just never really watched it i think i've seen the first episode
so
i thought the first episode was good i didn't see anything wrong with the first episode i was
like oh that was kind of cool just eat one you're making this hard go eat one of those
you're making me upset oh my god what do i have to do to get you to eat that
but finally
oh he dropped a tail that's i don't think i've seen i've not seen that item before
you better off watching twin peaks that's another show that i've never watched
let's see if i can do something weird here
got it i don't really watch tv that's fine
so now i can craft that thing that i wanted to craft
could you give us your best jora impression
no i'm sorry i can't actually replace that with this lots of accessories very expensive
these yams out of here we are now an accessory store crap section there it is i still have all
these bat wings in here all right let's go okay open welcome to
good day did you finally manage to get my order i did i'm under the name of duck tata have you
no i'm gonna do it i'm gonna do it it's you know it's like late and like
they're there are less people here right now so you won't even they won't even know i did this
i was gonna do do do do all right did it
my watch stopped what is this here i have a have a peek at my special merchandise
is this bullshit 500 percent of base price excuse me i'll do i'll do like i'll do like
54 go charm face price 221 got it got it got it got it i'm gonna do that every time i make a sale
hi there mommy asked me to sell this thing it's too expensive though sorry no
i can't afford this if you'll take 90 you know what listen to this i'll give you 99
percent i could just flip it for 25 oh i want this silver armor 20 grand this is a big one
although she doesn't like to spend that kind of money we'll do 180 she she's very cheap she
doesn't do it got it who's next you have my metal things uh-oh is that is is silver and metal what's
a metal what is metal what is metal what is metal what is metal what is metal what is metal
okay is what is what metal remember this one uh let's see what's the most expensive metal that i
have dude you're not you're fucked now you're gonna have to pay me a shitload of money this
is gonna be the most expensive thing i've done in the game silver is not precious metal metal
the price of daggers has increased all right i'm at that point where i'm at 160 000 though so
and then in the two day yeah this is going well i'm so happy about this
this is good shit you know what i mean oh i could sell this and just buy it again all right i'm
gonna sell this and then buy it again how are we doing over here it's all about cash flow now
welcome to oh great good day you seem to be longing about as usual well that's not true
i'm really very very busy even if i do have my feet up on the counter right putting that aside
for a moment i assume you've heard about the recent issues concerning trade of items deemed
by the chapel masters to be magical typical i have heard about that the chapel masters have
been seizing items that they claim have a corrupting influence on man's immortal soul
i believe the claim was yeah spot on just that i'd expect to view madame fairy hey anyway it's all
a super bad califragilisticexpialidocious nonsense interestingly though the items that
the chapel gathers for a destruction a lot of them are turning up in the dungeons and i mean
a lot well why very good question the dungeons have always been packed with mysterious
mysteries however so it may not be worth thinking about too hard it does however present an
opportunity which leads me to a guild card oh you want us to give the items back to the chapel
masters how can you be so dense and still be capable of breathing dense uh like a chocolate
cake i want to make sure that these items return to general circulation the chapel masters are
standing astride curiosity and knowledge and i won't have it if you help me you can recover
some of these to sell while i lay hands on other things for study the chapel masters won't try to
seize property from a spec to a secular shop so you would have nothing to worry about of course
the merchants guild is a jurisdiction over the behavior of the city's merchants
and the guild master would never cede authority to anyone so so they can't touch us aren't city
politics wonderfully headache-inducing regardless madame fairy you provide the material support i
provide the quite literal firepower we go into a dungeon together and get what we need agreed
well we'll pay the adventure fee for sure but you'll have to buy what we find here
in the shop just like everybody else oh man you gotta be uh well yeah that's acceptable
i'm looking forward to seeing you in action i expect a lot mr magician
you hardly need to worry on that front miss counter jockey make sure you can identify everything
is fine okay this chat is a mess why i'd like a weapon oh would you like a weapon i got one for
you and it's the one that i want you to have so badly do you have the cash to give me this
let's just do straight 200 yes money is no longer of concern
oh you're selling this to me i sure am for 20 000
dollar
what else you got how much for this 1450 somebody buy that silver helm yes
to 21 21 000 the biggest day i've had this is almost 100 000 in sales i need two weapons
i'll come back in two days okay you want to sell this to me 45 percent when do i
owe the 200k i owe 80 in a day or two and then 200k as long as i get over that hurdle
i'll be happy i came by to sell this today no i mean if you if you're willing to if you
willing to go 78 70 yeah 19 000 that's too cheap make the offer a little bit better all right 21
21 000 all right i got it i did it i got it 207 it's going down tomorrow that's cool because
tomorrow is not even right now it's still today it's meaty uh the anti venom here now
i have way too much of this shit no no no no no no no no no okay we're done big shiny thing
shiny thing what am i gonna do this game's gonna make me watch anime get the iron up there a couple
more pieces of iron let me check the uh joel raid incoming is that for real so how do i prepare for
what do i do i gotta prepare for this all right just wait what do i gotta be like
what do i do make a joke hold on wait everyone be laughing your ass off right like i i want like
i want only luls in the chat because i'm gonna be like going over a story that was like the funniest
fucking thing you've ever heard in your whole life is it happening now let me know when it's like
about that honest to god the cat the cat the cat is seriously up up in the tree and i'm trying to
find a way i i put on swimmies right to try to climb the tree better to think maybe there's
gonna be grip for the swimmies and i'm shuffling up the tree and i get up there and the cat's just
like and it's i swear to god and this is seriously one of the like most ridiculous things that ever
happened in my life the cat pukes as i get right up to the cat i'm about to like save the cat out
of the tree the cat rose up right into my face and it's just like but i still had to hold on
to the tree so as i'm holding on to the tree i almost lose grip like twice but thank god i had
those swimmies you know i'm saying like hello well so i finally get up to the on the perch
right after wiping the cat fugue off my face and i go back on top i'm sitting the cat has moved
over to the end of the branch by now so by the time the cat is sitting on the end of the branch
i'm just like don't jump up please don't do that like i'm trying my hardest to save you
a bird lands on the on like the right in front of where the cat is so the cat is the cat has
now got his attention on the bird so the bird yes yeah where is he is that did happen yes and
it's honest to god it was unbelievable so you've got like you've got like you've got a cat sitting
on the edge you've got a bird sitting there and the cat now has the attention on the bird
so the bird is the bird is like is squawking at the cat at this point and then they're moving
the branch back and forth i'm like shaking on the branch like holy shit dude like the branch is
shaking the cat is fucking screaming the bird is screaming and like honestly i'm not even kidding
about this the bird just starts throwing up and i don't know how that even happened makes absolutely
no sense so cat is on the branch bird now has thrown up and i'm sitting up there with my
swimmies on trying to find how how am i gonna get both i have to save both of these these animals
up here you know what i mean and then the fire truck you know like it's flying down the road
and i'm stuck in the tree now trying to save this bird and save this cat and the fireman has a big
megaphone hey can you get down from there son and i'm sitting like oh yeah what the heck am i going
to do about this so they they would they brought the trampoline over i know this is i know it's
crazy wait did we did we get a raid hold on i'm in the middle of telling this crazy crazy story
that happened to me when i was like fucking 19 it's it's hilarious so finally a long story short
i mean it's been like a like a 35 minute story so i can't even tell the end of it because i can't
think hard to do so the fireman is starts crawling up the tree because he has to climb up the tree
too by the way cat is already on the ground cat just climbed down the tree on his own the bird
flies away and i got this fireman that now has to help me get down from the tree my mother came out
it was so embarrassing it was most fucked up thing it was all over the place and finally like the
fireman said hey at least you tried right that was the last thing at least you tried oh my god
my stomach fucking hurts isn't that like insane though but uh thank you joel joel came in with a
raid right there thank you so much uh hope you guys had fun we're playing this um we're playing
this game called uh item tale a shop of a little shop of horrors i don't even know the title of the
name of the game is receipt here so it's a big game you buy stuff you sell stuff you trade stuff
you fight monsters it's pretty awesome but welcome everybody thank you joe hope you had a good
stream welcome but after that let's let's start a uh let's let's sell some stuff sorry for like a
long-winded like 40 minute story but it was it was it was the funniest thing i've probably ever said
all like in my life oh no no no no no no no no no no no can you repeat the story no i can't
it's just it just took it'll take too long i don't want to buy this for ten thousand dollars
but i'm gonna try i want to sell this no i'll give you 500 bucks for it that was so funny i
threw up on my bird here we are all right whistle over overcharge 250 wait what what happened i
literally come in i learned to come in and you're saying the bird shit and vomited no no no no no
there was a long story there was a very long story there i was talking about some crazy thing that
happened out like when i was like a teenager you want a treasure okay hey remember how everybody
made fun of me for doing this remember when everyone talked all the smack in the chat about
how i shouldn't have paid like ten twelve thousand dollars for this what do you say now
where are they where are they now where are they i just made a shitload of money we all said it was
a good idea no you didn't at least 10 of you said it was a bad idea i'm on an errand today yes you
are 185 somebody bought something for the vending machine brought you something good i mean that's
not that good that's like that's like 45 percent of base price good almost level 16 what can i do
with 16 need to get some sweets really quickly this is a birthday cake problem here peach tin
these things are way done baked in how about a knife no can we stop laughing now um yeah there's
nothing nothing funny is going on right now you can stop you can stop doing that because nothing
funny is currently happening right now so you can cease doing what you're doing you don't have to
do that now are we clear on that you know what i mean you get it you know what i'm saying okay
that hurts hurting my arm all right get the cheap shit out of here just fill up with any of them
hydrate i'm good i drank guys i drank a cup i already i drank water what was i gonna do
oh boy knight shield all these prices are so inflated yeah no no not just the shield
the knife up there all right let's just do it again we have plenty of money
you're supposed to drink six gallons of water a day you're not supposed to do that
i'm gonna be a dick 235 percent oh is that better yeah you have wood on
i want you to make sure that you buy it i'm loaded down i have so much money
no her name is not recess it's resetting it's receipt it's not recess somebody buy the night
shield night shield oh yeah i'll buy the durian okay will you take it with 30 3800 bucks knock
that one out of the park hold on what's that right down the middle 153 000 of profit this year's
harvest a disaster the price of food has increased sweet heaven the market around
bat wings has completely collapsed oh right hold on hold on how many bat
thankfully i already sold my bat wings so i don't care oh damn look at this all right i can keep
we're gonna be uh we do peach tin 3000 how much is what we got we got ham sandwiches 3500
okay ham sandwiches beef bowls we're talking food all food durian get the durian up there
ham sandwich let's put uh peach tin down here get the charm out of here i don't need it for
anything let's get the baked yam so it's you know variety beef bowl all right how does this look
pretty good ingredients bat wings they're terrible price crash too bad i can't buy them anywhere
let's go it pains me no you're selling me candy uh i'll give you i'll give you a base i'll give
you a full price for it it's turning around tomorrow i'm gonna put it in the machine tomorrow
no no i'm gonna no i'm gonna put it on display i need a candy anyways do i have some food yes
it's everywhere i do have food i actually have a durian and it's gonna be a lot of
that's gonna be very expensive wow i did not think that was gonna work
i am depositing this item i'll buy it for 2000 he's starving i'm a monster just take a quick
look it won't take long trust me eastern wallpaper is it worth it what's eastern wallpaper can i get
can i buy this from the store i know it's the scammer but i what if i just made everybody
scream right now what if i ruined the whole game the store sells it well here i'll give you 50
grand it's 62 percent of base price no i'll give you 40 that's it's 80 grand accessories
do i have anything that's like an accessory no necklace like a magnet necklace that's an
accessory right charm there it is would you look at that hey i need two weapons can i come pick
them up in three days yes you can you don't look too busy here i want to buy this all right this
is better than what you have i don't know your price uh gauge here let's just do one 16th
all right that's okay oh my darlala asked me to pick this up it's the night shield ultimate
dick that was reasonable i'm loaded now i want to ring this up 210
do the mr crabs voice i can't i can't even do mr crabs can we already just go over this
you just said you said a thing that had some type of connection to food and now i'm hungry why'd
you do that i want a crappy patty now even if it's like from the bottom of the ocean i would still
eat it all right that's fine fill this back up powerful anti-venom plus two all right just i'm
going to hold on to the ones that are plus four i'm going to keep a couple of these i feel like
i'm going to need them oh that was an angry voice what's up alabat why are you so upset
you liar that stupid walnut bread fisherman story was a lie why what no it isn't the walnut bread
fisherman wakes up early in the morning to risk his life on the open sea so that he can fish up
walnut bread for everyone it's the coolest thing ever oh thanks to your stupid story i made a fool
of myself why do i put up with this sort of treatment they're both real stupid it's your
own fault for believing something so silly if you think bread comes from the bread fisherman
you probably need to go back to the second grade i don't know you hold on the thing is though
they may be in the second grade so they don't even know that okay now i got it yeah you don't
know where bread comes from when you're like nine it just magically appears on the table
so no this makes sense i'm wrong papa told me that story yeah right the store brings the bread
yeah i had no no come to think of it i'm trying to think of where i thought food came from when
i was 10 11 years old bread and nuts and berries and shit i don't i knew somebody made it but i
didn't really know how oh i can get this for a good price 49 nice do you know where plants came
from of course buy this book you give me some pretty good stuff here oh you want the yam don't
you i'll be good to you sell this i'll take it i'll take it no you're gonna you messed up my
stupid you screwed up my combo looking for a book i got a book for you i got a few of them actually
200 warriors
will you take it for 2090 all right 18 18 now 50 oh i'll take a ham sandwich please
the dude has no more ham sandwiches i need something for my experiments
218 near perfect i want to get two books and i want them in three days i are i have books
i just i have been ready to go why is chat surprised that elan can read yeah sweets are
increasing in popularity with home makers prices for powerful anti-venoms are falling rapidly get
them out of here so what am i getting toothpicks what the hell am i even gonna put in here
i'm kind of running out of stuff to put in here i've sold all my junk i'm almost out of inventory
stuff is increasing in value candy apples let's get them up here sweets are already up
what day do i got one more day tomorrow's the day that it's an 80 000 payment
let me check something here hold on dark and gaudy vending machines at this level you if you are
defeated in the dungeon you may bring back two items level 17 is item storage i'm just dungeon
crawling stuff i'm just trying to stockpile money and then we can do dungeon runs for like a few
days there it is 7500 what's going on why are you guys doing this what's with the market meaning
what's manipulating the market here check this out what fine buy it i don't want it but i'll do this
this really the score is too high that doesn't look just because the score is high does not mean
you have to bring the score down that's not how that works i'm not gonna buy it i'll buy it for
1900 keep combo going a little lady how much for this for you 3500 bucks i got enough padding to
keep me going could i sell it i'll take it like that that's my best offer elliot wave patterns
surprise somebody here knows that that is oh that's an expensive hat derva thinks we're stupid
no i don't i just i i don't why would somebody here know what an elliot wave okay what is it
what's an elliot wave better explain it to me no that does not mean go to google and get the
wikipedia blog about it i want you to tell me what it is i want you to chart something for me
all right what do we got tomorrow tomorrow's the day i got one more time in the shop here
let's get the mermaid shoes up there golden pedestal up there what an economy nerd you don't know what
you're talking about okay we're a candy apple store now guys people are buying these and what
do i got crap in here shitty clothes in there raincoat scrap plate scrap plate arm band that's
fine he finally checked the second vending machine there's only one vending machine
put in the blue ones i will next month how much will i take for this i'll give you 66 percent for
it i'm not budget on this i need to start the combo all right 206 30 grand i have so much
padding don't you think some wonderful art like this would make life better i'm gonna accidentally
hit i'm gonna be talking to you guys or something i'm gonna accidentally just fuck this whole thing
up what is it ocean wallpaper i'll give you 10 grand for it i wanted the ocean i'm gonna go get
the ocean wallpaper i want it i'll take the ham sandwich right up to uh 226 yeah what's going on
here hello my game what just fucking happened what was that save game now hurry up before that
happens again i don't know what just happened i just hit every button and it fixed it fixed itself
price of armor has increased i got a lot of it price of food is normalized all right well
i still have a lot the camera oh okay all right food is normalized armor is not worth a lot
i got wizard robes i've got that's not worth more that's armor how's that not armor it just
it literally says armor keep the shoes up there so you guys are saying that put the blue shit in here
but i know i can sell this stuff normally it's base price only bat wings in i don't think i'd do
it no i gotta keep some bat wings so put some put the charms in here and just guaranteed what's this
doing in here bat wings all right looks good all right i wanted to do something very specific
today today's the day that i just keep selling i got plenty of inventory no i wanted to no
hold on i specifically wanted to get the ocean wall it's not even here she was trying to scam
me yeah but i want the i want the ocean wall i'm fine a little bit sad working hard i hope
are you out on a walk sir that i am i make you happen of getting out of the house on days like
this walking to the sun like this is good for us and we've already seen this i think this is good
i need some what have i got for orders today two weapons do i have two weapons i don't think i do
i have two spheres i gotta go buy them oh and they're cheap as shit too
perfume staff yeah hurricane bolt give me this give me it give me it okay stop buying i'm fine
oh you need to buy i have to buy to build afford things what do you mean don't buy the price is up
on this i think i'm gonna make it rank one helm oh this is that this is what i wanted remember
i bought the thankful statues okay i'm gonna make this worth it and the price is up on this
i'm gonna make this too all right finally get to have a nice big lunch for once time to dig in
the dog eats his food oh this place is dull as a rock today oh kai you hello what that you again
they aren't giving out candy today you know come on i'm totally too old to come in here fishing for
which kind of makes me sad but that's not the point well that reminds me yesterday
coonerp in the market was handing out those signature mud pies the store makes to anyone
who wanted one heaven those are great why didn't you come get me then now i want one too
you're about as predictable as a mud pie too
out of here stop selling it's all about the money it's all about the money it's all about the money
i'm the guy who ordered the weapons yes you are this is a weapon right i could do the perfume
staff in the hurricane book 20 000 if that staff for kai you i don't even want to play with kai
you right now oh i'll be 115 11,300 how can he still be playing this game because i am
painfully addicted to it can't buy to sell this book i'll buy for 800 book hi you oh
oh that's much better than your raincoat 5000 no 47
rich girl uh here's some bread i don't want to ruin my i don't want to ruin the combo
have a good combo going just give it to me wizard's robe i'm gonna be yeah let's do 16 000
nice
2 a.m eastern i know it's getting late it is we're almost at that point where uh yeah
ah but i gotta keep i gotta play this game again no but hold on oh you want i'll buy it
and i get away with like 49 level 17 there's also endless hell mode with high interest debt
that's hilarious 80 000 today and then the 200 000 payment we see where we are i got two of these
golden scales come up they're worth a shitload meditation ring all right let's do one more one
more uh self these are fine let's go i give you 124 i got this for my neighbor's husband
i have no interest in it i'll take it 42 take it or leave it 45 get out of here east coast is
full of milk drinkers with an 8 p.m bedtime what i need a weapon i don't want to get okay i'm gonna
give you a crappy one hey i'm originally from the east coast come on really just take it off me
i'm not an 8 p.m milk drinker don't worry i'm gonna get to the end of this game oh boy
let's be conservative here one 112 metal metal what do i got that's metal
the game doesn't like when you actually pick metals what is actually made out of metal
you think i drink skim milk what's no there's no silver or gold okay nothing here iron armor
yeah it'll do all right i don't even i don't drink milk oh oh oh doing a whole lot of
ooze oh ah oh i want this ocean wallpaper really bad i'll give you 30 grand for it
the debt has been paid coming up next is 200 000 which means i need to be at 400 000
we're getting we're getting to the end game here the end game is coming up it has to be
i'm gonna save it we're gonna power through this i only got one week
weapons has decreased get them off the sweet spoon has ended or everything is normalizing here the
price of bat wings is normalizer right right right get that up there knight's helm that thing's
awesome get it up there cloth hat up there cloth hamburger peach no one's buying these
let's give it one more day all right we got two hundred thousand dollars coming up here
i have enough but we are at the end game i'm ready i'm just gonna start the let's go
sell mommy asked me to sell this will you sell this to me girl i will you're such a kind old man
here these sell pretty well make a million or you're not a gamer get out here 2,700 for a bowl of
soup what's that i want the cat statue how much does she want for that i want that i was going
for it i was gonna pay 50 something percent over the print what there we go he needs this
10-8 now he has that for armor good she wants 200 minimum she ain't gonna get that
no one is buying this stuff from here come here gaudy and dark item storage at this level your
overall inventory capacity in a dungeon is increased by 25 i to 225 items but 18 is more items
how on earth do they expect you to get to level 50 that's kind of insane all right
let's get this crap out of here put the bracelet up there that looks all right
uh chess piece on there too all right we're open there it is 207 you're pretty stingy
i need 600k can i get a book you can get a book i've got at least a few of them
good night streamer boy good night chap have a great night if you gotta go you gotta go
i am gonna try to get through to the end of the debt
whatever how long that takes there we go here it is 125 000 is it really
nice this my combo what's a good price six on day 24 he's still playing the damn game i haven't
slept in weeks god help us thankfully this now i am going to do something here that might be
considered stupid but i'm gonna try to get 50 000 from her that's still worth it that was
fucking almost 40 grand two treasures in two days i can do that is that the only order that i have
tomorrow two weapons and two books i got weapons right yeah i got weapons i got books yeah oh yeah
oh yeah ah okay okay silk clothes yeah i'm killing it nobody can stop me right now
somebody bought it somebody did buy it hey put like a put like a candy in here whatever
at this stage in the game you're really going to come in here and try to sell me this
i'm only doing that for the combo change the decor change the decor like that's money i don't want
to spend right now changing the floor means i have to spend like 40 grand fix your floors and walls
you fuck you want me to i'm gonna lose the game if i buy if i spend like 50 000 right now
this is legend of zelda decor don't you guys love the legend of zelda fine silk need something
metal i've got something metal for you that combo going oh good 400 i've made it to double what i
have leather gloves are currently in price and metal things has normalized right oh wait a minute
this is up these are really in no one's buying this stuff how about this not bad
so fucking apple or something whatever all right i'll change the decor i'll do it all right change
the flooring planks tile we'll just plank change the walls let's do uh we'll do the resort wallpaper
or the lacquer resort wallpaper see now we're light and gaudy actually i do like the other
one better that looks that looks cool nice parade helm he'll bite beam bag sonic wallpaper
you're really into the parade stuff huh that means you'll buy it at 221 percent off
how's it being bag sonic mine selling this here you go 175 because i know you broke
that keeps breaking the combo what would you do if there was another payment after
no she didn't have that if there's another payment after 200 i expect there to be another
payment after 200 that's why i want to make sure i have like 500 grand don't have a gaudy tacky
store well i'll move it over to the other side price of heavy armor has decreased i don't think
i have any of it out uh all armor has normalized weapons are still shitty what do we have for days
here okay i got a few days when somebody coming in today i can't go adventuring can i today two
weapons and two books i can't go adventuring today what can i buy what do you got night
let's get another night's blade get into the pure edge get into the perfume staff hurricane bow
the grand nightmare silver gauntlets sell clothes no they're not cheap i only buy it when it's cheap
okay what about over here anything cheap over here no rings don't sell i got my i got my stock
fill your store with gloves i did this already all right so
i might as well put some stuff in here about thousandth of strong arm band and let's iron
get the necklace up there too let's go oh hey elon stop by today to give you one of these
goddess card strictly speaking i'm a guild member what's got used for a weapon haven't been in a
whole lot of dungeons but when i met you i got to thinking hey i need to start working too
you're embarrassing me a little i think maybe sure and give me a chance i'll go with you anytime
you want counting on you hell yeah we will never be using you he uses bare hands interesting
do i have the weapons i do have the weapons but um yeah i'm gonna they're cheap
i'm gonna sell these cheaper unfortunately you're everyone's gonna say no what are you
doing don't stop stop stop but i have i mean i have to i got screwed on that order
you got you can just take the 200 warriors twice perfect can you sell something for nothing i think
the one dollar here she is heretical carpet dude i can get the scary carpet too
what does she want dude no that'll ruin the whole playthrough i'm sorry i'm not gonna do it
too close can i pick up in three days yes i'm so close should have bought the carpet maybe
huh i'd like a treasure i got plenty of those and they're very expensive this one is 14,900
it is worth 117,500
oh i could probably get away with five five five five food i got food ham sandwich
i still have i got one more i got one more you're in luck
oh remember fellow chat boys sleep is important that goes for you too jeremy
i know but i'm almost level 18 i'm so close look i have one two three four days for 200,000 and then
why the 36 days in this month what month is this
that's not a real month it's a pretend month okay i did my orders outstanding orders we don't have
any we have tomorrow we have two treasures so i have i'm gonna go buy two extraordinarily
expensive treasures golden pedestal and i already have a thankful statue so that's fine
metal items has increased good weapons has normalized oh look at these knight's blades
put me over the edge i'll put me over the edge this is why i was holding for so long don't you
know this is what i was doing this for i've been saving it for so long for this purpose
shitty windbreakers who gives a fuck bring them in let's go big money tonight i like to buy a
weapon uh would you like to buy what's what's more knight's blade pure edge is more no look
oh whoa yeah how does this sound yep take this naginata 227 percent fish yeah no no i'll be nice
warrior's helm 225 is safe
you start to light and plane so the scammed lady doesn't come in anymore
okay here you can have a windbreaker 18 coming up too cold weather clothes
all right magnet necklace going out at 210 i'm doing so well this would be so sad if i couldn't
get to the next level after this look at this shit i'm dumping huge money here 2 12 18 000
18 that was a good day no no no no no no keep them up price of long swords is decreased that
doesn't matter leather gloves boom has ended people with tabs should all right so it's still
oh come on sorry wait wait wait wait wait wait wait 5 000 i put here put this back up
pure edge is still there charm here all right we're good
okay now what do you get at 18 even more items can be found at the guild and in the market
no shit really eskimo shoes graceful ring just eat it mont blanc chestnut cake checkered floor
140 grand no that's too much that's too much i can't super vend this is too much money
i'm thinking about getting the book it's an investment it's an investment in crystal sword
full blade cane staff ace bow platinum halberd giant's fist battle sweater sandwich plate
no it's too much money i got the crystal sword everything's too up right now there she is there
she has misperceived thank me for what oh yeah i remember this already did it all right let's
make it happen come on in glass apple there it is and this and he's it's the grandpa so i'm
thinking too i'm thinking 20 27 000 good good when my grandmother died she told me to sell
this piece of chocolate okay who's next i'd like you to buy this this gross bread
i do have the treasures that you're looking for i've got the golden pedestal and i also have
the you know let's just get rid of this damn thing 26 000
this guy's high as fuck
oh steel breastplate double it up 197 she's stingy grandson when i die i want you to sell
this bar of chocolate for a few dollars down the street that's true that is what yeah that's true
i don't know why i do have a cloth hat your luck my dying wish is for you to make
30 yams with me use me and the recipe and i want you to sell it to people oh everyone's buying all
the expensive stuff i love it i love it we'll go to we'll go 230 225 that was almost all expensive
items on the sunshine forecast beware of sunstroke price of armor has normalized
except this is still this is still catching some money i'm gonna move this stuff up here
pure edge yourself for a lot silver armor no it'll be worth a lot more does it i mean i could no
i'll hold on to it i can't wait till once swords increase i could probably get a hundred thousand
dollars for this these out uh i haven't i've i've let me just slow down here and talk
with bows out how about uh no no that's all right let's go bingo first time out the door
i'll take the sandwich i'll give you a good premium on it too 50 imagine playing this for
eight hours well not gonna be playing for that much longer i just need to pay off my debt and
then and then guess what and then just i was talking to kim last night about this i was like
honey this game's a lot fun we we should play this game together and sell stuff so after i'd pay off
my debt maybe we won't see it again maybe me and kim will just play it i talked i talked this game
up like crazy to kim how would playing together work well she would have a controller and i would
sit behind going oh look at that big price increase big price increase and she'd go big price
increase and she'd pay and i'd go i'd have my fingers in my mouth like oh no it's not bad guys
i wouldn't be back seating her i would be riding the ride with her okay there's a difference
riding the ride means whatever happens i it's just she's gonna play and i'm gonna react
i'm just in the car i mean i'm front okay i'm front seating her because i'm in the car but i'm
not back seating i'm front seating i'm just reacting yeah it's just a reaction out there
anyone deliveries tomorrow two cold weather clothes i think i got that right windbreaker
cloth robe made for adventuring no i don't have any no i gotta go buy this shit right now
it's too late i'm gonna do it tomorrow morning welcome to twitch be looking for something warm
oh here do you want some gauntlets decent protection no i don't got it cloth hat warrior's helm
get lost and sandwich look at that money 2300 is always a good price for that thing nice
perfect you want the iron armor i'll give it to you for four thousand dollars
level 19 what do i get oh i think i can sell it is this a is this your grandfather did you say that
that was a good day i'm gonna do this
daggers has increased look at that pure edge i'm out of daggers swords are way down though
let's get this ring up here and today's the day i need to get uh some warm clothes right
two warm clothes and anything else two clothes or two cold weather clothes all right so
let's buy some four clothes scarves does he sell this battle sweater should i get a battle sweater
fur robe oh extra warmth and style i can only get one of them will the battle sweater work
wizard robe thick robe cloth robe what helmets warm hat all right that's the two warm clothes
and then we just need regular clothes for grandpa i'm going to give grandpa a battle sweater and
so i want a weapon oh do you you're gonna pay a premium
battle sweater grandpa activate oh very cool why do i press the button to have rockets come out of
my chest that would be like part of the comedy in the movie when he presses the button for the
rockets to come up and the rock he has the sweater on backwards and it shoots him backwards and he
flies backwards but actually it would kill him you're right never mind it would just tear through
his uh chest you're right all right this is the cold weather clothes fur robe warm and then it was
warm hat that's in a mike meyers spy movie
oh you can afford it i think this might sell it will that's why i'm going to take it from you
for 40 that's a fucking huge combo precious metals has decreased
swords has normalized only a couple more days before we get to the end game i need to go
into the dungeon because i'm running out of stuff fusion rank three i i store expansion level 20
my god too close with the old man yeah i gotta i gotta get into the dungeon tomorrow is a dungeon
day because i'm i'm i'm out i'm i'm out oh durian i'll take it i'm running an errand how much is
this oh just get get it off the shelf it's been sitting at the two he wants the uh helmet 100
that's too much 125 he'll buy it shit sorry whatever fuck my spear you'll take it yeah
2000 i need to scream to wake the people up that no i'm not gonna scream here's what we're gonna do
hey hey i know you're sleeping right now but what you should what you should do
wake up just there you are hey wake up a little bit wake up there you go you probably should
just turn it off and just roll over and you can go right to bed they just hit like the top button
on the ipad the little have a great sleep we'll hopefully see you again soon have a great night
good night i was thinking about screaming but really loud there but why would i do that to people
um oh no no no no why is it still out there god damn it whatever i'm not i gotta get more
inventory this is bad i guess it's bad i have no leverage
use an air horn i would never want to do that to somebody i woke up a few hours ago right it's
it's like it's really late it is really late you're right don't worry it was the last day
before i clean up get that durian up here there it is beef bowl we gotta i got some expensive
food up here i got a lot of beef bowls come on in oh fuck that was 50 dollars just came in
five zero zero zero five thousand bits by an anonymous cheerer that's anonymous 50 bucks
thank you so much whoever you are an anonymous cheer you forgot he was streaming i kind of did
it thank you for staying up with me by the way those of you that are still here i know we're
going really late if you're going to bed have a great night take care of yourself the scammer is
by the way is in here there comes a scam no buddy pal can you get me some metal do i have any more
iron looks good i almost have the amount of money that i need i need what i need like what
800 000 i need like a million dollars to beat the game accessories has increased i don't
i don't have much accessories i have the shell necklace let's get it up there durian that's good
standard charm get it up there what do we got for a day all right hold on today too close
for the old man i will do that and i'm gonna go to the dungeon come on in old man
oh man all right rich girl wants i'm doing 300 that is the biggest increase
she just got destroyed you got the clothes i do battle sweater silk clothes
stamp it 19.5 i did it i'm gonna do it i'm gonna beat this the durian you can take it to 112
it's just fun just to sell things it's too addicting well i wish they would make this
game for ipad make this game for ipad remake this game or do it again do recedar 2 ipad edition
two pieces of armor in three days i can do that this i'm buying for a thousand
dollars not an app sequel no look i know this too i understand plants versus zombies one
to plants versus zombies two was dog shit okay i will agree with you there but if it was
if they don't have like pay three dollars to do a lightning strike across the board and kill
everything then then it'll be fine all right now it's time to go to the dungeon three days
here we go let's do it it is dungeon time level 23 what does he have levic love magician staff
she's got the it's her we're gonna stick with her can she use the crystal sword
does she what does she have on she i need to put a chess piece i'll be right back oh fuck i didn't
oops oops sorry i'm gonna get the sandwich plate put on the the guy at the baseball game that's
trying to get you to buy hot dogs let's do it i got the pure edge on i think this is gonna be
the end of this dungeon too 25 levels sounds about right
i'm so decked out right now i'm just gonna go wait there's a new enemy here
i just didn't identify new stuff
oh no i don't want to pick it up nothing come on block
ow uh i just want to find the boss i've got more money to make whoa that's gonna explode
good bow wooden bow the third area level 25 and you're still dropping wooden bows
that can't be right i must have like the wrong record quick
oh fuck that's not good what's that pop tart natural heater hold on one of those
things you wait one of those palm heater things the little baggies
so interesting okay i think it's done i felt that one it's called a hottie
is that what they call them i always thought they were called cds brand personal hand warmers
is those the ones that i buy attack power doubled from me only
now we can fill everything
oh nice i'll level up one more time here i don't want to be level 23 that's the satan number
don't die don't die i know i'm getting a little tired and a little
a little slow but it's all right this is a lot different than just putting numbers in a window
almost there too many conspiracy vids you don't want me conspiracy videos
okay i don't remember making me
oh oh oh because it said the 23 thing no that's just the it's just a scary gym carry number
nothing not even worth picking up attack power doubled for everyone
this is the one this is it let's see what's at the bottom of the ocean here skip skip
i'm gonna go through everybody again just go i got plenty of food i'll make sure before i go
into that i eat the melon whatever the hell i have what's funny roast chicken that's giant
turkey leg i'll take it
god damn it i gotta do it again let's go hurry up hurry up let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go damn i just like for wound my brain just i'm going i'm not going to opening
any that's worth it no sorry okay i'm not going to open any chest we're just gonna
are we good i think we're good everybody okay just narrow to a run through the whole level
nice pick consumption halved you know what that means
don't nothing come on all right now i just need to level up
all right i i'm not gonna lie i just like hard blinked three times i can't give up i'm almost
there oh don't kill me please i always got a million dollars i just gotta spend the million
all right now this is where i'm gonna level up
yeah oh i'll take it 25 i'll be level 25 at floor 25
almost 23 24
or
i thought that was a ham
well i leveled up
now run eight and a half hours and we're still fine this ain't even close to my like all-time
high stream got a long way to go my longest stream was like 13 hours or something this is like eight
and a half yeah now typically i sit somewhere between like six and seven and a half not today
simpson's hitting around that was it wasn't that 11
how long was simpson hit was it was that actually i thought it was that um lifeline game
so
stop floors are so huge look at how big this is this is massive this is so big break the record i
don't think i would even if i did i'm gonna do i'm gonna beat the debt even if i did that that i'm
assuming like another probably 45 minutes to an hour we're not gonna come even close to the record
here we go i think i'm gonna try to level up one more time here
probably worth it considering this is probably one of the last boss areas
for the death storyline i could be wrong i'm not even gonna attack the fire guys just guaranteed
death
oh what's this cutlet bowl i love chicken cutlets
they knew there's like my favorite food on earth and they're just taunting me with it now
i like cold chicken cutlets
i'm not even i don't think that's even a weird thing to say
cooked um you cook them you bread them you cook them you fry them up
and then you put them in the fridge and eat them cold like a sandwich
a little bit of mayonnaise a little bit of uh like swiss cheese maybe and i knew i didn't
want to touch any chest and this is the number one reason why this is the reason you're looking at
right now that's why i didn't want to even touch one what am i gonna eat my options are gonna be
pretty limited in like an hour or so no fire guys right all right just kill the pumpkin and
i can level up level up all right this is it i need to pay attention here because
i'm only gonna get one shot at this so this is it for the night two fire guys just avoid them
what if it blocks is in here this is the last shot until i've erased the debt
uh too much go around of course all right here we go it's double slime double slime
so
what the fuck was that
oh
oh don't get greedy here that would be a mistake
just in case
this is one
there's two and i got these lines hooray there's even more to go down here oh yeah
at least i get to keep everything i just want to see 26 to 30 all right well whatever i got debt to
pay i've seen this already i don't have much else to sell i need to go buy some stuff
okay that is tomorrow so i can i i got 32 000 book all right i got a ton of incredibly expensive
items uh i think we've already seen this i believe yeah we've already seen this actually maybe we
didn't all right time for bed bad financial decisions no those are gonna be good financial
decisions at about 20 minutes
oh news the price of sweets has increased the price of valuable things has normalized
all right crystals look at 28 grand i'm i'm gonna hold these until this you see what i'm saying
these are gonna be worth like 80 to 100 000 each let's put the snacks up here plenty of this stuff
all right what else we gotta move here place the stuff in here with uh fur balls i'm not going to
do this anymore uh i am done with that i don't i don't get time for that right now open the store
i might buy this yeah i'll buy somebody bought something there we go plus two grapes there you go
uh 3000 i can expand the shop again for the final stretch that's a pretty good necklace
yam i'll just be normal here back over 500k
i'll take it you have something warm uh-oh i think i do boots i guess i don't wait can i
give her the heater the cloth hat it's not even here where is it oh the heater is lost right
will you take the shoes i'll give you the hat yeah the nice warm hat level 20 come on
yes bigger shop let's go do it expansion 30 000 to expand let's go let me see the fusion though
rank one dagger this is all right hold on what about do anything rank two stuff unlocked
i can make some stuff wait a minute rank three treasure rank three food egg toast shark fins
and i can make rank three let's make this stuff though i have this stuff mermaid shoes
they're really expensive let's do the knight's helm again 9 000 let's also do this one more
thing i could do right rank one dagger 5200 this is too big oh man this is huge what happened to
my vending machine did you take my vending machine i was gonna say that was fucking thirty
thousand dollars two windows though pretty important sweets are still high let's get a
peach tin in the window get the honey in the window too i need money baked yam is that in the
way a dm maybe apple the apple teriyaki hurricane bow hold on to that perfume staff
silver gauntlet silver gauntlet all the really expensive stuff i'm not gonna sell
without the rope let's just get them out here just like a clothing store not selling that not
selling that put these up no get that off the windows uh i can't do it right now i have to
move this move tables i wish this was centered we do it again that's fine right there all right
hold on wait wait i got a lot of junk cherries double cherry and let's load up the the vending
can i turn it i can fit in there can i fit in there now
it's the sands oh fuck it i don't care they can just stay there just put the vending machine here
just it's fine there's nothing wrong with it open the store two treasures i'll pick them up in two
days i could use a weapon could you i don't want to give you the expensive one i'll give you the um
hurricane bow i would complain at the store non-stop well that's fine i i would i would say
okay thank you for your feedback sir got it no shit no no no i'll give you base price for it
you're fucking ruining my shit here i'll give you one no i'll give you just get out of here
get away from me your family heirloom is like peaches in a can why does everybody's fairly
suck grandpa's gonna buy the honey i like some clothes i got something for you
have a windbreaker sir six hundred bucks stamp it i am procuring this item for 4200 dollars
more sweets come on grandpa no i don't
know
the price of food has decreased the price of accessories has normalized i need
weapons to go up so that i can beat the game instantly look at this i got so many great items
just reopen the store i got it mermaid shoes anything here worth money top stone i'm gonna
put the book out i mean this is 30 that's a easy 30 to 40 000 right there this can stay out
anything in here yeah restock this with toothpicks
uh just whatever put this stuff in here too i don't even want it just free money reopen
two pieces of armor in three days yep i am looking for a snack you get class tomorrow
well go study i better be an economics class otherwise you you're not doing what you're
supposed to be doing all right one other straight up 10 grand this thing sucks you can just have it
i should put the thing in the vending machine what am i doing it starts at 8 a.m
all right this is where the game ends this is where we end 200 000 is coming out tonight
what's the what has to be one of the last ones i have 300 grand how much do i need
next week is it a million 800 000 600 000
i mean 200 000 might sound like not very much but it is a lot
so 50 dollars just came in from cyclops parker thank you for the 50 bucks this game is propaganda
thank you for the 50 dollars and five cents you went up a little bit there thank you though
really appreciate that the rusty daggers boom has ended today's dungeon index 70 whatever
all right here we go uh what's what is it it's 500 000 i can do it i've only got one more week
to make 500 grand i can i definitely can do this shit let's get the night let's get some weapons
out here not the expensive ones there's still stuff in there bring them in all i care about
his money somebody told me that even if you go back and like and get a bunch of items
at this level you might get reset again if we're like faced free i think i'm good i just can't buy
anything here we are no no no make it a no 1180 is fine it is the final payment and i
but i i can't purchase anything i just have to sell all my inventory and this is a scenario
where i will liquidate stuff if i have to wait he needs you wanted to armor oh don't worry i got
it thanks for the money buy blue shit i i did what do you think is out there i bought like three blue
items like six days ago these were look this was blue this was blue this was blue this was blue
i already did it all right tomorrow two treasures i'm gonna have to buy them yeah i gotta go buy two
treasures i know he told me i was not supposed to buy anything but i did no no more buying things
i'll get over there once i once a weapon surge happens i'll be good to go all right here we go
what's that doing out right now take it go sell candy apple i'll take it 50 percent really
oh 25 is safe i'm not supposed to be buying stuff i'm supposed to be buying things stop
selling me things i'm gonna i'll take it i need one day of weapons all right i can't fuck this up
come on seriously this game came out in 2007 yeah it's it's pretty good too it's really fun
you want a piece of armor i think i got some good stuff here yeah take the iron
how are we doing i got like six days i'm fine where's the person that comes in where's the
what happened to the double treasure tomorrow tomorrow two treasures i should get about 40 to 50
grand from this any two all right so tomorrow is i got one more day here let's get the iron up there
and give me if i don't get a surge of weapons very soon here i'm gonna have to start putting
this shit out no one's buying the book either that's fine come on any two books can i come
and pick them in two days oh yeah you can i'm taking that thing off the shelf
does this guy have like 60 000 though i'm taking the book off the shelf
okay for armor let's try to let's stay around like 120 that's a safe good amount anybody as
long as i do that okay 120 120 do a joke and delete your save that would not be a very funny
joke considering that would be a 18 hour long joke that would be an 18 to 20 hour long
joke two days in the making holy objects prices for fur balls are falling wait what do you mean
holy is it not holy objects what's a holy object and prices on uh candy apples out of there
no one wants to buy the bread they'll buy the cherries right swiss cheese is a holy object
i know i want to get the book off we're gonna do booze of the world and just eat it there are the
two let's put this up that looks good cloth up there common shield that's fine nice face here
all right uh let's go get in here that's exactly what i'm looking for yes it is 2200 to sell your
australian rocket launcher for 22 yams there we are i should be let me go around like 130 for this
back there back down to 120 i want to buy two clothes in three days
i'll take it all right where is my treasure person my daughter-in-law asked me to pick up a
night shell 22 i am less than 170 what 135 000 away just need one good day there it is
10 grand take it do you have the things i asked for the two treasures i do
this is gonna be a big one 25 000 25 000 50 60 000 dollars that's reasonable all right all right
all right just because i don't want to lose the game 52 000 it's in the bag price of precious
metals has decreased price of food has normalized the big big items are how much i got i got like
four days get this off how we doing on how we doing on cheap shit yeah more cheap shit i'll take
it all right all right okay okay all right all right everything's fine expensive stuff's going
off he's coming in for the book let's get a ham sandwich up there too oh the cutlet bowl who
cares yeah just i need it i need the money can i fill this let's buy uh roast chicken ham sandwich
in the window we're good here comes the big one i got some food i do yes i do i got a roast chicken
ham sandwich i got the cutlet right take this 10 000 somebody buy the bow somebody buy one of these
my grandmother treasured this sure she did fuck somebody buy something expensive
it looks good grandpa oh grandpa i i thought you i you're doing me real dirty here grandpa
bingo 30 grand i'm not gonna get greedy with this though let's do 35 000 i just need one or two more
of those and the debt is paid why would you pawn a half melted chocolate bar because you're insane
so close bring them in again let's go i'm not even putting a new inventory there let's go bring
them in do i have a weapon yep can you afford this oh all right we're fine we're fine he bought
it even if it was base price it doesn't matter i only need a little bit more there's the fishing
pole 120 you'll buy it i'm so close staff the super sandwich count down the clock
oh i have three four days to do it i got plenty of time
good morning good morning here so the final payment is due in a week it will be sizable i
recommend checking the pause menu in order to see how much you owe for this week can't you just tell
me now well are you quite sure you wish me to do that i'll just check on my own i think very good
please prepare yourself i hope i can actually pay this off okey-dokey price of long swords has
increased and accessories have normalized long swords just get some crystal swords up here
i know i'm not getting an increase from this but i gotta entice people
any more food i can put out here i'll put a beef bowl time to win game over i win i can relax for
the next four days you got something made out of metal uh-huh wait is this made out of crystals
does that count oh i came for the armor right does that count let's be safe here
i crossed it 500 000 hooray you do have the books i asked for yeah let's go way over here
just eat it and booze of the world
40 grand please 35 000 please oh he's gone your loss i i don't even need the money
can't get my weapons you want two crystal swords man oh take it 320 oh he's way overboard now i
got 600k good game so the final thing i'm gonna do i have money here's the last thing that i'm
gonna do i'm gonna try to get to the end of the dungeon as long as i'm not an idiot and don't blow
all my money i will have enough let's do let's try it let's see what the end of the dungeon is
never will do it tomorrow i'm so sad let's just try to sell the last little bits of stuff that i
have uh i'm gonna put the turkey leg up there roast turkey and we'll put uh peach two clothes
i want them in three days get out of my store i get to do that now i get to say get out of here
i'll take it i'll take it yeah that's pretty cool i'll take it what do you want for it
i'll give you 10 000 for it i'll give you 10 5 i'll give you 12 for it my wife wanted me to pick up
this helmet gave her 500 000 and turkey leg had a good placement i guess this is still game after
the last payment i know this i'm not gonna stream for another seven hours to do the rest of the
actual ending ending of this game i just said i wanted to pay the debt off
where you guys getting where you getting these vases this feels weird
why are there this many people with these these grandma faces off road they said poison
it's the grandma overpopulation crisis all right let's get to the end of the dungeon
as of tomorrow i got one more shot here let's just put some candy and some chocolate and
let's just load it up actually no no no no no no take this out
because i want to bring this to the dungeon but just put the fish in here
well put some chocolate in here put in some flooring no matter just don't put anything
in here put in like the toothpicks gunpowder do i have any other thing let's get them actually
the big swords and stuff up here might as well display them i have them look over here all right
come on in do a closing sale or you sell everything in them yeah i was gonna see if i could
sell everything at like 80 off i'm gonna do it i'm gonna do it how much money do i have
do you sell treasure here i'm looking for a very old vase
600k you gotta spend money to get it back let's see we gotta get that ocean wall i know i want
i need to have we'll see level 21 what do i get did you just pay for the ocean uh wall you may
have 150k day 33 the price of weapons has increased let's see let's see if i can
this is what i want to do just get the halberd up here after i sold everything i know right really
it's a pain in the ass all right i'm gonna go to the uh let's go let's see the end of that one
oh whatever just at least bring food i want to see the end attack power doubled for everyone
all right even if i die in here i just want to see the boss speed run can't believe i'm
keeping my promise of finishing the game today well i'm not really finishing the game as much as i am
uh getting to the end of the part that i want to get to the end at on screen
they're doing a lot of games i probably need to slow down here yeah i gotta slow down
so
am i gonna play this off stream uh probably
i think kim would think it was fun so we're gonna i'm gonna do a kim and jeremy stream this game but
not live
she'll be streaming it to me and then i get to be you guys i get to hang out and be you
yeah i'm just gonna be like in the bathroom she's gonna do a private like steam stream
don't blow up don't blow up don't blow up i'm gonna take like a four hour long dump and she's
gonna stream the game to me i need to heal i was trying to kill the little guy i
god how many avalanches can you have in a row
news movement speed increase for everyone oh this is gonna be bad and this is a bad idea
but i'm just gonna keep i'll level up on the next floor found it perfectly i feel like i'm
doing a mafisto run oh god i found it nice good i'm gonna level up
where did that come from
egg toast pumpkins give go to exp drop i can't believe that
okay don't die i swear
i might have to take an emergency cherry but i don't know if it's worth it
i'm so close to 27 yeah i'm gonna take an emergency cherry not ready yet i want to get i want i want
this these places are huge i at least know where i'm going
where did that come from running with the grass
knocked out cold
leather armor i've never really played the game this long i still haven't seen
leather armor 27 there it is let's get the hell out of here
boss time it's something wrong there's someone over there it looks like a girl a girl my age
a girl in a place like this i think she's crying she's perhaps lost yeah that's got to be it we need
to help her is this the lost girl this deep in a dungeon how could yeah this is the girl that's
been walking around in circles wait what yeah it is i'm supposed to reading don't come near me
hey what don't come any closer nasty human person what are you what are you human person
get away get away from me oh so she's she's turning red this girl i'm sure of it she's an elf
what no you mean to tell me those aren't apple slices on her head what i don't think we have time
to wonder let's fight her what's this cubit bullshit what's this bomber mansion i'm just going in
oh it's a puzzle one
where is she's in the corner
give me an asperger's jerry whoa where are you okay how the
watermelons give me the watermelon i need it i went what
there's too many people it's too many people it's too many fucking people everywhere
it's too late for this it's too late for this it's too late for this
oh i don't care i went no dude it's too late for this it's fucking almost 10 straight hours
of this shit i don't want to take anything i don't care pay my debt and get me the fuck out of here
that was ridiculous you're like 10 of those fox people throwing rocks at you the whole time
all right it's everyone just taking everything at base price can i sleep in the bed for two days
straight can i just sleep i did it just go back and i can just go in and out of town repeatedly
holy shit louis louis you're not actually going to buy this are you louis this is way out of your
budget he bought that on credit he just went down to bank of america and he got a loan to pay for
that hey i'm feeling generous today i'm what is that a boy you want to sell me a watermelon
how's your grandma doing by the way is grandma okay where did you get it from
oh i would love it everybody out the store's closed it's fair yeah two thousand percent increase
out of the store everybody out i'm going to bed nice okay good night just not going into the
dungeon and instantly dying i kind of want to just buy something for the crazy girl
the price of metal has increased who cares how long what day is it is it called out today
hmm i think i want to buy i'm stupid i'll take one what do we have here
this is the thing but they're super people with too much money this is what they actually do
let's go
oh i just fucking needed that thing oh my god you see what he did he just he just
yielded he just yielded that thing in the wall this guy's kind of cool oh he does an uppercut too
that's cool
we're surrounded
leave him was that the equivalent of snake snake snake good night i'm not joking i'm actually
fucking crying none of your jokes are funny your stream is making me cry what are you doing here
why are you doing this to yourself why are you doing this what's today oh we got one more day
i think my voice has changed no it hasn't i'm fine i just want to see what he does holy shit
you're the worst character i've ever seen what a shit character what a shitty character
good night good morning hey how are you well today's the final collection day it is
i've got to know if i close my eyes i can practically see our weeks of hard work stretching
up before me a lot sure has happened our hard work here adventures has been a heck of a month
but one final day work as hard as you possibly can regardless of how difficult the task may be
don't get lazy even if you believe you're ready i won't let's get to work everything is free today
okay what do you i had an order but you weren't around how much is that well sir you came in a
great day you came to everything is free day how much is this usually it's fifteen thousand dollars
holy shit this person's having a fucking mind the nightmare ends hold on hold on look at this
we're doing a fucking satan number hey what just happened i'm interested in buying no no no no i
need okay wait wait hold on 667 667 is there anyone to do with 667 542 minus 666666
876 i'd like to buy that for 876 dollars please everybody watching this stream sorry
i don't have weapons oh you have one of these shit i have to sell it for a dollar
nothing scary about 666 667 i'm gonna buy it finally a pot stand and i'm gonna buy i'm gonna
spend way too much money on this what's what a thousand a thousand dollars in a thousand percent
everybody can breathe thanks for all your help you did so good welcome to the end of the stream
it only took us about 10 hours to get here paying off the final debt five hundred thousand dollars
and with 142k left over congratulations receipt with this payment your father's loan has been
repaid in full you've worked very hard received well done so it's all over right the payments and
the weirdness and stuff it's kind of unreal somehow like it's over how's that possible
indeed may i have a moment could we step outside perhaps i don't like this oh the evening breeze
feels wonderful by the way i lied this is where the i lied comes up it does i like the city at
night like this looking down from the hill only five weeks have passed since i arrived here
quite a bit has happened despite the short amount of time i'll say i never thought i'd have to open
an item shop to help pay off one of my papa's bad loans when i arrived here i expected no i
deserved nothing but your scorn and hatred and you always trusted me from the day we met to
this very moment without questioning me once i do not understand it even now how are you capable
of such casual trust how can you be so ceaselessly positive about things um well um i don't know i
really understand i don't know anything but to tell you the truth when you told me that i had
to open an item store to pay off the debt all i could think was that sounds like a lot of fun
i met people i never could have dreamed of meeting when i was alone i got to run a shop i wanted
adventures i got to experience everything i never thought i'd see it was an exciting just
waking up in the morning wondering what happened more important than anything i got to meet you
tear i'm happier about that than i am about anything else you say such embarrassing things
oh i didn't mean to make you blush tear no no not at all i'm not blushing i know some scary
stuff happened too but i'm glad i got to experience with you tear move the cursor
i imagine you go all right i would laugh my ass off if you went to like infinity war
it's like a fucking cursor on the screen i know what it's like to lose and you're just freaking
out why is that up there somebody please help take it off and so my days of paying back endless debt
ended thank you i win i did it and all i had to do is rewind time and buy like a hundred thousand
dollars worth of stuff like seven hours ago i'm not gonna sing with this on the candlestick
papa gave to me what where's papa i thought we were gonna get a papa comes back and he's like
all like dirty and covered in like dragon shit i'm back is it gonna be an african look there's
gonna be a fucking there's gonna be a mouse on the screen infinity war after credit scene
dad's gonna open the door and be like why what have you done and we have to keep going
why would you sit on a candlestick what are you talking about sit on a candlestick and let it
sparkle with light from the smiles of everyone why the other people here why are the bunch of
people watching me stick a candlestick what what's going on here what i'd missed that
i don't want to sit on a candle i'm skipping that's translation for you sit on a can i'm not
sitting on a candlestick no stop this nonsense stop this i'm cutting i'm putting the end here
on this i put the sandwich mama oh no no that's the sandwich mama there's no there's gonna be a
comma there i'm gonna i put the sandwich mama no that would be the crisper walking in one of my
apron pockets as i head out even old magicians with gray hats and arch devils will do anything
to get their items back don't do it you're about to take the full brunt of a star
don't don't thorn don't sit on the candle he's insane he's about to take the full brunt of a
candlestick get it off the fucking screen i'm sorry i got it some of you guys are fucking crazy i
love it hey oh shh hey tier you haven't forgotten anything have you i have not i did not arrive
with all that much so all right well then i know thank you fair farewell recede be the best shop
keeper you possibly can be tier what something inside the barrel it's gonna be dad he's in
ledgers what are they for those yeah you see um stock books financial statements profit reports
asset ledgers accounts payable and receivable these uh m-e-r-d-e i said it over and over and over
make sure to keep these books straight receipt they're all blank i was totally gonna do them
right well why do today what you can do tomorrow and then tomorrow and oh well i ended up not doing
them at all i don't have any excuses
fucking scene it's like i well we need to go back take inventory and make sure nobody's
plundering our account tier what are you well it's perfectly clear that if i leave you here alone
you would end up crushed like an insect the moment i leave i tend to keep you working just as hard
mind you let's go back oh my god and so our days of running an item shop continue
oh i got the true card what that we're out what are we doing so you managed to pay off the loan
shark fairies debt have you well i suppose some congratulations are in order still i would expect
any common proletarian to have the holy basic skills needed to get this far and now for part
two the elegant graceful tale of alouette yeah like egs is interested in making that happen
what did you just say calm down they say you don't need to get this worked up over it more
importantly please just do the explanation right here's this one i don't see why of all the people
have to look here misters fine fine fine if i must okay well then without further ado allow me to
explain post game content or enjoying the game after beating it all right that's better to start
with if you load the game you're about to save you will begin endless mode where you can play
as long as you like without having to worry about any debts you may work as a common shopkeeper to
your heart's delight and you know there just might maybe possibly be some items and dungeons
and stuff that you haven't seen before in addition you have now unlocked new game plus and the
survival mode you start over again a new game plus but you choose a save and keep all the items
and levels from that save remember that you've got to pay off the debt from the beginning again
though survival mode is a nasty business where you keep paying back debt every single week until
it overwhelms you how long can you last against weeks of six digit payments i wonder especially
in that ridiculous survival hell mode you might have picked up a true card from an adventurer
you only get that from an adventurer you're really close to but if you have that you can hire them
from the start in these new modes anyway that should about do it really a proper player won't
be satisfied beating the game just once at the very least aim to fill out the entire item encyclopedia
pardon me see you guys enjoy the rest of the game okay let's go let's just make a new save
save okay how many do overwrite no how do i get out of this i made it okay well that's a lot
let me see items encyclopedia cool i got all swords all the daggers all the staves all the bows
all the spears all the gloves oh these are who knows but these are 29 completion rate oh my god
and then we were almost at exactly 10 hours
thor well that's gonna be it that was a lot of fun
candlestick no thor the candle i don't want to sit on it i'm not i'm done with talking about
i'm never gonna i'm not even gonna lie i'm never gonna talk about i'm not gonna say the word ever
again all right i'll see you guys later we have bits to go through but not very much i'm gonna go
through these very quickly thank you if you just stuck around if you're just getting here i mean
it's very late i am not going to be live tomorrow and i have some things to do with the carnival
stream so you will see me again you'll see my face again on thursday so i got some work to do
i'll see you guys in a couple days so he can't leave uh but i'm gonna i'm going through these
quick so there's gonna be some progress done on the carnival stream so this just got so much
louder for some reason why is it so loud yeah quit again what just happened did i quit out
everything no all right let's do these bits let's scroll back remember i'm gonna do these
rapid fire you're gonna see them rapidly we had uci kick hey germa i have a vid that i made
with one of your sims vids uh i know that you're not much of a jojo fan but some of the chat
members might get a kick out of it let me take a look at this we're going quick here hold on
now this is like an adam sandler with a this is an adam sandler video
let's see
hey are you uh that's what it is show i can't show my computer's broken i can't put it on
guys my control is broken i can't put it on it's just the scene part one of the 69
it's too long the 69 parts here there you go during the light about bits well he said i'm
not much of a jojo fan but some of the people in chat might like it so that's why i linked it
but thank you you see for the five dollars and that was the dio dio volo versus jojo i don't even
know if i should say that out loud because that might be i don't know what that is get the mouse
cursor off screen right i don't know it's a jojoke oh my god taeyon thanks for the 250 just take my
money greedy streamer please don't hurt me i'm not that's thank you for the 250 uh cold girl fever
thanks for the 15 i'm a high school history teacher i teach so that hopefully the world
doesn't continue to turn out selfish little uh maggots thanks for the streams they always
help me unwind during the school year thank you to the 15 cold girl fever if i can help you online
if we can help you online here hopefully those kids aren't uh aren't too crazy this year
thank you the 15 very much appreciate it thank you gnarly for the five dollars hey germa um this
is jackson don don a from the baskin robbins marketing team thanks for upholding your end
of the sponsorship deal we saw a total increase of 233 percent on bombs bacon cookie sales here's
your pay please contact us for any further sponsorship deals if i took a five dollar
sponsorship that would be like embarrassing five dollars that's what i'm worth
that is less than what it costs for one of their ice creams so i would at least want one large
ice cream but thank you uh gnarly the absolute not real fit message here thanks for the five bucks
uh s10w update thanks for the 250 hey how's it going germa also known as germa 95 on the video
platform such as twitch and youtube it's me so slow update oh it's not s10w update it's slow
update back at it again to say that this stream really resonates with me as i'm also in debt
with the mafia and they're going to break my fingers anyways peace and love good luck with
life good luck with that hopefully that guy you get you get that sorted out thank you thank you
ali melichroic for the five dollars no message thank you ali dr clay thanks for the 250
you say i found it what did you find i found it you found it you did find it yes you did
everyone thought i was insane brought to you by alex max do-it-yourself chemistry set
it's sunday 31st and it's nickelodeon's rabbit rabbit day well you did it you made it through
another month today prepare for next month before you go to bed tonight remind yourself that the
very first thing out of your mouth tomorrow morning should be rabbit rabbit they say it'll
bring you good luck for the whole month rabbit rabbit tomorrow is there any amount of times
where we can count how many times i've just been right about something and chat things up wrong and
then we just forget it happened thank you dr clay for the 250 appreciate it thank you pink boo
for the five dollars join the cult of john the anti-jex and prosper rid this world of high iq
plays and skill and make everyone mediocre at video games thank you pink boo with the five
dollars thank you pancat for the 28 dollars 28 bucks almost 30 dollars here from pancat thank
you so much hey it's my birthday and i wanted to give you some of my birthday money well happy
birthday keep that keep your birthday money make sure you have enough birthday money for you it's
not it's not my birthday it's your birthday i appreciate it nonetheless though thank you for
the 28 bucks it's a lot thank you happy birthday pancat hope you had a good one
airless thanks for the 250 germans saturn thank you midveid thanks for the 15 dollars 15 bucks
from midview seriously thanks a lot for your streams dog been going through a really stressful
week this has been putting my mind at ease pleasures all over here thank you for coming
out here thanks for the 15 dollars hopefully your week gets better well hopefully because i mean it's
sunday right technically monday hopefully you this new week uh is better for you thank you so much
for the 15 bucks much love to you thanks a lot take care of yourself uh he worked work he worked
work thanks for the five dollars germa play halo on pc please thank you probably i don't see why
not probably not tomorrow not the next day probably no on legendary mode just kidding
delete that demons v thanks for the five dollars thank you for the late stream
they happen sometimes i do a 10 nine to 10 hour stream
once every month or so once every couple dozen streams i usually go for at least like eight
hours i'm not even intentional either it just kind of happens i thank you uh demon speed
don't they're cute linger thanks for the five dollars hey germa just recently got a piano
and have so far taught myself the patties pub theme from always sunny and your song by elton john
tell me which song i should learn next and i'll do it yes i'm almost at the 5000 bit mark thank
you for that the next song you should learn is a bethoven second symphony thank you for the five
dollars oh no you've doomed them thank you the five dollars grats on the piano pianos are cool
but they're just huge having a piano in my opinion is like having a pool it's big it just gets in the
way and nobody wants to clean it it's like having a car in your living room it's a big music pool
they are really cool though especially some of the really nice ones uh again thank you joel joel
came in with a raid a few hours ago we were uh getting to the end there thank you so much joel
and everybody anybody that's still here from joel's channel uh thanks for staying up late
or getting up early globs you thanks for the five dollars and 25 cents hello germa long-time
youtube viewer here on stream for the first time any advice for someone that wants to start
streaming uh i'm a mute that i can only stream for 30 minutes a day i hate video games and i'm
extremely camera shy so how should i get into streaming hmm well open surprise eggs
go into that market completely you know how much those youtube videos make
people opening up surprise eggs with spider-man and shit just do it on stream
but thank you glossy for the five dollars 25 cents you can probably get that done
in 30 minutes let's get the credits rolling there's a long one so i'm assuming there's
going to be a long list let me take a look and see just how many yeah there's gonna be
there's gonna be fairly quick it's gonna be fairly quick it's gonna be fairly quick it's
gonna be pretty good yeah pretty normal pretty fairly quick still have a little bit more to go
we have uh thank you thank you nay for the five dollars not to be confused with
wreck a tear which is pronounced wreck a tear as opposed to wreck a tear like the first
wreck a tear you lost me but thank you for five dollars cyclops gave 50 dollars earlier as well
thank you cyclops we caught it but i want to catch it again because it was the last one that really
came through here demons v thanks for the four dollars please stream more you distract me from
the pain hopefully that is a joke if it's not then i'm sorry to hear that you're going through
something please use the necessary resources you can find to get on top of that but thank you for
the four dollars and take care of yourself you're the most important person in your damn universe
take care of you as well as you can wiki this thanks for the five dollars candlestick i mean
like give me a breakdown i look down and it's talking about how i'm like oh and i
people are like smiling i have a candle and i'm sitting on like i'm talking about me that was me
sitting there and now you got me all fucked up again and then somebody said thor and then
thor has it and then that's look i got a 10-hour stream jack me an envelope jack me quick
mario ground pound the i don't know why that came out all right it's been fun i'll see you
guys in a couple days have a wonderful rest of your evening or your morning good morning
those of you that just woke up
uh connor thank you connor for the 10 dollars connor q
germa i'm gonna need you to sit on that candlestick please it's important yep
uh thank you thank you clueless sniper for the 250 hey germa last stream you said you would do a
biannime voice if you don't do it today i'll be mildly disappointed thank you uh spicy pepe for
the 250 hey germa today's stream was very fun thanks for always putting on an entertaining show
for us to enjoy you always manage to make me laugh whenever i watch these streams and make
me feel pretty happy if the day's going bad you are an extremely talented person and i'm very
excited to see what the carnival stream brings germa heart one question before i go
what do you think you'll be playing over the next few streams have a great night
um next week because i'll be off to well not next week it is next week already thursday i'm
probably gonna do thursday friday uh or thursday friday saturday we'll see i'll probably we'll do
i'm gonna do two days in a row three days in a row but because of the carnival thing what i'm
trying to do is do like two days two days two days two days like two days three days three days
two days we'll probably go back to you know i'm sitting like two days on two days off like three
days three days two days two days two days on two days off two days on two days off two days on
three days off three days off three days on no no not six days off not six days off in a row not
three days off three days off three days off i mean i wouldn't be here for like two weeks
week you know what i'm talking about look i gotta eat food okay i haven't eaten it's been like 10
and a half hours sam and max is probably gonna come back next weekend maybe like on saturday
we'll start season three but for thursday and friday for friday or whatever it is i'm not so
sure i know i have like a kind of a backlog of things that i want to try but i can't wait for
the condo stream either it should be a lot of fun uh ever since kind of announcing it and talking
about it a little bit i've since wanted to kind of reel it in because i'd rather really start
talking about it when there's dates involved and when there's actual tangible things to talk about
you know and somebody is what what what what are we linking here this is the me doing the
anime voice you said you would do a the anime voice if you don't do it today i'll be mildly
disappointed pretty good all right i'll see you guys on thursday thank you for joining me
take care everybody i will do the stream legends because it's been enough time that
gives a lot of fun though i'm very much enjoyed that the last two days did not think i was gonna
play that game for like eight 19 hours but i did see you guys on thursday have a great beginning
of your week and that game is also i believe on sale for like four dollars or five dollars right
now so this seems to be a lot of content here comes the stream legends if you have it open
there it goes take care guys see you soon ta ta