Hey, what's happening everybody? How you doing? Hope your day is good. Hope your day has been great good
It better be great. My name is German. Nice to see you. Nice to meet you. Gonna be hanging out
Gonna be talking about this new game that's been around. I'm sure you've heard of it. Sure. You've seen it
Maybe it's overwatch. I got into the closed beta. This is closed beta footage
I'm sorry. There hasn't been very much content on the channel this last couple of weeks
But if you can't tell I've been kind of sick and it's been one of those sicknesses
That's a relapsing sickness where you get better and then you get worse and you get better than you get worse
I don't know
I don't know what like mad scientist gave me like a poison potion
But I don't know what the fuck happened with that being said let's go on and get started here
So this is Lucio
This is one of the support characters and he's probably my favorite character to play as it stands right now in the beta
And that's because of how Blizzard has handled support in this game
every time I ever play a game that has support characters, whether it be a
MOBA or
First-person action game or something multiplayer anytime support is an available option
Nobody really wants to play it right like you get those people that like love to play support
I love playing support right like engineer is my favorite class in TF2. I love playing the healers
I love playing the support characters when I played World of Warcraft all of my characters were pretty much tank or healer
I didn't have very many damage-dealing mains or alternative like that
But in the grand scheme of things people shy away from support mostly because of why?
Because it's boring because you only do one thing and it's not that fun
You kind of somebody has to do it
it's just a question of who's gonna do it right and you get to that point where like four people have something picked and
There's no support or there's no tank and you just pick it because god damn it
Somebody's got to do it. So it might as well be me. That's not really how it worked in overwatch
I think Blizzard if they one thing could be said about Blizzard right now
They've done a fantastic job of making sure that the support characters are fun to play and do more than one thing
Because how it usually works is you're the stand behind you guy or hey, I'm in a corner looking at health bars
Does anybody need a buff every now and then that's what happens in most games now
There is mercy mercy is that kind of character in this game. She has a heal beam
She has a damage boost beam, but she's still fun to play and the other three quote support characters play
Wildly different than that. This is Lucio Lucio is a healer support character, but as you've been watching I'm skiing around
I'm skating around putting up the speed boost getting some kills jumping around wrapping around back to my teammates
You're not glued to somebody there is no standardized
Obligation to a certain character when you're playing somebody like Lucio. I have to move around
It's just how active you get to be like look at this. It's like a big fat guy down
I just punched this fat guy right in his stomach. See how active that was
See how active I just got to be and the best part about playing Lucio is all of his support stuff is AoE
I can switch between heal or speed so right now anybody that's standing even remotely near me gets a heal over time
I can boost it up with one of the abilities or I can switch over and make everybody run faster right now
Everybody's running fast and I just fucking compression blast that dude off the cliff
You got a compression blast too, but I got a long way to go. There's a lot more playing
There's a lot more testing to do. I've got a lot of shit that I want to be playing in this game
I did so awesome. It's been a long time guys
It's been a really long time since I've cared about the numbers the damage numbers in a certain video game or what?
How fast am I moving as this particular character like it?
It's been a long time and it's really cool to see that
I'm actually enjoying myself and any complaints that I have so far about the game are
Very aesthetic if I could check a box to lower the amount of the giant explosions and it muzzle
Flashes and stuff because they are kind of ridiculous
Especially if there's like three people doing their ultimate at the same time
You kind of have no idea what the hell is going on and maybe a couple of things in the UI that I'd like to
See change some of the indicators are way too big
I wish you could scale them down
Especially if you're a healer some of that stuff could be shrunken by it like 30% and I would be totally okay with it
But besides that it's very very good
I don't have very much to say that's bad about the game besides that so far and look I only have
15 or so 16 hours in the game and I'm sure there'll be plenty of amazing things
I'd love to talk about and I'm sure there'll be plenty of things
I'd like to talk about that aren't so amazing, but that's what a beta is for that's a closed beta
I mean, that's how you figure that stuff out, and I'm sure they will but that's gonna wrap it up here guys
Just a quick video
Number one just saying that the game's great. I've been playing overwatch and number two that I've been sick
And I'm sorry that hasn't been very much content on this channel
I've been working on like three videos that I just have not been able to finish
But anyways, I'm probably streaming right now if you go to my twitch
I'm gonna be streaming this game a lot so come to the stream go to star stream
I'll put both of our stream links in the description at any given moment this next at least couple of weeks
You'll probably see us streaming this game so come say hello come hang out and yeah, take care everybody
Thanks for watching. I'll see you all soon good