What's up?
I'm seeing a lot of people in chat that we're maybe in a betting mood, potentially, one of the mods told me.
If you don't know, you're just getting here.
Today is a very, very, very special day for a lot of people here.
Today is the day that I beat Breath of the Wild.
Wow, didn't think you're going to hear that on a Sunday afternoon, did you?
It's been about four months.
I think the last time was, what, May, April?
So I haven't played in four months.
I got one, it's been five months, whatever, it's been more like six.
Well, all right, here's the thing.
I've got one more divine beast.
Kill that bastard.
Wait, no, you don't kill them.
It's been like five months since I played this.
We become friends.
I'm not going to, we're not killing any, any divine beasts.
I have, I forgot that that was, okay.
I forgot everything.
Apparently.
We're going to team up with the divine beast to take out Ganon.
That's better.
But, uh, I asked how long this would take to do.
If I beat the divine beast, I become friends with the divine beast.
Then go right to Ganon.
Could I do it in three hours?
And that is what you'll be betting on today.
We'll see if I can do it.
Can I beat this game in under three hours, three hours in one second?
Absolutely not.
I'm seeing a few absolutely not.
No way.
Absolutely not.
Well, I'm going to try anyways.
How long are you going to be live for?
I don't know.
That's a good question.
All right.
So if I don't get there and three hours, this, this is the last time I'm ever
going to play Breath of the Wild.
So it's either I beat the game or not.
I have to, I'm, I'm confident I'll do it.
No chance.
That's kind of, okay.
What if I get to the front door of Ganon and I aim the magical holy bow and I'm
about to shoot the first shot and it's three hours goes up and I exit the game.
That'd be kind of funny.
Yeah.
But after this, I'm going to play Breath of the Wild for at most three hours.
Then we're going to move on.
I want to play Punch Out.
I want to play Goldeneye too.
But Goldeneye, they, they re-released it.
They made it HD.
Well, they didn't make it HD graphics, but they made it upscaled it, right?
I want to play a bunch of Switch stuff.
It's plugged in.
It's being captured.
So I'm going to do it.
So what do you think?
Should we, should we go for a countdown?
Wait, I need to get ready first.
It's got a huge raid right at the very beginning.
Holy shit.
Thanks for the raid.
There's over 2000 people.
What's up?
Is it K4?
Thanks for the raid K4.
Welcome everybody.
It's a lot of people.
We're going to be playing Breath of the Wild.
Face cam off.
No, no face cam.
Put a timer up.
Yeah.
Well, don't worry.
We'll, we'll make sure we're very honest about this.
Face cam or riot.
Well, ain't going to be one.
So that's too bad.
Why does it have to be three hours?
Exactly.
Cause I think that's in pre-stream chat.
That's where we kind of all were like, well, some people said it's you.
So it'll be five hours, but I disagree.
I think I can do it in three and I'm not rushing to do this, but I, I kind of am
because I, I keep putting off Breath of the Wild.
I keep saying, I'm going to play it.
I keep saying, Hey, I'll do it.
I'll do it.
I just don't do it.
I have to get myself a timer.
Plus that's kind of fun.
I'm going to fall off the horse a hundred times in three hours.
And I'm not gonna make any progress.
So don't worry.
Those of you that are betting, if I can see, all right.
Is it just see the end credits in three hours?
He hates this game.
No, I did.
I don't.
I love Breath of the Wild.
Zelda.
Let's go.
Yeah.
It's so much fun.
I'm going to give myself a three hour timer to finish this game and I'm
never playing it ever again.
Oh, Nintendo.
Let's go.
Well, I give myself a timer.
I think it's just fun.
You guys ready?
It's the last hit on the final boss.
Okay.
So by the way, today is the backseat dream.
You just, I don't want to name emote only ever.
I'm going to be looking for solutions.
I'm going to be asking for help.
I'm going to say, Hey, what's the best product I could use right now.
And I expect help.
I expect to get through this.
We're looking for the best products.
We're looking for the best, um, equipment.
That's cheating.
That's fine.
All right.
Are we ready?
Are we ready to play this?
So I get five minutes of streamer.
Learn how to play the whole game again.
Cause you haven't played it in six months.
I get five minutes to run around in a circle and jump.
You understand?
Okay.
I get that.
So that timer, I'm just going to run around in a circle for a few minutes.
No emote.
Only all backseating.
Yeah.
You can backseat as much as you want.
Hey, let me remember how to play.
That's jump.
We're going.
All right.
That's jump.
Isn't there a triple jump?
Can't you go like, I'm just trying to make as much people leave as possible
in the first 10 minutes.
I'm just trying to get as many people to leave as possible in the first five
minutes.
You said the same thing twice.
No, that way that's in tears of the kingdom.
All right.
The timer does not start until I say it does.
Okay.
And we're going to keep, I have a, I'm keeping track over here.
All right.
That's, this is sprint slash.
Okay.
I got, I got the master sword last time.
This thing is unbreakable, right?
Let's put a timer on screen.
I don't want to put a timer on screen because I feel like it'll ruin the VOD.
They're okay.
Every VOD before this did not have a three hour timer.
And the people that watch the VODs and they're just trying to hang out and just
chill.
Like, Oh, cool.
What's this timer on the screen?
I want to watch the streamer play breath of the wild.
What is this?
No, he ruined it.
He ruined the playthrough.
You ruined the playthrough.
I don't want to hear that.
All right.
That's how you, right.
You got, I got the freezing.
I got the camera.
I've got the magnet.
That's a jump swing.
The master sword can't be broken.
Thank God we finally got it.
All right.
So this is the thunder blade.
So if this is going to be truly the last breath of the wild stream, you better
believe I'm going to be throwing these people.
Like I'm going to be, this is awesome.
I'm so happy about this.
Me saying this is the last time I'm going to play play breath of the wild.
I now the whole, everything is now open.
Now I'm just going to use this weapon because I feel like it.
That's so awesome.
I'm so happy about that.
I don't even care.
I don't even know what this is.
I'm going to use it now.
I finally am.
I'm going to, I'm allowed to use all these weapons because I know it's the
last time I'm going to play it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
The timer started.
Wait, the timer.
Oh, I, I, uh, timer started.
Hold on.
All right.
I know how to jump.
Right, right, right.
Here's what I, here's what I need to do.
Oh, wait, let me, let me turn this in first.
It's a question.
No, no.
Three, two, one.
Go.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
435.
Let me turn this down.
No, I have to turn this question.
A lot of people don't think I'm going to do this.
I cannot wait until you all get this completely wrong.
Skip the dialogue.
No, it hasn't officially started yet.
You want a different outcome this time?
Okay.
All right.
I think we have a cut scene here.
I am not going to fail.
Okay.
How strange.
Please beat it.
Please.
I give you five extra minutes.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
No, we're good.
We're good.
You wore that champion's tunic every day.
I feel as though I've been transported in time.
Link, our princess, you must rescue her.
All right.
So where's the, what, what is this a quest for?
I'm really glad you gave me that extra time.
You may not remember your last meeting with Ganon, but it did not end well for you.
Why, why is this a quest?
Upstairs?
Backseat as much as possible, by the way.
The shit that would get you banned in other chats of just like telling me where to go.
Oh, I want it all.
I want to see.
I want to, uh, anything that you would, we're talking backseat is open.
The floodgates are completely open.
I want exact coordinates to every single encounter.
What is this quest?
Captured memories.
What is this?
Princess Zelda left behind an album with 12 pictures in it.
Traveling to the places shown in these pictures may help you regain your memories.
What?
Why is this?
Oh, but that was, that was like set as a destination.
I just wasted five minutes.
Why was that set as a destination?
Okay.
Well, what time is it?
All right.
We didn't even start it yet.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, go back.
Go back.
Ignore everything, but go to the top left of the map.
Ignore this.
Where's all right.
Where's the beast?
Where's the, I don't, the next beast is not on the map.
Where is the beast?
Top left.
All right.
Like up here.
Fastest way to get there.
Ignore the beast.
Go right to get it.
No, I want to, I want to, I got three hours.
I'm the timer hadn't even started yet.
Go West.
Central tower.
Right here.
Let's go.
All right.
Let the, uh, timer starts now.
Exactly.
Wait.
Yeah.
And exactly three hours from right now, I plan on seeing the ending credits of
breath of the wild and exactly three hours.
Exactly.
Try to use the horse.
I actually should get a horse because Frank too is somewhere.
I didn't cook any food.
All right.
That's where I need to end up.
Right.
So we need to go this way.
Stable right here.
Stable right there.
I want the horse.
He's got another raid.
It's like two huge raids back to back.
Activate the divine beast quest, dude.
I don't have the divine beast quest on.
All right.
That was P S P S P one G P S P big.
I don't read.
I can't read names ever.
I think that's that what it is.
It looks different over here.
I fucked up big time.
Didn't I?
I, it, it says it looks like, okay.
PS one PSP one G.
I'm so sorry.
That's not how your name is said.
That's what it does.
It looks like over here on my other screen.
I'm really sorry, but you're fucking awesome for rating me.
Appreciate it.
Stop wasting time.
I'm not wasting time.
I'm apologizing.
What a PR disaster.
What I did.
Oh, I'm never going to do this in three hours.
I hope you bet accordingly.
God damn it.
Those are two huge rates though.
Thanks.
Welcome everybody.
All right, let's go.
We want Frank.
Where's Frank two.
On at this point, I don't know, but I need a horse and we're taking Frank.
Frank two died.
Unfortunate.
God damn it.
Frank two soft retired.
All right.
Let me turn the quest on.
Okay.
Divine beast captured.
Remember, right?
Free the divine beasts.
It's all the way up here.
Why am I going this way?
Why would I not go over here?
Oh, I wanted the horse.
Wait, I can go this way.
Should I go up the road?
Just follow the road.
Trust.
Go, go, go this way.
I need to cook food too.
Trust, trust, trust.
It's an ancient arrows.
Um, I'm just going, that's not the button to ride the horse.
I think that's the first time I've seen two just big raids back to back though.
Honestly, like all jokes aside.
Thanks guys.
Where would I start at the stream?
This is the easiest divine beast.
You definitely can do it.
All right.
Well, I also want to, I don't want to miss any shrines either.
That's my favorite part of the whole game.
There is no way you do this in three hours.
Oh, I hope you bet for it.
Shrines, no shot three hours.
I can do it.
Guys, it hasn't even been two minutes.
I've got a lot of those minutes lined up in a row.
And I have the horse this time.
The first time in the playthrough, I've actually used the horse more than five
minutes.
People right now are pissed that I actually went to the stable.
He's been running the entire game.
It's this time that he now uses the horse.
All right.
So where is it?
It's so far away.
Hell is that?
Look at the sky.
I crashed into a tree.
All right.
There's nothing here.
I'm looking for a tower.
Honestly, is there no tower like right here?
Hold on.
It has to be.
This is a huge mountain.
Follow the road.
That fox did a back flip.
Oh my God.
I didn't mean to.
Hold on a second.
You don't think I'm going to stop to get this stuff?
This stuff is still worth it.
I need to make food as well.
I'm going to stop at then whatever the next town is.
You laughed at him.
That was a crazy scenario.
I didn't mean to.
All right.
Uh, give me a tower.
Maybe I should just get a pie and just look through that.
I've not, I've seen this thing before.
Should I get a picture of this thing?
I'm going to take a picture of that.
Oh, I think I already did take a picture of this.
I can get a much better picture though.
Nice.
Wait, this one's better.
No, get it.
No, it has to be like touching his face.
Whatever.
Game sucks.
These are the easiest bits I ever made.
Wait, what do you mean?
Wait, did the, you can't bet bits and get bits back.
You mean channel point?
I can't move.
Hold on.
What's wrong with the horse?
Why is the horse not moving?
Okay.
I don't know what's going on, but I can't go that way.
All right.
You come to me then.
There we go.
How much time is left?
Hey, 10 minutes.
Okay.
I need help.
I need back seaters right now.
Help.
Where do I go?
I don't see a tower anywhere.
I don't do the point thing again.
I can't whatever.
I'm going that way.
Should have bet if you're going to beat this divine beast in three hours.
I've, I just saw the divine beast.
It's right there.
I found it.
And this is, I'm good.
Settle down.
You know what?
Why did I bring the horse?
I'm like, I, I like to glide.
What, what was the point of the horse?
I should have just glid.
Is that a word?
I glid.
That's correct.
Right?
Glowed.
Glided?
I glided over there.
I glid over there.
How'd you get over there?
Well, I had to glide.
I glid.
Wait, am I going?
Okay.
I'm going the right way now.
I want to get a big picture of everything over here.
Cause there's not a tower like here anywhere.
Can I stand up here?
Yes, I can.
I'm going for the glide.
Forget about the horse.
I can cover three miles with the glider in a 10th of the time it takes to ride
with the horse and I get special mushroom.
Okay.
To get there.
I'm good.
I want a big picture of everything going on here.
Trine right there.
I'm going to ignore it for now.
What else is up here?
Okay.
Tower that way.
Tower over there.
I think that's the closest tower for sure.
You should get the shrine so you can travel.
Now that person is smart and I know I get it.
That's a good idea, but I know why you just told me to do that because you're
trying to burn like 40 minutes in that shrine and uh, I'm going to have to say
no, can I get the horse over here?
At least, uh, no.
All right.
So if I head that way, this is, that's definitely going the right direction.
It is.
All right.
Let's start the glider.
I'm covering miles right now.
To go over that, uh, the bridge.
No, I'm not, I, I'll get the shrine because it is fast travel, but let me
just take a look what's in there.
I'm not going to do it.
I just want to look.
Okay.
Let's get to the fast travel.
All right.
There's one right there too.
Which one is closer?
Probably that one.
That's also in the right direction.
So we're going that way.
You get sidetracked so easily.
I think that's, isn't that the whole point of Breath of the Wild though?
Isn't Breath of the Wild the game to get sidetracked in, out of all games?
All right.
It's activated.
I don't want to even see what's in there.
Is there one?
There's one over there too.
Let me mark that.
I don't know how to do that.
Uh, all right.
I'm going to mark it as a treasure chest.
Is that, is that even correct?
Bro, that's not even the right way.
I'm going to fuck myself over so bad if that's still here.
It's here.
I don't even know if I placed it.
All right.
I placed the other markers five months ago.
I don't even know what they're for.
They're probably really important though.
I placed that, I placed that red marker back in, I want to say April or March of
this year or something.
Take all my clothes off quick!
I'm going to get struck by lightning.
What do I do?
How do I take this off?
Unequip?
How do I just unequip something?
Okay.
See?
That was right there.
Okay.
I think I'm good.
I'm going to head that way and we're going to get to the tower.
Uh, wait, hold on.
There's something here.
Stables.
Oh, hell yeah.
The fuck?
Oh my God.
Can this hit them?
Wait, I can cook.
I'm not going to take very much time doing this.
I know this is people are like, Oh my God, dude, this is such shit food.
It doesn't matter.
I just need to eat it.
Salt and jalapenos, whatever this is.
Okay.
Do I have any meat or anything?
Mushroom.
What, okay.
What is the thing I have to be worried about up here?
Is it electricity?
Is it wind?
Is it fire?
What's the thing?
It's cold, cold areas.
It's cold.
Okay.
I need to get cold resistant stuff.
So this is good for cold.
So let's go with this.
What about this one?
Stamina.
Uh, stealth.
Maybe just, uh, like a watermelon.
Heat resistance.
I don't think I have very much ingredients.
Do I?
I need more meat.
Banana.
Different effects.
Don't stack.
That's right.
Um, what does this do?
Uh, stop holding.
Should I just get, uh, you have an unsorted inventory.
Okay.
So it's sorted now.
So should I just do five of these?
Just one, two, three, four, five.
And just have like a bunch of low level.
Um, what do you guys think?
Just, that's what I got.
Just one, two, three, four, five with some salt.
Should I add salt or just one, two, three, four, five backseat.
Now, please put one wing in there.
No salt, just five.
See what it is.
Well, 10 minutes, 12 minutes.
Okay.
That's 12 minutes of low level cold resistance.
Is that going to be good enough?
What happens up here?
That's really all you need.
Okay.
Cause this will give us like 30 minutes.
I suppose too.
How much money do I have?
I'm going to, okay.
I think that's all right for now.
So let me get the horse.
How far away am I from though?
Thing there.
It's not that far.
All right.
I'm going to unlock that.
And then I'm going to get the horse.
I need to reveal the map.
Look, it's over there.
I'm getting close.
I need this.
Get the horse now.
I feel like I'm all right.
Here's what's going to happen.
I'm going to get the horse.
We're going to go across this bridge and I'm going to abandon the horse to
climb the side of the mountain up there.
It happens every time.
I'll try it though.
How much time do I have left?
Two and a half hours.
I got it.
Easy.
All right.
Let's get Frank to stay on the road.
I will stay on.
I'm not going to get off the horse.
Oh, okay.
All right.
Let's go.
Frank staying on the road.
No bullshit.
This is first time playing video.
No, I'll give you a little bit of insight though.
Um, so this is video game.
Let's just say video game one.
Um, since playing video game one, hold on a minute.
That was scary because I can possibly get struck by lightning on this bridge.
Yeah, I'm not going to go that way to stay on the bridge trying to stay on the
road.
They said stay on the road.
They said, look at all this shit on the road.
Where's he going to take that?
All right.
I'm getting close behind you.
I told you I was just going to climb the mountain after leaving the stable and
that's exactly what just happened.
You missed it.
What was there to miss?
He's leaving the road.
Yeah.
Look at this.
These things here, they're going to kill me.
You missed the dragon.
I don't know about any dragons.
I'm trying to get to the, I'm trying to get to the, the, the divine beast.
All right.
Well, so what I was saying is, so, okay.
Uh, so I, I played this game back in April of 2023.
I think it's been, it's been about five full months since I've not seen any of the
Zelda on the screen.
In the meantime, I played like 40 other video games, so it's like each video game
kind of is like, wait a minute.
Is that what it, oh no, that's from armored core.
That's the game I played a week ago.
Not four months ago.
Oh, wait a minute.
Okay.
This is what I can do.
I can do that.
No, no, no.
Wait, shit.
That's from hit man three.
Oh, I did it.
Wait, what?
Um, I, I need to shoot these.
Do I have any arrows?
What arrows do I have?
Hold on.
Do I have regular arrows?
Okay.
Well, I can do that.
Just come here.
I really don't want to use ice arrows.
Oh, I'm so impatient.
I hate it.
All right.
We got to see, I have, I can probably upgrade this, right?
Five.
All right.
Well, that's the destination.
I'm going that way.
Forget about these guys.
You won't beat this divine beast in three hours.
I bet you I do.
I want to unlock this.
You need to buy.
Yeah, I definitely gonna get arrows for sure.
Uh, oh yeah.
That's really funny.
You know, the, the, the Jeremy from eight months ago when I last played this would
have got hit by that a hundred percent.
Let me put on a different weapon.
Hold on.
Let me relearn the entire video game.
Got it.
Your name is Jeremy?
Uh, yeah.
Don't these things have eyes that you get to kill?
I wonder if it matters.
Maybe I can just climb it.
All right.
Whoever's editing this video, I want you to make it look like I hit that thing right
in the head and then have it like cut it out and to do an animation.
So it looks like I killed it in one hit.
That's why I did that.
Can I just get like, get on top of this right now?
Hold on.
Uh, I can't touch that stuff.
Where's the eye?
Is it going to eye on this?
That comes across here.
I feel like this is going to hurt.
Is there a better place for me to, let me kill the eye.
I know it exists somewhere over here.
Cause you can get rid of this purple stuff.
That's lying to you.
No, there's no eye.
Oh, it's okay.
Fine.
Is there a better place to grab it from?
I wonder.
Hold on.
Let me go up here.
The backseat dream stream.
This is windy.
Grab.
Oh, um, is there a place I can shit?
Is there no spot I can go up?
I don't think there is up here.
All right.
So I have to, I have to kill something then.
No jump.
Why are you?
No, I want to just jump backwards.
I want to just jump backwards, but of course not.
Oh my God.
I wanted to just jump backwards, but I'm not facing the exact perfect angle to go
back.
I have to save the game too.
Somebody just said, all right, where's the eye?
Tell me you should heal.
I'll eat a banana.
That sounds good.
Oh, everyone's lying.
There is no eye.
Okay.
All right.
So don't, don't trust chat.
I get it.
There's no eye.
How do I get up there then?
I'm the stump.
Um, I need to buy food if I can or harvest some food.
This just is what just gives you hearts and whatever.
Is there a place I can go from?
I bet if I get up here, I can do it.
You'd find a safe spot.
If there is an eye, it's going to be in some weird random place, isn't it?
But maybe I just can't get up there unless I do something in particular.
There's an eye behind you.
Not it right there.
Is it?
Did I just see it right there?
It's right there.
Look at, look at how hidden this is.
What?
Did you see how hidden that was?
Good to go.
Oh, please don't fall.
I wanted to jump backwards.
How do you just jump?
I pressed just B and he just fell down.
He didn't jump backwards.
By the way, I win.
I fall down here.
Can I ask you a backseat question?
How do you just drop?
Cause when I press B, he jumps up.
How do I just let go?
It's X, right?
Of course it is.
How do I, how do I jump backwards?
Is it down in B?
It is.
Okay.
But you have to be doing it the right, so it's not down in B.
It's like, if I was facing like over there, it'd be left in B.
Can I make it?
All right.
I got it.
That took 25 minutes.
He's not going to beat Ganon.
Watch me.
I can't wait till the credits roll and all the people that bet against
me are just seething.
There we go.
So we're going.
Oh, look at that.
Now I know exactly where the hell I can go.
This thing's on an Island.
I didn't know that.
All right, here we go.
What else is over here?
I think we're just gliding over there.
I'm gliding to that shrine over there.
Look at that.
Perfect.
Remember, if you get to the last hour, please just go right to Ganon.
Even if I'm in the middle of doing this, go immediately to Ganon when
they're, all right.
So what at 335, I have to go right to Ganon no matter what.
That's actually really funny.
All right, well, here we are.
There's a shrine here and the thing I need to do is right here.
It's right here.
What's the best way to get in here?
This way around here.
Maybe this.
Okay.
Top left, maybe.
All right.
There's a bridge over here.
Wait, does this do anything?
It's not like a thing I can activate, right?
Get away from me.
All right.
There's the bridge up into there.
And then I start that divine beast.
I'll have a solid, probably hour and 25 minutes, hour and 30 minutes to beat it.
I do need to buy stuff.
I need to buy arrows and I need to buy, um, I need to get some heals.
All right.
I think I made decent time going that way.
Fight Ganon blindfolded.
Well, we're not, we're not doing that today.
Have you done Hyrule castle at all?
I don't think so.
Hey, staples.
All right.
I am going, I actually, I'm going to take a minute to kind of, I need to get the horse.
I'll do that.
We'll actually keep the horse this time and not just throw away.
I do want to get at least somewhat prepared.
So can I buy stuff from you?
Just like a general store, right?
I wonder, can I?
No, you have to pay for this.
No, no, no, no.
Is there a store here?
This is just the stables and in a beetle was beetle is beetle random.
I think beetle.
Oh no, no, no.
You're right here.
Okay.
All right.
What do you got?
Uh, all right.
Incredibly important.
I need a ton of these, right?
I should get as many arrows as I can physically carry by every arrow.
All right.
I'm going to buy every single arrow.
These are expensive.
Okay.
What about this stuff?
Reset.
Okay.
Cold resist.
I'm going to get all these.
Okay.
With monster parts for an elixir.
Give me them all.
Okay.
Uh, temporarily maxed stamina, quiet movement.
I don't think, I don't think I need that.
Now let me go make some cold resist up over here.
All right.
The monster parts.
Uh, ingredient, any of these wings, higher quality, or just just by just
different properties, explode electricity.
I have a few of these frogs already.
Okay.
So I want to make an elixir.
That's monster parts.
The thing I just got up with some carrots.
Okay.
Where are those?
What are they?
Butterflies or something or moths?
Where are they?
There's a thing I just bought.
Oh, here they get down here.
All right.
So how many of these should I hold?
Just one?
Or should I put five of these in here?
Should I just make one with a bunch of random stuff or do four with all five?
Do them all.
Four with a, with a monster part or with guts.
Hell yeah.
Let's go.
Uh, any type of guts I should use?
I mean, this is, this thing's pretty, pretty good.
Would everybody be all right with this?
It needs to be guts, not tail.
How about this?
This looks pretty good.
All right.
That's high level cold resist.
The other thing.
What do you mean we got them?
Oh my God.
Wait, was that bad?
Now just go, go, go, go, go.
All right.
Right.
Okay.
Now go.
All right.
I'm going, I'm going.
That's going to make it to the bridge.
I can't turn.
How do you control the horse in this game?
Go on the bridge.
Oh my God.
Why?
That was so outrageous.
It's a horse on a bridge.
Leave him alone.
I, yeah, that is like kind of scary.
He's outraged right now.
All right, here we go.
It's time to start the mission.
All right.
You know what?
I'm getting off.
I'm getting off the horse.
Not only does the horse not like bridges, the horse just
wants to go on a straight line off the cliff.
I'm not about that right now.
Oh, he is not about that.
Cool.
All right.
So what's the strategy here?
How do we get up there?
I don't understand what's going on, dude.
Didn't you kill that guy in one shot?
Oh, earlier.
Yeah.
I got through phase one really quickly.
It's a speed run strat.
Uh, phase two is when the, the actual like ceiling fans start turning on.
Uh, which allows them to go a little bit higher.
So it's phase two.
Really a keen eye you have there though.
Really keen eye.
Okay.
Here we are.
Rito village.
I know there's not time to talk, but there is.
Now's not a good time.
Where am I?
This is Rito village, but well, you could say we're not in a welcoming mood.
Okay.
So we have to go.
I'm imagining probably up here at the top.
Blow the dust out of your switch, bro.
I think, I think that's just how this game runs.
All right.
This is really important.
Is it anything that I need from here?
More arrows.
I'll take them.
Three arrows for 60 bucks.
Oh, it's a bundle.
Okay.
Oh, it's expensive.
I'm imagining this probably gear I should get too.
I want to check that out first.
All right.
Snow quill trousers.
Cold resist.
Five, three, cold resist.
Okay.
So which one has the most cold resist?
Does it matter?
Are they all the same?
He's broke.
I have enough of the Chesapease.
What do I got on right now?
Have the, okay.
This is the swimming ones.
I want to keep the bandana on.
Okay.
This one's good.
Uh, I'm going to buy it.
I should, I need to upgrade this.
This thing is terrible.
Oh no, it's not.
13.
That's good.
Yeah.
Put it on.
That's fine.
Do some selling.
I could sell some stuff.
What should I sell?
Dude, I'm selling this.
Oh, it's only 15.
Nevermind.
Selling my exclusive Nintendo switch shirt for 15 coins.
I have a lot of Tophaz.
I'm just gonna sell like 10 of these.
Five?
Sell all the gems.
Sell all of them.
You look at all these gems you got.
I'm going to keep one of each.
1600 bucks.
Holy shit.
I'm rich right now.
You're never going to use these for any reason.
Okay.
True.
You guys got to, you have to absolutely gas me up for this.
I need every, I need every move.
I need all the incredibly expensive shit.
I want all the best gear in the whole game.
Like I got five grand now.
Where do I get it?
Okay.
Uh, I'm, I'm good.
I'm good.
I'm not selling everything.
No.
There's no reason to.
Okay.
I'm getting these and I'm going to get pants.
I could go to the, that area.
All right.
So, horsepower fire to make cold climates more tolerable.
So I am now completely resistant to cold.
Is there anything else I should buy that I should really get?
Get the bomb arrows.
I was going to say that too.
I was thinking it, I just didn't say it out loud.
You're a potato streamer.
That's all right.
I don't care.
Potatoes are fucking incredibly easy to like make and eat and stuff.
They're, they're, they're good.
They're healthy.
They're filling.
Who cares?
Yeah.
Why are you saying that like the bad thing?
The butter too.
Yeah.
Fine.
I'll take one.
Actually, I'm just getting this cause it's food.
Oh, you can't eat wheat.
I can combine it with stuff.
So he said, keep it moving.
Keep it moving.
Okay.
Oh, did you say I've never seen somebody spend $3,000 on food ever in this game?
Yeah, but they weren't up against the clock.
Oh, hold on a second.
Look at this.
I need to unlock the shrine.
Is there anything over here that I can teleport to?
That's not the shrine.
That's a good, let me actually get the quest first.
Here we go.
All right, let's go.
Let's do it.
Welcome.
Oh, an object on your hip.
Could it be?
Forgive me.
Where am I?
Man?
I am Kenobi elder of Rito village.
How then?
Is that not a sheikah slate dangling from your hip?
Oh my.
So it is true.
It means you must be a champion like master Revali.
One of the few able to board divine beast of Midor.
What am I thinking?
The champions have all been dead for a hundred years.
Boy must have, must be a mere descendant and inheritor of the sheikah slate.
Ah, forgive me.
Let me listen.
If you would listen to this old man's request, would you have to give my
eternal gratitude?
Sure.
Listen.
Now that I know that you have a champion, there's something I must ask you.
How should I put this?
I would like you to deal with the giant beast cycling above us.
Only a chosen one champion can stop a champion beast.
You must enter the beast and bring him to me.
I explained this to you, more headstrong Rito warriors, but
they wouldn't listen to what I did.
Tiba and Hearth tried to confront Midor, but it did not go well.
And Hearth was injured.
Tiba escaped unscathed, but I fear he now plans to face Midor alone.
That's it.
You get it.
All right.
Find Tiba.
If you work together, you may be able to stop divine beast Va-Midor.
Okay.
Forgive my intrusion, but I overheard you speaking with the elder.
Sounds like you intend to help my husband Tiba in the fight against Midor.
But to tell you the truth, there's not much I can do for you right now.
Beyond telling you where my husband went.
All right.
Where'd he go?
Well, my husband headed to a place called the flight range.
It's in Drawnox pass at the base of the Hebra mountains.
It's a place where Rito warriors prepare for aerial combat.
It's gone there to gather weapons for another run at Midor.
As it happens, he made his way to the flight range on foot this time.
You take off from Revali's landing.
It's a straight shot down to the flight range.
Revali's landing is a memorial for the Rito champion, Revali.
Okay.
All right.
I'm ready.
How much pizza do I eat a year?
Um, let's do the math.
We got, let's say like one to two pizzas a month.
Maybe like one pizza a month, baby.
12, maybe 12 to 15 pizzas a year.
Depends.
Those are rookie numbers.
Sometimes it's more.
Depends.
Impressive.
I know.
Very few can achieve a mastery of the sky.
Okay, cool.
Yet I have made an art of creating an updraft that allows me to
solve.
Oh, this is where I'm going to learn how to get it.
Considered to be quite the masterpiece of aerial techniques, even among the Rito.
With proper utilization of my superior skills, I see no reason why we couldn't
easily.
Didn't I get really mad at flying last time?
My ability to explore the firmament is certainly of note, but let's not pardon
me for being so blunt.
Let's not forget the fact that I am the most skilled archer of all
the Rito.
Yet despite these truths, it seems that I've been tapped to merely assist you all
because you happen to have that little darkness ceiling sword on your back.
The master sword, right?
I mean, I'm glad I picked that up.
Just asinine.
Unless you think you can prove me wrong.
Maybe we should just settle this one on one.
All right, but where?
Oh, I know.
How about up there?
Oh, you must pardon me.
I forgot you have no way of making it up to that divine beast on your own.
So so you don't have wings and I do.
Ha ha ha.
OK, wait, what's happened?
Are you all right?
My apologies.
I fear I have said far too much.
Is there anything you do not understand?
Please do not hesitate.
All right, let's go.
Or is that that's nothing I can literally.
I can fly there very easily.
Let me get the shrine, though.
I don't want to have to run back here.
Where is it?
It's beeping.
Where is it, though?
Back seaters, I need your help.
Oh, there it is.
Stop wasting time.
I am not wasting time.
I've got plenty of time.
I've got two.
I've got two full hours.
There might even be time to have a snack.
OK, cool.
Then we got to go that way.
You know what I'm doing?
I need to cook this food, though.
I need a fire to cook the food,
even though I do have some.
I do have some meals.
Wait, are you going to tell me
that I can do this?
I don't want to hear a story.
I'm sorry.
I don't think I can make that.
Give him up top.
What?
I don't know.
But now all of a sudden,
you guys don't care
about the time constraint.
Five seconds ago, it was hurry up.
Hurry up, dummy.
And now all of a sudden it's
I want to hear the story.
Can I make this?
I think I can get up here.
I promise this will shave time somehow.
I promise this will shave
a little bit of time
so we get a place where I can stand,
which I think I think I can stand up here.
Looks like I can, right?
Sometimes it lets you just.
It's not.
Come on, right there.
There's a lip right here.
OK, now from here,
I'm going to glide across
the entire thing
and walk on this for sure.
I can't. No way.
I can definitely walk right there.
No way I can definitely land on that.
Good. And now
I don't need to go all the way up.
I just wanted to do this.
I definitely shaved off
some time it had to over.
You would have made it without climbing.
I don't think I would have.
I just jumped off that dock.
Look at that. And here we are.
OK, so here's the thing.
If I do beat, if I OK,
if I get to Ganon
with an hour remaining,
maybe I have enough time
to load those shrines.
OK, we got that.
Here we go.
I do want to heal.
That's definitely smart.
What food can I eat?
That's not going to
this is just cold resist.
I should eat this right now.
Low level cold resist.
I get the hearts back.
Why not?
I'm going to eat it.
Oh, I got the master sword.
I got targets to shoot at.
Hyrule Castle is going to
take him two days.
No, it's not.
And a free bow.
All right. So what bow
do I have right now
that I just need to get rid of?
Which is the worst bow that I have.
This thing's almost dead.
So why not just use it?
Cook the wheat.
Yeah, I'll cook all the food here.
Yeah.
Hmm.
I need to find this person.
I don't know you.
And I'm actually pretty busy here.
You should probably go.
I'm going to cook and put some
some.
It doesn't matter.
So many materials.
And I just buy a bunch of wheat.
Where is it?
There's a little bit of butter.
One of these.
Another one of these.
Sure.
Why not?
Oh, and I'll do that one more time.
I have another.
I have a couple.
I just want the heart.
Up in there.
All right.
I I don't care about cooking.
I have I have.
I'll beat it.
All right.
So what's the deal here?
My name's Link.
Oh, by the way, stay tuned
because I'm going to be beating
punch out every regular circuit
without falling down more than once.
So if you want to see that,
I would stay tuned.
That's when the the lower right
corner of me with my arms crossed
kind of superimposed green screen
in the bottom right.
It's like and at eight o'clock
central, the punch out challenge.
And then it goes away
after like 10 seconds.
You should take your time.
OK.
Once Divine Beast Van Madoe
falls from the sky.
If I have to kill Madoe, so be it.
All right.
Let's go.
We can do it.
As the elder said,
the only way to stop
Divine Beast Van Madoe
is to get inside of it.
Bad chance of that happening.
There's no way we can set foot in Madoe.
Actually.
Wait, did I actually this guy?
So not only are you wingless,
you're brainless, too.
Oh, I am one of the five champions.
Let me tell you.
It hadn't been Ganon.
Never mind.
Let's focus on bringing down Madoe
one step at a time.
If we approach Madoe recklessly,
its cannons will blast us out of the sky
before we can even get close.
I need to test you
before I can take you with me.
We Rito warriors use the updraft
in this ravine
to hone our aerial archery skills.
The updrafts are so strong here
that a person could.
I'm going to fail this a lot.
So you just leave.
Some of you are debating.
Some of you are debating on like,
oh, man, maybe he'll get this done
in like 30 minutes.
Now is the time for you
just to go do laundry
or make lunch or something or dinner.
When you come back,
I'll still be here, don't worry.
All right, the updrafts
are so strong here that you can.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's go destroy all five targets
in three hours.
You got it.
I just shot three.
Hold on a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I don't want to shoot three arrows
at the same fucking time.
I want to shoot one arrow.
How do I go back?
It only uses one.
Oh, I can think broken my hands.
What's the second worst bow?
This one.
Perfect.
I really hope that wasn't
shooting more than one arrow.
Uh-huh.
You must have seen a battle or two.
I've seen a few.
It's not brag here.
I can tell just by looking at you.
Don't be modest.
You'll have heard the name somewhere.
Link.
Well, if you really want to
help me bring down Madoa,
it's now or never.
Let's get you into position
so you can give its cannons
all you got.
All right.
Inside that treasure
chest is a bow I've modified.
Take it and let me know
when you're ready.
Falcon bow.
Highly refined Rito made bow
created by a master Rito craftsman.
Rito Warriors favorite
for its superior rate of fire.
Oh, that's pretty good.
This thing's awesome.
Look at this thing.
OK, is it on fire now?
Were there arrows in here?
I could take or take them already.
Free bow.
All right, I'm ready.
Let's go.
You guys ready?
I need bomb arrows.
All right.
You just give me 20 of these.
These things that you just gave me
like five grand.
I'm good.
I already got food in me.
I've already got good clothes on.
Why are you doing this?
Why risk your life to bring down the dough?
Or it's for a bet to rescue Zelda.
The name of the princess
Revelle served 100 years ago
at Hyrule Castle.
As long as you're helping me
bring down the dough,
your motivation is fine by me.
Let's go.
All right, so let's do it.
Let me save the game first.
This is all about just landing shots.
I'm going to try really hard.
I'm not going to fuck around.
OK, just hit the targets.
It's showtime.
OK, so what do I need to hit the cannons?
There's divine beast,
Ven Madoe,
and it has its barrier up again.
What a pain.
It's wrong to scared.
See those cannons?
I'll draw their fire.
While I'm doing that,
use your bomb arrows
to destroy the cannons.
Got it.
I got it.
If you need to withdraw for a bit,
just spread your cloth
and float straight up
into the updraft for a while.
I'll take that as a sign
that we need to regroup.
Don't bother aiming for anything
covered by the barrier.
Whatever you do,
don't get close enough to touch it.
Well, that would be on you
because I'm not the one.
You're I'm on.
I'm on top of you.
All right.
Finally, I know I said this a few times.
I have cold on.
Let's go.
Now blow up those cannons.
What the fuck is happening?
Can you come back?
Holding up OK.
Get over here.
Why did I come?
Why did I fall off?
Let's go.
Why did I jump off?
It's on you.
What is happening?
I thought I was supposed
to be riding on him.
How do I change?
How do I change the arrow
that I have missing?
Is it alive?
That's it.
OK, we're good.
I thought I was staying on his back.
I was feeling there.
You can't hit the shit in the air,
can you know?
Oh, sorry.
Did you miss?
He's shit.
One of the top, maybe.
I think I can probably
hit this from here.
I aim it right.
I'll do the same thing.
I said, you know,
I think I can hit it from here.
Yeah, I got it.
Is that all of them?
Or is there one more?
Somewhere in the front, I bet.
Yep, let's go.
Now he's going to get inside, right?
Well done, Link.
That thing is history.
That's a two hour puzzle session.
Oh, coming up, you mean.
It'll be 45 minutes to beat this.
Whatever.
This one doesn't look that big.
This does not look as large
as the other ones were inside.
News, Link.
Looks like I got hit
pretty good back there.
I think I think I need to get back
to the flight doesn't know.
Is this actually a Pepe laugh?
That's I just hope that
I can make it back.
You head down to me.
Look, it's all you.
Pepe laugh.
Remember, can you wish me
a good day at school today?
Take a day off school.
Someday the weekend.
You mean for tomorrow?
Well, now I've seen that face before.
I had a feeling you would show up
eventually, but making me
probably five years is a bit indulgent.
Sunday school.
Have a good day at Sunday school.
You're I'm against clock right now.
Hold on, correct?
If so, then the first thing
you'll want to do is find yourself.
He thinks America is the only country.
It's EU is not in school right now.
Maybe Asia, Australia,
Australia from here is plus 14.
I don't think it's it.
I don't think it's school time for Australia.
Is it where you wait?
It is like it's like 6 a.m.
right now in Australia.
Hey, OK.
Hey, have a good day at school.
OK, I'm I got to I got to play.
So do we have to do
anything weird with this one?
Divine, because there's
no weird shit to do.
It's not like, oh,
I have to move the elephant.
Whatever I have to move
the trunk up and down.
It's not anything like that, right?
And I want that, whatever that is.
I have to just touch all those things.
I mean, all the way up.
It's up here.
I can keep going up
and I open the map of the.
I don't think I can.
All right, I need to find those kiosks.
Is it not up in this top?
Oh, wait.
At what point do I go too high up
and I lose
gravity of the divine beast
or whatever it is?
Does it matter?
OK, well.
I'm just going to go down here
to get the map first.
I'm sorry I was wishing somebody
good luck in Sunday school.
I was a little distracted, sorry.
I got to go to the map room.
OK, how do you swing?
I'm going to swing.
Here we go.
Somebody just said,
what is this boring ass game?
All right, come on, dude.
You can you can.
You would think that Zelda is boring,
but you know what the game is.
Do you know what I mean?
Like you have to know what the game is.
You know, this is Zelda.
I mean, you might think the game sucks.
That's all right.
Everybody has their own games.
They like to look closely,
but it's Zelda.
You know what it is.
The terminals that will activate
Meadow are marked
by those glowing points.
You'll need to agree with him.
All of the terminals to take.
No, I would.
No, I'm just.
Think you're right.
Thanks for defending us.
I was.
Wait, people think.
Was I agreeing?
He's agreeing with him.
OK, all right.
All right.
No, we're good.
We're good.
I have to move some things around.
Oops.
Oh, fuck.
This could take all day.
How was I ever going
to beat this in three hours?
Don't say that yet.
OK, so it's either.
OK, it's either up middle.
Tilts, you tilt it.
I get it.
So you can either tilt
left or tilt right.
Let me just take a quick look.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, no, we're good.
I don't want to shoot
bomb arrows, though.
Just.
Just go in again and do this.
No way you're going to be this puzzle.
I think no, I'm all right.
I'm all right.
I just need to actually sit here
and pay attention for real.
Can I try that?
All right, hold on.
Can I shoot that?
I'm going to I'm going to shoot this.
Save the game.
It's been a long time.
Just go to Ganon.
I mean, I'm I'm here right now.
This is a really bad idea.
I don't even know why I did that.
Is there anything I can fly up with?
Hold on.
Can I get can I grab on or something?
Oh, God, not to the helicopter, please.
OK, we're good.
So if it tells this way,
I can freeze them, I bet.
Chest down there.
I go this way.
The bird is so small.
Where is all this stuff up?
Like we're this way.
They're like in the wings.
We're in the way down below.
That gets me over here.
Why did you do that?
Look at this.
Wait, I can't walk up.
All right, so now I'm in here
and I'm going to tell it this way.
No, I did.
Yes.
So this one right up here is one.
There are four terminals remaining.
Still no ways to go.
OK.
Oh, I'm going to make it flat.
So the next one is in the left.
Is it like a little bunker
or something over here?
I'm going to get attacked, aren't I?
What are these things for?
All right, all right.
Stop the spawning.
What does this do?
OK, and open up the windows.
Get some fresh air.
That is doing what?
Is that going to stay open?
All right, hold on a second.
So if I go like this
and then which direction
should I move it this way?
Oh, shit, things are moving.
I just press this big button
and now do I close it
if I close it?
Will the no hold on
that close that gate?
What is if I close the window
that closes that?
Now this is stuck here,
which then I just I don't
what's the goal here?
I don't know.
I'm about to float out the window
to the Hyrule Castle, by the way.
I'm about to just go out the window
out, float out the window
to Hyrule Castle
because I need to get in here.
So how do I what button opens that?
And what do I have to press
to open this door?
Button's not pressed all the way.
Do I tilt the bird?
Because this presses the button
in all the way.
But what does that actually even do?
It closes this.
No, it is.
It doesn't.
It needs to go faster.
All right, I'm very confused.
I'm opening this again.
It would be blue if it was pressed.
So do I have to make it go
like super speed down?
Hold on.
What if I turn?
OK, so I have to get rid of that
because that's blocking this.
That's OK.
There it goes.
Now we make it go to the right
and it's going to be going wicked fast.
Hold on.
Oh, OK.
Now I have to freeze
my freezing the door.
What am I actually freezing here?
Freeze on the fan.
This one here, right?
And then tilt it, freeze this
so it'll move all the way over.
Freeze the metal block.
I don't think I can.
Freeze the square metal block.
So then now I tilt it
all the way up.
Oh, oh shit.
Wait.
I got it.
It's it's it's it's weird.
It's weird.
It's a puzzle.
It takes a minute.
Try it again.
Wait, waiting.
Keep waiting.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I don't get this at all.
Wait.
What what am I not getting here?
What?
I don't even need to do that at all.
What is actually happening?
What is what is making this great go down?
Does that thing have to go all the way to the other side?
I actually don't understand how this is the mechanics of how this works.
What is making the gate go up?
So turning it again this way.
Why wouldn't I want to just keep it right here?
How come it's doing that?
I just like get it.
Use the magnesis on the block so the fan can keep spinning.
Oh, it's not enough to freeze it.
I completely forgot this was an item in the game.
I completely forgot the magnet existed.
God damn it.
I literally can just go like this.
All right, well, let's try it again.
But now if I hold this, keep it right here.
Hey, look at that.
How come you keep forgetting this is in the game?
Because I do this really fun thing where I play Breath of the Wild every six months.
And then I don't play it for six months.
All right, six is generous.
There are three terminals remaining.
Keep going.
OK, can I get them all in a row?
No. All right.
We just got to get the other side.
There's three on the other side.
Turn it this way.
But what are we looking at here?
I got to get up there.
Cure that guy real quick over there.
Wait, I want that one.
I can't. I have no patience at all.
Like zero.
It's it goes to zero.
I was do I was doing it fine.
I just like my brain was like, I want to beat this so fast.
I don't want to wait for the bird to turn.
That's what was going through my head.
It's like I have to wait for the bird bird to turn.
It's going to take ten full seconds.
I don't want to wait.
OK, well, now I have to get back up there.
I got to get up there.
What's the best way to get up there?
Freezing this in the middle?
Yeah.
Then I'm going to head to the left.
Second part.
We've got you, hold on.
Get rid of the spawner.
All right, this is going to make this blow.
And what's happening?
I got to get up there.
Anything on the ceiling?
No, I think I know what to do.
Tilt it this way.
Maybe I can just fall in there.
I think I can just fall in and watch this, right?
I imagine that will work.
Will that work? Of course it does.
I almost got it.
We're good.
I think we're on pretty good pace right now.
I've got I've got more than a full hour to begin.
I'm going to have all the divine powers.
I need to get through this door.
I'm almost there.
Yeah, it doesn't blow up by itself.
Right.
How do I explain that?
I can't explain it.
Just laugh at the dumb thing I did.
OK, nice.
All right, now we put a bomb in there.
Turn that off
and we can pop that.
That's just right.
No, really?
I can't.
Well, now what do I do?
Oh, come on.
I had it.
I did it right.
No, we want to go this way.
OK, now I got to make it go that way.
I don't think I can.
Can I make it go that way?
Wait, I can.
OK, OK.
Very cool.
Now, now we do this
and I do magnetism
through the wall.
No, I don't.
I do tilt.
Which way should I tilt?
This way?
No.
Pull it out.
I can get it here.
I'll move it this way.
Can I reach now?
Oh, get it on the track over there.
Come here.
OK, get it right here.
And we tilt it
that slam into it.
They only got this only two more.
This is actually much better than I thought it was.
We're good.
Just one terminal remaining.
What do you know?
One terminal and it's down.
It is down, down there, right below me.
OK, so what's the deal?
I think I'm going to open this and then go out of the window.
Does that sound good?
Everybody, it's right underneath me.
I'm going to save it right now.
I feel like that's correct.
It probably isn't.
Is that not correct?
No, no, go this way.
It was not correct.
I didn't know if there was like a lip
because remember, there was a little lip over there.
All right, this is where I want to be.
So not above, but down to the left over there.
OK, so what the heck is going on over here?
Let's float in there.
Let's go.
OK, I'm going to eat something.
I'm going to keep the cold resistance going.
Yeah, that'll get rid of that.
It's pre-recorded.
No, it's that way.
Is there another one of those things on track?
So I got to get in there.
So wait a minute.
Hold on. If I tilt this way,
I can probably float in there.
Ooh, I got it.
It's done. I just beat it.
And we still have an hour and 20 minutes.
I am doing just fine, by the way.
I don't think I can make it.
Yeah, yeah, that's them all.
I got them all.
Let's turn it on.
So what's the superpower you get from the bird?
Right in the middle.
This one wasn't that bad.
This one was fun.
This was a lot shorter
than the other ones, it seems like.
I liked it, though. It was fun.
Can I make this?
OK. All the way up.
Longer than the lizard, at least.
Did I hate the lizard?
I thought.
I should probably get to full health.
This is a boss.
Or close to full health.
All right. Get the master sword out.
It's not out already.
Master sword is here.
60 damage.
Holy shit.
And what do I have for a bow?
Falcon bow, that's fine.
What do I have for arrows?
I have a lot of bomb arrows
and maybe I'll use them.
OK, well, that was annoying.
All right, are we ready? Let's go.
How do I turn it on?
Cannon.
Save the bombs for cannon.
I have to get a picture of that for sure.
OK.
Defeated me a hundred years ago.
Well, you see, when I played six months ago,
you know, I was OK.
I was good back then,
but I forgot how the game played.
I forgot the controls.
So it's your turn now.
I haven't played Breath of the Wild
in fucking a hundred years, Link.
Dodge?
These don't really hurt that much.
Ow.
I need to eat something.
What do I even have for food?
I got this.
I feel like I should have wasted all of this, but I did.
All right. No more.
OK, bomb arrows.
I'm not using them.
Where is he?
I just needed a complete 160 degrees
with 200 added on top of that.
Can I bring him down?
I feel like you have to see the gun or something.
Where is he?
Where even is this guy?
And why are you talking to me
like in the middle of a fight like this?
More food. What is this?
Oh, this is this is not good.
I have to dodge like everything.
Excuse me?
And what kind of crack
is this game smoking right now?
What?
I can't hurt him in the middle of that?
What the fuck was that?
I almost want to start over.
Yeah, I'm starting over.
What are we going to do?
Yeah, I got it.
I got it.
I just want to give him false insecurity.
I'm going to fucking crush him.
Land on top of him, please.
You're out of arrows?
No, I got arrows.
I don't know what the fuck that is.
Shoot?
All right, I need the, I need the gas thing.
No, go this way.
Shoot, what are you doing?
Why will you not shoot this?
No, you don't have a bow and arrow.
What are you talking about?
He was like,
Ah, now's my chance.
Yeah, it is.
OK, he would have been so funny
if he died of his health at zero.
This would be one of the best games
I've ever played in my entire life.
That happened.
We still have an hour and 20 minutes.
Everyone, everyone relax.
Everybody just settle down.
We've got an hour and 20 minutes,
at least.
Can you imagine if I looked over the edge?
He was just falling.
I could tell the whole time
dark souls died on the ground.
That would have been probably my favorite thing
I've ever seen in a game.
Enemies do that in Tears of the Kingdom.
Nice.
Will that bring me to two rows?
Maybe.
Heart container.
Oh, that's too bad.
Yeah, right.
One row, Andy.
I know it's bad, but it's not that bad.
It's fine.
Yeah, we can't skip the major cutscenes.
I'm going to see these.
Oh, look, it's Revelli.
Revelli.
Well done.
Well done, Revelli.
Don't preen yourself just for doing your job.
I do suppose you've proven your value as a warrior.
A warrior worthy of my unique ability.
And what is it?
The secret skill that I have dubbed Revelli's Gale.
Super jump.
It's now time to move on
and start making preparations for Meadow Strike on Ganon.
Good.
Crazy good.
Do you still need my help
while you're fighting inside Hyrule Castle?
I have them all.
I have all the powers.
Feel free to thank me now.
Or never watch us go.
You should have done this one way earlier.
Your job is far from finished, you know.
The princess has been waiting in awe.
It's very, very good.
Most people do this one first.
Six months.
He did this one last laughing.
Why?
You don't have, there's no order.
I thought that you guys told me two years ago
when I started this
that it didn't matter what order I did.
I kind of want to make the title of the stream.
Playing through Breath of the Wild again.
And then in parentheses, I don't do sequels.
No, I'm not playing the new one.
This is the original one.
I'm playing the new one.
I don't do sequels.
I don't watch movie sequels either.
I have no idea what happens in Star Wars.
Meadow sights are now set.
You'll have a precise speed on Ganon
from this vantage point.
When the time is right, give him everything you've got.
What about Diablo II?
Now we wait for that perfect moment.
Meadow, we've been artfully patient for the last 100 years.
I doubt you'll suffer a feather over a few more moments.
What about TF2?
After all these years, I simply must admit the truth.
Even without the power of flight,
Link made his way to this divine beast
and accomplished something that even I could not.
Guess I was wrong about how lucky I was.
No, they actually changed it.
Nice.
I hope that-
Your favorite movie is Gremlins 2.
Well, that makes it funnier.
Armored Core 6.
That's, there's many sequels in front of that.
Blustrous power born from the spirit
of the champion, Revali.
Creates an upward draft that carries you into the sky.
Activate by charging jump with B.
Link.
Is she under the boards?
Link, thanks to you.
Oh.
Both the divine beasts have returned to us
and the spirits of the champions are free.
We will all be awaiting your clash with Ganon
at Hyrule Castle.
Link, I'm under here.
Don't ask me how I got in here.
I was on an adventure and I fell down in here.
We were doing renovations.
I got stuck in here.
In fact, Link, you're standing
on the only air hole that exists.
Please move.
Okay.
Are we going?
Is it time to go?
So now we have to go back here, right?
That song.
Do I care about the song?
Stop being a comedian and just go.
Eh, yeah, all right, gotcha.
I have to make, no, now just go.
No, just go, go, go, go, go.
Right here?
You're not even wasting time to be funny.
Is it?
No, I see what's going on.
It's when we, when we added betting to this,
is when all of you now,
all of you now do not care about anything else.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, just shut the fuck up and go, man.
I put every channel point I have on you fucking losing
or winning, go, I don't care.
I should have done that first.
Are you serious?
This is like the power I should have gotten
in the very beginning of the game.
And I'm, and I have it an hour before
I'm never playing it ever again.
All right, I did it.
We did it.
Very cool, very good.
Life and the divine beast will ravage the calamity now.
All right.
Feel free to take what you find in that chest.
What are you doing?
I, there's an item in here.
That sword you have in your possession.
Would it be the sword that seals the darkness?
A Hylian champion who fought alongside
Master Revali a hundred years ago?
Would that be you?
It is.
All right, I got the great eagle bow.
I got a ton of bombs.
I'm ready.
I've got a full heal.
What, be honest with me for real.
What is the best possible way to do it?
Just teleport to here.
Fast travel right here.
Go, I'm just gonna go right in the front door.
I'm just gonna knock on the front door.
I need food.
All right, what kind of food am I looking for?
Is it fire?
Is it lightning?
Is it cold?
What should I be making?
Food then go, food then go.
I got it.
Just make only health, health, health, health, health, health.
Just heals.
Link, Link, Link.
I have witnessed your journey.
You have overcome every challenge laid before you.
Ruta, Rudania, Meadow, Naboris.
All of the divine beasts are now free.
With the strength you have attained,
I am certain you can unlock the powerful force
hidden within.
Go to the Shrine of Resurrection.
The Shrine of Resurrection.
And return the Sheikah Slate to its terminal.
Okay, I have to do that.
Why does that say EX?
That's DLC?
All right, no, we're not doing DLC.
I'm going in the front door.
I need a town though.
I need to buy shit at a town.
Where's there a good place to go and get some stuff?
There's good food where, okay.
I'm gonna say Zorro?
Where can I get good food?
You don't have time?
I got time for food.
There's food in the castle.
Is there actually like a shop or something?
You hate this game and want it to be over
as soon as possible.
That's not true.
I felt bad that I got this far without beating it.
And I wanna beat it.
And I'm very happy with how the game has been so far,
but I'm ready.
Let's go.
Get your Amiibo.
How much time is left on the timer?
There is about an hour.
There's a vendor in the castle.
Cooking pots in castle.
So there's no vendor in the castle then.
So people align.
Let me just go to,
I'm gonna go just to here.
I know, I know.
Everyone's like, just go, go, go.
But I wanna buy some stuff.
I don't trust there's one in the castle.
I feel like people align.
If he goes in without food, he'll just die anyways.
Yeah.
I wanna give myself a chance.
We still, there's still over an hour.
An hour and five minutes to get to the last hit on Ganon.
That's not happening, but I'll try.
I'm gonna speed it up.
Okay.
So where, I just need a vendor.
I just need, okay.
General store, right there.
Just straight ahead.
I don't know what that thing is.
I didn't wanna shoot.
Okay.
Do I have enough to upgrade anything?
Because I'm gonna do this quick.
If I have enough to upgrade,
what's the best gear that I have right now?
Probably the, I don't know.
Honestly, probably the thing I had on before.
Champion's tunic?
Probably this, all the soldier shit.
Okay.
All right, can I do, can I upgrade any of this?
Champion's tunic's probably the best.
Okay, what do we got?
I can upgrade the champion's tunic.
Should I?
That sounds like a good idea.
That'll be better than what I have on now, right?
Okay.
Being able to see health is important.
Upgrade it again.
Do I have enough?
If I can do it twice, I'll do it.
I don't think I can.
No, I can't do it again.
Okay.
We're going to make food.
I'm putting that on.
That's 20 defense, and now I can see enemy health.
20.
All right, this is, I've got a good set of gear on.
I'm good to go.
Right now, I need to go.
This is shaving a second off.
Yeah, I can't just go.
I'm guaranteed to lose if I just go.
I need to get at least another two or three big heals.
It's, you guys are saying, holy, you guys,
like, go, go, go.
All of you believers need to understand
that if I get to Ganon and I die, you'll lose anyways.
And I think I'm going to die more than once.
We're going to do it.
I got time.
There's like apples and shit right here.
This is good.
Okay, where's the general store?
All right.
Fire arrows.
At this point, I should just take them all, right?
Just take everything?
Might as well just buy every single thing I can.
Okay, now what about food?
Like, real food?
I'm willing to pay a premium, by the way.
Different store.
I don't think I have enough ingredients to cook any food.
I mean, what do I even have?
I think I just have to cook everything.
The store with the carrot on it.
Wait, this one?
This has a carrot on it.
Shitload of carrots here.
Okay, hell yeah.
All right, all right, all right.
We're good.
Now I'm just going to make a bunch of food.
Bro is hanging out in Publix with 45 minutes left.
I need to, I have to make this food, you don't understand.
All right, what's the best,
what's the best recipe I can do right now?
Carrot, carrot, carrot, apple, apple, apple, monster guts.
Carrot, carrot, carrot.
How many carrots?
How many carrots should I put in?
Who cares?
It doesn't matter.
It actually doesn't even matter.
There we go.
That's 10 health potions.
It actually doesn't even matter.
Who cares?
I need health.
I need heals.
Who cares?
I bought all these carrots
and I don't even know where the fuck they are.
Okay, there.
Okay, good.
That's movement speed, all right.
Okay.
What else can I use here?
Let's do carrot.
Carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot.
Butter.
Wait, shit.
Put away a carrot and put an egg in there.
Egg, carrot, carrot, carrot, butter.
That's gonna be fucking great.
Perfect.
I'm gonna make that a bunch of times in a row.
That's carrot, carrot, carrot, butter, egg.
What was wrong with that?
What was wrong with that one?
Egg, butter.
This one's gonna be really fatty.
Oh yeah, sure.
10, good.
I'm just gonna put a bunch of eggs and salt in this one.
I'm not wasting it.
I just need the heals.
What?
Use it to make...
Okay, this is good in stews.
We're gonna do two of these.
We're gonna do two of these, a little bit of salt.
Okay, I have a lot of heals now.
I think I'm good.
I need salt and shit too.
Hold on, salt, salt.
And who cares?
Well, that was not worth it.
All right, I'm good.
Now it's time to go.
All right, get the horse.
We're riding straight into Ganon's castle
and we're gonna take it back.
You guys ready?
What's the fastest way to get there?
Horse right here.
Just glide from the tower.
Ooh, actually smart call.
I got an hour.
I have one full hour.
Run past every enemy, dude.
Should I?
I got time, I got time, I got time.
I might not have very much time, but where's the tower?
All right, fuck it.
Yeah, fuck the horse.
The horse helped us a lot,
but I'm literally gonna slide from the tower.
It all comes down to this.
The end of the Breath of the Wild playthrough.
Over three years in the making.
How do I get the quest?
Destroy Ganon.
That was not far enough.
It's okay.
We're actually not that far.
There's a shrine over here too.
Oh, this is gonna be close.
I was not, you know,
what about let me see if I can do it in three hours.
I'm kind of amped up right now.
You got how to surf?
Yep.
I did.
You're right.
I don't know how.
ZL jump A.
I don't know.
We're good.
Come on.
Do I have less than a hundred seconds left in Mario?
Why does it get faster?
Oh no.
Can I block?
Okay.
I can probably just kill this thing, honestly.
Why would you face the, okay.
I'm locking on.
He's facing the camera.
Why are you facing the camera?
Why did he face the camera?
Wouldn't lock on turn him around?
There's another enemy off camera.
And why did it put me all the way back here?
What just happened?
You didn't save it?
Doesn't it put you?
Wait, did I not even do the cooking shit?
You gotta be kidding me.
Why?
I feel like I've died a million times
and it just puts me kind of,
oh, it's back to the last save point.
Oh, that's annoying.
Oh my God.
Well, that's it.
It's over.
Sorry, everybody.
I didn't even upgrade the armor.
Are you serious?
Manual saving?
Really?
Are we still to do manual saving
at the last fucking checkpoint in the game?
Okay.
That doesn't count.
I get an extra 10 minutes.
No, I don't.
Now I have to do everything I just did all over again.
Well, honestly, I much prefer
like the From Software version of gaming
where if you,
dude, if you sneeze, the game auto saves.
Do you know what I mean?
Give me manual saves, that's fine.
But if literally, if I fucking hit up on the control stick,
auto save the game.
Okay, well, let me,
did I even buy anything?
I don't even remember.
Did I actually?
Oh, come on, dude.
Oh my God.
I actually have to upgrade this again.
It was an auto save.
How come?
Wait, why would it not put me to the auto save?
Now I'm getting frustrated.
Where's the auto save?
What the hell?
Wait, how long ago is that?
Was this even further back?
Because this is on top of the tower.
No, this is like 25 minutes ago.
Isn't it?
Yeah.
Oh, come on.
It was three minutes.
Actually, that sucks so bad
that I don't have a save within the last like 15 minutes.
How often does Zelda auto save?
Is it more than 15 minutes?
20 minutes?
Well, I'm just gonna do what I just did again.
It's probably when you teleport.
I have to do all this again.
The game saves every five minutes.
No, it doesn't.
I walked around cooked food for 15 minutes straight.
Just go right to Ganon?
Suck it up, cry baby.
Okay.
Let me go make the food.
I don't want to get there and lose.
So sorry that we got screwed by an auto save teacher.
Sorry, guys.
That's my fault for not manually saving
before every single encounter that's important.
Oh, well.
You could just try killing Ganon right...
I guess I could just go try to kill Ganon right now.
Just run through the dungeon.
That's possible, right?
I don't think I...
No, no.
I could try it.
All right, here's the plan.
Here's the plan.
His plan is plan.
I'm going as fast as I can.
Did I at least buy?
No, I'm all right, I'm all right.
I don't think I was ever gonna do it anyways,
but it was worth a shot.
I'm still gonna beat it,
even if I don't do it in the timer.
I'm still gonna do it.
The joke of me turning off the game is not gonna happen.
I will complete it.
You're just gonna lose a lot of channel points.
Whoever bet for me to win.
All right, let's make the food again.
The recipes.
Okay.
Now I gotta remember what the hell I even did.
It was bat.
Okay, it was butter, salt, and...
Butter, salt, eggs, and carrots.
It's a double carrot.
Okay.
Butter, salt, egg, double carrot.
Where are my carrots?
Where are...
Oh my God, these carrots are so weird.
They blend in with everything.
No, don't eat one.
Stop cooking.
I'll die.
You think I'm gonna be able to kill Calamity Ganon
with no heals?
It's never gonna happen.
Okay, good.
Why was that so bad?
All right, only, I'm gonna do one more.
I should have enough after this.
Wait, don't I have something that gives a lot of hearts?
This one right here.
I'm gonna just cook that with salt.
So it's just a bunch of hearts?
Or should I just do it alone?
Should I just do it by itself?
It temporarily increases your maximum hearts
when cooked into a dish.
Or should I add stuff to it?
Add a melon, just salt.
Cook it alone?
Just cook alone, by itself?
Okay.
Holy shit.
I still have time.
There's still time.
I got time, I got time, everybody.
That was awesome.
Holy shit.
I got time, I got time, I got time, I got time.
Go to the waterfall?
Put on your Zora armor and swim up to the final battle?
Wait, is that real?
Are you giving me like the speed run strategy?
All right.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I'll go, I'll go, I'll go.
Any more goat butter or whatever it is?
I don't know what any of this shit does, who cares?
We're back, we're back.
Yeah, we're back, we're actually back.
All right.
Now, where's this?
Go to the waterfall in the southwest of the island
that Hyrule Castle is on.
Go to the waterfall in the southwest island.
This is cheating.
I saved it.
He is never gonna find that.
What, we got 35 minutes?
Please give us the underdog moment we've been waiting for.
Okay.
Waterfall in the southwest of the island
that Hyrule Castle is on.
Put on your Zora armor and swim up the waterfall.
Keep going up each waterfall that you reach.
It should be very close.
Pass a few guardians, okay?
So from here, from Hyrule Castle, southwest of the island.
So down here somewhere, like over here?
I'm gonna say like right here somewhere.
Should I get the horse, honestly?
The island the castle is on.
So you mean like here somewhere.
I gotta even get there first.
What's the safe way to even get over here?
I feel like there's a ton of those laser shooting guardians
that just fire machine guns at you.
My armor is different.
Right.
Zora armor.
That's it, all right.
Save it here.
I just saved it a second ago.
Go to the central tower.
I don't know what hell I'm going.
I guess I've never, I've never even seen this before.
I don't know where to go.
I guess, I mean, I'm,
I think I can get there from here.
There's no bullshit in the way.
I just gotta remember how you do the,
it's right here.
ZL jump and then A.
This thing's gonna fucking shatter.
All right, Tilda, I'm coming to save you.
How bad, how bad is this current?
Fuck.
What the fuck is that thing?
Yeah.
Okay, all right.
We're getting there, we're getting there.
Don't aggro that thing.
Oops.
Bro, I'm gonna start screaming.
Everybody fucking settle down, okay?
Settle down.
Everything is gonna be just fine.
Can't get in here.
I can't swim again.
Don't I have the swimming outfit on?
We're good.
Hey, if I could get this thing away from me, seriously.
You know what?
Just fucking die.
How do you parry?
What is parry?
It's A.
I would run by, but the thing just,
it's shield plus A.
Okay, well, I'm just gonna try to run away
from the lock-on enemy that locks on you
from across the entire video game.
Whoa!
Hold on.
Don't get angry at the enemy that you hate
more than anything in any video game you've ever played.
How does that sound?
You fucking idiot.
Nice shot, stupid.
No, no, great, great enemy.
I'm gonna get in there again
and I'm gonna kill you.
What happened?
Did I do it?
Skip the cutscene?
I can't skip the cutscene.
I wanna see what Ganon looks like.
Oh my God.
This is a whole fortress, guys.
What is aiming at me?
Okay, waterfall.
I gotta go this way.
Okay.
I wanna see the, no, I wanna see the map.
The other map.
How do I see the other map?
You missed it?
Wait, is it this one right here?
Right there?
That's the waterfall right there?
That's it?
No, not that one.
Oh, fuck.
Mods, help!
I don't know.
I'm gonna try that one.
That's not even a,
that's not a real waterfall.
You can't swim up that one.
Shit.
The bridge into the castle is south,
but I'm gonna try this water strategy.
I kinda like that.
Dude, that was a mist, not a waterfall.
Shit.
What's the?
Okay, so if I go this way,
there's a waterfall out here somewhere.
So like down to the left here, you mean.
Let me take a look.
There's a lot of bullshit over here.
I'm looking for a waterfall.
God damn it.
I don't, I don't know where,
I don't know where it is.
Oh my goodness.
That's a lot of shit.
A, right?
A?
Okay, got it, got it, got it.
I did it, I did it, I did it, I did it.
I got it.
Where?
What happened?
Okay, let me eat something.
I don't wanna eat everything now already.
This is it right here.
Give me up this waterfall so I can win this.
I was a stupid challenge.
Come on.
All right, now what?
Now what do I do?
What was the?
Where's my instructions?
Just go on this one?
More waterfalls, all the waterfalls.
Do all waterfalls now.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Got it, got it, got it, got it, got it.
Let's go.
Full stamina.
That was very ugly.
That was ugly.
Waterfall three.
What's that?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What do I do?
Just run in?
Just run, run in, run inside.
Oh my God, this really is right here.
No, no.
I'm right there, dude.
It's still possible.
We got, I got 20 minutes to beat this.
I didn't believe and neither did anybody else,
but I think I do believe now.
Where did this put me?
What did you just do?
Excuse me, what just happened?
What's going on here?
Waterfall again?
What's going on?
I don't remember this.
This is not where I just was.
Oh, yep, I remember.
Okay, I got it.
Okay, come on, here we go.
That's this, I got an idea.
I haven't been spotted yet.
That's fine, that's fine, fuck you.
Give a shit.
You can't give a shit.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
You can't be fucking serious.
Sad boy, suck it up.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I'm fine.
You know what?
I'm just gonna be a weirdo.
Wrong, I just pressed every single button on my controller.
All right, come on, Ganon, let's go.
What, I got 10 minutes?
Save it right here.
The Sanctum.
Did I actually just make it?
Oh, I'm killing him right now.
Let's go, I got 17 minutes to beat the game.
All right, I got bomb arrows.
It's a shitload of bomb arrows.
It's a bunch of heals.
Power-ups.
I have to change my armor too.
That's a good idea.
Good call.
Whoa, whoa, ow, loud.
Where did that come from?
This got so fucking loud.
That was loud as hell.
Jesus.
Dude, it's been this loud?
Has it really?
What?
I didn't realize it was that loud.
I turned it down.
It's been fine.
All right, here we go.
All right, so there's a giant spider.
Okay, there you are.
All right, bomb arrows right in the face.
Calamity Ganon, I'm ready.
Here we go, bomb arrows.
Gonna shoot 100 bomb arrows in his face at the same time.
No, it's my moment.
Each one of these is gonna take his health down by 25%.
If that's really what happens, I hope so.
Do it, get him.
Yes, one more.
All right, let's do it.
I'm just gonna shoot every bomb arrow I have.
I don't even wanna see what he has for moves.
I don't even care.
It actually is doing that.
Wow.
That's a pretty good, okay, it's 50%.
That was a great cleric beast.
How many bomb arrows do I have, like 40?
Okay, let's do it.
Save the game?
Can't.
Okay, I'm already dead.
Shoot.
Oh my God.
Okay, what do I have?
I have Heal somewhere.
Okay, I need this other armor on.
Where is it, right here?
Okay, and I also want these,
and that's fine, let's go.
What does that sound, Ganon?
I've got something for you.
And it's 24 bomb arrows right into your head.
How do you put on a new bow?
How do I put a new bow on?
What is, I don't wanna, what the fuck was that?
I'm doing, I'm holding right on the D-pad
and it was holding up.
This pro controller is a fucking piece of crap.
What the fuck are you doing?
What is happening?
Hold, this controller is actually fucking broken.
I forgot, Breath of the Wild has 80 inputs.
I forgot it has 800 inputs.
Hairs in my face.
I'm just gonna eat everything I have.
Now what?
Oh God.
All right, I can't hurt them,
I can't hurt them with that anymore.
Why do I not have a shield on?
What's the best shield in the whole game?
What's the best shield in the game?
This right here.
Why am I, why is the shield not,
guys, why is the shield not out?
What is happening in this game?
Go, go in.
Can I hurt that?
No.
Dude, I can't even, why am I crouching?
This game, I swear to God.
How do I, how do you stop crouching?
What is, why is there a crouch in the game?
I don't think, I've never pressed the crouch button.
How do I, how do I stop him from, how do I get him down?
Oh shit, I can't hurt him.
Okay, parry.
That didn't parry, what?
Why?
That looked perfect.
I don't know how to hurt him now.
I don't know how to hurt him.
He's made out of, like, he's made out of solidified shit.
I can't hurt him.
You have to parry.
Oh, I'm skipping this cutscene.
I got it.
I got it, I got it, I got time, I got time.
We got it.
Use that blue shield, it'll auto parry for you.
That's good to know.
I have all the bombs back,
but I have to put all my gear back on, don't I?
This will parry automatically, you mean?
I don't believe it.
Okay, hold on, let me get all my shit on here.
That and my bomb arrows.
Got it.
I don't even know if I got it.
What, did I?
It's hard to tell.
Is that still early?
I don't know how you fucking parry in this game.
All right, do it again.
Oh, let's go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Did I not get it?
Oh my God, my shield is broken.
Dude, you're breaking all, why is, ugh!
The parry, I feel like I don't, I don't get it.
You know what sucks too, is when you have the bow out,
and I got it right here, buddy.
Is that not hitting?
Yeah, shut up, game.
Do it again.
Come on, Gwen.
Oh, those don't, you can't parry those.
All right, come on, do it.
Fuck!
I did it, but it didn't reflect all the way.
My God, it's so hard, why?
I don't have a shield on?
Why is this game like this?
Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding me.
All right, do I not have armor on?
It's too late, I can get it right here.
I still got hit by it, shit.
It's gonna come down to literally seconds on the clock.
Shoot him, I can't, he's invincible.
Where is my character?
Why is the shield not out?
I don't get this game, half the time.
Oh my God.
All right, shoot me, shoot me, go!
Fuck you, motherfucker!
No!
Come here!
Do it again, quick!
Do it again, do it again, do it again!
No!
Yeah!
I did it!
With 30, with like 25 seconds to go.
Yes!
The answer is no.
Oh, there's a phase two, of course there is.
Shit, oh, that was so cool.
Can we just pretend that it was that?
Oh, I feel bad.
It was literally the save, fuck up.
Well, why is, you can't just save more frequently, hey?
Why do I have to make 10 fucking family dinners
and not get an auto-save?
You sit there, I sit there and cook for 15 straight minutes
and I don't get an auto-save?
10 restaurant style meals, that's right.
Uh-oh, okay.
This is probably gonna be hard.
There's Frank!
Frank, you've been there the whole time.
Come on, Frank, let's do it.
Is this like a dodge ball scenario,
like whoever gets to it first?
The bow of light.
Okay.
Oh, this is, all right, let's go.
Oh, come over here, come here, I need to get on.
Do I have infinite arrows?
All right, I have to shoot them.
In like, where?
Oh my God!
It's because A is not where I want it to be.
What the hell?
On the other side, I'm imagining, right?
Or no, shoot them?
Oh, I have to wait.
Too far away?
Stuck in a tree.
Okay.
Thanks everybody for watching
The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild.
The second that the boss's health goes to zero,
I'm uninstalling the game.
No, turn!
Frank, I, you know what, Frank?
I don't, remember B is A and A is B.
It's underneath him.
Get over here, come on, come on.
Over here, over here, quick.
I need you over here right now, please.
Look up there.
What am I looking at?
Oh, wow.
On his head.
I did it.
Hey, I beat the actual boss before the timer went out.
This is the,
would you consider this an extended cut scene?
I guess I technically did have to play it
and I did almost lose, so, true.
So how does this game leave Ganon?
That's what I'm curious about.
Damn.
Got him in a Ghostbuster trap, that's good.
Put him into the, put him into the generator.
We got him, all right.
Congrats from five years ago.
That's true.
Well, no.
A year and a half?
Time for Punch-Out?
Yeah, we'll move to Punch-Out.
How can you remember me?
Dun-dun-dun-dun.
The Legend of Zelda, Breath of the Wild.
Presented by Nintendo.
Dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun.
All right, I did it.
I beat Breath of the Wild.
I told you I would do it before the year was over.
My three hour estimate was very close, it was.
It just, it was a little bit of some fumbling
with the save system.
Is there an after credit scene or anything?
You had so much fun, didn't you?
Yeah, you had so much, I think, is that,
or I think the person's making a,
like a you didn't have fun joke.
It was all in just, no capitals, just,
yeah, you had so much fun.
I did.
I had fun.
I had fun playing Breath of the Wild.
It was fun.
I had fun.
I will not be playing Tears of the Kingdom.
It's not gonna happen.
It's not gonna play.
Just something that's not in the immediate cards right now.
And I'm just kidding, I have it installed right now.
And we're moving to it immediately.
That was also a lie.
I don't know where the truth is
in that last two sentences.
No, it was fun.
I wanted to play it.
I wanted to beat it.
Gave me an opportunity to actually see this game
for what it was, which was a great open world experience.
Tons of fun stuff to do.
Divine Beasts.
I have some complaints about the control scheme.
That's it.
I also have a few complaints about the,
this isn't, no, not add, what?
Somebody just wrote, laughing my ass off.
Like, oh, here it comes.
No, it was great.
I liked it.
I liked it a lot.
I'll give you something.
This is the first Zelda game I have completed
since Ocarina of Time.
This is the first Zelda game I have played truly,
actually since Ocarina of Time.
I don't really play Zelda games.
I'm not really into the franchise at all,
but this was really good.
I liked it a lot.
Is there an after credit scene?
Play Twilight Princess.
I can't play Twilight Princess
because it's chlorine eyes simulator.
Everything, every light I look at just has,
it's like I was swimming in a chlorine pool
for like an hour.
All right, cool.
Well, there's Breath of the Wild.
Should I press a button or anything?
I have heard Wind Waker is amazing.
Everybody recommends that game.
Maybe I'll play it.
I'm glad you beat it.
Me too.
Hey, I'll tell you though, these streams,
I think were some of the funnest streams.
I feel like there was a lot of fun times
on the Breath of the Wild streams.
Stressful a lot of times.
Yeah, but it was fun.
It's one of those games that just has a giant open world
with a bunch of funny stuff that can happen.
I love those games.
So I guess you could say I really liked it.
All right, now let me try to do the punch out thing.
See if I can do it.
Tears of the Kingdom is better in that aspect.
You know, it's funny because people have told me,
hey, I know you like Breath of the Wild,
but you'd like to see some things different in it.
That's Tears of the Kingdom.
So like is Tears of the Kingdom the Breath of the Wild
that I would have loved?
I guess is the question.
Not really, maybe, yeah, probably.
I think it really depends, right?
I guess it's possible I would play Tears of the Kingdom
and prefer Breath of the Wild.
Maybe, I don't know.
Some complaints remain and yeah, a lot of funny stuff.
That's cool.
All right, well, I'm ready to play punch out.
I promised I would beat Breath of the Wild.
That was not Tears of the Kingdom.
I know a lot of people may have been like,
what is he, why is he playing this game?
But yeah, finished it.
Hell yeah, I'm happy about it.
All right, now let me go pee
and then we're gonna come back
and do the punch out challenge.
I'll be right back.