Thank you for allowing me to hit people in the face with a pickaxe.
Probably recording right now, casual.
Indeed I was recording, indeed I was.
Hey hey, what is up guys, it's Jerma again with a gameplay commentary.
This time I am on Gold Rush defense on Gold Rush playing as the poly count pyro.
A lot of people ask for poly count and a lot of people ask me to do pyro gameplays,
especially when I did that video asking what you guys wanted to see.
A lot of the response was do pyro and do poly count.
So I figured, hey, why not kill two birds with one stone and do the poly count pyro.
So anyways, this is from the event that I had earlier today.
We were on a guy's, I think his name was Dispenser, that was his name.
It was his server. He was really concerned because I think there was only like two or three people in the server when we all flooded it.
And he was just like, uh, I don't know if my server can handle this.
But it did, it did. We had a good time.
I got a couple of gameplays from this particular event, but I'm going to just do one commentary today.
I'll probably get the other ones done either tomorrow or the next day, something like that.
But anyways, let's get into the gameplay.
The loadout for this match is going to be the Degreaser, the Flare Gun, and the Power Jack.
And watch this Jamps, Jamps is trying to come at me here and he's trying to taunt me with the melee kill.
So I say, you know what, whip out the Power Jack and shaboom!
Had a little bit of fraps lag there, but you saw what happened.
So anyways, he tries that the whole entire time, by the way.
It was his goal to try and melee kill me the entire time.
And I don't think he did it once, so we'll find out though.
I have only watched this gameplay once or twice, so I forget.
And I rage switch middle of the match to the shotgun because I can't get used to the Flare Gun.
Something about the arc and the drop off and the range and everything like that, I can't get used to.
I'm used to just whipping the shotgun out and pumping people full of lead.
Right here I'm just trying to massively spray back these rockets and try and get a lucky kill, but I don't.
And this is actually really cool.
I get this heavy lid on fire and I thought for sure that this was going to be a kill.
Boom, launch him in the air and boom, a crit!
But no, it doesn't kill him and I die.
But I do get an assist from the psycho crazy, not overpowered at all item called the Cow Mangler 5000.
And for just a second I would like to talk about the Cow Mangler 5000.
I'm not going to spend a whole lot of time on it, but I'm going to explain to you why I am very upset about Valve, what they did and why they did it.
Nobody else got any other items.
I know that on the forums and all over the place, all over the servers, people were saying,
no, no, no, no, no, the Engineer and the Pyro are definitely going to get items.
Is somebody else?
Why did they just give the Soldier more stuff?
The Soldier just got like a million items in the Uber update.
Why did they do this?
I am so annoyed.
And right there, sorry, I had to stop for a second.
Jamps was trying to come at me again and somebody just smoked him with the weapon I'm actually talking about.
So I don't know, I don't get it.
I don't understand why you add into a game something like that when you just gave him something.
They must be specifically trying to annoy people.
Either that or somebody gave me the idea, they said the Soldier is the most balanced class in the game, that it's really, really easy to give him items.
But I don't know.
I'm not going to talk about it anymore.
You guys already know how I feel about it.
But that's stupid that they didn't give anyone else anything, just the Soldier.
So now let's get back to the gameplay.
Peeking out around this corner, just trying to pick somebody off with one of the flare gun shots.
That's a Spy.
He gets destroyed by a Demoman's direct shot.
Just trying to get a flare gun into the spawn and this Soldier rocket jumps over here.
I get him lit on fire.
I don't get the kill though.
Trying to do that thing like I was doing before to that Heavy.
Launch somebody in the air and get him with the crit.
It's something I really want to learn how to do, but I just can't.
So I try to run away from this Heavy and he gets one little pellet on me before I go in the door.
And we're getting pretty close to when I rage switch over to the shotgun.
And you'll see how astronomically better I do when I use the shotgun.
So that Uber Heavy was a big, big advantage for them because now instead of it being one minute left and they're scrambling to get out of their spawn, they're now pushing to the second point.
And here is a great tip as a Pyro at these little choke point areas like this.
Look how many people are right here.
If I had reflected that rocket, if it didn't hit that Heavy in the back and I reflected it, I could have potentially killed like four people right there.
It's a great thing to do as a Pyro is just to suicide, run around a corner and just reflect.
And if you get lucky, you will kill everybody that's on the cart.
So just trying to get some flares up here.
I know there's a Sniper up there.
I'm trying just to get him with a little shot here.
And here comes Jamps again.
When I come around this corner, I kill a Soldier and you'll see.
So I get this Soldier.
I think it's an Assist.
Yeah, it's an Assist.
And then, oh, oh, oh, I thought he really was going to get me that time, but he didn't.
And I just died.
He was pissed about it.
He was yelling in the chat about it.
So he didn't get me.
You didn't get me, Jamps.
Not yet.
So you saw me just switch over to the shotgun.
At this point, I was like not messing around anymore.
It was time for me to start to do my duty and get like 10 kills in a row.
And it actually works out pretty well.
I love this setup.
The Degreaser and the Shotgun work well for me.
Most of my kills, believe it or not, are not with the Extinguisher.
I don't use the Extinguisher really that much.
Most of my kills are with the Shotgun.
My basic default setup for the Pyro is the Degreaser, the Shotgun,
and the Homewrecker, if you would believe.
That's my default Pyro setup, even on offense.
Offense.
I don't like using the Extinguisher.
If you've been around since I have my first videos, my first few videos,
you saw me try to use the Extinguisher and you probably laughed
because I can't use it that good.
So I turn this corner and shoot this scout in the face
and I know there's a teleporter up there and even though it doesn't really matter,
I'm so gung-ho on getting rid of it.
It really doesn't matter.
I could have killed so many people right here.
But no, I'm like, I have to get rid of this teleporter or we're going to lose.
But it's only like a 20-foot walk anyways.
I don't know what the hell I was thinking.
So this is where things get really good.
This is where I actually stop being a scrub and I start actually smoking people.
So I promise, oh, Spy, how are you?
How was your day?
Thank you for coming.
I promise now you'll get to see some shotgun kills, some good shotgun kills.
So me and this medic take a trip down memory lane over here.
We go across here.
There's a scout that comes down.
I pump him full of lead right here.
Here he is.
Flow him in the air.
Bang, you get killed with a shotgun shot.
That's one.
I got a little pocket medic here, pocket pyro medic, which is kind of funny.
We come back down to the same area.
I like this guy on fire.
He had low health anyways.
Don't even need to shoot him with a shotgun.
I get Ubered come out here.
I'm trying to get this guy over the corner with a few shots.
Boom, that's another shotgun kill.
And what do you know, reflect a dead, a dead ringer Spy.
I think that's what he was, but it doesn't matter.
Another shotgun kill right here.
That was Jamps again.
Come out here.
Hey, what's going on, sniper shotgun kill?
How you doing?
I don't know how I was not lighting this guy on fire.
Don't ask me how that was not happening.
Runaway time.
Here's their whole team.
And that's what I'm talking about.
That's my normal setup right there.
Bada bing, bada boom.
I'm not Italian, so don't even ask.
I just like saying that.
So this pyro just jumps down from heaven.
I thought he had no health because he's running away.
Turns out he had plenty of health and he gets me one more shot.
Would have done it too bad.
But you know what?
2020 hindsight, the modest Spy can't see health or a medic with a solemn bow.
Maybe one day they'll add something for the Pyro.
No, I'm not even going to pretend like that's a funny joke.
So it's under three minutes and they're getting on the cart here.
Just trying to cause a little bit of chaos.
I am no match for this heavy, so I jump away.
I go around the corner looking for a medic or something like that,
but there was not one around.
Now I'm covered in Girardi.
So just chilling out for a minute, trying to get some health back.
And look at that shot by Zack34.
I jumped in the air and he got a headshot.
It was awesome.
Nice job, Zack.
So here's another quick Pyro tip for those of you that are new.
The Pyro, as a class, is about causing chaos.
As I'm right here, watch this, ready?
Look at all these people I light on fire.
I don't necessarily kill any of them.
I get a couple assist kills, but I don't really kill any of them.
Don't be misled.
Your flamethrower is not meant to kill anyone.
The only time you should be concerned about killing somebody with a flamethrower
is if you have the backburner.
The regular default flamethrower and the degreaser are all about causing chaos
and then using your secondary or your melee to finish people off.
In that situation, see how I just ran in and kind of just got myself killed?
That's what's going to happen to you every single time you try to kill somebody
by spraying them or by trying to spray a group.
Always pull out your secondary after lighting them on fire,
especially if you're using the flare gun.
The flare gun crits people.
It does 90 damage to anyone that's on fire.
Here's another good example of being a good Pyro.
Watch what this guy's doing to me.
Right mouse button is your friend.
Look at this.
I can't do anything right now.
If you compression blast people, you can send them back flying
and they just get so disoriented that they can't do a damn thing.
See what I'm doing to this guy?
I was just confusing him so much by launching him in the air
and taking out my shotgun, shooting him, launching him in the air,
and he eventually dies.
This is a great kill right here.
I pull out the power jack.
This is like the second or third power jack kill I get.
The power jack, if you kill somebody with it, you just get 75 health.
You just instantly will get 75 health.
The downside is you take 20% more damage from melee when it's active.
Nice shotgun kill there.
This heavy medic pair I am no match for, so I go down instantly.
And one more little tip I can give you for the Pyro
before this gameplay ends is always spy check.
Always just spray every now.
You don't have to hold the mouse button down and run around in circles,
but you'll see what I do.
There's a sniper up here that I thought was a spy.
Just give us spritz here or there.
You'll see.
Ready?
Just like a whoop.
He's not a spy.
That's all it takes.
See, just little spritzes here and there.
You want to make sure that no one's going to get backstabbed
because people getting backstabbed is bad,
especially if this heavy medic pair got backstabbed.
We would not have been able to stuff these guys
into their little spawn area back here.
And I get Uber to end this gameplay.
It's actually pretty funny.
Get this heavy.
It takes forever.
See how long it just took me to kill him with the flamethrower?
That's what I was talking about before.
So Jamps is trying to get one more.
He's trying to get his revenge on me.
He's screaming over the mic.
And I end up killing him.
So sorry, Jamps.
You didn't get your revenge.
Thank you, everybody, for watching
and everybody for participating in the event.
They'll be more like these, so keep your eyes open.
And top frugen like a boost.
It's going to show up here any second here.
Top frugen like a boost.
And thanks for watching, guys.
I really appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys next time.
Take care.