okay uh this is a little loud so i'll turn it down uh horde announcer should i put that on
what does that mean horde announcer is my obs about to crash don't do it to me don't do it to me
don't you dare don't you do it oh thank god all right uh horde announcer resolution is fine right
1920 by 1080 that's good borderless yeah 1920 by 1080 that's the one uh resolution scale this is
probably fov that's got to change oh no no no 90 uh 92 92 sounds good to me uh movement bob nope
autorun that's fine uh strafe tilting what does that mean strafe tiltings i don't know what that is
uh hud scale that's probably fine all right we'll take a look quest codex this is by the same company
that published dusk same uh group of people i guess let's do quest main campaign hordes of evil
uh let's do main campaign all right
it came from the age beyond the ages the space beyond vision wheeling in an abyss of infinite
darkness a myriad vast ones that was a medieval game i think it is now pick up this gun with mouse
scroll all right hold on speaking of mouse scroll this looks pretty fucking awesome uh input
sensitivity let's bring this down to like 15 uh what what is going on here uh why why is it left
and right different up and down lock to respect lock to aspect oh that doesn't matter to
all right so uh i got i got an axe
so i got infinite health how does the movement work pretty cool gateway of the ancients
gateway of the ancients all right let's go
i might have to lower it a little bit more
easy difficulty less enemies more pickups uh no medium difficulty normal enemies and pickups
pickups hard more enemies normal pickups all right i'll do hard i was a little loud
all right here we go let's do uh how hard is hard i wonder let's do it it's quite hard okay
he's gonna kill me yeah well i missed you are not worthy turn back best lose the game
huh can i just jump across no all right you have to you have to actually you have to jump like
twice not worthy you go very fast in this game this is a this is a long call away from the thing
i was just doing oh man you the momentum is so fast this is like walking your grandmother across
a fucking road and then now you have to fly an airplane by the way walking your grandmother
across the road takes an hour and a half can i get up here oh i see or do i see no am i just not
worthy right now i see okay he lost 200 viewers coming off of a hand simulator
it's all right whatever evil has overrun our sacred lands free them visit the two worlds to
proceed travel to astral equinox to pass this gate all right it's kind of like an open environment
where i can go wherever what's up here i see return to difficulty selection i don't want to
do that should just jump over oh no fall off god damn it i shouldn't have even walked grandma
across the street i should have called an uber for grandma then this would now i should have just
started with this instead of walking grandma across the street for a fucking hour it's actually
pretty tricky damn the fucking forward momentum is so much okay so where do i go this doesn't open
over here portal to ab this is where we're going all right press tab for portal though that would
be nice domain of the sentinels astral equinox which is going to go here all right autosave
stronghold this is not like a the guy's going to fall off and he fell off the edge joke right
i don't think so please me to drop down is this a is this a fall off the edge like joke thing
left like you know laugh secret area i have mana is gonna kill me no all right there we go
okay well i'm getting my ass kicked what's the range on this thing
thing picked up a tiny soul increase the fov should i do that where is it game
auto run input where is it hud i have to like sit i have to like go five feet back from my in
my on my desk to see it video down here for no that's frame limit actually by the way
red set fov right here okay anything more than 95 will make me probably throw up
i'll i'll stretch right 95 yeah that's kind of pushing it already all right what's health
these red globes press tab to see levels stats i have an 80 secrets 109 time okay
uh time get off the screen and go over 100 health from these sacred waters the azure orb was formed
oh shit it's ranged doesn't hit the sick mana that is kind of cool the way forward
the way forward lies ball i can't read this font both left and right okay you need the gold key
you need the silver key let's go over here oh my god i'm getting overwhelmed
oh i feel like i'm gonna throw up i'm not kidding it's like the screen flashes on can
they turn those off i really think i'm gonna puke oh where is it soul glow is that it cross
his stuff show crosshair and that's fine hud scale that's kind of big just do this
can i do that help so that's i what do you mean blind i i i asked if it was soul glow
and everyone said yes show crosshair screen i swear to god it's hard to read this font
it's like a different language oh that's so much better okay now i can actually pay attention
what do you guys want me to do now go to video turn down the fov message size
i feel like there's a lot you have to do to get this to be at a decent viewable state
alternative message font v sync fraile alt anti where is it is it a hud alternative message font
yeah it doesn't change the menu though bring the soul glow on should i this looks like a different
enemy yes just go back to hand simulator maybe i should take out the axes you have a lot of
health all right there's the gold key these have a little bit of homing on them don't they
they do all right gold key was back down here where was it it's the same kind of system as
dusk huh i didn't get a gold key right and then you go here plus alt fire to engage soul power
holy shit uh how long is this last picked a medium green mana me but okay what was that
thing that i just picked up i'm gonna i'm almost dead souls are hard to see because you turn the
glow off i'm gonna try it is there a quick save i feel like i'm gonna i'm i had one save point and
i'm fucking terrified i gotta use it what is it f6 let's do a hard save here uh new save let's see
input change bindings crouch is c run is left ship but it's toggling walk
move forward wsd yeah yeah next weapon mouse wheel quick save f5 okay axe is one so i'm sure
there's probably a reason why you wouldn't use the stick versus the axe fire upon the red run
yes i will save axe oh fuck i'm dead does he walk does he come down here
i feel like this is gonna do a lot of damage but i'm scared i don't know how much damage
he's doing that does a lot there there's a silver key and uh you picked up a huge soul in a mod
what are the souls what are the souls for push that and bring that back up here wait was there
another door or anything souls for the rapid fire thing okay all right let's go whoa he's still live
is he blocking the shit all right motherfucker let's go
uh oh got him these things that these things are throwing grenades at me
uh all right it's quick save let's go can i make this jump it's down there uh let's go this way
first that's kind of cool holy fuck there's a lot of people couldn't even get the help
i feel like this is better for these guys yeah it is by a lot all right big guy still up there
i'm maxing the big guy he's dead all right easy use the whisper's edge wisely may strike many
foes at once so we can go through people should i go that way maybe i should go that way it's
probably a key um no no jump off the cliff oh all right i see what you're trying to do here
you're trying to kill me i have a lot of mana what should i use it for pick up press alt okay
soul power not yet not yet not yet not yet go back back back back back back this thing
does soul power do anything with the axe too i'm sure it does yeah man that is just
ammos and these take different types of okay i see cool pretty sick oh shoot this are there
bosses in this game are there oh fuck oh fuck this is a different guy what's not what's this
oh i this thing i activated all right use soul power not yet hold on platform to bastion of the
blue moon can you alt fire alt firing does uh the super move oh what was that it was what the
fuck was on the ceiling you guys remember when he was walking his grandma i do bastion of the blue
moon let's go eight and a nine secrets phone not quite is it there's no bunny hopping in this i
don't think there is it doesn't look like it i like the soul power of this why even use any other
weapon it's dusk without gum uh sort of all right don't just blow through everything i need to be
able to i need to see what i'm doing oh what's this the other weapon soul power is a good too
saved
okay that's pretty good oh are we doing like a wand battle okay it's blocked it does block it
what skyrim mod is this it's called uh into the into the abyss 1.1 what was that
that is almost quick saved up into the softlock
so
what the fuck was next to me all right don't don't don't don't don't don't slow down
all right i gotta i have a question i have a question is it like pokemon do do green enemies
take more damage from something else does red enemies take more damage from blue or it does
not enough because i have red green blue does it matter you can enslave them in a cube
what wait hell can i jump to this what do you guys think
good yeah this is this is like magician dust doesn't seem to be a health cap oh
the levels are stranded together so yes this is a strand game
oh
why why strand game
damn it i took way too many hits all right let me but i want to try out the super move for this
not yet it's gonna be more than one person
engage the soul power eventually i will definitely what look can't pick this up what's the big cube
for there's a huge cube over there there's a fucking huge cube do i have full mana yeah i do
oh okay it looks like 250s max for everything probably yeah probably yep maybe yeah all right
i'm going for it fuck this is pretty cool um they just bounce around secret turn it off turn it off
turn it off i like the one the best so far it reminds me of arcane missiles in world of warcraft
minus two minds if i say to the minus two i will delete you oh my god those who those who would
worship the sun are blind those who would worship the sun no don't do it i was gonna i was gonna say
i walked i walked grandma across the street for an hour and a half earlier so i can i
i gotta start to pull this back together do i have a soul thing yet
there's the throne grenades all right i'm going this way oh fuck oh never mind never mind never
mind give me this i wish i had it now oh you motherfuckers get over here all right i got it
back so do the axis time let me see what the axis power is what's that somebody's like flying
around over there i got the gold key don't remember anybody for the gold doors i don't
where's the gold door i don't know down here was it back down this way this isn't gonna kill me
isn't it if i drop from here this will hurt how bad will it hurt uh not terribly all right gold
door did i go this way yet yeah was it back in here this is the those who were worshiped the sun
you have to memorize doors again where was it i feel like we have to go back that far this
gold door gold door gold door gold door gold door not a gold door but some secret i guess
okay not that way shit where's this thing is it up there gold looking for gold looking for gold
oh get off screen back to hand simulator door all right that looks like something i haven't seen
gold ore gold ore where's gold ore well i found green door more obvious than i'm this is water
uh if i've been down here did i looked at it what into the water there it is that's a that's
gold right gold right three two one go you just turn into a meat grinder this is ridiculous you
gotta get close to people though i'm not sure i like it come on hit them hit them with something
need a green door you still want
all right now what was the game's name uh it's called green door g-r-e-e-n-d-o-a-r
sneak out oh this is where you how you get over here cool let me just keep using the best item in
the game juke found the door juke i found the door did you find it nice dude did you actually find
it it's fucking sick nice work but you could be lying you might be lying to me though you
did you find it i don't know i don't know man you might be lying to me
oh now where now now what am i going now where do i go where do i go where do i go
oh shit i hate this he hates it no not that kind of hate okay anything else in here besides this
all right all right passes to the vaults of midnight okay cool okay very cool new weapon
torch power up sit but no no no no no no go back down this is gonna kill me i just jumped at the
wrong time okay what is down here is that a pitchfork oh shit i've all tried secret power
reveals with overkill oh this is fun no no no no no no no no no damn it i didn't mean the right
click that's really cool fuck where's the elevator it's all good it's all right it's all right you
get it back really quickly now we can leave the game right it's the end of the level one secret
it's all right devs here really what's up they chained together that's pretty cool i like it but
not as much as i like this weapon he's playing your game terribly no no no no let's let the
devs of green door be able to tell us what they think you don't have to put words in their mouth
there's beside the stuff die die die die die die die die die die what does it say our leader
guardian of the moon he now dreams of death and pain all right hold on all right pay attention pay
attention pay attention pay attention i don't want to fuck myself zap him chain him guy comes
up not that effective sword actually i think is pretty effective uh guys is there any leveling up
in this game what's this say
it says uh midnight moonlight not today i'm gonna get over there uh
imagine having the scroll wheel as a game i have to get in here just go go go go go go go go go go
go go go go kill go go kill wait don't touch that i'm gonna activate super machine gun
now grab this oh i got it twice see i timed it unlimited zap he wants to play hand simulator
i do no i do you're not wrong but playing hand simulator gets the same reaction
as to if i took a dump on my desk on camera it would be the same you you could like open
up the chat and it would be the same thing oh what oh get this out of here what the fuck
report of the sock for disgusting get rid of them how do i go how about this way
what is this the grenade launcher this is like a okay this is i don't know don't use a planet
launcher they only have 15 bullets how do i get up there i need something with mana this shit
evil evil evil oh boy get off which way you going 10 community subs just came in from
a wild meryl thank you wild meryl thanks for the subs and uh grats to everybody that just got one
wait don't leave yet what do we got here okay cool cool cool cool cool cool
what does that do that open up the middle portion too hard to get sneakies in there
all right get that what does that do i missed shit what does it have to be one of the balls
oh damn it oh damn it that's a health orb oh okay i don't know i just want to see if you know
full blue mana nice i'll take out the electricity
okay full mana empty brain
by the moon i feel worried you're good you're good what's that secret
is the stream title innuendo what is the stream title oh it's still something about hand simulator
chilling out with my hands right right okay that doesn't make any sense well i guess it sort of
does like i'm i guess i am i don't know it's too late to change it now is there a torch upgrade
bounce the shit around everywhere that'll hit somebody now we
need light light light light please oh i think it has activated something wait all right i'm
just gonna go up wait for the planet gun which i haven't even used once let's try it
it's pretty great actually absolutely worth using never only when i'm in danger
was this nothing i'm not using the melee at all i don't feel like i shouldn't even have to
don't get killed don't get killed now don't get killed bingo how loud do you think i can
say without actually screaming like not like no no not like no like without actually screaming
screaming i could probably go pretty loud all right i'm going back this way that just now is
not screaming yeah that's what i'm saying keep going up forward homing missile time
bing sellout stream bing when was the last time you guys opened up uh google to use bing or no
not google that's on a web browser when was the last time you opened up bing you've never even
opened it yes you have you've at least opened bing to see what it was all about i have it's better
i'm not even gonna read that it's not uh i i can't read what you just said please forgive me this
this game's pretty fun i'm only here for the loud bingo well put on a seatbelt there's gonna be a
while ten community ten community ten community ten community ten community ten community ten
community subs from nearshrew thank you ten community subs from nearshrew there's been a
lot of ten sub drops today ten community subs ten thank you seriously all right uh looking for
silver door is that a silver door help me guys that's not a silver door you lied to me
our leader the guardian what it's opening slowly what are you what the heck
oh i did it one i'll always get one secret it's fine that was so condescending no it wasn't meant
to be condescending it was meant i'm just saying words it's not not meant to be condescending i'm
just saying words i'm just talking this is a uh boss room this is definitely a boss room
no way it's not a boss room i will eat fucking dinner tonight if this is a not a boss room
and i will whatever you know what i'm saying i knew it moon guardian here we go on camera
nope watch out for this spinning ow i didn't save it i have to win how much damage got it
17 health oh got it what the fuck i'm so fucking mad right now i'm seriously fucking so pissed
off that boss took me five to ten tries to beat and he did it in one try i'm so fucking pissed off
right now you know how many times i've actually seen that message at least like five times what
the fuck fuck this he just beat that boss it took me like an hour to beat that guy fuck this stream
i'm out of here touch it you've never seen that yes i have oh i sealed the uh ceiling okay cool
uh more than minus two doesn't count so sorry it does not work i didn't get a secret here
what was it don't ever do that again i'll make sure to do that five to ten more times before
i die i'm gonna be don't ever do that i'm gonna be on my deathbed i'm gonna be fucking i'm gonna
be 97 years old i'm on my deathbed and i'm gonna just fucking go lean into all my loved ones and go
it's the last thing i'm gonna do before i press tab for poor we did that so now we can do this
this one it was gonna open right if we did portal to the domain of the sentinels
oh we start over again huh okay makes sense it's like that way in dusk too isn't it oh
oh damn you take a lot of hits give me that give me that oh these guys are
gonna come alive aren't they small green small green small green small green small green okay
who's left anybody in there am i using using cheats what are you talking about
this is gonna be a miserable failure wait this is the silver door what's up here gold door up this way
all right here we go time to lose is there a way i can sneak in there
are they getting crushed i think they are good back up to the silver focusing cream ice cream
that's pretty good i like that stuff
oh you hurt a lot where are you is that you over there nope
almost have i got 61 health fuck somebody else up there okay what's over there
anyway that's me okay why are there people over there
all right i open them i'm gonna say you start using the axe which i don't want to do
oh fuck all right i gotta speed moving that guy is still alive up there
who's left he's left he's left he's left up there no no
you're in a smoke weed what are you guys talking about in here
can i jump no uh what is this doing no oh all right i know okay i got it i got it
fuck i thought i hadn't i'm so confident one at a time all right wait i can't even do one at a time
i have to go and like now again just came out of there what is in there uh i don't think
i guess nothing come through this way the button to press and here comes the enemies i think
i think it was an elevator don't kill me this brings me back up here through the glass
okay well i have the electricity gun now did i get a key did anyone remember if i got a key
i don't think i did not yet at least that's a lot let's be still dead let's stay alive ow
uh that's gonna open what is that i don't like this room this is a new weapon what is a crystal
star of torment oh i actually like this what was that uh holy shit this thing's amazing
damn this is great this might be better than the um what's it super move i wonder let's try it
so we got anybody bounce some shit around all right i gotta slow down how are my bones
uh they're all right well actually that might not even be true
not even be true what did i just do the head bones well i might have costochondritis
which is my ribs are fucked up and my like cartilage in my ribs is inflamed
well that sucks but you know whatever perfection is power order is perfection uh i just opened
something here didn't i secret area i guess that's what i opened or is there something i can do here
what's going on no i'm not just looking down in this area wait a minute i went all the way around
this is a dream please wake up no i have a fucking hernia and they also think i have fucking
costochondritis which essentially is your rib bones it's just like your rib cage just hurts
which is that's pretty much what it is that's pretty much it this testicle goes up into your
stomach uh you need you need to read a few medicine books that's not what that is by the way
what the fuck am i going i remember i pressed a button here where am i going i don't think i've
been over this way well there we go all right well wait wait wait wait let me on let me on
do i just keep moving fast i think probably all right i did it i gotta switch this is the best
weapon in the game it kills them instantly one hit on these guys and they're dead 120 120 130
130 140 140 120 120 all right i'm gonna i got 20 of these shots what's next under the button
oh no uh another elevator tumeric yeah i've kind of been on that train tumeric tease depending on
if that's really what's going on i might have to go get like an injection i've looked up a bunch
of stuff that trust me in the last three or four days has been pretty much only me looking up what
the fuck any of this stuff even means rejection not necessarily no no oh my god who's left
sequence complete all right wait don't leave anything behind here oh that was it 50 of the
secrets completed is the bitrate suffering this is the way that the game is encoded into this into
twitch let me see what's what's it going on right now yeah i'm at six six thousand up i think it
just looks like that yeah it just looks like that this game is 3d yeah i know it's pretty good
thanks a lot Jeremy now i have boomer eyes if we are right trust me do you even trust me
does anybody in this chat actually trust me do you trust me all right so if we if we were
doing an experiment where i stood behind you and you had to close your eyes and put your hands
across your chest and fall backwards and i catch you do you think i would catch you
well i would okay think about it and then i would make a decision how do i get this to go down
oh shit chaos begets destruction sure did i get him got him too all right i'm gonna go up
right i'm gonna have to jump around nice dog safer to fall forward yeah but that's not the whole
point of the test is to see if you trust me that i will catch you if you fall backwards
why would it actually be safer if you fell forward what if you didn't get caught you'd
smash your fucking mouth on the ground it's either lose all your teeth or
smash the back of your head what's worse please just hit me oh fuck i'm gonna die
no no no no no no no no no no not fall damage i'm fine i need help oh fuck you
you there's two of these motherfuckers help please thank you i can't reach this
oh please yes i can all right we're good for now through through through through you
what are your dicks i bet you have a severe case of gamer neck right now
no i have to be aware of my gamer neck oh boy what do i do here what do i do here
i'm gonna use fuck i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead oh no when was last time i saved i don't know
i have no idea it's been a while i think you know i actually i really do have to be aware of my
foster and stuff because the more strain i put on my rib cage the worse this can get
i'm so scared these guys they don't have very much health save it here but i'll tell you it's been a
real pain in the ass so hopefully over the next few weeks or a couple months or so
i'll start to figure out ways to alleviate it because damn is really irritating just having
like a painful all of your ribs just hurt every day like that sucks that's not cool
originally we thought it was something to do with my intestinal problems but no
apparently not easy okay one more one more where where where where where is that good
i think so all right save it somebody fill me on him when he's talking about
uh all right we'll go we'll break it down a little here all right so like a year ago
i started to get this weird like back pain it was on the right side of my back and it was kind of
flanking around the right side of my abdomen what's wrong obviously he went to the doctor
well i don't know and then my like stomach started to hurt my chest started to hurt too
like my sternum so my whole abdomen and wrapping around the right side of my back
just fucking just was hurting all the time i couldn't do anything about it i never turned off
it never got worse and it never got better so we did colonoscopy maybe it's something to do with
your uh colitis you have like you've had a irritable bowel disease for pretty much the last 12 years
maybe it's that nope that's doing just fine well as fine as that can be doing right all right well
let's try this is test for this test for that test test test test test test test test test
and then i had a this is three days ago i had an upper endoscopy done with a look at my stomach
and everything and they said i you have a hernia so it's number one that might be causing it and
then number two um i think you have this i think it's rib cage i'm like all right you think it's
my rib cage you sure give me some evidence and he said i don't i don't have any i'm not a doctor
we're in my garage right now
and i went oh right right right you're larry kate the hernia is gonna fuck you up pretty bad
hopefully the rib fucks are false alarm yeah so that just sucks because the if you have a high
over you your mind's apparently not that bad but it doesn't go away event you just have to like keep
manage it and keep an eye on it and like change your lifestyle a little bit health more healthy
eating don't eat before bed and you have to have surgery you have to have like laryngoscopic
surgery like the damn thing so it's annoying but the it's apparently it's not that serious
it's just kind of pretty much it i feel like the i know they did it you had a hernia before and
they were fucking painful yeah it's just how do i get that but i'm not certain about i mean i'm
certain obviously they did an endoscopy you have a hernia it's like that's the clearest thing
and the rib cage thing would make sense it just would it just would oh whatever i'm just gonna
just keep doing keep whatever keep going figure it out is manage it what do i need to do let's
do that fine all right they feel like it sometimes give me the key creek as you breathe
like if i lean back and i put my fingers like on my sternum and i like kind of lean back and
pull all this i'm just kind of following me it's just like oh and i have said to random
doctors before you know if i just like could pull pick up my rib cage and like pull it apart by like
10 i feel like my whole problem would go away i've said that out loud before so it i don't know
maybe it's pressure and inflammation in the rib cage i don't know i'm not a doctor i have the key
now silver key was back here it was down or was it i remember seeing it i remember looking at it
and the doctor goes well no no jeremy that's not that's not a good idea
can you spawn in place i'd like to not use where are you who where the fuck are you
that's what i want to do that oh it's so precise but oh it's so got it i remember initially this
this is the okay a lot of you guys can probably relate to this i'm sure i'm sure most people can
relate to this but when this all started it's like you know when you're like certain of something
and you like this has to like i thought i thought i thought i had lime to be completely up front
which is like i read a you know test me for lime you don't have lime fuck well what is wrong with
me then i think i might have a bacterial infection check it nope you don't fuck what do you think i
have we can test for this too maybe you have uh this uh inflammatory arthritis disease all right
do it please is this it nope what the fuck is going on it turns out my stomach is pushing up
into my diaphragm in my uh hyoidal esophageal area that's problem number one unfortunately
this surgery is the only way to get rid of it and it's mine's apparently not bad enough to have
surgery on so fuck so now what now what do you do you just have to i don't know you just have to
keep doing whatever you're doing to try to figure out what the fuck is wrong with you
i need health that's most important the human body sucks yeah one of you is going to replace
all of my like our parts i want to go to a car mechanic for me to get like a new rib cage
just let me lie on my back put me on one of those things that lift you all the way up into the air
at the car mechanic and just look under there and open up my back because there'll be a panel back
there and power me down and then just start replacing stuff it's gonna open here that he's
a new engine imagine we ran imagine we ran on gasoline you just chug gasoline you went to the
tank instead of your car you just like put your mouth in the nozzle and just like we run on food
yeah but i mean if you had like an engine in your body you need to pull your cord like five times
to like start again how loud would the world be i'm talking like
it would be horrible that's all you'd be it would be like a swarm of bees everywhere in every single
neighborhood in every single spot gold key for this everything would stink yeah it would everything
would be it would smell like gasoline everywhere you'd have to yeah you mute on your ear yeah you
no not mute on your ears your ears are still your ears you're just running gas
you wouldn't be able to ever have a phone call but we wouldn't even need phone calls because
at that point you'd just be communicating through your brain i don't know like whatever facebook is
in a hundred years nothing else this is key gold key gold key gold key up there found it how do i
get up there how do i get up there how do i get up there how do i get up here
shit how do i get up there a little bridge over here oh come on i heard you somebody invisible
no give me up there speaking of hearing things uh i like i think i just heard auto bark he might
need to i might need to take care of him i need to let him out or something can i actually rock
no no wait wait wait wait there i'm gonna cross this way this was the actual way
yeah i found it all right cool what's this purple mana do i even have anything purple
i don't think i have anything purple oh shit
oh i utilize utilize utilize
whoa i'm going so fast why do these games have a tip wiggle when you move left and right
realism let's get that key which is this way i almost fell off easy easy easy hey
well i guess we're going down save it here oh shit our reality is the truth whatever you say
show auto show auto our truth is all jesus three swings three auto autos
i was just hanging out on the stairs all right all right all right let me let me go home let me go
let me go free auto i'm gonna see what else i will be right back give me two seconds
you know go get yourself a snack he was saying feed me time for him to eat pretty much anyway so
feed auto yeah he's nice at bed okay where the hell was i going what was i doing
did they get a key i did what did you feed him he's dog food dog food ouch all right hold on
do i have things shit i eat that oh dog food good that's what i had today too
what the fuck why all has its place i need to i gotta change uh i gotta change weapons
oh what kind of dog food do you give them that's my favorite
i don't what is you guys want to know what auto's dog food is okay all right i didn't know this is
some some big thing we needed to know auto eats blue buffalo the chicken and brown rice formula
that's his favorite i think this is gonna be something that comes out of the store
oh wait is it chicken and rice or is it no no wait no it's not is it maybe it's sweet potato
it's the blue bag i'm gonna use my super move where is it number is it five it's five okay
50 of these fucking things chicken and rice okay yeah i got it right uh so up there i guess
i'm going up there doesn't even know his dog's favorite food i do i do all right how do we
this button i gotta press somewhere i saw it where was it
shit oh i gotta step on one of those buttons damn it i saw it too i know where i saw it where was
it it was one of these buttons shit there it is all has its place pressed the blue button blue
button low more than more than two hits bullshit oh i'm so sorry zero secrets i might as well
fucking just never stream again thank god you stopped playing the hand game that was a long
time ago that was at least like an hour and 40 minutes ago hand simulator but remember
this is an extra stream this week this doesn't count this is not an actual spring this is a
fake stream because tomorrow joel and i are gonna play halo reach and then after that
it's gonna be another co-op experience this is like the week of co-op and hand simulator i had to
look i know a lot of people are gonna say do what i said but i had to play that month i had to
i do you know how long i've had hand simulator for in my steam inventory since 2016
i had to play it and i'm not playing that by myself you didn't have to at all nobody forced
you to play it i did i forced myself to play it once because i needed to know there's so
many talks so much talk about how fucking fun it is and how funny and cool it is i had to try it
and there was my one opportunity the secret stream that's not a stream is the perfect opportunity
for that you think i'm gonna use a real stream for that game come on come on more more more more
more where are they there's another full one here what's the other co-op game uh we're gonna try
to play the game called tools up just came out today it's local only but we're gonna try to
use that steam remote play thing we're gonna test and see if that thing works it's the plan
i want to use let's try this okay that's pretty cool but i feel like i'm wasting it anybody have
any experience with the uh the steam remote play does it actually work it works but it could be a
little weird no okay how so it's all right won't you get horrendous ping um i don't think so because
it's gonna be me star and then probably talus and talus and i have the same so i don't think it'll
be an issue a game called tools up okay uh it's like star was telling me earlier and this is i
don't know he's a he's a salty bastard isn't he look at how salty this is he said it reminds
cleanup detail but an actual video game and i was like god that's salty it's true but that's not
even that's salty i don't think i've ever met anybody that hated this ever clean up detail
you know what i'm saying like he hated it he just didn't like it is that impossible is it possible
to not like this for cleanup detail i feel like that's saying super mario sucks
it's like you can't i think that you can't that's not true tomorrow is cool like you would never
find yourself saying i hope super mario gets hit by a bus would you you would never find
yourself saying that would you what's this uh holy shit it kills everything instantly on the screen
i love this or clean up detail it's like the best game
game shit well i wait you know i wish every game was mr clean up detail in fact i should
play mr clean up detail like the next week or something because i like it so much why aren't
i i don't know because i played hand simulator instead what do you mean right now no i'm not
yet hold on i'm i'm playing a medieval no i can't play that right now because i'll get stuck for
like seven more hours do it now what hold on hold on relax i want to fight another boss oh man
guys did okay did i just show you all the christmas presents in the closet like i said oh hey hey hey
hey little little johnny come here for a second right see this is where uh this is where your
mom and dad and i we keep your presence here oh yeah open book and then close it real quick
so you know i've been like a ps4 in there there might have been like a spongebob characters you
might just glimpsed it and i close it and i say no you can't you can't go in there did i just do
that ps4 in 2019 yeah what a deal it's like 116 dollars i don't know how much is a ps4 now
how much is a ps4 right now like 112 bucks
hole or riot hole or riot guys are we actually going to do the coveted three games in one screen
is that going to happen just let me get to another boss yeah fight yeah i'm going to fight the boss
detail am i really going to switch to viscera clean up detail it is a ps4 because you guys have
already played the ps4 somebody said lul ps4 in 2019 i'm gonna play viscera clean they can't
came out like six years ago so you are playing the ps4 you are getting the ps4 for christmas
oh no another one of these didn't i already do that i'm so confused right now what happened
where am i do i have the gold key i have the gold key right i have no idea i'm not playing
viscera is like choke slamming us off a hell in a cell what the fuck are you talking about
i need to focus it was up here right okay i will tell you though i have i have something coming
that i'm going to use may might not be tomorrow or the next day maybe i have a device that i
cannot wait to play with on stream it's it'll be here soon i don't know exactly what you're
gonna see it but you'll see it as a device and it is the coolest fucking device i think i've ever
seen if it works i don't know if it's gonna work or not stone unhewn has no purpose
jeez you say the word device and all of a sudden i gotta get the bread and butter out here no where
is it no actually no actually this yeah i'm not even gonna i'm gonna it's gonna be a surprise
he just gets gonna appear by the way it's gonna be on camp so boss no good take a lot of damage
back up you have the remote control thing from adam sandler no i don't have the remote control
thing from adam sandler everybody talks a lot of shit about adam sandler and if i know at least
at least a thousand of you liked that movie you were about to say none and then you squished
your face and you got wicked red two more to go i probably shouldn't be doing this
you've never seen him adam sandler movie how's that possible he's made like 60 you've never
accidentally just stumbled upon one just on tv one day what did that do what do you mean tv
oh my goodness this is bad i might just no fall damage good i'm stuck
oh not good not good not good not good not good it's gonna die for the second time only tonight
in this game not everybody has a tv i mean did you have a tv before you come down let's go
come down did i just hit one person with that wait a minute wait a minute how is that possible
don't chain it dead not just kill me i've wasted too much health points
give me the thing that i like to use no no this if you don't get hit you don't die
what kind of concept is that the dev said you stink drop you drop wait this health
all right drop one at a time focus on no no no fucking one hd man one all right where's those
heels no i need i need health this can't this can't work without health not playing viscera
is equal to you slamming my head into a glass table 32 times do my face is a bloody bruised
pulp please stop jesus christ why did i read that i don't know it was there as available
what map have i not done all right can this please come down i'm afraid to hit f5
what did i miss up here you play games like i use the bathroom very messily
uh that's a that's like a dig on you not me okay there's health over here it should be okay
now press the button which activated another thing the projectiles are way better than mine
in fact give me this give me the sword
ah they're raining hell i'm gonna be dead i'm not sure if you see me yeah no that's
hitting it's hitting somebody died got it all right five let's jump and then jump no i can't
hit this uh see you love watching germa 985 while balancing chemical equations
it's good luck on your history homework that you're going to do next because you're not doing
that now did it damn it i tried to make everybody laugh no secrets you are terrible no secrets
you're not even good no secrets get out of here no secrets stupid no secrets play viscera cleanup
no secrets this is the boss level damn it oh no it is okay it's called the
yeah i did it i did it i did it i did it i did it i did it i did it you didn't do it
because i fucking did it secret where viscera cleanup wait just wait a second
geez what's the secret mr clean up i'm not sure i still have the game installed just give me a
moment we're going for the try stream well the first game doesn't count i agree but but who cares
i feel like i'm missing something people are gonna laugh at me when i don't get 100
percent oh well okay oh they're three secrets in this level you gotta be kidding me
that seems like a lot killer award for killing all enemies yeah this is kind of this this game's fun
i like this game champion this is level three portals so this is how many portals have i done
two i got one two three four more four portals three portals something like that viscera all
right hold on