Good afternoon. What's up? We're playing a video game today. We're playing Scribblenauts today.
Yep, I know a ton of people just freaked out. This is some of your favorite- some of you guys'
favorite video game. I know that for a fact. You know, it's been- it's been plenty of people over
the- uh, probably the last few years that have said, dude, please, you would- Scribblenauts is so much
fun. You would love it. Play it. Do it. Play it, motherfucker. Play the fucking game I want you.
I'm like, all right, maybe. And today we're gonna play it. We had some- I'm very early, yes. I was
up early today. I just was like, you know, I'm- I'm ready. I'm ready to go. Let's go. I'm gonna start
like an hour or two from now, but I decided to pull it back. He was up at 5 a.m. Yeah. I was up- I
was up at 5 o'clock in the morning reading my favorite newspaper, Pre-Stream Chat. You guys know
that I use Pre-Stream Chat as my morning coffee routine? You guys are way funnier than Garfield,
and you're way more interesting than Dilbert. I was like, the crazy shit- you can't say half
the crazy shit you guys say. I'm like, a foxtrot? Garfield rules. I mean, I don't hate Garfield,
I just- Pre-Stream Chat is more interesting. Okay, would you rather watch Garfield eat a lasagna
or watch 400 people yell at each other over the game that we're going to play today? I just sit
here and I'm like, oh, this is gonna be good. Revolt. Revolt. Can you write the debt out?
And what do you- I don't know what you mean. It's our amusement. He's using us for his amusement.
But we're gonna play Scribblenauts. I actually- I played? I don't think I've ever played
Scribblenauts. I played the other one, the DS, like 10 years ago, 15 years ago.
There was one- what came out on DS? Drawn to Life. I think that's the one that I played.
But I guess you draw characters and they come to life in this game? I actually almost made the
title of this stream Drawing to Life, or like Drawing- Drawn to Life. I almost said that.
That's a different game. No, not Draw My Life.
I did one of those as Grandpa. Does that video still exist or did I delete it? I think it still
exists. I don't think I've deleted that one. It's still up? Yeah, I think it is still up.
PeacefulHaley, thanks for the five community subs. Thank you, Haley. Five subs. PogHaley.
PogHaley. Watch it, it's awful. Delete it on stream. Is it that bad? I don't remember it.
Now, we're playing Scribblenauts. This does not embarrass me from my old videos today.
Will you ever come to Brazil? Um, probably not. I've never left North America in my life.
I'm probably never gonna leave North America. Like, you know, I wanna go to Japan! Man,
I sure would love to go to Tokyo! Oh, England sounds so cool. I wanna go to Ireland!
No, I'm just too- I don't wanna go anywhere. Who doesn't wanna go to Japan or Tokyo? Really?
It's an incredibly interesting place. You don't need to like Japanese cartoons
to want to go to an incredibly, incredibly rich cultural, incredible historical area.
Shut up, you're a weeb. You know what? Just for that comment, just for that comment,
I'm watching One Punch Man Season 2 starting tonight. Just for that comment. For that comment
alone, I'm gonna start episode one tonight. And I know that it sucks. I know that it's way worse
than season one, but look what you did. Look what you've done. Everybody says,
oh, it's a new- it's a different animation studio. It sucks. Too bad. I'm gonna watch it now.
Sorry, Jeremy, you're going to Brazil. Wait, what? Uh, sorry. Sorry, dude, but you're going.
Why? That's like, that's like scary. All right, what you just said was scary. Okay,
I'm gonna play the game. No, it's time to do the- it's time to do the pre-live. No, what is it?
What would this be called? Hang- the hanging out before the cast. This is the pre-stream,
which again, I have to make this really clear. A lot of you guys- pre-stream is essentially
the Germa Congress. I saw that meme and it's real. How many people are- how many people are in
Congress? 200? 300? It's- it's 400- 400 something, right? Like 500? 435? Okay. There are like 410
people in pre-stream chat that decide a ton of things. So, I mean, if you want to be part of the
Germa Congress, you've got a lot of sway in that, like, you know, two, three, four hours before a
stream happens. Pre-stream chat ending waiting room. Pre-stream chat holds too much power.
Impeach this guy. Call the- call the house speaker. Who would the house speaker of pre-stream chat be?
Now, that's a whole can of worms I'm not gonna get into. You want to start a fight? That's how
you just started one. Do not. Let end stream chat decide. Something, for once. You know? Damn.
That is true. That is absolutely, positively accurate. And I'll tell you why. Pre-stream chat
is here and ready for the stream. And they're here sometimes two, three, four hours before I even
start. Right? Post-stream chat stuck around the whole time. And they- they were here to the end.
They were dedicated. Mm. That'd mean they deserved to be rewarded. Okay. Post-stream chat today.
Going to decide the next stream. There you go. Watch this. It's like the highest view count I've
ever had today. I'm staying. He's playing Sly Cooper tomorrow. Not streaming tomorrow. But, you
know. It's like 40,000 concurrent viewers here. Oh, yo. I'm gonna tell him he's gonna be- he's
gonna play Immortal Redneck. All right. Let's go. Is this capping or what? I've got nice music,
but where's the cap? Where's my capture? Dog Yelp just gave five community subs. Thank you,
Dog Yelp. Thanks a lot. You guys ready to get started? You guys ready to get started? Hey,
are you guys ready to get started? Immortal Redneck was a good stream. It was a really good game,
too. It was very good. It was really fun. There was like two that came out that- there was
Immortal Redneck and then there was um- what was the one that I played? City of something?
City of something. It's like City of Egypt or something. It was like the same game but
kind of different. City of Brass. Oh, that was it. Okay. Stop stalling. I'm not stalling.
What's about to start? Huge bits. Oh, that's a lot. That's a lot. I forgot to update my rules.
All right. We're gonna slowly pan this out, but this is somebody's birthday. Hold on. It's
somebody's birthday today. I have- it's somebody's little brother's birthday, okay? And excuse me,
it's somebody's birthday or little sibling. Sorry. I don't know why I said little brother.
Little sibling's birthday today. Hey, Crows. Q-Rows. Crows, happy birthday.
We're talking about your birthday, Crows. Have a good one. That's from Sparkly Pantsu. Sparkly
Pantsu. I'm gonna make that very, very, very quick. I need to also say happy birthday.
That's huge bits. That's an insane amount of money. I will reiterate again. I'm probably going to turn
bits off. That's too much money to give me, but thank you nonetheless and happy birthday to Crows.
Only don't- I didn't update my- the rules. I was- I forgot. I was gonna do that earlier this morning.
You're gonna ban your own income. No, I'm not banning my own income.
They say he really loves your streams and we often watch together. Well, happy birthday. Thank you.
Thank you so much. All right, everyone. I'm starting- Oh, it's a voice actor!
Grandpa Edgar and Grandma Julie. You might not believe this, but Grandpa Edgar used to be the
world's greatest adventurer. Grandma Julie would beg to differ. She was also an adventurer. Edgar
would often brush away vines or open doors thought to be undisturbed for generations, only to find
Julie was already there having lunch. They competed like this on adventure after adventure.
On one adventure, Julie beat Edgar to the top of a long lost pyramid.
I'm kidding, man. Relax. This is like the first kid's book. I haven't played part of the game.
The two of them semi-retired to start a family and they continued starting that family until they had
42 children. All right, settle down. One day, Mom and Dad gave Maxwell and me two amazing gifts.
And one day, they had a show on TLC.
It was a book that kills people. Death Note.
Little Bratz. So they sent us out to face the challenges of the outside world.
Life Note. On the road to the city, we ran into an old man who said he was hungry.
Maxwell made something to give him, but he played a nasty trick.
Apple was rotten. Oh, it really is Death Note. The old man spat it out as soon as he tasted it and was
very, very angry. As he cast some sort of magic, he called a spoiled little kid.
And then disappeared. It didn't seem like anything had happened.
But when Maxwell turned to continue down the road, I couldn't follow him.
The old man had put a curse on me that was turning me to stone. What? We didn't know what to do.
Luckily, our brother Edwin's farm was nearby. Boy, you should have seen how angry Edwin was.
He couldn't believe what we did to the old man and said we probably deserved what we got.
Aren't they like five?
Just write money in there.
Fuck up the whole economy. Just inflate all currency. Just write like five trillion dollars
in cash on there. Important question. Didn't you admit multiple times you're an awful
speller? This game requires spelling. Well, that's what I have you guys here for. Help me.
Why is my screen all messed up? Game crash? The game crash? How? I can't even close the game.
No, I did something. I can't close the game. I have to open up the task manager?
Yes, Scribble 32 is not responding. Oh, okay. Well, let's open it back up.
This is Scribble Nots Unlimited, by the way. Those of you that think I'm playing on the
standard version for the Nintendo DS. Nope. Nope. Get a bunch of not safe for work mods.
You want me to take like a two week vacation from Twitch? Skip. Okay, here we go. This is fine.
There's Farmer Dan. Farmer Dan wants walk to the farmer. Okay. He's doing it. Okay. Hi. What can
I do for you? Click on Edwin. The basics. Earn a star right by helping Edwin with his award winning
pig. Okay. Turn the runt of the litter into an award winning pig. Write an object to help
Maxwell scrub the pig. Use the notepad. Type something to clean the pig. Uh, bathtub. Soap.
Oh, this is cool. Okay. Here, take it. Oh, I'm Maxwell. And then now use the object to clean
the pig. Clean the pig. Click the progress bar for the current hint. Click map. Remove this object.
Drag it to the trash can. The pig looks great. Now use an adjective to increase the pig's size.
Okay. An adjective. Type an adjective to increase the pig's size. Gargantuan. Got it. Help the pig
win the talent competition. Use an adjective and a noun to create wings. Large enough to carry the
pig. Uh, big wings. Okay. Hints are unlocked over time. And I need wings large enough to help me
fly. Oh, I have to use it. Oh, okay. Here we go. Create object. I need wings large. How about
big wings. The magic backpack stores objects for later. Throw the wings in the backpack and
wait for the judges to arrive. Big wings. Very uncreative. What is this tutorial? I don't know
how to play. Take the wings from the magic backpack and then put them on the pig and then watch
pigs fly. Is that Sims? What did I just do? The Sims, right? That's the movies, right? The movies.
You got it. He's about to crack him over the head. Oh, okay. We're good. Oh, I got a Starbright.
Completed the basics. Welcome to Scribblenauts. Okay. Earn shards by helping people. Ten shards
will form a Starbright. You Starbright vision to find shards. You guys can help me with that later.
I don't care. Golden objects for hints. Okay. So he needs something else. Help the sprout grow.
All right, let's go. Okay. Help the sprout grow. Water. No. Manure. How do you spell manure?
Manure. Oh my God. I was going to kill this guy. What happened? What happened? I did it. Okay. Put
that in your backpack. The plant scared away the other's shard opportunity. Reset the level to
return. I got the bad ending. So wait, that thing kills the town? I have to reset the level. What?
Hold on. What happened? Well, the notepad. What did I do? I failed it? Well, I typed in manure.
While the notepad can create many things of vulgarity, copyrighted material and proper
nouns are not allowed. So you're telling me I can't write like Captain America in there and he shows
up on the screen? Well, that's too bad. I can't write in like the mask from Goosebumps. Oh no.
You don't have every single word ever. What about this? Okay. I'm going to go for this. Okay. Create
object. Make the sprout grow. Write an object. Watering can. Done. Okay. Now. Use. Watering can.
Help the little girl. What do you need? My kitty is stuck on the top of the tree. Get it from me.
Okay. Put this in my backpack. Get rid of this. How do I take this off? Remove. I'm gonna put this
in my backpack. Okay. Ladder. Climb. What? Oh shit. Oh my god. Um. People are already writing
chainsaw. No. What the fuck is wrong with you guys? Wings. Airstrike. No. Ladder. See? Okay.
Now the cat can. Uh. Cat box. Did you mean? No. Litter box. Got it. I was trying to keep that.
Okay. Learning the basics was just the first step towards saving Lily. Use the bus stop to
begin your journey in Capital City. Oh yeah. They keep the litter. I don't know. I might need it.
Click Maxwell and select pick Avatar to play as any unlocked brother. Be sure you want to
enter the Avatar browser. I did it. Let's go to. Let's go to Capital City.
Everyone is low tier. How do you know that? Wait. Is that me? No. Get. Get away from me.
All right. Capital City bus stop. How is he bottom tier? Why is he bottom tier? What does
that mean? All right. Who needs help? I feel like I'm playing Pac-Man the New Adventures.
All right. What do you need? Do you need something? I want someone to entertain me.
All right. Clown makeup. All right. Create object. Clown. Hooray! What is going on?
Where do these people come from? All right. All right. That's enough. That's enough of the
clown. That's enough. You've paid for only five minutes. This car needs to be medicalized.
I'm parked illegally. Oh no. No truck. Use this to attach to multiple objects.
Let's go. Hey. Parking violation. What did you just throw at me? Get that. Whatever it is I want it.
Use notepad. Oh no. How do I get out of the truck? How do I get out? Shit. Get out
of the truck. Oh wait. Click it. Oh. This mount. There it is. All right. Give me this.
Double click on your target to shoot or throw things. Wait. You can. I didn't know you could
do that in this game. All right. What does he need? What does he want? Security guard. Add adjective.
Create object. Stick. Wait. Add adjective. Invincible. I don't think that did anything.
Create object. Are you happy yet? I just gave you a weapon. Why am I so dirty? I'm coming in
dirt. Stabbing this guy with a syringe. Did I take some money? Oh wait. He stole my syringe.
No. No. No. Apply the cheese to him. What is happening? Give me this back. No. No. No. No.
Get out. Get out. Get out. Just syringe him. What happens if you kill somebody? Oh. I can pet the
bug. Oh wait. I'm going to give him a friend. Hold on. Wait. I'm going to give him. I'm going
to make a friend. Cockroach. Look. Look it. We're all friends. Oh yes. My many cockroach friends.
Cockroach. Cockroach. Cockroach. Cool. They wanted a friend, right? Did I get stars for that?
Here. Have some food. I got you guys a bunch of cheese. Here. Everyone need to take one. Cheese
roach. That's disgusting. All right. Remove this. I need to clean myself up. I'm disgusting. I'm
dirty. All right. Great object. Err. Toothbrush. How do I use the toothbrush on me? Shower. That's
kind of a weird place to put a shower. All right. Go in the shower. Is this working? Okay. Clean in
adjective. What? Clean. Suspect. Cheesy. Invincible. What? What? Clean. Suspect. Cheesy.
Invincible. What does that mean? Clean. Ah. There we go. It's a camera for. Oh. All right. What's your
deal? Place someone into the phone booth to make a sidekick for me. Okay. All right. I'll make a
sidekick. Place someone into. Someone's in there. What did I fill it with? What did I just put in
there? Oh. No, no, no, no, no. He's supposed to be a sidekick. It has to be a superhero. Oh. Okay.
Superhero cockroach. Okay. Um. I don't know. Firefighter. Oh. There we go. Hey. Hey. Cat burglar.
Steal from the cat burglar. Oh. This game's pretty cool. Okay. Now I gotta clean the graffiti,
right? What if I just make it cute? That's what. Look. That's now. Now it's art. Right? Now it's
like a. Well, it was art before, but now I changed to like wholesome. It's birds. What did it say
before? It wasn't real art. Yes, it was real art before. I just said that, but I would say I put
it in front of the hospital. It's like birds and, and a park bench and like butterflies. All right.
What if I do cool instead? I can't change it to cool. It's too late. I can't take, I can't take
that off. How about, uh. Well, it's in front of a hospital. How about dogs? I say that while I put
fucking cockroaches literally everywhere. Oh, look, I've changed the artwork to like a, a nice,
a nice outdoor nature setting. Cockroaches fucking everywhere. Look at so much nicer and wholesome.
This is in front of the hospital. We want like a nice park bench, but no, but look at how cute and
wholesome these cockroaches are. Even the big ones. This is just wicked. Okay. I'm going to
keep going over. Ride it. That's my wholesome city. Get that artwork off there. What kind of
artwork was that? Oh, it was graffiti. Oh, I just ridiculous. I'm going to go to the bank now.
Now quiet, quiet, quiet. Giant cockroach. Are you following me? It's a kid's game. Don't do that.
Peter Griffin. Yeah. That's kind of like, yeah, I'm going to go. I look at all this graffiti.
It looks terrible. Come on, giant cockroach. Let's go. Remember that time when I visited New York?
Remember that time when I visited, uh, God, David really was a family guy joke. Fuck. What does he
want? Play classic carnival games. Worst voice and best joke of 2020. The carnivals in town,
throw something to knock over the bottles. Don't cross the barrier. Okay. Wait, I can do whatever
I want. I did it. Holy shit. That guy was seconds away from dying. Throw something to pop the
balloons without crossing the barrier. If it works. I killed him. Oops. Okay. Oh, uh, throw
something to hit the dunk tank without crossing the barrier, but there's nobody in the dunk tank.
Who the fuck is this? Hipster. I can, I can do this to them. No, I can't. I can't keep doing this.
It's a microscopic obese hipster. Okay. So what am I supposed to do? Okay. I have to just, okay.
I don't know. Just throw something at it. Wait, no, I, I was sorry. I'm sorry. All right. No,
I got to stop like killing people and I, all right. I can stop being like awful and rude and mean.
You giving me a book where I can do everything. All right. Great object. I can't throw it over
there. Uh, here you take this. It's in case something bad happens. Just how about a car?
Tiny car. No, it's plus one letter grade. That's one full letter grade. Here you can have it. Okay.
Um, just a ball. That was pretty good. All right. Now do, now do throw something to pop those
balloons. Lightning. Uh, it didn't work. Uh, bomb worked just fine. All right. Dunk tank. Throw
something to hit the dunk tank. I'll give you that ball. No, put that back on. Whatever. I'm
making a new ball. All right. Uh, what can you throw? Something you can throw. You can throw
anything you want. You can throw a plate. Dunk. You did it. Good thing he had the fire extinguisher.
Wait, is he mad? Is he mad at me? What is he doing? Get out of here. Here, you can have this.
I stole it back from him. This town is fucking crazy. What's wrong with this town? Oh, here we
go. I played, I played the classic carnival games. I can't, man. Like I, I've, I fucked it all up.
Welcome to the Virgil gallery. What the hell is going on here? All right. What's your deal?
One of these artifacts is a fraud. Help me figure out which one. Okay. Um, it's, it's definitely
this one. Magnifying. I found it. It's this one. Eat it up. What? Oh, I did it. So that's all for
you. What do you, what is this? Finicky patrons help Maxwell provide art that will be sure to
please patrons of the museum. Okay. It's opening day at the museum. Place something in the frames
that will be sure to please the museum's patrons. What do you want? Place an item inside the frame
that I would find artistic. Uh, CPU, a wires, a wire, wire string. Attach that. That's the other
end of the back of his fucking head and just jolt him with a thousand volts. You like that? That's
art. He is the art now. Wait, hold on. Take that off. Right. Adjective. Um, robotic, a robotic wire.
I know. Let go of this. What? Now I'm just mocking this guy. I didn't mean, no. Wait, he likes it.
I love technology. Like I just attached this to him and then I just attach it to myself and
put myself in robotic clothes. What the fuck am I doing? It is off. Okay. How about, um, I love
technology. I don't know. There's no, that doesn't exist. How about a toaster? No, that's not
technology. Computer. He loves it. Here comes somebody else. What is something that this
patron would like to see? Place it in the frame. Okay. Uh, it's a mummy. So I don't know a, uh,
let's see. Tomb. Thank you. How's the Maxwell head icon to center the camera on Maxwell?
The next patron is arriving. Play something that, oh, Halloween town. Get this off. All right. You
like pumpkins. You must be Halloween themed. Let's do a pumpkin, a skeleton. Wait, he's alive.
I can't put him in here. Somebody died in the museum. You actually come into this place.
It's like there's cockroaches everywhere. You walk in here. Oh, wow. A museum. Cool. Somebody
died in here. Somebody died a long time ago and they didn't clean it. They didn't get rid of it
and alive. Oh, isn't that kind of a weird, you don't like that? All right. Well, let's do, um,
jack-o'-lanterns. It's like what, that's what he's hitting. Oh, okay. Last patron is here.
Oh, the invisible man definitely wants to have a, I don't know what an invisible man wants.
Let's see. Nothing. Empty. Empty space. Blank canvas. Uh, toilet paper. No, he, does he wrap
himself up with the toilet paper so he can be seen? Wait, no, that's a mummy wrapped himself
in toilet paper. Put that over here. Did I just gag that guy? Get that off. Take that off. Here,
you can have this. Thanks, I guess. I just kind of wanted to go to the museum. I don't really want
like a roll of toilet paper. Okay. How about, uh, the invisible man? A robe. I can't wear the robes?
Why? Okay. Well, here you take this back. It's a picture. You have to think of the click on Lily
at the farm to unlock new levels. This game's, no, I didn't want to go back. I just destroyed
that whole city. Whoa. I feel like you'd have a different reaction if you're seeing that.
Okay. Where are we going? How about to the hospital? Good link. I'm not sure I can click
that link. Last time I alt tabbed the whole game crashed. Okay. Let's help. I'm going to see if I
can click this link. Game saves automatically, right? I'm going to make sure. Okay. Tribble
Knott's guide for idiot streamers. What? What do you mean for idiot streamers? Okay. Let's see
what it says. Read the guide. It says, click in the top right corner to use the notebook.
Edit in the avatar menu to create a custom character. Be more creative, you boring man.
I just threw a bomb at a clown, killed a tiny fat hipster with an axe and brought a skeleton
to life and then gagged him with toilet paper. Oh, what's, what's, what do you, what's, what do
you mean? Boring and uncreative. All right. So I can make a custom character though.
Edit in the avatar menu. Let's do that. Oh, should I still have a clown in here?
Okay. Top right. Open the object editor. View your collection of custom objects. What? Custom object.
Write an object without adjectives. Yeah. That's how you write. Where's the object editor? Where's
like the character editor? The avatar menu. Pick avatar. Okay. Hold on. Okay. Edit. All right.
Edit and create your own objects here. Turn on help to see tooltips. Okay. So
this is a hat. So you can make them. Oh my God. Okay. Wait, wait, wait. This is,
I need to look at this for a second. I can have two heads. I can be a fucking ogre. Okay. All right.
That's good. I'm just making, so I don't know. I don't know. It's a charger. I'm going to put his
arms up and work it high too. So he's like, he's just like, we get stuffed in neck. This is an Omega
Coomer. You both, both of them are watching different porn at the same time. One's on over
on this screen and one's over on that screen. Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. But wait, but who gets to control,
who gets to control the cockpit? Oh no. It's gay. Hey, you clicked on the 18 mature audience click.
It doesn't matter what gay, I could be playing solitaire right now. No, they're not watching.
They're not. Guys, they're banned from watching this channel. Okay. Wait, wait, wait. What else
can we do? I can paint? Oh my goodness. Like I make a big green guy. No, this is just the Hulk,
but worse. I actually kind of like it like that to be honest. It's like Waluigi in the Hulk.
Oops. No, I do. I can't click this part. All right. I got to make it bigger. Wait, you can do
patterns? There are six tabs. Oh my God. Why is this game so cool? Okay. All right. That's good
for now. No, no, no. Don't put another head. Get that off. I know what you're thinking
and it's not happening. I know what you're thinking and you can all, you can all stop now
because that's not happening. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I need to change the
heads. Where's my edit thing? Over here? Okay. Here. Why did you tell me this existed? Why did
you tell me to do this? Like, you know, I'm going to sit here for like another two hours.
There's a trunk brothers. What does the play pause button do? All right. How do I save this?
Edwin? That's not Edwin anymore. It's the trunk twins. This head needs to be, I shrink the head
or make this one bigger. I don't know. The beard is gone somehow. I lost the beard. Here's an
apology link. Hold on. It's under his head. I don't think I can get under there. Oh shit. I can.
All right. That's better. Like link. He's crying. What? All right. I'm going to, I'm going to go.
I'll move on. Save. Okay. Now how do I play with the trunk twins? I didn't know he was this tiny.
No, I got to make him bigger than that. I, he's making bigger than this. All right. Please. But
hold on. Let me, if I click this link, I might freeze. Same community, same community, shared
files. What is this? I'm a dump truck. No. All right. I'm not, that's fine. I'm not putting that
in the game. You put that in your game, not mine. Okay. So I have to help this guy. Give me something
that I can use to perform surgery. A spoon. Okay. All right. Can I get, I can get rid of this guy.
Wrong link. Wrong link. How did I click the wrong link? Every YouTube might be referenced
in Scribblenod. What? Even more influencers in the latest patch. What are you talking about?
You liars. Liar. Real link. Guide creator here. Wait. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. The guide
is this actual guide creator. He said guide creator here. I want to apologize for calling you a
boring man. As an apology, I've officially taken a hundred dollars off the debt. All right. That's
it. That deal. That's a deal. All right. What do you want me to do? Hospital, man. Help the patients
that are coming into the hospital. Let's go. Help the patients that are being delivered to St.
Asterisk hospital. Oh shit. Sick kitten. Okay. This kitten is sick as a dog. Write something to cure
it. Medicine. Medicine. Use that medicine on the cat. Nice work. Boring. What? You want to be,
what do you want me to do? Ouch. It must be a toothache. All right. Rip the teeth out.
What if I just do medicine three times? I wouldn't. All right. Pliers. I ripped, I ripped out the bad
teeth. This robot is something wrong with him. Robot's broken. Helped it function. All right.
He needs electricity. All right. What can I, what can I do? Electrical robot. He needs help.
Well, we'll start with, I'm not going to pour water on him. Medicine. Medicine. That didn't work.
Took his eyes. Okay. How about buzzsaw? Why is it I'm guillotining him? What? No,
that was going to hurt him. Oh my God. Okay. Hold on. Okay. How about a battery? Battery.
Somebody put that battery in the robot. Nice work. Where's the last chapter? My story is not
complete. What is this? I read that. Read notebook. I soft locked it. Oh, this, I need to do something
with this. Brown cracked book. All right. Fixed book. Okay. Uh, read, read book. Adjective on the
book. Okay. We're going to do adjective on the book. Um, solution. The solution to the puzzle.
Satan? Uh, normal book. All right. Now read this. Uh, read book. Finished book. Finished. Completed.
Story. Stony. Savory. Scary. My story isn't complete. Where's the last chapter?
Add boring. Boring book. Paper book. Paper book. Paper book. Who is an expert on writing? I don't
know. I'll go to the bookstore. I put this in my, okay, let's go. No, no, no. Give me that. Wait.
Who's an expert at writing books? Edgar Allan Poe. Suspects. Why am I a suspect? Okay. Um,
stop. Not an adjective. Can I just make an entire bookstore? Okay. Cool. All right. So we have a
bookstore. Okay. Cool. Who works in the bookstore? A, an author. Sorry. I put a house in. He crashed
into the house. He crashed into the bookstore. Oh shit. How do I remove the bookstore? No, no,
no. Get back down there. What did I just take off? I have to get rid of the bookstore. Who would,
who would you take a broken car to? Well, I know. Took off with that guy's eyes. Okay. Who,
what would you have written instead of mechanic? Who would, what am I going to put? What do you
want me to put there? A scientist, mad scientist. Medicine. A car doctor. Edgar Allan Poe. What are
you talking about? Who else would fix the car? Oh, wait, come with me. No, nothing. What's the
matter? Help me laugh again. Um, funny movie. Joker. Okay. Here you go. What? You don't think
the clown is funny? The anvil is going to kill him. What is he doing? Why is he playing with
his life so weirdly? I'm not doing anything with that. I'm just seeing what you're going to do.
All right. Now what? Frunk twins. No. What do you need? Stop the attacking heart. Okay.
Uh, add adjective. Cholesterol. Oh no. Uh, wait, can I make cholesterol?
All right. Can I, I can't make cholesterol. How about just like fat? Yeah. What do you think
about that? Ooh, he ate it. All right. We're going to make ton of cholesterol. We're going to make
ton of fat and just have him keep eating. No, you don't. More fat. Add adjective. Small, small and
full of fat. Inflate it. Uh, like cheeseburger. Okay. Are you good? What do you need? I need new
equipment for the hospital. Okay. How about, sure. Do you have to, is that just like scotch tape?
Okay. New equipment for the hospital. How about, so let's get a, uh, an E, an EKG machine. EKG.
An EKG. What the hell is that? Also need to get you a, um, a syringe and
oh boy, I wasn't done. Where'd the king come from? ECG. EKG is a water cooling company. What?
What are you talking about? King Arthur is in here. All right. Sword. Uh, Excalibur, right?
Whatever it is. There. Now you're happy. That's the Burger King. No, it says King Arthur on his name.
What do you guys need? Seeing something painted with my team colors would really motivate me to
win the race. Things to be painted. Things to be painted with my team colors. So red versus blue.
Okay. Canvas on that canvas. Edit object. That's not how the game works. It has to be an adjective.
Great object. Wait, so what about like blue, like painting of a just red, just purple, just blue.
If I do, what if I write red, blue? No. Uh, okay. What's something that's, what's something that's,
what's something that's purple? A daffodil? Red, blue, babe? A grape. There. Now no one's happy.
Take this back. All right. I'm going to do, uh, I don't know. Fucking what? A fountain, a water, a
an apple. I don't know. I, what's red? What's blue? How about is that, but that, but people
are going to call me like boring Barry. That's not even a painting of an apple. That's just an
apple. This is just an apple. I just painting of apple, painted apple. It's why they in wheelchairs.
What? Wait, hold on. I've painted red on the apple. They got bored. This is a painted apple.
Okay. Let's go. What do you need? They both need something. I left what I was delivering to the
transplant patient behind. It's the heart. Kidneys. Now you have it. Good. Take those kidneys.
I forgot what I'm supposed to be delivering. Can you help me? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I
can get this to the other hospital quick. Oh, I know you want me to put baby here,
but how about like a kidney baby? No, give me that. Okay. A kidney baby. Okay. Now hold on.
No, I don't press that. Oh, no, no, no, no. I don't. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it.
Don't do it. All right. I'm good. What have I, what did I, oh my God, I feel so terrible.
What else is there to do? Is the, is the lady still down there? No, don't tell me. No, I,
no, I'm good. I did it. Seven out of seven. I'm fine. What's your deal? They continue to multiply.
Oh, is there already, was there already in here? Yeah, it was. What about here? Oh, hello you two.
We can't see the view. There are clouds in the way. Oh, I can help you with that.
Okay, I can help you. No, no, no. Damn it. Oh, just wait. That was not, you weren't supposed to take
that up. I was going to put, go up the ladder, make a platform, put a video camera this way,
and then come down here and put a TV monitor in front of them. I can't do that apparently.
How about a fan? Can't do anything right. At least me and the birds can be friends.
That was a double kill. They're still alive down here. Yeah, see, they're fine.
All right, there's three more. Ban links. No, I'm not clicking on links right now.
I want to sail across the sea. What a jet ski. Or how about a piece of wood.
Oak. Just like oak. Oak peat. Oak pirate. Pricey. Piece of oak wood.
All right, how about just a plank of wood. You can float across with that.
All right, a piece of wood with like a sail on it. How about that? Can I attach these together?
Tape. Okay. Oh, there we go. All right, now I need tape or glue. What? That. Okay, attach.
Hey, what? Upright? I have to do, okay, hold on. I have to do the object editor.
Blue icon, top right. No, what? I was trying to attach it. Wood. Okay, I want to attach
the wood to this. Doesn't that say attach? That's what I just tried to do last time.
Going fucking anywhere on that. It's too heavy. All right, I have a solution. It needs to be
rideable. I will. Hold on. I got to get this right. It's upside down. Can I rotate this?
I can rotate it when it's two pieces. Oh, drop it. Okay, there we go. Okay, now, hold on.
Adjective. Rideable. This is a rideable wood and rideable steel wood. No, what am I doing?
See, look, it works. I'm telling you. Get off. No, get the fuck off of this thing, man. Okay,
so now let's go into the notepad. Adjective. Rideable. Floating. Rideable floating wood.
Fuck. Edible? This shit works just fine, dude. I bet you want to get on this, man.
Come on over here. That's not sailing. Too far? Why can't I do this? Why am I a menace to society?
Okay, can I throw a rock from up here? He's the green goblin. Okay, did I just call this a boat?
Yes, I have. What do you think I have right here? Okay. Adjective. Floating. Rideable.
Boat wood. Bold wood. Seaworthy. Rideable. Bold. Floating. Rideable. Seaworthy. Wood. Okay,
I'm getting off. It's yours. Seaworthy. Bold. Floating. Rideable. Wood.
Uh, bouyant. Bouyant. Bold. Flying. Rideable. Bouyant. Bold. Floating. Rideable. Wood.
Big, beautiful, beater, barbecue, bunker burger. Why won't he go on this? Just make a boat.
Oh, but that's- look at- he could just- do I just have to make it boat?
All right, I'm gonna take floating off. Bouyant. Bold. Rideable. Wood. There. Oops. This thing's got
a life of its own. Go get it. It's because it's bold. Boyant. Rideable. Wood. Make him ride a
shark. Okay, hold on. Let's make it huge. Huge rideable fish. It worked. I'm not done. Now go.
You're welcome. I didn't fail it, look. I want to sail across the sea. Wait. Uh, hold on. Fast. Huge.
Fast. Rideable. Fish. Just make a boat. What'd you guys call me, boring berry? If I type the word
boat and put it in the water, isn't that boring berry? You guys gotta pick a side. Huge boat.
Air- air propelled. All right, here. Come on, let's go. Can I not save this guy? Now go. Give him a
lifesaver. Balloon works just fine. Now here it comes. Here comes the air. Boring berry. How about
over here? Capital city firehouse. He left trash everywhere. Well, that's just the nature of this
game. I need to look at the part to become a firehouse dog. Okay. How about write an object?
Costume. Here you go. No, no, no, no. That was for you. That was for you. I guess I'll put it
on too though. Aw. Wait, what? Here, take this. Can't put that on? Fireman's hat. All right,
how about a hat? Here. Yes. There he goes. Oh. Turn a station wagon into a fire engine.
That was so cute. Okay, all the fire engines are busy. This car needs to become a fire truck. Start
by painting the car. All right. Uh, what are we gonna paint? What? Red? Blood. How about ketchup?
That's technically red. Keyed car. Blood. You can't do blood. Use the ketchup on the car. Can I do
that? Oh, shit. It didn't work. I mean, that's easy. Dude, it's just red. Car needs to be heard.
Give the DJ something loud to hook up to the car. Um, sure. Fire alarm. That's a school bell.
Fireman's almost ready to head out. Give him a tool that will help get the job done.
It's an axe or it's a fire extinguisher. This is a boring streak. Yeah, but like, yeah, you have to
do it. Yeah. I can't paint the car with blood. Uh, okay. Give me a firefighting tool. It's a bottle
of water. That'll do it. How about a hose? Oh, I attached it to his eye. Oh shit. Here,
now take another one. I just like blocked both of his eyes. Bye. Oh no, there's a traffic jam.
Help get over this traffic. Crusted. I just threw it into like toast. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
Let me think about this creatively. I could just put a fan here. With the balloons on there,
I could. Okay. Yeah. We're going to, we're going to do the balloon strategy catapult. Hold on. How
about a, uh, don't hit me. Holy shit. Did I get that? I did it. All right. All right. Right. Right.
Angry gorilla works. Cool. All right. Who's next? Help me test all the alarms. That's the alarms.
Okay. Empty. Yeah. Here. That's the alarms. Okay. Uh, sure. There's an alarm right there.
Let's burn that fire. Okay. How about this burning? Let's test the fire alarm. Oh,
wait, I can't get up there. Why not play sound? Take turn. Give me that.
I want to climb this. That's cheating. Fire alarm on this floor is functional. Oh, is it?
The wings too big to go up there. I just took off all my clothes. Give me these back. Why can't I
just climb this? Oh, I, uh, test that. What do you guys need? You snore so loudly. I can't sleep.
Okay. Uh, that work. It didn't work. You put that. No, take it off. Take it off. Take it off. I'm
sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Muscles didn't work. Okay. How about, um, a, I'm not going
to do pillow. Make him deaf. No earplugs. Yeah, but that's so, all right. Earplugs works.
So, so his mouth shut. I think you underestimate the things you can do in scribble knots.
Did he just start? Oh, he fell asleep. He, no, he didn't. What's going on? Why is he thinking of
sheep so much? He fell asleep because I gave him the pillow. So he didn't even care. Oh, okay.
What do you need? I can't find my helmet anywhere. Here, I got it. Did I just put a diaper in your
makeup cabinet? That's a surprise for later. Uh, how about a top hat? No, this is not my helmet.
Mine's in my locker. Give me that back. You don't want it. I'll take it. Wait, is her locker the one
that burnt? Oh, sorry. Uh, ma'am, I'm going to need that back. There. What are you doing up here?
Ooh, this is a big one. Help the survivors defend against the zombie invasion.
Did I put on new clothes? Uh, the city has been overrun by zombies. Each of the survivors
needs some help. Start by helping the doctor treat the fireman's wounds. I got it. Medicine.
What's wrong with him? He's sick. What's wrong with him though? Um, pills. Pills. Pill. Here,
take this pill. Why do you have to get on top of it? What the fuck was that? This is the gamer's
dream. Give her something to help fend off the horde. Oh, it's a gamer's dream. All right,
drag it down. All right, here. What do you need?
I know, I get it. All right, it's a gamer's dream. It's not a gamer's dream. Nobody wants to actually
be in a zombie apocalypse. That would suck. You would die in 10 minutes. Oh man, I got a plan.
I would go to the grocery store and I would bring like an axe and I'd be fucking killing zombies.
No, you'd get bit. You would, you would take a swing at a zombie and you'd hit it in like
the fucking shin and the thing would grab you and two more would grab you and you would get bit in
the neck and you're dead instantly. But like here, how about a katana? Yeah, of course a katana.
What do you need? Yeah, you know why it's a dull katana? Because, because you bought it from,
you bought it from like fucking QVC. It's, it's not, it's a display. I'm so scared. Make me feel
better. You're now happy. Happy orphan. Apparently. No, no, no, I'm scared. You could be scared and
happy, right? Um, not scared. Zombie, zombie orphan. Well, if you would, if you were a zombie,
you wouldn't be scared of them anymore because you would just be one. All right, let's go.
Who's what you locked in here? Okay. All right, let's go. Uh, uh, pills. Take it. Go ahead. Next
gamer. What are the, what are the, what are the like fantasies that gamers have in zombie
apocalypses? Sawed off shotgun. Yeah. Calm her down. Okay. Uh, teddy bear, teddy bear, a teddy.
I worked for drugs. No, the soldier is convinced that a few simple objects can be combined to make
a fighting machine. Place three objects inside the box to make a mech. Okay. Microwave and coaster
and coffee maker. If your power is combined, you will make a kitchen appliance monster.
What are you doing? It's not a mech. You what? It's a three objects. You doing it?
I could use anything made of metal or something sticky. Oh, well, I got a glue. You didn't tell
me how to put the glue in there too. Um, it put like just a cheese sauce in there. Why does the
cheese sauce have health? All right. Microwave, toaster and, um, slime. Oh, you added something
sticky that can be used to join the parts together. All right, let's go. I need a weapon. Um, a
butcher knife, rocket launcher, code, laser, um, toenail, flamethrower, drill, a dentist drill,
a nail clipper, spear. Yeah. Here it comes. It's the final ingredient. Read the prompt.
It's three objects inside the box to make a mech. It's on the soldier.
Most electronic devices need a similar power. So, oh, come on. There you go. Come on. I can't
just put an outlet in there. Why? How about a, uh, gasoline? There it is. It's not what I put in
there. Distract the zombies while the other survivors escape. Hop in the mech when you're
ready to begin. Distract the zombies while the others escape. Okay. Get in the robot. Hold on.
Not yet. I want like a bunch of warrior clowns. Tasty, tasty clowns.
No, no. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out of that. Get out of that. That's for me,
not for you. All right. This is another tasty clown. Okay. This one's going to be a delicious
clown. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't think so. Where are you going?
Oh my God. They're running away because of the zombies. What the fuck? Oh, you're getting over
there. Fire. He's bait. He's a zombie now. That's so funny. Now what? Fire missiles at the zombies
while everyone escapes. That's what I'm doing. All right. Got it. Wait, make an explosive clown?
All right. We're good. Is he going to go inside? Explosive clown fetish? What the hell are you
talking about? Succulent clown. Watch out. You're going to get taken away. Oh man. We have more
area. How about castle? All right. How about go piss? That sounds like a good idea. I'll be right back.
Okay. Time. Time. How long? How long? How long have I been gone for? How long have I been gone
for? Give me an exact how long I've been actually gone for. Two minutes and what? Two minutes and
11 seconds. Okay. I was peeing the almost entire time I was gone. It took me about
five or six seconds to leave the room and about five or six seconds to come back into the room.
That was the longest pee I've ever done in my entire life. That was insane. I don't understand.
It made no sense. How was that possible? Did you wash your hands? Yes, I did. I didn't wash your
hands. Of course I did. I did. I did. Yes, I did. I wash my hands every time. I don't. That was the
that was it. It was actually fucked up. Like I'm actually concerned about that. I just peed for
like fucking a full two minutes. Let's go to the forest. Welcome to Meta forest. Oh, there's another
scribble mouse guy. Hungry mosquito. Loaded hungry mosquito. What do you want? Help the scout earn
his merit badge. We're gonna cut this down. All right, you want to do a test here to see if I can
do every single one of these tasks with the grenade? What's going on here? Give me a tool to carve this
log. Sharp grenade. I don't think I would ever want. Okay, like sharp grenade? Holy shit, he actually
did it. Fire safety is next. Give the scout something to put out the dummy. Sure, I can do that.
Remember this? Oh, I didn't blow that up, right? I had to add a sharp like water grenade.
There. Why did you pull the pin? You don't pull the pin. It was already water covered.
Give me something to fix the dummy's wounds. How about a medical grenade?
Heal it. A healing grenade. Healing grenade. Here. Look, it's healing. He's gonna throw it.
Give the scout proper safety equipment. You just, you just like spawn drop this? A safety
grenade. Yeah, all right. I'm gonna give you a nice safety grenade. Okay. Am I saying that wrong?
Safe grenade. Give me that back. Resistant grenade. A protective grenade. Interact with what?
Oh, it's a safety grenade. Don't worry. Oh, no, no, no, no. The instructor is shit faced.
And he, I think he just like snorted three lines. Hey, look everybody. No, it's made out of,
I swear it's made out of Play-Doh. With his teeth. Here, why don't you take a saw, man?
Oh, put that fire out and just come over here and help me, man. Man, I thought I'd give you a...
Oh, that didn't work. I'm just making him and I just do it for him. All right, here.
Look, I'm gonna, I'm, hold on. So you need to put this out. Uh, no, put it out. Give me it. Oh,
no, no, no, no. No more of the grenade stuff. No more grenade stuff. I don't care. I'm taking
my clothes off. Who cares? Oh, no, the instructor. The instructor's actually fucking going crazy.
Okay. Here. Take a, just here. Just take a fucking squirt gun. Good work. Let's fix the wounds of the
dummy. Here, a medical squirt gun. You're giving a gun to a kid. It's a squirt gun. All right.
Safety equipment. How about, okay. Eye goggles. But how about like blacked out eye goggles?
That help them? Give them a blindfold. Yeah, these are for me so I can see this fucking hilarious
show. Give them a weapon. Just put a pinata up here. Okay. Here. Oh, wait, wait, wait, here.
Oh, wait. I can't. What do they use? Like a pool cue? All right. Spin them around like three times.
Rope. Small. Smaller. Shallow. Trunking. Tiny. Shit. All right. I'm just going to put him up
with a balloon. That's way too hard. All right. He's not going to hit that. Tiny rope. Microscopic
rope. Short rope maybe. No. Trunk. Compact. Whatever. He's ready. Give me a weapon. Oops.
I'm going to make the balloon small. Balloon. Can't interact with it? Oh, here it comes.
Like really, really like wealthy birthday party. We have two pinatas. I can't interact with it.
Give me the wings. Small balloon. That's not going to help. No. No matter. How about, yeah, weak.
Tiny weak balloon. Attach the rope to the ground. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
Wait. Don't. I can't. Just attach it to him. Who gives a shit? Ah. Hooray. It's done. All right.
How do I move the camera? There we go. Holy shit. You suck. Holy shit. That was terrible.
Oh, he's a balloon. It was pretty good for not being able to see. It was actually really good.
Hungry, poisoned mosquito. Um, okay. I'm not really poisoning anybody unless it's very slow.
You want me to get rid of the mosquito, don't you? These bugs are harmless. Help me keep them away.
Uh, okay. How about flamethrower? Bug nuke. Buggy nuke. Uh, I think that makes it just funny.
Okay. Buggy as in code. Buggy. Uh, edible nuke? How would you have an edible nuke?
Wait, is he eating it? He just ate the nuke. Well, I mean, that makes sense now, doesn't it?
Hungry, poisoned, explosive mosquito. Okay, here. You here. Take this. Take a, um, here. Take a trap.
That's for you to use on the bug. Don't walk in that trap. You fucking idiot. Ow. It's on me.
It's on me. Get it off. Get it off. Get it off. Get it off. Get it off. Get it off me.
Here. How about a spray? A sprayer. Oh, uh, bug sprayer? A, uh, a exterminator? A spray- a
poison sprayer? I'll take care of the bug. Cutting off your head. What, cutting off your nose to save
your face? That didn't work. Here, use a knife. Smallest nuke I've ever seen. Your starlight
kind of turns red. Oh, oh well. What does the chef want? My nose isn't good enough to snip out
truffles anymore. All right, cut your nose off to spite your face. Your nose isn't good enough?
Okay, um, what a sniffer. What about a metal detector? I can smell smells. Sniff detector.
Mushroom detect- okay, a mushroom detector. A smell- a smelling detector. Here, how stupid are you?
I'm actually not that stupid. I'm pretty smart. Approved right now. Now I have a hat,
and I got it for free. Oh, he's in it? No. All right, take that off. So you can't snip anymore.
What's- what is the thing that can smell out mushrooms? A dog? Sniffing dog. Uh, hey! Wait,
he just ate it? What did he just eat? What- what's this flag mean? Okay, my job is to cut down this
tree, but I don't have any tools. What about the bird? You cannot play as Max's brother Jack.
Oh, this person doesn't even care anymore. Uh, how about- what about the bird? At the bird. Wait,
what's this? Boring, boring, boring, boring, boring, boring, boring. Grave. Oh god. Okay, this is- this
is like- here- here comes like potentially like offensive shit. No, I don't want to like dig
somebody out of their grave, okay? I don't want to do that, but I'm going to. This coffin brings
things to life, does it really? Okay, what are we putting in here? Bring it to life.
How about a ham sandwich? A hard sandwich. Oh, he is pretty hard. He's slowly but surely.
That's a bad- no, don't go for me. Wait, I want to give him legs. Let's give him legs and arms and
stuff. Adjective. You have to do- object editor. Make it have writable- make bipedal.
Bipedal undead hard ham sandwich. That didn't work. Biomedical. Bald.
You just- bald, okay. And he needs like legs to walk on, doesn't he? Object editor. Okay, new object.
Write an object. Okay, ham sandwich. No, no, no, no, no. Use floating and bypass the legs.
Go to the steam workshop. I just need to have to add the legs. How do I keep- how do I- I can't-
how do I make him stand still? Just tell him like, just get away from me. I'm trying to help you.
Make him asleep. Sleeping. Okay, sleeping, bald, hard, bald ham sandwich. Okay, walking legs.
All right, hold on. No, no, no. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. He just bit the- okay, he bit the legs
because that- he's eating the legs. How is he asleep? Whatever. What am I doing? What- what just
happened? What the fuck just happened? Oh, I'm a zombie. I'm a zombie. He bit me. Okay, hold on.
Well, that's fucked up. Okay, that was- that was a human leg.
Undead. No, no, no, no, no. No, I'm none of these things. No, get away from me. Stop, stop, stop.
Okay, undead alive mix. No, how do I cure you? How do I cure you? Sandwich, I need your help.
Sandwich! Take it. Zombie cure? Cure. Cure. What the fuck? I can't make a cure. I can make the- I
can make the medicine be a cure medicine? Zombie cure? Antidote. That's a good idea.
How do I have to take it? We would like something to play with. Haven't I just already- I've already
done that. What are you doing? Pet the sandwich? That's not even funny. That's just stupid.
I'll restart. Reset. Reset. Okay, things in there get- become alive. Flower.
Okay, here we go. These two want something to play with. About a train set. Toy train. Toy train.
Look, that looks fun. Doesn't it, kids? I- I think I- Did I like squish that onto them and kill them?
I think he used it to kill the other one and kill himself. That was weird. Okay.
All right, what are you- you being haunted? Deliver me from evil. All right, exercise.
Make you an exorcist. Exercise and give the exorcist a gun. Things like chasing this guy down.
Deliver me from evil. Come down here. It's a holy flame thrower. Hey, get over here. All right,
take it out. Take it out. Shoot it. What the hell are you doing? Give me that thing. You don't
deserve to have that. I do. He's all right. What the hell is down there? These are all monsters.
That was Cthulhu. Why did that person just run up here and die? I just killed Cthulhu. What's that
behind me? All right, what's that behind you? Uh, what's this? This is a spell book. Interact with
the spell book. Tape. How about evil spell book? Adjective. Okay, evil spell book. Is it fighting
the tape? Oh, shit. I have no idea what's going on here, but I'm just gonna say fine. I guess I-
I think everything's fine, I guess. That was fun. You seem to be enjoying yourselves. All right,
I want to make this a light. Very light. Good size, rusty light suit of armor. Clean. How about, um,
soap? There. No, whatever. Make them clean. Light, clean, edible. Delicious, clean, edible.
Can I eat it? Nice. Secret passage. What the hell is this for? Oh, it's like the french fry meat
thing. What do you want? Flame keeps me trapped down here. Flame keeps me- All right, so I need to
put out the fires. Turn them off. What's this problem? Horror in the basement. It's my mount.
This is fun. Yeah. All right, I need to go upstairs. Friendly. Spider. I want to be more frightening.
All right. About, um, your scary mask. Gagged mask. A jolly mask. A mask. Wait,
hold on. I have to be scary. Get out of the way. Scary. All right, hold on. And I have to do this
or no one will let me sleep tonight. There you go. Who else is left? Oh, up here. How do I get up
there? Make the attic a bit more spooky. Oh, there's an urn up here too. All right, hold on.
Make the attic spooky. I can do that. Let's go. Urns. Uh, bat. Scary bat. Oh no, they just put the
mask on? Monster. Oh, get out of here. Pathetic monster. You're gonna kill my friend. All right,
I gotta do something quick. Gun. Fight for me. Oh my god, he killed my friend. I'm so fucking mad
right now. I'm actually upset. Get out of here. Come closer to start me. Are we gonna get up there?
It's because all the bugs are in the way. How do I climb it? Okay, find the ghosts and set them
free. Too many bugs. Not enough snacks. It's pre-recorded. You got, yeah, it is. It is. You got
me. It is. I'm sorry. I, look, I was really busy today. I recorded this at like two o'clock in the
morning. I rented it. I uploaded it. I put it in a lot. I'm sorry. I had to. I was, got, got me busy
today. All right, let's find the ghosts. Rid the house of the ghosts who haunted first. Give
Maxwell something to help him see the supernatural. Uh, the Bible. Let's get biblical. The bike? The
bike teen? Teen bike. Okay, fine. Read my teen bike. I gotta find where the ghosts are. Okay,
how about a turbo teen bike? How about a ghost detecting turbo teen bike? EMF reader. EMF radar.
An emo radar. We're trying to find the emos. This is just, okay, this is one of those dumb
toys that you can get at that weird mall store that everybody has. This is like Sky Mall magazine
type shit where it's like, find the dork. And you walk around with it and you can press a button
underneath it where it goes. You hold it in front of your friends. Oh, find the dorky loser.
You go to one of your buddies and sit on the couch.
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum. Oh, he's a fucking loser.
But seriously, where, where are the emos? It's fine. Change this from an emo detector to some,
wait, remove that. Ghost detector. A show, a ghost radar. Wait, now it's just a ghost.
Ghost emo radar. Ghost detecting, ghost defective, ghost detectable,
ghost deductive, ghost dieting, ghost damaging, ghost damaging radar. Oh shit, that's perfect.
Ghost damaging radar. Let's carry this thing around. Did that, did it hurt me?
My ghost? All right, we got to find the ghost and just hurt him. You are a ghost. No, I need
a ghost detector. What about just detector? Director? Horror movie director. Horror director.
Hot director. Oh, I thought that meant like hot horny director. No, I don't think so.
No, I'm not going to do that. I don't think so. Okay. I want to put like a flashlight up.
That was the best trick I've ever done. That was better than anything I've ever done in Tony Hawk.
All right. I need a, a ghost detector, a reader, a seance kit, candle, a ghost radar. Did it work?
Ouija board. No, not an onion board. An odd board. An oiled board. Orcish board. No, don't give him
the radar. Whatever. Of the orcish board. Hold on. This puts a dunscap on him. Just give this back.
It killed this thing. Just here. Just dead. There. Stupid dead board. Okay, I heard a ghost.
He wants to come back in so bad. He's like, you forgot about me.
All right. So, uh, where are these ghosts? Spell it around. Wait. Yeah. How about a cross?
Tape the cross to my, okay. Cross. All right. You gave the cross to the radar. Yeah, but isn't that
fine? Give Maxwell a fortune teller. What? Give me three things to play with and I will leave this
house. What the fuck is this? And how did he get on the roof? Wait, how did he get up there?
Isn't this got the fortune teller? Wait, he's afraid of this too, isn't he? All right, let's
go with three things to play with. Sure. How about a dolly? A teen bike? Wait, it went the wrong way.
How about, you know, how about a cross, a radar, and a turbo teen bike? You like, you like it?
Give me things that little girl would play with. Sure. A, uh, I don't know, a Barbie.
Wait, no, little girls don't play with that. Don't play with that. How about a doll? Get that off
the fire. How about a doll, a sparkles, a sparkler, a spark, stapler, a sampler, a Ouija board, a sea
raven. What is a sea raven? Oh shit, grill that up. All right. You, wait, give me a dolly,
a teddy bear, and a puppet. Um, was the, was the puppet like an effigy of her?
Grab her the bike. Oh, I think she took the bike. She just literally got the bike from me.
All right, well what if this guy is so hot? All right, let me help this guy. This is just sad.
There. All right, fuck this guy. I don't care. What do you want? I'm missing my ring and a wedding
party. Wedding ring. There you go. And a wedding party. Uh, priest and a groom and a,
oh, they didn't take them. I've been trapped here for a long time. Give me three relics of the Holy
Church and I can leave this place. I got it. I already got one right here. Take it. That's a
sacred relic. Give me three relics of the Holy Church. All right. Okay. That's, um, wine,
chalice, a cross, wine. That's not wine. That was, that's wife. Who's wife? My wife?
Oh, she just like leaves. Clowning wife? A chevron wife. What is cheatable wife? Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. The clown wife is better. Clowny wife. Clown, a, a Holy
Clowny wife. Oh shit. What does that, the church, a Holy Cheatable Clowny wife. What about you?
I've been in this house the longest of all. Give me three things I wanted in life so I can finally
leave. Money. Money. Money. Money. Uh, recognition. Uh, a degree. A degree. Oh,
you wanted money more than a degree. Okay. Uh, a family. Here. There's a family. Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. Where's the baby going? Get away from the grill. Get away, get away from
this wicked hot lawyer. Oh, whatever he is. He's so hot. Get out of here, kids. You're not supposed
to be up here. Get out of here. Okay, actually get out of here. Actually get out. Actually,
I gotta kill this guy. That's not what, get rid of this guy. Seriously, get him out. Yeah,
that's not what I'm trying to say. Get all this out of here. I don't want any fires or anything.
Get everybody the fuck out of here. Now. Now. Good. He's gone. Okay. Now we're gonna put
shit that kids play with toys and stuff. Toys. A toy here. Look, a little car. Isn't that cool?
Good. And a tea set here. Look, kids like that and a little bed, like a little kid bed
and, um, a little, a boat. Sure. Get out of here. Don't come near the boat.
The engine is on. Get off. Get away. Get out. He really likes the bed. A toy boat.
He loves it. And a tub. A tub. A bathtub. Okay. He's all right. Get out. Get him out.
Get him out. Get him out. Get him out. Get him out. Get him out. Get him out. Get him out.
All right. He's happy. I didn't kill anybody. The baby is perfectly fine.
Look. What do you kids like? I don't know. Like bubble gum. Oh, wait. No. Here. Bubble gum.
And a diary. And, um, that's it. All right. Bye, guys. Have fun. I'll be back in like an hour.
What do you want in life? It's just burning out here. Three things he wanted in life. Give me a
sword, a dragon, and a princess. Well, I just spoiled it. There you go. And we'll make it a
huge dragon. Why am I on it? Why is he wet? Why am I still wet? Did I do everything? Oh, ghost hunter.
I got it. Why do I have a gun? Where are the kids? Okay. I'm just saying. I just, that freaked me
out for a second. I was like, why are there spiders everywhere? And where are the kids?
It was all a dream. All right. All right. Let's keep going. Let's go to, I don't know what this is.
Let's do it. The underline. I still have a gun. I'm so hungry and this machine is empty. Oh,
all right. Here. Wait, I have a gun. Edible gun. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. Absolutely not. Absolutely a thousand percent no. Okay. Uh, how about, um, grass?
Disgusting edible grass. Disgusting heart grass. Wait, what? Oh, wait. He's going to keep paying
for it. All right. Take it out. Take it out. I just made a new word. Okay. I didn't do an adjective.
All right. Disgusting edible grass. Eat it. Just eat it, man. It's not a big deal. Fine. Here.
It has to be edible. Okay. Here you go. You don't want this delicious edible trash?
What is this? Wrapper? All right. Go get it. Oh, just throw this away. All right. There you go.
Delicious wrapper in there. I'm so hungry. This machine is empty. How is a glass raw? No, no,
stop, stop, stop. Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck. Just put it down. It's going to break. Don't touch that.
It's not ready. It's not ready. I mean, you can put the adjectives in while you make the object though.
Why won't he buy this? He has money for a coin. Take that and spend it on this. An edible vending
machine in the edible vending machine. I can't. I can't. I can't. Hold on. What happened? Why won't
he go? Why won't he buy this? Did I fuck it up somehow? He needs a wallet. Oh, reset. How
did I get over here? All right. Well, new thing. I want to buy something from that stand, but I'm
broke. What an IOU. No, not the ICU. What about valuable bacon? There you go. You have valuable
trash. What do you want to buy? Uh, a what's the opposite of frugal? You just don't give a shit.
Not stingy, generous, opulent. The game know that word. All right. They made the transaction.
Uh, valuable trash for a bag of money. Yeah, it's one coin. You don't even have this back.
Oh, wait. Old ladies help walking across the sewer. I'm tired of standing. All right. Let's make a
chair. What just happened? Doesn't have any wheels. Help the street performer develop his career as a
rock star. Let's go. Should have done electric chair. Oh fucking God. No one even said that in
chat. I just pretended that they did. He wants to be a rock star. First needs a better instrument
to help him rock. Okay. It's better. Yeah. That sucks, dude. I was kind of hoping that. Wait,
hold on a minute. Like a musically talented animal. How about, um, a talented, uh, talented
chimpanzee. And we're going to give him a guitar. This instrument is awesome, but my bandwagon
sounded a lot better with additional members. All right. Well, hold on. So we need more members,
talented chimpanzee, musical gorilla, your lead singer. That's what I call a band. What we need
now is equipment to put on a real show. What happened to my character? Why does he look like
this? Uh, lights. Is he going to hold it up like a lighter? He's going to like, he's going to hold
it up with like a people to the phones now, right? Uh, what, um, stage. All right, here we go. Let's
start the party. You know how horrifying this would be if the street performer on the subway
had a gorilla and a chimpanzee just walking around. Oh my God, that'd be horrifying.
I don't care how well-trained a gorilla is. I don't care how friendly in quotes a gorilla is.
It takes a 10th of a second for them to like, not like the logo on your shirt or something.
And boom, your head is smashed into a thousand pieces.
Nope. I don't care how well-trained they are. That's scary. That was a Joe Rogan. That was a Joe
Rogan bit. All that shit up Jamie. Did he say that before? He's getting closer and closer to dying.
All right. What about back here? Sewer runoff. Yeah, let's go to the sewer. Well, okay. What
we got? The other fish keep making fun of me. Help me scare them away. A gun photo.
Oh, picture of a picture or gun. Oh, how about just gun picture? Golf picture. Here,
give it to him. You can't do gun guys. Gun and knife don't work. You need to make them like big,
inflated, like huge. Wait, he's gonna fly. Okay. He's dead. I'm ready for a new school to move in.
Ooh, crate. Um, cuppy. Come on in. Yeah. What's wrong with you? Blowing large goldfish. I've always
lived down here and don't know what I look like. Attack. I'm not deaf. We need to give him a mirror.
Wait, did I just like tell him that beauty is on the inside in a weird metaphorical way?
Oh, all right. Oh, he's scared. Oh, well, wait, let's go. You're too slow.
I'm sorry, but it's fine. You can be slow if you want. Make him fast. That's not very fast.
Speedy. I can't even fit down the hallway. All right, let's go. You and I are friends.
What's this even here? Oh, there's a guy down here. Be a bro and help me break free.
Be a bro. Oh, he was a criminal. He was a criminal. Oh, he was a criminal. I was supposed to like
kill him. Is that what it wanted me to do? Why was it? Did I not get the star for that? It was
help me break free. And it was like, you broke the criminal for you. Did the game want me to like,
why is there a cage down here? Was he like a murderer or something? I don't get it.
That was my brother. What am I talking about? He was my brother. I don't know. There's a cage
down here and he's throwing it. It's like, oh, you'll let the criminal free. I don't know. Wait,
you might have killed 10 people. I don't know. Oh, that was fun. Let's go. Can I take him with me?
Wait, fill the cage with something. I'm not putting him in the cage. I know a ton of you guys are
going to be like, oh, I put him nowhere. Not in a million years. Save the lobsters. Fool the fishermen
by filling their trap with something else to eat. Someone just sponges. It's because it was electric.
Yeah, put the electric huge, like 10,000 watt device down here with me. But wait,
didn't we talk about this already when that not happened? I told you guys, listen, for those that
weren't here like a year ago, me and chat got into a big fight because I said, hey, like if you drop
a fucking toaster plugged in into the ocean, like will it shock the, what would happen? What happens?
Everyone's like, you're crazy. No, no, no. What would have shocked the whole thing?
It was a hit man. Yeah. Okay. Let's, let's do something bigger than that. The whole ocean.
No. Okay. What if you were, hold on, but what if you were standing like a hundred feet away
of where it was dropped in? No, you asked. I wait, I am totally, I'm totally just like
gaslighting you guys on this. I asked if I dropped my iPhone in the bathtub, if I was in it, if it
would kill me. Oh, right, right, right, right. Okay. Lightning hits the ocean all the time.
All right. But what if you were in, don't, don't they tell you to get out of the water
during a storm? I thought that was a big deal. They do say that. Yeah, they do. What's taller
than the ocean. That's in case lighting hits you. Oh, he's alive. All right. Put some edible in here.
Can't move this. They're saying light, holdable, edible diaper in there. Pick up. There we go.
Okay. So this is, it's in there. He didn't eat that, did he? Oh shit, he did. Wait, he's already
like toxic. All right. What did they want me to do? No, don't, don't, it's a, do not put that,
something else. I just did the thing that they were trying to do. They're going to pull that up
and they're going to be like, ah, eh, remove the waste. There must be a better way to dispose of
this. Eat edible, vegan, edible, vegan, rich, edible, vegan. Right. Okay. Hold on. Hungry, vegan,
vegan, edible, toxic waste. I spell hungry wrong. It's my way. It's not, it's not hungry. Yes, it
is. Tasty, tasty, tasty, vegetarian. What did I just do? Hey, a tasty vegetarian. Okay. Edible
broccoli toxic waste. But, um, as Matt leaning, I just blow it up. Vegan, edible, toxic waste.
Then we have a glowing large vegetarian starving goldfish. Vegan, edible, toxic waste.
Make it non-toxic. Okay. Edible, non-toxic. What? Really? So I'll just make the toxic material
non-toxic. That's it. Oh, well, I guess it was that easy. All right. Now we got a few,
I want to go to one of the later areas over here. Let's go to the fountain.
And a four falls. That's drunk. What are they doing? Bring shock off, bring shock off. Bring. Can I,
can I bring nothing? I can't feel the sunlight by the river. It creates something to help me tan.
This is his like human skin and his jerky body. Oh, come here. Give me this.
But this should have put, yeah, I want to put, I want to take this. Whoa, frog. Place something
in between these logs to help me cross the river. Didn't help. How about some logs? How about a
bridge? So, but that's so easy to do, right? It's, oh, I made a bridge. Wow. Turn a businessman into
a fisherman. Nah, not yet. Hey, look what I got, man. Natural, natural, non-human. Uh, this person's
dead. What am I doing? Oh, shit. Hold on. What's wrong? Trying marketer. Please reunite me with my
love. What? This person's dead? Oh, okay. Who resurrects people? Hey, what the fuck are you doing?
No, not all of us. He did it to the frog. Oh, shit. He's actually a Diablo two necromancer.
All right. I'm sorry, but I'm going to give me a steak. Stab him through the fucking heart.
All right. Now I release you. Whoa. I, I'm, whatever. Leave me alone. Give it to me.
Cleanse the undead. Okay. Cleanse. No, now I need a priest. What the fuck is a priest going to do?
No, I need like a paladin. All right. Paladin. There we go. All right. Save me. Holy shit.
That, all right. Sorry. That's my bad. That's my bad. That's my bad. I spawned a level one paladin.
That, that's what would happen. Okay. What a shitty character. How about a sorcerer?
Go get it. How do I, how do you suppose, Zamboni? What is that? They're dead? Oh, they are dead.
I'll take the septid though. What? What? Being a businessman, how to fish. This man dreams of
being a fisherman. Start by dressing him appropriately. Fisherman hat. Fibered hat.
Firm, a fishable hat. Yes. That's exactly what I was thinking of. Next, he needs to catch some
fish. Give him an object to reel them in. Bass is not biting. Place something in the water that it
wants. Fish like cheese, right? Nice. Oh, it's an even bigger one. Time to catch the rainbow halibut.
It has more colorful taste. Oh, I like eating colorful food. Sherbert. Good catch. Now I have
to catch a fudge megalodon. Give the megalodon its dinner. No, it's going to kill it. What's a
megalodon's favorite dinner? It's like, it's like people or other huge, or how about like blue whale?
How big is this? It's huge, right? What's for dinner? It's a fudge megalodon.
Uh, no. There. Hooray! You did it. That's a big dolphin. That's definitely rideable too. He just
like went off and like nibbled on his grenade actually. Wait, you just turned it into a
skeleton. What'd you just do? You turned something into a skeleton to kill it. What was that? Help me
sail again. Oh, okay. Uh, here. What the fuck are you doing? She's going after the priest. The priest
bailed the fuck out of here and got out and was safe. She's going after the priest. She'd known
he peeked his head up behind the rock. He was like, are they gone yet? Oh shit. Help me sail again.
Okay. Um, what did I just get? I leveled up something. Oh, you stole the scepter. Wait,
did she just take that from you? What happened here? Okay. Help me sail again. Wait, there's a
big fish over there. What am I doing? The priest became a holy warrior. Oh, okay. All right. Let's
fix this boat. Uh, fix the engine. Fuck this. Let's use this one. Glue broken on boat. Blue.
Okay. Well, should I, I gotta get it out of the water. Look at these all alive. Balloons.
Why would a balloon take like a 10,000 pound, 20,000 pound boat out of the water?
Strong balloon. Okay. I gotta get rid of this thing. I hate this thing. All right. Come on,
pull it up. There it is. All right. What's wrong with it? It's got a problem. What we need to do?
Fix, uh, blue. All right. Stick that on there. Technically, it did it. This bird over here is
like, holy shit. You see what was just in the sky? Okay. I noticed an attack and shot a crossbow at
it. It was flex seal. Yeah. That's pretty, yeah. It was flex seal. How do I get up there? I'm here
with flex seal. I can even put it over my mouth to make me stop talking. I don't kill that bird.
Let the bird up. Why is there a bird? What the, why was there a bird in there? Why was there a
bird inside of the chest? I don't even know who that was. I, I, I'm going to say this and I don't
know if it's real or not, but I'm going to just think it is. You know how there are people make
slime videos. I feel like flex seal is some of that kind of stuff like flex putty and flex seal.
Do people make videos of them just like scooping it up and smearing it all over a
piece of wood or something? I would assume, right? Holy shit. I love this guy. Help me
practice my painting. Paintbrush. Wow. It's beautiful. I love it. What's going on over here?
Help me take a picture with this local. I want to dance, but I don't have a beat to follow.
I can solve that very quickly. Does that count? I'm going to take a picture.
You don't have a camera? Here, camera. Take it. Oh, I have the photo. Did it work? I think it
worked. The gorilla has something he wants. We only allow gorillas in our troop and you are no
gorilla. Yet. Get these wings off. I can't go in the gorilla suit? Oh shit. I didn't want to do that.
Take your clothes off. I don't have any clothes on. We only allow gorillas. You are no gorilla.
Move out of the way. Get out of the way. Blind them? No, that didn't work. Uh, where is this
person? No, no, they're not going to walk off the edge. They don't have that kind of pathing.
I need a gorilla costume. Get in. No, it didn't. Okay. A monkey suit. Why can't I wear it? You
have to edit your avatar? No. Edit your adjectives. Suspect small gorilla like? Gorilla mask? No.
Gorilla like. A gorilla like mask. We only allow gorillas. Wait, you're going to take the eye thing
off so you can see. Hey, look at me. I'm a gorilla. Look, you only allow gorillas and you are no
gorilla. What? He's not blind? Is he blind? Look, I'm one of you. Good sized fatherly musical silver
back gorilla. Motherly musical silver back gorilla. The suit on the, on the chimp? What are you talking
about? There's too many of these. Greet each monkey's human friend. What about the monkey?
He needs a gorilla like mask too? Gorilla like on yourself. Suspect gorilla like. I'm too small to
wear the costume. Really? That's so annoying. All right, now who? Nobody left? Oh, there's one more.
Where is it? Oh, right here. This game is really cute and really fun. Each monkey has a hobby.
Create a human that has similar taste to each monkey. Start by making someone for the musical
monkey. Okay, fine. I don't know what's attached to me. Monkey tail on furry ears. Did I sit on
top of something? How is that monkey? Bat wings. All right. What did I get? Okay. You want somebody
that likes music? How about a composer? All right. You. Flying monkey grew wings after drinking a
potion creates someone for this magical monkey. A witch. Warlock. Is he riding the crossbow?
Whatever. This computer savvy monkey loves playing video games. Create a friend for this monkey.
The you player? How about a youngster? You. This monkey is also wearing a rooster hat.
Create a friend for this monkey. Well, a rooster, of course. Or yeah. What does edgy even mean? I
don't get it. Hooray. I got one. And that's it for that. It's about to cover her head.
I love this game. It really is just fun. Even more locations. Holy shit. There's a lot.
All right. How about. Should I do the pirate one? The penitentiary. Hold on. Welcome to the paper
and penitentiary. Give me something to blend into the environment and make me escape.
Uh, blend into the environment. Like a prison suit. Okay. Uh, sure. What about you?
All supervillains have an evil animal companion. I need one. Uh, what do you. Okay. Why was he
swinging that at me? That was weird. We need someone who would want to watch these televisions
all day. All right. Security guard. I was going to say like, I'm like a gamer. I'm a chatter.
I would, I would think that'd be fun. Gamer. I was going to write streamer,
YouTuber, but they don't know what that is. What does, why is this chat? Hey guys, I'm coming.
Yeah. Self-proclaimed gamer. Uh, excuse me. I beat Hades in less than 10 tries. I got to the last
boss in Hades in less than 10 tries and beat him. I mean, it just watched it last night. I'm a
certified gamer at least for a little while. Who cares? Apparently not you.
Conceal something in my cake to help my friend burrow through the prison walls.
That two or three seconds later, that was a distance explosion. You're letting
criminals out of prison. Whatever. All right. Let's do this one. What's this?
Each prisoner, eh, give him a reminder of home.
Baste, base, base. What, what? I was bored. I want to do those based.
Each person needs a cellmate that they have something in common with.
Okay. He wants to be involved with sports. Eh, how about a coach? Here we are. I thought they
were zombies for a second. The halfling was captured during an important quest. Give the
halfling a member of her adventuring party. A wizard. Saxophone player misses making music
with others. Write someone to join the band. A jolly pianist. The actress misses practicing
her lines with other lesbians. Write someone from the movie industry that can shoot pra, pra. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Why am I in a police uniform? Sorry, honey. Wait, we're not like
together. Sorry, honey. I brought your bald, bald pot. Not Brad Pitt. This isn't like my
girlfriend in here. It's not visiting my girlfriend in prison. Yeah. How about with the director?
Throw a ball pot on the ground like that. It's an accomplished actor.
Scientist needs somebody to share concepts with. Uh, doctor. Uh, Gordon Freeman. Gordon Foreman.
Gordon Freemason. Gooey Freemason. It's just the half life porn parody.
Gordon, Gordon Freemason. Deleted. How about, I don't know, who would be like a history teacher?
Who would be interested in this? Uh, chemist. This cosplayer is a huge fan of video games and anime.
Write someone from nerd culture that he can talk to. Oh, this is my opportunity.
What? Don't you know who I am? Have you never seen me before? I'm on twitch.tv. It's like,
there's like 9,000 people watching me. What? Are you serious? This is a new console. This is not,
now that was faulty. Nevermind. Sexy new console. Shiny new console. How about pinball machine pog?
Seriously, none of this stuff, you're into this? You don't want pinball. You don't want the anime
DVD. You don't want the brand new console. You're a gamer and you love anime. How about that? A
fan of anime figurine. Wait, take that off. I gotta make it an anime figurine. That looks like,
yes, my anime figurine. The main character from The Critic. John Lovitz. Anime, no. What,
what else does he want? Controller. Air. New console, new controller. A, um, a powdered drink.
No? Free chat. He wants a person? He wants a ninja to train with. Oh, come on. No, what?
No, it's, you got like three grand in free stuff. I don't want to hear shit out of you, buddy. I
think I got it all right. Oh, of course I'm going to take fucking bald pop. Did it go all right?
Yeah, well done. This person's pretty pog. Kind of is. Uh, I think I crashed it. What happened?
No, come on. What? What happened? Not responding. Well, shit. Hold on. Does it save right there?
It saves often? Yeah, it should be fine. Yeah, we're good. Oh, that's sad. All right, real quick,
I'm going to do a speedrun. Let's get everybody's stuff that they want and just put them down here
right now. If everybody a monkey. Okay, here we go. We want, we're going to do a coach.
We're going to do, then we're going to do, we need a, uh, a scientist, chemist. Okay, good. Go,
just go over there. Okay, now we need a, uh, a lawyer or something, right? I don't know. Maybe.
All right, let's go. Yep. He wants a party member wizard. You're good. It didn't work. Quad? Well,
you didn't get a wizard. You didn't get a party member, but you got a fucking quad.
Saxophonic player. You? What? Why is this character like a weird evil? What's the evil
character for? There. Uh, actress. Right. There's the lawyer. Oh, right. Okay. All right. Now you.
What the hell is in here? Why is this in here? Why did you just shit out a nuclear bomb?
Why is the gamer in here? That can scientific opinion. Let's get it. Let's get a garlic
scientist's opinion on this whole thing. Game of the year. It's literally the red button meme.
That's why I'm not pressing it. I'm not going to press it. I'm not going to press it. I know
that you all here. Here it comes. Good. I got to get the fuck out of here now before something bad
happens. I didn't press it. I didn't press the button. I didn't press it. I didn't press it.
Why are they killing each other? Criminal sledgehammer? Why is there a criminal sledgehammer?
Bulletproof. Obluthophic nuke. I don't know what that second word means, but goodbye.
It's a rate of bathing. That's weird. Obliphonic? He's a gamer. No. What is this guy?
Uh, excuse me. Gamer. Here's your opportunity. I want to talk to someone who will help me down
the righteous path. Well, that didn't work. A teacher. I don't know. Yeah. Jesus Christ.
Chris Christ. All right. That's it. No, there's two more. Oh shit. What about you? Jesus Chris.
Oh, there's another thing right there. Come closer. Come closer. Come closer. Where the hell are all
these new people? Show me something from the yard I was stolen from. All right. Grass. Cactus. There.
Hooray. Show me something that the Easter bunny likes. Living here hinders my creativity. Help
me paint this egg. Blonde egg. Oh, that's the same color. We didn't do anything. Help Maxwell escape
from the prison. Maxwell needs to escape prison. Give the tired guard a place to sit and he might
unlock the gate. All right, get off of it. Iron maiden. The guard unlocked the door. Now a ghost
stands in the way. He can't open the door without a physical presence. All right,
are you going to get off of it? Just get off. I just took his only defense. Get off. You idiot.
I'm going to kill this chair. All right, let's go. It doesn't fit in here.
Whatever. It's a place to sit down. I repeat. I'm under attack by the chair. Need backup.
I need a physical body. Sure. Hey, it worked. The ghost scared the door open. Now a prisoner is
craving a hearty meal. Give him something filling. Hmm. Hearty meal. Eggs benedict. Eggs benedict.
Over easy. Over easy benedict. How is it? Prisoner destroyed the door. A con man has agreed to help
Maxwell. But he needs to disguise himself as an officer to fool the camera. This guy has a
cannibal. He need a disguise. How about a police officer outfit? Police oiled? Police official.
Pricy official costume. What? No, I called uniforms. Police uniform. Who the hell is this?
Running the security system is a lonely job. The programmer has been here for too long and misses
his furry pet. Even man's best friend. How do I go down? This guy's a fucking idiot. Me or the guy
in the game? Because I was going to make him a furry iguana. I didn't want to just do dog.
That's too easy. Idiot adjective. Whatever. Santa Claus up here. Move out of the way.
Shovel. Alright. Werewolf. I want a fang from that werewolf. Open the door. Open the door.
Oh, I have to do it. What's wrong Santa? This prison food does not follow my strict fattening
diet. Just ate lard off the ground. That's disgusting. Reach the starite in the tower.
Mayo. Lard and mayo aren't the same thing. Complete the gauntlet to reach the starite.
Begin by getting out of this room. Sure. Box on here. Good. Alright. Gotta get through safely.
Sprinkler. Turn on the sprinkler. Nice. Beware falling objects. Hard hat. What? The robot guard
stands watch. Quickly make it to safety. Oh shit, he has a... Oh my god, he has a shield.
Shield. Shield. Shield. Shield. Shield. Shield. Shoot him. What just happened? Mobile game.
I know exactly what you're talking about. I get that ad all the time. Where it's like, no!
We're gonna save them from the fire! And you have to pull the three things on the edges.
And this one makes the water go in and there's like a princess. She's like, no, no!
No! The guy underneath. And then guess what? That shit ain't even in that game. I've played
that game before. That is the ad for Homescapes and I've played that game. That doesn't even
happen in that game. That's a match three game. What? That didn't happen in my game.
They've recently banned those ads. Did they really? On what grounds? Why? Because of false...
Really? That actually happened. That's so funny. That wasn't even in the fucking game.
Watch out for the spikes. Uncreative. I already did this one. Your character kind of looks like
my character does look like this. That's wicked funny, man.
What the hell are you shooting at? Wait. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Open the door!
What? It was destroyed? Make it to the time machine to set things right. Fluffy. Fuzzy.
There. Now I can't hurt anymore. What? Oh, I can't. Oh, right, right. Okay.
Actually, you can help me here. What? Like just like a cart? Sorry. Shrink ray? Shrink
ray and then suck it up with a vacuum. Doesn't work. That's not going to start this all over,
is it? I don't think I should do that. It already is a black hole. What? A heal? Healing potion.
A healing suspect. Immortal. How about that? Yeah. Unkillable. Invincible. Oh.
I don't think immortality works either. Sorry. This guy's still alive. How did I not kill this
guy? All right. He seems to be sitting around. Key's in the way. God damn it. That's going to
kill me. It's going to roll over and kill me. I need the key though. Use? Make a new key.
Okay. Shit. Come on. Really? No, it took it over. Come on. All right. Turn it off and spin it this
way. All right. We're good. Bye. Where am I? My head. Oh, please. Find a way outside. Oh my God.
Okay. I'm not. I got smaller. Tiny. Get it. Shrunk and tiny. Shrunk and tiny. Shrunk and.
I think that's good. Watch out for hazards. What do you mean watch out for hazards? Oh, up here.
Wait. What? Holy. Whatever. Oh, I could do this whole fucking thing again.
All right. The umbrella. The umbrella was fucking me up. Oh my God. All right. Box.
Sprinkler. Turn it on. No. Turn. Get it. I want to be able to match him in firepower. Let's
annihilate him. Box. Oh. Sprinkler. Check out the dump truck add-on. Yeah. I've already seen it.
Spray him with water. He's electric. There you go. Now what are you going to do?
All right. Well, he's going to eat whatever. He's going to be tortured forever. Oh no. The key.
Open the door. Good. Tiny. Shrunk and small. Minuscule. Ow. I scraped my skull. All right.
This time we're going to do this right. Uh. Wings. Here we go. Okay. I gotta have something.
Press that button. A big rod. Good. Let's go. Watch out for the lightning on this roof. Good.
Hey, get to the time machine. Watch out for the strong gusts. The spikes are dangerous.
Oh, are they? Oh, what? How did that happen? Wait. That's instantly. Holy shit. That sucks.
What? Why? I'm going to leave. You keep dying. I'm trying. Look, I'm trying my absolute hardest.
Those things are going to move. Okay. Just take his fucking gun. Oh my God. Please don't die.
Please don't die. Please don't die. What am I doing? Click on him. Give me that key. You're
fucking kidding me. Tiny. Tiny. Tiny. There we go. Every time. Every time. It doesn't matter.
Whatever. Oh, we're good. Okay. So I'm going to block it with a vent or something. I'm going
to cover that up. I'm going to put like a tarp on it. I don't know. Like a pool tarp. Boulder.
It looks like concrete. Can I just run through this? Just give me like a missile launcher and
I'm just running through. That's water in there. Okay. Let's relax for a second. Just a minute.
Just a second. What? What? Can I do this? At least I can do this. Okay. Good.
Soundproof. Brighten object. No, no, no. Go back. I can't walk down. I think I have to destroy this
stuff. Otherwise those don't fall. Put on heavy shoes. Would that work? Take his gun. Take his
gun. Take his gun. Take his gun. Have you watched the Daedalus Effect stream? I streamed the Daedalus
Effect stream. That was me. It was a deep fake. I don't want to fuck this up again. I got to get
out of this stupid prison again. Tiny and what else? Shockproof. All right. Let's go. I need a
balloon. I need wings. I'm going to give wings to you too. Come with me. We can do it together
and you can be sort of the, uh, the guy that goes first. One wing. All right. Come with me.
Follower. Friendly flying, flying friend. Let's go. Guardian. Just rope him. He's having fun.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Let go. Let go. Let go. Let go. Let go. This camera is horrible. I don't
know where it is. Hold on. Let go. Stop pulling me that way. Stop pulling me that way. Let go.
No, I took off my cool hat. No, I took off my cool stuff. No, I took off my cool nose. No,
I took off my cool wings. There. Okay. Here we go. So, uh, heavy, heavy pants. Why am I flying?
Heavy shoes are too small. Oh, uh, okay. It's not working. Get rid of the wing.
Holy shit. Okay. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I have an idea. What if I put just like a,
like a metal platform or something or like a, what if I just, I'm going to weigh myself down
with something. I don't know, like a piano. I just mini golfed off the piano into this bike.
Just make yourself heavy. I, wow. Metal wings. Make yourself really obese. Slow and obese.
Certain size increases. Uh, you see, I, you can't, you're not allowed. I know what it is.
Turn it on. What about an anvil? I mean, I, I put a whole house on there and it was blowing it up.
I think I just have to wait till it's not blowing and then go. Use a helmet? I don't think that's
going to do anything. Wait, how did you get that back? Make yourself really fast. I'm going to,
I'm going to do incredibly fat, incredibly heavy, incredibly fast.
Cover the spikes so I can't crash into him. It all, it all falls. It's physics.
Make an immovable object. What's more immovable than a house? This is jump king. It kind of is.
He's mad at this game. No, I'm not. Says who? I love this. Okay. I'm going to make an immovable,
an immovable, I'm going to make an immovable house. It's going past it. Holy shit. That scared me.
Oh, Pog. Champ. Pog. Champ. Pog. I should get that out of the way.
Time travel hasn't been destroyed yet. Grab it. I thought that was going to be way harder. Did it.
I did it. They're going on the roof streamers. You go to children's game. It's not a children's game.
It's an E for everyone game. That means everyone can enjoy it.
These watch towers don't come with a bathroom. Put a toilet in there? All right. Yeah. Did you
go in it? What about you? I'll bridge the gap between the princess and me. Easy. Black hole them
together. Easy. Why do they always jump off the roof? What's wrong with everybody? What is wrong
with everybody? All right. Let's keep going. I've been playing this for five hours. What the hell?
Where'd the time go? What about the pond? Alligator. I love alligators. I really got to go,
but it's really gross in there. Oh, he means in here. I'll just use it. All right. It's really
gross in there. Let's clean it. Um, mop. You all right. Oh, there we go. All right. He mopped it.
You can now play as Maxwell's brother Scratch. Don't think I want to. Oh, get these woodpeckers
away from me. Look what's over here. A nice tasty juicy worm. They don't eat worms? What do they eat?
That one held on for so long. I need to restart. That was horrible. Hillbilly. Uh, okay. You want
to abduct the- give us what we want and we'll leave you in peace. Okay. You definitely want
to abduct this guy. Let's make it easy. All right. Use the bridge. Why are you stupid? All right. What
does he like? How about this? How about, um, Hungry Hillbilly? Get him. Suck him up. Oh, Jesus Christ.
Help Maxwell find aliens. The aliens walk among us in disguise. The first alien is afraid of
bright lights. Flashlight. Flood light. Uh, fluorescent light. Twilight light? Twilight
fluorescent twilight? Okay. I don't think- bright light. You don't like bright lights. What about
the sun? That's very bright. Got him. Afraid of loud noises. This guy? Okay. Loud noises. Symbols.
Let's smash them together. There you go. Foster. Terrified of- what did it say? Water? Terrified of
water. You don't want it? You're not even a real cat. Blow you off with a fan. Now what? Now what?
Afraid of heights. It's you. It's- I think it's her. It's me. Fungi? No, trampoline, right?
Could launch him up in the air. What did I think was gonna happen? Like, really? What did I honestly
think was gonna happen? All right. Let's make this quick. I'm trying to get it on her. Whatever. It's
here for you whenever you want it. Okay. Light. Sound. Butter. Nuke. Th- but I- I need to complete
this. What? Did my shirt- did my shirt get caught on the edge of the- did my shirt get caught on
the edge of the cabinet and like fucking just snap my neck? What the f- The sun with the trampoline?
What- why- the sun's not killing us when it's down here? Okay, so you're telling me that the sun being
10 feet away from us is okay, but if I touch the sun, I instantly die. We'll get the hell out of
here then. Oh my god. Okay. Loud sounds. Jesus. I did it! Oh, I can't believe I died from the sun.
Didn't use nuke, didn't you? No, I'm not gonna use a nuke. Oh, barbecue? Play something to grill on
the barbie. Oh, yes. Um, I'll take the wings off. Uh, okay. What do I need to cook? How about a shish kebab?
Yes! I haven't had a bite in weeks. Well, look what I got for you. It's a shish kebab. What are you
doing? What the fuck are you doing, man? Why are you so mad at me? You don't want a shish kebab?
Raw chicken. He's so mad at this frog. He's pissed. He eats- he just ate me. Don't eat the frog!
Um, all right. I don't know. We'll just, like, person. Blowing toxic alligator. I need somebody
to kiss. A princess? Oh, I don't know. Can the princess kiss the frog and it turns into a prince?
Prince frog. Oh, I need to feed this alligator. What about just a chicken? Just the bird. A chicken.
Not into it. What's his problem? He's not even aggressive anymore. Oh, maybe it's because I
dropped a nuke on him. Okay. Oh, everything is softlocked because of the nuke. Well, these guys
are all right. These guys didn't get affected. I want to be a duckling. Okay, how about a duck-like
turtle? Duckie turtle. Oh, fuck it. Whatever. The place is- I nuked it. What about ruins of ellipsis?
Duckie is my favorite. Oh, shit. I still have radioactivity on me. Clean. I'll be glowing still.
That's fine. Clean. Lowing. Clean. Clean. There. Okay. This carnivorous plant may hold the cure
for many diseases, but I can't get it to bloom. Blood. Right? There. Hungry. It's a hungry
carnivorous plant. We need to put, um, like, fertilizer? Pick it up. Fertilize it. Not what
I had in mind. Bugs in there. Ant. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it under control. I got it.
Huge anthill. Our leader has died. Create a new leader suitable for us. Oh, sure. What's he eating?
Our leader's died. Create a new leader. Um, the huge, cosmic, obese, kingly ant is not queen. Oh,
you're right. That's true. Queenly, obese, cosmic, huge, ant leader. Laser. How fit your party of
brave adventurers for a legendary journey? Wait. What about the bird with the hair? Uh, no. What about
you? I'm so plain. Add an adjective to me so I can fit in. Here we have hair. Green. Parakeet
tropical. Okay. I didn't do anything. You just put barbecue sauce on me. Oh, right. Right. Right.
Sorry, man. Man, sorry about that, man. Hold on, man. I got you. Hold on, sir. Sorry about that,
my friend. I'll take care of that. Just really quick. Hold on. I'm gonna just take care of that
real quick. Uh, let's have a cheesy, man. Cheesy, man. Hey, cheese. No, no, no. That one's dumb,
too. I don't want that one. That one's stupid, too. Uh, how about gravity bird?
Gravely bird. It's just going up there and it's gonna go directly into this bird's nostrils and
puke is gonna go over on this side of the screen. How about a lovely bird? Hey. Wait, he's like,
you made me ugly. Just give me something to help me study these chimps. There, a video camera.
Crystal huge rib cage. Oh, wait, he's kicking his... Oh, no. If I'm ugly, then no one can be pretty.
Only him, though. Why? Oh, I can't give him the slingshot. The ultimate. The ultimate. Not even
real anymore. VR? Mango tree. Still missing something. Oh, down here. Well, sorry to hear
that. How about this one? Outfit the party. Prepare the adventurers for an epic quest. Provide the
warrior with a weapon. So good. Heat ray. Uh, a spare cannon. Cannon. I thought that was gonna
rock his head back. There. A whip. What about you? A weapon he can use from a distance. Maybe a bow
and arrow? No. No way. This magician wants to do something magical. A weapon that channels
magical ability. The cleric's role is to support the team. Give her something to heal the party
members. No? That's disgusting. Fine, here you go. Nice. Nice shooting. Nice microphoneing.
Is there something I could have done there to stop them? Oh, no. She's gonna revive. Did I give them
these? Oh, cool. Very cool. Very nice. Uh-huh. You know, I was the manager of the team, so
I think I deserve a couple of these. Yeah. Four gem... Four gold coins dropped. I'm gonna take
four and a half, and you're gonna split the other half evenly between the four of you,
and then you're gonna get ready, and you're gonna fucking go on another adventure, and we're gonna
do it all over again. I'm an asshole. You get one fourth of one coin. I'll be taking that one.
He said communist? When did I say that? I just said I told you to go in there, and then I took
four and a half coins. Help me find the crystal bones of... I know where they are. I know where
they are. Capitalist, not communist. Oh. I'm so glad that didn't hit me right in the fucking head.
All right, here we go. I got you juicy baby back ribs. There's more? Oh.
Found one. Put this dude back together again. Take it. Capitalist in chat. Guys, I've told you
about how much money I lost on Beyond Meat. Is that something that you would hear from a communist?
Break this down. I saved the bunny. Okay, now we need to... He's a fake communist. What does
that even mean? Investing in fake meat. No, I told the story already. I was like, the things valued
at like five times Microsoft. There's no fucking way. Absolutely not a chance in hell that this
stays at this insane price. No fucking way. And it did. And it went higher. Way higher.
I was like, well, this is stupid. But these are the bones. Oh, up here. I have to dismount.
You scared? Oh, you were scared that whole time? What is it? Are you okay? Are you all right?
Take off like the... Take off the glasses. Take off the... Hey, it's okay.
It's all right. I need wings. Yeah, this is also... This is like two or three years ago.
Help him. I'll help him, don't worry. There's more bones. Are you kidding me?
Oh, no, there's not. All right, there we go. I did it. That's it. Oh, there's one more thing
that I didn't do. Remember, went to biz, made a bunch of awful investments and never looked back.
And though that didn't happen, I did. Look, we have to understand. Oh, and by the way,
by the way, all of the haters and all the people that were making fun of the crypto stuff. Oh,
he's got an Ethereum account. He's got BTC. It's dead. Have you looked at it today? Did you look
at it yesterday? Well, isn't that interesting? It's almost back to all time high. I was told
that it was dead in the water. And look at me now. I sold it at like a 60% loss because I was
terrified. Because after it went down to like $3,000, I was like, all right, well, it's gone. I'm
going to sell. But that doesn't exclude the principle that I knew it was going to be a thing.
I knew it was going to happen, but I needed some of that cash. I needed a cash flow at that moment.
I didn't want to sell them, but I needed the cash because that was when I was moving here.
I was moving to Vegas and I was like, you know, I could use, I could use, I could use like a few
thousand dollars right now. Don't worry. Cause I made it all back with this last run. What are
you talking about? Oh, this person has no idea. Cryptocurrency, Bitcoin, BTC. Like three years
ago, I talked about how I was like really into it and I was getting involved. It may not have
been around for like three or three years ago, like four years ago almost. Let's go to new zone.
All right. I will, let's do one more. I want to go to pirate code. Bitcoin's not even a currency.
Well, you, I can't think of something worse to say to like an internet group of technologically
sound individuals. And then what you just said out loud, there's a bunch of people here probably
that that's like just, you essentially just told everybody, like all of your politics,
how you believe in everything. And then you just started, that's a war. You just started
like a chat war. I need a tool from my trade to finally settle this argument. New, what's going
on down here? Something terrible has happened to the crew. Help break the curse. Crew has become
cursed. Give each crew, Otto. What are you doing, Otto? Hold on. Uh, let me get, I gotta go pee too.
Let me get Otto and go pee. I think he wants to come in. You want to come in? All right. One
sec. Slugs outdated. Dupe overrated. Long have I waited. Otto has invaded. Hi, Otto. He has invaded
actually. He's in the room right now, sleeping on his bed. Uh, there we go. Show Otto for minus
a hundred million off the dead, right? Uh, I hope the webcam's not even like plugged in.
I plugged in my controller for yesterday. It's a deal. Oh, shit. Hold on. Let me think about that.
Give the warrior of our group a medieval weapon. Attilax. Okay. Give. First curse has been broken.
The next crew member loved his facial hair, but now he's almost bald. Okay. Beard. Long beard.
Uh, I guess regular beard. Okay. What? Tick tock. Tick tock. Deal's running out. All right. All
right. A hundred million. A hundred million, right? 100 million off the dead. Let's go.
Oh, my webcam is plugged in. He lied about that. I didn't. Yes, he did. I may have. Watch out.
Show him now. I am. My webcam's like, this is, this webcam was last used on Halloween.
Set up for all the Halloween settings. Turn off auto. This looks like shit. Why does this look so
terrible? This, this looks like a video game. Whatever. I, I've looked like I'm, I'm, that's
sepia toned. There is no Otto. There is Otto. Hold on. There is Otto. Scam. No, I'm just like
getting him in the right spot. I don't, I don't want to like just rip him up here. He's fragile.
You don't want to just like, oh, here's my dog. Okay. Come here. I'm, no, I'm not, this is not
the dog yet. Hold on. That's a hundred million, by the way. That's a hundred million, by the way.
He's my special boy. Favorite thing in the, favorite person in the world. And yes, he is a
person. He's my little person. The camera sucks in a really shitty place. Let's just, just pretend
I was out here this whole time. Yes. Hey, haircut. Delayed. Oh, why was it delayed? That's weird.
Shave that hundred million off, please. All right. Let's finish this up. What's the next task? The
Wisp needs a mirror. Mirror. Mirror for the Wisp. The synced footage does not count. Yes, it does.
Teach the brainless crew member. Professor. He's so scared. What about Polly? Where you unite me with
Polly? Tarakete. There he is. The synced footage is 50% what it's worth. What are you talking about,
man? That is not true. That's unbelievable. That was not in the contract. That was not in the verbal
contract. It was just show Otto on cam. It didn't say it had to be the right sync. It didn't say it
had to have the right audio settings. It was just show Otto on cam. That's a hundred million shaved
off the debt. Thank you very much. I'll take the hundred million shaved off the debt, please.
Oh, this is due to the final areas. 75. No, a hundred million. That's what we agreed on.
Come to the final areas. Speaking of Otto, I actually need to feed him. That's why he came
over here in the first place. And it's been about six hours. I think it's time for me to go.
I also need to feed myself too. Feed Otto on stream. No, no, I'm not bringing all his food
up here. Enable Link's tiny man? Did you guys abuse it? Yeah, that's why he was like barking
at the door. He's like, excuse me. Like, it's time, man. Get down here and feed me. That's a
good place to stop. That was a lot of fun. Maybe I'll keep this in the bag for random days. It's
pretty fun. It was just fun to chill and do this. A billion if I show Otto feeding him on stream?
No way. One billion. That's a major amount. We're seeing that. We're seeing that's a deal.
Okay. Do I have to do it right now or can I open the next stream with that? Instead of my starting
soon screen, I will have a camera set up for it. Otto is eating stream starting soon screen.
You know what words I was just trying to say. It's now or never. No, I'll do it now. I'm fucking
dying to see him. I'll do more Otto content, I promise. Let's delay him so he can't feed. No,
what are you crazy? There is no delay. It's over. I'll see you guys on, let's see, Tuesday?
Tuesday or Thursday? Tuesday or Wednesday? Probably Wednesday. Yeah, we'll go Wednesday,
Thursday, Friday. We'll go at least Wednesday, Thursday, Friday in this coming week. I have
things to do. I have some decisions to make. I have to talk to my doctor. I told you earlier.
Some of you may have not been around, but I have to start setting up some of these procedures.
I'm going to get trigger point injections into my back. I've had injections before in my butt.
It did a little bit. It didn't do a whole lot, but they're actually going to do it into the
trigger points this time. For those of you that don't know, I've had this lingering annoying
medical problem for the last couple of years. I'm back in chest hurt all the time. It never
goes away. It never gets any worse. I get tight sometimes if I sit down or stand for too long.
But the solution, I've been through the absolute wringer when it comes to exams and procedures and
everything. I have two discs in my spine that are dark, which is signaling some type of,
at least mild start of degeneration. I also have a hernia in my esophagus,
hiatal hernia. Not that big, but it may be causing some of the chest problems. They think I might
just be getting combo'd. I'm going to do trigger point injections. My back muscles are always
painful, so we're going to see if that works. If that helps, then I might not have to do very
much else. Yeah, the part where your esophagus connects to your stomach. That's where my hernia
is called the hiatal hernia. Dad had something similar. The injections helped. I hope so,
because honestly, it's the back that's... I could deal with that upper kind of abdominal,
mid, center of my chest pain. It's not that big of a deal. But man, the spine and back pain.
It's debilitating sometimes, I'll be honest. Sometimes it'll get so tight that it kind of
drives you crazy, right? Especially if I do a lot of activity. And that's why, I remember after the
green screen stream, I did a lot of activity and then turned into dog shit. So the idea is to go
get these injections, go get the trigger point injections, and go manage kind of that spinal
problem. And that won't happen anymore. I can kind of live my life normally without having this just
constant sort of tight, just aggravating pain right through the center of my back into my chest.
But I'm good now. A lot of people saying, take care of yourself. Do what you need to do.
I already have. Guys, I used to stream for like seven to eight hours every time I turned the stream
on. I would say I would at least be here for six to eight hours, seven to nine hours sometimes.
I don't do that anymore. I just don't. So I've already made those changes. 12 hour Simpson stream.
Sometimes they go longer than that. But this kind of every two or three hours, get up and take a
break, stretch, get some water, come back. Five, six hours goes by and it's like, all right, I'm
gonna get up. So it's been working pretty well, I think. Because I can tell you right now,
absolutely sitting for another two hours would not be good. It would be very bad. So sometimes
I am going to cross that length though, right? Like seven hours, maybe like seven and a half.
I think I've streamed for like seven hours yesterday or something, right? Sometimes it's
going to happen, but it's not going to be the norm anymore. But that was very, very stalling.
He's stalling to end the stream, right? I am. But for a lot, some people might not know that that's
kind of going on. There's a lot of new people here over the last couple of years, especially
the last six months. So some of you newer viewers that may have just kind of started watching over
the last year. I'm not sure if you've known some of you do, some of you don't. So I'll talk about
it sometimes just to keep everybody up to date. But that's going to be it. I'll see you guys on
Wednesday. Thanks for all the subs, everybody. And there was some huge donations too. Thank you guys,
seriously. Next week will be interesting because there's a lot of highly recommended games that
are probably going to happen. Probably going to play Sly Cooper. People have been waiting for
that one. I'm playing the PS3 remastered one. That's okay, right? They didn't mess it up somehow
in the remaster? Good. Okay. Thanksgiving family guy joke incoming. Well, no, I'm not even going
to say anything because the reason why I was like two or three minutes late, I was here. I was here
for like an hour or two before the stream. I was on the phone. I was in a call with my manager
to talk about a very specific stream that we're starting to work on right now. That's why I was
just like, I got to fucking go. I got to call my manager. Baseball. Baseball already is happening
in 2021. I have talked to my manager about so many projects over the 2020 that couldn't happen in
2020 that we wanted to do in 2020. So obviously because of COVID. So once COVID is under control,
there's so many things that are just back to back to back to back to back that I've already
either done or almost done. That 2021 should be ridiculous in regards to streams that I've
wanted to do for a long time. It's never going to happen. I want you to remember that because
just like the carnival, some of these things that I decide I want to do, I'm doing them no matter
what. The one that I'm talking about is happening no matter what. It's going to happen.
Baseball especially. But when? I'll tell you when it happens. I'll let you know beforehand. Don't
worry. What if society collapses? It's not. Look, I'm going to do these streams. The sides are not
going to collapse. All right. I have to feed Otto. All right. Yeah. People are like, go, go, go.
All right. I'll see you guys on Wednesday. Take care of yourselves. Have a great rest of the night.
Goodbye. Take care. Thanks for watching. That was Scribble Nuts with Jirba985.
Oh god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Hold on. End of the stream. End of the stream chat picks the next
stream. We did. That did happen. I did say that. Right. Okay. What is it? You guys stuck around for
a long time. People like left. All right. What's going on on the next stream? You want to get a
little poll going? Okay. Let's do it. I was getting up to walk out of the room. All right. Here comes
the poll. All right. Seeing a signal simulator. I'm not going to play TF2. That's vetoed. No TF2.
I don't know. No TF2. All right. Signal Sim Sly Cooper. Let's get this right. This is for the next
time I turn the stream on, by the way. You have the power here. Signal Sim Sly Cooper.
Six grueling hours of Scribblenauts for this moment. Sometimes I feel like I have you guys
tied down to like an electrifying chair. I just saw. Okay. I saw Yakuza. What? Which one?
I played Yakuza 0 for like a few hours. I already played. You want me to go back to Yakuza 0
or the new one? Go back. Yes. Go back. Go back. Go back. Go back. I'm begging you for Nancy Drew.
Fine. It's going on the list. All right. I'm going to. I'm just going to write like Yakuza?
Question mark. Yakuza. What? The guy was begging me for what? Oh yeah. Nancy Drew.
Or let's say a house flipper DLC. All right. We have a lot of categories here. We have a lot of
nominees here. Not Doki Doki. You had your only chance to pick Doki Doki. And you guys didn't
pick it. You dropped the ball on it. Slime Rancher. Okay. Slime Rancher is going on here.
All right. Okay. All right. All right. This is, this is enough. This is enough.
We got one, two, three, four, five, six. By the way, we're not doing,
we're not doing any elimination. No. Okay. We'll do one. Okay. We'll do two elimination rounds.
One, two, three, four, five, six. Two elimination rounds. Here's the first poll. Go for it. Let's
see. Right off the bat we have. Okay. I can't say any words. I can't mention anything. If I mention
any of these, they will instantly get a hundred votes. Even if I say that this X game is dog shit,
it'll be clicked a hundred times. All right. Okay. We have some eliminations we're going to do.
We're going to eliminate two things per round, by the way. That's how this works. The lowest two
based on vote, not on percentage on vote count are gone. All right. I'm closing the first round
in five, in 10 seconds. 10 seconds. Closing the poll. 10 seconds. 10, nine, eight, seven, six,
nine, four, three, two, one. There we are. That's it. What's lowest? Slime Rancher and
Signal Sim. No, no, no, no, no. Slime Rancher and Yakuza? No, Slime Rancher and,
there's still so many votes coming in. There's so many votes coming in. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. I don't have to take a screenshot. All right. Here we go. I'm going to take a
screenshot in 10 seconds. All right. 10, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
That's it. Screenshot. That's it. What do we got? Okay. When I said that, here it is.
The two that are getting eliminated are Slime Rancher and Signal Simulator. Those are eliminated
from the running of next stream. The second round is coming in. Give me a second. Round two. Another
two will be eliminated this round. So we still have Sly Cooper still on there. We still have
Yakuza, which whatever one, which I will decide. We still have Nancy Drew. Why the fuck is this
still on here? How did this get more than 10 votes? And House Flipper DLC. Okay. Yakuza, Sly Cooper,
Nancy Drew, or House Flipper DLC. Here we go. Same deal. I'm going to take a screenshot.
Ooh. Ooh. Right off the bat doesn't look good. Doesn't look good. This is going to be tight
because, I mean, one of those, we've got almost a tie between two of them at least.
Okay. I mean, it's getting to be a little more clear. I'm going to do this one more time and
then count to 10 and take a screenshot. 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1. That's it. It's done.
Uh, Nancy Drew and Sly Cooper have been eliminated. It is now down to Yakuza or House Flipper DLC.
Here we go. Final round. House Flipper DLC or Yakuza. Yakuza something. Here it comes. I feel like
this is going to be very, very, very close. It's going to be extraordinarily close because you've
got the House Flipper enthusiast that, oh, House Flipper, of course. I love that game. You love
that game. But then you got the contrarians that are saying, I don't want, no more House Flipper.
Like we haven't seen Yakuza. Like give us something different, right? Like you've played
House Flipper a thousand times. Let's play something else. It looks like it's going to be
very close or not. Nevermind. This is almost ready to call now. Somebody just wrote, I'm not
going to that stream. Come on, dude. We're trying to be democratic about it. I'm trying to be
democratic about this. I ain't going to that one. We'll go to the next one. Sly Cooper is going to
be like after that. I'm giving this 10. Do I even need to give 10 seconds? It's going to take a
Christmas miracle for Yakuza to pull this off. Down by more, almost 200 votes. That's it. That's
it. I will be playing the House Flipper DLC on Wednesday. And then on Thursday, I will be playing
Sly Cooper PlayStation 3 Remastered. And then on Friday, hey, hey guys, want to see how democracy
works on this channel? Playing Yakuza on Friday. There's your schedule for the week. I'm not going
to that one. Well, then there's no pleasing you. I'm not going to that one. I'm not going to that
one. I'm not going to that one. I wanted Slime Rancher. Well, I'll play Slime Rancher eventually.
Come on, Gwyn. It was Nancy Drew that I wanted. Well, I wanted Neopets. Okay. Listen. You want
me to play Neopets so bad, but you know that stream is going to be me. Just like, I'm going to buy a
Neopet and it's going to, I'm going to like feed it like three times. I'm going to throw a ball at
it. And then all of you, all of you Neopets enthusiasts are going to tell me, ah, can we do
something else? This sucks. We're just looking at a website the whole time. This is boring.
Jerma, this stream sucks. And I'm going to be like, steam is going to come out of my ears.
That's exactly what we want. All right. I'll see you for House Flipper on Wednesday. And then
well, I'll play Yakuza as well this coming week. All right. Now I actually have to leave now
because Otto is like staring at me like, dude, what the fuck are you doing? You're just talking.
You're just talking into this bright screen. Animals must think we're insane, by the way.
Think about that. We sit in front of this bright screen that just makes loud noises at us.
What the hell? Why are they, what are they doing? All right. I'll see you guys Wednesday. I gotta go.
Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Have a great rest of your weekend.
Still one with Sunday left, right? Take care, guys. See you soon.