Hold on now, hold on, just a second here. I need to go like this. Okay, so, uh, we are going without
notifications tonight, so no, uh, there will be no sub or bit notifications on the screen,
because obviously this is, uh, German wrestling. This is Germany in 2018. I'm gonna give it a
little bit for people to show up, because I heard that there were some issues with Twitch.
I don't know how widespread they are. I don't know how fucked up they are,
but, uh, want to make sure that the stream actually goes through to people and,
you know, works. So give me just a moment. I know I wanted to start originally like 20
or 30 minutes ago, but, uh, we're going to take a little bit of time. I wanted to make
sure I was done before 5 Pacific, because that's too long, but it's ready. It's done.
It's ready to go. So just give me a moment. We'll talk. Actually, we could bring up a couple
things before this starts. Hey, you know, I'm going to milk the absolute hell out of this.
You know what I mean? Hold on a second. Let's talk about a few things, because the stream
is probably only going to be two or three hours long, because, you know, it is what it
is. But, uh, give me one second. I will be right back. Tata for a second. Shouldn't I be a
little more excited for this? Oh, the rumble is here. I'm like, okay, guys, let's talk about
a few things first of all. Okay. So let's, let's go over just a few stream related things.
No, but this is very, very, very important. Next weekend is the green screen movie night.
Now, if you have not submitted your, uh, your piece of art, then I advise you to do so before
the 29th. If you are curious of the rules, they're all posted in that discord channel.
There's a pinned message. Go read on the green screen submission channel. There's a pinned
bunch of rules. Read them. You got to have your video on YouTube. It's got to be uploaded
to YouTube. No Reddit videos, no discord videos. Got to, it's going to go into a
giant YouTube playlist. So please go read those rules. I want to make sure I say that again,
cause we're doing that next weekend. If you're like, what the fuck am I supposed to do? Just
go take a look. Pin message. All right. So, uh, I was, I was at Starbucks today and man,
what, what's the deal with their large? You know what I mean? It's like not even bigger
than the medium. It's like two ounces bigger. Are you guys ready? Are you guys ready to do
this? The reason why I'm stalling. It's only been four minutes. What? Not even stalling.
But here's the reason why. The last couple of times I've done this,
a bunch of people have missed the first two matches or so because, oh shit,
I got a notification. The stream just started. I spent like 44 hours on this. So like,
I'm going to milk it. I'm going to sit here and talk about my Starbucks trip.
Ah, play a 10 minute drum roll. Uh, by the way, um, there are, there are 36 characters
and I think only two or three of them are returning characters.
I went, I went fucking crazy and just made 35, 34 people. So there's a, it's not,
let's look at it this way. It's not just like, cause let's say, you know, usually I spend a
lot of time on these, but you know, I got the complaints about Falco, about Wolf,
about Star Fox. I got the complaints about it. Nobody wants to see seven serpents in a rumble.
So, uh, there, there are no clones. Well, actually hold on a minute. That might,
that might not be entirely true. And everybody's here except for everyone beside,
like from like a year ago. None of them are there from like a year and a half ago.
It's all people from the last year. So everyone from this last year is here,
except for the, everybody else. There you go. All right. What do you say we get it done?
Let's start. Jamania 2018. What told you I was going to look, I told you I was going to get
done before December. Everyone was yelling at me. Oh, there's no way he is going to have
enough time. Oh yeah. 36 fucking characters. Can you hear it? You can hear it. I don't,
I don't want to spoil it. Hopefully this is set up correctly. If not,
I'm going to fucking shit my pants. But anyways, welcome everybody to Jamania 2018.
Hey, where are we? Where are we? Hey, where do you think we are?
Where do you think we are right now? I'll tell you where we are. We're in beautiful
Las Vegas, Nevada. Just waiting for it to pop up on the screen to prove that I've been
Las Vegas. San Diego. That's not real. There we are, ladies and gentlemen in San Diego.
I turned the music off. I don't want this. I'm going to get copyright strike.
All right, here we go. It's time for it to begin. First match of the evening coming up
right now. It's an extreme rules match. One on one. I fucking hate this music.
Don't delete me. How do I like, hold on. I got to like be really, really loud
because this is going to mute the VOD. Don't delete this. But anyways guys,
welcome to the first match of the evening. This is one that I'm going to put this to
rest forever. I cannot wait until this, this argument that I've made for the last
almost full fucking year is, is just stupid at this point. And you'll see what I'm talking
about. Oh, you didn't do it. You didn't do it. You didn't kill this guy. You didn't
beat this guy first try. That's fine. We'll find out tonight what really is going on
because we got the first match of the evening out of five total here is
Jerva985 in a one on one match. Looking old as shit. Losing his hair.
That's what I look like right now. Somebody just went out. Jerva985 is
getting a little higher in age, as I just said. 30, 33. I feel 53. And it's funny
because every time we do one of these rumbles, I always make me how I currently feel.
That's how I feel right now. Like I, the last time I was like fat,
you did boo with me and that's fine. You boo me on my own channel. I don't give shit.
But who could I be facing to finally put this bullshit to rest forever?
Ladies and gentlemen, my opponent for the first match of the evening
is one of the easiest bosses in Dark Souls. That's right. We're talking about a person
that I absolutely did not lose to. That's Pinwheel! Extreme rules. One on one.
Will I beat Pinwheel again without dying? Because that's what I did. Will I do it?
And then we can stop this. Whatever happens here on out. If I lose, I'll accept it.
If I win, you all gotta stop that shit. This ain't even, this ain't a meme stream,
but I'm telling you. We're making the canon tonight. Go get him. Go get him.
What is he doing? He's, he's being a, I don't know. He's being a slow Dark Souls boss.
An easy boss. But I will absolutely beat within five minutes. Because I'm the one in control,
as you'll see very plainly. But I've gotten older. No entrance music. And there's a very
good reason for that. Apparently, you can get, you can get in trouble with copyrighted
music these days. So I've heard. No entrance music. Really is. Let's go. Hurry up. Get the
fuck in there, Pinwheel. He has taken a long time. What? Jerma's outside the ring, getting ready.
Starting his new exercise routine. Well, Pinwheel really milks this intro for good measure.
What a good way to make sure everybody gets here. And there it's all angry. Oh dear,
you suck. You lost to Pinwheel. No, I didn't. And I'm about to prove it right now.
Welcome to Germania 2018. Ring the bell. One-on-one extreme rules. Jerma versus Pinwheel.
Couple of right-handed punches there to start. Jerma is old, but can still hang with a young
kid. Right into the turnbuckle, his face goes. Twice. Three. Four. Five. Six. Seven. Eight. Nine.
Ten. Eleven. Eleven times. Ooh, Jerma with a little stomp there, but he missed. Got him in
a headlock. No, he's gonna go. Ooh, a little elbow to the face. Pinwheel now on the
reversal. Into the corner, Jerma goes. Pinwheel. Uh-oh. He's turning him upside down. He's
tying him. He's tying Jerma to the turnbuckle and now stepping on his face.
That was an interesting tree of woe there by Pinwheel. Is that made out of concrete?
That's not gonna win. No, no, no. That's one. There's no way I'm gonna lose that one.
I'm not gonna get pinned after getting my hit. Ooh, what a beautiful break dance move
into a Jerma Suplex by Jerma. Absolutely fantastic. You can hear the crowd. Half of
them really getting behind me. Half of them yelling about how short I am. And another
200 people screaming about how I lost. You can really hear. Oh, what a miss by Pinwheel
there. Can Jerma capitalize on it? No, he's gonna get. Oh, what a reverse neckbreaker
there by Pinwheel on Jerma 985. He dropped the 985 recently in recent years. I'm not
sure why that is. Maybe it's because no. Ooh, beautiful reversal. Maybe it's because
numbers back in the day of YouTube where everybody had a numbered channel. But you
didn't even really. I don't know why. And people had their birthdays. Why would you
ever put your birthday online for a bunch of people to see? And now it looks like Jerma
is gonna try the same technique on Pinwheel. The crowd didn't really like that, but it
wasn't gonna be enough. Let's see. One. No, only one. Only one. Now remember,
this is an extreme rules matchup. So that means every... I'm pretty sure.
Whoa, what a hurricane run. A springboard. We saw him do these moves in the green screen.
Now he's setting up for a special move, I think. Yep, it's called the whoops-a-daisy.
That's old Jerma's special technique, the whoops-a-daisy. He grabs you by the wrist
and just falls backwards as you lie down on your back, too. Jerma into the corner.
Are we gonna see? Uh-oh. Are we gonna see it? Are we gonna see the diaper? No,
that wasn't the diaper. I thought it was gonna be the diaper. That was the double
fisted. Uh-oh, he's going to the top rope. Got up there real quickly. What are we gonna
see from Jerma? Oh, the stomp. The step on your chest. And that's gotta be it.
That has to be it. One. Two. Oh, just barely. He didn't make it. Pinwheel just
barely got out of that one. I was like, somebody better check his shoes.
Somebody check Jerma's shoes. I think there's fucking weights in there.
He might be cheating. He doesn't want to be lambasted and accused and made
fun of for the rest of his life. People are cheering. Pinwheel now.
He's got him in the submission lock. Is Jerma gonna... No! He... Oh, I thought he tapped
out for a second. I was about to scream. Oh, out to the outside we go and Jerma's
feeling the adrenaline. You can just smell his armpits from here. They smell like
Dove Men plus Care and he's going to the top rope. He's pointing down. This is a daredevil
move here from Jerma. Will he? What's he gonna do? Holy shit! I don't know what. That
was so unnecessary. That hurt Jerma probably more than it hurt Pinwheel.
All I did was hurt my legs. Why wouldn't you kick him? Why wouldn't you jump on him?
And now a DDT into the concrete and he stepped on his balls too for good measure. Are we
going to get a pin on the outside? Where are they taking this? Just two extremely
tall... Uh-oh. Pinwheel is going underneath the... And he's got a pull cue. No, he
doesn't want it. I don't want that. He didn't. Oh! Big mistake. A capitalization
from Jerma. The slap. Is he gonna go into the... No, it's a reversal. Back down. I'm
not sure why he picked up that pull cue there. He's not going to use it. I think
he... I don't think he wants to cheat. I think he wants to beat Jerma fair and
square. I'm like, uh-oh. I think Jerma might be dead. Jerma's face just
erupted. The red marker means you're in trouble. Is Jerma going to tap out
here? No, no, no, no. He's not going to tap out. He's not going to tap
out. Jerma's got more perseverance than this. Good reversal there by Jerma.
As the referee is standing there awkwardly just trying to figure out
what to do about this whole thing. And they're going up the alley. He
Jerma gets thrown into the entrance way. I think he might have a headache
trying to get back in. Both going at the same time. The pull cue is still on
the ground. Nice DDT. Perfectly executed. And Jerma is bleeding from the
head. Did Jerma get... He didn't... What happened? Oh, right into the
concrete. That's right. Oh! Two closed lines. Three closed lines. Will
it be enough? Is he going to go for a pin potentially here? Now he's
going to pick him up and punch him in the face. Does Jerma know any
other moves? A reverse su... Oh, that was a reverse suplex. Could that
be it? Is that going to be it? I think. One, two, three. That's it.
Jerma beats Pinwheel first try. He got him with the reverse suplex.
And everybody's booing and they can boo all they want. It's proven.
That's it. No more of this bullshit. I beat Pinwheel on stream first
try. Look at all these awesome moves that I did. I was surprised
that the double stump diaper trash did not seal the deal there for.
We did have a nice move by Pinwheel here. It was a DDT. People in the
audience right now, in the arena, are screaming right now.
Oh, hold on. Jerma's got something to say. Yeah, see? First try. He's
holding up the one finger. First try. I'm as angry as he is. He's
taunting Twitch chat right now, saying, yeah, like, look what I did.
By the way, that's an actual picture of my face, just in case
anyone was wondering. Moving on to the next match.
We've got... This is going to be a fan favorite one here.
After Jerma very, very clearly beats Pinwheel first try.
Pre-recorded and rigged. No, we're watching it live.
Hey, scream over the... Hold on. There we go. I can just do that.
I wouldn't have to worry about the VOD getting deleted. But the next one
coming up is going to be quite an interesting match.
It is a six-man ladder match. Six people in the ring
have to climb up to the top and grab the briefcase. Six people.
I wonder who's going to win this one. Oh, it's still loading. This has got
a lot of people are in this one. Well, might as well bring it up here.
We've had a short little intermission. Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the
six-man, six-man ladder match. The six participants
are a lot of people that you guys know.
There's the money in the bank. It's two twenty dollar bills.
I said there's like a hundred grand in there, but I lied. And there's
Chuck Schnauzwell. Contestant number one in the
money in the bank six-man. Grab the briefcase challenge.
Chuck Schnauzwell, one of the murderers of the Sims murder house.
And you probably could guess who the other five contestants are.
Maybe you can't. Everybody loves Chuck. The Schnauz,
as they call him in the locker room, because he's got really great teeth.
That's what they say. Oh, Twitch chat really seems to like that.
I wonder... Oh, hold on a minute. Who's the next contestant in the six-man
ladder match? Six-man? Why don't you add six-woman?
That's D56TFO98, one of the other members of the Sims murder house.
D56, very adamant on coming in here and winning.
Landed on this planet ten years ago. Nice slide.
You can't practice that five times. D56 trying to show off to the crowd,
get some people to back her endeavor here.
You gotta let them have at least a few minutes in the ring, you know what I mean?
You can't skip their beloved entrance. Contestant number three
coming in here. No, no, she's got more to say. No,
I can't really hear what she's saying, because she's not mic'd up.
But anyways, here comes the third contestant in the...
and getting booed here. There are loud boos coming in for Frufru.
If you could... If you could guess...
Yeah, this is... This is... They're all here.
Frufru, one of the worst people in the whole house.
Nobody liked him. I don't like him. And people ironically like him, but he sucks.
I hope he doesn't win. I'm glad he's getting booed.
Nice anime stance. He's a big fan of anime. That's what he says, but that's
what they say in the locker room. You know, because of his hat.
I like him. I like him. Well, that's fine.
He's ready. Contestant number four. Let's see who it is.
That's Gavrett. Gavrett from the murder house.
Just kind of a regular guy with a weirdly shaped head.
There wasn't really anything crazy about him. He's practicing his
Sims dance, because they are Sims, right? That is very
important for you to realize. They've been computer-generated scanned
into the into the German wrestling universe.
You think you'd have any other moves besides put your fists out back and
forth. Get him the fuck out of here.
Okay. Oh, by the way, that t-shirt took like
an hour and 40 minutes to make. So let's just be real about that.
That's not in the game. Coming up next, number five.
After Gavrett. I really hope that people are prepared for this one.
That's Adam Sandler. He's coming out doing his patented
comedy.
He's known for that. One of the most talented comedians of our
of our generation. Probably 10 generations.
Such comedic routines as Baby Noise does the same weird voice
and thinks they're way funnier than they are.
And no, I'm not describing me. I mean, I am. But
I mean, look, he's a fucking funny guy, okay?
He's really talented. He's really funny. And this commentator's coming to a very
strong realization in the right in the middle of it.
Don't matter. Somebody said that before, didn't they? It doesn't matter. Here
comes Wally Wheat. Wally Wheat's the real contestant and he's gonna wipe
the floor with all these motherfuckers in the ring.
Here are your six. The Sims Rumble. The Sims Murderhouse ladder match.
These people in this ring right now, all of them
are insane. They will kill. They will kill.
They have no problem with it. Half of them are not even from this planet.
Dangerous people. Incredibly dangerous people. What do you say you ring that
bell? Six man ladder match, ladies and
gentlemen. The Sims Murderhouse. Chuck wasting no time. He's going outside to
go to the ladder. Adam Sandler now with a reversal on
D56. Chuck does not want this to last long.
He's got the ladder all ready. It hadn't even been 10 seconds. While
Frufru is gonna see if he can make that
a different story. We'll head to the apron outside the ring for Chuck.
Adam Sandler now with the offensive. There are no teams here. Keep that in
mind. Nobody is on any team. Whoever gets to
the top of that ladder first wins. Now Adam Sandler doing his
patented funny noise. Let me see if I can top him. Let me
see if I can top him. Hey it's me. It's me. It's me. It's me.
We're not so different, you and I, Adam.
Adam Sandler goes over the top ropes and now they're outside. While D56
is got Adam Sandler smashing his head into
the steps. Well Garrett. What's something we didn't know about
Garrett? He seems to be a pretty talented submission artist.
While Frufru is on the outside trying to get his composure.
No one has touched the ladder or anything else for that matter.
Well speaking of the devil here, Wally Wheat's got the ladder
going over to Garrett. No, Garrett's gonna rip it out of his hands.
No, I don't know what the deal is with that. Why do they put it down? You have
a weapon. You're a bloodthirsty murderer. Use it.
What a wonderful bulldog by DF 5694. Whatever your name is.
You're not supposed to be able to understand it. It's not even English.
It's like a weird alien. It's a weird alien dialect. Garrett
with oh what a reversal by D56 and a scoop slam coming up. No,
is D56 gonna dump him over the rails? No. She holds back. She does hold back.
As Wally Wheat now in the corner. Chuck Schnoswell. It seems that they've all
been training vigorously. Oh what a pose by Frufru.
That's the, you gotta, you have to get him out of the ring. You know what I'm
saying? There's six people. No one's ever
gonna climb to the top of this thing. You gotta throw above the top.
You gotta go get a weapon. Go grab like a grenade or something.
As now we've got three in the ring. This could end very quickly. Garrett thought
about it for a second. Now I'm gonna get the ladder.
Garrett's got the ladder. No. I don't want that. I think I'd rather
pick this guy up like a backpack. Oh it was, that's the backpack.
That's Garrett's special move. I can't believe we just saw that. That's the
backpack. Adam Sandlin now coming in with a
couple of punches. What a reversal by Garrett.
Garrett is on fire here. If I'm gonna make a bet here I'm gonna say
Garrett's gonna be the one to take the money in that briefcase and win the
murder house brawl as we're gonna call it. What a
fireman's carry knee smash to the spinal column. That's the name of her move.
That's her special move. That's her special move. As D56 is
gonna grab. No and finally we get to see the ladder used.
D56 is going pretty much all in on Adam Sandlin.
Oh it gets taken and nobody's really trying to do anything with the
ladder besides small pushes to somebody's face. We
could see blood here. D56 now trying to work that bad
knee on Chuck Schnoswell. Because his nose is so large other
parts of his body are weaker. He's got bad knees, bad
elbows, but he could have real strong fucking nose.
Garrett now has got the ladder. It didn't even phase her at first.
That was a little odd. Dropping the ladder again. Garrett's
going for Chuck Schnoswell into the corner.
He's facing the ground. Oh what an elbow to stop that. No another
reversal. They all trained in the same dojo by the way.
For what I'm being told on my desk here. When they first got there.
She throws it over the top ropes. Essentially handing it
to somebody on the outside. Adam Sandler contemplating his next movie script.
Will it involve a giant pac-man? I'm not sure but it's going to involve a
broken neck. Nice reverse back neck breaker by
Adam Sandlin. And a Russian leg sweep here too.
We've got a problem here though. Chuck Schnoswell on the top with
D56. It's going to be a superplex. Off the top turnbuckle.
Oh that's a broken alien spine. She is out. She's out cold. Maybe not.
But what I was gonna say is they'd all trained in the same dojo from what I
what I got on my paper here. And weirdly enough they were thrown out
of every dojo besides they ended up going to some back alley dojo.
They're not even that's not even uh sanctioned it's not even uh you know
it's not there's no it's not like unionized there's no
it's it's just like it was an alleyway that they were allowed in because
they kept bringing uh glass tubes they're bringing knives into the
other dojos to try to fight each other and they were just like throwing
the fuck out. People were saying you can't bring those in here.
So they ended up getting trained by an unnamed uh sensei and uh they're the
sensei question mark and I'm not it's it's it's it's actually the word
question space mark. That's the person's name.
So and wait Garrett's going up there just barely. Everyone just kind of
stopped doing something for a minute here. No no no no no. Garrett's gonna
get that. Is he gonna get that money? Did
Garrett just sneakily no he stopped it. Garrett almost just sneakily got
up there and picked up that entire that was insane.
I can't believe they just almost let that happen and now Chuck has got the
ladder. We are seeing fatigue settle in right
now as Chuck is going to try to get the
ring cleared. There goes D56. Chuck Schnoswell
is going up there. Will it be enough? Molly Wheat is
out cold. Chuck Schnoswell's got the briefcase. Is he gonna
oh they're gonna help they're gonna work together. Oh just hit Adam Sandler
in the face. I can't believe they actually work
together. Oh not for long not anymore.
Oh and the alliances stop right there. Molly Wheat is getting
killed by the ladder. Garrett now is gonna make another attempt here.
Is he gonna be able to get up there? This could be it.
Garrett's gonna chase what a punch to Adam Sandler's face.
Come on D56 you gotta get up there. Garrett's gonna get it.
Garrett's gonna get it. No is this gonna be it?
Garrett is on the edge. They're both on the edge. Garrett just fell off.
Molly Wheat now can D56 can she make the attempt? Uh oh he
no she why did she step down? Why did she step down off the ladder?
Anyway oh and now we've got a forward object in the middle of the ring here.
Frufru is now going absolute ham on the back of D56 with that big piece
of steel. Adam Sandler just keeps finding his way outside
and getting hurt outside. Oh what a clobber into the forehead
that at least 30 pounds of steel not even gonna set it up he's just
doing no it's gonna get reversed again. Reversed again doesn't want the
ladder does want the ladder who knows what the fuck they're
doing. Just a little tap to make sure that
she wouldn't get it again. Oh what the fuck was that?
Molly Wheat now sees an opportunity after Frufru just broke.
Garrett's back with his knees. Is this ever gonna end?
Is there ever gonna be an opportunity for one of these psychos to put this
shit up and go grab that money? Adam Sandler now in the ring for the
first time in probably five minutes. Nice snap neck breaker there setting
him up for it. Look at the exhaustion everybody's so
tired I don't think no one's gonna be able to climb to the top of
this thing. Garrett's been really consistently the only one that's
carried and he currently still has the ladder.
Adam Sandler's got Chuck Schnosswell. What a Chuck's play.
He tried to do it again he tried to do it to something else.
He tried to do two in a row but he couldn't get it he missed with the
other one. That's Garrett now these two have done
this over and over and over again back and forth trading the ladder.
What a somersault heel kick by Garrett.
Garrett now what a leg drop there the ladder is finally set up and Garrett
has a beautiful sneaky opportunity. You're
gonna get the briefcase he's got two of his hands on it.
Can he unclip it? I think he might be able to get it. D56 now
is barely no barely just stopping it. Is D56 gonna be taking a capital
decision here? This is it. This is gonna be it.
D56 has almost got it. Frufru it sees an opportunity to push it over.
No and she's still holding on. That's gotta be it. That's gotta be it.
That's it. Frufru just has to climb up and grab it. He is completely
he's got a free no traffic he's no lane.
Uh-oh Chuck is seeing they're both seeing it now.
But was it too late they were too busy fighting each other. What is Wally
Wheat doing? Why would you do that? Why would you just what? She can't push it.
No he wins. She couldn't push it. She didn't she ran out of strength.
Frufru is your winner of the sims murder house
ladder match. The fucking worst character just won.
Why would she click that of all the things?
That guys don't worry this this thing fucking snakes in there. He's
gonna open that and his life is gonna end.
So don't worry. Wally fucked it up. No I just
ran out of gas. D56 got up trying to push the ladder over and just
didn't have enough strength. The Sandler chokeslam.
Oh that's fucking great. Can I edit people's chances to win a match?
I think I can but I know I don't they gotta earn it man.
I don't give I don't hand anybody victories here. You you gotta earn it.
I'm not gonna predetermine who wins. It's uh that whoever wins
they get in there and they fucking fight. If you thought okay if you guys
thought I could rig these matches why the fuck would I have this guy
win? Why the fuck would I do that? Hey I got an idea. Let me have like
the shittiest character win. We got a table match coming up here.
This is a 2v2 table match.
Tag match. Oh whoops I forgot I have to mute the audio.
Sorry about that. We are going back to a different era here
on the channel. By era I mean different
console generation. Different console generation than you're used to.
Oh fuck I asked back there. Yeah because some could say that we are
going back a few generations. Some could say.
Let's go and get it started. 2v2 table match.
Let's see who it is. Hailing all the way from Monster Rancher.
That's right ladies and gentlemen that's Beanbag Sonic.
Are we gonna get to see it? Are we gonna get to see it? There it is.
Beanbag Sonic making his first appearance ever in the rubble.
Top seed. Yep and Beanbag Sonic's partner.
Beanbag Sonic's partner. Are we gonna get to see another dab?
Oh that was a nice move. Is it the mosquito? It's not the mosquito.
It's somebody else. Somebody equally as important in the Monster Rancher
streams and the PlayStation 1 streams in general. Beanbag Sonic's
partner for the table match is Sweet Rhind.
Rewind to the Rhind. Ladies and gentlemen there is Sweet Rhind. Beanbag
Sonic is Sweet Rhind. Uh he is fucking huge.
Well they're very large. They're monsters. He's a giant wall. What do
you expect? And their opponents. From point blank.
That's Dr. Dawn. Can you guess who his
teammate will be? Who? That's Dr. Dawn from point blank.
You guys don't know who this is? Well then you're not gonna know his partner
Dr. Dan. Wait did nobody watch those streams?
I streamed that like four times. No wait no yeah yeah you did.
Yeah you guys were there for those streams. Did what did those streams
have low viewers? Well some of you guys know who
Dr. Dawn and Dr. Dan is. It's not a clone. That's not a clone.
That's a different person. That's not a copy and paste. Go look
him up. Dr. Dawn and Dr. Dan. I hope they fucking win. I hope they
fucking win. I hope they destroy these two.
Beanbag Sonic and Sweet Rhind versus Dr. Dawn and Dr. Dan. PlayStation 1
battle. And it is a table match.
Dr. Dawn is is getting a table immediately. And Sweet Rhind
has got a table. The match has just begun. Beanbag Sonic.
Two tables are inside of the ring right now. Sweet Rhind is
huge. Sweet Rhind is too big. How do I edit this
in the middle of the stream and make him like 30% smaller? Dr. Dawn with a
with a nice spinning heel kick. Beanbag Sonic using his upper body
strength on Dr. Dan. I may have mixed the two of them up.
No clones by the way. Oh what a delicious right-handed punch
into the face of the world. Does Sweet Rhind have a face?
I can't even tell. I don't know. Does Sweet Rhind have a head?
DDT. They're a big fan of that. Wait now we got. Hold on. There's a problem here
though. Dr. Dawn and Dr. Dan are both in the
ring. Beanbag Sonic is outside in pain.
All it takes is one of those tables to get set up and this could be over.
Yeah. Dr. Dawn and Dr. Dan. They're not clones. Dr. Dan has
three inches of reach. A larger head. Oh right under the table
which is probably a better surface to land on.
Are we gonna see the Sweet Rhind's special move? I'm not sure. I did make
sure to put it in. I wonder if we'll see it. All right. I
can't tell who did the move there. What a
jumping scissor kick to Beanbag Sonic's stomach. Everybody talked all the shit
about Dr. Dawn and Dr. Dan but they are
some of the top competitors we've seen in probably three years.
They weren't allowed to bring their guns. He accidentally just hurt his
partner there. I don't know how. They're I would
say at this point it's a 70-30 with Dr. Dawn and Dr. Dan. Dr.
Dawn you just fucked up. What? What? You blew everything. You
absolutely blew it. Sweet Rhind that's like a four thousand pound
hunk of concrete on the top rope right now. Waiting for Dr. Dawn to get up.
While Dr. Dan has Beanbag Sonic up in a fireman's carry.
Beautifully executed. Well still waiting. Didn't even affect him.
He just got him with the tip of his toes. He just scratched under his
mustache with that kick. He waited so long to time that too
but they're not known for their agility.
A wall type monster rancher. Monsters are very
they're not they're known for strength not for finesse. Just going
onto the back of Sweet Rhind. Dr. Dan now
uh sorry there is a blockage in the way. I don't know what happened.
You have a giant person standing in front of the camera.
Uh-oh it has the momentum shifted here with Beanbag Sonic and Dr. Dawn
and Dr. Dan. No just when you thought it could have
changed. The reversals here seems to be the
reversal king is Dr. Dawn. I've probably said their names
backwards five times. They just dropped him on his head.
He just picked him up and just dropped him on his head. Beanbag Sonic
just absolutely oh he was going for a dab there. Never taunt in the middle of
a match. He was going for a dab and he got
caught by Dr. Dan. Dr. Dawn and Dr. Dan now double teaming Sonic.
Caught him right in the back. Oh I'm not sure Dr. Dan's getting up
from that one. Throwing the table outside for some
strange reason. Sweet Ry now I have really no idea what they're
doing. It's the first person to go through a table that
their team loses. He's wrapping up both of his arms now.
Throwing him behind a German suplex with his arms tied behind his back.
The AI is his AI is really dumb. He's desperately trying to figure out
how to pick up the table. He got confused there. They must
what the hell was that? No don't don't don't set it up and then get
thrown through it Beanbag. This could be it. He doesn't move
through this table. This is it. This game over.
Beanbag Sonic. This is it. That's it. Powerbomb through the table.
Beanbag Sonic and Sweet Ry are your winners. Unbelievable super kick. That was
intense. That's what set it all up. And here's the finisher here. He just
throws him through the table into the corner. I think he may have
gotten injured there himself. It's all right. We're gonna give you
meat tonight. Well I'm gonna give I'll give a potato to Sweet Ry.
But he's getting meat and he's getting candy. There they are.
Two best friends from one of the best PlayStation 1 games ever.
Dr. Don and Dr. Dan thank you for participating.
But it's time for you to go home because you two are not in the rumble.
Go home. That was a fucking bismuth. You just got you just got
shit canned on the air. But anyways Beanbag Sonic and Sweet Ry are the
winners. Getting ever so closer to the main event here.
How many matches did I miss? This is the third one.
Or is it another way? This is yeah. So you got you got two more.
You get the next match and then you get the rumble. The rumble is going to be
like probably 30 or 40 minutes. Three fixed matches? I didn't fix anything.
I wanted Dr. Don and Dr. Dan to win. All right let's go. The next one.
What was the first one? The first one was the me versus pinwheel.
And I made it I made it look really easy. Second match was a
six-man ladder between the Sims murder house. Dr. Don and Dr. Dan
versus Sweet Ry and Beanbag Sonic. And then you got this one a
backstage brawl. Oh no okay I know I know what this is.
They make a lot of money. So I kind of let them
use the space here at the German arena. So
it's okay though. I don't think this will take very long.
So yeah this won't take very long. They're filming a YouTube video.
Oh that's Gary the fuck up and Bill crazy. I let them. Were they
supposed to come out? Yeah they're making like a hardcore
like we're fucked up YouTube video. Okay yeah oh so that's Gary the fuck up.
That's the cameraman. I'm not sure what they're doing back here though. I just
I let them use the space. They make like 30 million dollars a
year guys. I'm one of the most subscribed YouTube channels.
Now it's something I heard. I've been wondering about the feet there.
Apparently for a top YouTube dares thing that he did a long time ago.
He had his feet severed and had bird feet put on
surgically. I guess that he he's kind of fucked up. He's kind of a
fucked up guy. I dropped the camera. They're filming.
Oh that might look nice on the on the YouTube channel.
Oh that was insane. Wow he just jumped into the wall.
Smashing his face on the ground. These guys are fucked.
What else are they going to do for the video? Oh right into that. His
head just hit the top of that amp there.
What are they going to do again? Okay I took like a 60 or 70 thousand dollar
commission for this. Under the wall pool. No this is just
what they do. They jump into pools with fucking
like blood pools. They they shoot baseballs at each other out of a
pitching machine. I think number three or four most
subscribed like I said. I'm not sure like how this is gonna
Oh they fucked that one up. They'll take care of that in editing.
They'll edit that one out. Oh he's setting up the shot. He's setting up a
really good camera angle here. Oh right in the balls. Dude they just
got a ball shot. I can't wait to see that in a compilation.
He can't get dirt on him. Oh no that might be the last video he
has ever made. He can't just like stop at somebody's
head. He survived way worse. That's it.
You've been like you've jumped off a building before man.
You've been electrocuted. You can't like your head stepped on you die.
Oh I almost want to do it again because that's so
there's so many ways for them to do fuck them shit back here.
They can I may I checked a bunch of boxes for them to like fucking like
kill each other back here and you step on his head and that's it he's
dead. Oh no I can't. I can't. I can't do it.
I can't do a rematch. That ends this whole thing.
But I kind of can't do a rematch. You know what I mean?
We can do a rematch after. We'll do like an encore presentation.
He's still. All right that concludes that. Hopefully that
upload is good and it gets 50 million views and
they sell all their merch. This is the main event here.
Oh I muted it. I like almost broke something. Hold on I freaked out.
So uh something that you need to know is just because you were in the
pre-matches does not mean you are in the rumble.
I need to make I had to make room for a lot of fucking people. So
there are way there are a lot more characters that you have not seen.
I can't get over that. I was thinking they were gonna throw him through a
TV. I can't. I can't. I gotta like compose
myself here. All right I'm ready.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the main event. This is the Jerma Rumble
2018. I hope you enjoy it. Let's get it started. You know the
rules. Every minute or so another contestant
is going to come out to the ring. Uh there is no commentary so this
you cannot hear what this person is saying.
The first 10 usually have an incredibly incredibly high disadvantage
but it is very possible. Welcome to the Jerma Rumble 2018
stream edition. They're all stream editions at this point.
Over the top ropes you're out. That's the only way. That is the only way.
30 contestants. 30. That's right. 30. Mic muted. Well her mic is muted.
That's fine. Mine's not. Mine's open. I wonder who the first
contestant is. It's all random. It's completely randomized so I have no
idea. I'm watching this at the same time
as you guys. The first contestant coming out.
Why is there music? Why is there music for Jax?
There shouldn't be any music but there's Jax, the first contestant.
Making his first ever appearance. One of the most highly skilled video game
players to ever live. He had an embroidery down I see.
That's a pretty nice embroidery. I will say it looks pretty nice.
Can we see some Jax's in the chat? I would like to see it maybe.
We already see them. He's at a severe disadvantage though.
Because Jax is number one which is nearly impossible.
Maybe he'll go all the way. We've seen stranger things for sure.
Tag me in. No that's not going to happen. Contestant number two.
The first two. Who is number two? I'm excited. I'm ready.
That's Sweet Rind. Sweet Rind is contestant number two.
Just coming off of a victory with Beanbag Sonic.
Sweet Rind and Jax are the first two. I wonder how long it's going to take.
David and Goliath. Well this is Jax we're talking about.
This ain't just some shitty regular Jerma. You know.
This is my alternate personality. Jax. 2018 Germania.
Jerma rumble has started. Oh game almost crashed at the very beginning.
That would have been real bad. But we got Jax and Sweet Rind in at
the very beginning here trying to get his
up the leg there. Nice throwing him backwards.
And we already have another contestant coming in here.
Already. It hasn't even been 20 seconds. Contestant number three coming in as
Jax does a patented Jerma move. Garrett's coming in next from the
Sims murder house as contestant number three. There he is.
Making his way. Oh nice fireman's carry. Tossing him over the shoulder
there. Blocks that punch. Jax is going to be in it. I would
triple or quadruple or septuple team Jax.
He has the highest stats in the whole game. He's literally unbeatable.
He is 100% unbeatable. I'd like to see what they do here.
As Garrett is just taunting the crowd. Here comes contestant number four.
It's Pinwheel. Pinwheel with a small eye.
He just picked him up and made him do a leg drop onto Sweet Rind's head.
That was a tag team effort there. That was not somebody doing a move.
That was an actual double team on Sweet Rind. So you
got Jax, Pinwheel, Garrett and Sweet Rind
in the ring right now and Sweet Rind is going to try to eliminate the
competition here. Can Sweet Rind get rid of Jax?
Is Jax going to go out first ever? No that can't be. It's impossible.
It's impossible. It's impossible. I told you. Here comes contestant number
five. Lou. Oh of course I know who Lou is.
That's Lou Elberton from the Elberton family.
Jeremy's Uncle Lou. Jax and Uncle Lou both incredibly powerful.
He was so excited to come here. He was so excited he was going to make
his first appearance and he's going to eliminate Pinwheel
for Jeremy because he knows he hates his fucking character and he hates all the
chat memes. No he's not strong enough and without
even thinking Sweet Rind has been eliminated
and now we've got Jax giving a powerbomb and here comes Glueman.
Glueman making his appearance. Jax seems to for some reason have powerbombed
Uncle Lou and he's... Glueman is going to go right for Jax.
He is certain that if he wants to win this rumble for the first time ever
he's been a part of every single rumble. He has to take out the
strongest competitor but it's going to be very difficult for Glueman.
We've got a very very full ring here. Sweet Rind first to be eliminated.
Jax with a jumping drop kick on Glueman. This is going to be a tough one
and Dr. Schmeichsen. The lie detector doctor
making his first ever appearance as well. A lot of first timers here. Dr.
Schmeichsen trying to go for a diving face
butt but he did not make it. Garrett now
is going to get over the top rubs. Is it possible they're going to double team?
Garrett here. Lou in pinwheel. There he goes.
Garrett has been eliminated by Uncle Lou in pinwheel. Dr. Schmeichsen,
Lou, Jax, Glueman in pinwheel. Here comes another contestant. I'm hearing
a lot of boos. Oh they put... what is that Bill? Oh
did he get up? Did he actually get up? It's Bill crazy!
He's actually not dead. Dr. Schmeichsen
is about to eliminate Jax. No it's impossible.
It's it's literally not even possible. Good luck.
He's the most under speeded video game champion to ever live. Bill crazy now
has Uncle Lou in a powerbomb! Is he gone? Jax did not like that.
His Uncle Lou has been eliminated. Oh my god. Is he gonna do it?
Manchester from... he's naked. He's naked. Manchester from oblivion
is going to get instantly eliminated. Bill crazy is gone.
Lou is gone. Jax doing some fancy footwork. Taunting the crowd. He knows
he is an indisputable champion. He'll never be beaten.
Nice right hand on a Majestank or the Flu for those of you that are keeping
track. Pinwheel now two weird characters from very different games.
Is it possible? Will pinwheel be eliminated by? No not by Majestank.
The Flu. Dr. Schmeichsen now. He's got a
cure for the Flu. It's called two right hands and an elbow to the back
of the skull. He's got a cure for the Flu.
Ladies and gentlemen coming in here next is the Car Valet from Sleeping Dogs.
Somebody order a car? I think so. There he is.
The Car Valet. Oh and immediately gets stopped by Glue Man.
We got the Dr. Schmeichsen now who seemed to have. Oh no.
Wow is is is Car is the Car Valet gonna actually eliminate Glue Man? This
would be so sad. This would be so sad for Glue Man.
He's tried so many times. He's tried... Jax is about to be
eliminated by Pinwheel. Don't you fucking dare.
No. Yes it's impossible. Don't do it. Do not. Pinwheel do not eliminate Jax.
Please god. Thank god. Here comes the green screen.
Put whatever character you want here. This is the green screen from last
weekend. If you want to put uh like Super
Mario here or you want to put you know like the fat guy or like
Peter Griffin or something. He's there for you. He's marked. He's huge.
Well the green screen is huge. Dr. Schmeichsen now going
with a couple of kicks into Jax's face.
There are so many people in this ring. It's actually getting ridiculous.
What? Is that actually Sans from Undertale?
That's Sans from Undertale. There he is. There are too many people in the
ring. Sans making his first appearance in
Gerber Rumble. One, two, three, four, five, six.
There are eight people in the ring. Is Glue Man gonna get his
elimination here on Dr. Schmeichsen? This is a this is
assault on another person. Oh but he reverses it. Green
screen now. We got the car valets in a bad spot.
Dr. Schmeichsen now trying to. Oh no. Green screen. The green screen almost
just eliminated Sans in what seems like three or four
seconds. How do you fight a green screen?
You just get tangled up in it. You can't even go near it. You're gonna
cast shadows on it. People are gonna scream at you.
Glue Man though trying again. Trying to do it. No.
No eliminations with eight people. Glue Man reverses it now.
He's gonna push him out. There's a lot of possibilities here.
Jax just eliminated the car valet. That's another elimination from Jax.
He was the first one in. Will he be the last one in as well as
go after Pinwheel? Dump him out of here. Jax is unbeatable
and I mean that. I mean it. And he's not gonna lose to Pinwheel.
No like old shit Gerber beat Pinwheel. Jax cannot lose to Pinwheel.
That would. Don't do it. Please don't do it. Fight back Jax.
Do so. The Jax. There we go. Thank god.
The green screen now has got Dr. Schmeichsen while Sands is in the
corner. Is he gonna go for elimination? I wonder
what character is about to eliminate Dr. Schmeichsen.
He's got a chance. No. No. He's not gonna.
A shooting star press from Magistake and there goes Dr. Schmeichsen.
Dr. Schmeichsen is gone. Pinwheel is just
taunting. Pinwheel is taunting everybody. Sands did not like that.
Sands is gonna come up with Pinwheel. Now gets chopped in the face
for his efforts. Here comes. What is with the moves
from Magistake? Another competitor it seems like ages since we've seen
somebody new. And it's Beanbag Sonic coming in
somewhere about at the midway point. That's a pretty good place to be.
Beanbag Sonic making his first ever appearance in the rumble.
What happened? Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Did Jax. Wait. Hold on.
Hey. No. Hold on. Jax. Who. I didn't even see it.
Who eliminated Jax and Glooman? Those are the two
favorites. They're not gonna win. Jax and Glooman are both gone.
Did the green screen eliminate Jax? No fucking way.
God damn it. I was looking at like. I was looking at.
They're both doing the same animation. There it goes.
Jax and Glooman. Glooman will never win. He's just never gonna win.
We'll take your pick in here. I'm rooting for Beanbag Sonic.
I think he deserves it. And Beanbag Sonic and Sands both
equal weight here. Sonic is fresh. Beanbag Sonic is brand
new so no fatigue while Sands. What does Sonic have in mind here?
What is he doing? Beanbag Sonic. You hear that crowd scream.
Is Beanbag Sonic going to go around and eliminate every person?
That is elimination number one for Beanbag Sonic.
Dropped him on his head. Here comes another contestant all the way from
the one stream that everybody hated. Soon to be on a Christmas special.
That's BF Bugleberry. Resident scary storyteller.
There goes Pinwheel. The green screen is too strong.
The green screen is too strong. I don't know why it's this powerful.
BF Bugleberry. Sands is gone. Green screen now looking like the
person to beat here. Defense is still outside.
Beanbag Sonic. The green screen. Willem Dafoe is number 15 at the halfway
mark. We have made it to halfway through the
2018 rumble. And there is Willem Dafoe. Something of a
scientist. There he is. Half of one of Jeremy's emotes.
And please get rid of the fucking green screen. Do it, Dafoe.
Channel the goblin. You can do it. Channel the green goblin. He's green.
He didn't even want to do it. He didn't care. Why did you do that?
Let the goblin take over. Don't just let him eliminate you. What are you
doing? No. Bugleberry is gone. Bugleberry.
I wanted him to win. Bugleberry is gone. Gets eliminated by Beanbag Sonic.
And in comes binary man. 0-1-1-0-1-10-0-0-2-2.
From the detective stream. He's incredibly strong.
He's not. Oh no, he's not. Is Beanbag Sonic about to-
Yeah, binary man 0-1-1-0-1-0-0-1-1. Welcome to the rumble. Nice cartwheel by
the green goblin, aka Willem Dafoe. Just testing the mat, I guess. Beanbag
Sonic, it would be a shame if binary man eliminated you.
It's all right. Because I think I just heard something.
I just heard that. I've waited. The green screen's about to come out. Green
screen's going out. Maybe wall dad's coming in.
No, it's- Oh, what a right hand by wall dad. I just heard a sledgehammer break
over on the side of the wall there, and I
I heard it, but what is that for a t-shirt? What is that?
Okay, he's wearing his son's Minecon shirt.
Okay, that's fine. I mean, he has to find a way to put clothes on.
He's hiding the wall. Wall dad from House Flipper. What's that smell?
That smells delicious. That smells kind of like a red blend wine to me.
Binary man has been eliminated as red blend. The wine glass
with the cork head comes in. Binary man is gone. Beanbag Sonic is still in.
Magistank is still in. Willem Dafoe is still in. Green screen.
Sonic is about to get eliminated by the red blend. Oh, that would be
unfortunate. It does taste great, though.
Beanbag Sonic is on the ropes. No, wall dad
misses a punch there from the green screen. Oh, and here comes Adam Sandler.
No, no, no. The green screen needs to be eliminated. Adam Sandler
going right for the green screen. Using his comedic comedy technique.
Will he eliminate the green screen? Pick him up. He's fired up after that
loss. Adam Sandler, and there goes the
red blend. Beanbag Sonic has eliminated another
contestant. Red blend is now gone, but it is good. So you got Willem Dafoe,
Beanbag Sonic, green screen, Adam Sandler, and Magistank,
except maybe not for long. Big drop kick there by Willem Dafoe.
Don't. The green screen is about to eliminate another person.
No, no. Somebody has to stop him. Somebody stop the green screen before
he eliminates like 50 people. Hopefully it'll be Elvis.
Hopefully it'll be Elvis from Las Vegas, Nevada.
Come on, get in there, Elvis. Jerma's move to Vegas
has proved to be successful. Elvis, of course, and look at how many
people it takes to try to get the green screen out.
You need three. Elvis, get over. Don't touch Beanbag Sonic.
Go after the green screen. He's unbeatable. He's the Jex of this
competition. What are you thinking? Nice reverse. Then there goes Beanbag
Sonic. Elvis eliminated Beanbag Sonic.
Sad day, but he may eliminate the green screen. That's unfortunate.
Oh, fucking great. How did he get in here?
Really? He fucking, he hacked my, he hacked my fucking game.
Put himself in. Fucking loser. That's GrillmasterxBDQ.
The guy that I made a video with or something like that.
He's another, like, screamer. He sucks.
This is his, like, haha, ultimate, like, I got you, right? Like, you come
in with the Jerma Rumble. Like, my fucking thing.
I don't even know what he made of stats, but that's fucking annoying.
Anyways, GrillmasterxBDQ, an old cooking channel from YouTube, is
going to be welcomed by GaryTheFuckUp. Maybe GaryTheFuckUp can
get some more YouTube footage of him hurting people,
as he's got Willem Dafoe over the shoulder here. No, gets reversed by
Willem Dafoe. Elvis, Grillmaster, the green
screen, GaryTheFuckUp, Magistank, and speaking of Grillmaster, is he
going to eliminate Elvis? Elvis is not eliminated. He's still in
the ring, and here comes Otto. Otto the Duxen. It's taken me four or
five years to put him in, but there he is. There's Otto.
Hey, come on. Like, please let him get in the ring for a second.
GaryTheFuckUp is gone. Willem Dafoe with a Lariat.
An absolutely hellish Lariat to GaryTheFuckUp.
Both the duo of Bill Crazy and GaryTheFuckUp are gone.
Otto comes in. The longest person that's been in here, the green screen, has been
in here the absolute longest. It's been
almost 20 straight minutes. Oh, right. I forgot.
There comes Jerma Raptor. The most embarrassing thing I've ever done
is now in the ring. I feel like he deserved to be there, and I would make
I would be so happy if you threw this guy out right now.
I would be ecstatic if Jerma Raptor threw Grillmaster XBBQ out right now.
What do you do? Are you using it as an exercise ball? Are you going to let
him do that to you? Really? Willem Dafoe taking a
little bit of a break as the green screen just knows how strong
he is and knows that no one stands a chance.
He just pushed Jerma Raptor, and thank God.
Thank you, Elvis. Elvis just eliminated Grillmaster XBBQ
to never return. They'll never be in another Rumble ever again. I'm
deleting the character. Is he eliminating himself? What the
fuck was that? What? What did Otto just do? Did
Otto just fake him? Why didn't you put a Raptor?
Just jump over the ropes for no reason. Well, it's okay.
Jerma Raptor will get replaced by another Jerma character. Here comes
Odd Michael. You can't put capes on in this game for some reason, but
there's Odd Michael. This is going to get interesting. There
goes Willem Dafoe. Magistank throws Willem Dafoe over the top ropes.
You've got Elvis and Odd Michael in the same spot. Will they work together?
I would love to see a Jerma Odd Michael and an Elvis collaboration here.
Going after his own dog while the fucking green screen is about to throw
another person over the top ropes. Thankfully, Elvis ain't down with that
as he breaks out of what could have been a terrible situation for him.
No, they're fighting each other. Don't fight each other. You should be
helping each other. The three of you. Yes, just get taunted by the green
screen while he just does a boot party on Elvis. Magistank is still
in the ear clap. He just crushed it. He just gave him a
migrate. Otto now has Odd Michael while the green screen,
thank god, has not eliminated a seventh person potentially.
No, there it is. There goes Elvis by the green screen, but I have high hopes
for the Nintendo Labo. I have extraordinarily high hopes.
Taking a long time to get in here. There he is. The Nintendo Switch Labo.
And he just just goes right after Jerma for making such a terribly
boring stream three times. Make sure you do it on the fold lines.
Crease the fold lines well when you throw him out. Otherwise, what the
fuck are you doing, Odd Michael? There was absolutely no reason to do that.
This would be pretty poetic if Odd Michael were to be eliminated by the
Labo as the green screen is in a very bad
position for the Quiet Man to come in. Quiet Man number 27. 27. In comes the
Quiet Man from literally the worst game ever as
he picks up Odd Michael over the shoulder. No, a reversal.
Quiet Man is one of the last three. Get him out of here.
Get the green screen out of here of all the people.
I can't fucking believe he's still in this. He's about to throw a magic tank
over the top ropes. Is it gonna be possible? There he goes.
Chuck Schnoswell number 28. Will somebody stop him?
Somebody please. He's just, he's just the new Jax.
Chuck Schnoswell coming in. Will he be the hero that we all hope for?
Come on, Chuck. He feels the crowd. He feels the energy of the audience.
Will Chuck Schnoswell eliminate the most impossible to eliminate Contender?
He's got him over the top just barely pushing his legs.
Come on, Chuck. Use the fucking nose. Use your nose, Chuck.
Get it! Get it! No!
Otto is about to throw Odd Michael over the top ropes.
And here comes a Hornet from the fucking wall of the old house.
If there's anybody that can do it, it's definitely him. And the Quiet Man
is about to throw. No, thank God it was just a scoopslam. Chuck Schnoswell
now for that insolence. And that's
come on. No. Well, somebody sprayed the Hornet.
He's gone. That was all it took. Just swatted him. What an
overhead press by the Quiet Man. On to Otto the Dog.
Odd Michael trying to put work into the green screen.
Huge chokeslam. And there goes Odd. No. There goes. Who the fuck was it?
Who just got thrown out? Otto. Oh God. It's Otto the Dog has been
eliminated by the Quiet Man. And the Quiet Man is about to
powerbomb the Labo. He is incredibly strong. Green screen
still cannot get thrown out after being double teamed.
We only have two more people coming in. Nice miss, Odd Michael.
You're shitty Dr. Strange. This booze coming in.
Could this be? Can we get the last person?
The last person is Fireman. What is he?
Holy shit. He's fresh and he's the last contestant.
Get rid of that fucking green screen. The green screen is dazed.
He's tired. He's confused. Fireman. Oh no. Just barely. You didn't do it.
I think he's so stupid. He thinks he did it.
He thought he eliminated him. He couldn't tell he was invisible. Somebody
keyed him out. Somebody keyed the green screen out. No.
There goes Odd Michael. Fireman fighting for his life.
The green screen just can't seem to do it. One of these contestants will
win. One of these contestants will win. The
Labo has just been limited by Chuck Schnauzwell.
Fireman green screen to the Quiet Man. One of these four will be your 2018
champion. It's just absolute bullshit that he
can just be keyed out whenever he wants. He can turn invisible.
He can turn into other people. He can turn into you
and you think you're in the ring. What a reversal by Fireman. Will
Fireman come in as the last spot and clean up the whole ring?
No. Not quite. Quiet Man gets dropped on a knee there.
What is he pointing to? I think he's just trying to get some energy here.
Chuck Schnauzwell doing a dab from one of his best friends, Beanbag Sonic. They
become really close friends actually since those videos. And can Chuck
Schnauzwell with the strength of 50. No.
No. With the strength of 50 bats. Being able to throw him over.
Uh-oh. Quiet Man with a big right hand.
We've got to see an elimination here. We got to see a green screen
Quiet Man elimination. Chuck Schnauzwell with a huge suplex.
You've got two fan favorites. A character that I put in
because of a stream I did three days ago and the green screen.
Who is going to win? Chuck Schnauzwell now in the air. The green screen
just seems to pick up all these characters like toys
as Fireman is going to see an opportunity to pick up Quiet Man and
maybe get something done here. Scooping him up over the shoulder.
Throwing him backwards into the ground. Oh knees to the face.
That's got to hurt though. He might get burnt. The top of the head
of Fireman is very very strong now and I don't know what he's doing here.
He's working trying to break his leg as the green screen
has no gets reversed by Fireman. Not in a good position.
Oh Quiet Man has Chuck on the this is not good for Chuck.
Quiet Man could see an elimination here and will be down to three.
Fireman is awaiting the consciousness to it.
Come on Fireman. Oh no. He gets stopped by a stray punch
by Chuck Schnauzwell. I will say though these four
they're giving it all they got. Chuck is just getting punched. Have to punch
in the face over and over again. Thank god he's got that nose armor and
now Chuck is in the grasp of the green screen.
No man. No thing. No person has been able to
stop him. As you see the Quiet Man. Chuck Schnauzwell is gone. It's
Quiet Man. No. Thank goodness. Come on Fireman.
Fireman stop it. Fireman no. No Fireman. Do what you can. No. Oh no.
It's the green screen versus Quiet Man.
How many eliminations has the green screen done?
This is like 12 eliminations. Is he gonna throw him over the ropes
right now? There's no way. I can't. I would be so
shocked if the Quiet Man eliminates the green screen. What?
Oh that's it. That's gonna be it. That's it. The winner of the 2018
Rumble is the green screen. I can't believe it. He destroyed
everybody. It wasn't even a chance. Nobody had a chance.
Not. Nobody could even match his strength.
The green screen. There you go. Yep. See you at WrestleMania. This is
WrestleMania. He lasted a very very long time too.
That was so long. He was like number one. Like 11 or 12
or something. He stayed in the whole time.
Holy shit. But it could be anybody. This could be
anybody. Correct the timeline. I can't. That is the timeline.
Fucking green screen. God damn it. All right. Well if I rematch it's not
gonna randomize him again. I'm gonna have to just do another
one. The green screen winning is worse than the pencil.
I don't think that's true. All right. I'll do another one for fun.
We'll do the encore here. Congratulations to the 2018
Jermania Rumble for the green screen. At least it wasn't the quiet man.
Oh thank god. There's nothing. I would have been
so upset. All right. Let's just do another rumble.
So this next one is not canon but it's just for fun. I guess we can
throw. How about this? It's canon. No. The green
screen wins. It's out of my hands. I can't fucking
believe it. All right. Let me get this set up.
Let's put the same people in at random. Show the stats of everybody.
They're all very very similar. I'll show you. Hold on.
I don't think the green screen has that high of
stats. Yeah he doesn't. Lou has more stats than the green
screen. Like we'll just put it that way.
Like look. Lou is a hundred overall. Green screen is 92.
Like you know what I mean? He's a fucking hundred. But everybody.
I never put anybody under like 85. Like ever. Like 90. Because it's more fun
that way. Because if you have. It doesn't really
matter as much. Oh and it's 92. No they're all
like in the 80s and 90s. What does Sandler have?
Never mind. That's not true. He's 79.
All right.
All right. Let's get. Let's get everybody in here. See. Well binary man's 80.
Yeah everybody's within like 80 to 100. 80 to 95.
So then it's not like unfair for anybody. Fucking green screen.
Gary the fuck up's 100. Well you. Yeah I don't know why he's stronger
than Bill. He should not be stronger than Bill
crazy. But he is apparently. Yeah 94. Except for Sandler. Well
but you really want me to make Adam Sandler
the strongest person. All right hold on. Let me get rid of you.
Who's not in it? Wait I don't think. I don't think she was in it before.
Oh you can be in there this time. Binary man. Binary man was so bad.
Did you even get to see his face? Look at his face. He's got like.
You can only have eight numbers of letters on a character.
Green screens of weight and stats. Yeah but wouldn't that be the same
thing with um like the labo and the the labo is
the same stats. He I know for I am certain that he is like a super heavy
weight. Bugleberry. I made him like four or five
hundred pounds. Let's go here. But if you were just
joining us for the the festivities there thank you for
joining. There's a lot of people here. So thanks a lot. Thanks for sticking
around. Now we're gonna do the the encore.
Yeah but here they all are. Otto versus Jeremy.
You have to see how it says random. Like I can't. I don't. You can do it.
See entry order. I can do it. But that's not fun.
I'd rather let the cards lie however they lie you know.
Okay but look at these other wrestlers like
73. 70. Come on man. Poor blue man. Blue man's never gonna win.
Green screen first. But you can't. We can't do that.
I have to at least give the it's not random at that point.
All right we got red blend. Chris Jericho is not going to be in it.
Uh there's real faster. Sans. Yeah there was no bf. Do I deserve to
I didn't put myself in the rumble. I'm already there like three times. Do
I deserve to be there this time? All right I guess I deserve to be there
on the encore. It's not canon so it's fine.
Now these two these two aren't being in it Labo.
I don't know who the hell you are but you're not in it. Uh Jax.
I really thought he was gonna go far. Look at his stats. Come on.
Elvis is 88. Who eliminated Jax? Leave John Cena in.
All right John Cena can replace Elvis. Who the hell is John Cena?
That's so odd. Oh Chad Gable. Chris Jericho. Oh Kurt Hawkins.
Okay. DDP. Nice. Oh Dr Dan and Dr Don. You
belong in this universe. Where the hell is he? Seth Rollins.
Let's see. Where's John? Oh this is champions. Okay.
Jim. John Cena. Why the fuck am I putting him in this?
He's not even as strong as Jax. Why you don't even shouldn't even be here.
Adam Sandler stays. Be the very stays. All right uh poor wall dad.
How is pinwheel 96? Because it wouldn't have been fair.
If I made pinwheel like 10 and be 90
or 80 that match would you'd be able to say that's not fair.
I beat him as a fucking 90 plus. Uh Wally Wheat. Willem Dafoe.
Pinwheel. Okay. Yeah you're out of here.
Never allowed in another rumble ever again. All right so we put uh
Sweet Rhyne, Odd Michael, Magistank, or Fru Fru or Elvis.
Put pinwheel at 10. All right Sweet Rhyne.
So yeah the green screen's staying in. We can't just because they're all
powerful doesn't mean that they're impossible to overcome. All right
looks good. Uh yeah you can't do anything in a rumble.
Momentum is normal. Entrances are fine. Uh we could do
fast momentum. I usually put it on normal. Fast.
All right let's do it. All right let's go. Here's the encore rumble.
Let's see what happens. And then we'll do a um we'll do like a
hardcore like cage match or something with random people.
But that was a lot of fun. It always is. All right we already know how the rules
work. Skip. Can I skip? Oh yeah I forgot
John Cena is in the game. Well look I'm gonna get like another
drink. We'll we'll do another match or two.
Don't worry. All right I'll be right back. I'm gonna grab a drink.
Just let this play out. I don't even know. I'm not even gonna know who the
first two are so I'll be right back. Oh somebody said no Avril Lavigne. I
tried. The problem is you can't have uh
I'm pretty sure you can't have uh female and male wrestlers in the same ring at
the same time. I'm fairly certain about that.
Unless they changed it but I don't think they did because I couldn't do it.
So I tried. Avril Lavigne was supposed to be in place
of like one of the one of like the rain like the red blend like the
fucking wine. That was the last character by the
way. I just like I was oh shit I gotta have like a 36 person.
Oh come on. I don't want to see this. I'll be right back.
All right what I miss. Wait is this this entrance has been going off us so long?
This is all you've been seeing.
All right well here's the his alternate timeline.
Let's do it. Welcome to the encore rumble. B.F. Bilgerberri my favorite
character. Uh he's probably gonna get eliminated
in like 15 seconds. Here we go. And different camera angle for some
reason. That was nice. Can we get more cannon match?
No this is this is the alternate fucking timeline.
You know like civil war or marvel. How like
that did that happen in its own universe. Number three coming in is
Bill Krazy. Why do they wipe the dirt? I don't understand.
This is cannon. This is not cannon. It's not cannon because Bilgerberri
is gonna get eliminated first. And that just angers me. Bill Krazy
now has got pinwheel. Hopefully eliminating you first because
you're the worst character. So please get rid of pinwheel.
Get rid of him. Yes thank god. And are you sure you guys want this
cannon? Because beanbag sonic's coming in at number four. Are you sure you
want this to be cannon? You sure? Or do you want to write
your fan fiction where beanbag sonic wins and eliminates 29 people?
What the fuck? No no this is my favorite this is my favorite character.
Don't do it. Don't you fucking dare. Come on B.F.
Bugleberry. Pull a green screen. Yeah by the way I told you this already.
You'll be seeing this guy real fucking soon on Christmas.
Christmas spooktacular. Gonna be the scariest fucking Christmas scream you've
ever seen. Oh what a beautiful move by B.F.
Bugleberry. Quiet man coming in number five.
Thank god. Why would you roll to the outside of the ring? What are you
doing? Why would you ever do that? For what
reason? Bill Krazy is still taking punches
here for the quiet man. Going for his bird feet kick. The
claws there is gonna rip. I almost just set something really
fucked up. Let's just pretend let's just say we
kicked him. Dermaraptor coming in number six.
That guy back there is really excited in the white shirt.
Dermaraptor. Which by the way again next weekend is the movie night with
the green screen stuff. If you have a submission please go
check out the discord and check out the rules associated with
that. It's gonna be a lot of fun. I've already seen a couple submissions and
they are... What the fuck? That was crazy. This is
now canon. Just because of that. Like he's been
practicing for his YouTube channel. Here comes Garrett from the Sims
family house. I did that on the green screen. I did that
six days ago. That exact move. Nice reversal there by Garrett.
B.F. Bugleberry is still in. There goes the quiet man. Thank god.
If there was a straw poll right now he would be... Yeah there goes
Beanbag Sonic by B.F. Bugleberry. If I did a poll right now I think the
quiet man would be number one. Okay that...
What the hell was that? A lot of weird shit in this one. The
computer's trying to load a bunch of random things.
We get two Sims murder house. Nice recovery there by Chuck Schnozwell.
I mean they all hate each other so it makes sense of why they would be
fighting each other anyways. Belly to belly suplex. No he's
just kind of hugging him really tightly.
Not much you can do to build crazy that he has not done to himself
already. And Jerma Raptor's about to learn the hard way here. Well he's
gonna get scooped out and possibly thrown over by Bill Krazy.
Is it possible? Is he gonna get it done? B.F. Bugleberry now coming into
aid. Bill Krazy and they get it done.
Jerma Raptor is gone. Bugleberry showing lots of strength
here. He crossed arm. Check into Bill Krazy. After the
help I think it's time for me to fuck up your face.
Carvalet comes in. He's probably a little confused because this is the
second time that somebody has called in the last 30 minutes.
He keeps parking cars out there. By the way his entrance
is him riding it on a motorcycle and stopping. But you know you don't get to
see that because this is the rumble and it didn't make it. Number 10 is
Sands Undertale. He left after the last one. Yeah
we're just doing an encore one for fun.
That is now officially canon because Bill Krazy did a back flip so now
it's canon. Sands coming to number 10 and
probably instantly eliminated by Bill Krazy. Taunting is a bad move here.
Why would you do that? He did the Hulk Hogan and he kind of
looks like Hulk Hogan. I didn't intend that to happen but it just happened.
Otto the dog coming at number 11. Bugleberry looks like he's in...
No. Come on. Make this canon. Big suplex to Garrett from the Carvalet
from Sleeping Dogs. I thought that Bill Krazy was going
over the top ropes there but no. Big wow. Oh big wow. Otto is gone.
God damn it man. Can he catch a break? Bugleberry is top seat right
now. He didn't even get to take a second breath.
He inhaled, walked into the ring, got eliminated and then exhaled.
He didn't get to even breathe. Otto the dog is gone. Here comes Sweet Rind.
Still getting close to the halfway point on our
Marvel Ultimate alternate universe. Oh there goes the Carvalet Sweet Rind
with a big right head to punch. Throws him over. He's gone. Sorry if you
were betting on him. That was wild. Just swinging in
every direction was Bill Krazy. He didn't even care. He was just going
to hurt anybody that was near him. Powerbomb potentially over the top
ropes but to Sweet Rind from Bill Krazy. Are we going to see it?
Holy shit. That was dead happen twice. They both did it.
Bugleberry and Bill Krazy with the double.
In it comes John Cena. The chanting his name. Stop chanting his name.
Shut up everybody. Stop saying that. No. He's going to eliminate Chuck
Schnoswell. You happy about that? Is that what you guys want to see?
Don't say that. John Cena comes in. I forgot he was there. I thought there
was a mistake. I forgot I put him in here. Good.
The drop kick him over the top. Fireman coming in number 14.
B.F. Bugleberry has Bill Krazy now in a bad position. Fireman coming in
instead of 30 at 14. Yeah I want to see Fireman. I don't want to see
John Cena and now they both are working on Bill Krazy. There goes Bill
Krazy. He's out. Add him to the list of people eliminated by B.F.
Bugleberry. Right into the turnbuckle. Big
Fireman with an overhead throw. Throws over Chuck Schnoswell.
They're chanting some shit for John Cena.
Oh that's great. I'm so happy about this. Is he going to do a thing
where he puts a hand in front of his face
and like sneezes. Nice. The Hornet comes in with a big
right hand. Will the Hornet stay in for more than five seconds this time?
Maybe. Cena. John Cena. So here's the the question I have to ask you
guys. Is is it possible here that Fireman near
the Hornet. Can we get an up and smoke potential
scenario here? Glue Man coming in at 16. If you had one opportunity Glue Man
it's right now. Here's your shot. By the way I just
want to make this very clear. The Glue Man shirt will be back on sale
here. Oh.
Whoa. Not gonna waste any time. Get rid of Cena too.
Fire yourself up man. Come on. Get rid of Cena.
Bingo. That's a double elimination too from Glue Man. He's like fuck this man
if this is gonna be canon. I'm gonna make this shit canon.
I'm gonna win this shit. Red Blend wine coming in.
Will Glue Man and Bugleberry make this canon? I wonder. That was odd.
But nice work. Red Blend. Let me go ahead and.
Ah. Glue Man with a reversal to Red Blend. The best kind of wine you can
drink. It actually is. A lot of wines are gross. Red
Blend is the best of all red wines. Highly recommended. You're a
fucking weirdo. I know that's not even true. That's not true.
All right come on Bugleberry. Throw him over. Here comes the Greenscreen.
Greenscreen stuck on the ropes. No. Fuck you Greenscreen.
No. He ruined another one. He ruined another rumble.
He ruined another one. He's stuck on the ropes
and he can't even game crashed. He's like if I ain't winning I'm bringing
the whole fucking thing to the ground. I love and hate this. I fucking hate
this because we were in the middle of this. Like it was
we were doing something. Fuck the Greenscreen.
Now it has to be canon. All you guys that were so upset about this.
What what would you have me do about this? You understand?
What am I supposed to do about this? It's that he wins.
I'm sorry. Rewatch it. I can't even get out of here. I'm
stuck in here. My computer is hard locked. The
Greenscreen is about to turn the stream off.
You understand? That's unfucking believable.
Hold on. No. Oh wait wait wait. I got it. I got it.
No I don't. I have access to my mouse but I can't
force quit the game. Oh my god. I can't do anything. It's stuck here
forever. There's nothing I can do. I have to
control alt delete. I can't see the task manager because it's behind the
game. Hold on. Can I pull it up from here?
No I can't. Alt tap. Yeah alt tap doesn't do anything. Hold on wait wait.
Come on come on come on. No I can't do anything. It's fucked.
I am forced quitting the game right now and it's not doing anything.
Why? Of all things. I can't get out of it.
Start a new desktop. Put windows into a shutdown then
force the exe to stop. Yeah but then the computer turns off.
Now let me try this. Control Windows D. What does that do?
Hold on. No. Oh the whole thing's fucked.
Physically remove your hard drive from your computer. If I could just get the
task manager to like hold on. What if I do this?
I gotta make one of my other monitors the main display.
How the fuck can I even do that without seeing it?
Uh oh. Did I get it? Oh god what the fuck have I done?
Oh god what's happening? Oh boy this is not good.
Come on. Did I get it? Come on let me get it. Right here.
Get over here. Fuck. I can't do it. Why?
Well I'm gonna have to like turn off the screen.
I can't even see chat anymore. Force quitting it doesn't do anything.
Fucking green screen. God damn it. No I refuse to give up. What is this?
Hold on. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. This is bad. I'll be right. I'll be. Hold on. I'll be
right back. Hey. How are you doing?
Yeah I had to force boot my computer. That's canon. I'm not
changing it. There's no way. How can I change that now? We can do
another one? I mean at this point
that's the way it is. Let's do it. Let's do something different. Let's do
another one. Let's do like uh instead of a rumble.
The universe is making me not do one. So let's do uh
let's do like a hardcore cage match or something with
random characters. Hell in a cell. Let's do hell in a cell.
Green screen versus me in backstage rumble. I'm gonna lose. It's gonna crash
the game. All these fucking people. Jesus Christ.
All right. Are we talking about like alternate me or
or actual like old shitty me? Does anybody know what that picture is from?
Please tell me you do. Yeah that's from twitter.
All right let's do. See I'm 97. Yeah I do low blows. I'm an asshole. All
right. Let's see if I can take the green
screen down once and for all. See 90. Look everyone that was talking
shit about how the green screen is so powerful. You made the green screen to
see 92 versus 97. 92. He's not that good. There are
people that are like eight points higher than him. He's
too big. No he's not. Look at the labo. Labo. Okay
the labo is just as big just as heavy in 95.
And uh also by the way sweet rind is 92 and bigger.
He's bigger than the green screen. Hold on. How is the green screen
a super heavyweight? And nobody else? Do I have is he the only super heavyweight?
How? How does that make any sense? Why is he a super heavyweight?
There's another. There's another super heavyweight. All right I'm fucking kicking
this guy's ass. He has poison mist. It's green. I
figured maybe he was going to spit out green mist and it'd be funny.
All right let's go. Backstage brawl. I'm gonna kick the
fucking green screen's ass. Even as like old 33 year old shit
germa. The green screen has to be big. He's
huge. He's the size of a wall. Let's. Oh god. And here's the
worst part about this. This is very keyable. You could
you could put whatever you want there. So now I just fucked myself for like
another four years. Come on get up and fight him. Get up
and do anything. Do something. No don't let him beat you like
this. Somebody has to beat the green screen.
There it is. Oh he tripped. It's a little slippery over here.
All right let's go into the bathroom. I'm gonna like flush you down the
toilet. What? Oh no. No. We're going to the
tv. There's a desk. There's a table. Raw.
Come on reverse it germa. No get back in here. There's so much more interesting
shit in here. God this is gonna turn like Scooby
Doo isn't it? All right into the tv. Just like
nice. Nice lariat. Who the fuck is that?
Who is this lady? What? Are we in somebody's office?
Oh no not the chair. Oh not the chair green screen. Come on.
This is nothing he's had enough already. Somebody said this is a porn intro.
Just key out the green screen. Can somebody please do that?
For the green screen stream next weekend. Key this fucking guy out of
here. What? No don't do it.
No. I'm still alive. I'm still alive.
I'm persevering. That's one thing I got guarantee for you.
It didn't break. I don't weigh enough for it to break.
I'm like 148 pounds. No put him through it. Pick him up germa. You can do it.
Do something. Punch him. Throw him. Throw him through the tv.
No don't. Not me. Oh my god. I tripped over the chair that was in the way.
Seriously. This is just sad. I'm just it's like
I'm just getting bullied right now. I feel bad about this whole thing.
Nobody can stop him. I lost. That's it. The game's over.
No it's not. Stay alive. Just fucking electrocute him.
Just like hitman style. Walk him into water and fucking throw
throw like a toaster at him. Come on. No. I got a better idea. I know who can
fucking stop this motherfucker. Now you're fucked. You're dead. I'm
channeling my Jecks. I beat Jebel first try guys.
I beat Jebel first try. You want me to first try this guy too?
Turn on the Jecks. A little bit taller. Yeah.
Push him. Come on. No. Come on. This is like the
this is my like ultimate character. You can't get embarrassed right now.
Oh my fucking lord. Don't get embarrassed.
Kick his ass. All the germas fail to the green screen.
No. That's not gonna happen. Jecks is gonna come back
and he's gonna hit him in the head with an iron.
He's a fucking hundred. You can't have better stats than Jecks.
Who's ironing? I'll open up a closet and find one.
I don't need to have an I'll find an iron. All right wipe the floor with
them Jecks. Come on. Why would you walk with them? You
can't toy with the green screen. End him. That's not it right? Okay
we're good. Come on. Come back here. Nice. Nice.
Very good. Very good. Why do I care this much about this?
I'm so upset with the green screen. Somebody has to beat him.
Where are you taking me? Where are we going now? Oh my god. I tripped over the
speed bump. Give me a break. That's not a Jecks move.
What the fuck? There are attendants? There's a truck?
Go to the car. Can we like run somebody over with the car? I will lose
my mind if that happens. If Jecks like gets in the car and
runs him over, I'll die on screen. You'll see me die on screen.
Come on. Twist the elbow. He's like no I can't take that.
There it is. There's the Jeremy Elbrittson family line.
I grab your wrist. I fall down. You fall down.
That's been for generations. My father taught me that. You want to fuck
somebody up in a fight? Just grab with two hands their
fucking wrist and fall down as hard as you can.
You're gonna fuck him up. Guaranteed. Break his neck.
Snap his neck. Come on Jecks. Snap his fucking neck.
Ugh. Come on. What? Give me a break. And watch out for the electricity.
No. No. Don't. Did I die? Is that? What? No. No.
No. No. Come on. There's no way. I got fucking electrocuted. The thing
that I said I wanted to do to him, he does to me. And I'm still alive.
You can't stop, Jecks. Even with electrocution.
Get over to the cars. I want to see a car death.
We need super Jecks. Should I make super Jecks?
Just make them like seven feet tall. Just turn them like green and make them
like fucking eight feet tall. Why is this turning into a DBZ timeline?
Oh I can't beat him as regular Jecks. I have to go super Jecks.
That's it. No. That's not it. What? No. Don't taunt. What are you doing?
What the fuck? Did we just watch?
Oh my fucking back hurts. I thought I won and he's...
It's time to bring in Adam Sandler. Fuck it. We're going with the real. The real. S-tier.
Fucking Adam Sandler. Where is he? Somebody. Come on. He's 79. He sucks.
Let's go. Come on, Sandler. If it doesn't work, we're gonna combine Jecks and Sandler.
We're gonna make super Adam Sandler Jecks. All right. Come on, Sandler.
It's always backstage. I wonder what's gonna happen. He's gonna push him and he's gonna punch
in the face. Why did I think this was gonna work? He's gonna break his neck.
He's gonna kill him. We just sent Adam Sandler to his death.
This wasn't even an attempt. He's 79 and he's a piece of shit.
Oh, I really thought he was gonna snap his neck right there. I was about to fucking lose my mind.
Electrocute. Sandler, electrocute. Sandler, use electrocute. No, don't get electrocuted.
Oh my god. Come on, fight back. Use the Metacritic score of your last six movies
to combine until like 72 percent. God damn it, man. I'm gonna die. Where are you taking him? This
is just bad. Take him into the car. Powerbomb Adam Sandler through the roof of the car
and I will piss my pants. People come out of my fucking penis. It just, that will happen.
Oh, what a reversal. Holy shit. That was an absolute, that was a beautiful reversal.
Oh, come on. Don't let that be the end. Is that the end? It always ends right here. Can
we not end in the fucking hallway? Uh, excuse me. Excuse me attendant. Fire extinguisher. Get it.
Sandler, if you're smart, you're gonna get that fire extinguisher and you're gonna throw it
in his face. Nice. Come on. He did it. Is that it? No, it's never it. He's like,
it's like Michael Myers, man. You can't taunt before. These really are like Microsoft
3D movie maker sound effects. Get out to the cars. At least finish it on the cars, guys.
Nice parry. No, don't take him back here. Uh, I'll tell you one thing. Green screen is slow
to get up. Now where are we going? All the way down this hallway. Wherever the hell this is,
he's doing the, I'm gonna end this taunt. Uh, that's it. He's gonna taunt. While he's
lying on the ground, you had an opportunity there. Nice job. This is a fucking idiot.
This is three matches in a row. He's tired. And now people are booing. I don't blame them.
I would be booing too. Come on, Sandler. Now is it over? What's going on with his legs?
He's prepping up like a finishing move. No, he does it every time and he wins with that
every time. What are you doing? Adam Sandler is fine. No, he's not. Break his leg. Get up.
Don't get choked out. Oh my God. Look, he's limp. Did you see that leg? Did you see how
fucked up that was? This is bad. Adam Sandler is limp right now. This is just fucking sad.
Sadler. And with that, a reversal. He's not gonna be Adam Sandler for all. Come on,
Sandler. He's got him in the chokeslip. This is his finishing move. Do it. Holy shit.
Did he win? He wins, right? Come on. At the Sandler chokeslip. Dude, no. I can't. This is
going on for a long time. I'm gonna fucking die. I need to stop. I need to like look away
from the screen. What did he do? Break his neck. Oh, what a fucking recovery. Oh my God.
I need to stop. I need to stop looking at the screen. This is fucking stupid.
All right, it's time. It's time to make super jacks. Fuck this guy. Are you kidding me?
It's time to overclock me. What? Why is it Willem Dafoe? I don't know. Okay. All right.
It's time to make fucking super jacks. Let's fucking power him up. You know what I mean?
Like feed him up. Like 640 pounds. Inject him. There you go. Right here. Fucking inject him.
It actually will be unfucking beatable. Thick ass neck too. You know what I mean? Right there.
So many muscles in the back that it's actually like it looks bad. Yep. An incredibly defined
chest. Washboard abs. Look at this shit. That looks gross because it's so good.
Fucking veins everywhere. We are meticulously making a creature, a person that will
absolutely never be beaten. Ever. Give him a nice ass too. No, no, no, no. It's gonna be like a
fatter one. What? What the fuck am I talking about? No. There we go. No, no, no, no. Where
were they? Where were they? The huge ones. The fucking Thanksgiving turkey legs. And we're gonna
make them glow. It's gonna be obnoxious how much he glows. Look at these. Nobody has legs
like this. And put oil all over his body so it's slippery and shit. Look at that. We're not even
done. Fucking RGB glasses. Look at those. Those are like a thousand dollars. Make them fucking
shine. Gold? No shirt. Okay fine. Fuck it. Material? Gold. Gold and shining. And he's
gonna be a hundred in every stat. 100. Gold hair too? Oh you better believe it. And he's
getting fucking DBZ hair. Yeah, fuck this material. If it ain't glowing and gold, I don't want it.
And that's maximum gold intensity. Look at that shit. He looks fucking absolutely fabulous.
All right. Now it's time for the hair. Macaroni pants? You thought I was kidding. We're
actually doing like the Super Saiyan hair. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Excuse me.
And, and he's getting an infinity gauntlet. This, I want to make sure he fucking wins
guaranteed. We can only have one stone. The power stone. That's the only fucking one that
matters anyways. Give him two infinity gauntlets. Okay. Was it the mind stone? What's the,
what's the other most expensive fucking thing in the world? Expensive. I mean,
you know what I'm saying. It's blue, right? Give him a sans eye. I can't give him a sans
eye. I can't make a sans eye. This, no, I don't have a, I can't make a sans eye.
Sans eye. Sans eye. Sans eye. Close enough. Wrong eye. Well he can have it in both eyes.
No, I can't do wrong. I can't change the eye. Do you understand? It's only that. That's it.
That's your sans eye. You can. What do you mean you can? How? It's only that one on the one
side. Sunglasses. Go back. Well, how would I, what, okay. I'll make them sans glasses.
Okay. There. That's fucking sans glasses. I think he's ready. Two infinity gauntlets,
two sans eyes. Super Saiyan. And he's fucking seven and a half feet tall.
Put Jax across. Okay. Jax across the chest. I'll write Jax across his chest. That's a good
idea. And fucking, like, blood. Now, you know what else he's gonna fucking have?
He's gonna channel fucking Beanbag Sonic. No, that, there's a reason why I didn't put him
in the game. You understand? Now I have it on my chest. That means it's fucking real.
Okay. Blood. All right. I need the glow. That's right. I need the glow. No, not Q.
Q Jax. What? Q Jax. Quadruple Jax. It's done. Now let's go to the most important part.
100 in every single step. Every single one. As high as I can get it. Minecraft logo. Well,
that's an incredibly powerful thing. The presentation name. V. Oh, from Boston.
Leg power. Grappling everything at 100. Every single thing. If there's not something at max,
then there's a problem. V for vengeance. Mic performance. What a stupid stat. He is 100.
Abilities. Give him fucking everything. Skills. He's already got like, they all have that
anyways. Okay, I'm ready. New screen pose. That's pretty good. With the two infinity gauntlets.
Level three. Level three. Level three. Hold on, wait. Let's get the pose. Level one. Level,
level three. Let's see it. All level three. You can't have everything level three.
Let's watch the absolute destruction of the green screen. All level three. Hold on. Where is
he? Oh, that's great. 100 everything. Okay, let's do this. Everything level three.
Literal god. And the payback is, look at this. Teleport behind your opponent. Uh, sure.
Instant recovery. The buff enhances your buff. Save it. Let's go. He's ready. All right,
now let's play, uh, what's that song from, uh, what's that song from fucking my hero
academia? I don't like watch anime. I've watched like one. I've only seen one anime.
One-on-one. Backstage brawl. Super Jex. Good fucking luck. 92. Give me a break. Okay.
Acid base. Good call. That's a good call. Let me get it ready. What am I gonna chat?
We're gonna get to see Super Jex fucking just absolutely dunk on somebody. So here we go.
Let me make sure it's fucking loud enough. Come on, Super Jex. This is what you were made for.
You were created for this one fucking moment. Super Jex versus green screen. Oh,
you think you're tall? You think you're like as tall as me? I don't think so.
You wanna talk shit? Let's go. Super Jex. Come on, Super. No fucking way.
Come on, turn up Super Jex. Turn the fuck up. What? Dude, are you really gonna let
Adam Sandler do a better job than you? Give me a fucking break. Powerbomb him through glass table.
You got two infinity gauntlets. Two infinity gauntlets. That's 640 pounds. He's immutable.
He's unbeatable. Come on, Super Jex. Where are you taking him? Oh my god. He's only
fighting at 20%. No, I mean very clearly he's lit the fuck up at like 120%.
20%. This is the comeback right here. What are you doing? What? You just missed like four times.
You can't. What are you doing? Wait, why is the meme funeral about to play autoplay?
Meme funeral. That's a fucking. Break his neck. Break his fucking neck. Snap it.
Come on, Super Jex. Yes.
Oh, shut up. No, I don't. We did it. Super Jex. Timeline has been restored.
Now I need to make a super green screen.
No.
And then we gotta put him in a fucking hell in a cell. Oh god damn it. Why?
Hold on, I gotta duplicate it and make him gold.
And then I gotta put him in a hell in a cell. The ultimate battle.
Look at how good that Willem Dafoe is. I'm sorry, that's fucking perfect.
What a perfect Willem Dafoe. He's as big as he can get. He's six. He already is there.
Make him a blue screen. Super gold screen. Well, no, he has to be a gold screen. Blue screen.
Oh god damn it. Sans blue screen. But forget about the Sans. Let's see. Gold.
He kind of has to be a gold screen. I mean, he just does. Blue or riot. Can he have a gold
head? Blue. Can he have like a gold face? This is going to be unbearable to look at.
This is going to be awful on the eyes. Gold X's. Okay, that makes sense.
Oh, that's gonna be a pain in the ass to put all those up. Jesus fucking christ.
It already, it already hurts my head. This is gonna take a long time.
If you guys are curious as to how long it makes to make a character, like just to make one.
I mean, you painstakingly go through and do this. That's not showing up well.
Maybe an orange will work. A dark orange with a gold look. It's just Dr. Manhattan.
That's what it's turning into. And then make Giga Sandler. We're going too deep, I think.
If I make the material different. Giga Sandler. I'll just make it darker blue.
That's the only way it's gonna work. That's okay. No, that's fine. It's glowing. In
every way the blue is a different looking blue, but because it's glowing. I wonder if
we can make it darker. Yes, we can. But I don't want to go to like purple though.
That looks good. That's the correct looking blue, I think. Remember, it is glowing. He looks like
a tube of toothpaste. I'm sorry. Well, it's fucking super green screen. You think I'm gonna
change his name? Super Sweet Rind. We're going too deep. That's too deep. That looks good.
I gotta fix the other one though. Giga Rind. You guys see how you can just get lost in
these games, right? What the fuck does that present even mean? What does that mean? What
does that even mean? I can't even, I don't know what that means. All right, that's fine. Wait,
is that the right color? Is that the right color? Now it is. There's so many X's on them.
I'm going as fast as I can. One, two, three, one, one, two, three, four, five. Thankfully,
it's already in place and I have to spend like an hour making this. It takes about
30 to, 30 minutes to an hour to make every character. Think about how easy they are.
So if you can imagine 36 characters, it was about 30 to 40 hours to make everything.
But I love it. I have so much fun just making weird shit. No, don't emboss it. I need to make
it glow, man. Material. There we go. Because even like this, this shit I'm doing right now,
you wouldn't imagine it would take long, but time just melts the fuck away. And this
shit is already here. And this guy is like a fairly simple person. Galoo Man God form.
Okay, that's all right. And then the one, the two in the back. Oh, he's got four in the
back, actually. Well, here's a little behind the scenes, how things work when you make
characters in these games. Fuck. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. One,
two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. Still angry that the game crashed when
he was doing, when Galoo Man was doing. I know. I don't know why that seems to happen
every time we do these. Blue screen of death, green screen. All right. Almost done.
Only two more. Thankfully, I'm familiar with the menus too, because I'd be like,
wait, where do I go? What, what, what, what does this do? Why is this headed there?
The head will be changed, don't worry. The head's gonna get changed. All right,
there's all the markers. Gold markers glowing. So now we're gonna go to the
head. Hands too, need to be changed. Edit them. That's fine. Make them glow.
And make them that blue. That matches pretty well. Good. Pretty good. Fucking
giga blue screen. That's it. Make his head the right color. He's already
glowing. That's good. Matches pretty well. I'm gonna change the material
though. No, I'm not. Because that would take the glow off. That's good.
He's so, he's so oily and shiny. All right, gonna do his feet. He's wearing
just green socks. That doesn't match. It's weird because sometimes you pick
the same color, but it just doesn't match. That's close enough, I think,
right here. Maybe a little bit darker. Oh, because it needs to be glowing,
right? All right, he's done. There's giga blue screen. I don't know.
There he is. Hair? I can't, I can't put hair on him.
Put Goku hair on him? I can't, I can't. I can't. Should I just take the mask off
and give him Goku hair? I can't. Hair can't go. Here's the most
infuriating thing about WWE since 2K14, okay? Here's a major complaint.
Half of the stuff for clothing and masks and face masks and head gear
is not compatible with half of the other stuff in the game.
So, for instance, look at this. Ready? Like, appearance, right? Even clothing.
Let me go to, like, upper body, for instance. And, like, oh, jackets.
So, like, there are a bunch of shit. Like, I can't put any of these on.
None of these can go on. See that in the lower left corner?
That means it can only be put on during an entrance.
Look at, let's, like, half the fucking list is unusable.
And then you run into the problem of, you see the ones with the,
these on the Xs here? See the lower left? I literally have to take off my mask to put
this jacket on. Oh, you want to put this shirt on? No, no, no, no. You have to take off the mask.
I don't, I don't understand why. More than half the options are not usable together.
And that's been happening since 2K14. It seems like 2K, whatever,
Yuke's and Visual Concepts, they're so concerned. They are so fucking concerned
about clipping that they make it so you can't customize the character.
Like, they're so scared that if I put this on, it's going to clip through the mask.
Who gives a shit? It limits so many of the, like, I'm like, oh, this is a cool,
look at this jacket, the puffy blue jacket, this exact thing.
Nope, can't use it, sorry. Move on. I can use this one, though.
It's the same reason why you can't put on, like, look at this.
Like, see, like, uh, like, torso accessories or something.
See, look, like, why can't I put this on? I can't put this on.
But I can put these on. Why? Is this, what?
I could put a fucking rubber ducky on for an entrance, but I can't put on a scarf.
I have to take off the mask. Put it on.
You see? See how dumb this is? Go back, go back.
Well, I, see, now, now, if I make that mistake, I have to put everything back on.
See? I have to go all the way back.
Neck accessories. What do we got for neck accessories in WWE?
Oh, oh, I can put headphones. No, you can't, no, you can't do that.
Oh, what about, no, sorry, you can't do that either.
Oh, um, oh, and all of these I can't use unless I'm on an entrance.
I can't, no, I can't put that on.
Visual concepts and yukes. If you're watching this right now,
nobody gives a shit if it's going to clip through the fucking back of the mask.
Nobody cares. Put it back.
Let us fucking put the shit on that we want to put on.
For the love of God.
Like, nobody gives a shit if this is going to, like, clip through my head or if this,
like, I can only put this on an entrance.
No, I don't care. I can't just have this on in the match. Why?
It just doesn't make any sense.
But anyways, use the neck feathers.
Like, why can I use this but not, like, the headphones?
It doesn't make any sense.
Golden duck? You're not even going to get to see it.
The duck is only, I can't even put it on.
Oh, sorry, you can't use this.
Let's limit 45% of every item in the whole game.
You know, I do consulting work.
2K. I do consulting work.
Need a consultant.
Gold neck. All right.
Still glowing. That's fine.
Well, if we're going that far, we might as well do this.
Sands. I don't even care about sands.
Stop this right now.
What am I doing?
I'm just, like, adding.
I'm adding and adding and adding and adding.
No, I don't like these.
I don't like them. Get rid of them.
All right. Stats.
It's like a fucking cartoon character.
Put his name on his chest.
Super green screen, right?
There you go.
Take it off.
No, it's a blue screen of death.
Ruined.
What? What do you mean ruined?
It's nasty. Remove it.
I'm going to keep it.
Disgusting.
No, it's staying there.
Give him a gold thong.
I mean, I kind of have to.
And I can't.
I can't do that.
Would you like me to do that?
Oh, look at all these options.
Look at all. Wow.
Look at these options.
Oh, wow.
Oh, I sure wish I could put them on.
No, look at the hundreds of fucking options.
No, no, no, no.
I can't. Sorry.
You can't do that.
Sorry. He gets underneath.
You can't put it over.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, sir.
Did you want to create a custom character?
No. Get a JPG of a thong.
Give me a second.
Uploading it now.
I'm not fucking around.
Are you still?
Okay. Uploading now.
It's a thong.
It's done. Done.
Done. Let's go get it.
Hold on.
Upload an actual blue screen.
Wait, let me just save.
Super fucking.
No, I got to change his name.
Stats.
No, no, I'll do the stats.
Just wait a second.
I got to go download this image.
I'm putting a fucking gold thong on him.
Why the thong?
Somebody told me to do it.
If you're new to the stream,
just listen.
This is important.
If you're a new viewer
or if you're an old viewer,
you're not sure.
If one person, one guy,
one person said to do that,
okay, you will eventually be the one guy
that I take the request.
You'll be the one guy at some point.
You can't give shit to the one guy
when you'll be the one guy
at some point soon.
Let me download my community fucking thing.
It's not even, it's pink.
Well, that kind of fucks
that whole thing up, doesn't it?
Super blue screen of death.
I can't even change the color.
That person's right.
That one guy's right.
I'm not making super Willow.
No, hold on.
Just wait.
It's only the front.
Just hold on.
I can't even.
Yes, I can.
I can change the color.
No, I can't.
Oh my god.
At least I can make it match.
It's like riding up his ass so bad.
What the fuck did this achieve?
This didn't achieve anything.
I don't, I don't.
No, what am I doing?
I'm thinking like an arrow.
Get this out of here.
Delete this.
What am I, what are you doing?
No, no, no, no.
Get out.
Okay, we're fine.
Oh, fuck.
Juicy's gone.
What the fuck was I doing?
Arrow to like my crotch.
All right, we're good.
It just went off the rails real quick.
Really quickly.
All right.
Now I can do the stats.
I gotta make sure the stats are 100.
Remember the fight?
Yeah, I do.
So many fucking people.
Where are you?
Okay.
Super PSOD from Las Vegas.
It's true.
All right, let's go.
Wasn't this supposed to only be like a two to three hour stream?
Yeah, this is the encore.
I mean, the event already happened.
The green screen won twice.
So we're just kind of having fun sticking around now.
All right.
Actually 100.
All level three skills.
And here is the final match of this particular circuit.
We spent so much time on these two idiots.
Menu pose.
Pretty good.
Done.
He's doing a Jojo pose.
No, he's not.
Thank you for the thong.
You're welcome.
One guy out of 7,000 people.
What have I done to him?
I made him that much more powerful.
All right, let's go.
While this loads, I'm going to go grab another drink.
Because why not, right?
One on one, Hell in a Cell.
Super Jax versus super blue screen of death.
There are no rules in Hell in a Cell.
All right.
For the entrances, here they come.
I'm going to grab a drink.
I'm not sure these two even have entrances.
I'll be right back.
See you in a second.
Watch the intros.
I can't, why can I not turn my stream?
It doesn't want to, hold on.
It really, it's going to be so much brighter than this.
Because that's not even a rendered light source.
I still can't do it.
What the fuck not?
Apparently I can't mute my microphone, so whatever.
We're in Illinois.
See you in a second.
It's going to be the same two entrances back to back,
because I never gave them that.
It started.
It started already, what?
Oh my god, what did I miss?
What did I miss?
Nothing, it just, okay, just started, good.
So if you don't know the Hell in a Cell rules,
the only way you can win is by pinning.
You just have to pin the guy.
That's it.
But, but, super juicy, by the way.
We've got the two strongest competitors
that have ever been in a German Rumble, ever.
We've got the super blue screen of death and super Jax.
Mere mortals are in attendance right now.
What about Zaraxos?
Well Zaraxos is the most powerful in the underworld.
We're talking about on Earth.
I wonder if, I'm going to go for a pin here,
super Jax on blue screen of death.
No, not even a one count.
This is going to be like a four hour long match.
We're just watching gods fight each other.
That fucking thong.
Zaraxos is not even in their league.
He's a commoner.
I, I mean, he doesn't glow, so there's that.
I wonder if we're going to see any,
all right, now we're going to the outside here.
Are we going to get to see some Hell in a Cell mayhem?
They're locked in here until somebody wins.
Reversal there by super blue screen of death.
Onto the corner, falls over the steps.
Play music.
Hold on.
Oh, you can, ah, this is a spoiler right here.
You can like see their stats.
Fighting music.
This is, this is called best fight music.
So here's best fight music.
Oh, people are going to hate this.
Let's get the stream copyright striked.
What do you say?
Oh, what a reversal by blue screen of death.
No, that better not be it.
One, two of Jax is bleeding from the face.
The signature choke move from blue screen of death.
They've both evolved since the beginning of this stream.
Can super Jax make it a two for two?
That's the fucking move.
Pass down the Elberton line.
Nobody can stop super Jax.
Not even God himself.
Here it comes.
The diaper on the top rope.
This is live by the way.
Look at the top right corner.
It's live.
Hurricane Rana.
No, no.
Reversal and a spear.
Can he get the pin?
What a pathetic way to end.
Does Jax have it in him?
Can Jax possibly recover here?
I don't think it's possible.
Reversal.
Oh, there's nothing that can be done.
Jax is going to lose.
He's going to the top rope to crash the computer.
Wait a minute.
Can he?
No, he can't.
He can't.
But wait, he dodged it.
No, they both suck.
Gods among men.
Out to the outside again.
Do a spirit bomb.
Do anything.
Climb on top of the cage and fucking kill somebody.
Power bomb him from the top of the cage and kill him.
Backwards.
Oh, there it is.
The backwards move.
Is that going to be enough?
One.
Two.
No.
Let's go.
That's a power bomb pin.
Two.
Three.
No, that's not it.
That's not it.
Wait, what is he?
What?
Nice recovery.
He's running away.
What are you doing?
Check him.
What is happening?
So loud.
So he just pinned him again?
One.
Two.
He didn't get.
That's too much for me.
Crash it.
Oh, two.
And a backspinning soccer ball kick.
Can he go all the way here?
All he needed was the default YouTuber elevator music.
Was that going to be enough?
One.
Two.
Three.
He just did it.
He did.
That was lame.
That's...
They didn't even go on the top of the cell.
That was fucking stupid.
I don't even want to see this.
Ape man.
Ape man fucking ladder match.
No.
Ape man battle royale.
Ape man ladder?
That's not going to work.
Ladder tag?
Four-way?
Ladder...
Four-way tag?
What is it I tell him?
Turn entrances off.
Battle royale.
Can I change the rules?
Oh, let me see here.
Ladder.
What if I don't do ape man?
It's a rumble.
How do I...
Really rumble tournament.
Let me see here.
Extreme iron man last man's mission custom match.
Oh, fuck it.
Let's put like the shittiest characters in an ape man fucking ladder match.
Who gives a shit?
This is gonna be impossible.
Who are the worst characters in the whole thing?
Dr. Donna?
Dr. Dan?
And put super jacks in it.
All right.
Adam Sandler.
Adam Sandler sands the hornet 95.
Hold on you.
I can let Otto out here in a second.
No, I've refused to put quiet man in here.
He sucks.
Let's put fireman's...
I just want to put fireman in a match because I believe he's in 99.
I believe he deserves it.
The hornet's...
What?
Oh, he's already there.
No, pinwheel sucks.
Super blue screen of death.
Come on, let's go.
And this will probably be the last one of the night.
This is...
I'm going against the grain here.
Usually I do the event and then that's it.
But I've been having a lot of fun.
All right.
So let's put the car valet in there.
Deserves to be there.
Let's get rid of the paybacks though because they're not fair.
Wall dad put in super jex.
That's going to be so...
They're going to win.
Super jex is going to win.
All right.
We'll put wall dad in.
Blue man.
All right.
Blue man deserves to be there.
You're right.
And last one.
Otto.
Now Willem Dafoe.
I agree.
All right.
Sand low hornet, sands, fireman, wall dad, Willem Dafoe, car valet,
blue man in an eight man ladder match.
Before it was six man.
And I thought that was too much.
So entrance is off.
They all like...
Look, I didn't make entrances for people that weren't going to be in the like actual card.
Let's go.
Place your bets.
And who's going to win the eight fucking man ladder match?
I'm saying like a bunch of fucking dumb asses.
All right.
Good luck.
Good luck to who?
Wow.
What a joke.
This is an absolute joke.
Nothing's going to get done.
There's too many people.
There's two ladders.
What a reversal by Willem Dafoe.
Car valet is already outside.
Adam Sandler in the car valet.
All right.
What time is it?
It's 8.09 Pacific.
I bet you this takes 30 minutes.
Hope to God you guys like watching this because this is going to take an hour.
Duel.
Hornet and wall dad outside there.
It's interesting because there's a pair for everything.
Two, four, six, eight.
It's one of the pairs.
Wall dad and wall hornet are fighting.
Which is weird.
Kind of strange.
Blue man and Willem Dafoe.
Wall dad is really trying to get rid of those hornets.
Sandler in car valet.
Is this louder than it typically is?
Why is it so loud?
Sand's in fire, man.
It's weird.
The two fucking weird characters are fighting.
The two human characters are fighting.
And the two comic book characters are fighting.
You saw me do it.
I didn't fucking do it.
Wall dad, wall hornet.
Two normal guys.
Car valet, Adam Sandler.
Comic book characters.
Blue man, Willem Dafoe.
And the two weirdos, fireman and sand.
I didn't do that.
It just did it itself.
Wall dad is like, I'm doing this.
I'm doing this for my son.
Fucking minecon.
Big clothesline there from Willem Dafoe on the car valet.
Great commentary.
Yes, minecon.
What's with the ring?
Holy shit.
Wall dad just absolutely annihilated the hornet.
Just punched him in the face so hard that he fell into the ladder.
Blue man now getting a couple of shots on fireman
who has rolled onto the outside.
Wall dad with a wall knee.
Blue man is going up.
He wants to win at least one competition, right?
Blue man has to win a fucking competition.
He's been around for like six years.
Can he please win something?
No, apparently not.
Willem Dafoe puts a quick work of blue man
while the two human characters are still fighting.
Sandler and car valet are still fighting each other.
Adam Sandler is kicking his ass somehow.
Why is fireman just sitting there?
Fireman does not understand what to do.
I mean he does have like four brain cells
so you really can't put that on him.
He probably could have won the match right there
but he decided he decided he's not gonna do it.
He'd rather throw blue man out and go after him
rather than win the match.
He could have just won.
And now the hornet's going up there to try to win the game.
Adam Sandler now is the only person in the ring that has any eyeballs
and he's not doing anything.
He's gonna go up the other side of the fucking ladder
stops the hornet potentially.
Adam Sandler now has an opportunity
but wall dad coming in to take a fucking wall down.
Oh he's not strong enough.
He's not strong enough.
Come on with all your dad strength.
Take the fucking wall down.
There it is.
He's from house flipper.
He's fucking strong.
Oh my god.
He did it.
Wall dad saves the day.
This is never gonna get done.
Big.
No I thought it was gonna be a powerbomb.
Willem Dafoe on the ground.
Now Sands going after Willem Dafoe on the back with the ladder
and now on the stomach.
Hornet is taking a break
while blue man has like three dead bodies in front of him.
Adam Sandler is unconscious sitting up.
No he seems to be coming too.
Sands under tail or should I say Deltarune
going up to the top of the fucking top rope
to get the briefcase.
Willem Dafoe is the only one that can see.
Wall dad get the fuck out of here.
I'm the only one that stops this.
No he doesn't care.
Willem Dafoe.
No.
Come on wall dad.
Take it to the wall down.
Wall dad again showing his brute house flipper strength.
Wall dad receiving a lot of punishment
for his saving the match.
Car valet.
Is that a car?
Declare.
He's going up to the top to get the briefcase.
Can Car valet end this right now
and cause a conniption?
No.
Hornet's going up top.
The conniption is over.
Is it though?
This is just a brutal multiple punches in the face.
Car valet is stopping this.
Somebody got really hurt and I don't know who it was.
Wall dad.
He's like yeah I did it I fucking knocked it down
right into the Sands power bump.
You can never set up a you can't set up a ladder
in front of wall dad.
He'll take it down and put a bathtub in the other room.
Adam Sandler is dead.
Uh oh.
Sands undertale gonna unimpeded go up top here.
Wall dad with the strength.
Trying glue man now getting up here.
Hornet getting up here.
Can they stop it?
Big punches.
Jumping punch.
He decides to put hornet in a headlock.
Wall dad is going hard again.
He can't do it.
Sands is gonna get the briefcase.
Somehow Adam Sandler and wall dad.
No he didn't get it.
He's up.
No.
Carvalli goes underneath his legs.
Oh nobody wins.
Hornet's on the top ropes.
What a stinger.
Let's call the stinger Willem Dafoe pointing to the crowd
to try to get some.
I can't even fucking talk.
Don't tell Harry.
Fireman going up to the top.
Is fireman gonna get the briefcase?
Can he do it unimpeded?
Willem Dafoe.
Hornet is coming up here.
Possibly to get it to stop.
Willem Dafoe no.
Pulling a wall dad.
Trying to get it to stop fireman holding on with his flames.
He lets go gets thrown up by the hornet.
Hornet is now it's their opportunity to try to get the briefcase.
Somebody call wall dad.
Hornet's gonna get it.
Nobody's Sands is standing there scratching his head.
The hornet is the winner.
Why is it showing us this?
Oh you kicked him who fucking cares.
You kicked him in the back of the leg.
Another chokeslam from Adam Sandler.
We don't even get to see it.
One more.
All right we'll do another one.
How many can you do in a backstage brawl?
Can I do more than five?
Fatal four way.
False count anywhere.
Triple threat.
Two on three.
One on two.
One on three.
Do another Helen.
I wish they would go up top for the Helen as well.
One on three versus super Jax.
All right fine.
One on three tag.
All right here's super Jax versus BF Bugleberry.
He's gonna he's a hundred.
I can't do that.
Versus the Sims.
Get wall dad back in there.
Sandler.
All the different germas.
All right how about wall dad.
Germa raptor.
And no.
Odd Michael.
Fuck odd Michael.
And Lou.
That sounds like a pretty good fight.
No Adam Sandler's been a part of like three of the last five matches.
All right let's do it.
Match options.
All right uh referee.
Whatever who cares.
We want Adam Sandler.
What a bunch of bums.
Lou is a hundred.
As he should be.
Oh it's actually a tag match.
Wall dad is in there first so it's not tornado tag.
Snickers.
Oh yeah that's like Snickers logos in the game.
Go with the elbow drop there for wall dad.
He's got that knee brace on.
He's got a bad knee.
Please beat him right now.
Wall dad.
Oh well.
Super Jax versus Snickers.
I'm not making.
That's it.
Game's over.
Wall dad somehow is destroying Jax.
No super Jax with the overhead throw there.
Super wall versus super Jax.
That's right.
Dragging him to the middle of the ring.
Super Jax is gonna grab his arm.
What's he doing here?
Oh of course the secret fucking technique.
Doesn't matter how strong you are that always works.
He's got wall dad in a submission here.
Hopefully get a tag in.
Otherwise wall dad looks like he could be.
No what a knee to the face of super Jax.
Two infinity gauntlets is not enough.
For a minecon 2013 gift bag with two stickers.
And a diamond pickaxe plastic toy.
It's not enough.
He's got dad instinct.
Nice.
What a just charging dash.
And here comes German Raptor.
The worst person you could have tagged in.
You should have tagged in Luke.
German Raptor now is going to get instantly power bombed.
Okay.
Good work.
Shittiest thing ever.
He's just beating the shit out of his head.
He's already done.
He's dead.
Game over.
Come on.
Do like a Raptor move.
Fuck you super Jax.
You get two infinity gauntlets.
I get a mask from Walmart.
This is embarrassing again.
Get Lou Elbertson in there.
He at least has a chance.
German Raptor is about to go extinct.
Just stepping on his head.
Going to the top rope.
Somebody get in there please.
Oh he missed with a stomp.
This is German Raptor's chance.
Into the corner.
Tag him in.
Let's get a double team here.
There we go.
Beautiful.
Walledad German Raptor with a double swinging slacks.
Whatever that means.
Teamwork.
Walledad now going to the corner.
Super Jax now.
Why would you tag it?
Walledad is so tired.
Oh dear.
That's not good.
We got a one.
We've got only one.
Only one.
Trying to.
You got nobody to tag in Walled.
German.
What the fuck is this?
Oh no.
He just put his legs in the air and put them up and down.
Some super Jax.
Throw him outside.
Let's get Lou in here.
Walledad going to Lou maybe.
No.
Tagging back in German Raptor.
What is this?
German Raptor didn't do anything.
He pretended like he helped.
All he did was jump up the ropes.
That's it.
And look what happened.
Oh yeah.
Nice, nice.
Good work German Raptor.
Watch out for the riff.
Super Jax is going up top.
Going for another somersault pin here.
One.
That's all they're going to get.
Are we going to get even get to see Lou in this whole match?
He's 100.
He has 100 stats and he's just sitting out there hanging up.
That's right Lou.
Uncle Lou.
T-pose.
German Raptor has Jax in the corner.
You could have guessed that was going to happen.
Big crashing downward spiral into the mat there.
German Raptor is in a lot of trouble in the corner.
Super Jax is on the top rope again.
The same flipping scoop powerbomb thing.
And Walledad can't handle it.
Walledad saying this is bullshit.
He's got 100 stats.
It's not fair.
Walledad coming out of the walls.
Behind the wall you could say.
Look at this dad instinct.
Saved the day.
Now Jerma Jax.
Super Jax is going for the next snap.
Will he get it?
No he will not.
It's powering up here.
The two infinity gauntlets.
He's got the mind stone and the power stone.
He can control all of reality.
And that's all it took was one, two punches.
And a badly to back suplex on his neck.
The people reaching out desperately to get a tag from German Raptor.
They know he's the shittiest character in this entire rumble.
No German Raptor.
No.
Nobody cares.
It's not cool.
Tag out.
You have to tag out now.
Before you keep embarrassing yourself.
Tag Lu in.
Tag out.
No.
You stop proving yourself.
This is the worst joke you've ever made.
Stop trying to prove it.
It's worth doing.
See look what happened.
He's like no I can make it funny.
I'll go.
No it's not funny.
It's not gonna happen.
It's not gonna be funny.
Jerma gets out of the top row.
What a reversal there by Jerma Raptor.
All the shit we just talked.
Oh boy he got hit right in the skull.
You don't stand a chance against Super Jax.
Use your teammates.
Use your friends and your family members.
There's one right next to you with a hundred stats.
Stop staring at him.
He scoops him up.
How can he pick him up?
He's like a thousand pounds.
Holy shit.
He's got a lot to prove.
Drag him to the middle of the ring.
And he's going for the pin.
Can we get a one two.
Oh a two count.
Oh unbelievable.
I can't believe he got out of that one.
Jerma Raptor had a chance there.
A small chance.
Oh what a lariat with a leg.
A leg lariat as you would say.
By Super Jax.
There it is.
The spindy doodle.
I've said that word like 30 times already.
It's not tagging.
Wall dad's coming in.
Lou is essentially a manager right now.
And then Super Jax is like fuck this.
I'll see you next time or the next episode.
And it's the next episode.
It's the next episode.
And there it is.
He got him in the back.
Backwards elbow by wall dad.
Scoops him up with a choke slam.
Could that be it?
That's one.
That's two.
Can he get the third one?
He got the third one.
Can wall dad close this one out?
Can it be the end of the situation here for Super Jax?
Can we get to the end of the season already?
Into the corner he goes.
Wall dad.
And he gets a pin.
And a power bump.
Wall dad.
He's got him in the.
Sacrific.
There it is.
The sacrificial wall.
I can't believe he just did it.
That's called the wall knockdown.
The sacrificial wall knockdown.
Here comes a pin.
One.
Oh, only one.
I wonder why.
I wonder why that happened.
Maybe if you pinned him after doing the move.
It might not have happened.
As wall dad goes into the corner.
We've got us.
Oh, he did the diaper.
That's a super diaper.
Super Jax for the super diaper on his super fucking face.
Right hand.
Got him on the neck.
Spinning back.
Backward suplex.
Into the diaper.
He has multiple diaper moves.
That's diaper two he calls it.
2.0.
Whoa!
Uh oh, he's got him in the bad boy.
He's like, you're a bad boy.
Is this gonna be it?
Can he end it?
With the bad boy?
No, he's not.
He's gonna get power bombed.
One.
Two.
Oh, Lou made an attempt.
Somebody just wrote, I'm unfollowing.
Nice.
Wall dad catches the leg.
Can he get him?
With the backwards neck breaking.
He's getting energy from twitch chat.
Wall dad should have been the guy who picked up two lariat.
Three.
That's gonna be it.
He calls everyone the sledgehammer.
He's gonna do it again?
No, that's 640 pounds.
You gotta be a goddamn titan to be able to pick that up.
Lou is watching ever so patiently as supergex.
Here comes germa raptor.
What the hell are they doing?
He's helping him getting on his shoulders.
Germa raptor is going for the raptor lunge.
That's gonna be it.
Teamwork!
Can they put an end to supergex once and for all as three?
I mean two.
Because Lou hasn't done anything.
He's stood there the whole time.
No, he's gonna get power bombed again.
Hey, how about this one?
Remember that?
Hey, get out of here.
I'm Lou.
I'll do something once.
Watch my looks.
Isn't that a cool kick?
Going to the top rope is supergex slowly though.
What's the move here?
Oh dear.
This is...
That's it.
That has to be the end.
That's 20,000 pounds on his chest.
He doesn't have a chest anymore.
Wall dad coming in.
Catching his dad instinct.
Stay with my son.
How dare you?
Oh shit.
My like four-year-old almost fell down off a cliff.
I got him though in that Reddit video.
I caught him.
I got a wall dad instinct.
What the fuck?
Oh, it's okay.
I'll go back to Reddit.
Turbo raptor with a toss.
And he's getting ready.
He's getting ready for his signature move.
Oh, there it was.
I didn't have time to tell you what it was.
Into the corner, Jex goes.
Who is he going to tag in?
Oh, I wonder.
Is it going to be...
A suplex.
Pulling him into the center of the ring.
One.
Two.
That's too bad.
Germa raptor going for a pin.
Didn't get it though.
Into the corner again.
Here comes Lou Albertson to stop this and end the fucking match.
Well, they bumped into each other.
They're going for it again.
He loves his uncle.
It's his favorite uncle.
Lou Albertson coming in.
Let's see if he can...
He's doing the arm pull.
He used to work in a meat factory.
He knows how to pull chicken.
Up to the top rope.
He's finally got his pounding his chest.
That's right.
Oh, he got reversed by super Jex.
He makes a great pulled chicken.
He brings it to fucking Thanksgiving every year.
We don't do turkey.
We do chicken.
We do fucking Boston market chicken.
We go to the Boston market and we get chicken.
Corner to corner, Lou Albertson.
That's two.
Can he go for a third?
Into the third corner.
Go after him?
Do I fight him?
Do I fight the guy in the corner?
He'll get him.
I don't know.
Should I?
Maybe?
I don't know.
He gets it!
Right hand!
Lou Albertson!
And that's called the Thanksgiving Turkey Chicken Dinner.
Didn't even get a chance.
Oh, he threw his hand into the ground.
Unbelievable.
Going for the neck break.
Can somebody finally get the neck break to end a match?
Nope.
Go for it again.
No, he gets reversed in a clothesline by super Jex on Lou Albertson.
Albertson trying to take his head clean off of his shoulders.
Did not seem to work in this scenario.
Now we've got...
Oh, he's dragging him around like fucking dirty underwear on the ground.
He's kind of by the neck.
That's a very bad position to be in.
Is he going to break Lou's neck?
No!
Lou reversed it!
Somehow!
Ooh!
Took a slap into his face!
Oh, my face!
He's got a backwards suplex into the diaper!
The dupe diaper 2.0!
Why would you...
All right.
One!
Not even a one count on Lou Albertson.
Why is every move the diaper?
That's the diaper 2.0.
The diaper 1 is the double...
The feet jump into the ground.
He jumps in the air and kicks you.
Diaper 1, diaper 2.
Just taunting Lou Albertson here.
As Lou, it does not look good.
He's got great stats, but he can't go up against the Infinity Gauntlet.
He throws him outside.
He doesn't give a fuck.
He's going to win?
No, he's going to wait.
Is he going to go up top?
He's like, I like this one better.
He's up top.
Is Jermaraptor going to cause a problem here for him?
No, I would go like this one.
No, no.
I think I'm going to do this one.
Let me try this one.
No.
Top left part is better.
No, I think I'll just go out there.
My brain is fucking adult Swiss cheese.
And there he goes.
Lou Albertson goes down.
Now we got two count.
20 count means the end of the match.
Nice reversal into the balls.
Will it be enough to stop Super Jex?
I don't think so.
He's going to throw him into the crowd.
No, just into the banister here.
Five seconds have elapsed.
Right hand, left hand, right hand.
This is bad.
This is really bad.
Oh, come on.
A count out is literally the worst thing you could ever do.
Why is the ref not counting?
That was the longest eight seconds I've ever seen
in the history of the German arena.
And there goes Jerm-
Jermat Jex is in the ring.
Oh, make sure you show Lou clapping though.
That's great.
He doesn't need to be maxed.
He doesn't need that.
There's a wall dad, and here's a wall chat.
2.0.
What's the difference?
You have a glowing hat.
You can't beat Minecon 2013.
TLC match.
Wall chat 2.0 versus Jerm-
It's Super Jex.
Wall dad.
The only thing that needs to glow is his helmet.
Look, you can't even fucking do anything versus Minecon.
Remember when they announced sheep?
They're like wolves.
He was there for that.
He stood in line.
Hey, my son's like a real big fan of your YouTube channel.
Do you mind if I take a picture with you?
He was there for that.
Don't you understand?
Let's get some tables in here.
Do a mega version rumble.
That would take so long.
Hey, I mean, like, I know.
Hey, I just want to say that, you know,
little Jason is like such a huge fan of your channel.
He really loved when you played the Hunger Games.
Do you mind if I get like a picture with you?
Which is, well, him, not me.
Thanks, man.
Minecraft Hunger Games.
I'm not going to play Minecraft music.
This is probably the last match of the night.
Fucking my, no, what the hell just happened?
That was the equivalent of two planets colliding
and now they're outside under the tables.
The commentators are getting up.
We got a table from Super Jex,
but wall Chad 2.0 is going to stop that from happening.
They're bigger than the tables.
Uh-oh, where is Super Jex going?
Possibly to the ladder, it seems.
Yep, you got to get that.
You got to get the money up top.
You got to get your free two tickets to Minecon.
And wall dad is getting a table.
There is the ladder set up.
Nice dodge by Super Jex.
Wall Chad can't seem to get it right into the table.
Now that is devastating.
Super Jex is going to the outside for some reason.
I'm not sure why.
Yeah, wall dad brought out his own wall
and wall dad is going and getting the briefcase.
Super Jex is an observer
and he's fiddling with the hook there
and trying to get it.
It's a tough hook.
I almost got it.
No, he kind of fucked it up there.
He's going to try it again.
It's a tough lock.
Might take four, two sets of hands there.
No, he's got it.
Here it is.
Yeah, this is for my son.
Yeah, I can't believe it.
This is signed by all the YouTubers.
That's it.
I don't know what the hell that was
but we haven't done that before.
That was fun.
Well, the first like two hour and a half of the stream
was like the real shit
and then the last like three hours was bullshit.
But it was fun.
Thank you so much everybody for coming.
There were a lot.
I there was so many people here tonight.
I can't even believe it.
There's almost 10,000 people at the stream concurrently.
That's fucking out of control.
So thank you for participating.
Thanks for being part of the community
because a lot of these random characters are, you know,
at least half of them, more than half of them
because we thought they were fun and funny.
You know what I mean?
So thank you for participating everybody.
It's always a blast.
Good night.
Take care of yourself.
I will see you guys on Tuesday.
I'm going to take tomorrow off
because I really the last four days straight
I've kind of been making characters.
So I'm going to take tomorrow off.
I'll see you on Tuesday.
We'll probably, you know, I have no idea
what the fuck we're going to do on Tuesday.
That's a good question.
But if you're new, thanks for dropping by.
If not, then hey, good to see you again.
We're probably going to have fucked up credits
because of the I had stream labs turned off
just for the sake of because I wanted to know
I have no notifications on the stream.
So this might be difficult to do this.
Let's see.
I think it's still here.
Is it though?
Try Soul Calibur.
You know, I've heard here's the thing about Soul Calibur.
It's got a really great character creator
but I would get to the game, the actual
we'd make like five characters in Soul Calibur
and then I'd get to the video game and go,
I don't know about this.
But see you guys on Tuesday if you're taking off.
Thanks for sticking around.
Let me see if I can pull up the at least the bits.
Let's see.
Soul Calibur is great.
It's for PC, right?
Soul Calibur is PC.
But we do this once like every eight or nine months
once there's enough characters or new ideas
to put into a rumble.
So thank you so much everybody for sticking around.
I don't have any of the subs I don't think.
Let's see.
I'll run the credits either way.
Because I didn't have streamlabs going but it's okay.
No, actually, how the fuck did I delete it?
What the hell am I doing?
But people gave so much money tonight.
There was at least $50 from Nay.
From Nay means Nay.
Thanks for $50.
Stream is the best birthday present ever.
Thank you so much.
$10 from Riggle Rat.
They say Jax God.
$10 from Elizabeth.
I love you stuff so much.
Please take these bits.
Thank you.
OBS.
Make sure you get OBS Studio.
Thank you guys.
OBS Hijack.
On Tuesday we'll be live again.
Peaked at 9,000 viewers this stream.
Holy shit.
Are you kidding me?
I saw like eight.
God damn.
Thank you everybody.
Hope you had fun.
9,085.
Really?
Are you serious?
9,085.
Jesus Christ.
Well, if you that's a lot of new people.
If you're new, we'll hopefully see you again.
We try to do fun stuff like this on like a monthly basis.
So top WWE streamer.
But I think I'm going to end it here.
I've got to go take care of Otto.
He ran downstairs and I got to go let him out and feed him and shit.
I got to go.
You guys are fucking incredible.
Thank you everybody for subscribing, for giving money.
Thank you so much.
And I'll see you next weekend.
There's even more.
We're not fucking stopping.
The brakes don't we don't fucking hit the brakes anymore.
Next weekend is the movie night for the green screen.
That's going to be a fucking ton of fun.
I've seen some of the shit you guys have made so far and it's hilarious.
So that's next weekend.
Every fucking weekend we're doing something new.
Again, if you don't know, in the discord there is a channel called movie night.
There's a pinned message.
The video has to be uploaded to YouTube.
You can't just put it on like Reddit or something.
It's got to be a YouTube video, going to go to YouTube playlist.
It has to be there by next Thursday, 29th, Thursday or Friday.
Join the discord.
A lot of great people there.
And that's where I'm going to end it.
So I have my stream.
Unfortunately, I'm sorry.
I can't do the subs tonight and I got to go take care of the dog.
So all your subscriptions, all the money you guys gave the stream is fucking incredibly appreciated.
I can't believe people paid money to this stream,
but that's why I want to do stuff that's fun or at least I try.
If I, if I'm having fun, I hope you guys are too.
Cheers.
Much love to you.
See you guys on Tuesday.
Take care of yourselves.
Ta-ta for now.