I feel like I'm in a Disney movie, where the main character comes into class, and he's late by one second, and he gets detention.
Okay, let's see what I'm talking about. He's got like books in his hands. He's like, oh no, my first day!
Sprinting down. Which one? 102? Where's 102 math? Oh shoot!
Before he drops a book on the ground, he gets in. He doesn't sit down.
Mr. Albertson, you're late.
Oh man.
And we don't take kindly to late students.
And I get, they get detention. Is that what's happening right now?
It's a JoJo reference?
That happens in Jo... Guys, everything happens in a TV show.
You know, just, if you have any idea how many TV shows exist, think of every second of television.
I'm sure what I'm saying has happened in a hundred different series.
Yeah, that was a fucking JoJo reference.
No, it's a human reference. Because people are late.
And then if people make references to human behavior in their TV shows.
I'm never watching it now.
Wait, is that? Oh, that's a meme. Okay. Sorry. Hold on.
I'll be right back. See, I gotta tweet this. Be right back.
All right. So tonight we're gonna do obviously community content night.
Make sure I don't hear myself in my own microphone. Good thing I don't.
Let's make sure I don't hear this either.
We gotta have a good OST. What's a good OST?
Gonna be ready for more JoJo tonight?
I have something to tell you. Those of you waiting for JoJo's Bizarre Adventure Video Files.
I don't think there's any. I think there might be one reference to it.
I don't think there's any. This is up till March 1st, by the way.
So this is from late January all through February.
And we're gonna do another catch up here.
We're gonna do a second community content night.
Probably at some point a week or so from now.
And we're gonna try to catch up through March into April.
So then we'll be really actually caught up with community content night.
Boomer content night.
I didn't like where my mic was.
I changed it.
Anyways, yeah, we have a lot of submissions.
A lot of stuff to go through. Gonna hang out and play.
We have a bunch of subs. AmnesticOW.
Just gave 10 community subs. Thank you Amnestic.
And The Chef's Corner.
I feel like the last few nights, last three or four streams,
The Chef's Corner has opened us up with at least five to ten community subs.
So thank you. It's a lot.
Thanks both of you.
I missed the pre-stream chat. PepeHands, it's okay.
There'll be plenty more.
So tomorrow, after we do this,
tomorrow is gonna be public domain movie night.
And I have a few things to say about that.
So we're gonna start with The Gorilla.
The Gorilla is a public domain movie from 1939 about a killer gorilla.
Apparently the movie sucks total ass.
And it's only an hour long.
This full movie is one hour long.
So we're gonna be watching another one too.
I'm trying not to look too hard into this movie.
But I've heard that it's a horror comedy, if you could believe it.
And we're gonna open with it.
And we have to watch the whole thing. That's part of this.
We don't get to skip anything. We don't get to change anything.
We have to stay there and watch it for the hour.
Well, you don't have to, but I do.
Because it's my stream.
It's like, if you think it's stupid, you're like,
no, I'm fucking out of here. That's fine.
I have to watch the whole thing.
So we'll see.
But I'll have a second one queued up after that, which will be a mystery movie.
I was speaking of more subs.
Nondescript Civilian and Neftwitch.
Nondescript gave 10 community subs.
And Neftwitch gave five community subs.
30 community subs have come in in like the last 30 seconds.
Thanks, guys.
Vod viewers will skip.
The one time we're being a VOD viewer is like, whoa, you got an advantage here.
Telling you.
Play Yoshi's Island OST. Yeah, we gotta get a good OST.
Let's do an OST that we haven't done like a thousand times.
We keep doing Yoshi's Story and stuff.
Invader is another five community subs.
Thanks for another five.
It makes like 40 or 30 or 50.
I can't even keep track. There's just so many.
You guys give so much money to this stream.
It's fucking insane.
Mario Galaxy.
Mario Galaxy is too upbeat, I think.
Mario Galaxy is like...
That's too...
I don't want to be so energetic.
I need to be relaxed and hanging out.
Sonic Rush.
No, that's too much.
That's too...
That's a heavy guitar.
I don't want a heavy guitar.
Hollow Knight.
Now, that's...
That's interesting to me right now.
Hollow Knight OST.
Oh, let's check it out.
Okay.
Hey, Aiden, thanks for the five community subs.
It's like a little too fast, though.
Is there a slow part?
It's too upbeat for me.
I feel like I'm going to fight with somebody.
No, not too...
All right, let's start here.
All right, yeah.
Here we go.
That's the busted up one.
All right.
So, we're going to move on here.
To a...
This thing.
And move on to this thing.
There's no PC game on.
Let's move over here.
Hey, look at that.
I already got one.
Is this a JoJo reference?
Did I say no JoJo?
Is this a JoJo?
No, it's not.
This is not a JoJo reference.
Not everything is a...
That's too fast.
Not everything is a JoJo's reference.
Why am I saying JoJo's like it's a family restaurant?
Come on down to JoJo's.
Fried fish and a side of sweet potatoes.
Only $9.99.
All right, let's go.
Once I turn this on, I can't turn it off, right?
I hope I'm not naked.
Okay.
Once this is on, it can't turn off.
That's too...
That's too fast.
Oh, hold on.
It's got zits all over me.
It's been...
All right.
It's off.
I'm turning it off.
No, this is too fast.
Here we go.
How do you like better lighting?
Oh, the light's on.
Don't make fun of my hair.
It's like all fucked up.
I haven't had a haircut in like two months, three months.
I can't...
Somebody just give 20 subs.
Hold on.
Let me fix this fucking bad video.
Somebody just give 20 community subs right now.
Blast Master just gave 20 subs.
Thank you, Blast Master.
I know.
It's like...
It got like wispy hairs.
Usually the stylist like...
Yeah, and I had a little bit of a problem this morning with my finger.
I got it cut.
Yeah, look at that.
Look at this like big flap of hair.
It's all wrong.
I'm gonna do it like this.
I cut...
This is from a hummus container, by the way.
I slid my finger already to open the hummus container
and I just...
I slipped my finger open.
It was a disaster.
All right.
Let me...
Hold on.
Before we get started, I gotta fix this.
Like shit.
Give me that back.
Auto-focus is on too.
What the fuck is this bullshit?
How do people...
How does it...
White balance is wrong too.
It's fine.
Whatever.
Like I don't care.
When I turn to the side, you're gonna see.
Like this is what it's gonna be like.
So what the fuck do I care?
And I know it looks like somebody like...
Put like melted chocolate on my head.
But that's just the way it is.
And that's the way it's gonna be.
Somebody just gave a huge amount of money.
Somebody's just like just...
This is like a cake decoration here.
I get it.
I know.
You don't think I look in the mirror
and don't think I see like a decorated cake?
Anyways, we had a lot of money just come in.
We had...
How much did we just have come in?
10,000 bits just came in.
By West.
West 095 just gave a fucking hundred bucks.
And they don't...
This...
They don't...
There's nothing here.
It's just a hundred dollars.
It's a huge amount of fucking money.
Thank you, West.
Thank you.
Bad Nutrition 5 Community Subs as well.
You guys are just giving me money.
And anybody even here?
There's zero viewers right now.
And nobody even here.
How can I know reliably that people are actually even here?
Like how am I supposed to...
How am I supposed to determine with my...
What my analytics look like?
Lip cream hair.
All right.
Let's get started.
I'm going to shrink myself a little bit.
Nobody...
There's another hundred fucking dollars.
A hundred more dollars.
This is like five...
This is like four or five hundred dollars in 15 minutes.
Holy shit.
Okay.
That's...
Boz...
Bertlar.
Boz Bertlar gave a hundred dollars.
Greetings from Sweden.
Hello from the United States of America.
Specifically, the Las Vegas.
Now they say long time viewer, first time donator.
Oh, and also play Yakuza Zero.
I already did.
And I gave up on it because I have the attention span of a fucking eight-year-old.
But thanks for the huge amount of fucking money.
All right.
We got our first Joe Joe's Bizarre Adventure reference.
Hey, Tona.
Thanks for the 10 subs.
Yeah.
I'll just...
I'll just bring it at five hundred dollars.
Holy shit, guys.
You're out of your minds.
We got Glue Man and the Rat.
And of course, yeah, in the background.
This is very well done.
Not to say the last one wasn't well done.
But this one's very good.
But on clown music.
What do you mean clown music?
Oh, no, the Rat got confirmed for Smash.
Clown, clown, clown, clown.
I don't...
Clown...
I don't get it.
What is clown OST?
That doesn't make any sense.
Clown OST.
The first thing that comes up is the Joker movie.
There's no clown OST.
A clown doesn't have a CD that he puts in
when he goes and does balloon animals at your house.
By the way, I got to like...
I got to get a little close to this microphone
so you can hear me.
We got to change where the webcam is too.
All right, there we go.
All right, what's what?
Clown OST.
I don't get it.
I'm not putting on the Joker.
I haven't seen that movie.
Play clown music.
I don't even know what you taught.
What is that even supposed to mean?
Clown...
One hour of...
I'm not putting...
No, circus theme song for 10 hours.
It's even lined up, really.
I got to get out of the way
so you can see the whole picture.
Do it.
I don't want to just put on fucking clown music.
No, I'm not going to keep this on.
This is fucking stupid.
How about just like...
One hour of scary clown music.
One hour of creepy clown music.
45 minutes of classic circus music.
I think I've already played this.
Yeah, yeah, I've played this before.
Okay, I'm going to do this as long as I can possibly handle this.
But that's it.
But this is fantastic, though.
Nice work.
Ah, this is scary.
It's me.
Looks like I've got a knife in my hand.
I...
Why is it happening twice again?
Why is this happening?
I changed my thing.
That's...
Hello?
What the fuck?
Okay, hold on.
Here we go.
There we are.
Now we got some real clown music going.
I like the knife.
I like the knife work that you've got here.
We can't hear it.
Yes, you can.
What's going on up here?
Is this blood?
Oh, I...
Why?
How do I not...
This is the spy.
That's your eternal reward.
How do I not know this?
It was disguised.
Okay.
I don't know why.
I'm so fucking dumb.
I'm a fool.
I know.
Ah, this is somebody...
Somebody had a birthday or somebody had a...
All right.
Somebody had a...
There was a baby involved or something.
There was a baby reveal.
I don't know.
But this is...
That's a joke.
Wait, that's from the...
I don't...
I've never said I haven't seen the movie.
This is a joker of game?
It's a game.
This is a good image.
You got...
Hey, look.
Those of you that don't know,
I don't wear two headphones
because when I cover both my ears,
I don't know where I am.
And it fucks with my spatial awareness.
When I...
I say I can't hear myself talk right now.
And me not being able to hear myself talk right now
is being drowned out by like clown music.
So it's like when a vacuum cleaner is on
and you're talking,
I can't do it.
I have to be able to hear...
I have to be able to hear and sense the surroundings.
Otherwise, I lose my mind.
But no, this is pretty accurate.
Yo, that's the old hair too.
All right.
One in the chat,
if you want me to go back to short,
free Vegas hair.
Who in the chat if you want me to let this grow
and don't cut it for at least three years?
Eh, I've seen a lot of ones.
Or three is shave it off.
I can't listen to that song a fourth time.
I'm sorry.
We have to do something.
We have to put something else on.
Yoshi's.
What was it?
Yoshi's story.
We keep going.
We always go back to like Yoshi's Island.
To a pole.
No, no, no.
I'm not going to be like,
oh, should I cut my hair?
Should I dye it fucking orange
or should I cut it off?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm going to decide what I'm...
Cut my finger by the way today.
Of course you see that.
To a mohawk.
No.
Why did you ask?
I just...
I was just seeing what people thought.
I said, hey, one in chat if you think.
Two in chat if you think.
But what you...
It's what I think though.
Because it's my hair.
I was just curious to see how many people
would be angry with it.
Jerma doesn't think.
All right.
We're going to do Yoshi's.
Yoshi's story.
What's the one for Nintendo 64
where they sing like little kids?
They go...
Where is it?
It's horrendous.
Here it comes.
I remember playing this when I was younger.
When I was younger,
it wasn't that long ago but it was.
And it's this ear piercing like...
I'm telling you it's horrible.
Where is it?
No.
Not this one.
Where is it?
It's...
Then they say the end.
The end of...
Like it's the end of the story.
What's it called?
How come I can't find it?
Nintendo.
On the beach.
Love is in the air.
Tough guys don't cry.
What's that one?
It's the rat found in the sewer.
The small enemy spider.
That's supposed to be me?
Chad is a cutie.
Is that supposed to be you?
The garbage-filled baby arms
are because I drew on one layer unintentionally.
Didn't want to start over like a dum-dum.
What's wrong with it?
It's fine.
It looks good.
I think it looks good.
Trust no one, not even yourself.
This is just my regular clothes.
I wear like the same three superhero shirts
and then like a few...
A handful of Star Wars shirts.
Jax has a way better fashion sense as you can see.
He's got a Nightwing shirt on.
That's it.
Wow.
Also a superhero shirt.
Do I have any real clothes?
I do, but they just all...
Okay.
I have real clothes,
but they're all hung up on hangers
and I don't ever take them off the hangers
because it's way easier just to put a t-shirt on
than it is to like put a button-up shirt with like a tie on.
Prove it.
Prove that I have real clothes?
No, it has nothing to do with going to Reddit.
It has to do with...
I don't...
I like having...
It's comfy.
Do it.
Let's do a fashion show.
Hold that thought.
We got community fucking content tonight.
Although it's kind of still the day.
I'll prove it.
I will.
Life imitates art.
It sure does.
Jerma and Jax.
Pretty cool dudes here.
Is this it?
No.
I thought that was going to be it.
I was waiting for it.
Well, there's Jax and Jerma.
We're both not the same person.
We both have different...
We're both different people, I guess.
I skipped it already.
How is that even possible?
By the way, take this out.
I can't even...
I can't even hear myself talk.
I need no headphones.
You know, I know people that put both headphones in
and pump their audio through,
so they hear themselves talking.
I would throw up if I had to do that.
I would actually throw up.
Like, I would...
It would never work.
It would be impossible.
This looks like a sticker to me.
Looks very good.
The big thick outlines.
I like it.
I would love this on the back of a laptop.
Get your laptop.
I think it would look good.
It would look good.
Like a Redditor.
Not everything is...
You guys are on that recently.
I don't understand.
Not everything is based on a news aggregate website.
How come you guys aren't like...
Oh, wow.
That's a real CNN thing to do.
NBC streamer.
Nice NBC room.
I get my news from Reddit.
I read the headlines and see and go to articles on Reddit.
That's like calling me an NBC guy.
Or like a...
Wow, man.
That's what a real NBC thing to do, huh?
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to have a laptop with a sticker on it.
What are you, fucking CNN?
I just only go to Reddit for news.
That explains a lot.
No, it doesn't.
I don't even...
Guys, I don't even watch TV.
I don't even watch TV.
I don't watch television.
I don't listen to music.
I'm just a fucking weirdo.
I just sit in a room and stare at a wall.
I just go like this.
Wow, I make up my own TV shows.
I like my own characters.
And I let them do their own things in my head.
I just said that to everybody.
This is pretty scary.
You're a psycho?
No, it's called free entertainment.
I can't wait to the next episode of two alligators.
Because that's the thing I dreamed last night.
Two alligators.
Made that up.
I did.
Yeah.
Good call.
Good catch.
Two and a half alligators.
This is scary.
I like the background, though.
Looks good.
Big screaming mouth.
Look at this guy.
Yeah.
Why are people saying sour please?
What is it?
I don't want to miss out.
Why are we sour pleasing the language?
Sneaking around music.
That's what this is.
This is the evil guy.
It's sneaking around corners.
This is like the...
Hold on.
This is this music.
All righty?
Like I'm going to come in frame.
Where's the end?
985.
A story of a madman.
Now that was another good internet clown moment.
Thank you.
I'm not even...
These are all like jokes.
All right.
I can't hear myself breathe.
These are all like jokes.
I'm not a madman.
This is okay.
This is a character.
This is Odd Michael.
This is me crying and laughing at a fart compilation.
So that's me.
That's also me.
That's not even me.
That's Jex.
That's a TIE fighter guy.
That's a clown.
That's not even me.
And then this is a ninja turtle.
So sorry.
These are all...
These are characters.
What's that old saying?
I'm not a doctor, but I play one on TV.
This is...
These are characters of mine.
This is not me.
Socrates.
You're a character.
Post fart.
Thanks for the five subs.
Oh, so you're a scientist.
No, I'm not a scientist.
I love this.
This is great.
Getting defensive.
Not really.
He's really happy about something.
And I do appreciate the big ding on the teeth.
I like the ding.
Whatever.
I don't even know what the song is.
Here's some Dunky Donut because you're epic.
That really took off, too.
This Dunkin' Donuts thing.
Isn't this like a meme from somebody else?
This is like another meme, right?
This is like...
We've adapted.
We've taken over and adapted the meme.
Oh, I didn't, but this is a Reddit meme.
No, it's not.
It's not...
It's not mine.
Nothing.
None of this is mine.
This is all yours.
This is community content night.
I almost just burped because it was loud in the microphone.
Told you how I got this cut from a hummus.
When you eat a lot of hummus, it can boil back up.
It can be like gas because of all the hummus gas.
So I'm not a scientist.
I don't watch any news.
No, I do.
This is interesting because this person is Tony Hawk's underground.
And they've decided to use that.
This is the image that all of us have when our parents took the picture of us on our
first day of school in first grade.
In fact, I could probably ask my mother to send me the picture of this exact thing I'm
talking about.
Even the stance too.
The only thing is at a backpack.
With huge shoes.
They are.
They are fucking huge, aren't they?
Oh my god.
All right.
I wasn't going to include this, but I just did it anyways.
I was going to just remove this one, but it's just, it's stupid.
I just had to put it in.
Here is, uh, I believe that's fireman.
Clown shoes.
I don't, I know everything has to be clown related.
Why can everything not be clown related?
EOS.
What?
For a second, I thought it was going to be a dick and it was a clown.
I'm like, no, this is what you're talking about.
Are links still banned?
I think they are.
It's a clown reddit Jojo.
Anime villain goblin face.
This is from, uh, sins.
I know.
Saw this last time.
Fucking like this so much.
It's going to be my new profile picture.
Should this just be the profile, my profile picture?
I feel like that's not going to help me though.
Anywhere.
It would be the other one.
No.
Are my eyes close together?
They kind of are.
Yeah, kind of, but not.
No, it's because I just got a, I got a big broken fucked up nose.
My like big ridge of my nose makes my eyes look closer together.
If I didn't have like a big like squidward schnoz, but I just, I would, it would be fine.
Bad music.
Oh, that's why everyone was doing that emo.
Hey, I thought you were saying that's what I looked like.
I thought it was.
Yeah.
You look like this character.
Oh yeah.
Like your eyes are too close together and your nose is too big.
You look like an orc streamer.
God.
It's both.
Hold the music for a second.
We had two huge donations coming.
We had 5,000 bits from West.
Oh nine five.
They say I forgot the message.
So here's more bits.
Thanks for the years of entertainment.
Watched you since I was in like seventh grade.
That's so long.
I'm so old.
And I'm currently in college.
God, that makes me fucking old.
That makes me, that makes me ancient.
Thanks so much for making a lot of otherwise boring days.
Not boring, especially in a time like this.
Well, thanks for the $50.
I'm incredibly happy to have raised you.
My son, you're in the seventh, you're in the seventh grade.
You see your kids get all off to college.
You speak such a big boy now.
But seriously, thank you.
Thanks for the $50.
Thanks for watching for that long.
We also had another 5,000 bits come in.
$50 from a big boy.
She's gotten so big.
My big boy.
I didn't even read that.
A big boy Ego.
Germany streams mean a whole lot to me
and have made me smile during some really harsh times.
Hope you're doing well and I hope you have a nice day.
Also, please make a sequel to Demon Lord Freddy's.
I can't adhere to that request.
I can't do that.
I can't.
That's like that's...
I know people say,
Jeremy, that video is not even that bad.
You're overreacting.
I know.
But they'll never...
No.
Need to return that money then.
All sales are final.
Speaking of sales, thanks Super Bruce.
Oh, Super Bruce.
Super Frog Bruce.
Thanks for the five community subs.
Is that written down anywhere by the way?
Do I say all sales are final anywhere?
Probably should.
But anyways, that's $50 from two different people.
Thank you West and thank you big boy.
Both of you.
And thanks Super Frog for those five community subs.
Keep going.
Let's put that fucking music back on.
Can I find the end thing?
Is this it?
Guys, I think they omitted this because it was so annoying.
Yoshi's Story, the end.
It's not on here.
No, they removed it.
Nobody has it anywhere.
The end of...
End credits music?
No, it's been removed.
Another 10 subs.
Harold Albertson, 985.
Thanks, thanks me for the 10 community subs.
Thank you, Harold.
That's 10 subs.
Where the fuck is this?
A book opens.
It's the intro.
I had the right song?
No, it's not.
I have no idea.
I can't stop worrying about the song.
This fucking picture.
Look at this shit.
Look at how...
This is fucking...
I want to be this.
So bad.
Officer Jack's Space Police.
This is so detailed.
Big...
I cannot be...
Yeah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't want to talk about that.
That's just...
Let's zoom in on that face for a minute here.
I love this, though.
This is fucking fantastic.
Look at here.
You've even got that Nightwing.
You've just successfully...
Besides that part, I mean...
You've just successfully made like a cool Nightwing.
This is just Nightwing but cool.
Nightwing is cool, but like this is like a cool Nightwing.
It's incredibly detailed, yeah?
This is fantastic.
We got...
I make that face a lot.
This is like how I feel when I play Animal Crossing.
This exact image.
You know what I mean?
Anybody else feel like that?
I do.
Looks great.
Thank you.
Here he's an OK streamer.
This is from, I believe...
Was it WarioWare?
There you guys.
That's me.
Yoshi's Happy Song, please.
Is that what it's called?
Rhythm Heaven.
It's not WarioWare.
Oh, well, whatever.
I thought it was...
This is not WarioWare?
Oh, no, yeah.
It's Rhythm Heaven.
You're right.
Fucking hate this picture.
Why would I...
Oh, it's so bad.
It's just...
Like my...
Look at my skin is so like blotchy and...
Feel like I'm sweating.
My hair is really greasy and stuff.
That looks just bad.
I hate this fucking picture.
You guys don't know that.
You mean you do, but you don't.
I really, really don't like this picture.
I hate it.
Look at how many images exist of my face
doing something fucking weird.
This is the only one that I truly don't like.
I truly hate this picture.
Truly.
Not even making a joke.
Like no fucking around.
I hate this photo.
Every time I see it, I'm just like...
Oh, it's so fucking gross and shitty.
I know this life.
This is me trying to beat chili.
Fast chilies.
It wasn't fucking completable.
It wasn't completable.
This is making me want to click this.
Happy Yoshi's song.
Yoshi's happy song.
Where is it?
I just typed in happy Yoshi.
Happy Yoshi's song.
Yoshi's happy song.
Is this it?
This is it.
You ready?
So I had...
What?
Eat what?
Not even fucking close.
You jokers.
You jokesters.
Not even fucking close.
Not even close.
I was going to give you the benefit of the doubt on that one.
Not even remotely close.
All right.
How about what about the OST?
It's literally the same.
No, it's not.
Eat.
No, you're stretching so far.
I can hear the first part.
But the...
Eat.
No, sorry.
No, you're not even close.
I'm not going to give that one to you.
This is the six stages of fireman.
The six stages of fireman.
It's confusion.
Confusion.
Insanity.
Lust.
Depression.
Wistfulness.
And suave.
The six stages of fireman.
This is great though.
How do you get it to look like this?
That's what I want to know.
How do you get the eyes to look like that?
That like the shiny...
The shiny eyes would...
They look like they're coming out.
They're bulging.
It's just...
How do you...
What is that technique?
It's just...
It's a shading technique.
It looks insane.
It's called talent.
Maybe I should find some.
Is that what you were going to say next?
Even if that person is now...
That's not what they were going to say next.
I predict that that's what they were going to say.
So ban them.
You're a big rat for you.
I don't know why I put this one in.
I don't know.
It's just...
I just...
I know...
Okay.
I know like I've said that not every submission is guaranteed to get in.
And there's...
There's a lot of submissions and some fault...
I don't put them all in.
And then some people are like,
Why did you fucking put this in then?
It's like I don't...
I don't know.
I just did.
I just was like,
Oh, I just won.
I don't know.
Some of them just get...
Some of them going.
I try.
Oh, look.
He ate so much honey.
What is that?
Mustard?
It's cheese.
Because he's a fucking rat.
Thank you, Mr. Spicy Dude.
I don't know.
The only time you ever see like yellow like that
is Winnie the Pooh when he like stuffs his hand inside
and puts it all over his face.
No, I don't want to control W.
He drank Girardi.
This one's not much more sane.
I'm just...
I don't know.
It's fucked up.
And I don't know why I have the rat in a bottle like that.
I...
It's relevant.
It was relevant because it was like the crack streams
from the last day or two.
Why is he in the...
Why is he screwed in here?
I'm a quick...
What?
What happened?
What was it?
What?
What happened?
What was it?
Is there a dick or something?
Is there a dick on camera?
Skip it.
I don't...
It's just me.
What?
Bottom right.
There's no dick on the bottom right.
I'm just like...
I have a rat.
I don't know like...
The Fraggles used to do this shit.
And Fraggle Rock, the guy that used to catch the Fraggles.
What is this?
Bottom right.
Funny.
I don't get it.
What?
I mean what happened?
Look at how cool this is.
Not bottom right on you.
Bottom right on my screen.
This is...
Oh, here are the eight stages of Jerma.
Sadness.
Confusion.
Pretending to know.
Adequate.
Sad.
Anger.
Acceptance.
3D.
There are the eight stages of Jerma 985.
This is awesome.
I guess this is what it would be like if I was a real cartoon character.
Although real and cartoon characters don't.
That's an oxymoron.
That doesn't make any sense.
What are you...
What stage are you in right now?
Find out.
Fucking anger.
Always anger.
Always.
Hey, this is me from Rhythm Heaven.
There are no more stages.
Anger only.
And this is beautiful.
With a little golf...
With a little golf guy.
Oh, she's burped on you again.
Put on the Outer Wilds OST.
Ooh.
That's a good one.
That's a really good one.
Oh, this is exactly what I was looking for.
And I won't be listening to it.
I hope it's good.
Because I can't...
I have to talk to you.
Music fucks with my brain.
I can't have a good message.
But it goes into my electrodes.
On my head.
Inside my brain.
I can't talk.
That's why I don't listen to music.
This is great, though.
Hey, we have a fucking animated rat.
Animated rat.
Back and forth.
He's doing this way, that way.
This way, that way.
Please get some this way, that ways in the chat, please.
Hey, any this way, that way in the chat?
Or sorry, I'm saying it wrong.
This way, that way.
German auto, of course.
Good heavens, would you look at the time.
This is about...
This is the Lord of the Rings...
The...
Video game.
The ladder mission.
I just thought it was funny.
The more orc sounds.
Oh, no, that's what's on the screen.
Right.
It's...
I don't know.
It just was...
It made me laugh.
And...
Here's your criteria for how to get on community content night.
Did I open this and go...
That's it.
Or did I open this and go...
Or...
Huh?
As long as I hit one of the eight stages of fucking...
Germagreif.
Whatever it is.
Eight stages of Gurb...
Gurb...
Gurbababy.
As long as I turn into a Gurbababy on stream, that's how you know.
The eight stages of Gurbababy.
That is...
I just explained to you what they were.
I just...
That's all baby.
Sad, confusion, anger, 3D.
There are...
There are no other baby emotions.
Jex is back for another round.
And Jex reloaded.
Jeremy Elbertson and Willem Dafoe.
Is Willem Dafoe Jex in this scenario?
And Willem Dafoe is Jex.
Why are we listening to what?
There.
Okay.
I changed it.
Compact streamed pictures presents.
Loud P and Cloud...
Cloud car films.
Willem Dafoe film.
Jeremy Elbertson.
Steven...
Sorry.
Why?
Why is...
Willem Dafoe Jex reloaded.
Music by John Williams.
There are more.
The adventure comes to an end.
This is Jex, 1985.
Willem Dafoe is in this one too, apparently.
Jeremy Elbertson, Willem Dafoe, Alicia Winder, Gabe Degrossi.
Well, I love how Xeraxos is just in here too.
Why is this the end of the stream, boys?
Jex, 1980.
I think there's another one.
Yeah.
From the director that brought you Socrates.
A Jerva Craft story.
Willem Dafoe and Jeremy Elbertson is Jex.
A Jermacraft story.
Okay, like that...
This is like the...
If I made the...
You know, like when the YouTuber makes the movie?
Like, Jex, a Jermacraft story.
That would probably be what it was.
I mean, no one would ever give me the money to do that, though.
No, I don't think so.
I'm not sure...
Here's the thing, guys.
Anytime an investor wants to invest in film production or into a movie,
they're anticipating some kind of return.
I could guarantee that whatever movie that...
If you were an investor in my movie, you would go negative.
It would not be a single return.
You would just be able to watch the movie and go,
oh, that was kind of...
That was...
All right.
Maybe like...
I could probably reliably guarantee 1,000 to 2,000 downloads on iTunes.
Like, you know...
And then I could say, you know, maybe like 10,000 clicks.
And maybe like 1,000 to 2,000 iTunes downloads.
And that's it.
It would be a flop.
It would be.
If you don't...
Do you don't think this movie would be a flop?
How much money did this cost?
There are 6,500 people right now.
If every single person here watched this movie 50 times,
that wouldn't even scratch the surface of the last Adam Sandler movie that released on Netflix.
It would be like one hour of revenue from the latest Adam Sandler movie.
I don't think it would turn out all right.
I like it.
This one made me laugh.
Hey, Fred.
Did you know there are a bunch of cavemen in the car?
Bonnie, shut the fuck up!
Something like that, right?
This is not corny.
It better not be.
Why would he?
Why was he Bernie?
What do you mean, Bernie?
Hey, Fred.
Did you know there's a bunch of cavemen in the car?
That's not everybody's Bernie Sanders, guys.
Hey, Fred.
Did you know that the banks...
Okay, it could be.
This needs a little bit more.
It needs a little bit more Bernie pog on it.
I can see it.
This is just cute.
I would probably hurt.
You're literally on fire.
I mean, kind of.
Not literally.
I got the hair pretty good, too.
And you've got my big cheekbones and my fucking eye sink.
Ego maniac.
I didn't say anything and that makes me fucking irresistible.
No, I just said that.
You got my face good.
But I didn't even have to.
I'm not the Joker.
I'm the Riddler.
And I know, we've gone over this before.
Everyone that says they're the Riddler is the Joker.
And everyone that says they're the Joker is Robin.
I know.
I get it.
Trust me, we've talked about it.
But I wasn't crying on that one.
I wasn't crying.
I was not crying.
I was just, I was just stage, I was stage five.
Confused.
Change the world.
I don't know.
What is this?
Goodbye.
My message.
Change, change, change.
What?
Do I need to?
Okay.
Do I need some screening?
Do I need screening on these?
Have I gotten to the point where I need these to be screened?
Yes.
Fuck.
This is from the take a picture of your face with your iPhone
and everyone looks like that.
What's this though?
What's the whole dug here?
Is that a Game Boy?
Oh, that's Hidden Folk.
Oh, right, right, right.
This one's just, this one's the kiss.
The kiss.
Is there any music playing?
Why does it look like there's no music?
That's very clever.
Well, let's get some, let's get something upbeat.
Something upbeat but still relatively smooth and calm.
What's another one that's like a smooth and calm but upbeat at the same time?
Mario Galaxy.
Yeah, oh yeah, let's go.
Mario Galaxy OST.
Oh yeah, perfect.
This is empty and it's annoying me.
This is annoying to me.
No, what I saw, you know what I would love to install in this room?
It's like a fucking spigot that is connected to like high C fruit juice shit.
Like it's connected to the ceiling and there's a pipe
that goes all the way like around into the fridge
and it's just the high C like red juice is just filled in a big bucket
and there's a little spigot that comes down right here.
Like literally right there.
And I can just go over here and just go and fill it up with high C fruit punch.
Oh, that's a hamster.
Okay, and have you noticed how just, how well that works?
If I had, don't even give me this bullshit.
If you guys had a hamster feeder in your room, you don't, you wouldn't use it.
It wouldn't be something that you did every day.
If you were able to, there was a big thing right there that just always,
always gave you never ending liquid and food.
I would be okay with this.
If it turned out that I was just, I was just in like, I was a hamster
and there was somebody just feeding me fucking just huge water.
I would be like, oh shit, this is free.
This is awesome.
The Reddit, you're a Reddit hamster man child.
Okay.
If there was a never ending supply of water and food right there, huge.
And all I had to do was go like, wow, it's fucking never ending.
And so, and every like, every like few days, a huge hand comes in
and just like unscrews the fucking thing.
And then I see another huge hand, put it back and it's just, I didn't have to do shit.
I didn't have to do anything.
You just, you gave that to me.
Oh, let's get another free refill, man.
You're lazy.
This is weird, weird, weird.
What do you mean weird?
How is this weird?
This is a, what?
This is due to, why are you doing this?
This is a, this is a, this is a creepy fetish.
What?
No, I just wanted, I just thought it would be cool to have a bunch of stuff for free.
Like a never ending water.
I just want to be like the hamster.
Is that, what?
I just wanted to have a big giant.
All right.
You know how you can get like the water jugs with the water cooler thing?
A water cooler.
You can get one of those.
Imagine if the water cooler was a hundred times the size
and it was connected to your garage.
What's so wrong with that?
What's wrong with that?
Would you rather have a place to put your car in your garage
or a big water jug that was like 6,000 gallons?
I don't understand what the problem is.
This is cool though.
Nice image.
This is great.
I love this one too.
Auto in the baby carrier.
I mean, tap water.
No, no, like purified, clean, super quadruple osmosis
and then cleaned and then put through another filter.
Triple water, not tap water.
No.
You guys always make fun of boomers.
Boomers drink tap water.
That's like a boomer thing.
I'll take that tap water from the sinks.
That's a boomer thing.
You guys have more in common than you think?
Yes, it is.
You know how I know that?
Because my grandmother used to have friends over to play bridge.
And that's where this voice comes from, by the way.
This is just me doing an imitation of my grandmother.
This is exactly how my grandmother used to talk.
This is her exact voice.
So they would come over and all of them would drink tap water.
They'd be like, oh, do you want something to drink?
Yeah, I'll drink tap water.
It's fine.
They would all line up.
We had sodas.
We had bottles.
We had all kinds of...
We had like juice.
We had orange juice.
We had fucking...
They were like beers.
No, just tap water is fine.
It's cute.
They are zoomers, Jerma.
Water equals boomer.
No.
I'm telling you, drinking tap water out of like the kitchen sink.
That's a...
Boomers love that.
You're a furry.
How does this make me a furry?
Drinking tap water makes me a furry.
This is fantastic, though.
I love this.
And I love coffee, too.
I should just get one of these mugs.
You were purring.
Motherfuckers.
You motherfuckers.
Because I was doing the water sound.
Whatever.
I was going to use that and put it somewhere that I...
This is how I feel every day.
Everybody else get up in the morning, look in the mirror, and this is what you see.
That's just how I feel when I get...
When I'm looking in the mirror in the morning, this is just what I feel.
It's like, but look at...
You've got the...
The...
Butthead.
From Beavis and Butthead.
Yes, I'm coming to the realization now that I am the combination of both Beavis and Butthead.
I know.
Laugh at everything.
I think the dumbest shit is cool.
I look like that.
I know.
I'm both Beavis and Butthead.
But I have linguistic skills.
I have high linguistic skills.
My talking and my pronunciation.
I'm only like 40% Beavis and Butthead.
I don't know half the things I'm saying.
But phonetically, I can say whatever you want.
Uh...
Excellent.
Excellent articulation.
Yeah.
Excellent.
Excellent articulation.
I love this.
Skip this one.
No, that's not...
That's a pencil.
He's got...
It's an eraser.
It's just an eraser.
This is great, though.
Thank you.
Shido's back there.
You've seen Shido.
Everyone always...
No, it's not underwear.
It's an eraser.
Why is Super Mario Galaxy playing?
It's...
I don't know.
Because people wanted to...
Well, this doesn't really match up at all.
That's better.
There's the winks.
Should I do it?
Should I redeem one?
Look at this.
And these have become so bad.
It's like...
There's too much here.
And too much here.
It's the same shirt.
It's like a blue shirt.
Whatever.
Yeah, I can't have more than one or two blue shirts.
And then you got like this shit here.
Okay, you want to see how to make yourself look really old real quickly?
I'll show you.
Okay.
Guess.
Guess my age.
32?
30?
28?
Okay.
Now guess my age.
40.
Ready?
28.
40.
These hairs on these sideburn hairs?
When they stick out, you just look fucking 100 years old.
You're losing it.
No, I'm not.
That's real.
It was literally the same.
No, it wasn't.
It was these like sideburn hairs.
Look at...
This is like...
This is...
Look at that.
That increases my age by 10 years by doing this.
Look.
I just reduced my age by 10 years.
You're so self-conscious.
No, I'm self-awareness.
Tell me.
Just close these down and you'll look like fucking 20 again.
You are too self-conscious.
No, I'm not.
I...
I just showed my sideburn hair to 6,500 people.
That's not self-conscious.
That's...
Look at me.
I believe that's Joel.
I'm not...
Self-conscious be like,
Holy shit, I don't like this.
Therefore, you'll never see me again.
No, we're on.
I remember this.
This was...
This was bad.
God of War, you motherfucker.
Yeah.
Remember, you have a weird anxiety about social perception.
I don't think so.
Hold on.
Let me just...
Let's test that hypothesis.
What was...
Anything interesting written in the chat?
I think I saw...
No, no, nothing.
I don't think so.
I didn't see anything about potential...
Of huge zits that I could have on my forehead.
No, but why would I really write that?
What an odd social perception that I have.
I don't want to...
I don't want to hear music.
He's ugly.
It's a collection of zits.
No, it's two.
I don't care.
Ugly.
I think I'm beautiful.
That's all that matters.
Here's some go-go squeezy.
Because you're epic.
Is this me just doing a JoJo dance?
But yes, these are good.
Why do people have such a problem with that?
These are fantastic.
I actually haven't eaten one of these in a long time.
I do highly recommend them.
It's baby food.
It's a streamer food.
And people like to call me crazy for it, but that's fine.
This was prefaced by saying,
Jerma, please play The Sims 1.
Maybe one day.
I'll be taking that one.
Look at this shit.
Oh, I love this.
It's so good.
It's so detailed.
This is a great poster.
Take a look.
Make sure you show who did it.
He's an actual demon.
I want to get like a bunch of big coins.
Where can I get like a big heavy like minted good
just real like coin?
Like a silver coin.
I feel like just holding them and moving around.
Just forge one yourself.
Go to the bank.
So if I walk into the bank and I say,
what's the biggest coin you guys have here?
What are they going to say?
Was it a half dollar?
Go to Etsy.
Yeah, but I want it to be as an Etsy coin fake.
It's not like a real tender.
You know what I'm annoyed with?
Why on earth over the years did I not listen?
To those commercials that were on always at two to four o'clock in the morning.
And this never before minted gold rhino.
Only $19.99.
Two for the price of one.
Why did I not get a bunch of those?
This 1917 golden rhino was only available for three days until now.
We allowed four collectors into the vault to find this one piece.
And it could be yours for a limited time only.
The first 1,000 callers will get access to the golden 1916 rhino.
By the way, even if 10,000 people call, you'll all get one.
This is a way to make old people think they have to hurry the fuck to the telephone
to call as soon as possible.
But by the way, the 800 number will stay the same
over the course of 16 weeks that this commercial airs.
Hurry, get to a phone line now and reserve your 1917 golden rhino.
I wish I did.
Why didn't I do that?
I want those now.
And they were huge.
They were like this big.
There was a 1917 golden rhino that was this fucking big.
You'd break your thumb and it would hurt.
And you have to be careful.
Like you could break a cheekbone with that thing.
I want one.
Penis music.
Anyways, I want like a big heavy coin.
I know like, what do you think you are?
Two fish?
Like, no, I just think I want them.
I don't care what they are.
I'll just I want one.
All right, somebody made a custom mod for Diablo 2,
by the way, favorite game of all time.
The giant enemy spider.
Demon cursed extra strong spectral hit.
You got to watch out.
It's a modded Diablo.
They also have the giant rat who makes all the rules.
That's so fun.
Demon spectral hit cursed extra strong.
It's a long tagline, too, for a monster name.
It's funny.
All the cat police.
Say the line, Bart.
I'm the giant rat that makes all the rules.
See what kind of trouble we can get ourselves into.
I said it.
I say I said it.
I'm the giant rat that makes all the rules.
And this is, of course, how could I forget
that this is a Jew wizard reset.
Red dress with a Diablo 2 paladin scepter.
That's fucking funny.
I love it.
Bathrobe wizard.
Yeah, I love how it's the set is red dress bathrobe
and then a Diablo 2 paladin scepter.
But we're in the game Diablo 2.
Why does it have to be the Diablo 2 paladin scepter?
Oh, I love it.
I love humor.
Everybody else just love humor.
It keeps me rolling.
Monkey sees action.
Streamer sees action.
Forgive me.
Omega Lulz in chat, I guess.
And then Omega Lulz in chat.
Thank you.
Thank you, boogers95.
$50 just came in from phylactery lich.
5,000 bits.
Ha ha, streamer say funny thing.
Make brain go brrr.
Omega Lulz, Omega Lulz, Omega Lulz.
Yeah, Omega Lulz in chat, guys.
Yeah, they are.
Darkest dungeon.
This game was really fun until I got frustrated and couldn't do it.
But thanks for the $50, phylactery.
Game is fun until it isn't.
I mean every game.
I was about to turn on the effects.
You weren't going to like it.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
What about point blank free?
Oh, yeah.
What about point blank when I did the bonus round in the first try?
With the light gun.
We don't forget about those.
What about when I beat champion Gundyr first try?
We forget about those.
Remember when I beat Dancer first try?
We don't remember that.
I'm going to beat the last boss.
The final actual boss in Sekiro in like a couple hours.
We forget about that, though.
We don't talk about that here.
No.
No, no, idiot.
Idiot go brrr, right?
Unbelievable.
Ratatouille 6 piece was never an option.
No, I can't go back.
Change music?
All right, I'll skip ahead.
This is scary.
There's another greedy grinner.
See, look at that big ass coin.
We could make decisions with that coin.
Imagine if we made stream decisions with like a big gold coin.
I want one.
I'm going to get one.
It's a quarter.
No, it can't be a quarter.
It's going to be like a big, at least like half a pound coin.
That's going to have to wait.
It's going to be like a quarter inch thick.
How much is like a quarter inch thick?
Like a half a pound gold coin?
Find out.
How much is a pound of gold worth?
One pound of gold is what?
One pound of gold price.
One pound of gold today would sell for about $15,000, $18,000.
Well, okay.
So can I get a comedy one?
You can afford that.
I can't think of things that I'm trying to think of.
That's a weird flex to like just have this giant fucking like $20,000 coin.
That would be, that would be pretty fucked up.
Let me, let me like address you directly here.
That would be pretty fucked up.
If I was just the guy.
Oh, streamer.
This is what he does.
He has a $20,000, one inch thick gold coin that he just shows off every day.
I don't think I want one of those.
And he flips this, this, this 20 K gold coin to like make stream decisions.
It's big Reddit gold.
All right.
How much is like a, all right.
What about silver?
Oh no.
What about platinum?
How much is like a, like a, like a, how much is a platinum coin?
Like a big platinum coin.
Platinum is okay.
One pound platinum coin.
Do they exist?
Okay.
There's a thousand dollars for a gigantic platinum coin.
And this has a kangaroo on it.
Hold on.
What about one gold coin?
Rhino with like a rhino on it.
What are the animals you can put on?
Gold coin praying mantis.
That's what I want.
You get a huge praying mantis gold coin.
What about a rat?
Gold coin rat.
I'm spinning on my own mouth.
Oh yeah.
It's like the year of the rat.
I could probably find like a, I'm going to get a one pound gold rat coin.
Why would I ever do that?
No, I'm going to get it.
I'm going to get a, um, what's the fool's gold stuff?
What's it called?
It's called, uh, arconite.
What's arconite, right?
No, that's a warcraft ore.
Pyrite.
Okay.
Pyrite coin.
Perfect.
Yes.
Okay.
I'm going to get how much I'm going to talk.
I'm going to buy like three pounds of pyrite.
And I'm going to have it customly made into a giant coin like this big.
Pyrite coin.
How much is pyrite?
Pyrite an ounce.
Pyrite per ounce.
Is this expensive?
It's fifteen fucking hundred dollars.
Why is this like the same amount of money?
Hold on.
All right.
What about gold plated?
Should I just get like, should I just buy like a pound of zinc?
And then spray paint it gold?
How much do you get?
Zinc per ounce.
It's 1900 fucking dollars.
What's the cheap?
All right.
How about graphite?
Graphite per ounce.
They make pencils out of this shit.
How much is graphite per ounce?
How much is graphite per pound?
This is 1500 bucks.
Wood.
How much is wood?
How much is wood per pound?
One pound of oven dry wood of any hardwood of a heat value.
No, not wood for fuel.
How, how, how is wood?
No.
Okay.
This is what I just wrote.
This is what I just wrote into Google.
I don't know what happened.
That's what I just wrote.
How is wood per pound?
How much is wood per ounce?
Okay.
Lumber price today.
What is the current price of lumber?
313 dollars.
Okay.
Good.
I'm going to get a bunch of lumber and I'm going to grind it up into a big coin
and then spray paint it gold.
How much is gold spray paint?
How much is real gold spray paint with real gold in it?
Okay.
40, 18 karat gold spray paint.
11 dollars.
All right.
Nice.
Use grams.
What?
I can make anything gold.
Wait a minute.
Should I, should I spray paint my Wii gold?
Should I just spray paint my Wii and Xbox gold and just have gold stuff?
Why would you buy wood by the ounce?
I don't know.
That's the spot price.
Paint your teeth gold.
Golden Shito.
I'm going to have a, all right.
I'm going to have a gold Wii.
I'm going to spray paint it with eight.
Will that damage the Wii?
No.
As long as I like put, like protect it, right?
Well, why would spray painting a Wii damage it?
What?
If I cover the vents, cover the holes and then spray paint it gold.
Who cares?
Cover the vent.
Yeah.
What?
You guys think I'm just going to spray paint the vents?
I think I'll never turn on.
It's going to overheat.
Unscrew the plastic first.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's probably a better idea.
This is from the iPhone thing.
I bought a chocolate dipped Wii.
Let's skip ahead in the soundtrack.
This is, everybody looks like this in their iPhone.
This is awesome though.
Thank you.
It's Murius, of course.
I think we've seen this image before, but I got to showcase it again.
Everybody loves Murius.
How could you not like Murius?
That's my question.
That's not the name of this.
That's the name of this cow is Murius because Murius is curious, but also furious.
It's so good.
Like such a good name.
You guys are using like a meme name that is like apparently fucked up.
Not the cow's name.
That's not the cow's name.
This is great image, but that's not the cow's name.
How's name is Murius.
Change it.
I okay.
Good draw.
It's good art though.
Throw rocks, throw rocks, start stream on time or draw 25.
This is good.
This is very, very good.
You even got the boomer brace there too.
20, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
This is a very, very good image.
It's great.
What was the messed up name he's talking about?
Don't just don't tell them because like I don't want to be the reason
why that person starts searching shit.
I like, I don't, I, the stream is not going to be like a place for people to like,
oh, hey, let's talk about like fucking weird shit.
Oh, all right.
Whatever.
Don't Google anything.
Don't Google anything ever.
Here's the thing.
I don't know if that's my face or not.
Is that me?
I don't know.
Is this just the poster?
I think this is just the poster.
I don't think that's even my face.
Although that would be like, I don't know.
That would make sense.
That would be weird.
The mouth is mine.
Is it?
I guess a cast of thousands, thousands of people in this movie.
Is this public domain?
Can we watch this?
Is it public domain?
Let's see if it's actually me in that.
I mean, it's not, I'm not fucking.
90 fucking thousand years old.
Pretty good.
I like, I like what you did here.
You skipped the song.
I did it again.
This is fucking awesome, though.
Mustache here.
Nice work.
Bloodborne McGee.
Can I go back to short hair?
I don't know.
Let's see what I look.
I mean, I'm using this as if this is what,
this is a real image of my face.
But I mean, it's like, I kind of miss this.
All right.
This is, this is a poll.
Making it right now.
Flip your coin.
I don't have one yet.
Okay.
Wow.
This is, this is getting a lot of votes.
Okay.
Nice.
Thousand votes.
This, we don't break a thousand votes on these polls.
Ever.
All right.
Buy the coin and flip it.
I need to get one first.
Link it again.
Link.
All right.
Here, here, here, here.
There, there, there.
Look, look, look.
This is going to break like 1500 votes.
It never happens.
Okay.
Almost a 2000 votes.
So you guys, you guys are going nuts.
All right.
10 more seconds.
Gold spray paint here.
Okay.
And we're going back to short here.
I'm glad that I put up the meme filter.
We could get a real accurate statement
of what people really thought would be better.
Going back to short here.
I was going to anyways, yeah.
Thanks for the confirmation, visor.
Appreciate it.
Thanks for the vote.
This is another one.
I just like, it made me chuckle for some reason.
I don't know why.
It's just, I look, it made me chuckle.
This is the BB unit.
Yes.
By the way, what the hell?
Why?
I guess that's like illegal.
Yeah, it's like, that's illegal.
That's like, it's the movie came out literally
a few, like what?
Three years ago.
It just like dubbed me over.
Now that's illegal.
Nevermind.
Can't do that one.
Uh, this is from the cooking mama stream.
It was just, uh, I made a pizza
and it was a shitload of shit.
Why do people always use this image too?
It was a corn and strawberry pizza.
It's a Bitcoin miner.
That's false.
That's fake.
I don't want to push that
because that's not even real.
But it doesn't matter.
Oh, oh, this is the kind of shit
that you frame and put on your wall.
And people just assume that this is
something really, really interesting.
Oh, wow.
I won't do that what that is.
That's in, oh, put that up on your wall.
And I have a lot of, I'm going to walk by that
and be like, holy shit.
That's really interesting and cool to me.
Even though I don't know what that is.
Perfect.
Viewers are plummeting because of this.
He didn't even talk.
It's just an image of his face.
This is great though.
I love it.
This is very frameable.
Very frameable.
The music is perfect right now.
Yeah, it is.
Uh, these are different, um,
stances of mine, apparently.
I just thought they would,
I thought they were cool.
I mean, I like, I dream of having powers.
No, everybody does.
I mean, it's just like, uh, it's like,
it's cute to me.
Like, I like it.
Press Z and wait.
Dr. Seuss is from, uh, Chibi-Robo.
I just, it's irritating.
Okay, we're good.
It's adorable.
Play this again.
I can't.
It's, I already did.
I played it all.
I beat it all.
It was so good.
It was awesome.
And I, I, I can just play it again.
Five years can go by and I can do it again.
What about the sequel?
Yeah, but I have to get a Nintendo DS.
Um, oh, it's a 1920s movie camera.
Uh, emulate a DSer thing.
Um, the thing, a way to play,
to put it through to my computer.
Just emulate it.
Just get every game for free and just emulate, dude.
Just do it.
I, what is, what do you got to, where are you afraid?
Just emulate everything.
Just don't buy any games.
Illegal.
So what?
Hey, I own it.
Look, I, I own it.
I own the console.
I own the disc.
I own it.
Hey, you printed that.
Oh yeah?
What are all these games?
New Avengers, Captain America, Fantastic Four, Iron Man,
Young Avengers.
Who's Young Avengers?
Is it a, how, what game is that?
Like, is that a game I can play?
Did I get scammed?
No, I didn't.
I'm, look, teacher's copy versus what they give you.
I hate that image even more.
It's just scary.
It's scary.
Like, why, why did you animate the eyes?
I love this too.
It's Chibi-Robo and Fireman.
Together at last.
At last.
Look out.
It's gonna impale him.
Why?
What?
This OST is too stressful.
All right, I'll put on fucking relaxation music.
Has this channel ever been offline?
Lo-Fi Hip-Hop Beats to Relax 2.
This channel, I think, is live.
I think it's, it's literally never been turned off.
But that's crazy.
It went offline once.
Only once.
Holy shit.
How many computers do you have?
How many fucking computers do you have to be able to keep that going?
Relaxing, how about flute music?
Mario music.
This one has a dog on it.
Classical music for relaxation.
Chopping.
Beethoven, oh, no, no, no, no, no.
That's, that's chopping is the, all right, let's try it.
Did we go over how this is surgery music?
I can't listen to classical music because it's surgery music.
Do we ever talk about that?
Have I ever gone over this?
Why?
I have, right?
I've never gone over this.
Explain, explain.
Okay, so yeah, like dentist music.
Yeah, I want, I, I had my wisdom teeth pulled.
And I was kind of put under anesthesia for it.
And this music was just playing.
Guy just had classical music playing while he was pulling my teeth.
And it was crazy because like, obviously you could, you get,
when I was putting, getting put under the sedation, it was like,
the song, it was scary.
It was like going, and that's just classical, classical, classical.
This is surgery music.
I've had two procedures and there's, this always plays.
There's always like a fucking surgery song.
Yeah, like this is like, and they like get in there and
Hannibal did that.
See, right?
He's got a classical music phobia.
And I think it gets angry too.
You know, you notice how it's like boom.
You can tell when he like fucking pushes hard down on the fucking keys.
Listen, ready?
It's like, you can hear his hands hit the bottom of the wood on the piano.
Where is it?
You can feel the wood getting hit.
It's angry.
I don't like it.
It's wonderful.
It's created so magically and the skill that it takes to be able to do that.
And the concentration and how it flows against like a story in a song.
I get it.
But I've had my, I've had teeth pulled twice and the surgery music.
And I think that's all I can think of now.
It's beautiful.
Play MF Doom.
That's copyright.
I mean, too bad.
What?
Hey, play copyright music.
No, too bad.
Okay.
Anything else you like me to do?
Sure.
Do a movie soundtrack.
All right.
How about Inception?
Now, this is surgery music.
I don't like it.
That's surgery music.
That's copyrighted.
Fuck.
I know.
All right.
How about put on jazz?
Jazz royalty free.
Coffee house jazz.
Go ahead and pull up to the coffee shop.
All right.
Just find your self standing in line.
Getting to order a nice hot cup of coffee.
You got it.
What's that smell?
Cappuccino.
Freshly brewed.
You look around the coffee shop and you look for a place to sit down.
But something catches your eye.
And every single available seat is a man or woman with their computer.
And they may have been sitting there for two to three hours at this point.
No place to sit.
Just computers and typing sounds.
You think to say, how long have these people been here for?
And is my money worth the same as theirs?
But you don't.
You just walk out.
Thought you'd like to have a seat.
But you can't.
You take that coffee into the car.
You sit down and you figure out, how am I going to drink this coffee in this car?
Gosh.
You turn the engine on.
Oh, what's that?
You put it down in the cup holder.
A little bit spilt on your hand.
Dripped on the ground.
Nice leather.
Car's got to get detailed now.
Chucks.
Really would have liked a seat at that coffee shop.
You repeat in your head over and over again as you drive.
Angry now.
Coffee's supposed to relax you and slow you down.
Except that's absolutely not true.
Caffeine makes you speed up.
Slow down.
It's a red light.
I don't want, I don't like that music.
All right.
That's better.
He's not insane.
Would you get the Evangelion figurines?
I, I fucking eBay.
I don't know.
Look them up.
Irma, do funny, do funny, do funny.
This is, why is this just like my life?
Not insane.
And that's the Spider-Man meme.
Irma, what, like 35 minutes into my ass, a gnome is just sitting there.
But that's out of context.
We were, that's out of context.
I got to, hold on.
Let me defend myself on that.
That's what I was talking about if I streamed my colonoscopy.
And if elaborate, just elaborately, somewhere on that video.
After like, because a colonoscopy takes like half an hour.
That I just put a gnome on in there.
Like not in, not obviously not in there.
But like on the screen.
Like there was just a gnome like going through the colonoscopy is real boring.
It's just a, it's just a tunnel.
And all this, it's okay.
It's just, we're just in this guy's intestines.
Oh, there's a, there's a gnome there and they just pass it.
This needs to be context here.
I'm not crazy.
Context.
This is great.
Pretty good.
Oh, we've got Jazzy in here.
Is this the Hulk?
Um, I don't think so.
The Hulk.
It's green meat.
It's the Grinch.
It looks great.
Whatever.
Love the eyes.
Well, I don't know.
It's Beast Boy.
It's whoever you want it to be.
Use your imagination.
Great.
Top 1000 stream.
What am I at now?
What is it?
Well, I was a top 1000 stream before.
What's the, what's the rank now?
What am I at now?
Did I go down or up?
I was at like 840 or something, right?
810.
I went down.
467.
Wait, I jumped up to 467?
Did I?
I don't think we, is that real?
I think we have to, we have to get rid of this top 1000 streamer.
We're going to have to go with top 500.
Top 500 streamer.
Okay.
You're at 808 for follower rank.
Top 476.
Nice.
Top 500.
I'm 500.
Yeah.
I, I, I did it.
I did it.
Me.
Hey, look, it's Pluto.
Ego fucking mania.
Hey, it's Pluto in 1994.
Now we got a good image of it.
Bury me.
Bury me with my money.
Bury me with my sub count.
Thank you, East Waffles, for the fives.
Money.
Thanks for the five community subs.
Thank you, Ms. Jackie, for the five community subs.
Money.
Yes.
Five, his ego's getting bigger.
No, it's not.
I'm just kidding.
It's a joke.
That's Pluto in 2018.
Can we see some Pluto's please?
Music's too loud.
I'm just, I can't find the right place for it.
Half this soundtrack is really loud and half it's really soft.
There it is.
Pluto.
Would you look at this?
I gotta get off camera for this one so you can see it.
This is my D&D character.
Rat King German, 985th of his name.
Stats.
TV.
Strength.
Strength is TV.
Dexterity is dab.
Constitution is heart.
Intelligence is high.
Wisdom.
Oh, I see.
Alignment.
Chaotic evil.
That's not true.
Oh, I have disciplined emotional.
Halfling Warlock.
Play your name.
Whatever.
Height.
Compact.
Inventory.
Crown of bits.
A crown made, let's see.
Let's get in there so you can see.
Crown made of bits that were generously donated by fans.
The unnecessarily large size of his crown inflates the already gigantic ego of the wearer.
Gamer certificate.
Grants permission to Jex.
Informs common casuals of the wearer's elite gaming status.
A spie knife.
A comb.
And a light gun.
Exactly two and a half bald coin.
Five common rats.
One giant rat who makes all the rules and one uncommon good rat.
It's not Otto.
What is it, Otto?
Abilities.
You're doing a great job.
Summon, hold on.
Summon an ethereal being that begins to chant encouraging words.
Plus one to pride and plus one to gaming ability.
The master of comedy.
When character makes an intelligent and funny joke plus two to all stats.
That's pretty good.
But yeah, when character makes a bad joke, minus two to all stats.
Free shit.
Once a day, character can summon a random item into the inventory.
This item always is worthless and has no use.
And then my ultimate ability.
Summon Bugleberry.
Summons Bugleberry.
Both friendly and enemy characters nearby get bored and leave.
Oh shit.
Well, this is awesome.
Good shit.
Plus two to all stats.
Oh, that would be so bad.
You know, if you guys think about how passive buffs and debuffs would just hurt.
And life would just suck.
Can you imagine if you just all of a sudden you did some random act or some random reason.
You had a ring in your inventory that increased like your,
like increased your intelligence by plus five randomly.
Or it could take, you know, minus five or something.
That would be horrible.
You'd be walking around.
You'd be like driving your car and you'd get hit by the debuff.
And you just wouldn't be able to drive your fucking car anymore.
You'd have to.
I don't know how to do this.
It'd be terrible.
Zoom in on the chest.
The gamer license.
Comb as a gamer necklace.
Good shit.
Awesome.
And that's it for the art.
Up until the beginning of March, I'm going to move on to videos now.
Video files.
But before we do that, I'm going to go take a pee and refill my hamster drink.
Be right back.
Anthony Wendell.
Jazz musician.
Only 22 years old.
You could believe it.
The album's available today.
As we come back here.
Let's talk.
So today we're going to move to the video section.
Right now.
Radio joke.
Oh my god, we're radio joke.
No.
All right, let's go.
We are going to move to the videos.
The first one is called Darth Jerma.
I already know what this one is.
I don't even have to watch it.
But here we go.
I already know what this is.
Oh, by the way, if you've never seen Star Wars, this is a Star Wars spoiler, I guess.
This is the part of the movie Star Wars.
And you know who Darth Vader is, right?
You know that.
But like, you might not know anything else.
This is a potential spoiler for the movie Star Wars.
Okay.
By the way, I have to say this every time we do this.
If you've ever watched a TV show in your life, just be careful.
Because this like, I'm going to try.
But this, no, no, I'm being serious.
I got like a direct message like a year ago that was like, dude, you really have like
spoiled a movie for me.
And I'm just like, all right, I got to be careful now.
One guy had power.
Oh, got it.
We all knew what this was.
I don't know who, everybody knows what that was.
I didn't have to pretend like, there's no way.
You know what would be funny if that's what, if that was not what it was.
Got it.
Bro, that was a spoiler.
Okay, coming up next.
This is called the Elf Jerma Picnic.
Coffee, Cheetos, chicken.
Yeah.
Yes.
Hey.
You.
What?
It's time for you to come look at me.
Shut up.
I'll be going this way now.
What a gamer.
You know, my mother always told me, be a good boy.
Yeah.
Taking you guys on the scenic route.
What were you expecting?
Super frog.
Oh, I was.
How could you not like it?
It's got candy.
Small.
Get a big spider.
Hello.
I've heard some nice things about you.
I have nothing to do with this.
I was just trying to go to the bathroom.
Fuck you.
I'm the man.
Hey, mom.
Mom, I see it.
Yeah.
Wow.
Look.
That's fucked up.
Why is it a fucking Egypt?
What? No, no, no.
No, it's Egypt and we're both flog pyros.
No.
I think this one's on here.
This one's on here, I think.
All right.
Well, that was that one.
German picnic.
The best part was you.
It's time for you to look at me.
Very good use.
Give this one a link.
This one.
Okay, here.
Don't give any spoilers.
Here's the link to that one.
Hang on.
This one's called German gets down.
It's down.
This could be a dancing number.
I don't know what it is.
I can't believe I did all of these.
I really can't believe I did all of these.
This really was like your grandfather when you're like,
hey, grandpa, do this move.
And he's like, okay, I don't know what that is.
But are you sure, son?
Disable auto play.
I forgot.
I did on the last like six.
But I didn't on the these ones because I forgot.
And this like it's like 60 videos.
So I forgot.
That's too bad for me.
And for you apparently too,
because you have to deal with the two.
I'm sorry about that.
But that's the way it is.
Let's keep going.
No spoilers here.
Oh, these.
Okay, these next couple are very, very interesting.
These next couple are animations of the rats,
as you'll see in a second.
That old intro.
Take a look at this.
Cute rat characters in a marching band.
Rats don't chat.
We pray at night.
We stomp at night.
Rats don't rest.
We pray at night.
We stomp at night.
We're rats, rats, rats, rats, rats.
Oh, the giant rat that makes all of the rules.
Giant rat, giant rat.
I'm so glad you said thank you.
Thank you for this.
Oh, is this?
That's what this is.
Okay.
All right.
The next one is also auto plays off.
I know.
Same thing, but it was a different edition.
Spoilers.
All right.
Fine.
Spoiler.
I know.
Fine.
I told you.
I know.
Tabs.
Giant rat coming this one, too.
All right.
There he is.
Giant rat.
Again, again, do it again.
Rample them again.
Do it again.
It's time for you to kick to the sixth or beat.
This song makes it impossible to really get it right with anything.
Is that what it is?
Four?
I don't even know.
No spoilers.
Fine.
I'm up next is one.
This is called the green screen DLC waiting room.
Off to a great start on this one.
Here it comes.
We have first up.
Jerma.
That's me.
Jerma985.
Y'all know who I am.
Do I need an introduction?
Um, what the fuck?
Hey, if I lean back, can you spit in my mouth?
Piss on me.
Piss it.
Piss in my face.
Do it.
I'm fine.
I can hold my breath.
He's going to go sit down on the toilet and piss up into my face.
I think about, um, I think eating going on a diet.
It's not a bad idea.
My calculations are correct.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, hold on.
Be a virgin, right?
I meant Virgo.
Sorry.
I know Virgos are very sensitive.
Oh, my God.
You see that?
Look at these Pogchamps.
All right.
Okay.
Easy.
Do I eat penis?
Of course I do.
Okay.
All right.
Good.
Very good.
Great.
Yes.
Oh, okay.
I'm happy.
We're happy.
Okay.
We're very happy.
We're...
All right.
Okay.
Oh, God damn it.
Turn it up.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
What the fuck, man?
Okay.
We're done with this one.
That one was fun.
Thank you.
Okay.
Yeah.
Good.
What else is on here?
Okay.
Sure.
That's fucking fine.
Okay.
What the fuck?
No, it's not an emote.
Still, you're right.
Yes, it's not.
Jesus.
Fucking crack night.
You want a link to this one?
Okay.
Fine.
Sure.
There you go.
That was a video.
My God.
Okay.
This one's called,
is Jerma real?
Well, we'll find out soon enough.
So, those of you that said this was not real.
It is.
It's very real.
Okay.
Now, wrap it up, Jeremias.
We had enough of our shit today.
Not only you tried to sell us a wallet,
but also played Firewatch for three days.
SDR8 now play Poi Poi on the PS1.
Oh, is that just a game request?
Hold on.
Did I get baited into watching a video?
But it's a game request.
Thanks.
Okay.
Maybe I'll...
I don't even know what that game was.
I forgot it already.
And I'm not going back.
This one's called Jerma Slappy.
I feel like I'm going to like this one.
Oh, you want to fight?
You want to fight?
Don't fuck with that.
I'm going in.
You want to fight?
Don't fuck with that.
I'm going in.
That's good.
Riff the Pet.
Yeah.
I don't even know...
I'm not going to click Jerma Lick.
Yeah, I have no idea what that's going to do.
You don't click random YouTube videos.
You don't know what they are.
You have to...
No, I don't.
I don't know what it is.
No, I'm not going to click it.
High Risk.
High Risk, High Reward?
Explain to me what the reward is.
High Risk is...
Oh, yeah, that could be TOS.
Reward.
I get banned for three days
and have a strike on my account.
What's the reward?
It could be funny.
All right, let's go.
You want to hear a real vain.
I think we've seen this.
Have you never seen...
Have you ever seen Batman?
Fucking whatever.
You make darkness, is all I like.
But I was born it.
I drank up the darkness.
And you were just a baby.
What's that line?
I gotta look up the line.
Hold on.
Good Bane quote.
Good Bane...
Best Bane quote.
You make darkness, is all I like.
But I was born it.
I drank up the darkness.
And you were just a baby.
What's that line?
I gotta look up the line.
Hold on.
Good Bane quote.
Good Bane...
Best Bane quote.
That's like my favorite video now.
Derma Lick.
No!
What's that line?
Oh my god.
This is called Derma Mouse Has a...
Derma95 Mouse Has a Bad Hiccup.
I'm gonna blind you in a second.
Hi.
Hello.
You okay?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Well, I have just never talked to a detective before.
I've heard so many nice things about you.
I don't want to be embarrassing.
That was cute.
What a cute one.
That was adorable.
This next one's called Derma Has Fallen into a River in Lego City.
A man has fallen...
Hold on. That hurt my head.
God damn it.
That fucking hurt.
That was so loud.
A man has fallen into the river in Lego City.
Start the new rescue helicopter.
Hey!
I better ban that guy.
Ban him. I don't want to see him ever fucking again in my chat.
Ever again!
Now at least I know where that thing is from now.
It's the first time I've ever seen the Lego City a man has fallen into the river.
I had...
You guys would write that shit all the time and I didn't even know what it was.
Please play Derma Lick.
All right. I'm gonna look up Derma Lick.
And I'm gonna see if it's appropriate for me.
Derma Lick.
Okay. Let's find out.
I'm muting this.
It's just kind of me going like...
All right. Fine.
It's...
Go it.
All right. It's fine.
Just me going like...
We watched it. Good.
All right. Come on up.
It's keep your hands off my stream.
This looks to be animated.
Go, Joe!
No, it's not.
This is good.
This is really good.
That's Joel and Vinnie?
That was really, really well done.
That was very well made.
That was awesome.
Here's a link to that one.
By the way, I noticed something about that video.
I'm sorry.
I'm like six inches tall than Joel is.
Pretty sick.
Pretty good, actually. That's pretty nice.
This one's called Jerma Wolf.
With this ruby, I replace your soul.
You will obey.
This ruby, I replace your soul.
You hear the breathing, right?
After that, that's like a, no, fuck.
After that, listen.
You can hear the exhausted, like, no.
That's good.
Coming up next, we have Jerma Has Lunch.
That was awesome.
That was just a true testament
that you can make anything.
You can.
As long as you've got creative juices flowing.
Look at this.
With the Discord edits.
That was great. Absolutely great.
This is Jerma Without Context.
The urinal rant.
I love Jerma Without Context stuff because
of course it's going to sound probably weird.
What do I say? That I like shit?
I like shit in the toilet and then piss on the shit
and then shit in the toilet again and then shitter.
How many times do I say shit, shit, right? I shit on the toilet.
Oh, that's, oh, that's disgusting.
Not if you piss right onto the drain.
Right?
Like, if you piss directly
onto the, right in the metal pocket.
What?
You could just stand in it.
Are they made like that?
Unless you stand through.
It'll splash back.
Here's the door.
P hits here.
Butter hits here.
And what does it do?
Flashes over you
and your shoes and
What are you doing?
No, that's not what I'm talking about.
That's like, I wouldn't put my penis into that.
I wouldn't put my penis
in like that Venus flytrap
looking thing.
What?
Oh, it's all over the place.
I wouldn't.
I wouldn't do that.
That was pretty good though.
Nice work. Excellent work.
Joel checks the bathroom.
You guys hearing something?
Shake the bathroom?
You guys
hearing something? Shake the bathroom?
That's pretty
quality.
What is
this bath video?
Only
true fans know, Danny.
You'll find it someday. Oh, here
it is. Here's the job interview one that
was almost auto-played.
Just imagine
I drank like fucking a pint of vodka.
I gotta
keep it like that though. That's so fucking
funny.
I see that they zipped up.
Wait, what happened?
Prepares for
a job
interview in a locked bathroom?
Just imagine I drank like fucking a pint of vodka.
Am I in a bathroom?
It's a mystery.
What the fuck?
I haven't, no, I haven't played Deus Ex.
I don't know what that is.
This next video could be titled
Proof that Jeremy Owns Others Shirts.
I'm gonna have to go get my rack
up close. Why?
What?
Wait, that was so low. Hold on.
I thought it was a deep fake.
It does look like a
deep fake.
It does. It looks like a deep fake.
Yeah, like this is a deep fake video.
But I remember filming this.
What is this from? It's from like a Twitter
video. I said Happy New Year on Twitter
like three and a half years
ago. And wait, there's another
oh, this is the April, wait,
there's more noise videos?
Hey, April Fools.
It's a toilet,
you know what I mean?
Okay, so
for those of you that might not, you may not have been here
for a while.
Four years ago, three, I don't know, it was a long
time ago. I filmed this like, look at
me, I'm making a joke, April Fools video,
haha. Funny joke. Look,
April Fools toilet, haha, like I'm
making a joke, making a joke,
making a pretend joke video
for Twitter. And I dropped the phone
in the toilet for real. I was doing
this thing that, oh, like I pretend to hit my head on the
door. And I dropped the phone and it went
right into the toilet for real. It was
not good.
Coming up next is Jerma's Funniest
Home Videos.
Oh, shit!
What's his degree in?
Physical comedy?
Some performers drop a mic.
Don't fuck, don't fuck, come back.
Do this.
God damn it, that was fucking
perfect. Who wins?
Who wins?
God damn it,
that's so good. Here's
the link.
Some performers are good at deadlifting.
Coming up next is
The Witch's Curse Part 1.
You will see a familiar style
to this one. Humble Buck
Incorporated Pictures presents
The Witch's Curse.
Starring
Bass Jerma and
Purple Alien. The saga
continues. Wait, why
is it still driving?
I'm so immersed.
I wonder what that means.
Oh no, we've been shrunken.
What?
What is that?
What is that? What is that? What is this thing right here?
What? What the fuck is that?
Wyvern.
Isn't that just wonderful?
Yeah.
Wyvern.
Faster. Purple alien.
What is our wish scientist scientist
The board idle NPC
To peak it all come on. No we need to know what happens. No
scientists scientists oh
Oh
No, I'm at the edge of my seat. I need to know
That was part one this one's very quick, and I remember making this reference. I know what this is this is
It's gonna scare you just be aware
Are you want the link to the verbal alien one hold on there you go come on next we have
And his name is
Okay, it's John Cena and his name is the amazingly amazingly nearly fully Jewish ghost that is John
Well part two is out it's part wait part two is out
Which part two what was that a couple weeks ago for watch part two right now all right boys part two I?
Need to know what's it called which is cursed part two links are banned
Fuck help. What is it? Yeah? How I do it help me
What's it titled?
Which is cursed part two the scientist?
Okay, here it is all right. Let's watch it. I'm so into this
They go we don't need to wait. We don't need to wait a week for episode two
That's awesome. Don't you guys just love fucking Netflix times is very smart
VR chat
The swamp which is cat, that's a real cat
Hammers
What this is
No, no, no, wait, wait, wait, wait
Why is this I don't understand why I get it because
He's gonna turn the sink on look out
This is so much
Watch out for the cat you forgot about the cat was that bazooka? It was perfect. Oh what we continued oh
No, but oh, I see this part again
Oh
There's no part three not yet, it's said to be continued though oh
That was fucking all over the place if I'm honest all over the place actually
This one I lost my place. I actually just grabbed one wait. Where am I?
How are we?
Okay, fuck. I accidentally just clicked and dragged
And this one's called drama the razor death adder. Hey guys, it's me Greg from Nvidia
Remember me. I used to be a lame-o just like you until I found the death adder
Nvidia death adder 2.7. Are you gonna die on death that I just think sucks
That's it
What hold on? Hey guys, it's me Greg from Nvidia
Remember me. I used to be a lame-o just like you
Until I found the death adder
Nvidia death adder 2.7
Sucks I don't
My script what I mean nice grip. I don't understand the bad grip. That's how I grew. That's how I grip
That's disgusting. Is it what what's wrong with that grip? What's I don't understand
You got sausage hands. No, I need a bit. I got big hands. I need a big mouse
It's why I like the death adder. Well, I don't I actually hate this thing, but I'd used to
The death that is like a big chunky mouse
I like big chunky mice because my hands I get these big palms that any idea I palm a mouse
I have to do it like that. I get these big thick hands
Come up next. This is called the rumor
Commander we have received a report that German is trying to stream shall we deploy the rumor?
Is already on his way the rumor status report. Are you ready to initiate operation interrupt the stream?
167 miles per hour. Oh my god
All right that fucking guy driving the car the guy in the fucking car that just sped by at a thousand miles per hour
It's she screamed in my ear. That was good. It was good. That was a long
All right that fucking guy
That's a good shit. Um, by the way driving a car at 300 miles per hour, I get scared
going like 60 65
Like 65 68 70 wouldn't going don't that would scare the shit out of me
I get scared at 75 like that's when it's like slow. I don't want to go. This is too fast
It's scary. I got some people drive 80 90 100 like what the fuck that's scream out loud speeds for me
imagine
Twice that yeah scream out loud. This was called a meal Honda chases derma through two Ford
We're gonna combine a game that I know and love with a meme. I don't know anything about
All right, you get shot by me oh, okay
Well, I don't I don't get it. Thanks for the video. I
Don't know who that is. I have no idea what that character is
Please give me the link. Give me the link link link link. Oh my god. All right
You know
Character I don't know cartoon even with the team fortress theme
We've seen this already, but it's worth watching again
Who's coming down somebody sprinting down oh my god
What night Travis Scott concert I don't
I'm not gonna watch that
Derma animated dumb shit at life
Here we go. That's weird. Who would build a bridge like this? Maybe they just wanted to get rid of us
Why did it fall?
Why did it fall ah
Because I'm dumb well at least you're not dead
Would you like to join me sure?
How much does it cost to join you a lot?
Wow, that was easy
Let's go find another way across the river
Literally dumb as in a rock literally scanned by a rock
This room
Every item in the game. Oh, okay
What is this thumbnail like that?
this thumbnail I
Was cute. I liked that one
Blink the previous one. Hold on. That was Murius
If his next one is called a germa fan cam. I feel like I've we've seen this one. I think we've seen this one
I
Was
Yeah, that was every Nickelodeon live-action intro
Or Disney Channel, right Disney Channel caught on to that real quick and then the Disney Channel started making their own
like live-action
sitcom laugh out loud shows give us the link
Like what I'm gonna throw together a few words here and you tell me if this is a show
on either a Nickelodeon live-action or Disney live-action, um
Angie in the city. Is that one does that is that that's one right? That's probably one. There's no link to this one here
It's on Disney. It's called that doesn't sound real. You know, it could be though
All right coming up next is what is this is called the germa of the crowd
That's called that's literally Jessie
Is it Jesse in the city?
Jesse Disney
channel, right
Yeah, Jesse Disney Channel
Jesse is an American comedy television series
created
Series follows Jesse young woman from a small town with big dreams who rebelling against her strict father decides to leave the military base in
Texas where she grew up and moves to New York City
She accepts a job as a nanny and moves into a multi-million dollar penthouse on the Upper West Side
Okay, there it is. Hey the intro
Spoilers is it okay. Let's see if it's the same
It kind of is is it the same
Oh fuck wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
How many of these have I done as jokes from my channel? Oh
Oh
Done a singing scream
Okay, I haven't had any animals on stream, but no I haven't had any big lizards on stream
Alright, I've like dropped a bunch of shit before. Oh the wasp the hornet. Okay, that's true
I
Don't think they got it did all these I said music video
Crazy hair. Oh
I haven't done them all. It's all right. I get to keep my drama in the city. I
The genius of the crowd
There is another treachery hatred violence absurdity in the average human being
to supply any given
And the best is murder or those who preach against and the best
The fuck was this that was insane, okay
Uh, germa incredibles, this is okay. This is again if you never seen the movie the incredibles
um
This is probably a spoiler for the movie the incredibles from apparently the disney channel
So if you haven't seen it here here it comes here comes like probably the ending of the fucking whole movie
Okay, here we go. I'm serious people. I've never seen the incredibles. I've never seen the incredibles
I'm about to get the whole movie spoiled. Here we go
So you don't know where he is what you like to find out
What oh no, I don't know what any of that meant but it was interesting
I just I just saw the end of the movie of the incredibles. I think
Uh, this is germa 95 virus on my pc
The second time today, it's the second time today i've had an absolute horrible hacking on my pc to the fact
That it's not even used the state where it's not even usable. I'll show you what's on
Watching star trek
I've had such a bad hack on my pc. I can't do anything here. Look, this is just I can't even click on microsoft edge there
That on the task manager. This is not working. Nothing's working
This is the second time today that someone's hacked my pc so badly i can do nothing on the pc
I don't want to be in it because if somebody i'd like this to date here
It's only getting to america now night states of america at this second
I'll never come back to this god-awful country where people are allowed to attack my pc and behaving this awful way towards me
I can't stand being in this house with people to mess me around. I want to be out of this country. Somebody get me out of this country now
I'll never come back to this awful awful country
Here's what in the name of god is going on that was crazy
Why did why did I hack that? I didn't do that
Oh spoilers
Uh, this one's called penis streamer. I can't wait to delete this one halfway through
What I mean, what was what did it say
Uh, penis music, I guess
I don't get it. I don't get it. I don't get it
I don't get it
I don't I don't get it
I
I can't even play as the fec
Fundraising deadline for 2019 approaches. I am once again asking for your financial support
Because I think all of you know, we don't have a super PAC. I'm not running all over this country raising enormous sums of money
from some of the wealthiest people in america
I am so proud of all of us that we have up to this point in the campaign
Received more individual contributions. It's the whole video more americans than any
Candidate in the history of american politics
That's the way we raise money. That's why we're going to win this election
You all right, you you spent like six thousand dollars worth of pc computing power to make this video
Now the truth is we have an excellent chance to win in iowa an excellent chance to win in new hampshire
I can't watch the rest of this video
And don't tell him don't tell him don't tell him don't tell him
I already I already know
You better mean don't tell him
and
Tell him
All right, guys. I've been busy putting earplugs in my ears covering my eyes
And having a loud screaming sounds just blasting into my I don't hear anything. I don't see anything
I don't know anything
Let's go derma drives a honda civic
That's it
What happens in
It's a good car though. That's a real nice car
quality vehicle
I last a long time
some of the best mileage of any
economy car
Why are these right next to each other? This is how you know google algorithms are just
You should be scared
Like we should be terrified of the ai overtake look at this
I don't know the man of very few voices derma frog detective
This rant again, it's right here in front of you
I don't need to go on a fucking rant
Okay, come on up next is
Uh, this is called
This is a short one. This is germ monkey
You gotta chuckle out of me
And I believe the next one is a follow-up
it is
Yeah, it has to be
Yeah, this is living with germa sucks. I all I had to do is put my mouse on it to see a monkey on it
Uh, this is living with germa fucking sucks apparently and okay look I just okay
What is that
Yeah
That's all that's the only image you needed to see right there
Do it again
What is that?
Why does he have a picture of me coming up next?
This unedited footage from a lost germa 985 stream
Scary one
Pretty good playstation 3 commercial. Hello everyone
Welcome to the show
I'm everyone's only friend jeremy
Me that's not me. How are you? That's not me. How was your day? That's great
How many times must I tell you I am not sure
You are frustrating me do not test my patience today
I have already shown you all countless evidence of my above average height. I have is real
Whatever
I will smite you. I will smite you with the fury of a thousand suns
Pretty accurate chat
That was an accurate depiction of the chat room. Sometimes I look over and there are sometimes are just letters here
Uh, this next one is called meet the germa
Have we seen this before? I don't think maybe we have have we seen this one?
What the
Okay
It's just and then it just screams at you
I believe we have made it to the end of the videos
There are a lot of songs
We have a lot of songs tonight
We play them. Oh this what about the play? Yeah, there was like a play right a school play
But where's that? I told you they weren't that many jojos
I thought I said I said I was gonna skim through that. I don't know. What is it called rats movie?
um university
I can't look at links
Yeah, here it is. Wait, what?
Wait, what the fuck I need to see some of this. It's the whole video like table read style
Pick it up
We stock at night
Oh my fucking god
I'm i'm getting it. Hold on
Look at all these look at all these straight a students, by the way
We pray at night we stock at night we're the rats tiny rat falls off the bridge
Who is in the audience laughing at this?
They get this
Moments later in the castle, there's like a full audience laughing
So sue me for being thorough I want to know that you know what the plan is seriously
How many artifacts do we have to steal before you trust me with these jokes?
Well, I just want to make sure you know what's happened. Oh, I hear the audience
I get out of there and we're also the blue dick mumbles in the background. Yeah, what?
Holy shit, let's
All right. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. This is a this is a packed crowd of people
You got I
There's like 600 people in this audience
This is so many people
All right, imagine being imagine being the person serving the school lunch and peeking in being
I want to see those kids laughing at it here
We don't get in
They drive off cut to interior cafe day inside the cafe. The chef commands his patrons. The man is dancing
Um, yeah, excuse me, sir. Yeah
Over there dancing. It's actually ten dollars to dance in this building. So you're gonna have to give me like
Oh my god, we're gonna die
Go get it boys i'll follow you in and let me tell you something
They do the whole thing
To put the cops off their scent. Hello, sir. Welcome to the rat cafe. There's no rats here. Just uh
Hamburgers, yeah, that would be real nice if uh, that were true except uh, it isn't you're a rat aren't you?
You know, wouldn't it be like funny if this is like uh, this we're all real
Just kidding. Yeah. Yeah, be careful. Apparently there's a
Hey the next day the neck what you know people talk at hold on listen
Sue them
What are you talking about? What are you talking about?
You know, I what if I could maybe do uh, this is college maybe I could come and i'll give speech
Uh, then it's like 6 000 people in this audience. I could probably come and do his speech
What if I could can I do that?
He's an egomaniac. What if I come and do uh, no, I can't go there. I can't go that
The giant rat problem
This is so surreal for me and i'll tell you why
What knowing that this exists?
Is like I can't even believe this shit. No, here's what I can't believe
I can't believe that people are doing this and I can't believe there's an audience of people watching it
It's unbelievable to me. That's I can't even fucking believe it. Is that a video unlisted? No, it's not
Egomaniac from last. Okay. Let's get the audience reaction
Are you wearing a rat on your shoulder the small rat runs away
Oh shit on your shoulder the small rat runs away
God
I it's I can't even believe it. I can't but didn't like didn't this happen before too
It's I can't even fathom
Some thing in movie maker there are people watching this and laughing at it and doing it
with musical with
Musical notepads in front of them. It was adorable make a full production broadway play. I actually was going to do
a germa rumble play
That fell through then we're going to try to get as many people in the audience as possible
uh
We were just going to just sell tickets for like a dollar
and like advertise it in whatever local town or city we were in and just
See what happened
Hard to do some of these things but that was fucking that was fucking awesome
I I don't know what to say. It's
It's crazy to see people will do that
This is a video I made
Feed his ego. Thank you when you're gonna do a live stage show. I don't know maybe it's it'll be fun
Oh, I probably should have warned. Uh, this this has got some flashing lights
I didn't realize that
Sorry about that
There's flashing lights in this one
Actually, this hurts my head
Okay, okay flashing lights here it comes yeah, i'm serious
Go warning
A little blue and black together. All right. Now we've got some songs
Hey, it's me. Hey, it's me your best friend
Oh, i'm not your best friend. I i'm just a guy you
Don't don't what?
Hold on. I gotta look at oh man. It's like
Part of my hair turned into like california
Cutting it off. It's coming off. All right, let's get the songs on here
While we say good night
We'll call it here. We'll call it after the songs, obviously
Throw the reddit shelf never again
We'll see you tomorrow. If you take it off. We're gonna do public domain movie night
As of tomorrow, we should be able to watch two maybe even three public domain movies
I'm gonna start with the gorilla
And we have to watch the whole thing. No, we cannot skip a second of it
Depends on how long they are
The gorilla is one hour long
It'll be fun. I plan on drinking at least one or two glasses of wine
It'll be a wine night
wine movie night
But uh, let's get some songs on while we do the bits
I'm gonna change up the music for the bits as
Probably understand makes sense that way doesn't it?
Thanks for joining us for community content night number five six gonna get drunk. Let's be real. No, no, no, maybe
We'll see you tomorrow
And let's check out some of these tracks
Thanks again
We'll see you soon
This one is called
Uh, it's a giant enemy spider guardian
whole song
Let's take a listen
the giant enemy spider
Two glass george
What?
This is actually pretty good
This is pretty good
This is a battle. Is the link to this one? I mean it is a giant enemy spider. That's right
Hey, thank you kutade for five dollars earlier this evening. Thanks kutade
Let's say hey jerma. I just want to say thank you for helping me get over a breakup
Keep doing what you do
thanks to five dollars and
hopefully
Hopefully you do better better good
Not better. Well, hopefully you do better. I hope all of you do better
That pops up. Yeah. Well, hold on
I realized that putting both headphones in was probably a bad idea
I'm gonna say shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up
respect the music
This is why I can't wear two headphones
The music's freaking the music's freaking fantastic mate
Coming up next
We have a giant enemy tree. This is an original song by the way
I made this one up
I didn't make this like I did the original tune
It's good
This is fucking really good
It's fantastic. It's a seriously
Fucking hate streaming it's like the stupid I fucking am so done with it. It's like not even
It's seriously i'm just not gonna do it anymore. It's done. I think
Hey, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo nine eight five here
Saw that I was muted for a little while
Sorry about that. I'm not sure what happened something got screwed up
But i'm back and i'm ready
By the way, that was from me going
Nice job. Good shit. I said bad bad joke. I guess you hate us
Uh, no, of course not. Why would I hate anybody?
That was good
Coming up next we have
A streamer dumb
Oh my god, that's you
Me
Is that a piss in my face
Hey
So much more
Yeah
This is fucking good
Link link up. Oh god, I got you
That's good shit
That's called the streamer dumb but kutade we're gonna do a few in between songs here respect the music, right?
Um, sorry about you hear about your breakup
Thanks to the five dollars. I wish you the best
It's never easy
Give it a little bit of time
Sam freelance police. Thanks for 250
Hey jeremy remember two months ago when I said I was torn between game design and music and university
do
Well, in the meantime, I applied for a semester abroad at a music university in australia and I got accepted
With a super pug today
I woke up to an email from them saying that international students had their applications withdrawn because of the corona virus
Thanks for being there and cheering us up with your streams during these fucked up times
Yeah, I i've heard
I have no idea what's gonna happen with school and stuff
Because a lot of places are still canceling school through the end of the year what happens to the students
Is everybody just kind of held back a year. Do you do it again? What do you do with that the group of students?
Do it online
Just do online classes
I yeah, I guess
All school is on zoom now
That's rough. You can't do online classes on everything. Yeah
I would imagine a lot of stuff that requires hands-on experience and
Lab work and
It's gonna be a really really strange time
But hopefully when this is all over with and done and we can go back to normal. Hopefully
or at least
However, we can get there. Hopefully
They reach back out and you can get that done and you can go travel and go do things and study abroad
Thanks for the 250. I'm glad you're making some decisions though
Windar thanks for the five dollars. Hey jermis super excited for tomorrow's stream
Is it gonna be a normal time like usual? Yeah around four o'clock pacific
I'm gonna buy a nice pizza pie to share with chat tomorrow pepperoni only good. I do not hear any complaints from chat
I'm treating you can have a slice too streamer, but I bet you like pineapples on yours
Anyway, thanks for all you do. I don't
I think pineapple is I love pineapple as a fruit. I don't like it on pizza. I'm sorry
That's fine. Yeah, you all you all know that opinion by now
Thanks a lot dark soul. Thanks for the 250. There's a link deleted band really cool to see you bringing back last year's style
Sure, what it was
Let's speaking of styles. How about a giant enemy spider epic version the giant enemy spider?
Like a boss fight in the castlevania game
It's a good game, too
Next is giant enemy stir
Oh
It's catchy
It's a good one. Thanks for those
enemy spiders
Don't get the vod muted
I don't think that I should have muted vod
Hey swiggity swanky. Thanks for the 250. I don't have much money, but how much for the clips links to be back?
They'll be back next week broke it you guys broke it links will be back next week with a slight change
Uh-oh, what's that mean?
Thanks the 250 though whole of one zombie. Thanks for 250. I've been having back issues
So I finally decided to augment myself in order to boomer brace
Hopefully now i'll soon have the posture of a closed door and double as a shelf boomers rise up if you still can
That's posture goals right there
the door
Thanks for the 250. Good luck. Hopefully you feel better soon garfield the monday killer. Thanks for the 250
Remember jeremy you silly dog. You're still gonna watch garf sonic rebuilt video. It got canned
Last community content night in favor of joel's movie. That's true. You promised you'd watch it this time
Well, that's probably super late for you
Movies like an hour long you all know how much garf likes his naps in the cat box
If it's gotta wait till next time it's still gotta wait and take out a lasagna out of the oven before it's cooked
But if you do watch make sure to see the credits in the climax
Yeah, I did say I was gonna skip through it
Watch it tomorrow
I'll watch it tomorrow. I'll watch it tomorrow. I'll watch it. I know but here's the thing right
When all right the community content night maximum video watching is supposed to be five minutes
And you tell me this thing's an hour long
That is a long time
It would that would be live action. Yeah live action garfield night
Why did you agree to it? I don't know
See, I just did I said I was gonna skim through it and I still will
No viewer gets an hour dedicated to them
well that
Because then if you don't if I don't put like a cap on it, then
You watch this one hour video. Why don't you watch mine watch my video of why I don't want to watch your video
Well, why the fuck no you watch garfield's hour long video
Yeah, I
Oh, I did. Okay. What what's yours?
Gotta put some kind of cap on it, but I will I promise I will watch at least a handful of the clips
One hour long. Ayaya is mine
I will watch it garfield. I promise not the whole thing some of it pieces of it clips
Hey milka stant. Thanks for the ten dollars and fifty cents hyper light drifter. Ost. Please. Thank you
Remember this for next time next community content night. I want that I want that in the chat room, please
Remember that one this next one is called tea break
tea break
Probably match it pretty well with what the screen is showing right now. So let's just keep it there
Like perfect background music for what i'm doing right now
Thanks for the ten dollars though milka stant whole of one zombie. Thanks for the 250
Oh, yeah, you should watch bugleberry christmas stream at times two speed
Talk so slowly the sudden quick outbursts are funny
I don't think I want to do that
And i'm not going to
Hey potion dweller. Thanks for the five dollars. I'm glad you are moved friend
This message is however for chat
Hope you don't mind me using you as a bulletin board for a request
Chat if you have ac and can help me buy turnips tomorrow, please do my turnip stonks
Are poop and likely going to be 40 per tomorrow. I bought a lot of them and need to sell them
You can help me. Please dm me on twitch anything above 91 will help me break even
There you go
That was potion dweller
Um potion dweller enjoy the 5 000 dms half of which will be fake
Good luck finding the real friend code
i'm jai and
Hopefully somebody helps you. Hey, thanks to garfield propaganda
An interesting name
I was showing my friend some of your stream highlights when her mom walked in wondering what we were watching
After watching you for about five minutes her mom asked us if you were clinically insane. I just said probably
Anyways, german keep up the great work. Thanks for the thousand bits. Appreciate it and
Mom i'm telling you i'm fine
Moms do be saying that shit
Marvash mcgally. Thanks for the 250. Yo gerbolo
I want to let you know that the rat in a jar pick that chat told you to skip was a reference
to a
Oh
I have to start screening these
It's we've done five or six of these
It's time to start screening them
And I have to have a uh, we're gonna have to have an academy
That screens them
Didn't want to get there, but we've gotten there
Now i'm gonna have to include an academy now
God damn it potion dweller. Thanks for the 250. It is time for your daily hamster pellet feeding eat up my little pet
Is that a weird? That's a weird thing too. Is that a weird?
Party power thanks to three dollars. What a fucking legend streamer
Is just such a he's just such great company a genuine. Thank you. Well, thank you
party power seven
Thanks a lot. This is really good. This is good
That's a nice just chill song. I like this one
This is great
Nice work coming up next is uh, this one's called father
50th anniversary
My father was fairly well
Thanks for the subs guys
All of you
This works too
Word soup is what it is
You missed the student bits
Explain the rat would be live your huge inspiration to a small group of us at neu
And if you're wondering
The if you're wondering that it's too spam. I can't read it
I'm wondering performance
Was shown at an open mic type venue with a hundred people
But the video was quite short friends. I was finishing up a little after that. We were never friends david and jake. Thanks a lot guys
Thanks a lot seriously
A hundred people I told you there was a huge crowd
Thanks a lot you two
I'm shocked and honored that somebody would think that was worth doing in front of people
And admitting that you've seen that video by the way, that's like another one that i'm happy. Thanks for that, too
I can't even uh
Moving on
Generate blue. Thanks for the three dollars. I'm moving next week and i'm nervous wreck about moving
But either watching or thinking about your stream calms me down
So thanks for that
Also seeing all these greedy grinner images people make are hysterical glad my two minutes in photoshop of your face
During metal wolf chaos caught on makes me feel like I belong much love some of you guys have created such funny shit here
I give it. Yeah, sure. Have I made up a ton of random things for this stream?
Yeah
But how many random things have you guys just done that we all react to it happens all the time?
It was generate blue
Thanks for three dollars
Uh keta meme. Thanks for the 250. Thanks for the lockdown entertainment
It's much better than watching heroin addicts fighting the street. Hope you're staying safe. Holy shit. Who is talking right now?
link oh, yeah
A great canadian fuck club. Thanks for the 1500 bits grow a mullet. They're both short and long. Yes, they are. Thanks for the 15 dollars
Hey, radly. Thanks for the 250 shave head. My face is too rocky for a shaved head
We were we've talked about that a kin the swin
Thanks for the five dollars. Hey jim. I love your content
I know you're still looking for some public domain movies from my major in history
I've had to watch a lot of old soviet movies, which are all public domain
That'll ship for tempkin alexander nevsky man with a movie camera
There's a lot of really good ones from around 1920 to 1930 might be worth checking out
Some are pretty crazy and silly. Hey if this goes over well tomorrow
I'm gonna turn this down for just a second if this goes over well tomorrow and this is fun
And this isn't just like well that sucked. Let's never do that again. Of course. I want to do it again
We'll see how it goes tomorrow. We also had uh three dollars from robo fusion
I genuinely watch every stream I can in hopes that bugleberry shows up
You're gonna be so happy at some point in the future. I can guarantee it gradually grace. Thanks for five dollars
You cannot understand the pure fucking hilarity you caused for me by showing my mega milk image a wish
Mega
I can I ever get away from this is i'm never gonna be able to get away
I'm never gonna be able to get away from it. I will never be able to avoid that ever again. Will I damn it?
Well, also they say
Uh my mega milk image a wish. Uh, I was I wish I was sorry, but i'm just not
I'm howling man. Absolutely howling so to make up for it
I have the first ever bits i've ever donated in much love from scotland from a relatively new viewer
Who wishes they had known you earlier? Well, welcome gradually grace. Thanks for the five dollars and thanks for the image
I'm howling man. Did I catch these five subs from eased waffles?
I don't think I said thanks five subs from eased waffles and then five subs from jingo jango wizard
Spy, thanks both of you next up on our song list is called
Giant enemy spider piano edition somebody doing it on a piano take a listen
Here
Dentist hey stripes beast. Thanks for the 250
Saloon music
Kind of is
Thanks stripes beast. Uh, hey germa you think before you die we should build
A terracotta soldier tomb for you so your subscribers can follow you into the afterlife
Instead of weapons we can bring you gamer gear. That's freaking me out, man
That's funny to a point where if I don't know no, that's too weird
No, no, I I want to I want to get cremated. I want my ashes to be fucking spread
All my ashes to be spreaded. Uh, I don't know and into like a clown shoe
Not a gamer tomb. No
Don't say that
Have somebody snort your ashes
What so they can get my power?
No, no, no
Oh
Omega monka s
Probably not though. Hey rail
rail puner
Thanks for the thousand bits germa smell like poopy
That's a ten dollar message to say germa smells like poopy. That was ten dollars
1,000 bits
How about next we have a bia walk?
expensive poopy
All these seem to work really well at the end, don't they?
Thank you to mars
for the three dollars
Germa, I just want to let you know that you made a joke during last night's scream similar to a joke
You made in city skylines you joked about raising the price of crack to its max for just one day
Which is similar to when you said you'd fix every problem in your city by raising all taxes to 100% for a day
I just thought you should know this also. I am high
Uh that that is that a joke or is that a business strategy he mars for the three dollars
Let's link this one here to make sure you can see it. It's called bia wall
Hey urdevious, thanks for the 260
Jeremiah I go to northeastern the school that the rats played
School that did the rats play I can guarantee if you showed up to do a talk
There would be at least like a hundred people who would show up
You're really popular here
Please come give a ted talk
on centennial quad
At least a hundred people would go cult leader cult leader god damn it
Germa is actually a celebrity
in one place
Germa in 3d. Yeah
I'd have to want to do something. I wouldn't be able to come talk about anything. I would need a plan
That's stupid enough for me to want to do though maybe in the future. Who knows they would even let me
What about the musical
I I don't I don't think so
Just go look at me for an hour
No, it would never let me back in
I'm not doing it. But thank you ty. Thank you tile go maniac the three bucks on the topic of schooling. Yes
most
Somebody's beating something of this is speedrun in three seconds. What the fuck?
Uh, thank you tile
They say on the topic of schooling. Yes, most everything has been moved online. It's really interesting how things are being handled
It's hard to stay motivated in the same place where I normally would relax and work on personal projects
Motivation is motivation is a bitch. We're just all trying our best
Thanks for the entertainment while this whack-ass shit plays out
Yeah
No, that makes it makes total sense
Separating your work and your play
It's actually a really good idea
And if you can't then you sort of kind of mix them together and it's it's
Doesn't work out so well for a lot of people. I'm one of them. I know we make you use that term office
But if if I didn't have my computer and my monitors and my desk in a different room
I'm not I would I think it would be kind of fucked up
Like it has to be like this. I have to have it in here. It has to be like in a separate area
So I can imagine
Especially something like schoolwork. Well, you need that environment
But yeah, hopefully it is over soon
Everybody wants this in the rearview mirror
so
People can try to go back to normal
Just a question of when how and logistically how does that work?
Hopefully over the coming months we can figure that out
Thanks for the three bucks. Thank you
Imoli, okay. Thanks for the 250 jerma. I'm emily emily. Okay, there we go
And it's my birthday today. So I brought I bought you bits as a treat for your birthday
Thank you for an awesome stream. He bought me on your birthday
If you should be getting you you should be celebrating your birthday and getting bits on your birthday
Hopefully somebody gave you bits for your birthday
Did you did you have a birthday party and have have did somebody send you bits send them back send the bits back?
I don't have the capability to do that
What does it say? What does it say? All refunds are?
Um final or whatever it was what's the thing I got it right all sales are final. Happy birthday though emily
Thanks and take care
Hope you had a good one. Hey freak out. Thanks for the five dollars jerma
Have you watched the sopranos if not, here's the whole series, but only when they say gabagool
I i'm gonna watch that eventually
I'm gonna watch that eventually i've seen like four episodes of it. I'm gonna watch it eventually so I don't want to be spoiled
Thanks for the five dollars. I'm not gonna watch it
Thanks for the five bucks freak up
Give us the link
No, I don't want you to be spoiled either
All right here. I don't know. I I don't know. Let me just make sure this is what this is
There's not something else
Okay, I guess that is what it is, um, this is the video um spoilers for the sopranos maybe I don't know
Thanks for the five dollars
Cyrix thanks for three dollars honest opinion on the mario galaxy ost
Um, I actually love it
I love the pivot that nintendo did with the orchestral mixes they've done for the mario games since mario galaxy
good choice
16 seconds of spoilers probably that's what i'm saying. Just be careful
Hey apple shift. Thanks for the 250
apple shift
School stuff really is wild right now. Yeah
The rest of my senior year is being done online
And my high school graduation was cancelled not to mention prom and senior breakfast were also canned
And I might have to take my first semester of art college online
Shit really be sucking class of 2020 got it rough. Yeah, that's
That fucking sucks
It really does
That's just it's just a total just detonation of everybody's lives
Or do a roblox prom
I mean
People used to get married in world of warcraft, didn't they?
Nothing wrong with that
Yeah, just do it like warcraft. They still do. Yeah, it's fine
And we got more we got a couple more songs to put on here. We have I think two or three
I think this is called uh, try another
That's pretty good I can't link this one because it was not put anywhere besides in the discord
I do want to stress one more time very very loudly
uh
Please put your images your links if you can get them on a website
Because this is my on my computer. I had to download it get it on a site like a youtube or a like even like a soundcloud
or
Directly in the discord can work but it's easier for me if it's on like an actual website
Turn down your mic. That was good though. This one's called german nightmare music
I've had like we're getting fucked up dreams with this song would play in the background. Yeah, this is bad. I don't know where
and
The tempo was decreased
Holy shit, this is fucking
Oh you asshole
Holy shit, it's exactly the way it is in my nightmare
Fuck oh my god, it's harmful
I can't listen to this anymore. This is exactly what it's like when I in the nightmare
Oh, thank you for that one. I don't know who you were but why I didn't know
That there was a boss battle of this giant enemy spider
I'm playing that one again. Thanks for the uh clip appreciate it
Moo means moo. Thanks for five dollars in the spirit of community content night
Here's my doo-doo rats remix that I made ages ago before these were a thing
doo-doo doo-doo
Filling it so far
Filling it rip vaude. This is a vaude ripper
also rip vaude
Didn't put that in the message
Vaude's probably already dead
Chef's corner. Thanks for the five dollars literally dye your hair green. No, i'll never dye my hair any color
ever I can't
I cannot I will not
What is that?
No, i'm not gonna i'm not gonna do that
It'd be funny for a day and then I would hate it
Hey treble clefairy. Thanks for the three dollars. No message
Superintendent chalmers. Thanks for three dollars two dollars and 97 cents germa louis waiting room
Silverjack thanks for three dollars. Love you germa been watching since 2011 2019 now never stop streaming, please
Also, where is hulk on hard?
Not streamed on this channel
Appreciate it though. Thanks for watching for 10 fucking years
Hey evan jelly on thanks for the 300 bits, please include bugleberry in the next germa rumble
We can watch as a 1 000 real audience members leave
As he does pottery in the ring
That would probably be bad right i think it was the pirate spy
Here's the mashup
Siren, thanks for the three dollars siren. Hey germa. Thanks for continuing your role
Of court jester for people stuck at home really bummed that my senior year is ruined by all this crap
Love to all my fellow class of 2020
Would your streams help me laugh and kind of not think about it?
Anyways, much love and a big hug from texas
Thanks a lot for the three dollars siren first of all and
Happy to be some company for you
I will continue to be the
court the king of this
this court
Esther is what the people call the king sometimes when they think he's funny
I get it
Fucking naked
Hey gyro say thanks for the three dollars. Hi germa. Am I doing this right? Yes, you are
Great, and I love everything you do bro, and I call you bro
Yeah, whatever
Okay. Anyways, thanks for all the happiness while I do absolutely nothing these days
My pleasure
Thanks a lot bro. See I can do it too right back at you
Stanktron thanks for 250. Hey since you're coming to schools now, would you come to mine?
Also, I have a few friends at different schools. So if you could come to their schools, that would be so cool
I'm not gonna do like a college tour
No, I ain't even doing this once come to mind go do a world school tour
And then finally we have ex whimsical moose thanks for 250
Thank you germa i've been watching for three years now and i've loved every bit of it
Gotten me in the chat through tough times germa heart
Thanks for continuing to watch
Thanks for being here
And that's the end
Thanks for joining us again for another community content night. We're gonna do the other one sooner than later
Because I do want to catch up again all the way through april
Or at least all the way through march into april
Appreciate everybody
We had a couple more bits come in right now. Appreciate the streams germa. This is from evil fish five dollars
Thanks a lot evil fish
I'm a math and science teacher had been figuring out how to teach math and science from a distance
It's been proper hectic
But have thankfully been able to make
Take a relaxing time the past few days. I'm feeling recharged enough to take on the next term
I want to thank you and chat for helping me reset
All the best guys. Good luck
You are an uncharted waters as a teacher
You have to redo and rethink literally everything, you know
About how to teach. Oh, by the way, uh, you have three days to figure that out
You have like two weeks to figure that out. Thanks for doing what you do. Keep
Educating our students. You're doing a great thing. Thank you. There's a link for that one. I can give you a link for that one
Thank you evil fish. Thank you lag x for the three dollars. I lost my job found some of your streams online
This is the first room i've been able to go to
Thanks for being you
Sorry to hear about your job first stream here. Welcome. Hopefully this all resets soon
And we can get as many people as we can back to normal
Thanks for the three dollars. I wish you the best
And I will see you tomorrow for public domain movie night
Enjoy the rest of your day if you have some time enjoy the rest of your evening
Thanks a lot everybody
We'll see you real soon tomorrow around 4 p.m pacific
i'm gonna watch the gorilla and i'm gonna have some wine because I find that's
Probably an opportune time to have a few glasses of wine because when you watch a movie from 1939
Few more bitches came in right at the end crypto. Thanks for the four dollars. No message. Just four dollars from crypto 28 63. Thank you
Skull fluffy. Thanks for five dollars. Keep donating so he can't leave
Well, I will leave eventually
Appreciate it though. Thank you
Gooberry juice. Thanks for five dollars. Hey, yo, jlo 985. I just finished my last final right before I joined
I aced it by the way, that's good to hear
Glad to have it finished but worried about the future
How can I have anything to do for a long time?
And i'm glad I can spend it with you and chat. They're happy to have you
Good to hear that you aced that test by the way
If we go back to normal soon
Everybody wants to
Thanks for the five dollars
And then finally stanktron again 250. Hey, I want to know about your drumming days. What kind of music did you play?
Were you in any bands? No
I was not in any bands
I just had a drum set and I was very capable and I still am if you gave me a drum set right now
I would be able to do it
One of these days somebody's gonna call me out on this
Whether somewhere with his drum set and instead of just sweating and being like fuck i've been lying for years
I will get up there and I will I will drum the fuck out of that set and i'll be and everyone to go
Holy fuck. He was not lying
One day it's gonna happen. I don't know what I have no idea when
One day but thanks for the 250 stanktron. I'll prove it to you one day
It's basically most mostly rock and roll
See you at the public domain new meaning moving moving the night
Words are hard to say
See you tomorrow
4 pm
Take care guys