How's it going? Welcome. Welcome back. He's already telling us to relax.
Yeah, a mod will make it funny in a few minutes. Well then here's the thing.
You tell me. I have a question for you. So, a title. The title of this stream.
A lot of people will say, okay, so the game we're playing is The Last Hero of Nostalgia.
It's like a comedy parody Dark Souls game. It looks like something I wanted to play for a while.
The problem is, I don't know what's in this game. Right? How do you title something that you don't
know? I can't make a reference to this game. I don't know what's in it. So how do you title that?
We need to wait. We need, we should take a system on this channel of soft titles. Because after
about 30 minutes, you know that some monster is going to show up and everyone's going to give it
a name and the title is going to be like Gunu's Revenge. You understand? It's a soft title.
Anyways, how you doing? Hope you're doing well. Kind of just play a game today. I can tell you
the plan. Oh, that is, uh, well, I haven't told you yet. So today we're going to play this. Just
going to chill out. Play it until it's in. Look, if I don't like it, then I'll play something else.
Maybe jump around to a few games. Maybe I really like this. Looks really cool. Looks really
interesting. A soft Gunu stream. But so this is, we're doing this tonight. Tomorrow night,
tomorrow night, uh, I have a sponsor stream. I haven't seen one of those in a while. It's
been a few months and that sponsor stream is going to be to play Wild Hearts. Those of you that have
seen Wild Hearts, it looks like it's pretty fun. It'll be sponsored to play it. I'll be playing
tomorrow with Vinny. That's the plan. We don't, we're trying to figure it out. It's possible. It's
set in stone kind of, but I will be sponsored to play it. If you don't know what it is,
it's kind of in that. It's like a monster hunter in that monster hunter world, but I believe there's
changes. There are some pretty interesting changes to that sort of monster hunting game. Check it
out. We'll see. It seems like people think it's good. So I'm really, really interested in really
happy to play it. What about Elden Ring? Well, Forster, Forster. Yeah, he hit me up. He's like,
Hey, you have an interest to keep going. And I'm like, nah, it was fun, but nah, I feel bad.
Why you rude? No, no, we, we had a, look, we were very, very clear about how we felt about
everything, but don't worry. He fucking hated it. I didn't hate it. I've just, I just had to say,
you know, the vibes were off and we knew that. Look, I like hanging out with Forster. Okay.
It doesn't matter what the game is. We'll do something else. Don't worry. We even started
talking about what the new thing could be. Did we, or did I make that up? Just, I don't know,
just in case somebody asks them. Oh, I made it up. I made it up. No, no, no, no, no, I didn't. No,
I didn't. No, I didn't. Okay. Yeah. Like it was like, Oh, we'll do something else at some point.
Yeah. Yeah. Wait, that's all good. Anyways, you're a liar. Oh, let's go. This is last hero of nostalgia
and this could be exciting. Just going to chill out, play a game. You know how it is. Let's go.
Last hero of nostalgia. So I don't, I mean, this game is kind of looks like a souls game,
but it's not, I think it's like a comedy game. It might be multiple genres. I, I have no idea.
But I wonder, is this a controller game? It might be. Yeah. I'm going in without any
knowledge about anything. Okay. Make sure I, okay. I got to get that off the screen.
All right. Brightness to set this low, great hero. You need not see the corpses.
I mean, I have to play games like this. Otherwise I can't see anything. I know that it's intended
for you to play stuff down here, but I'm sorry. I, I, I know that lots of games that do this,
it has to be up a little bit. Otherwise I physically can't see. How about like right here
is all right. Yeah. Uh, this will help you understand the game a bit and will help you
find the fun. Yeah. Why not? Let's do a tutorial. Okay. Good. That's the question. I just,
I just asked that character customization. Please use your keyboard to enter a name.
Okay. This is my character. Um, this isn't doing anything. Oh, I think this is the point.
It's not doing anything. It's all the way. Uh, max it coward. I just did. How about tattoos,
a couple of accessories. Um, I don't know, like here. All right. Every, how everything gets zero
besides endowment. All right. That looks good. How about, uh, how about, uh, I'm so bad at making
names now. I used to be so good at this, but now I feel like I've, I've diluted the, I've diluted
too much. I've, I've made up too many names in my life where now I'm just sitting here going like,
I don't know, uh, Fred one. How about, um, no, we have to go. It was a different character,
but, uh, slightly, slightly, like slightly sharp, extremely sharp, moderately. Well,
now I'm just naming cheeses. That's like how that's like a cheddar cheese scale. Uh,
minced meat, minced meat, minced meat. Is it minced meat or is it minced meat,
minced meat, minced meat. I like it. I think that looks good.
Anybody have any complaints? Minced meat glass. All right. This is important.
Data din or matter resolutionary sorcerer or random master. I feel like this is like the,
the subject line of a company email at a tech company. Like, yeah, don't, please don't say
this stuff. Don't call us this. All right. Hold on. We're just having to wield heavy weapons,
favors strength, a noble and stalwart defender of order favors vitality. Champions of fidelity.
They are well-rounded and versatile. Okay. Well, dexterity. I can't pick this channel.
Uh, a channel of nostalgia, primal energies favors source, which is magic or a scoundrel who
specializes in critical hits, backstabs and Perry's favors luck. I can't play the, I'm not
going to play the joke character right now. Should I, I don't know this. I feel like I'm going to get
my ass kicked for strength. Just do it. It's a joke game. You're going to be fine. It's a joke
game. You're fine. Okay. It's assassin slash rogue. It's not a joke. Oh, I kind of just want
a shitload of health. I think I just want a bunch of health. It's boring, but whatever. You are a
joke. Shut up. Okay. All right. Fine. I'll try it. I'll try it. I'll try it. I'll try it. So this is
like Perry's and backstabs. You're going to get me killed at whatever. All right. Let's go. Yes,
indeed. Voice acted. It is called Nostral Gaia where the wait, wait, cut, cut, cut. Was that
your customization screen? Oh, oh, might he save me. I don't know what you are, but you're no hero.
So I'm not playing the intro. They'll just get good at pairing. Okay. Cool. Cool. Cool.
Be hero became headed dignity. How do I move? It would impale itself on its own appendages
and the rid us of its pixelated shame. Okay. So there's a dodge roll actually feels pretty good.
Stand in a bar. Anything else I need to know? That's all. Hey, that's it. Just literally give
me a dodge roll with iframes to give me a light and heavy attack and I will beat your game. I
promise you no E the welcome host was absent. No one to tell the newest spawn what to do
or what it was. E. Okay. Oh, here's the messages on the ground. Yep. Okay. Wait,
left bumper is shield. Uh huh. Yep. You are not alone. We have walked before you go back to where
you came from. Hero over. Oh, hero lover had become slightly unwelcoming to new heroes
and those who assist them. Lock on. Use your heroic icon and heal. Oh, I have three. All right. How
does this work layout? Okay. Is there iframes? I think there is. There is. Okay. Cool. Do you
get experience? Also three uses to be replenished when you get to the next checkpoint. Okay. Use
it carefully. How long does it take? Oh, it takes a little while. If stirrer looks over at this
stream, he's going to think I'm playing modded Eldritch Ring. He's going to be like, what the
fuck is this? Where were these cool mods? Switch stances. Oh, okay. Green herb. You just picked up
an item. Check your inventory to see it. Okay. It looks like it is just like a from software game.
Toggle item description. The consumable heal. What is all this? The would be hero began to suspect
it. Perhaps it was a crit. Okay. How many hits can I take? Dude, modded. Dude, look at these cool
mods, man. Access, access, access. They're probably bosses too. Is there a back? There's a backstab.
Otherwise this character would be fucking stupid. Excess place. What does this mean? The confused
stick figure would find no answers in the narrator's library. All right. I'm going to die.
The spreading pixelization had twisted everything and everyone into retro. Oh my God. I'm going to die.
It's you're supposed to lose during the tutorial. It's like every game that's ever come out. That's
in the same genre. You die and you wake up and it's like, it's like, see death is not the end.
And then you go back and I'm going to come back here with like three. Okay. I died. I saw that
scripted death. And so the stick figure proved its ineptitude. Okay. Pretty good. So now what
happens? Let's see. There we go. Okay. So you're. So I, so I died. All right. I did. I thought it
was going to do the thing that they all do. Does everything respawn? Everything does respond. All
right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. What about parries? Okay.
That is a parry try. Do I dare attempt to try to figure out the parry system in this game? Let's
see. All right. That's not bad. Pretty good. It's actually pretty forgiving. But here's the big
question. Can you parry on stairs? It's way better than Elden Ring. Way better. I actually,
it does feel fun to play though. I'm interested. Just don't die in the tutorial again. Oh, come on.
Be invincible during this? Yep. Oh, what is that? Reclaim memory. Memory restored. Oh, that's my
souls. Why? Whatever. I call it whatever I want. We're good. This is probably secrets and stuff,
but whatever. There we go. I like this game. This is a Picross like. Um, I could see where you're
coming from. It's a granny like. Nostalgia's memories had flattened like books without pages.
Oh, how the narration wound pixels were the problem. Oh, fuck. Don't be an idiot here.
Okay. If I die here, I'm going to be actually pissed off. Oh, yeah. It's a bugle berry like
that. That's cool. All right. But wait a minute. What's over here? Is there a sprint? I just
accidentally took the last heel. That's very, I'm happy about that. That's great. What is he
hitting me with? What's he hitting me with? What was that? All right. We're good. That was really
good play. I made sure to get the parry to get the iframes to get the kill and be invincible.
That was not a bad play. That's years of experience right there. And I know for a
fact that some of you are going to say true because it is that kind of experience with souls games
is why I just did not die. That's fine. You can troll me all you want, but that's true.
Knowing how to perfectly pixel perfect play that was only because of how many times I played souls
games. It was this peculiar stick figure. And had it even noticed how retro everything was becoming?
Of course not. It was made out of pixels. It was part of the problem. Oh, everything is like
becoming retro. Oh, wait, is this a okay. I'm starting to get it. It's an item back here.
Where was it? You saw it, right? Where was it? Did I am I losing my mind? It was like glowing on
a pedestal. What was it? Am I seeing things? No, it is right there. How do I get over there?
148 seven momentum special abilities. I mean, this thing is this thing's better. All right.
Yeah. How do I get over there? Illusory books, illusory bookcase. Take that herb. Good call.
I don't want to miss the first secret of the game. I don't get it. How do I do it?
I don't think there's no jump. Why is there no face cam on? Because I don't feel like having it on.
End of discussion. I don't think I can get in there. I'm going to miss the first secret of the
game and everyone's going to make fun of me. Oh, well, I'm going to go through here though.
Turn back. Maybe I should. Oh, everything's fine. What is that? Jesus. Fuck. That hurt a lot,
guys. That hurt a lot, man. God damn it. Oh, I didn't have enough stamina to swing again.
Oh, shit. That's not good. Oh, no. He's still in the tutorial. Oh, shit. He is actually still
in the tutorial. He's still in the tutorial. Judging by the four reactions to why there's no
face cam, there was gigachad, bald, naked, or pregnant. Okay. No, actually, back a year ago,
I never had face cam on. That was a new thing. I would put it on for horror games.
It was pretty rare. I kind of like it like this. It'll come on. You're never going to not see my
face again. Don't worry. Just like when I want to. And that's it. A year ago? No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Not... All right. I mean face cam. Now you're getting me killed. Don't ever show
your face again. You're going to come back looking way different. You know, that's actually kind of
funny. I'm going to do that. Like, I hope you understand that. This is not some long, elaborate
bit to turn my face cam on in like three months and be like, I don't know, like a fat guy or
something. But you know what I mean? Like, what if I had like a fucking different haircut? I had
like different facial hair? I don't know. It might be kind of funny. Oh, stir! Raid from stir. What's
going on? Stir. Hope you're having fun in Elden Ring. I am playing a different game that looks
kind of like modded Elden Ring, doesn't it? See, I decided that like, oh no, dude, I'm not like into
playing like the modded stuff anymore. I'm going to play a video game whose sole purpose is to be
a modded Elden Ring. You know, it's like, you know, but you know how it is. Nah, thanks for the raid.
Hope you're doing good. Hope all the stir watchers are doing good. All right, this time I'm not going
to mess it up. I have enough health. I'm going to kill this mini boss. That's mean to the devs of
this game. What? No, no, no. I mean, this game is very clearly supposed to be a Dark Souls parody.
That's the whole point of this game is a Dark Souls parody. It's very good. Hey, when did I say
this wasn't fun? In fact, I'm going to tell you right now, of all the souls likes I have played,
the parody one seems to have the best first 45 minutes. I'm just saying. Ooh, there's more
over here. Oh, you played like 15 minutes. Yeah. And I'm having fun time. Now the merits of this
game are not solely to be held of it being a parody of Dark Souls. No, that's absolutely accurate.
But it's definitely initial intent intent is to get you to say, well, this is kind of like a
Dark Souls parody. Doesn't mean that it's all about that. Ooh, that was cool. Was that armor?
I don't know what that was. It is. All right, this game is way cooler than I think any of you
thought it was going to be. Is that all I have? Cool. Okay. All right. Well, I got that. Were
there any properties on this? Just physical defense. Oh, here's lore pixelating chest piece
with a target painted where the heart would lie. After I was splintered as so often as I was,
I would be taken back to the repair shop and restrung for the next encounter. I can't,
there's a memory in this thing. I think this is a sprint button, right? It has to be. What is it?
Don't even do it. Oh my goodness. I wonder if you need to break any boxes for any reason.
This happened to my buddy, Eric. That's kind of crazy. It seems like Eric's,
a lot of stuff's happening to Eric lately. It's kind of weird because it seems like, uh,
five to 10,000 of you have this friend of yours named Eric. It seems to do a lot of crazy shit.
That's kind of, all right, I'm not going to fucking lose again.
Don't talk about Eric. You don't even know him. I can't make references to Eric because he's not
my friend. Oh, I see. Dude, don't, you don't know Eric. Like why are you talking about him?
I know Eric, you don't. Stop bringing him up. You know, all right. That's true. I don't know.
I don't know Eric. You do. What? Oh, this is better. Isn't it? Is this better for me?
I'm supposed to use daggers. I'm going to stick with that. No, please. Not in the tutorial. Not
again. How do I sprint? We're good. Hold control. Ooh, the spell will consume access when you use it.
Access 119 damage and uses access. Oh, I have 20 access. Oh, I get it. Is there a door here?
Let me see a door drop down. Yeah, but I don't want to miss anything. I can go.
I don't want to miss anything. Oh, I see what you're saying. Yeah. Yep. I get it. I know. Yeah.
Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. I see. I know. I know. I know. I get you. I get you. I get you.
Intentionally frustrating fall joke. All right. Where is it at? Side is it on? Is it over here?
I don't think there's a jump. Memory of an important NPC. How do I get out of here?
Can I get out of here? Yes, I can. All right. Let's continue. Let's get out of the tutorial.
Weapon upgrades. What's the thing that I do? Oh, oh, this is this game's crunchies.
You're going to die to the first boss. I haven't gotten there yet. So just wait. I know a lot of
you are. Some of you guys have like a notepad that just has like omega low so bad on it.
So you can just go like control, control, control, control. Just so you can paste it in here. You're
ready for it. You have like a whole notepad ready, but I'm not going to die to the first boss.
So might as well clear your clipboard. Oh, that's cool. That clear, clear like your clipboard,
just clear your cache and everything. Rape some memory because you're not going to need it.
Hold down. Yeah, it doesn't. I think the world is sick and you're like final pixelated.
The narrator bowed to save the world. The narrator bowed to cut you from it. Oh,
I like the dynamic here. Left stick is sprint is. Oh, I want to make that a toggle. I know it was
in the options here somewhere. Toggle sprint. There it is. Oh no, wait a minute. Let's make
this even better. Yeah. Okay. Now that's familiar. It takes a lot of stamina. Okay. This is the first
boss. Everyone, everyone get your copy and paste ready. Transformed to an impossible adversary.
One written to crush the stick figure on site. Is there a crouch? I don't think I can crouch.
Don't give up. We need you. Okay, I got it. Staging room NPCs only. But wait, there's probably an
item. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
I don't want to. I went the wrong way. There's a whole nother area over there. Turn already.
Why am I ignoring the door? I wanted to come up here because there's an area up here that all of
heroes staging room key conduit on fire. Lay your pixels upon it. Bonfire locksmith serrated saw.
More access. Be our hero. Well, not yet. I got to go check out that other thing. There's so many
weapons already. Okay. What about like the beacon? Do I go fight that? I'm going to go fight that
thing in the middle. You're you're in the void. Are you? Oh, don't know what you are or why you're
here. Do you want me to guide you? Uh, I don't know. You are no hero and I am no travel brochure.
Now I have no idea what your little gestures were meant to convey. Probably rude, but I will tell
you what you are. Proof that nostalgia is dying. And what a stick person gesture. Can I level up?
Level up. Ah, sometimes you may want to backtrack. Tether to a beacon before you do so. Later,
when you are finished backtracking, you can warp to your tethered beacon. So allow you to pick up
where you left off. Okay. So tether here, like tether warp. Like does this count as me tethering
here? Or did I just tell it? Where did I just go? Okay. So tether. All right. Level up. What do I do?
Luck. 15 luck gets me a new ability. What should I do? I don't know. Luck. I mean,
vitality, stamina. Set your tether first. Okay. This is tethered. Let's go all luck. All in on luck.
This is such a bad idea. I want 10 stamina. What about equipment load? Yeah. All right. I'm happy
with that. I hope that was a good idea. Wait, I have crunchies too. How much does this do?
Luck only. I need 200 more. I should get it from this. What do you think? Last point in luck?
Really? It's 1100. Oh my God. We'll just kill something. There we go. Okay. Get all up. I'm
going to go kill a thing in the middle. Stamina or health. I'm going to say just get stamina up.
All right. Let's go. I'm going to go fight this fucking thing right in the middle. I'm excited.
I didn't mean to press that. Reset. Reset it. What? Why is it over here? Why is it over here?
I was not ready for this. There it is. All right. Hope you bet for me. I hoped you bet for me because
I beat it. Oh, now all of a sudden everybody's freaking out. Everybody wants to change their
bet. Yeah. Sorry. When you can't, if you're at the roulette table and it's spinning and you put it
all on black and they say no more bets. Sorry. It's so funny. I looked over and I saw the,
that was an immediate change. When it was down to like half, 20% health very quickly,
it was like 200,000 points and it jumped to like 3 million in one or two seconds. That's so stupid.
All right. First boss is down. It was so fast. That was only a moderately large enemy, dude.
All right. Now I want to go back to this thing where the key was. Okay. What the? Um,
a lot harder than I thought it was going to be. Jesus. Too many in here. There are too many in
here. Remember to smile while you stab them. Remember to occasionally miss. I like that.
So this is where they hang out. Ooh, is it a real door? It is not stable. Wait, huh? There's somebody
behind that door. All right. That's cool. It changes. It's like a, as this, okay. I like that
fireplace stone. Ooh, it's a new area, but there's more to look at out here.
Why are you playing as a Minecraft sword? I don't know. Why not? All right. So there's a new area
that way, but this behind here too, what is over here? Memory is sacred. Receive blessing. No,
the hero was rejected. Oh, that's great. I love this walk. This is, I love this. This,
this reminds me of Demon's Souls, the music of what do I do? So I wait for a swing.
That hurt a lot. Can I parry it? He's doing the yanky splanky. Did it work? I'm not taking damage,
but it's not working. All right. Well, I don't think I can. Oops. This music is great.
I tried to dodge it. It didn't work. I'm dodging and it didn't work.
The spirit had a final. Jesus. It's so long. Fuck. All right. I get it. It's not, it's not hard.
It's just that here it comes. Boss fights require timing and patience. At first it might seem like
there's no safe time to attack, but if you pay attention, a window will open. I think I'm going,
we're going Axe. I can't parry it. You just got Luigi. No, I got a tutorial message. There's a
difference. Fuck. It reminds me of the, okay. I pressed it. I pressed dodge. What the hell?
There we go. All right. The spirit had a final form. A final form. Oh my God. He went to kick me.
He got way harder. Fuck. Oh, all right. You got to be a little early. Ooh, the crits happen randomly.
I like it. Let's go. This is fun. Wait, that might not be it. Finish him. Huh? Shield of inspiration.
You did it. These extra tutorial messages will now stop. The last hero of nostalgia is a mystery.
What are you? What happened to this world? What is expected of you? You won't be handed the answers.
Can you uncover them? This game is cool. That music was good too. Yeah. Time to blow up this
whole character and ruin it and have to start over in like an hour. You can't go wrong with
vitality and stamina until I figure out what I want. I don't know. I'm too scared to do anything.
Up strength a little. Let me just hold on. Let me see what I got. Did I get anything new? Attribute
bonus. Dexterity 1.1, 2.3, 2, 2.2. So this is the biggest scaling then. Luck influences crits,
so that might, that stat might actually be really good. It seemed like it was pretty good.
So this is just a better shield. It's bigger. Is there anything else on it? Stability, weight,
physical. This is 100% physical damage reduction. Oh, there's no parry anymore. I'm the parry class.
Fuck. I don't know what to do. Saw. This thing's pretty good. Ooh, two handed. Pretty good too.
Oh, it's a key. All right. I have to make a choice and that choice is to be a coward and just do
stamina and health until I figure out what the hell I'm doing. Coward plays, but it's all right.
Yeah, it's always good. It's never a bad idea. Art flow alter. The pixel art and the not pixel
art. I like the style of this game. It was undeniable that the scattered bundle of sticks
remained pathetic, but something was amiss. The narrator never confused was curious.
There's also that other way too. What class am I playing? I'm playing the luck. I forget
what this class is named. It's called like random, random class, random master or something. Yeah.
I'm going to go explore that other area. You're fat rolling right now. There is fat rolling. Okay.
Well, what is actually doing more damage? I think I'm going to stay with the yeah. I'm going to stay
with the ax. I'm so pumped for this playthrough. Yeah. I mean, how long is this game? I'm just
going to run. It's about 15. That's cool. I'm just going to play it until I don't really care anymore.
Maybe I'll beat it. It seems interesting enough to continue to play.
It's definitely got me. I have been gotten. The game has grabbed my attention for sure. NPC city.
Don't even get over here. Oh my God. Stop. Stop. NPC city. Descend quickly is B. Is there a jump?
I don't think so. Oh, these are weird. That really hurt. All right. Ladders back there. Blood of
nostalgia. Are there bonfires? There are. How mad are you that you guys just voted for a regular
ass enemy? Cause wait, no, this is back. Wait, where am I? This is that other room. That hurt a lot.
Okay. It's too bad you didn't vote this time. I actually did try to dodge and it didn't work.
I pressed. I, I wouldn't have just sat there. I promise. He dodged into it. You know what I
think it is? This game has freeze frame when you get hit. So it's, what's probably happening is
because the freeze frame of being hit is overriding your dodge. So there are frames
for being hit. Therefore, if it's not perfect, you're going to get that frame from hit damage.
Right? Interesting stuff. Cause there is freeze hits, but what did I get from doing that? I mean,
I opened the door, but that really do anything for me today. I learned when you get hit, you can't
dodge. Well, no, I'm just saying like the game has freeze hits. You know what I mean? But I think
you know what I mean? Freeze damage. When you get hit, the whole game goes for like one second,
like half a second. So what was down here that I could do? I hate these things already. No,
stop. Okay. I'm fine. Yeah. The ladder will take me back up, but what was the point of coming down
here in the first place? Just to open up this shortcut. But for what? I guess if you keep
dying to the boss, is it just for fun? Check the doors. It looks like I couldn't open any of them.
I don't think I can open any of these. I think it's just to teach you that shortcuts exist and
that they can be used. Or I mean, maybe this opens later. This right here, like the sewers or
something. I don't know. Yeah, it's probably for later. Oh, I'm just going to run. I don't want
to fight this thing. I, uh, I ran the way that I should not have run. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. Is this different? Wait, what's happening? Where am I? Is this, this is, is this,
no, this is different. Where am I going? This is the beginning of the whole game. All right. I'm
running this way. So there really is no purpose to that. And this is just later. Maybe just,
you know, I might just die. I'm imagining like there was a purpose to that opening that,
but I guess there is none. I can't run up that. Uh, I'm going to die here. Maybe not. You can do
it. Uh, yeah, it's over here. Did I just seriously run all the way back down? But wait a minute. No.
Okay. Yeah. I was like, what the fuck is happening right now? Well, there is no point to that. How
come there's no point? It's just like a little Easter egg. Where are we? We made it back here.
This is, I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. Oh, I can't cheese it. I have to fight everything
that's aggroed. Oh, that's not good. At least I'll end up right here. What is he on about?
I opened up like a door over there and it went down to like the, yeah, you're,
you're here. What do you mean? You're literally watching. I just did it. Okay. It's damn enough.
Lost Larry. Quiet. I had my eyes closed because I was scared. Oh, all right. I'm sorry, man.
I didn't mean to say that. You got the secrets all over games like this. You have to be prepared
for running around in circles. All right. There's a bonfire. Secrets looks climbable. Doesn't it?
Well, is this a, Oh, should I kill him? Not going to kill him. Yeah. All right. Tether.
So this is a warp. That's cool. Okay. What does return icon mean? Look up what you have restored
by your touch. A hero is known by their actions. Yes. Oh yeah. I know what you are or rather
what you might prove to be. You do not yourself though. Memory of what was is vanishing,
but do not despair through your journey. You may yet discover your nature.
Your touch upon this beacon has caused a remembering of what was that jagged blade.
You scavenged. Can you, can you hear its whisper rummage through your belongings and find it?
R1, R1, R1. Okay. Item description. This relic has a pixelating memory.
If you can help the relic remember, it will get stronger. The location of its memory could be
anywhere in the world. Relics in the correct location will quiver in your inventory. To find
the location, listen to what it tells you. See how this relic mentions an old man? Try standing
beside the old man, selecting this relic and choosing remember. Oh, that's just kind of cool.
Spin slash. Holy shit. As you remember different relics, you will gain permanent insight bonuses.
That's highly advantage, a lot of advantage to remembering relics, even if you don't equip them.
See your player status screen for your insight bonuses. Okay. But now this is just better. Cool.
Feared such depth to be lost forever. You may be whom I've been waiting for.
Nostalgia is dying. The great forgetting is taking us all into pixelization and then
oblivion. Heroes, the great ones, most especially were meant to save Nostalgia,
but they have forsaken their purpose. They now choke the arteries meant to carry memory back
into our world's heart. I remember their failures, but I shall not lecture you who they were and what
they did was to be yours to discover, yours to make meaning from. The first great one wails
from within the depths of Nostalgia's memory. Oh, the big bad ones. Oh, you got the gate open for
me. Thank you. Oh, no. Why? Oh, you think you're stronger than me. Oh, they always did that. It was
so fun. They would all be like, please stop it. What are you? Oh, so it's a fight you want.
You have one item that can be remembered here. Increase. I need to wait. I do. Did I already do
it? These moving? I don't think so. Okay. Um, let's just go. Heart of a hero, heart of a hero's touch,
heart of a hero's path. Like starter gear. Oh, 22. This relic's memory yearns to be found.
New heroes were once tutorialized that the heart of heroism is not gold and glitter,
pomp and celebration, but humility and ultimately sacrifice. They were taught how to give back to
nostalgia. So I got to go to the tutorial room, look to its heart. Okay. Heart of a hero. I go
to the tutorial room. He was like, Oh, tutorials are very interesting. Maybe that'll do it.
Memory lingers in an undiscovered location is that's what it would say, right? Undiscovered
region. Undo. Okay. Okay. Yep. Yep. Yep. All right. Let's go. That's an, I like that mechanic.
Remembering ahead. Wait, is this real? People putting those down? All right. That's cool.
What the hell is this? Peer down. Do I want to do that? Remember offense. Message box. Yeah,
it is in the game. You, it is styles. Just heart is constricted. Barely any memory goes in or comes
out. I got to repair this. No style Gaia. And so at an old man's behest, the stick figure raised
its frail limbs to limply push onward. The hero's journey too arduous for its meager pixels would
prove a humanist bad guy. How do I do the slash? It's like a spinning slash, right?
Spin slash. How do I do it? Okay. It's, uh, L two. These are a lot of, um, Oh God. All right. The
scale of the game was very small up until five seconds ago. Suddenly lust. I'm not reading all
these. So it's pretty good. Soon the walking scribble would understand all that was lost.
This is our Dark Souls one. What is it called? That area with, uh, the capper demon undead
burg. Yeah. That's what it reminds me of. Yeah. I'm dumping every point in the luck. I'll be
cutting it like a 30 to 40% rate. Why does this actually look fun as hell? Cause it is, it is,
it is fun. Luring ahead. Oh, there's only one rating on this. Worship village. You carry one
relic that can be remembered ahead. Yep. Oh my God. That's so many people. Oh,
cool. That was a lot, um, scarier than it was hard. Get your quest and leave.
Keep moving. What's going on here? Hello. That was a very loud sounding monster. What is that?
Okay. Well we got to go in there. Jesus. Okay. Don't fucking die here. Dab on them, dude.
I'm working on it. I don't want to, I have funny heels and I don't want to reset the area. So I'm
going to, not going to do that yet. The windows are frowning there. They are a little room. Wait.
Oh, wait a minute. Don't go there. Okay. No, out of stamina. Fuck. That's a lot of hurt.
All right. The rolling, uh, the rolling is fine. Unlocked somewhere else. All right. I am not going
to remember any of this. So I hope people in chat are paying attention because I'm not going to,
I won't know. Just, I hope there's at least one person here keeping a, a log of every single
place that my character is gone. I know there's somebody in here doing it because I'm just kind
of wandering. And it's, that's always a bad thing to do in games like this, but I'm all right.
I'm going to turn around after this, dude. Everyone is too high to do that. I don't think
that's accurate. I can do that too. You know, nice. All right. So far so good.
Hmm. How did I not hit you? All right. I'm going to turn around. Just one more of these rooms.
Fireplace stone. Yes. Prickly mirror. What was that? Prickly mirror code is a spell.
Your stats are too low to use this. Oh, I need whatever that is. Uh, all right. So that's a
spell. Well, cool. You don't matter. Is that elevator? Weird. Okay. I'm not jumping in there.
I'm not jumping in there. It's treasure in there. You don't know that. I'll come back later. You
loser. I didn't, I didn't do the thing you wanted me to do. All right. I'm coming out here now
where I could go the other way. You know what? All right. I gotta, I gotta, I gotta, I gotta,
I gotta, I gotta get out of here. I'm not doing this. I have to go, um, I gotta go this way and
then I gotta go down. I'm going to that bonfire that was out here. Yeah. No, no, no, no, no. I got
3,500 memory. I haven't even turned this on yet. So is it decks? I wonder if it's decks or just,
I already made the decision and it was probably wrong. All right. So I could go over here.
Oh, I can remember here. What can I remember? I don't see anything shaking.
No, it'd be in the way. We have to go in here. This is right. Come on. Are we not going in here?
It's not even real. Oh, it's a, it's a way for you to die, but they were in the middle of their NPC
route and they didn't see me. It's bait for you to get killed by these, but they were all the way
at the bottom of their cycle. It's bad. I'm going to die down here. No, I'm dead. All right. So let
me, let me try this again. Do a weed pole. No, I don't care. I don't care if you're high or not.
High avoid enemy. Oh, I should have read these enemies ahead. No, that's yeah. Hey, look,
that's between you and, and you. That's not, I don't have to do with me. I don't need to know
that item down here. Why would I avoid these enemies when there's an item at the bottom?
Oh, not it's worth it. Trust me. He hates people that use weed. Oh, it's, I can't do it. And
suddenly I can't do it. Oh, nothing here though. I can't go in there. Classic.
Well, at least we got to see it. Okay. So I'm going to go up or I don't know,
maybe I'll try to fight that little mini boss. Legend of independence used for weapon upgrades.
Okay. All right. I'm going to go for it. Let's fight this thing and I hope I can do it. Well,
try remembering. Oh, thanks for the cheating. Oh, they were full of shit. Okay. Wait,
they mean inside suddenly annoying enemy. Oh, they're lying. Okay. Oh, that hurt. Can we,
so somebody's, can we please do an allergy poll? Okay. Yeah. How many people here are allergic
to peanuts? That sounds fun. That's not really fun, but how many people are allergic to peanuts
in chat? Ooh, just an unassuming and insignificant house. I look cool. Are you allergic to peanuts?
Really? Okay. So luck bonuses, critical hits, extra item from pickups, 25% damage for 30 seconds on
attack. What? So this is milestones for luck. Two times memory healing costs nothing. All right.
This game's pretty cool. Uh, 95%. Okay. So 5% of the audience here is allergic to peanuts.
That's kind of interesting. Uh, all right. I'm going to go up or should I,
maybe I'll go this way because there's a way to go. No, I went this way before. I'm going to go
here. I'm just going to rest and then go up. What about shellfish? Uh, yeah. How many people here
are allergic to shellfish? 5% peanut allergy, Andy's. Why did I say it like that? I was trying
to think of like a way to say that. That was like such a dumb way to say that. Allergy, Andy's.
You know, thankfully I am not allergic to anything that I know of. All right. This is strength.
Cool looking though. Can't get in here. Well, cause I was trying to figure out like if people
that have, I wanted to say people that have peanut allergies, but I said peanut allergies
first. So I was like, Oh wow. Like we have a lot of people who are allergic to peanuts,
but I said we have peanut. Oh, I already said the first, I already said it.
So how do I fix that mid sentence? 5% again. Damn. Okay. So where's game progress?
Nice game progress over here. No, I came from over here. Where is game progress?
Up from where I was. Cause that's blocked. Do lactose intolerance. Do lactose intolerance.
All right. All right. All right. Game progress. I wish I could close this door. All right. Wait,
wait, wait, wait. You know, I feel like lactose intolerance is going to be pretty high.
All right. One more. Are you lactose intolerant? Oh, oh my God. What a disaster. Oh, this is it.
Nope. All right. I know where to go. I know where to go. This pole is weird. This is a goofy pole.
Is it? I don't think it's that goofy. Nice goofy ass pole. All right. I'm not going to aggro the
entire instance. I'm going to sit down again. These, you got to dodge. Okay. These things are
hard because dodging back doesn't help. I got to dodge right. And then you get put lined up. No,
how do I, that's a shitload of people that have lacked homelands. 25%. 26% is lactose intolerant.
I just lost those souls, but this is an incredibly eye-opening experience to see this.
25% said lactose intolerant. Jesus. That's a lot. I actually, I haven't had that much
milk. And you know, I'm full of shit and I know I'm full of shit. So I can tell you that before
we talk about this, but I'm one of the, well, let's be real. I'm going to be honest. So I'm
one of those people that says, I don't take in that much dairy. Like, no, I don't take in that
much dairy anymore. You know, I, I, oat milk, I drink oat milk and I put oat milk in my coffee.
I still eat a shitload of cheese. I still eat a ton of fucking ice cream. I'm full of shit.
Right. And it sucks. And I, cause I really do want, you know, I, I try to get you,
and I don't want to, I want to, I am eating, I'm trying to eat better, you know, trying to
get cut out dairy, dairy is just, I don't know, it feels like bad for my skin and, but how do you,
how do you replace cheese? Like how? And I've tried the cheese alternatives and they are not good.
They are not good. Let's be real. I've tried a bunch of them, a sharp cheddar cheese,
Oh my God. Like I, you, I don't, it can never be replaced. If they figure it out, I'm willing to
try. I am. I'm very willing to try it, but like an extremely sharp cheddar cheese. Oh, no, I,
it's can't, it's, it's irreplaceable. I'd like to play the game now. Okay. Cheese is addictive.
Yeah. I mean, I could, I could see that. It just tastes so good, but milk, I don't know.
If there's one thing that I can tell you that I have absolutely completely cut out of my entire
diet, it's just, it's regular milk. It's just, no, no thanks. Something about it now, even like
kind of grosses me out. Like I still eat meat and everything. Like, I don't know. Just eat what you
like. I'm just trying to be conscious of just, you know, just be conscious and all things in
moderation. Ben Frank, Ben Franklin was the smartest fucking person to ever live. I've said that a
thousand times on this stream and Franklin smartest man ever. So listen to Ben Franklin, all things
in moderation. Don't eat steak every day and have it, have it when you feel like it. You don't have
to eat it every single day. Don't chug milk every day. You, Ben Franklin wouldn't have done that.
Item ahead. Watch me like Ben Franklin was like a huge proponent of drinking milk every day.
All things in moderation, except of course for milk. All Americans should be drinking at least
two gallons of milk a day. And those of you that disagree off, I'm dead. I got to pay attention.
No, I'm not going to read that because I disagree. Ben Franklin is no, I refuse to say it because I
don't believe you. I don't believe it. I refuse to say it. No, I'm not even going to manifest that.
No, I'm not going to even manifest it because no, I've refused to give that. I'm not going to even
say that. I will say it. Okay, fine. All right. Ben Franklin is not in hell. The person that said
that time them up for five minutes. You said Ben Franklin's in hell and no, I'm sorry. I don't
believe you. Why is Ben Franklin? No, I said it out loud. Now I don't know what to do.
No, that's not real. Nope. Ben Franklin's not in hell. I have 1500 souls on the ground
and you've lost them. You lost him. I didn't. Benjamin Franklin had a milk punch. He was a
milk punch aficionado. It serves 12 people, six cups of brandy, 11 lemons, two cups lemon juice,
four cups water, three fourths cups sugar, one whole nutmeg, plus extra nutmeg for garnish,
three cups whole milk, one remove peel from all 11 lemons with a vegetable peeler, taking care
to remove only the yellow part. So he like, all right, but he probably, all right, but he probably
only drank like two glasses of that. He got to the end of one. He was like, ah, that was delicious.
I guess I'll have another delicious milk punch. Okay. Ah, that's another milk punch down.
I've had enough. All things in moderation. And he just dumped the rest down the sink or something.
You know what I mean? Or he like, he like gave it to other people. He like gave it to like a bunch
of other people. He didn't drink at all. All things in moderation. He's in hell. He's in hell.
So it's no, I got to play this game. I got to play this game.
He's in hell. Okay. I need to fucking relax. I need to pull if he's in hell or not.
Fine. The last poll you're going to get the whole night is Ben Franklin in hell.
Yes or no. 11 lemons and two cups of lemon juice. What? Yeah. What a weird fucking recipe.
I do not. I do. I would say, do not drink that. Why did we get here? We were just asking if you
had a peanut allergy. Now, now we need to, now we're talking about Ben Franklin in hell.
No. All right. So 5% of you have a peanut allergy. That's interesting stuff. That's
interesting stuff. All right. Some of you got peanut allergy, which I wonder what I've always
wondered what that was potentially like. All right. This is weirdly like out of place.
I'm slow. Oh, it's a poison. Okay. Yes. What the fuck? Okay. Yeah. Ben Franklin is definitely at
least in purgatory. I love how somebody just said it has been ruled. What? Why we don't get to decide
that? What do you mean it has been ruled? Democracy, just democracy manifests. Can't believe it.
Nice crit. It's what Ben Franklin would have wanted. Ben Franklin could be sitting on like a cloud
somewhere and like God just kind of knocks on the door. Hey, Ben, don't want to interrupt or
anything, but there seems to be a poll going on in this weird fucking weirdos channel.
German nine, eight, five, but probably you'd never heard of them before. But, um, so they're voting
to determine whether you go to hell or whether you're in hell or not. And kind of have to,
I mean, you know, democracy manifests, right? God watches German. No, whatever. Nice family guy bit.
Hey, other, other pieces of media can reference God talking to people in purgatory. Okay. It's not
his family guy, although that is a, that would happen on family guy. It'd be like, God, if you're
like, Hey, excuse me, Benjamin Franklin, whatever. Like, you don't act like you didn't laugh at a
family guy joke before. Don't act like you never laughed at family guy. You're full of fucking,
you're full of baloney. You're full of baloney. I know you're full of baloney. You have laughed at
a family guy joke before. You're full of baloney. And yes, ironic Peter Griffin memes count. Ironic
Peter Griffin memes count. You're full of baloney. Okay. So where do I go? Great one. Family guy has
good jokes, but a lot of bad ones. Sure. But you still laughed at it at time. And you just,
you can't stand it. He was sitting there on the couch and it was like, Oh Lois, remember the time
that I met Ben Franklin in hell and it played out. And you went and covered your mouth. I'm like,
fuck. No, no. Um, okay. Let me, what's the, all right. Time to do what I do and not pay attention
for like half an hour. Interesting. Armor ahead. Should I just delete these? I always had these
off during from software games because I feel like it's kind of cheating. All right. This guy's scary.
That hurts so much. Oh my God. Where is this? Where is this? I don't remember. I got hit and
I got killed in three hits. I'm going to run. I'm going to try to remember where that was
as best as I can. Yep. Okay. Then it was this way and then in here. All right. Do not follow me.
Open the gate. I will after this. Why is it on his head? Wow. No, we're not doing no more
pull. We're not doing any more pulls. Master chef, fireplace stone. Oh yeah. I just got a whole
new set of gear. Cuts and scrapes. This thing's probably heavy. This thing is very heavy. Yeah.
I'm overburdened right now. I think this is good gear for now. Anything else? Anything pulsing?
He hates us. I don't. I just healed because he said that. Memory of an important NPC. Watch
out for the NPC. What had its story been? What telling had spawned it? Well, I definitely don't
want to do that right now. Nostalgia did not want it. I just got a new weapon. 93 plus 67.
This thing's better. Higher crit too. I'm going to put the buckler on because I want to be able
to parry. Well, I'm not doing that right now. I just made a quiche with half and half. You know
what's funny about quiches? I feel like I've never seen anyone make a quiche. They just sort of appear
randomly during the year at random holidays. I've never seen somebody make one. It's just like, oh,
there's a quiche on this table. I've never seen anyone make it. It's like, oh, it's a quiche. Oh,
okay. All right. All right. Cool. Quiche is gross. I disagree. I think default quiche is not great.
Yeah, bacon. Ham quiche is really good. Ham and cheese quiche.
Broccoli too. Oh yeah, that's good.
Oops. Wow. He didn't even need the bench. This is him just completely asserting how strong
of a character he really is. Okay. 20 luck. I have multiple crunchies. What do you think?
Dexterity? If I'm going to be using quick fast daggers, it has to be dexterity. Dexterity, luck
or vitality. Luck only? No, let's do health. All right. Now I'm going to go fight over the
hell that thing is. Okay. And then it was this way, right? And then, uh, uh, uh, uh, found it.
Well, that's absolutely a boss. Are we knocking? Hey, wing. Oh my God. What?
He almost just killed me. A hero did come, but not the one you wanted.
Is there, be you a hero, my beloved. One's in the chat if you know what that is. Friend ahead.
Okay. No, no, no. I, I cannot let you in. I, I love everything. My stars. We cannot risk it.
No, no, no. Yes. Should you come upon something with which I could restrain myself in your
presence, uh, uh, a manacle or a shack of some fidelity. Bring it to me so I shan't
unduly. Then I would open my door and serve you. What? No, no, no. Bring then.
How about I just put a fucking land mine right here? How would you do that? I don't know. Ooh,
the Smith's hammer. Such waste. What did you find? Are you a hero? I'm an apprentice Smith.
Oh, I was meant to be. I've sought some memory of Nostalgaia's craft in tradition, but
all I've found is forgotten with no masters to teach me. I'll never become a Smith,
but you could work on my gear. That ain't no crude tool friend. It's the Smith's hammer,
the instrument of Nostalgaia's greatest crafts folk. Any apprentice would know it,
even in its current state. A shame it don't remember itself, but that ain't no crude tool.
It can remember. Remember overhead smash, increased damage to armored. Can you use this now?
Jesus. How? What did you do? I ain't worthy. I'll do my utmost to honor and
carry forth our traditions. The hammer has bound itself to me or bound me to it.
My skills are meager. Should you find a workable anvil, you can use this relic to summon me.
I'll improve your arms best I can. The Smith's hammer is the greatest
relic of Nostalgaia's crafts folk, transcending all who swing it. It's the primordial repository
of our art. Such legacy. Of course it still clings to some memory. Throughout the cycles,
each of Nostalgaia's masters wielded the hammer to enhance relics for our heroes.
I've always longed to be a smith, to be a part of that.
Miners in the cliffs above Orsha, once excavated and readied great repositories of all.
Lore. Should you find an anvil there, with enough fidelity for my craft,
limited as my skills may be, might even find a lingering master there.
Ain't much likely, but a little hope is something. Miners in Shulim might aim us.
Wait, it's the same, hold on.
It's the same, right? Miners in Shulim might aim us.
Oh no, the chuckle is at the end. It's part of the last. Oh, it's different. It is different.
Okay, well, sliver of tradition. You can do it. Try love. All right, try patience.
How about you stop? All right, this thing's gonna move, right? We all know it.
Consider remembering. Meet. Fully heal health and cure all status ailments.
This thing is shaking. Remember. Ooh. Wait, we have lore. I'm gonna read it. Okay.
The NPC anti-heroes built barbaric pits where they fought one another to the death.
Their aspiration was to rise above the heroes they'd grown to hate. To strip away the weakness
which had kept them subservient, and save the world themselves. They called their champions
potheads due to their distinct armor. The anti-hero Brendan Merkel was the only known NPC to
single-handedly slay heroes. Unlike the other potheads, he donned the armor of his victims.
I could still feel my hero's blood congealing in me while Brendan Merkel slipped me on. Jesus.
Whoa! Whoa! Look, look, look, look, look! Look it! I'm like a person! What? Holy shit! That's a-
Okay, that was actually a pretty cool reveal. What? He's a real boy! Very cool. All right. Yeah!
All right, let's go. It's a full set bonus. You actually look normal. That's pretty cool. I'm
not gonna lie. Take the armor off. Let's find out. Yeah, so if I take a piece off. Ah. Yeah,
it's all kind of pixely. When you complete it, it turns into like a 3D game. See how these are kind
of low fidelity? This whole outfit was low fidelity until I completed it. It's a metaphor. Cool.
I gotta remember so then the world can look like a 3D game. Not gonna lie, that's kind of freaking
pog. I don't have any heals. Oh, fuck you. I gotta make it count right now. God damn it.
That's all right. It's all right. Shit. Mind your tongue, one who lacks peanut allergy.
Why did you say it like that? That's just a weird way to say that. Mind your tongue. All right,
let's get back over there. That was kind of a long ways away. Don't freak out. I gotta get better at
that because that this whole class is about parrying and backstabs and crits and I gotta be
better at that. That's how I'm gonna get any kills at all. Okay, go on, do it. Do it. You're only
behind here. Got it. You can do well too. It's good to know. Gesture trust. Load and die. Oh,
all right, something bad down here. Blue jerry wall. Somebody's behind me. Right behind. Just
use the Zweander. I think that's it. What's going on? Oh, they were all following me from before,
I guess. Clean. Barnacles. This guy is good. These unstable pixel doors. I wonder what that
means. Legend of Independence. Ugly thing. What? Who rated that good? Ugly thing. What was that?
That was very weird. Okay, I'm very far right now. I do not want to die. I'm going to play like a
coward. I'm written. Betray. Trade? Are these scripted messages? I, no, I don't think so. NPC?
Is this bait?
Was that a bad idea? I don't know. I don't know. I've never played this before. Ugly thing. No.
I'm going to say, um, a bunch of swears. Oh, okay. How about, um, consider, consider, uh,
consider a concept. Tiny, tiny cardboard box. This is aggro range. Forgotten knight armor.
This relic's memory has been forgotten. So I can't do anything about that. Maybe some things you
just can't do. They have no memory. Here's the, all right, I gotta remember this. This is the
shortcut. That was cute. Making sure. Oh fuck. Okay. Parry, parry, parry, parry, parry. I'm
going to die in one fucking hit. Jesus. I have a lot of souls. Okay. Oh, nope. What? Oh, it's
kind of slowed. All right. This looks like progress. Do I want to drop down here though?
I guess over that way. Whatever. I'm going for it. Have I not been, how did I not get this?
Caliber of memory. Shit. Flow state entered. I wonder what that means. More damage or something.
Okay. This guy's wearing pots and pans. I'm dead. God damn it. I got killed by the guy with a
fucking pot on his head. I was so, all right. That's 6,000 souls. I don't want to lose that.
Okay. I opened up a new place. There was a new place I opened. I think it's up here. Why was it?
And then I don't really remember. I'm probably going the long way, but
it's all right. I did not go in these. Oh, big mistake. Get it. Did I get it? Nope. All right.
That's better. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All
right. The door was, I don't remember. Oh, wait. It's this guy. I got to get better at parrying.
Truly fucking awful at this game. The parrying aspect of it. All right. This is the Smith and
then it was up and around because I opened the door up here. Right. No, did I? I'm in the right
vicinity. I know that. We'll get your souls. Yeah. I'm, I'm making my way over there. Okay.
Almost there. This was a huge backtrack and I'm really not happy about it at all. But I'm
almost there. There's definitely a door. I could have just gone in, but whatever. All right. Here
we are. Good, good, good, good, good, good. Let's go. I went in here. I went across and then the
guy with the pot in his head killed me. Okay. Don't screw this up. Where, where, where was it?
Shit. I'm confused. No. Was it through here? I'm in the right vicinity. I just don't know
exactly where I need to go. Was it actually across the bridge? I think this is accurate. Yep. Okay.
Good. All right. Round two. Let's go. Antihero pothead. This relic is part of a set. Okay. So
this is part of a set. 7.8, 1.6. Am I fat rolling? Cause it looks kind of funny. Wait a minute.
Aha. I knew I, wait, that's not even the shovel. Wait, it costs money to do some of these. Do it.
I mean, I guess it just does scale with dexterity. I'll do it. First damage to evil. Let's try it.
Uh, 66 or 63. Ooh, that's not good at all. 93 plus 67 versus 60 say this is way worse. I try it.
It's a really good scaling weapon. Yeah. If I had more decks, maybe it'd be cool, but nope.
Still cool though. Yeah. Good range. What the fuck is that? Uh, okay.
You've been left to figure things out for yourself and that's terrible. So let me help.
Nostal guy was a gauntlet where heroes, I want to R one so bad for a bit, unfortunately,
and then sacrifice themselves back to the world's heart so that new stories could begin.
These new stories were inspired by what came before. They built on the beauty of the past,
but heroes quit letting go. They grew obsessed with maintaining their dominance,
live in their own legacies. And without new inspiration, Nostal Gaia is being forgotten.
Anywho, if selfish heroes won't give themselves back willingly, a real hero will have to make
them let go. Then Nostal Gaia's heart will open again. The first great one chokes Nostal Gaia from
the depths. Oh, no, he likes it. The first great one chokes Nostal. All you gotta do is kill it.
I can't believe that must have been really hard. Oh, it hurts. Oh, yeah, it hurts. Oh,
fuck you. Oh my God. All right, I'm leaving. I can take it. I can take it.
I'm going to leave now. I'm going to leave now. The lanky bundle wobbled and climbed,
ever eager to reach some height unsuited to it. I thought I could kill it. Gold shortage,
hunters wanted. OK, I got a lot of stuff. Wait, I can bring that back to that guy. Oh, it's
happiness. I can't. OK, this is important. What do I level up here? Decks, probably right.
Oh, new luck ability. Decks and luck. And there's an anvil.
The sake of you and yours. But some materials were used for meaningful things,
like improving our hero's arms. Took pride in our work back then.
No sign of a master smith. Well, I have some crude skills. I'll aid you. Best I can, hero.
OK, hone weapons. Uh, sliver of tradition. Oh, shit, I have to actually think about this.
It's probably this one, right? I feel like it's that one. The voice acting is legit good.
It is. What about infuse? So I can infuse the this with the legend of independence,
independent edge of entropy 214. That's better. But I'm going to go for this. I feel like this
thing's pretty good. It makes it pure with no scaling. Um, this is just way better. So I'm
going to stick with this. I mean, this is the other one that probably is pretty good, but
I'm going to go with this. OK, I need three of those to get it higher. Do the halberd too.
Eventually, this might be really good with the scaling. I'm going to hold on for now.
If you find another anvil, especially with a master smith, remember to summon me there, too.
OK. Uh, yeah. All right. 15 decks, I think is good. I'll stop there. We'll get vitality
stamina to 15 and then luck to 25. Go do the shackle quest. All right. Can I teleport tether
warp? I mean, this is going to bring me. I definitely want to keep it here. All right.
Time for me to work backwards. Good luck, because I don't have I don't remember anything that just
happened. I remember going this way. I know I don't. All right. I'm going to go check out
that NPC. What is it? Can I open that? OK, this is locked. It's like glitched out. Yeah, I remember
this. Oh, I can take it. Oh, yeah. OK. Uh, drop down. All right. Where was that guy over there?
That's doing 533 damage. OK, we got to go across. I don't know. Is it going to kill me? All right.
Where this guy's right here somewhere, right? All right. Are you ready? I don't know if I want
this person to hang out with me. OK. My hero. Get like traps in here or something. I'm going
to get killed or something. Welcome to my shop. It's a shopkeeper. I have long longed for you,
my radiance. We all did once. I wish you could experience the parades and feasts we held in your
honor. Banner maidens and clamoring children all thronging the streets to glimpse our salvation,
our markets overflowing with the bounty each hero's deeds had brought us. That was enough,
but we have forgotten. I must never read them myself in your presence, my everything.
For should the great forgetting take me, I could not bear that these pixels I was should turn
ravenous upon you. Oh, what is this shit? You could be a caster. That's right. That's cool.
Should I buy any? Vibrating sword. This thing's kind of cool looking. Deck scaling. Noble E.
Pien. Is this a spell? No, this is no, it is a spell. I kind of want this. Not that expensive
either. Hold on. I'm gonna get it. Wilk, I would make you such but never must I make such an ease
of it. Therefore, tis for memory for meaning. Okay, I want it. Let me have it. Oh, one of these
too. Torch. I get that. Maybe I should get the torch. This thing's ready to get. Oh, this it's
in here. Thousand. All right, hold on. Let's go for it. Remember, thousand. Crit damage up in offhand.
Wait, by how much? Do welding. I'll rock this for a little while. The rest of this stuff I'll have
to come back for. I don't really know what it's I know what this is for. But maybe I should get the
torch. I'm probably going to be pissed if I don't buy this. You know, in an hour, I'm going to be
like I was right there. I had an opportunity and I didn't do it. Is this thing vibrate? Okay, that
was cool. It was worth coming back here for. I could upgrade this too. All right, I'm going to
upgrade this. Hold on. I feel like I could just die and just wake up at that bonfire. Let me test
it out. All right, I actually like it. This is way, way cooler than what I was doing before.
All right. What's the fat? The fastest way is probably just to go backwards,
right? And just teleport to the bonfire. It's like right here. It's like over here, right? I don't
remember. No, it's not. It's back. Um, just kill me. Just kill me. Just kill me. If there's more
than two layers to a level, I will forget where I am every time. If your game has three layers,
one of them is always not in is always gone. It could be the middle layer. It could be the top
layer. It could be the bottom layer. One of them is gone. No matter what, it always happens to me.
All right, let me upgrade this. If the Smith's hammer choosing me,
ain't assigned them. Ooh, yeah. Hopefully this wasn't a bad decision, especially with the master
Smith. All right, let's go check over here. Now, is there a jump? Uh, but hold on. Is that bad?
Yeah, it's bad. Why are you using rivers of blood? Because it's good. How come you don't do the
ooh, ooh anymore? Because I, we might have to have another kill the meme stream. I'm telling you.
Do you remember that? I keep seeing a lot of similar memes show up and you know,
it's time to kill the fucking meme. I think we've got to do another one.
80% of everybody here does not remember that. Yeah, I mean, I'm starting to see some of the same
jokes, right? It might be time. It might be time. And I, I'm at fault of this too.
What about scorn? You can't kill scorn. Oh, no, I don't think, I don't think scorn is part of this.
Where do I go? Ooh, is this where we going? Memes have an expiration date. It'll happen naturally.
It depends on what it is. All right. So this is all right. Where am I now?
This is back in the beginning. This is that like undead at Berg area.
So I don't really want to be, no, I don't want to be here. They get unfunny,
then become legacy memes and then are funny again. I think after the kill the meme stream,
I, I think there was a lot of people that really came up with a lot of new stuff
because of that shit. I mean, I guess I'm going over there.
I just got magnetized to the ground. Whoa. Lacking any depth of its own,
the sticks began poking into the depths of our world. Rude. Is this like bad what I'm doing?
Why do they have that over their heads? Oh, they're cobalt. I get it. Okay. Friend curiosity.
Memory of an inanimate object. Try patience. People, people saying, stop, stop, stop.
This is 200 experience every time. Hold on. Wait, remembrance. What does that mean? Wait,
now they're in a different mode. This offhanded weapon is, is I'm never going to take this off.
This thing is so good. Extra crit too. Oh, you have a lot of health.
What is that? Strength. Heavy prying tool. Strength weapon. It's the half life crowbar.
What does this one say? It's probably really funny. Actually kind of funny.
One hit. Try rushing. All right. Actually be careful. I'll have a try rushing and then try
patience. What was that? Okay. It's fine. What did you hit me with? Oh, I'm out of stamina.
Don't do it. Okay. I need, where is it? I know I have like two of them, right?
Shit. I thought I got it off. I thought I killed them. Damn it.
It yelled like I do when I have a bug on me. Gold coins. Oh, just like a marker,
which should censor the censor the word poop. What? It's not stable. I can't open it. This is
locked. Oh, that's creepy. Was there another way to go? Is that it? Oh, suddenly a fire erupted
to burn the kindling down. This is going to be a hard poll. So you're not, everybody's running.
Okay. I don't have any more heels either. This is going to be pain in the ass. Thank God. I think
he would like a hundred gecks. Um, we've listened to that on stream before coins. I didn't think
he was going to turn around that quick. I thought he was busy mining chain mail. What is this damage
that bounces between enemies send out some loaded correspondence that damages one enemy and then get
sent to additional enemies. That's funny. I really don't want to blow this and I'm probably going to
whatever falling. Um, our one, please don't, I don't want to do this again. Just turn around and
run. Oh my God. This is a wall. Uh, do I have any heels? Ah, I just probably woke somebody up. I'm
sorry. Jesus. Thank God. I don't have any heels. Remember my newborn is crying. Well, go, go take
care of your baby. Why are you, why are you writing that here? Hey, he's going to let you know my
newborn's crying. Uh, chat. What should I do? I don't know. Is the baby hungry? Is the baby tired?
I don't know anything about you or your life. I have no idea who you even are. I don't have any
advice for your baby. Oh, you've got a magical enchanted to pickaxe. This is some Minecraft
shit right here and he's going to kill me in one hit swing, swing it, swing it, please.
Fuck you. Oh my God. Oh no, that was a weird animation. I don't know where this is.
Shit. No, no, no, no. I do. I do. I know what this is. I know what this is. I know what that is.
Be remembered ahead. All right, we got to go all the freaking way. Where was it? This way or that
way? God, all the freaking way. Where was it? This is the wrong way. Isn't it? This is the wrong way.
Isn't it? All right, come on. Do you have any tips? I just started the game. Um, it's pretty fun.
It's, it's, I would hold on. Okay. It's yes. Do you have any tips? It's fun. That was, yeah,
that was not a good tip. I apologize for that bad tip. I'll give you a real tip though.
So dodge rolling is your friend. Hey, dodge rolling is your friend stuck. That's the wrong
fucking way. This is the wrong way. Well, I have to kill everything now for the wrong way. It's,
it's left instead of right. Go up that. I'm just going to say stupid, but you go up there and just
go left straight. Do not go right, right. Lazy to the bottom of that thing. Okay. Move. That was
absolute bullshit. This way. All right. Then we go, um, here. All right. This is new shit swing.
What the hell was that? Okay. I got to pull you over here. Oh, God damn it. Sorry. One little
piece of shit of life. Don't kill me. Chill, man. It's stressful. I, what do you mean? Chill. Okay.
Um, so I was down there. You're going to cast that bullshit. Everyone's going to run down this
hall. I don't want to fight in the water either. Rooting voice potion. Oh, nice. A green herb.
I have never seen a squirrel in real life. You haven't? I mean, that's not that weird.
Where would, I don't know what part of the world you're from. Where in the world are there no
squirrels? Okay. This is a conversation that I need to not pay attention to. Yeah. Squirrels are
kind of interesting, I guess. Are there any squirrels in Vegas? I think so. I don't know.
I think so. Although I can't tell you I've really, I haven't really seen any squirrels. Squirrels.
Maybe. It's something I didn't put into my memory bank. This is a dangerous room. I don't know.
There are two NPCs. Your lack of caution is what I fear. I would never fear that. Shh. Someone's
coming. I might have to fight these people. Hello. You don't look like the forgotten we've been
slaughtering. Don't look like much of anything. Like we should criticize?
True, true. What a ridiculously rendered three are we. Take our company, friend. I call myself
nameless Nero. My companion is the lady Sco Peacutt. Just Sco, please. Nero's titles
don't fit. We are pondering a most dubious task. A quest, I like to think. We don't have to be
reckless to prove our worth. Ah, but we must when the world is filled. Assassin's Creed unity,
girl. That's funny. I can see the latent heroism in their stature. Not unlike my own. Would you
help us, stranger? This quest might give my friend the value he needs. Shh. Really, you're bravery,
Sco. I do not need aid, but I welcome a compatriot always. I'll do it. There is a creature down this
corridor that seems not of this story. The lady is fascinated. While I seek cause to vanquish without
question, that is evil as a thing we agree upon wholeheartedly. So I give you this quest. Well,
actually, I share it. I, uh, gave it to myself first. Are you ready to face the unknown at our
side? What about I don't have any heels. I knew it. Come my allies for today. We prove our worth.
Let's go. You can do it. Suddenly victory. Holy shit. We have, what is this? All right. You guys
fight it. That hurt a lot. Help them. I'm using these spells. I'm casting. We did it.
Arachnid stinger. We did it. We're incredible. In nameless Nero, you have made an ally. Henceforth,
our paths towards heroism are entwined. It's going to make me laugh every time. Oh, it was a quest,
but I didn't really plan a reward. Ah, it's not much. That sucks. It is a token of my esteem.
We shall be the forms the future follows. That sucked. I feel bigger. May we meet again,
my friend. We would have failed without you friend. Nero means well with his quests and his titles.
I suppose we each have to make meaning of this world or impose meaning upon it. Nero is certain
of his path, or at least he's certain he has one for myself. I do wonder. Take this,
a small token of my gratitude. That's a way better reward than yours. What was that creature? The
pieces do not fit. What was that? I feel me. All right. What else? Anything that's down here?
Wait. Important, right? Hold on. Torch. Maybe. Maybe. No. Maybe. I did get some new weapon,
though. What was that? Strength. Always check. Anything is vibrating down here. No. That's
pretty cool. All right. Goodbye. I thought this game was going to be a 45 minute joke game,
but this is actually cool as hell. I would very much agree with you. This has just been sitting
in my Steam. I've just been waiting to play it. Just like, oh yeah. Okay. So I mentioned this
months and months ago. I just had it in my Steam library. And I told you guys before,
there's not going to be like, oh, should I play that today? Am I going to play that tonight?
Maybe another night. I don't know. Might not be any good. No, we're in a new era. A new era of
just play anything. And who cares? Wow. Double swing? Really? Why am I not swinging with this
other weapon? Shit. All right. That looks pretty cool. Shaking. Wait, what kind of gear is this?
This is way too heavy. Is it too heavy? I mean in fat rolling. Might as well just do it. Why not?
Pretty cool. Ancient alloy. 2000. Fine. Oh, look it. It looks cool now. I still haven't unlocked
this one yet either. That's pretty cool. But I got to keep this on. I guess I keep the pants on,
right? Yeah. I like that look. All right. I don't want to blow this. I very much could.
I need to go game progress route. I don't know where that is. Kind of turned around here. This
looks accurate. I guess that's what the gold coins are for. Oh my God. I just swing already. You're
driving me crazy. Swing already. You're driving me crazy. I'm not fucking around. Sorry. Not
messing around. I have no health. You think I'm going to find my way back to this place? You're
dreaming. Exploding. Whatever that is. Now he's being serious. Yeah. Because do you see how far
down I am? I don't remember how I got here. You killed me through the door. I'm going to be
very upset about it. Shit. Can I close the door? I'm dead. I am dead here. No. He turned around so
quickly. I thought I had like another half second. The shrine was right there. All right. Dude,
that's mad embarrassing. It is embarrassing. Okay. Then it was over here and then over here
and then over here and then this way and then through here and then down here and then this way
and this way and then down. Wait, there's this weird person down here. I forgot. Oh God. I'm down
here with the fucking Minecraft guy. 5,000 souls about to be deleted. Wait, I can cheese the hell
out of this. Where are my weapons? Where am I? What's going on with my weapons? They're all
getting I was hoping just for a crit and just killed like three or four of them in a row.
Fuck. Whatever. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Don't worry. Shit. Shit. Minus 5k. It's all right.
We'll get him back. Bullshit. All right. Same deal. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. This time it's
is it this way instead? I think it's wait. I don't know. I went the same way. All right. I
killed the Minecraft character. Does that do anything? Nothing in the water or anything?
Oh shit. Uh, this is a shortcut. Yeah. Right. I'm not going to remember what this is. I mean,
I know it exists though. I'm going to aggro that thing behind me accidentally. Aren't I friend?
Foe? Oh geez. Okay. Green herb. Do you have a shirt on? I'm not going to confirm or deny if I
have any clothing on. Well, I have that do, but not consider. Wow. Interesting. Minus two. Really?
I am so far gone at this point. Yes. I'm going to go over there. Padlock. Oh, there it is. Oh,
this is it. I made it. I made it. I actually made it. Okay. Cool. Oh, I have no stamina.
No, please. Please. Please. No, please. Uh, um, this way. Oh my goodness. Oh my goodness. Touch
it. Touch it. Touch it. Touch it. Touch it. Touch it. Quick. Sit at it. Quick. Sit down. Sit down.
Sit down. Sit down. Sit down. Sit down. Sit. Sit. Sit. Sit. Sit. I can't attack them. I don't have
a good opportunity. Oh God. All right. Thank goodness. I definitely want more stamina. I can
feel it. Uh, tether it here. Now I have a lot of crunchies. I think I'm going to use most of them.
Yeah. Let's use them all. 500. That's it. That's nothing. That was a weird hiccup weapon upgrade.
I don't see anything vibrating. Dexterity. Marking yourself with this willing. Wait,
what does this mean? I did this. I wonder if these are permanent or is it just for a short
duration? Okay. Kill on site. So where is the right way up? Up and around you. Ooh, item.
Leonard's lounge shorts. There's a pair of boxers. I mean, that's a comedy. There's a comedy item.
Comedy items are fine. I'm going to go across. Can I even go across? Maybe I could fall the bird
armor on with the boxers. It's fat rolling still. Where's my weight? There it is. Load 87%. I wonder
how much you need to have not fat roll 76. That's still fat rolling 37%. I think that's mid.
Don't think much is this way. 31. That's actually really heavy. 61. All right. 60%. I think it's
75%. We rate this out of 10. I think it's a little early to say that. Ooh, is something else down
there? Weird. Um, I definitely can't drop the best way to go. I don't know. Is there like a
better way to go? You should be fine if you jump. I was down here. Patience. No, there's no way.
I am absolutely dead. I'm dead. So might as well just laugh. And that was kind of funny.
I can't do it. Oh, you actually can't do it. Why did I even come over here? Well, you actually
can't do it. That person was right. Okay. So where is the right way to go down and around?
I don't know. Is there another? I can go in here. I think it's in here. No. All right. Deeper into
the mine. Just just swing with the offhand. Honestly, the offhand just does way more damage
in the combo. Can you tell me the germa meal? I want McDonald's. Um, grab yourself a McChicken.
Look capable of besting the victims of Nostalgia's decay. The stick figure had
not yet faced a healer. A great one. Such would reveal the futility of everything an old man
and some sticks sought to prove. Oh, it's that guy again. Enemies ahead. All right. I'm not reading
them anymore. Oh, you're going to come help me fight. We help. They like this consequences
for each one of these tether. I can tether him. I don't know what that means. Sure. Why not?
You coming? Oh, that's a lot of people. Are you coming or what? Grindr? What is it?
What are these people supposed to be? That's a guy naked.
All right. Don't die. Don't die. It's music. We do it. Uh, what on earth is that?
Let's go. Holy shit. That was so much easier than I thought it was going to be.
That was so simple. Oh no, it's, it's a joke. It's a joke. What? All right. What do we do? Jesus.
What if my friend dies? No, he's going to die. Oh, one hit, one hit, one hit, one hit, one hit.
Got it. And he stayed alive. The legendary. Thanks for the help. Actually, really thanks
for the help because that probably would have been really hard. Why? Why would you even help?
The Grindr's withered icon. Oh, that was supposed to be World of Warcraft players.
That explains the naked guy, right? What is it? Increases heroic icon uses?
The withered heroic icon of an obsessed hero, Amalgam. There was once something meaningful
about this item. A legacy that can live on in you. Returning this to Astelgaia through her beacons
will increase the uses of your own heroic icon. Interesting. What was the weapon? The Lair
Generic. We were once distinct weapons. Our heroes grouping up beside the tavern's hearth strength.
Very interesting. Um, well, that was cool. I'm going to go. Thanks for the help. These are
probably a bunch of weird messages. Let's find out what this one says. I did it and I can't believe
it. Yes, let's go. Your McDonald's order. Oh, um, McChicken and a large fry.
Uh, maybe a McDouble. I've since tamed my, uh, my McDonald's order.
That helps. Remember a head, but consider pixels. Um, what? A head? I mean, I think I'm just dead
if I walk here. What the fuck? Oh, okay. What is with that aim? That just was targeting me.
I'm trying to survive here. Unburdened. Ooh, unburdened. Oh, it's a quality weapon. Dex and
strength. Does he even know he's streaming? What? What happened? I'm fucking live. I like the sound
effects you make when you run. My crafter. When she discarded all the implements of tradition,
all the tools of craftsmanship that had defined progress here before, I was among the refuse.
Minecraft pickaxe or the bonfire. I'm all right for now. I'm all right. I'm doing good. You are
literally shaking. Uh, watch out for left. Hey, look at that cheating. Like what happened? Why did
my game fucking froze? Oh, my game froze. Um, where do I go from here? I straight up don't know
where I am. Oh, I know where I am. Bridges down that way. Yeah. Okay. Actually I'm going to play
here because I don't want to lose. I'm not, I'm not going to pull the whole room. That'd be so awful.
Okay. Let's do it again. I don't even need to look. Lucky flow state. Oh, shut up. There's no way.
Whatever. You should do an oil tier list. Uh, olive oil S. Um, peanut oil probably high A or low S.
Crude oil. Uh, no, crude oil is probably like, I would say like probably a D. You know what I mean?
That's like a D. Come on, let's go. I got 13,000 right now. There's got to be another bonfire
coming up. I bet. Sunflower oil, seed oils. What about mineral oil? Eh, maybe a C. Don't, don't,
don't, don't, don't. I almost died. All that to get all the way over here and pick this up. But
what about that? The door. Um, what's the right way to go? What about lavender oil? That's not bad.
Are they going to run all the way around? Actually this is incredible for me. This is the best thing
that could have happened. They're all just going to leave. They're going the long way. They're all
coming back. They're all coming back. They're all coming back. They're all coming back. They're all
coming back. Is this a dead end? No. Um, no, I go up. This is so stupid. Okay, let's go. Oh, not you
again. Um, they're all going to make it up here eventually. I got to kill them one by one. What
the fuck was that? I don't know what I just opened, but, um, I couldn't dodge. I just pressed it. I
swear to God. I did just open something. What did I just open something? Anybody know where that is?
That's a shortcut, but who knows where the hell that is. It's a door. It's some kind of door.
Somebody said, dude, did you even try? I like that comment. Dude, did you eat? Nah, I was,
I just like felt like just dying there. Is this this door which leads? No. All right, slow down.
Anybody know anybody know where to go from here to get there? Oh my goodness behind you. So like
through here and then there's another door somewhere. I don't think this is right down there. I don't
remember. I could go across and then to the right, but is that where the door is? This is the way
that I was straight through here, but where's the door? You know, Hey, do you know down there
over there? Um, I think I'll be all right. I'm going to have like 20,000 souls. That shit took
so long. You did this to yourself? Um, I got two heels. I'm fine getting there. Slow as shit right
now. I'm so slow. I'm so slow in the fucking, in whatever the poisons swamp. Okay, we're good.
This is where I left off was down here. I remember this. I don't even give him a chance. Stop being
so cocky. I just killed this guy right here. Don't let him cast that thing and I should be fine.
Okay. Nevermind. Oh, oh, oh, I got disappeared. That was really weird. All right. I'm so close.
I can feel it. I think shaken. I'm going to be a level up like five times this bullshit. I remember
this room. Uh, don't let him do it. Did you do it? He did it. I got full health though. Just don't
be stupid. It's very simple. They have one attack pattern. Just wait. Everything's good. Who are
you talking to? You. I'm talking to you directly. I'm talking to you right now. I'm speaking to you.
All right. I'm almost there. I want to kill everything in this room because you know that
I'm going to aggro it somehow. Some ways stupidly. All right. Made it. Now. Where is it from here?
I remember going in there and freaking out. You got to run all the way up. They throw the bombs.
Yeah. Everything's fine. Everything's shut up. Do not kill me. They're right here. Where are my
souls? Thank you. Okay. Don't die. This person's freaking me out. Oh no. Um, okay. Where is there
a lever to pull? You did it is kill. The hostile guy has been suffering because no one was removing
her pain except me. I try to lift some of the burden from those who carry to gosh darn much,
but actions speak louder than words. Now you're a hero. You, you get that. I have a gift for you.
Relic from a friend I once helped. I have two of these. If you can use it to make
hostile guy a super duper again, then I'm happy to part with it. Don't prick yourself.
Oh, it hurts. Oh yeah. Oh, I can take it. All right. No more of that. No more of that.
I just didn't, didn't know. All right. What about here? So I just said, what a freak.
What you talking about me? 21,000. Let's go. I can level up five times. 25 luck, 15 stamina.
What a mad man. What a bad man. Enemies dropped two times memory. That's going to be amazing.
Look at this thing. Unburdened, unburdened. What's that mean? I know a few things. What do
you think? Should I pivot to something else or this is kind of this thing. And on the offhand is
amazing. I definitely want to keep this in my offhand 110, 109, 500. I don't know. Keep this,
but replace the other thing. What do I really think? This is probably the best thing I have.
One seven. That's a lot of damage though. 176. This is, has an upgrade. 184, 193. Yeah. This
thing is amazing. I think I'm just going to upgrade this. Yeah. It's definitely this.
Okay. Now, um, anything else? What is this thing versus heroic icon uses?
Heroic icon is this thing that I, all right. So how do I use it? Is it the bonfire return icon
release of withered heroic icon back into the world. Wait, what does that mean?
Are we speaking Spanish right now? Hey, when are you going to come to Maryland for some crabs?
I hope this is not going to mess something up. Your own heroic icon becomes stronger,
increasing its uses. Oh yeah. Okay. Cool. Let's do it. Or very nice. I don't think I have any more.
All right. I am ready. I got a new weapon upgrade. I go in here, then we go
up and we go out and then we don't attack this. Let me go up and we continue. I'm really enjoying
this. I think this game is actually really fun. I'm very much enjoying this video game experience.
One more interface. Suddenly. Do I know that? Okay. New area. Maryland crabs are fantastic.
I bet you they are. I can't say I've ever had a crab from Maryland. New England had a lot of
great seafood though. Northeast had plenty of that though. So I mean, I kind of already got
that experience. This looks bad. Carriage door. You guys are strong as fuck. Oh my God. And I
know I said that I'm like 37. You know what I mean? But whatever. I gotta, I gotta use some
of the lingo that you guys use, but did you have them with an old lady? Does that make it better?
No, I have, I did not eat any crabs with any old ladies. Now is this old lady, uh, pressuring me to
use a certain sauce that I don't want to use? No, no, no. You've put, put some of that, put,
put that on there. Put it, you've been, yeah, I gotta put on more than that. I'll try it. Now
there's not enough on there. Put it down. Now let me see. Let me, let me do it. Eating this person.
Can you stop jumping, please? Oh, I like this zone. Castle. Why have you been obsessed with
sauce lately? Who made it? Who made the first sauce is really just when did civilization actually
begin? It's pretty much what that is. That's kind of what it is. Uh, where does this take me?
First thing. All right. All right. Well, that's good to know. Can you do a live yoga stream?
Dude, I'd pull a muscle and I would have to get taken out in a stretcher. So no, I would definitely
be, oh, here we go. It's time. We've got like a whole room full of people and like there's like
30, there's like 20 people in the yoga class, whatever. Oh, and there's the yoga instructor.
And we're going to do a bunch of made up yoga moves that aren't real. And that's like funny.
But at about 10 minutes into that stream, I'm going to go, oh, now we're going to do, um,
you know, uh, the, the twisted Turkey and it's going to be some dumb move. And I'm going to do
it. And I'm going to, you're going to see, I'm going to go, oh, oh, oh, no, no, no, no, no.
And I'm going to roll over my back and then you're going to go to a BRB screen for 25 minutes.
And then it's going to come back and there's going to be me being taken out in a stretcher
and somebody from the crew or somebody else that was there is going to be like, Hey, sorry,
buddy. But like, he pulled a fucking, he like tore a muscle on his knee or something or his leg.
And yeah, we're going to have to stop the stream. Like, see you next time. I don't know. He's
probably going to get, go to the doctor or something. That's why I don't want to do that stream.
You're going to spawn another train, bro. Where are you going? See, I saw it. There it is.
Make it Bugleberry's haunted yoga. This is a bunch of demons. People dressed up in like weird,
like fucking monster costumes. Like in the middle of the yoga class, the door
fucking burst open or like burst down. There's somebody like an adventurer being chased by like
a giant dragon or something or two or three enemies and just fighting in the middle of yoga
and Bugleberry doesn't give a shit. Nobody pays attention to it at all. It's just shit is going
down. Well, I don't know where we are. Like these monsters, like kill the adventure and start like,
eating them. We're not even paying attention. This just happens in this world. First is gold.
Yeah, that hurt a lot. Excuse me. Oh, sorry. That's a hard one. This, I don't know. My
grandfather built this place a hundred years ago. You probably need to add a zero, but I get what
you're saying. Nice. Cracked wall. True. These people, 15 health, I think is probably good.
Yeah. Hey dude, I couldn't help but notice that you haven't mentioned the fact that you spent
$75 on Family Guy, the mobile game you have to stream. What's what gives
it's you. Change makers often have good intentions, but they can't control the pain
their changes bring. You know, it's a cycle. I don't know about you, but I just want to stop
the suffering. Well, I'm a giver like that. The local great one was not a giver. He devoured
Nostal Gaia's memories from within the player housing mansion up above.
Desperate housing mansion. Oh, terrible things. And even the best of us. I know you can beat him.
I believe in you. Oh, it hurts. Don't act like you wouldn't click. Don't act like you're not
going to click to see what happens. Oh yeah. That's why you put all your points into luck
right there. All right. So where's the, where's progress across the hall? Maybe
well, greater the aggregate, everything. The emaciated toothpick felt the bite of
Nostal Gaia's hunger. Stop. You don't just restart the area. Just kill me. I got to go to the,
up into the left. Bad at video games, Andy. Just looking for that one crit. That's all you need.
2000 souls down here. Not a big deal. Like that. Like that. Do you like, uh, crepes? I do. I'm a
fan. I don't remember the last time I ate a crepe, but they're very good. You know what? I like,
somebody might call me a weirdo for this, but I don't think they will. I like savory crepes
more than sweet crepes. Please don't hurt me. Don't hurt me. You've reared your fist back.
You were going to punch me. I just saw you do that and relax. What's, what's wrong with you?
100% agree. Right. Confusion. Nice view. Nostalgia. I'm kind of curious. Does it? All
right. I need to know. Will it take a half of a second to follow the bottom? This is a research.
Is it going to take one 10th of a second to fall all the way? One, two, three, four. It's very far.
Okay. You've seen all the other times I've fallen off. It's like been a magnet fall joke for research.
Yeah. I got it. Can I bypass this person? All joke hypothesis. Yeah. You get it. Oh,
shit. It's you. Oh my, I am a failure. What happened? They do not want me. Look at me.
They do not want any of us. Nearly heroes are with the unproven, the unnamed. We follow in the
footsteps of the greatest protagonists ever conceived. Why fail? I now realize we are only
here to confirm our value. It wasn't I who vanquished the darkness in those minds.
We both know it on the balcony above. I faced a foe. I could not best. She was fast and filled
with conviction though. I did not recognize her story. She threw me down with the skill of someone
whose story should be well known. I can handle this. Go. And I were separated when I charged
into the confrontation. Be wary. If you go forth, I will stay here to be forgotten. The nothing that
I am wrote. Give any idea how much money I've put into this game. This sword alone is worth
probably 15 to 1600 dollars. I'm going to be just fine. You wish to uplift me heroic quest in itself.
It's futile friend. I am no hero. Whoa, wait a minute. I have a shield of inspiration.
Should I give it to him? Yeah, sure. What is that a relic? You would have me remember myself through,
but it can't even remember itself. You wish it's few. Okay, so I need to remember the shield
heart flow altar. So that's in the first area. So I have to get the memory from the shield,
bring it back here, give it to this guy. I wonder what that is. Should I go look for it? That's way
back. Too much work. Well, I feel like this is part two of this quest and I kind of feel like
I want to do it. Yeah, why not? I want to do it. I have no idea where I'm going. Can somebody just
tell me, can somebody give me exact directions? And I'm talking like walk forward five seconds,
turn left, walk forward five seconds, turn right, walk forward 10 seconds to give me all the way
back. It'd be like really helpful. I'm going to try it. See if I can know where the hell I'm going.
I need to tether though, take a ride at the taco bell. Let me tether here. It's back where you first
met that old man. Okay, so I'm here in the theater. All right. Uh, I'm to backtrack. There is that
elevator, right? Which brings me out. Yeah, let's go back. I want to see what happens. I might get a
cool item or something. If I was an item over here. I can't get it. Can you fast travel? I don't know.
That's a good question. Maybe I can. That's a great question. Okay, we're not quite there. I need to
go back even further. You can only TP to your tether. All right. So I remember going, oh,
shoot. It's a boss. It's through here. Let's get out of this way here. Um, okay. I remember this.
Now we go back here. Uh huh. This is where the old man was sitting. Is it here? No, we're all the
way back here. That's not the tutorial zone. Is it? Where did I first meet that guy? It's right after
the tutorial. So right here, this game feels like a, like just dance 2016. All right, here we are.
And we're in this zone. Come on. What does it say? My siblings and I encouraged pledging heroes
through their doubts and toward their purpose. Purpose ultimately found rest in the style guy's
heart somewhere beneath her central shrine. So under low, how do I get under here? Oh, wait a
minute. How do I get down there? Okay. Right here. Yep. Remember. Very cool. All right. So
now I can, how do I teleport back? Do I have an item? This one is a multiplayer. Oh, okay. Cool.
Reminds me of a midi evil for the original PlayStation. I could see that. That'd give us
you. You can't be serious. Stop. Oh my goodness. I just want to complete the quest. Yep. Well,
I know where I'm going. No more stamina. I already, I'm just getting absolutely just dominated by
these people. Okay. All right, let's go. Hey dude, I'm trying to do surgery on somebody. Can you
please keep it down? I'm just in the operating room. All right. Here we go. You wish to uplift
me. It's you. What is that? This is thank you. Thank you. Fellow hero. We are heroes. We, we
together. Our company defines us. Yes, I am the great self named nameless Nero. As with my title,
so too am I the determiner of my actions. Thank you, friend. I shall don this with pride.
For was it not I who vanquished the darkness deep within the minds?
It's true. You did do that. Soon. I shall resume my quest. I will be immortalized in the pantheon of
heroes. You'll be there too. I think. Hope so. Soon you'll be. All right. We make progress.
See you in the next random spot. You're going to be standing. The irredeemable sliver persisted
onward witnessing what nostalgy might once have been and what it had become. Here wings. You are
a weirdo. Hey, I'm currently watching this on a roller coaster. Can you please keep it up? Like,
turn it up. Memory of an NPC zone boss. That's funny. Watching like YouTube shorts on a
roller coaster is, I think, peak 2023. Don't you think? I mean, this is not a YouTube short, but
you know, you get it. Watching a Twitch stream is like, no, what do you think? It's a gamer joke.
Why'd you say YouTube shorts? Because you guys watch YouTube shorts, don't you? No. Is YouTube
shorts the not cool one? You guys watch TikTok? Yes. Yes. Oh, fuck. I'm going to be relatable
to the younger generation and I screwed it up. Shit. Get off me. Blood of a blood of a blood
of a blood. What is that? Applies recursion. Nice try. Brain piercer. Let's try it again. Wait,
I hear something flying. Lucky hit. Why does everybody bite you? Oh, how do I get over there?
I think we're almost at the boss. Something terrible ahead. Oh, it's a toilet. You know,
my buddy stopped watching the stream. L plus U fell off. I just imagine you sitting in a Discord
call with a friend. You're both watching the stream and this friend is just like, oh, yeah,
I don't know. I'm not a big fan of Germany anymore. Nah, I like I'm out of here. Maybe if
you want to play like fucking like a battle of vapex, whatever the fucking game is, just let me
know tomorrow or whatever. And you know what? It's hard to talk and play at the same time a
game like this. So never mind. But why would you be? Never mind. I don't even know what I said.
There's a gun. It's just trash. Stupid. Your job is to talk and play games. You know how hard it
is to talk and do anything? Hey, you know what? My job is whatever I want it to be. How does that
sound? Sometimes I do a comb stream where I just comb my hair. Is that a video game? No.
Sometimes I'm on camera doing something. Is that playing a game? No. He's rebelling. Yes. Yeah,
I am. Yeah, let's go. I'm rebelling. I'm afraid of this room. I can't imagine you on camera.
It's gross. You don't want to see it. This thing's just wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. The ground is moving. This is a lot nicer toilet. Oh, look at failure. Oh, it's Sonic the
Hedgehog. Cute. Funny. That's a cute little reference. I'm okay. Somebody was in the doorway,
but I don't want to go that way because I think that's the boss. And I want to try to see if
there's anything over here I can find, like a bonfire that I can get level up with. And I'm
thinking that's probably down here. Scope cutter. Wait. Oh, it's the Assassin's Creed Unity person.
You have a different weapon. Peculiar world, isn't it? Nero confronted a woman upon the tower
behind us. He fell, but he wasn't broken. What? The being he fought was, I'm not sure. I think
she's connected to something larger. She's not forgotten. That's for sure. Though I worry for
Nero, I think it's time our paths diverge. Oh, no. I met a creature. It called itself the Reservoir
of Pain. It had a generous smile, but a heavy heart. It gave me this blade as a gift. I think
it feels Nostalgaia's suffering in a profound way, but also yearns to ease that suffering.
I can imagine nothing more heroic. Can you? I need to wear better clothes. I look like a fucking
dickhead. Sometimes I feel to try and understand it all like like a finger staring at its hand
or its arm or its whole body. A thing trying to glean its purpose from the thing it is a part of.
Though my body lacks much sense at all. So perhaps I've spun a feudal metaphor.
Voice work is really good in this game. Actually pretty surprising that it is
considering it's, you know, sometimes that's the last thing that an indie developer thinks about is
stuff like that. But it's very, very, very good. Everything's very well done. Feels very good to
play. I can imagine a lot of times if you're an indie game developer and you make this game and
it's like, oh shit, I have to, I have to hire a bunch of voice acting or, you know, however it
works, I guess like an expense. Okay, Roger Ebert, play the game. What the fuck? I am. What are you
talking about? I'm so, that tells it to me so much. Oh, hey, isn't it your, isn't it your job to play
games? Let's talk about like something in the industry. Hey, no, don't do that. Don't do it.
I don't want to hear you say anything about that. All right, now I'm going to die because I'm not
paying attention. I'm dead. I'm dead. And I blame that person for that. Let's have like a conversation
about like, you know, the industry. In the mod chat right now, I'm surprised your chat knows who
Roger Ebert even is. Yeah. All right. I got to get over there before I lose all my souls.
Sometimes the stream feels like how long can 10,000 people bully a 40 year old man
until he turns his stream off? I, I do not agree. I don't agree. What you said was funny,
but I disagree. You've got to be kidding me. And I had an opportunity right there.
There we go. You see that flourish. Yeah. You see that snap right there at the end.
Did you see that snap finish? That was actually bullshit. That was like a double animation.
Cherries. Where did I even die? I hate Jerma. I hope he reads my comment and gets sad in that
person. You know what? How does this sound in that person for an hour? Yeah. But one full hour,
one full hour, and then let them repent and then reduce it five minutes.
Be please land because you just land and mess everything up. Oh my God. That move is so annoying.
I'm just running. No, I need my shit. Hold on. What is this? You tell me this was right here
the whole time. God damn it. This is one of those Superman all arcade games. What does that mean?
I had the exact same question. Am I missing something? Do I like butterscotch? I do.
Butterscotch is good only in very, very small doses though. You can really overdo butterscotch
and it'll ruin everything. All right. Let me go on out here. It's like pesto. Yeah, that's true.
Butterscotch on ice cream, just straight up vanilla bean ice cream with butterscotch hot.
Then you let that rest and then you eat it after it kind of solidifies a little.
You know what I'm talking about? When it gets to that point where it sort of
becomes one with the ice cream drizzled. Let me out. I want to get that item. Whatever.
And then I don't even get me talking about this. At the very end, you have this weird mixture at
the bottom of the cup. It's this weird fucked up liquid, isn't it? Super Mario Castle? It's this
weird, weird liquid that's kind of, if you know, you know, it's kind of runny ice cream, but
weirdly solidified almost butterscotch bits. And it's probably the best part. Where did I die?
Where did I die? Right there. Shot. So sloppy. Okay. I just looked over a chat and somebody said,
take those boxes off now. And I was going to ban you. I was going to have you get banned
because I was like, what the fuck are you talking about? And I'm like, wait, right.
I was about to be like, yeah, big ban. This person's being a weirdo. Like, what the fuck
are they talking about? And they go, right. Okay. But you are right. Okay. What's my total weight?
That's actually not bad. Coward. Coward. Coward. Dead in one hit. Jesus. Almost there. Shut up.
There's no way. Spear enemies are the worst in any video game. Doesn't matter what it is.
Across all platforms, across all genres, across all console generations, across every game,
across every arcade cabinet, across every dice game. It doesn't matter what it is across every
tabletop game. It doesn't matter what it is. Spear enemies are the worst enemies in all media
because spears are superior to swords. Yeah. We all saw, we all saw that history channel video
or show like who would win samurai or a medieval warrior. We've all seen it and we all know that
spear is the best weapon. We all saw that the samurai lost to the caveman. Caveman have club
and raw chicken. And that's, I mean, we all saw it. And then it was the tier list they made and
the caveman came out on top every time. It was weird because they even went as far as to, what
was it? They did like modern stuff too. And the caveman beat modern military person with weapons
like guns and stuff, which is, I don't know how strange. I think it's just the force that a caveman
could swing a club. It was like 600,000 pounds per square inch or something, something crazy,
more than like a dinosaur jaw. That didn't happen. You're an idiot. Well, what did I watch then?
What did I watch then? Huh? What did I watch? I'm being weird tonight. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You got to put these stupid, I hate being up on these rafters. Come on. What worth it? Not really.
Do I have any heels? Cherry. Oh, brain piercer. I can, oh wait, I got multiple memories here.
Quack strut, pixelating cane, concealing a telescoping blade. This is a dex weapon.
Joust. I mean, this is a sorceress, a sorcery weapon, whatever. Is that it? Is there any more?
I'm really interested in this one. Where is it? Quack strut. I really hope I was, I think I,
I think I'm all right. This thing is awesome. I want this. All right. So this is, yep,
is the plan. This is a, like a poke. This is a slash. I think this is the right call. This is
a spear. It's a sharp weapon. Wristless tooth. I hate those things. Um, there's more to do in here.
I need, I need, when you're talking about me having no health, that's when you're talking,
you know, when you're talking about having no health, right? That's what I'm talking about.
When you're talking about the damage sucks ass, but it doesn't matter what's in my main hand.
Anyways, all my upgrades in my offhand. Shit. You know what? Just play it safe. There is an item
over here. And is that an NPC? Holy shit. Everything's fine. I'm, I, I think I died.
No, I don't wanna, I don't wanna, I don't want to fight. I don't want to fight you.
I don't want to, don't fucking come at me. That's the only thing I could think of.
Okay. Thank God. So what is the item? There's another person too. Holy shit. That went right
by my face and I got grabbed. I tried so hard. It was so stressful because I knew I was backing up
into the wall and I didn't know where the staircase was behind me. Something shit.
I don't know how far back I can go. Oh, I don't know how far I am. I'm just going to run. This
is actually, no, no, no. I got the, um, I got the shortcut here. Not as bad as it could be.
That show was called Deadliest Warrior. Yeah. Why can't I, Deadliest War, Deadliest War we're,
why am I saying like Deadliest Warrior? It's not that far. This thing is cool. Should I,
should I upgrade the cane? This is the wrong way, isn't it? This guy stinks. Oh, by the way,
tomorrow, if you did not know, I mentioned it in the beginning of the stream, but let's bring it
up again. Tomorrow is a sponsored stream. I'm going to be playing Wild Hearts, Monster Hunter
kind of game. It seems pretty fun. And I believe I'll be playing it with Vinny. So that should be
fun. This actually was a pretty good question. I'm going to, I'm going to answer it. I kind of,
I can't alt tab. Um, somebody asked, that's not a bad question. What do you do genuinely if a game
sucks? That's a good question. I'm going to answer it as best as I can in about five minutes when
this room is clear. Spear is such a bad weapon. Honestly, give me a club. Shit was way better,
way stronger. Just huge surface area to just hit somebody in the fucking face with. So much better
than a spear. Give me a huge club. Almost there. Now you land. All right, go ahead and do it,
please. You're just not going to do it. You're just going to die. Um, what do you do if a game
sucks? There's a couple of options there. So if a game, when you say sucks, you mean the game is
genuinely bad. Like I can't, I cannot stomach even playing it anymore. Then I will, I won't,
I'll stop. I'll move on to something else. If a game sucks just barely enough, I will typically
stay with it. Cause you never know when a kind of a dumpy game gets, might actually get really fun.
There's definitely been opportunities where I thought the game wasn't that fun. Then an hour
goes by and it's, I'm having a great time. Very, very good example of this was Dark and Darker.
Uh, the first hour or two, Dark and Darker, I was like, this game is fucking an ass. Why do
people play this? And I may have stopped, but I kind of played it for a little longer. And it
was like, no, no, no, wait a minute. This is actually really fun. I really, really like this.
This is awesome. You gotta be careful. You don't know if the game actually sucks or not, or if
you're just not giving it the time and the kind of brain power that it deserves. You never know.
And also everybody has such different opinions on stuff that a game that I say sucks. Oh,
this game's ass. What a terrible fucking game. This might be your favorite game of all time.
Right? Like it could be a thing that you really, really enjoy. So many different opinions. What's
the time tomorrow? Oh, same time. Probably around six. This is the way to get in here. Uh huh.
Where, where did I, I don't know. Where did I die down? No, I came through this way. No,
I never got the item. That's right. I died in here. This is going to be really stupid and really bad
idea, but I don't care. Where's my shit. Goodbye. Was there anything else in here? Shit. I have to
go that way. See you get down to the bottom. Almost there. Ooh. All right. Important. Wait,
anything, anything vibrating? Oh, come on. This staircase just fucking ruined everything, dude.
Why everybody ran all the own? Oh, that's bad. That's very bad. That's so bad. I'm so fucked
here. Wizard, help. Wizard, please. They're all just single file. Dude, help. Oh my goodness. Okay.
I need to do this so much faster than me because he has to, he drank my fucking fluid. So whatever
it was, there's no way. Nope. I have to be a total coward here. I'm sorry. It's scary. It's
intense. I'm sorry. Jeez. Okay. Everything's fine. That was gnarly. I just don't want to run all the
way back here. Hey, we're not doing Bugleberry's yoga class yet. All right. Very, very cool.
Whoa. I didn't even see that. Way too much to lose. Hmm. Do you think? All right. Now let me
actually pay attention to what, uh, I feel like they might be stuff blowing in here. Tooth? No.
Staying in a regen on parry. Please tell me everything you just said again. You've put the
show as your answers or has the struggle to discover been taken from you? Have you been
gifted direction? Hmm. For my part, I seem to remember more as you struggle. There's value in
that struggle. In struggle. I'm certain of it. The past, even in its pain, gives meaning to the
future. I wonder, you have no doubt seen the flickering doors throughout Nostalgia. They are
chasms with no path forward because they hold no memory of what they were. What might happen
if you offered memory back to these, these forgetting spaces? Why don't you try
it? It can be restored. Offering some of your collected memory. Place your stick arm on this
flickering door. You gotta pay. That's it? 50 memory. That's nothing. Like two, that's two quarters. Oh.
I expected as much. Tis not only objects that are forgetting themselves in Nostalgia. Her
hostile denizens may also be affected by your generosity. Your weaponless stick arms do more
damage. They also have other effects. For example, try punching an enemy's shield.
Wait, what do you mean? Unarmed playthrough? Oh, there's another playthrough. That's cool.
The past and future are inseparable. The future cannot be interpreted without the
context of the past. And if the past is meaningful, it is only so because of the
future it enables. Your own meaning, hero, is becoming clearer to me. Restore our memory,
personal, as much as pragmatic request. Restore. I will try. You gave back the useless, ugly
abomination gave back. One of those pothead people. I'm dead instantly. I died in one hit.
This is so far. And it was 18,000. Wait, I did get a shortcut. I forget where it is. I unlocked it.
Ah, it's too late. I don't know where it is. I don't remember. It was right next to the
bonfire. Ah, whatever. We want you to be scared more. You don't get to demand anything from me.
No more demands. How does that sound? It's gonna run. I just aggroed everything here for no reason.
There it is. I'm coming. Be there shortly. Hitbox on that is just broken. All right, where am I
going? There's like, there's three ways for me to go. There's this way, which is where the pothead is,
and then there's up through there. Should I fight the pothead? Don't even start with this bullshit.
Oh, you're so annoying. Back off. Shortcut is through that door. All right. All right, round two.
Let's, uh, win by cheating. Oh my god, you kill. I just crit your weapon. That was stupid. Anti-hero
establishment. Anything glowing? No. New area that way. Gems and jewels. Chasm ahead. Wow, look at
hilarious thing. I want to see the funny thing. Where is it? What is it? Quest reward vault.
Imagine if you can being strung to a thing which you love, but which you cannot save.
Hmm. Imagination requires depth scribble. Five of these can be remembered. Nothing in this room.
Weird. Why do I, it sounds like glintstone. Sure it is. Conversion of it. Oh, wait. How much?
A thousand bucks to open this. Better be worth it. Unburdened. Another one. Okay. Strength and
dex. All right. Is there a bonfire down here? Not. Does the game have powers dancing? It
actually might. Fuck that. I'm just going into the vault. They can fight each other for all I care.
Oh, not you again. All right. What is it? Oh, a lot of anguish out there, isn't there, good buddy?
Oh, geez. Yeah, there is. Oh, remember that sweet sword I gave you? Powerful, right? I can give you
more powerful artifacts. All you have to do is bring me the relics you find that are burdened
with memories. I can absorb their suffering. Their longing. So you don't need to solve their
mysteries. Instead, you'll get to wield super duper awesome versions of them to beat up whatever
bad guys you chase. And their liberated husks won't have any memories left to burden you with.
Win. Wait, what? Unburdened. Unburdened relics are stronger, but lose their lore and special
ability. This cannot be undone. Oh, you turn it in. You probably can go the other way. I'm
imagining there's somebody in the game that can. Because I have three weapons that are unburdened
already. Just for pure damage. Yeah. I mean, that's kind of. Maybe I should just do it to this. Do I
really care what this does? Don't do it. Lore is important. It can't be, cannot be undone. So, oh,
five thousand bucks. Sure. What a waste of money. But is this, does this get consumed?
Is it, can I just put it on or is it like a talisman? I'm afraid to use it. Oh, how did I
not even look down here? Oops. I haven't even looked down here. Uh, health regen.
Probably dexterity. Yeah, how much is that? 20 decks. That's a lot. How much is that giving me?
That's five decks. Oh my goodness. That's a lot. Okay. Nice. Don't you play games for a living?
No, I don't. How could I? Okay. What else is out here? Crown of the undone. New hat.
A pixelating warlock's crown. The murders of my NPC retaliated where his corpses were dumped.
Uh, in the World of Warcraft cave? 8.1 and 11. What does degradation mean? I think this thing's
just better. Very interesting. I'm going to keep moving. I hope there's a bonfire. Easy maker key.
A key to a crate of smuggled easy maker goods. What is that? Depths. Oh, this is another shortcut
somewhere. Good game design, but try patience. Is that a joke? Is that making fun of the game?
Try patience. What? Oh, wait, this wraps back into here. Okay. No. What is this? Some kind of
currency thing? Quest reward vault. Wasn't there a door in the starting area that was flickering?
I think you're right. That's one way. That sound is getting louder. You know what's kind of cool
about this game? It's scratching that from software itch. It just is actually very well made.
This is like really good. It's cool. This is a cool game. What's wrong with my weapon? What's wrong with
my weapon? Why am I holding my weapon so weird? Um, why am I holding it like this? I like this area.
Didn't see me, right? All right. The play here is wait till he turns around. Go turn it on and
everybody will kill him. That's the plan. Fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight,
fight. Everybody come out and fight. Fight. Yeah. Chaos. Chaos. Chaos. Oh shit. You all did it.
Uh, I'm in trouble. I need to heal. Fridge. What is it? Bucko blade. Bucko blade. This is
definitely strength. Yeah. A pixelating really, really, really big sword. My wielder was frequently
sized up at a place where being stung was sought as a delight. Little pink guy. This is so dangerous
right now. Get me out of here. They're following me. How did all of you make it out alive? He didn't
kill one person. He's the hugest guy in this whole dungeon. How are you? Every single one of you is
alive. Oh, there's a wall. There's a wall. There's a wall. Holy shit. I almost got hit. My heart just
like stopped. My game, my game went down. I have to use the, okay. I have to, I'm using the literally
the OBS preview to play the game. My game minimized. I can't see anything. It's on the OBS preview.
Oh my God. How do I pause it? What happened? What? That was okay. That was insane. I don't
think you even saw that. That didn't translate it. My game went down. How many layers are in this
fucking dungeon? Nobody saw it. Weird. My game went down. Oh, I'm putting this on. It's like, relax.
Geez. Right. Oh my goodness. This like hurts my head. And if you see, I think so. Finally,
time for old blade to face the chasm. No, wait, you don't serve my captors. You're one of us.
Never thought I'd meet a young spawn again. Yeah, it looks like I think it is dragon slayer.
No, I had pressed it accidentally. Everything's fine. Face the chasm. No, what a sad ending. That
would have been... Oh, I'm sorry. One of us. Never thought I'd meet a young spawn again. My game
went down. I lost my courage, see? Lost my heroic icon with it. Listen, I can tell you're a good kid.
I've sent enough heroes to know. If you find my icon out there, maybe, could you return it to me?
I want to be meaningful again before this whole thing ends. Do we have it already?
Ain't no reason for me to leave this cell. I'm meaningless.
Honey, if they'd have thrown me in the chasm, at least there'd be no memory of my shame.
Get out there and save the day. Ain't no reason. If they'd have... You still got heroism in you,
kid. I can tell. Get out there. Do we not have his item? Well, somebody will... One of you guys
please remember where this is. Fuck, I will not. Dude, you're a walking Christmas tree.
I think I look pretty cool. This is bad, and I think I'm going to...
Uh, hmm. I think the plan is to just take one of the... Yeah, I'm gonna... Uh-huh. Uh, yeah.
Maybe another time. You went really far back. Um, it's really not. End of the stream, voice?
Yeah, it's probably a good place to stop. What the fuck? Why'd that guy say that? Don't tell
the teacher we have homework. We are going to finish this. You will see this game be completed.
Because I think it's really, really good. 28 luck. Something new. Healing costs nothing. Yeah. Uh,
from what I have gathered, I believe there's only probably... I think we're about halfway.
The game's about 10 to 15 hours, depending on how slow you play. I don't know about completionist
stuff, but it's probably like 12 to 15 hours. I, uh, I would love to finish it. I think it's great.
But that is not what is happening tomorrow. Although, it might. It might happen after.
Tomorrow, I'm going to be playing Wild Hearts, sponsored. First sponsored stream of the year.
It's been about three months or so. Looks really fun. I'm looking forward to it. Hey!
Somebody... I am so sorry. But yeah, uh, Vinny and I are going to be playing it. I think that's the
idea. If there is any changes or any updates, I will let you know. Keep an eye on the sus. That's
the plan for tomorrow at 6 PM. And after that, I might just come back into this. We'll see. Or
maybe we'll play that. Vinny and I might play it for longer. I don't know. We will figure that out
tomorrow. But that's the plan. Sponsored stream tomorrow. And see you later. Can you give it a
rating yet? Um, I don't think you can. I don't know. You can't rate some stuff. I would tell you that
this is worth playing. It's, it's very good. I very much enjoy this game. In fact, I think it's great.
But I don't know. Oh, it's an uh, it's an eight. It's an 8.3. Nah, it's just great. It's just a great
game. That's all you need to know. It seems like there's a lot of kind of depth somehow, even though
it's like a parody game. It's very, very good. Plays very well. Runs very well. It's voice acting.
The story seems pretty, I'm, I'm engaged. I would like to know what's going on. I think it's great.
There you go. Is my review in progress. I think it's great. And with that, I'll see you guys
tomorrow. 6 PM Pacific. Let's check out Wild Hearts. Very cool. Do I have to save it or anything?
Yes. Okay. There we go. Uh huh. See you tomorrow. Take care of yourselves. Call your mother.
Bring some water. Eat a couple of broccoli. You know what to do. We need the music. That's right.
You do. Let me get out of here first. There we go. Save and quit. Okay. And play us out.
Is the entire stream going to be that one game? Probably not. Vinny and I will play Wild Hearts
for a while. I don't know. If we, if I'm having a great time, I probably just won't stop. What if
I want to pivot at some point after I'm done with the sponsor? We'll see. Take care. Good night.
Get some sleep. What about Sorcery and Frog Detective? Well, I did promise Frog Detective
would happen before the end of February or I was going to, I don't know. I was, I don't know. I
was going to do something weird. So that will happen. Write the yoga stream down. I will.
I'm looking forward to finishing this game. What about Sorcery? I know. I got to find a spot for
it. There's a lot of games that I've just kept on the back burner for a long time. The goal is to
play through most of them. You ever practice your voices? Yes, I do. Um, on twitch.tv slash German
nine, eight, five, a couple of times a week. Pretty much what you hear. What about Breath of
the Wild? I'll, I will make sure to finish Breath of the Wild before the new one comes out.
There's your other promise or I will, I will. All right. Good night. Shameless plug. Yeah,
sorry. I'm shouting out a twitch channel here. Is there anywhere to suggest older games? There
is a place for it in the discord. There's the recommended channel. You have something you,
a lot of, I think this game you're seeing right now, I took from recommended a few months ago.
I could be making that up, but I don't think I am. Yeah. I check it all the time.
I always pull from it. Have a great night. See you tomorrow. Take care of yourselves.
If for some reason we play through a lot more Wild Hearts tomorrow, then we will finish
Last Hero of Nostalgia a day or two later. It'll be the next time we finish. Good night, guys. See you tomorrow.