Hello, everyone. Hello.
Hi. He's alive.
Yeah. Yeah.
Welcome back. Been gone for a little while.
Been a little busy, but, you know, those of you that saw all the streamer awards was there in Los Angeles.
Ooh, he was in L.A.
I always feel like that's such a, I don't know, those of you that live in L.A.
You just live in L.A., but those of us that visit L.A., it's I went to L.A.
Yeah, I was in L.A.
Cool. Isn't that cool?
It's like a cool thing to go do for people that don't live there.
Every time you tell somebody you were in L.A., they go, really?
Los Angeles, California.
Yeah. Wow.
Really? No one lives there.
That would be weird considering it's one of the most populated cities in the entire country of the United States.
That'd be interesting. What you said is true.
But yeah, it was a great weekend.
Took a little bit of time. I probably will take a little bit more time, if I'm honest with you.
Not right now, obviously, but we'll go for the week.
Yeah, I'm just turning the stream on just to be like, hey, what's up?
And then I'm out of here. I'm kidding. Stop.
Please address the goblin picture.
I know there's a lot to address.
I kind of had one of those moments where with the thing picture and
it's like, no, that's not real.
That's not a real picture of a person.
That's not a picture of me.
But it is.
If you'd. All right.
Let's let me just talk about the close up Ren and Stimpy detailed spongebob picture.
Or, you know, I've seen a lot of people, I've seen a lot of takes on it.
The CEO rushing out of the courtroom with all the bodyguards trying to get into a limousine to avoid the interviews and the news cameras because of the scandal that they are involved in.
I've heard it all, seen many of them, but yeah, I don't take.
OK, you guys already know this.
I don't take good pictures.
I never have and I never will.
When a photo was taken of me, my face morphs into something else.
It's not even my face anymore.
Me on video versus me in pictures.
It's almost like it's two completely different people that I've never gotten it.
I mean, it doesn't make sense.
You can't take a picture because it's his true form.
He morphs. He doesn't want you to see his true form.
You're literally Bigfoot.
I have my face is really angular, too, like it just depends on what angle you take it from.
You got a bunch of flash in the face, right?
It's all good. I think it's funny that I'm here.
I have a pointy face.
Yeah, I kind of do.
It doesn't also help that I don't even know what I was.
It almost sounds like I'm leaning.
It looks like I'm leaning in, pointing at my ear.
Saying, could you say that again?
Like I didn't hear what the person said.
I don't know.
But yeah, it was a good day.
It was a good weekend.
That legacy award is something I honestly had no idea was happening.
It's kind of funny because I started to understand what was going on when the two
camera guys started leaning down in front of the table we were sitting at and like
rack focusing the camera directly in front of me, like on my face.
Like just right in front of me.
And I'm like, why is this person here?
This person is literally focusing like I can see them moving the dial and they're
right in front of me. Why are they here in front of me?
So it's really cool.
I don't, you know, obviously there's a lot of people in the streaming world and in
the content creation world that deserve that award.
I'm just surprised and shocked that it was me.
There's a lot of other people here.
I wish I could tell you more.
I wish I could say more.
But people have been incredibly nice to me, incredibly supportive to me for a decade.
More than that. And a lot of times I look at it and I kind of, I don't know, it's
like, do I deserve it?
I don't know. It's a weird feeling sometimes.
But I really do hope that whoever's here, whether you started watching 10 years ago,
12 years ago, or you found the channel a month ago.
Cool. I hope you'll like it.
That's all I care about.
Other streamers have come up and said a lot of really nice things that it was, it was
really, I just hope, I hope people like it.
That's all I care about.
And the thing about like other streamers, too, there's a lot of really, really funny
people, really, really interesting people that do this.
And I kind of want to make sure they understand that they are fucking awesome.
There's lots of really cool people in this space.
And although I don't get a lot of opportunity to tell them that, I hope I could this
past weekend. I met people that I watch that say things to me about like how I'm
awesome at what I do, but they are, too.
They really fucking are.
Dude, just cry already.
I knew when I turned this, I was waiting to turn the stream.
I was like, fuck, man, I'm going to talk about those that are going to cry.
No, I'm good. But yeah, I want to make people aware that there's a lot of other
people that do really interesting things, and I want them to know that, too.
Especially the people that I've watched that I have seen lots of their content before.
And it's funny because people are almost surprised when they hear that I've seen
some stuff that they do.
Like, wait, what? How?
You've never seen me. What are you talking about?
Yeah, I have. And what you do is fucking cool.
But anyways, it was a it was a great weekend.
He's always watching.
Tony said, you're the you do you guy.
But it's true.
There's a lot of people that should be recognized that are doing amazing things.
It's time for a staring contest.
Who is your successor?
There is no successor.
There are tons of people that are already doing their own thing very well.
Nobody has to succeed me.
I don't I don't like that.
It's that's weird. That's a weird thing to think about.
Yeah, I saw the Bill Clinton kid, too.
That was interesting.
At first, I didn't know what was going on.
I was really tired after the awards.
And I was just kind of like, you know,
had a couple of drinks and he kind of leaned in.
He was like, hey, he was trying to get me to talk into the camera.
And I think I was like, oh, yeah, what I'm going to do is I'm going to go
and I'm going to get a massage.
I was just saying words.
I don't even know if they were.
I go to like fucking talking about
it was a vodka pineapple.
Yeah, Bansley interview.
That's right. I did.
I need to like think of other things to talk about
when I have nothing really to talk about.
You know, the drink of choice is a vodka pineapple.
Yeah, it's very clean.
It's like, is there anything else you could talk and the gorillas?
Oh, yeah. Plastic Beach is my favorite album.
OK, dude.
What else do you have anything else to say to anybody? Yeah.
We all have the things that we default to, I think.
Plastic Beach, really basic.
I like Plastic Beach.
I think Plastic Beach was hold on.
Don't say that easy.
I don't say that the Demon Days fans are going to be very upset with me.
I think they're both equally fantastic albums.
They go. Yeah, there's not too much more to say.
I'm just overwhelmed with the support that people give me.
And I just hope it's worth it.
I think about it every single day.
How to improve stuff, how to be funnier, better.
But I don't want to get too much in my own head, though,
because I think that's where you get into trouble.
Because I told you before that I got to be funnier.
I've got to be better. I've got to be faster.
I've got to be stronger.
I've got to. At some point, you end up flying into the sun.
And I don't want to do that.
Part of the reasons for telling you guys that this year was going to be
a little slower was because of that.
And then some. So, dude, just keep doing you.
Exactly. Exactly. You get it.
I mean it, though, I really do.
I really do. I promise you do.
That's hey, I'm telling you, it's true.
There's been people that have been here for a decade.
And I don't know.
It's hard to put into words, overwhelming.
That's why I pull out a lot.
That's why I disconnect so often because I need to.
I don't want to get too overwhelmed that I end up.
All right. I pulled back from the Internet.
All right. That's what I was trying to say.
I pull out from the Internet.
I can't. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Excuse me.
Cry on camera.
What if I turn the camera on was bawling for 10 straight minutes?
What people think that would be weird.
And I just I like have the I'm holding the trophy.
I'm holding the award.
It's just crying.
What if that's how I started this stream?
And then I moved on after about 20 straight minutes.
And then I get like I get like I look at it.
I like start to look at the reflection in it and stuff.
And I just sit there and I turn it so you can see me looking
in the reflection into the metal.
Would people leave the chance?
Would you leave?
Would you be like, all right, this is fucking weird.
I'm leaving this. This guy's a weirdo.
I don't want to really be here anymore.
How long into the 20 minute cry with the award in my hands
that before you leave this stream for hours?
My God. All right.
We can move on.
I just wanted to talk a little bit briefly about the streamer awards.
There's a lot of awesome people in this industry.
And I like telling people that
because I genuinely watch a lot of different people.
And I'm shocked that this many people think that I'm cool enough to
or nice enough or interesting enough to even just decide
that that's something that I should have received.
Shocked. I'm floored.
And thank you, everybody that's been here for this long.
Even if you don't like it, even if you fucking came here
and you're like, this guy sucks, this guy's not funny.
Thanks for checking me out in the first place.
I appreciate it. Thank you.
So now we're going to play Diablo 4 if we can
and not get booted in 10 minutes from the server.
We have a contingency plan.
If Diablo 4 does not work, if I get booted and can't play it,
some of you are going to be really excited over this.
And I don't even know if I want to say it,
because I feel like it's going to derail the entire stream.
And I'm just going to play D4.
But I do have to tell you about the contingency plan.
If we do get booted and there's like a 60 minute wait time,
I'm going to go back into the queue
and we're going to play Nancy Drew,
Mystery of the Icicle Wolf in between in the downtime.
By the way, I don't even know if I can capture that game.
I tried to three or four times and it was kind of a mess,
but I got it to work very briefly.
So we'll see if it works.
We're going to hit downtime in the Diablo 4 server,
and it's going to take me 40 minutes to capture this Nancy Drew game.
So it might not even be worth it at all.
We're also going to talk about Grotto Beast a little bit later.
There's a couple of little things to kind of show you
or to let you know exist,
some stuff that something people have been waiting for.
So that's cool.
And I think it's time to play.
This is I don't want to say I'm excited for Diablo 4
because I told you a week or two ago when this was a thing
that I don't want to be excited for this because I refuse to be excited
over a game like this because my entire life revolved around Diablo 2.
And Diablo 3 was like, eh, is that right?
They made a bunch of improvements to it over the years,
but it just wasn't it.
Diablo Immortal came out, thought it was awful.
So Diablo 4 comes out awful.
So let I'm just I have zero.
We're going in with zero expectations. Zero.
I'm here we are.
OK, ready? Character creator.
I wanted to make sure I was in the game,
so I had to kind of get into the character creator
because there was a 70 plus minute wait to get in here.
I wanted to name the character internal temp, 145 degrees.
But as like, oh, yeah, like a fire character.
I don't know. I mean, this is Sorceress.
We're just going to go with internal temp.
We've probably already seen the cut scene before.
You've probably already seen it.
If you haven't, then I mean, this is probably on YouTube.
145 degrees. That's that's meat, right?
Internal temperature of 145.
Is that accurate? Or is that 160, 165?
Give him a real name.
It's the best.
This character is going to get deleted probably in three days.
What do you mean? It needs to be a real name.
This guy is getting deleted, probably.
It's 145, isn't it? All right, let's go.
I am not excited.
Don't get excited ever.
Just let's start at zero. Here we go.
You ready? I mean, it's this one, right?
World tier.
This may be changing anytime for the characters.
So, OK, this is like normal nightmare hell.
Imagining enemies are more challenging, more experience.
I mean, we're doing this one.
Hey, here we go.
I'm not. I don't get excited.
Come on. Sanctuary was never meant for humankind.
It's all right. I'm not.
It was forged as a refuge from the war
and the burning hells.
Instead, it became a new battleground in this eternal conflict.
A secretive group called the Haradrim has kept mortal safe.
But now this once powerful order is a husk of what it was.
And centuries, ancient creators have returned
to claim the hearts of humankind. All right.
This is the story of their downfall.
It's Decker Cane in this game.
Tell me it's Decker Cane in the game.
I just jump scared to shitload of people.
I'm sorry. Well, it's a cut scene.
What am I even doing here?
Decker Cane. If you didn't play Diablo 3, let me tell you something.
Decker Cane. Something happens to him in the third game.
Oh, that's me.
That's not my computer.
I thought I was telling me my computer was overheating.
How did I forget that already?
I need to drink some fucking water. Jesus.
All right. What are the controls?
Oh, I am so excited. I don't even care.
If this game sucks or whatever, I'm here.
I just want to collect loot on the ground and have a go.
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle.
His internal temperature is way too low.
True. The only dialogue we've had this whole cut scene
has been gasping and heavy breathing.
Oh, I should find better shelter before I freeze.
OK, well, I'm going to give you my initial assessment here.
How far can I pull the camera out?
OK, melee range is very big.
Oh, a fine shelter in a nearby town.
OK, let's go. So I'm a I'm a sorcerer.
Melee range is not melee.
I guess. It's like a little.
What is this? Oh, it's just a that's just attack.
OK, you're going to do face cam.
I'm doing I'm only doing face cam for like the first 10 minutes.
It's just game viewership.
And then it's going off.
Oh, OK, I don't want to hold all.
All right, I'll tell you that my initial reactions to the one swing,
the few swings on enemies and stuff, I love it.
Well, hold on. No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's a weird way to say that.
So one thing that they added in this game that I don't know if, you know,
you could turn it off in Diablo three.
You're probably noticing that every time I attack an enemy,
they don't light up like a Christmas tree.
I'm so glad that I can turn that off.
I don't know why we decided to put that in in games.
Like, let me I'm so glad I can just turn it off.
I hate that so much.
Everywhere, things in the dark.
Keep it on now.
And there's no screen shake either.
I turn that off, too. He's a wild one.
I said, is it too loud?
I think it's too loud.
What's going on here? What's it to you?
Also, and hush.
I'm sorry, Wanderer.
You've come at a difficult time.
This madman just stumbled into town and started causing trouble.
Demons spilling from the ruins.
Kill us all.
Interesting. Ruins.
What is he talking about?
Come, I'll explain.
Turn it up. It was OK.
OK, I'll put it a little higher.
There is evil staring in the room.
All right.
That poor monk back there must have gone inside.
In this game, it's like MMO.
I know it's like MMO, whatever he saw is like MMO internal temperature here.
Right.
Oh, wait, I'm going to slow down.
All right, that's the heel.
If Devmir is taking up all the space by the fire, just give him a shove.
What's that? You say something.
OK, fire is looking good, but I should watch it a little longer
to make sure it doesn't go out.
All right. Could you protect us from whatever is out there?
We have nowhere else to turn.
There is evil lurking in those ruins.
I will drag it into the light of day.
Oh, thank you.
Are you wearing a periodic periodic table?
Oh, this is this is embarrassing
because this is a periodic table of all the Star Wars characters that's ever existed.
I don't know why I own all these shirts.
I don't know why I have all these.
I think they were I think most of them were gifts.
That's a shirt for a 12 year old.
It's you know, maybe one day I'm going to give all these Star Wars shirts to somebody.
It's going to kill me.
Gold. Oh, it's heels.
OK, Q is an instant heel and then it's a heel over time.
That's interesting.
Didn't I level up? Hold on.
I leveled up, didn't I?
I want to compare. Oh, I don't have gloves on.
All right. Abilities on Earth.
OK, hold on a second.
So this is the skill tree.
I guess I have not looked at anything of this game.
I know absolutely nothing.
I saw like two or three little videos just kind of describing the game as it
sort of turned into what it is today.
But I've deliberately avoided almost everything.
So it looks like it's a big.
So you start up here and then you can go down this way and then this way
and then this way and then this way and then this way and then this down here.
OK, well, what can I do? Spark.
Is that what I have right now? No.
Launch a bolt of lightning that shocks an enemy four times.
Frostbolt. Oh, firebolt.
It's kind of like the character's name is internal temp.
It makes sense for me to have this flaming and it's a burn and Arc Lash.
What do you think? Should I go? Let us pick.
OK, what do I do? Let us choose. Yeah, that's fine.
Thematically, it does kind of have to be firebolt, but I'll let you decide.
Spark, frostbolt, firebolt or Arc Lash.
Let's go pull up two minutes less than two minutes.
Unleash arcing lightning that does 13 damage to enemies in front of you.
Every 10 times Arc Lash swipes, it stuns all enemies.
Why does it seem like the best thing here?
It is the best one. Yeah, but do we want to?
I don't want to do the thing.
Wait a minute. I might veto this.
Does every sorceress that you've seen on Twitch pick this?
Because I want to I don't know, I want to do something different.
Enhanced spark, percent crit strike.
You're going to make the worst character.
Why are you such a hipster?
I'm not. I just don't know.
It's a beta. I want to be able to showcase the other stuff.
What about down here?
Incinerate. Are these out of five or are these just three points?
So what it would be would be eight points to max it out.
Those are one. OK.
What is the cap? 50 level 50 is the cap.
So you realistically, realistically, you really only could be able to add level 50.
Only get a handful of these, right?
Interesting. OK, so you really have to kind of decide.
We want fire. What is it at right now?
All right, we'll go with fire.
That's what I would have picked anyways.
All right. Fire bolt.
Here it is. Oh, so this is now here, but I want it here.
Oh, it's locked.
Oh, how much man it is to use.
Oh, yeah. So Nancy Drew is a game that we're going to be checking out today.
Diablo four happens to be not functioning that as we have intended.
Nancy Drew is going to be the game that we are going to be taking a look at today.
God damn it. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on. I think I'm still in.
Am I still good?
Wait, I think I'm still good.
Shit, I really wanted to play Diablo four.
What does that mean? Just restart the game.
OK. Well, we start restart the game.
Won't I have to go back into the queue for like a fucking hour?
Don't restart, people saying.
I unlocked one move and I know I can't play anymore.
Shit. It says restart.
You need to restart. You're playing day one.
Well, I mean, day one of two days for a beta.
It's not it's day one of two or three days, one of three.
OK, I'm going to just restart it and see how long it takes to get back in.
And then I'm going to play Nancy Drew three days next weekend.
Yeah, it's still all right. Let's try it.
I'm hoping for like less than five minutes.
I was just getting good.
That felt like it felt good from what I was walking around.
All right. What's what's the queue?
Oh, we got a queue of only nine minutes.
Let's open up Nancy Drew.
Why does it just get it open?
Here's one big problem.
This game was made in like out of like 1996 or something.
So I don't even know if I can see this.
Since you can tell a lot about a person by where he or she lives,
I thought I'd introduce myself by showing you my room.
As you can see, I keep it pretty neat.
Of course, I don't spend that much time in here.
I always seem to be off solving.
No, anyway, here's yes, you can.
Don't lie to me right now.
I can't all tab. Don't lie. Stop lying.
My desk. Go ahead and poke around.
If you want to know the particulars of how I do what I do,
take a look at the book titled How to Be a Detective.
It's real helpful, especially if you're new to the mystery solving.
This is Nancy Drew and the check out my scrap history
and the mystery of the wolf in the icicle cave or something.
I don't say anything about it.
And I said, head to the Icicle Creek Lodge,
a small guest lodge deep in the Canadian Rockies of Alberta, Canada,
and try to figure out why so many accidents have been happening there.
The woman who runs the lodge, Chantal Mowee,
he called me out the blue, saying the bed and I can't even read
fucking English words from Shadow Ranch and it's recommended.
I'm so flustered right now.
You sound so desperate that I couldn't refuse.
It's something with the way the words are blurry and I can't read them.
She said she was on her way to Edmonton to meet with her lawyers.
So her handyman, Ollie Randall, will pick me up at the airport.
She told me it's been really cold and snowy there
that I should pack accordingly.
And then she said something about a wolf.
The connection was getting really bad and I could barely hear her.
But I'm pretty sure she used the word prowling or was it howling
along with dangerous and be careful.
Couldn't you have just said she told me to be careful of the howling
and it might be dangerous?
Why do you have to do all this weird prowling, howling, dangerous and be careful?
She just said one sentence to you.
Like, why do you have to break it up like this?
OK, but wild animals, I hope I know what I'm getting into.
OK, how do I do it?
I just fucking exit to the goddamn game.
I didn't thank God. OK.
Oh, there it is.
So get on the plane.
The junior level provides a lot of help and hints.
Most more experienced players may enjoy playing the senior level.
I don't want to click this because it makes me feel old.
I don't want to click this because it's going to be like two plus two equals four.
When Chantal told me you were just a young thing,
well, I thought she was pulling my leg.
But you're not much older than my little girl, Freddy.
Well, if one of the people at the lodge is to blame for all those accidents,
Chantal thinks somebody like me has a better chance of figuring out who it is
and somebody more, you know, hard nosed.
Chantal has a bad habit of making up her mind
without thinking things clear through.
No need for you to tell her.
Look at the road, dude.
Is she still in Edmonton?
Afraid so.
Insurance companies given her and her lawyers a real hard time.
Left running the lodge up to me, which is why I'm not real crazy.
Oh, my God.
I knew underfoot, especially if something else happens.
I won't be underfoot, Mr.
Randall, and I may be young, but I'm no novice when it comes to solving.
I'm sorry if you look over at somebody in the pastor's seat.
One, two, three, or it's that's the car spinning.
What actually happened there?
No, ma'am.
Everyone here at the lodge is accounted for.
He said he'd know more after the lab was done running tests
on the debris he collected.
He did say the blast was pretty powerful.
And he slide up to the back door, clear out on the highway.
You sure you don't want to give your daddy a call?
Well, I was thinking that maybe I'd just be your new maid.
How's the audio give me access to everyone's room?
And I could question people without making them overly suspicious.
The phone's not connected to anything.
I think that's a fine idea, ma'am.
I'm going to be pretty busy trying to get rid of that wolf, Chantal.
We heard it. How that sounds like stir doing one of his voices.
Everybody all right?
OK, I'll get you a master key and leave it in your room.
If you need anything else, I'll be in the basement.
It's stir's wolf voice from when we played that game.
The only thing I can hear. OK, mystery.
What's this key?
What's this? What's that? What's this?
What's that? What's this?
What's in there? What's that?
What is this? What's this thing? What's that?
What's that? There's a key inside of that.
Open that key here.
This must be the key.
All he said, he'd leave for me.
And this must be a list of which guest is in what room.
That'll come in handy.
OK. All right, we got a clock here.
Nine. If I can read it, it's nine fifteen.
We don't have any information for this yet.
What's this? Daily cleaning, pick up laundry bag at the front desk.
Available after five forty five a.m.
Enter and clean only those rooms displaying the housekeeping sign.
Make the bed. Wait, I actually I actually have to do it.
I thought I was just pretending to be the maid.
I don't actually have to do this, do I?
Skating pond maintenance.
Do you want me to be doing a little bit of everything while I'm here?
I thought that I was just
I thought part of this routine was I was going to pretend to be the maid
so I could go in and question people.
All right, whatever. OK.
On must be shoveled out after every snowfall.
Some sections of ice would be very thin due to hot spring activity.
Pay close attention to the color of the ice
and only shovel off those areas which are safe to skate on.
The shade of the ice will reveal how many adjacent ice grids
have dangerously thin ice.
Mark these areas with an orange safety cone.
OK, so we don't want to. This is bad.
So at what point is it safe to skate on?
Oh, my goodness.
Diablo is still
I have authentication pending.
I don't think we're getting that anytime soon.
This color means that there are three patches of its minesweeper.
Report all avalanches to the Avalanche Patrol.
Do not make loud noises when in the backcountry where snow shoes.
Can you imagine if this is what a clock sounded like?
This thing would be smashed in a second if it was near me for more than a minute.
Report any criminal activity.
OK, I can't even think when that's in my ears.
Employees should remember that heat and moisture
sometimes cause the door to the side of the stick.
Check to make sure. Is this giving me all the solutions to the puzzles?
This is puzzle solutions.
Breakfast is served from seven to eight.
Lunch from noon to one. Dinner from six to seven.
OK, I think I just crashed my computer.
All right. Oh, no, this is very loud now.
Oh, don't worry, guys, I'm going to kill three more skeletons
and we'll play Nancy Drew again.
Ocean Chargers, that's right.
OK, you can only have up to four. Got it.
Let's check over here. What is A?
Oh, right, right, right, right.
Whoa, guys, Nancy Drew is still open in the background.
That clock is ticking into Nancy Drew's AI brain
and she just has to sit there.
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick.
It's still open. Oh, don't worry, it's open.
I'm making sure I'm prepared now.
Um, I think I'm just going to do that one in here.
Yeah. How many points to get? Oh, I already can.
All right. I think I'm going to be a weirdo and just do this five times.
Doesn't Nancy Drew have a day night cycle?
I'm going to laugh my ass off if we go back over there.
It's like 12 days have passed.
Just staring at the clock.
What a miserable fucking life Nancy Drew has right now.
I'm so sorry, Nancy.
He's better. Yeah, he's stuck in purgatory.
Actually, it is kind of loud, isn't it?
Just a little, just a little bit, just a little chest.
Oh, uniques.
OK, so search the depths of Icehowl Ruins.
The games are blending together for me.
I feel like I'm in Nancy Drew.
I feel like I am Nancy Drew right now.
Icehowl Wolf. Icy.
It's like the same thing.
Guys, just pretend that we went to go investigate the wolf.
It does feel pretty fun to play so far, but let's not say that yet.
The first 10 minutes of Diablo 3 were fun, too.
Were they? Yeah, they were.
I would be lying if I didn't say that they weren't.
It definitely feels a little slower than D3,
which is a good thing.
They really took it in a new direction.
It's like a dodge roll.
Oh, shit, hold on. It's like a.
What?
Deep demons.
Oh, that original sound.
Wait, I want to check over here.
Skeleton captain with the loot, with the items.
This is pretty much a Roblox gameplay.
It is not Roblox gameplay.
Actually, just take it.
So true.
Shit. OK, hold on.
I do like the fire.
I need time.
Yeah. How much time?
Oh, it's five seconds. OK.
Yeah, I need some splash damage or something.
Oh, shit. First blue ever in D4.
So what is the itemization like?
What does it look like?
Thirty six armor, four decks.
OK, he's better than I have item power.
OK, take arc last year.
Mo should help with mobs.
Hold on a second here.
I have a lot of choices here now.
Incinerate. This is a flamethrower.
This is kind of better than this.
But this is a this is a damage on it.
Refund fireball is better than fireball.
I think firebolt maybe with the damage over time is good.
Is Nancy all right?
I think this is all right.
Don't stack bolt.
So this is 19.
This is 17 and 14 of it is over eight seconds.
So I definitely want to go for.
Wait, what about the other ones?
Frozen orb? No, I don't think so.
That's not bad. I don't need it right now, though.
All right, we'll go fireball.
And then should I refund this?
I don't think I can.
So now I can go, but it probably costs a lot of mana, though.
All right. That's why you do.
I get it. All right. Cool, cool, cool, cool, cool.
Let's go.
Yeah. Only if you have no mana.
Yep. It's a good way to put it.
Yes, yeah. All right.
I understand. I get the rotation.
It's a good sound effect.
I do appreciate this for dummies like me
that walk in circles and forget where I just was.
I do appreciate that lightning resistance.
Where are my here we go.
Well, these materials, strength.
So resistances are in the game.
That's cool to know.
Yeah, well, I'll check. I'll check on Nancy.
I will. I promise.
We just open up the other game and she's just screaming.
Where? OK, I've been over here this way.
Dude, she's wolf food now.
Tick tock tick tick. Go start a Nancy timer.
No, we're good. We're good. We're good.
I can do that two times before I have to do it again.
I think mana potions probably, right?
It's so funny because I can do
showing Nancy Drew was just going to be.
That was a bad idea because now everyone knows
that she's just sitting there looking at the clock.
I am curious, though, because I really do wonder
if there's a time limit on that game, that's going to be very funny, too.
So let's see how it plays out.
This is what we want.
I'll tell you that this this is fun.
This is this is fun to play.
This is a thousand times better than Diablo immortal.
I mean, and I mean a hundred million times.
I like I'm not excited yet.
Don't get excited.
You haven't played Diablo in a while.
That's why it's fun.
I'm not excited yet.
In fact, this, you know what I mean?
Lucky hit chance.
What is is a lucky hit a crit lucky hit?
I don't get it. It's a baby crit.
OK, well, so something.
Another thing I want to ask, which is important.
I didn't really think to ask this question originally.
This is not because Diablo three was like weapon power
is what scaled everything.
So this is just for damage and burning for 16 damage.
Is it like Diablo two and they just kind of got away from that
and its skills just do damage and you get plus two skills?
Or is it based on your weapon damage?
It is weapon damage.
It's weapon damage and intelligence.
I never played Diablo in my life.
Ask Nancy.
Oh, I'll ask. Yeah, I'll ask her.
Yeah, let's see what she says.
She's been reading this note.
It's still nine thirty, so no time has passed.
Only one guys, only one minute passed.
It's fine. All right. We're fine.
Wait. OK, hold on. It's nine thirty two.
Wait, I need to save it.
I need to know. I'm saving the game. OK.
We're going to let this run and see what happens.
Check back on her every 30 minutes. OK.
That sounds like a good idea. We'll see what happens.
She's looking at a wardrobe right now.
I'm curious what happens.
Six months are going to go by. She hasn't left her room.
She's going to be a skeleton when you go back.
That's it. Was that a yellow?
Oh, what? What Nancy drew in the corner?
I wish I could do that because that would be very funny.
It'd be a very interesting little joke to do today.
That game is so old.
It takes over the whole computer and it makes your resolution.
It just ruins the resolution on every screen.
And I just it's not possible.
It's like you put Diablo in the corner then.
No, you don't understand. I can't.
I can't like I cannot interact with any screen
when Nancy Drew is active on a monitor.
Put it in windowed. I tried. You can't.
It's too old. It's a cool little first boss.
This is cool.
I wonder how many difficulty tiers there's going to be.
Hi. All right.
We got to split this gear up.
I know it's all right. All right. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, yes.
OK, so who's going to get what?
I mean, you're the rogue.
So you definitely take the dagger and I'm a sorcerer.
So I probably get staff, but I'm just relaxed.
It's really I'll take it so I can identify it.
And then core skill damage.
I'm imagining that's just abilities, right?
Because what core skill I'm imagining is these are not core skills.
That's all right.
I feel like it's not worth a point right now.
I just beef up fireball.
Oh, core core. I get it. Yeah.
I don't want to spread out too thin.
I think it's just fireball.
After casting a non-basic skill, you gain two percent resistance
to all elements and one percent additional resistance to that skills element.
That's not number goes higher when you click on somebody boring.
Let's do it with fireball.
That was pretty cool. It's fun.
I'm very much enjoying this more than I, I don't know, stop saying things.
I don't want to look back six months from now and be like,
remember when you played Diablo four and it's beta and you were like,
wow, oh, my God, it's so good.
And then you, you know what I mean?
I'm just going to this is I'm having a I'm having a good time.
I'm having a good time.
Your town should be safe now.
Truly by the centrist, Andy, I've that that's not even a step.
I'm just having a decent time playing the game.
I think it's fun so far.
That's me taking a take. That's a take.
Somebody get Nancy Drew on the fucking line.
There's been a murder.
What's wrong with me?
The hell is going on?
Turn it up.
So what? This wasn't a town after all.
This was a is this like a
they kind of like poisoned me or are they going to like sacrifice me or something?
Mother's blood, my mother's body.
So shall you witness her glory
before you die.
I'm not ready yet.
Coming to hold them to fill it.
Get up. We have to fight our way out.
Is the light preserve us?
Lost souls, all of you.
Oh, good.
Oh, a leather doublet.
I think that's better for me.
That was cool.
That was creepy. Interesting.
That was all of them like willing.
Oh, hold on. Wait a minute.
Oh, more healing received.
Oh, it's a dagger.
I need to put that on the bar, don't I?
Hmm. Am I ever going to be doing this?
Probably not ever.
You're the madman from the shed.
Madman.
Those heretics drugged me after I returned from the ruins.
Just like you.
I came to my wits.
You've adopted so far.
Try to get inside the chapel, but it was locked.
Manner of evil is this.
What petals?
I don't think that came out that way.
Hey, that was to fed them to me.
A blasphemous ritual.
How did they learn this?
Perhaps the answer lies in the chapel.
They kept it locked up for a reason.
The key might be on that woman who was leading them.
Mute your mic.
No. OK, look, the chapel key from the corpse.
Oh, cool.
Yeah. What else is going on over here?
Why does it want me to go over this way?
Oh, um, isn't beta only fire.
The smart thing to do is just always have your game in zero point nine, nine, nine.
It's just you never in one point.
It's still, you know, blood petals like the ones I was fed.
Don't ever come out of it.
Is this real? Nancy Drew would have solved this.
Those who they're asked.
Yeah, I'm playing the Resident Evil 4 remake on launch day.
Get your ass. That's happening.
Shameful. Our father has granted you a path to salvation.
And yet you stray from it at every opportunity.
You drink and gamble.
You covet and steal.
Shameful. So if you eat these, you
sin is their birthright.
What about God? Oh, my God.
My children of hell are coming to devour our salvation lies, not in the light.
But in you, the faith has taught you to deny your heart's desire
and turned you into a prisoner within yourself.
She's made out of wood.
Break the chains and discover who you were meant to be.
Break the chains and be beautiful in sin.
What are you doing?
Resist. Resist her temptation.
Lani, it's me.
I brought your child into this world.
What's going on?
Why is the audio so slow down?
My God, they just destroyed this guy.
Go to the dry steps and continue your preparations.
Now true work begins.
Hey, guys, only only one minute has passed in the world of Nancy Drew.
So, hey, guys, one minute in Nancy Drew time is an hour in real life.
Right. It's like the time is passed slower here.
Let me just go ahead and do reconnect.
Let me just start the queue again.
And it's it's just going to get longer and longer, isn't it?
It was P.M. before. Was it?
No. Yes, it was.
No, it wasn't.
Give me a second. I got to just reconnect.
It's so funny, like immersion.
Like this this unbelievable.
OK, it's a 20 minute queue, by the way.
This amazing world of Diablo and all these these crazy cutscenes.
And it's the immersion just gets just snapped out of reality.
What is just like, and let them come, let them try to find us.
We will be buried into the caverns like.
You've been disconnected.
It's a video game. It's a video game.
It's like, oh, shit. OK, it's a video game.
It's right. Damn it.
It's a video game.
And I'm connected to a video game.
Do you actually want to a movie?
And 10, 20 minutes of the movie, there's a very touching scene
with this like a very insane scene.
Something crazy happens.
And the movie, it's like, wow, like, like Thanos, like
And it freezes on Thanos doing this with like the Infinity Gauntlet.
And it just it just says, ladies and gentlemen,
I would like to remind you that you are watching a movie.
This is a movie.
And isn't it an interesting one?
Now, please use the bathroom.
Please go and get some snacks at the concession stand.
We'll be back in 20 minutes.
It's like, I was fucking watching that.
That's kind of how it feels like playing like a day one launch sometimes.
OK, I'm ready.
No, it's I'm clicking out of the window. Come on.
All right. So what are we doing?
Am I like opening this person's door?
I have to call Ned.
No, we're not doing that.
This must be where I drop the laundry bag after I'm done cleaning all the rooms.
This shoot is for dirty laundry.
OK, so we're going to clean the rooms.
Well, huh? What was that?
What was that?
I got to clean the rooms.
Don't have the key.
How do I get in here?
You have to make breakfast first.
Bone, which Trapper Dan found near the lodge.
He believed it came from a race of giants known as Rex's.
The bone's not there.
Wonder what happened to it.
Find the bone.
So I've been playing a lot of Diablo.
Blue, red, white, green, blue, red.
I somebody remember that one.
Hmm. How would you read that?
That's not it. That's like a two point font.
Sasquatch sightings hit five year low.
Area man attacked by Wolverine.
That's just the name of the next Marvel movie coming up.
Don't forget to catch area man attacked by Wolverine in theaters this Friday.
We're getting there.
I think that's hello.
Well, hello there.
You must be the new maid Ali told us about.
I'm Bill Kessler.
This guy's Lou Talbot.
Hey, what's your name again?
Nancy, Nancy Drew.
Just thought I'd come over and say hello.
Well, Lou, here's a grad student.
Art major of all things.
You're probably going to need a jackhammer and some hydrochloric acid
to clean his roommate.
Are you two old friends?
Not hardly. I've known Lou for all of what?
But a week, I guess.
I checked in right after he did.
We sat down after breakfast one morning and discovered that this fox
and geese game is pretty darn fun.
I've been whipping his tail ever since.
Hmm.
You didn't just come here to play games, did you?
Heck, no.
I came for the ice fishing.
Of course, knowing there's a renegade wolf running around
is kind of damp in my enthusiasm.
Have you seen the wolf?
Just heard it every night since I've been here, in fact,
gets creepier each time.
They should get rid of it.
And the sooner the better.
They didn't put up with wolves prowling around this place 40 years ago,
and they shouldn't put up with them now.
What are you, Little Red Riding Hood?
That wolf's not hurting anybody.
People should just leave it alone.
You'll be singing a different tune when it has some little kid for breakfast
than has you for lunch.
Not going to happen, dude.
Trust me, if something bad can happen, chances are it eventually will, dude.
Hey, I know what you can do.
Shovel the snow off the skating pond so we can do some speed skating.
Lou here thinks he's faster than me.
You're like ancient.
Course I'm faster than you.
You may have youth on your side, my friend,
but I've been working construction since before you were born,
which means I am more fit now than you will ever be.
Go shovel the pond.
Get that pond shoveled so we can settle this.
OK, kiddo? Consider it done.
OK, so we got to shovel the pond.
Not time for kitchen duty yet.
OK, wait, where's my schedule?
Oh, shit, this is the key. All right.
OK, OK, OK, OK.
All right. OK, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I want to turn the page.
I want to turn the page of the book because I want to see the my schedule.
Turn the page. I can't turn the page.
OK, I can't turn the page.
There's no more pages. Yeah.
Where wouldn't it like a telling me all these things?
I can't do the kitchen yet.
What is this here?
Do I have to get everything?
OK, I think I have to get everything the same animal.
OK, so it's I got to make this and I got to go like this.
Oh, shit, it's going to be all moose.
All right. Hold on.
I got to get this to the right spot.
So to get all mooses, all meeses, most mooses, moose.
It's just moose, right?
Me all moose, all meese, meeses.
All right. You're distracting me.
OK, let's figure this out.
If I need to do all moose, fuck it.
I'm so torn apart in like three directions.
OK, I need to get a second.
OK. All right. I'm ready.
This needs to be so to get this all.
So I need to get this. Let's go like this.
It's raccoon, raccoon, raccoon, raccoon, raccoon.
There we go. Now there we are.
OK, Izzy wasn't even hard.
I messed it up. I got it.
It's not it's not all meeses.
Needs to be all raccoons, all wolves, all pigs, all raccoons, all mooses.
What is it? Is it wolves?
It's definitely wolves. All right.
Everything is ready. I just have to move it.
It's definitely why would it not?
Why would it be moose?
The whole game is based around this ice wolf in the forest.
OK, let's get it.
Shit, that's all wolves.
I don't think this is I don't think we have the solution to this yet.
Worth a shot. Chicken Ridge.
OK, so they want me to go outside.
I could do that.
What is that?
Is the lake better not follow this trail until I know for sure where it goes.
Oh, you'll be fine.
Just bring enough sandwiches to last you there too.
OK, here we go. It's getting fun.
Don't ever underestimate our four
bologna and cheese sandwiches wrapped in like sandwich wrap.
Don't underestimate it.
Guess I better get this pond shoveled off.
OK, so I need to.
How do I do that?
It's like it's like Minesweeper, but how do I have to hold click?
Holding click is not doing anything.
Bash it with the shovel.
Start in a corner.
Oh, shit. OK, so this is unsafe.
I don't touch that one.
So this is unsafe.
How do I know it's safe?
Just don't step on that.
So wait, this is safe.
This is unsafe.
He's never played Minesweeper.
I mean, I've played the amount of time that most people that have a Windows
machine played Minesweeper and as you opened it for 10 seconds,
put it on the highest possible difficulty and then clicked in one spot and lost.
Or you put it on the lowest possible difficulty.
Click in three places and win.
I understand the concept of Minesweeper, but like what am I trying to?
I guess I'm just right.
OK, so that means that there I don't even know what this is trying to tell me, though.
All right. So this is a little bit.
This is kind of this is. Yeah.
Yes, but I'm OK now.
I just got a little wet and cold.
Actually, I got really cold.
My lips turned this really interesting shade of violet.
What I know.
I'll be more careful next time. I promise.
You don't mean if you don't want to concern your employer,
you don't say, you know what I mean?
Like, oh, yeah.
Hey, so everything OK? Oh, yeah.
Hey, dude, my lips turned this really crazy shade of purple.
It's like, huh?
What are you talking about?
That was that was like a funny thing for Nancy to say.
That was like, oh, my lips turned purple.
Now, are you all right?
No, no, no, no, no.
You got to go check.
We got to check you out at the doctor.
Guess I better get this pond shoveled off.
OK, well, and fun, Nancy.
See you in a little bit.
Don't worry, Nancy. We absolutely will be back.
See you in probably 30 minutes.
She's freezing. She's fine.
There's a timer.
I don't think the game.
Here's the thing.
I don't think the game is active if it is alt tabbed.
I think we're going to be fine.
I believe the Nancy Drew client has to be active.
My lips turned this wacky shade of violet.
Only fire can cleanse the darkness.
I can do that.
Have a look inside.
But hurry, I will prepare the torch.
Blood petals like the ones I was fed.
Here, we already saw this on this real.
We already saw that.
You came to thank the light.
You collapsed inside.
I thought that darkness had swallowed you.
OK, we are good.
Why do you skip?
We not see that one.
Oh, shit. That's right.
It happened. Oh, that's right.
Oops. Can you say it again?
Oops. He surrounds himself as it ended.
I forgot. Sorry.
Tread carefully and pray he has not fallen to Lilith as well.
It's a beta. We're going to see this all in a week or two anyways.
All right. There's a hermit that I have to find.
Lilith Lilith is able to manipulate people.
She's the lord of manipulation.
Lord of all right.
Permanent stat boost to all characters on the realm.
Maximum capacity of murmuring all balls.
Blame and alter of Lilith.
OK, interesting.
This is permanent reward.
Lucky commoner player title.
All right, let's keep going.
Very loud.
Guys, it's still so loud.
Every time I restart the game, it gets louder.
Greetings, gold Thunder Bear out of manor.
It's an elite.
Can I say how do I sell stuff?
This looks like a granny like.
I can assure you it's not.
Nancy Drew is more a granny like than this.
That's actually in fact, all of your hits are crits.
Cool. Going fast to random dungeon.
Sellers are small chambers that can contain a wide range of content.
Let's check it out.
Yeah. Yeah.
Turtles have his engaged skeleton captain.
Yeah, I'm not.
OK, that was just like an elite.
Anything else in here?
What do you think Nancy Drew's internal temperature is right now?
Probably low. Slain militia.
Ooh, try salvage.
Just as soon as we hold the salvage button, right?
Because you can do that, can't you own a mark as junk?
Is this junk?
Hold on a second.
Fifty two damage a second.
This is a staff.
You definitely should put this on.
This is more of a core damage.
Yeah, I'm going to this way.
Oh, man. Get Elden Ringed.
Is this OK?
Resistance to all one max health.
Better than what? Better than nothing.
He's he's in Green's Omega law.
I'm going to I just started the game.
I like fire. It's good.
Like the big splash challenge.
Swift Hunter was I mean, I'm down.
Green is frozen.
I think we're fine. We try.
Oh, Nancy is.
Yeah, I see what you mean. I see.
I got it. I think I'm going the right way, right?
Group up, group up, group up.
Am I the only streamer doing fire?
If not, I'll change.
What else is down here?
Is anybody else streaming this?
I think a lot of people were today, weren't they?
I always go back up.
All right. Find the hermit's cabin.
Herbs and ore can be found throughout the world and are used by artisans
for a variety of functions.
We wait as this material of this, like, OK.
Lightberry is crafting.
This is literally for tonight.
Quite for tonight.
I don't mind crafting that light.
Crafting is fun.
I think it's cool.
I don't mind it.
I actually do not mind random busy work in game sometimes.
I don't really mind it.
Now, this is the kind of thing you just hop in a discord call
and it's just like you just doing it doing what?
Picking up herbs and spices and more.
And you make like a like a steak.
It's my one friend.
I have one friend.
OK, or picking up herbs with the bros.
Yeah, sometimes you just pick up herbs with the bros.
This is better.
Will. OK, hold on.
I should look at this first.
Strength is armor.
This is skill damage and resistance.
This is resource, Jen.
Healing received and what is overpower damage overpower?
These are new terms.
The lucky hits overpower damage.
This is new. I don't know.
Aspects are going to run out of inventory space.
Whatever is still glowing.
How much you throwing in for the herbs?
You can play pizza tower some more.
Probably not. Not on stream.
I think I got exactly what I wanted out of that game and it was fantastic.
So I'm not really the type to get
you know, P rank or S rank on every level.
So I got what I wanted out of it.
Is anyone here?
No, I got it first try.
I wanted to like look around.
I wanted to Nancy Drew, by the way.
Nancy, how are you doing?
You all right? We're fine.
I didn't mean to click twice.
He's all right. Herbs, mushrooms, organs, healers, tools.
I suppose anything in it.
Strange skull.
Young freshly turned easy kill
further south than the others.
They're spreading. OK.
If you're going to trespass into my home,
rifle through my things.
And at least have the decency to join me for supper.
Bloody hungry.
It's not the it's not the response.
I would think would happen.
That's quite the story.
I wish it wasn't true, but it is.
Why did I have that vision?
Thank those friendly villages.
They gave you the blood of Lewis, the blood of a demon.
Not just any demon, the daughter of hatred,
the mother of sanctuary.
She was banished ages ago.
But this world is her creation.
It was prophesied she would come back.
We know this person's name won't.
That's the question.
Sanctuary has always been trapped amid the eternal conflict.
A war between angels and demons.
But Lilith serves neither side.
She has her own plans for us and me.
And my people that have booming low voices like this.
I wonder what happens if you pitch this down.
What it sound like.
Use it. Find out what she's after.
Then we're in this together.
Rest while you can.
Then we'll start to kill the shot.
Do it. Oh, I don't.
Reporting software right here.
Record the audio.
We'll all company Lorath to kill Vashad.
Oh, wait, I have new points tonight.
All right.
Should I be boring Barry and just keep doing fireball?
Or should I keep should I do something else?
That's kind of good.
The radius increases for distance traveled.
That's pretty good.
Keep it hot. Keep it hot.
OK, it's going to go boring, Barry.
Herbs and spices and jewels and chips.
I'm OK doing boring, Barry. It just works.
I honestly don't.
I can't hear what he's saying.
Ah, Shaman.
Jerma changes the audio mixing.
Jerma, I can't hear what he says.
I mean, the audio mixing is in line with the way that you know what I'm saying?
Like, I should be able to hear it fine.
Greetings, greetings, greetings.
The audio mixing was fine.
It's just, you know what?
Time that person out for one full minute.
No, OK, it's the effects volume that has to come down.
Dialogue come up, effects come down, music up a little,
master volume up a little bit, ambient down, dialogue up.
There. Perfect.
Out of mana.
All right. Now that's too loud.
He's talking into my ears.
He just leaned over from behind my chair out of mana.
Dude, get away from me.
Out of mana.
I just imagine there's a fucking actor in the room right now.
Just the angel in.
I'm sure you've heard the Cathedral of Life.
It's dressed as a sorcerer.
Well, he's real.
An angel walks across his arms, pacing back and forth to cloak on.
Like Lilith is here.
Blood will flow.
I wouldn't have done it like that ancient enemies.
They'll drag the whole damn world into their feud unless we can stop it.
Let's not linger.
Keovashad lies just ahead.
Roads blocked should clear up when the storm has passed.
Oh, it's a town.
You need to have an original thought right now.
Hold. What are you talking about?
We have no time for this.
What does that mean?
To answer Keovashad, you must perform a cleansing ritual.
Meaningless gesture, but some people take comfort in it.
How dare you?
Just let him through, lad.
I've tried for years to get Lorath to do the ritual.
Fine, but this one stays.
I'll meet you inside.
Take a piece of holy cedar wood from the shrine and inscribe it with the sin which troubles you.
Then cast it into the brazier.
As the fire burns the wood, so too will the light burn away your sin.
I mean, I'm fire, so...
Let's do it.
Okay, let's inscribe fear into the wood, anger, pride, greed, or just scribble all over it.
I don't think I want to do this because what if I write something...
I don't know what it says and it's something really bad and I don't want to, like, have that be burnt into my character.
Hmm. No.
Hmm. Hmm.
Greed.
That means I get extra gold for kill, right?
It's probably some bonus, right? It's probably a money bonus.
Good. You must feel as though a great weight has been lifted from you.
Welcome to Kyova Shard.
Okay.
Well, a man that old has lived through some dark days.
Explains why he's so cross.
Doesn't do anything?
Oh, there.
Okay, it's time to take a BRB because I'm going to come back and I'm going to give you a little bit of Grotto Beast's info.
Not long. Just going to give you a couple of quick little pieces of information.
It'll take literally two minutes.
And by that I mean I'll be back. I'm not leaving yet.
I'm going to leave in about 20 minutes.
So just be aware that in like 20 minutes I'm going to leave and then I'll come back with some info.
There you go. Sorry about that. I had it completely wrong.
It's my fault. What a bad announcement.
So what did you write on that piece of wood?
Something about greed or gluttony perhaps?
It matters little, I suppose.
Where are you going?
I'm off to the dry steps in search of that pale man from your vision.
I must know what party plays in all this.
But first, I need you to retrieve something of mine while I finish my negotiations.
A merchant in the center of the city has it.
Just tell him I sent you.
Stable merchant. Give me one sec.
Drink water. I've got a big ass water right here.
I've been drinking it the whole time.
When I go BRB, I'll refill the water. Don't worry. Don't worry. I'm good.
I'm hydrated. I promise.
OK. The mod said do slash dance.
Really? I didn't do anything.
Pratoos. Sway back.
And somewhere else to get warm. I was here first.
OK, so this is this seems like a big hub town then.
Got you. OK, wait, waypoint.
Our waypoints. What about town portals?
Elections, plan, majority clan.
Oh, wait, this is blacksmith.
Waypoints allow you to fast travel freely across Sanctuary.
Yep. Activate them.
You can earn renown by completing various activities across the continent.
Obtaining renown will grant rewards and certain thresholds.
View the status of your renown for each region from the map.
What will it be?
All right, so I can salvage just all junk.
And imagining this means that it's just unlocks new look on a salvage.
Oh, OK. Is that a stupid idea?
All right, let's just salvage this.
Oh, there we go. This is better.
Is it, though? No, it's not.
I want the willpower.
Came apart nicely.
OK. Prepare.
Upgrade. Can't really do anything here yet.
If you press P, you'll P.
That's made up and is an incredibly immature thing to say.
In fact, that's just that's just a very immature thing for you to say.
I'm not going to tolerate that.
Preveyor of curiosities.
Twenty five of this.
The curiosity is this gambling?
How do I get this? OK, this is gold.
This is red dot PVP.
And this is all balls.
How do I get those?
An in-game currency.
OK, I don't think I'm going to buy or do anything.
What's that like a random event?
How fair is the city guard?
The new militia recruits have been training night and day.
They deserve.
I I need to know what's going on here.
Hold on. I need to know what's going on.
Giving them a cheer for me.
Easy going for you.
I need to know what's going on.
Confidence for the recruits.
And I get to go on being the hardest.
What's going on right now?
I will. OK, this is a side quest.
What's happening here?
OK, so this is a little side quest.
There are side quests in Diablo four.
Hold on. OK, never mind.
It's nothing. Never mind.
Fossil arm fossil arm.
I got a little distracted. What was I doing here?
Let us in on the joke. I don't know.
I got distracted. All right.
What was going on here?
Cheer at the training area.
Oh, cheer E.
Oh, there is a dance.
Is there a dance?
There's no dance. What?
Well done. Hello.
You are courting pain at death.
It's kind of a dance.
Thanks. I hope they don't get used to it.
I guess I'm renowned.
What's that?
Is that a oh, I got like a loot chest.
Oh, an herb cache.
Let's open it back to Nancy.
You crashed the server when I crashed the server.
No, I didn't.
I don't think I crashed the whole server.
All right. What's the queue time?
I got disconnected, too.
That means we all got disconnected.
Twenty one minutes.
Long enough for us to just go like this.
And you see it. No, you can't.
Now you can. All right.
Let me get this. How do I do this?
Guess I better get this pawn shoveled off.
OK. All right.
So that means that there is one crack.
So there's one.
This means there's one crack.
So that means it has to be here.
Right. Because it was there before.
Zero is nothing here.
But is it adjacent?
Like it's just one, two or three.
So they can't be here.
That means it has to be either here or here.
I'm going to say here.
No, that means zero, zero.
So it has to be right there.
OK. So now I know.
There we go. What?
I have a question. I have a question.
That means it's zero here, here, here and here.
Right. That's how my sweep works.
This is zero here. Right.
OK. That means it has to be right there.
I don't play this game.
Oh, shit. Zero.
Is it right? Oh, OK.
All right. Hold on. Zero, zero.
All eight squares around zero are not mine.
OK. That's what I thought.
That just scared the shit out of me.
They're definitely going to sell dances.
I don't know what they're going to do.
I made this way harder on myself for no reason.
OK. All right.
So this means there's two.
That means it has to be one here and one here.
Has to be.
This means there has to be one here and here.
Technically could be the same.
This one could be here and here.
This one's two could be here, but also could be here.
This one is two. One, two has to be there.
This one is also two. Has to be here.
Because one, two, one, two has to be.
What do you mean? No. What do you mean?
What do you mean? Wrong.
This has to. This is two.
So this is one, two.
It has to be here.
This is also a two. One, two.
One, two, one, two, one, two.
I think this is safe, then.
These are all one.
OK, well, this has to be here because nothing else it could be.
This could be it. This could be it.
This is a two. Two has to be one.
But it could be this one here.
These might be safe. I think they're safe.
Thank you. I was right.
Is one. That means this is safe.
There's another one, right? Wait, no, this is technically.
It's talking about this one, technically.
This is safe. Three, one, two, three, one, two, one, two, three, one, two, one.
You just ditch this and pack a bowl on stream.
No, dude, I'm playing. I'm busy.
Oh, shut up. I thought it was talking about this one.
What? How is it not talking about this one?
What happened here?
This is how is it not adjacent?
What is that's one?
This one is right. What?
Who told me to put that cone there?
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two.
It could be one, two, one.
I just tried to guess.
OK, if this is just a one, then this is safe.
One, two, who knows one.
So it has to be this one or this one.
One, two, three.
I don't know. I couldn't.
I can't get this one.
You click maps, please.
No, I mean, I played Minesweeper.
I don't play Minesweeper. I don't play it.
Oh, this is wrong. Skill issue.
Yeah, whatever.
It can't be skilled at all.
The things you try to do.
Hey, you have most of them for you.
Shut the fuck.
Ban that person for an hour.
All right. Let me let's pay attention here.
So this is these are safe, then
because this is the only one.
Here's another zero.
OK, five, one, two, three, four, five.
Damn. OK, it's not five.
Oh, it's four. Shit.
It is four. Is it one?
Well, it's it has.
There's no way it's not here.
One, two, three. Yeah, it's at least these three.
Has to be two could be here.
This has to be one could be there.
This is three.
One, two, three, potentially.
This is three as well.
One, two now.
Well, this is one.
So it has to be there.
This is also one.
Therefore, this is safe.
Therefore, this is safe as well.
This is this has to be here.
What are you talking about, bro?
This is three.
So one, two, three.
That means this is safe.
This is not safe.
Get off of this nonsense.
I don't want to do this again.
So I can look at this.
My timer.
How long is that relative?
Hold on a minute.
The countdown right now for D4 is 10 minutes.
It was 21 minutes.
So this is 10 minutes of time.
10, 20, 30, 40, 50, 60, 70, 80, 90, 100.
This is almost 200 minutes of time.
This is three hour.
This is like a two to three hour timer.
That's a lot of time to do this.
Is that what that is happening?
I can't tell.
All right.
I'm almost there.
Two, one, two.
There's the three.
One, two, three.
Therefore, this is safe.
This game is kind of fun.
It's kind of reminds me of Picross.
One, two, three.
There's the four.
One, two, three, four.
This is safe.
There's your one.
This is not safe.
This is.
There are three more.
I think that's that's it.
It's safe to walk on the ice now.
I guess not.
But wait, wait, wait.
Two, this is not safe.
How is it safe?
No, am I missing a square?
One, two.
OK, one, two, one, two, one, two.
Is it this one?
But I'm on the cracks.
Oh, that ought to do it.
Wait a second.
Those look like wolf tracks.
Maybe I should find out where they go.
Wolf tracks.
Weird.
Looks like some kind of monument.
What's this doing here?
Strange.
It's halfway in and halfway out.
This thing must open up somehow.
I don't know how to open it.
I don't know what the fuck I just did.
Let's go back.
Can I pull this?
There's got to be something I can pull.
Chicken Ridge.
Hey, Chicken Ridge.
Let's go for it.
See tracks.
Sounded like an explosion.
Why is this wolf throwing grenades?
What?
I saw out before I run out of air.
Oh, God.
OK.
I'll never make it.
I can barely breathe.
One's up there.
It's going to be the dog.
Yeah, that's like that's like that's like a sniffing dog.
Easy.
It's OK.
I'll be about the situation either.
Quick, just throw a raw turkey out there.
It's gone.
But thanks to that hole it dug, I can breathe again.
Now, if I can just pull myself out.
OK, well, we got to see the we got to see the wolf.
That was pretty cool.
Oh, this is where the grenade went off.
Awesome.
Cool.
Warning, Diablo 4, there was a problem logging in.
Well, that's not good.
Oh, that's bad.
Try it again.
I'm going to laugh.
This is like two hours.
Hey, 15 more minutes to wait.
That's funny.
OK, back to Nancy Drew.
Oh, right.
I'm going to BRB.
It's a good time to BRB.
I'm going to come back.
I'm going to talk about Grotto Beast very, very quickly.
A couple of things to let you know.
Very interesting things.
I will be right back.
Just a second.
I'll be right back.
OK, let's see.
Let's see if this works.
Might not work that well because I'm trying to.
Holly and I have been trying to like charge it with a little light.
Let's see.
I turned my monitors off so I can't see you.
Hold on.
Ha ha.
I'm going to turn this off.
Let's see if it works.
Can you see it?
This is the glow in the dark.
I got one of the hoodies.
It probably works better if you charge it in like actual light, light,
like sunlight.
What if I do this?
This is like scary.
All right, ready?
I'm going to turn everything off.
I'm going to stand over there.
Let's see if it works.
Can you see me?
The camera might not be able to pick it up.
Ow.
Fuck.
It just hit my knee so hard.
Can you see it?
I can't even tell if you can see it.
All right, I need to see chat.
You can't see it.
Shit.
We were trying to charge it with this little light.
It comes up pretty well.
Bro, get a flashlight.
Hold on, let me see.
Usually need some intense sunlight.
I got this little thing.
I wanted to show it earlier with the sunlight,
but I couldn't because you can't really turn the sun off.
All right, ready?
This is like a seance.
I don't like this.
I'm like, yes.
All right, ready?
These are not that bright, unfortunately.
Boy, is there another solution?
Hold on.
Oh, hello.
No, you're an idiot.
Oh, Gradovich, I see you.
Welcome.
These things are cool.
Well, I can't really show that well, unfortunately.
I thought maybe it would work.
Unfortunately, it's too dark out.
I can see it pretty well.
It's not coming through the camera that good.
You need UV light.
Still cool.
I mean, it's glowing, but just not that brightly.
Yeah, I'll turn the light on so you can see.
Here's one of the shirts.
I think it came out pretty good.
Turn the light back off.
This is a large, by the way.
Wait, let me turn this on.
Hey, there we go.
So you can see the color better.
This is a man-sized hoodie, that's right.
Would you have maybe like a UV light?
So me and Holly played around with these.
We got it to work before, but it was daytime,
so that makes sense.
It's a comfy hoodie, it is.
Well, this is a large, so I usually wear mediums.
Somebody said he's so ugly.
Shut up.
Use your phone if you have a black light.
Why do you look so sweaty?
Because I am sweaty.
Oh, let me try something.
I'll be right back.
There we go.
All right, there it is.
Ha ha ha.
Wait, why am I using it twice?
No, the phone light works much better
than just like a regular light, I wonder why.
Yeah, this is cool.
All right, yeah, let's do it.
Let's see, you ready?
I gotta turn on my monitors off.
Okay, here it comes.
Should be able to see it now.
Yeah, there it is.
Can you see it?
It works.
Is it being picked up by the camera?
Because it looks great here.
I don't know if you guys can see it or not.
You can't see, fuck.
Well, I assure you, it looks really cool.
We can't see anything.
It's the cameras.
The camera's not good enough.
We'll take a photo of it.
But you can see, yeah, you can see it now,
but I think the camera's not good enough
to pick up the light.
We believe you.
Ha ha.
I promise it glows, I promise.
All right, give me one second.
I think there's too much light in here.
This is the Cybertruck brick demo.
No, I swear to God, it is glowing.
It's just not picking up well on camera.
There we go, hold on.
All right, I'm gonna go pee, I'll be right back.
Okay, well, I wish it showed up.
We'll take a picture with it
so we can prove it actually works.
You didn't just piss?
Yes, I did.
I think the issue is that trying to just blast it
with like a flashlight and then stand in the corner
with a webcam probably doesn't show it that well.
We'll take a picture.
After stream, we'll light it up.
I'll get into a dark room so you can see it.
It actually is pretty awesome.
But anyways, the brick went through the Cybertruck.
Sorry about that.
Ha ha ha.
Keep the blue lighting?
I missed the Reddit shelf.
It's okay.
All right, this will take two minutes.
Well, it was supposed to take two minutes.
Also, hey, let me show this.
Wait, let me just get into Diablo first.
What's my hair routine?
It's called use a decent conditioner.
Don't overwash, all right?
Don't sit there and just scrub your head for too long.
Okay, let me do this.
Nancy Drew is okay.
She'll be fine.
Another thing I want to show you real quick.
We've been getting lots of questions
about the rules of the game.
Because I'm sure a lot of you understand
that it's channel merch first,
but on top of that, it's also a game.
And people saying, how does this game play?
What the hell are you even doing?
Is this like magic or Pokemon or Yu-Gi-Oh?
Like, what can I compare this to?
And we haven't really given any rules.
So the game designer has put together a quick start video
and is ready to watch.
We're gonna link it into the chat room
if you want to see how the game is played.
Why is that person's name glowing?
What was that?
That person's name is literally glowing in the chat.
I can't even find it anymore.
Am I going crazy?
What was that?
Somebody's name was glowing.
But yeah, we got a video Grotto Beasts
on the Grotto Beasts YouTube.
They'll be on listing it, be showing it.
Probably get a link here in a second.
Maybe, possibly, eventually.
They went offline.
There is again, there is again.
Stop talking, I wanna see what they're doing.
But anyways, here is the quick start guide.
It's only about, it's less than 10 minutes.
This is not the entire rules of the game.
This is just telling you how it's played.
It's showing you some basic tutorials of how it works.
This is from our game designer.
It's on the Grotto Beasts YouTube right now.
Here is the video in question.
The rules and the FAQ will be up on the site very soon,
probably in the next two or three days.
But for those of you that want to know
exactly what the hell the game portion is, there it is.
Give you a pretty good idea of how it works.
And two minutes is up.
That was a two minute Grotto Beasts talk.
And from there, also keep in mind,
some of that merch, the actual apparel,
like the shirts and stuff is leaving the store soon.
That glow in the dark hoodie,
I promise I proved that it will work.
This webcam just sucks.
That is going off the store.
I believe a couple of days,
we moved it up until like the second or third of April.
We gave like two or three more days.
It was gonna be March 31st,
but now it's like April 2nd, April 3rd.
I believe the original 40 shirt, the posters,
and the glow in the dark shirt are all leaving the store
as of the second or third of April.
So if you wanna watch the video,
the quick start guide is there.
The game portion of the, and there is the two minutes,
took about 20.
Very, very cool.
Thanks for postponing this just for my birthday.
All right.
This is the glowing guy.
Did it even show up at all?
Could you even see it?
Cause it was showing up in real life.
That's unfortunate.
Oh well.
All right, let's get back to Diablo.
You were having a vision.
Is Nancy Driscoll open?
I think it is.
Okay, there we go.
All right.
Missed my camera.
There it is.
I look a little sweaty.
All right.
For the inevitable next crash, I'm ready.
We have the fossil in view.
I didn't even get a water.
Shit.
I'll be here in like 10 more minutes.
Is this fun?
I can't tell you.
I'm not allowed to tell you.
Maybe in an hour or two, I will give you my real opinions.
I'll give you my real thoughts.
Didn't I already talk to him?
Oh, it's cause the game crashed.
Right, right, right, right, right.
So what did you write on that piece of wood?
I'm off to the dry steps and something about green.
All right, here we go.
Crack twos, sway back.
You hate the game?
Stop saying that.
It's gonna make me look bad.
I'm enjoying it so far.
So the old man's finally decided to fight back.
Can you rush me to level three?
Knowing him, he didn't mention coin, did he?
If he wants his weapon, you will need to pay.
Okay.
Lorath's polearm.
This shit was 20 bucks.
How is that cheaper?
So this is like kind of embarrassing.
20 cents and the next thing you got is 1500.
Wait, the old man sold me this too.
Said he didn't need it anymore,
but I think he'd want it back all the same.
No charge.
Okay.
Strange amulet.
What is Nancy's funeral?
Ah, apologies.
He also gave me this amulet.
What is it?
The mark of the Haradrim,
an ancient order of scholars and mages
sworn to protect sanctuary from demons.
These days we are few in number.
There is another.
This game should have a hypothermia meter.
His breadth of knowledge about demons
is equal only to his hubris.
Sounds like he could help us.
You should seek him out in Scotland.
When are you gonna shave your head on stream?
But don't forget about the cathedral.
He's like, near, near.
And they might prove to be useful allies too.
You're not coming with me.
I'm going to the dry steps
to find out who that pale man is.
Join me when you can.
Just be careful.
Your ties to Lilith, the visions you see.
You are the key to finding her
and stopping whatever she has planned.
There it is.
Sometimes our paths in life are set to collide.
We just don't know it.
Whether it is by accident or fate's hand,
there is nothing we can do about it.
The wanderer lost in the storm,
fed the blood of Lilith, saved by a lone monk.
Different lives and incidents drawn together.
By what?
I like listening to this voice.
I want this guy to read a book.
Or some greater power pulling the strings.
At the time, I thought I had the chance
to protect humanity from the daughter of hatred.
The wanderer's connection to her gave me hope.
Imagine that.
Okay.
So now this is like, hey, the world has opened up.
Now go pretty much everywhere.
Oh, this is like, hey, you're almost at the end of the demo.
Like Mario's about to pop in and be like,
that's enough, next player, please.
Okay.
Locations tab.
You purchased items?
You have a wardrobe, all right.
Okay.
So you can buy emotes.
Wait, is that it?
Oh, I thought that actually was the end of the beta.
I was like, that's not right, right?
I was like, hold on a minute, what's happening?
I thought I just got Mario.
I really thought that's what just happened.
Okay, we're good.
Aren't I in the beta right now?
Okay.
Open your journal to view active quests.
Not Q.
Okay.
Travel to the Cathedral of Light.
I think that's the one I'm gonna do.
Pin activities on the map with right click.
I think it already is pinned, right?
That is.
Should I do this?
I mean, do I really need to?
I probably shouldn't even do these.
Yes.
Beta's probably gonna get shut off anyway.
I wonder if this progress go through the beta?
I doubt it.
Perhaps you could sweep the roads
and see what's taking him so long.
The cathedral must receive its dues.
It doesn't, okay.
Yeah, we'll just do the main thing then.
Why does cilantro taste like soap?
Cilantro is good.
I think, aren't there certain people
that have like a genetic code in their body
that makes it so it tastes gross to them?
We were born in sin.
Children of darkness.
The Father's light can be sought
through penitence and faith.
Walk in the light.
What is going on here?
We must be ever vigilant against sin, brother.
Yes, Reverend Mother.
Cilantro fall?
With the light of an aria.
Actually, do it.
I'm curious.
Burden away wickedness.
Let not temptation lead you from his holy radiance.
Do you think cilantro tastes
like awful?
Yes or no?
Here's the percentage of people there.
Cast out thine darkness for only light must remain.
Is this the one from the vest?
Yes, Reverend Mother.
Did Lorath not accompany you?
He sent me on without him.
Putting faith in that old man was a mistake.
What could possibly be of greater import?
Lilith.
So, you know, we have received word from one of our knights
of a demon sighting in Gale Valley.
The description matches too closely
to the sighting in the vest.
I can't really help that yet.
If you travel to Yalesi and take stock of your events there,
you would have the gratitude of the Cathedral of Light.
I had thought to send Lorath, but.
Again, he fails in his duty.
With or without Lorath, the will of Inaris shall be done.
Here, take the knight's report before you go.
Let's go.
Reverend Mother, I received a report
of a potential demon sighting.
Horned woman near Yalesna Mines
performed routine inspection.
Nothing yet.
Sent in priest and escort of knights.
Oh, most of the next step.
We'll report in when we find something.
Remember, you banned my grandmother.
We'll tell your grandmother to chill the fuck out.
Tell your grandmother to stop fucking screaming
awful shit in the chat then.
Baste granny.
Go open up your granny's chat logs
and see like the wacky ass shit granny's been saying.
So 72% say it tastes good.
That's a lot of people that said it tastes awful.
28%.
That seems kind of high, doesn't it?
I'm out of mana.
You don't have to have the gene to not like cilantro.
That's true.
I'm low on precious mana.
What just hurt?
Bad.
Definitely helped though.
I lack the needed mana.
Hog wizard gameplay.
I wonder how many people are playing as the other classes.
Kill the animals.
Event joined.
Caravan under siege.
Slay the enemies.
Oh, okay.
Be careful.
How much time?
Oh, it's like a minute.
Am I destroying the caravans accidentally?
Shit.
I'm not quite prepared for this.
I should have bought two more spells.
I'm low on precious mana.
I'm taking a lighter and just going like click, click, click.
Any potion?
Oh my God.
Come on, man.
There we go.
Wouldn't have made it without you.
Ooh, I got some orbs.
Gain all those by completing events and spend them.
Okay, so that's cool.
So that's how you get those.
I got a rare.
Stop biting your lip.
Cold, shadow resist, five dex.
Boring Barry.
Boring Barry, should I continue?
I'm doing it.
It just does too much damage to not do it.
Where's Nancy?
Nancy only appears when there's a problem with this game.
And it's been pretty frequent,
so I'm sure we'll check in with her soon.
Am I not allowed down here?
Is the wind blowing too far?
The winds are blowing.
How do I stop the wind from blowing?
Oh, it's not supposed to be happening.
Nancy, how are you?
Nancy?
All right, I'm gonna get some water.
I'll be right back.
We'll get Nancy up here and I'm gonna,
give me one second.
Let me get some water.
Sorry, I had to redo my queue.
Okay, hello.
So where were we?
Nancy and I were digging up fossils.
Oh shit, this, no.
No, we're good, we're good.
Do I have to take like a picture of this or no?
This must've been made by the explosion I heard.
Should I go back and tell them that the dog is real?
Go back to Chicken Ridge and risk getting caught
in another avalanche?
I don't think so.
Is this like a sprint back and yell like,
the dog is real, the dog is real.
Did they believe us?
The dog is real.
Yeah, that might make you look a little weird.
Did I even get any items or anything?
It's like lunchtime, right?
Warm again.
They were the two guys playing that chess game
or whatever it was, right?
Where were those guys?
Cause they were like, oh, I gotta make burgers?
Avoid overcooking anything on the griddle
or in a frying pan, fire may result.
Guests may order French toast and omelet
or Canadian bacon.
French toast and Canadian bacon
should be cooked on the griddle.
Omelets, well, it's not breakfast anymore, it's lunch.
Hamburgers or quesadilla.
Put hamburger patties on the griddle
and remove them from the griddle when they are dark brown
to ensure that they have been thoroughly cooked.
Put the cooked hamburger patty on the bun first
and any extra ingredients.
So dark brown, put it down first, then any extras.
Quesadilla, put the tortilla into which cheese
has already been folded in a frying pan.
Never on the griddle.
Remove the quesadilla from the pan
when it has been lightly browned.
They'll put it in the frying pan.
Don't, and just remove it when it's been browned.
All right, are we ordering food or what?
You want a quesadilla and one hamburger.
Something don't look right.
Do this one again.
What?
Oh, shit, sorry, I handed you an empty plate.
All right, you want one hamburger,
two cheese, one lettuce, two pickle, one tomato.
Onion, wait, is this, okay, you want two cheese,
one lettuce, two pickle, one tomato.
Two cheese, one, two cheese,
two cheese, one lettuce, two pickle, two cheese.
Now what?
Where do I put it?
Where did I just put that meat?
Where did I, oh, okay, well, somebody's gonna find that
at some point.
How do I put it on a plate?
Two cheese, oh, son of a, god damn it.
I, all right, I thought I was looking for a plate.
I didn't, I thought, all right, two cheese,
one lettuce, two pickle, one tomato,
and then ketchup, okay?
It looks like fucking dog shit.
Order up.
All right, you just want a quesadilla.
You don't, do you want anything on it?
No.
Order up.
One quesadilla.
One, two cheese, all right.
This messes the hamburger patties like in the onion tray.
The person should be like, all right,
you're trolling the restaurant, you're fired.
Like, stop.
Like, why did you do that?
I don't know, I thought it was funny for the internet.
All right, well, sorry, but like,
what the hell are you doing?
It's been buried at the bottom.
All right, what do you want on these?
Cheese, lettuce, pickles.
Shit.
Nope, this one's two cheese, two lettuce, one pickle.
One tomato, two onion, okay?
One ketchup.
Order up.
Two cheese, one lettuce, two pickle.
One tomato, mustard, ketchup.
Order up.
And then you want two things.
You want one burger, one quesadilla.
One cheese, two pickle, one tomato.
One mustard, ketchup.
And a quesadilla.
This one's for me.
That easy.
Hey, there we go.
I'm low on precious mana.
Bro, what?
Anytime I'm gonna queue for Diablo 4,
I play Nancy Drew.
Out of mana, once again.
I'm gonna like play Nancy Drew, though.
Like, I'm like feeling that right now.
All right, let me get to the end of this
and we'll go back to Nancy Drew for a little bit.
I do like this, though.
I probably, this would probably be like,
probably play this like on a chill stream
when it actually releases or maybe next week or something.
What do you need?
Because I actually do like it.
I'm looking for Viggo.
You and that nuisance of a child both.
Girl's been nagging us about a demon woman all week.
Viggo's gone, looking into her claims.
He should be at the mining camp north of here.
All escort of knights went missing there last week,
along with the girl's mother and another woman.
Like Grim Dawn?
I played Grim Dawn when it was in early access
up to, I believe, Act Three.
I played it a long time ago.
Waypoint.
Map is actually really big.
I wonder if it's just this or if it's any more.
This is actually pretty large.
Pretty cool.
I can't, wait, can I afford this?
Not much.
The mining camp, let me just see what these things are.
I provide a steady supply of, shall we say,
specimens for the clergy nearby.
However, the desire for knowledge has become more dangerous
to satisfy.
I require a host of intact ghoul hearts
from the surrounding area.
There's something special about the ravenous dead nearby.
They can reanimate with only a few drops of blood.
I don't know what happened.
I'd venture out and retrieve these myself,
but I'm more accustomed to dealing with the fully dead.
Your discretion is appreciated, of course,
and you will be rewarded.
Better?
Cool.
Yeah, let me just do this next little arc
and we'll go back to, we'll go back to Nasidro.
Stay in Diablo?
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm down for pretty much anything.
We'll see how this goes.
I am enjoying playing this, just saying.
Ghoul hearts.
Indecisive?
That's literally my entire life.
My whole life is being indecisive of things.
What's that?
Offhand?
I think the stab is better.
We got a great hairline.
Well, the thing about hairlines is
what they change every five to seven years, right?
I've been told.
You notice a difference every five to 10 years.
So if it stays like this for like five to 10 years,
I'm happy with that.
Although, at what point of the cycle am I in, right?
Am I at the end of the 10 years
or am I at the beginning of a new 10 years?
For a hairline, what your hairline looks like.
That's the question.
Would be the end.
I lack the needed magic.
That's a cool shrine.
Dude, your roots are holding on for dear life.
You're definitely at the end of the cycle.
More strangers in the camp.
Ooh, iron.
Your roots are hanging on.
Well, I think they're fine for a little another while,
at least, I don't know.
Are you Viggo?
I was sent here.
That.
This is a loud.
Mother's trapped in there with her.
You let my mother through, sir.
Shouldn't you be responsible for her safety?
We have soldiers stationed inside.
You should be worried about them too.
Did I fuck this up?
Maybe you can help.
I think it's gonna...
All right, we have to fix this.
The pots and pans are louder than the people.
I think it's because I have the...
This is all fucked up.
Hello.
Mines are closed on church orders.
They're not safe.
Especially not for children.
She did.
The horned woman is the demon Lilith.
No, that can't be.
My mother taught me that name.
You speak of the daughter of hatred.
Did Prava mention me?
She wasn't angry, was she?
There's more than your job at stake here.
Come on.
Let's get this over with.
Oh, what's my shirt say?
It's the Star Wars Periodic Table.
I like it.
I'm hoisted stuck.
We've got to go on foot.
Look out.
Level up.
Hey, that's my mother's charm on your wrist.
It's mine now, girl.
She gave it to me when I let her and her friend...
Ooh, wait a minute.
So engulf yourself in flames for two seconds,
burning surrounding enemies for 18 damage per second.
20 second cooldown.
That seems kind of good though.
18 damage a second.
I mean, that's like 40 damage over two seconds.
This heal, self-heal.
Teleport is always good.
I kind of like this frost nova.
I think I'm just gonna do this.
Just be damaged.
Two-spell Andy.
I know, but it does so much damage.
I'm destroying stuff.
Hey, look, if you wanna...
The person that has to go like...
Ice lance.
And then she...
Electric, electrical pulse.
Dash.
And then, machine gun.
I just go like this
and I do the same amount of damage that you did.
I just go like this.
Then motherfuckers explode.
But you have less fun.
Who said I was having less fun?
I kill people in one hit.
They die in one hit.
He's having no fun.
He's talking.
Whatever, we're playing.
Your face says you're not having fun.
Huh, what are you talking about?
Yeah, I don't know.
I only have two moves.
And one of them is here.
That doesn't really...
I should just take this off the bar, right?
Cause I'm not really doing it.
One move.
Maybe we should go back.
Round up the knights.
And leave my mother in...
Hey, nobody complains to Cyclops
when he takes his glasses off.
No, I'm going on.
Cyclops.
I mean, you should do something else.
Why?
Out of mana, once again.
What do you mean what?
Cyclops takes his glasses off
and he has red beams come out of his eyes.
That's all he has.
That's what he does.
He just goes...
And it's like, holy shit, dude.
He's annihilated the whole room.
Nice job.
Bro, you're onto nothing.
Cyclops has the glasses that kind of constricts his eyes
to make it so the blazer beams don't come out.
And he takes glasses off and he...
I've seen every...
Cyclops is like my favorite character in Marvel.
I'm low on practice.
Side Spider-Man.
And Wolverine.
And what is Cyclops' name?
Scott.
Real fan.
I didn't even have to even type that one
on the second monitor.
I'm low on precious mana.
Beams are too damn old.
What happened?
Shaking like leaves.
Cyclops was never given a chance to level up
and pick a new skill.
That's fair.
I'm low on precious mana.
What?
All right, but hold on a minute.
Why are you assuming that Cyclops,
Scott Cyclops would pick like Icebolt?
No, he would just be like,
wait a minute,
the thing that I already know how to do,
the thing I already know what's happening,
the thing I already have been used to,
I can just make it do 20% more damage.
Who's picking that one?
Itchy ear.
When is the...
Special about this place anyway.
What would draw Lilith here?
What's the level cap in the beta?
Hell if I know.
Is there one?
Trevor doesn't tell us anything.
No one goes in, nothing comes out.
That's all.
Ego is no longer following you.
They're not following me anymore.
No lift.
The jam must be deeper down.
Does he like it?
I do.
The thing about a game like this though,
is going through the story
and going through the game progression,
it's enjoyable, it's fun.
It's kind of just relaxing to play, right?
But the real test, if this game is any good,
is 12 hours from now, 20 hours from now.
I think that's how you really tell
of a game like this, is there any fun for real?
Because that's where the loot,
you go find the certain gear
and do the high level bosses and the dungeons
and is that fun.
It's hard to say, oh wow, Diablo 4, this is fantastic.
I kind of don't know until you have to play it.
I think there's enough time that you have to pass
for you to experience this,
at least the part of the game that I want to experience.
Nowhere to go.
My favorite part about Diablo 2
was just opening up the Mephisto loot box.
That was my favorite thing to do.
I loved the item hunting.
That was the best part for me.
My favorite part about Diablo 4
is Nancy Drew out of Mana once again.
That's a pretty good part as well.
My favorite part about Diablo was the loot boxes.
I mean, kind of.
Killing Mephisto or killing Diablo was,
boom, boom, boom, boom.
There's the, okay, two greens, a yellow,
and ah, there's no unique.
That's all right, but cool.
What's the set though?
It's just fun to do.
And then trading was kind of fun too,
being able to be like, oh, I got this
and this is kind of fun, I can trade this.
That's a huge part of why I feel like a lot of people
played the old Diablo games.
I liked collecting stuff too.
Every time I made a character in old Diablo,
I always had to have a,
I'd have like three or four other characters
just to hold perfect topazes.
I would never use them.
I just wanted to have them.
You'd have like 20 rows of ding, ding, ding, ding.
Just perfect skulls, perfect topazes, perfect emeralds.
It's fun to collect.
It was a collecting game for me.
That was quick thinking.
You freak hoarder.
You hoarder.
It's Diablo.
Why would your mother leave you like that?
She wouldn't, or she shouldn't have.
I really was like a little loot goblin
is having like the sack over my shoulder.
Like, oh, you're looking for perfect skulls?
I've got plenty of those.
Identifying an item was always cool too.
I don't know how many people don't know
how Diablo really works or I don't even know
how it works in this game
because I haven't really found one yet,
but getting an item that you know
was potentially really cool
and needing to have that second step of,
all right, what is it?
Or what are the roles on it?
What's the enhanced defense role?
What's the enhanced damage role?
Enhanced damage role, this is a big deal.
What is it?
It was fun.
Now, I don't love wild RNG.
One of my favorite parts about D2 was the unique items.
I know you can just spam that, that's fine.
Spam the emote.
That's, I don't fucking have chat anymore.
Shit.
All right, one of my favorite parts about Diablo 2
was that a unique item was the same.
Every time you found it,
let's say it was like a unique colossal sword, right?
It was always gonna be the grandfather colossal sword, right?
But when you opened it, when you identified it,
there was a couple of parameters that were random.
It was always the same parameter,
but it was either a good percentage, lower or higher.
It was always a percentage that was lower or higher.
And I, and I'm getting booed off the stage.
But you know what I mean.
But an item having 200 to 250% enhanced damage
and it rolls a 201 is like a,
I'm still gonna use this and, but no, it sucks,
but it's okay because it's still the same item.
Now it's of mana once again.
I wasn't a big fan of having everything
be random on the item.
Just be kind of just throw dice in the air.
But if you rolled like a 240, okay.
Now you're talking.
I'm just gonna get up and do this
in an open mic night one day.
This game is cringe.
Okay.
Yeah.
This cringe.
Well, I only have two moves,
so it doesn't look cool when I do that.
But you know what I mean?
It would have been cool if I had three or four moves.
All right, here we go.
An opening.
Get more spells.
Actually, all jokes aside,
this is working out pretty fine.
Flame shield.
Charge bolts is fun.
At least it was in the other games.
Upgrade fireball.
Mana wouldn't be bad.
Upgrade fireball to be more like a hot.
That is actually really good.
Bigger radius.
Yeah.
If I got five points in this already,
then I definitely should just keep going this way.
Increased based on the distance traveled.
Tunnels closed.
We're trapped without the hoist.
Look, there she is.
Remember, why do you look like a Calvin Klein model?
Like your lips are doing some Zoolander shit tonight.
I think it's because I'm biting my lip
and I'm going like, look, I'm biting my lip.
I just turned the facecum on and I'm just like.
It's her.
The way I saw her.
Lilith.
We need to find my mother.
Now he's extra conscious of it.
Ah, it's all right.
I don't care.
I feel like this is gonna be a boss
and I really want to see what it is.
With my enhanced fireball.
No filters, no makeup.
I don't even know how to put one of those on.
Over there.
The hoist.
Filter.
At last, I'll ride out.
Oh hell.
Slane.
What happened?
This is on normal.
This is on the whatever tier two, whatever it is.
Veteran.
We need reinforcements.
I would even want to turn it up with another one.
I wonder how many they're gonna have at launch.
What was that?
It's came from beyond the gate.
This is definitely a boss room.
All right, let's do it.
The escort.
They're all dead.
Over there.
Who did this?
A woman.
Vico.
It was one of the women you sent.
Are they actually difficulty settings or are they bullshit?
Hi.
That's a good question.
I don't know.
This just makes monsters have more health, right?
You get more experience.
I don't know exactly what it does.
20% more health.
We can take a look.
Second hand.
I'm pretty sure you can change it off with life.
You did nothing.
Spells.
Bears.
All you supposed to do is go to Korvala,
tell Prava, raise the army.
The father, evil, itself.
Mox sanctuary.
Do this for me.
He's dead.
Hand on tail.
Your mother told me this trinket would bring good fortune
to think I trusted her.
She bribed you with it, didn't she?
You weren't supposed to let her through at all.
But it's not too late.
She can still be saved.
Not by me.
Not anymore.
There it was.
Prava will know what to do.
You're leaving us?
Abandoning her?
What happened to my buddy, Eric?
There's nothing left to abandon.
Yeah.
She's good as dead.
I'm sorry, kid.
Yeah.
I heard about Eric.
He really just left us.
Damn.
It's up to us now.
He's bored?
I'm just playing a game, relax.
Lilith can't be too far.
We're actually gonna fight Lilith right now, are we?
What is this?
Now your mother races.
Yes.
I am Lilith, mother of sanctuary.
Daughter of hatred.
I have what you seek.
You hunger for knowledge.
Water.
You dragged your child all over sanctuary
in pursuit of it.
No, I taught her how to survive.
Is that what you want to believe?
Drop the act.
You have questions.
I have answers.
I know the fabric of the cosmos.
Everything I've read has warned me against you.
You've read so much, yet know so little.
Will you accept my offer?
No.
I don't know.
Will you let me try?
Take the fucking glasses off.
Your mother is alive.
She came this way with Lilith.
How can you be sure?
Sometimes I see visions of the past.
I saw them.
What?
How?
Lilith's petals.
Her blood was fed to me once.
You stupid human.
I'm immune to the plasma damage that your eyes emit.
It's too bad because ice and fire both hurt a lot.
It has 10 points in it.
That was too much.
Oh well.
Chat is more divided.
You watched X-Man yesterday, didn't you?
No.
Are we really going to argue that Cyclops didn't have the best drip out of all the X-Men?
It would be weird if you were to say that.
Just drip.
What are you talking about?
I said drip, drip, drip.
You guys.
Fucked.
I didn't say drip.
I said drip.
Watch the clip.
Boy, just go download a clip and watch it.
I didn't say that.
I said drip.
They're going to get out of here.
They're going to get out of here for a minute.
Yeah.
You definitely said no.
Give me a clip.
I want to see it right now.
Somebody show it to me.
Link it to me.
I want to see.
I prove it to me.
Fucking die.
Out of mana once again.
Are we really going to argue that Cyclops didn't have the best drip out of all the X-Men?
I didn't do that!
What?
Are we really going to argue that Cyclops didn't have the best drip out of all-
It's drip!
I said drip.
I swear to you.
Are we really going to argue that Cyclops didn't have the best drip out of all the X-Men?
No, dude, it's D. I'm telling you. I said D
I don't know. We're really gonna argue that
like
It's the noise gate on here or something I why would I say that i'm talking about his clothes
He's got these he's got the blue and he's got the yellow
And it's it's I
I whatever who cares?
Fuck it. You know, fuck it. Whatever. Yeah, cool. I don't care. Yeah
Yeah, we're good. We're cool. But either way, I don't care
Yeah, we're good
Fuck it. We're still alive. It's fine
I can't fucking believe it's funny
It literally is the noise gate
Well, let them let them have their let them have their fun. It's okay
Okay, I need to find a deeper way
into
kasama
this works
rathma
Yeah
there
All right, let's go. You think you're better than us. Just remember when I said that
grip gate
So curious
You are eager to know why you were spared
Yes
Do you have faith in me freaking water through straw is hard to do
want to
Good for now. All you need know
Is that we are going to meet?
my son
rathma the first necromancer
Here's that I just want to like
You know what I mean? Here's the key to my plant
It sounds like they're searching for lilith's son rathma
together
What are you thinking?
Just drink it
Okay, so when you drink water, oh my god drinking water through a straw it's like
This I want to just
I want to just you know what grottobeast.net
Uh, if I were you out check it out. It's a fun game that we got a fun piece of community merchandise
I would love for you to check it out
And uh, I got a glow in the dark shirt
We'll take a picture of it so you can see what the glow in the dark really looks like about a shitty webcam
Should be cool. It looks pretty cool
Grip game
What I was trying to say is I like to drink water faster than I can get it out through straw
Especially when i'm just thirsty as hell just use a bigger straw I need mana
I was gonna say that was this
Do the vortex trick so the water goes into the straw faster. How does that work? Oh, I completely forgot
um
So the grottobeast resale stuff
There's been some questions on that i'll answer very quickly
so the whole point of the presale was to make sure that
We didn't run out of inventory
We'd be able to get more for this period
But as of this coming, I believe this coming week
We're going to be coming out of the presale
So what that really realistically means
is that
We're not
gonna die
Okay, so with that really with that. Ooh, hold on 10 almost 10 crowd controlled enemies
Close enemies
Okay, so just it's essentially 14. It's 13 to 14 percent more damage. No matter what very cool. Got a lucky hit
And then more lightning damage
So I gotta get close
But yeah, so
We're confident now
That a lot of the we want to make sure that the people that really wanted to get in on it
Had access to it. So now we're just coming out of presale soon
so just
When they're gone if they are gone, then that's it
um
There's still availability
So I wouldn't worry too much about oh shit. I gotta hurry the fuck up
Uh, but we're we don't need to be in a presale anymore as of um, this this first shipment especially
So this first shipment is going
Pretty soon from my understanding. So
Yeah
Did you die your eyes, um, no
You've mastered your fear. I was at selling but first your expectations sense. We'll talk about this
You miss your daughter
My magpie
She's scared right now
She must be
Go or stay
It is time to choose
I I trained her. Well, she's a good kid strong
She'll be all right. She
You've chosen well
my child
To reach rathma
We will need to cross a lake at the bottom of these ruins
It requires a ritual
I will teach you
As you wish mother you're ready for lesson one
Blood is the key
What did you see this time?
I don't need sparing tell me
Lilith plans to teach your mother a ritual one that needs blood your mother seemed
receptive
We have to reach them
Okay, so
It's been selling that the sales have absolutely been
Above and beyond expectations. It's part of the reason to do the presale
So I told you a couple weeks ago the booster packs. We had to do another print on the boosters
because
We essentially went through the whole first print
of the booster packs
So that was part of the reason to stay in a presale for a while because we didn't want to just have it run out
And then it's just okay. Well, that's it whoever gets it gets it
without making sure that people that want to get in
on this first pass
Are able to get in so
The second print of the boosters we're in the middle of going through that now so there's inventory now
And I think we're comfortable and confident to now just pull us out of a presale and just let it just exist now
Again, we were trying to make sure to make it so
We were just gonna get it if you wanted it
And now it should be able to be available. I mean, I I don't think there's any
If you were thinking right now that
Oh my god, it's gonna run out tomorrow when they come out of presale. That's that's not going to happen. I can
Um, well, I don't know but
We we do have plenty of inventory
now that being said
I i'm not going to promise you that there will be because who knows in the future i'm not going to say
But when it's gone
It will be gone
Uh, at least uh, once when we come out of presale
And I can briefly talk about the digital version
I talked about it very briefly. I'm just gonna reiterate it one more time
The idea is to have a digital version of this
Whether it be a mod of something else or some other standalone. We don't know
We're trying to figure that out. But the whole idea is to make it because this is channel merch
it's merch for this community, but
we do understand that
There is a game on top of it
And a lot of you guys a lot of people that would be buying this
Maybe you don't have access to be able to play a physical card game with somebody
So we want to make it so it was possible
We're able to play the actual game portion of it. You don't have to worry about it too much
So the merch can be merch for the channel and then we can have a game
a digital version of the game
That you don't really have to worry about and again, this would not be let me i'm gonna make this really clear
Whatever digital version that we do and like what I said, whether it's a mod or something else
This is not a case of
Oh now I have to buy digital card packs. No
No
That's not what would be happening
Would it be all card access in the digital version?
Think the idea is that that would be yes
We're still trying to figure that out. We don't know how to implement everything perfectly
But I think that's the idea
But we're not doing booster pack openings digitally. That's just not happening
Uh, because I don't it's not something I really want to do and everybody on the team agrees with that
That'd be kind of scummy
well, I mean, yeah, that's
like I want people to to enjoy the experience right whether you
The card box the card
The booster packs
It's it's merch. It's an interesting way for me to do instead of doing a hoodie
It's okay. Well, let's do this instead and this is like when we open up. What would you get? What's in the card packs?
What's in your booster or whatever?
Um, it was just an interesting idea
But we're not going to pretend that there's not a game on top of this that people might actually want to play and might actually care
About and how do you let everybody participate and have everybody enjoy something like that?
Especially when we think of how many people
You know from different countries, you know
You can't just play like a physical card game with somebody from like a different state or a different country or a different town, right?
And I don't want to have this turn into some never-ending monetized thing
That is oh, yeah, you bought the physical cards buy all the digital packs too. Good luck
No, I don't think so
We all seem to agree on that
We are very excited. So when people actually
Get them. I wonder what the the experience will be, right?
Yeah
Starter kit and the boosters are already 80 dollars and 10 dollars respectively
I'm not going to tell you
I'm not gonna make you buy a bunch of shit in a digital version. It's not gonna happen
Play with people online
Yeah, that that's kind of the idea
And there's plenty of opportunities to make something where that's possible
The reason to do it pretty much
this barrier
It looks like the same kind of magic as before
You're gonna run grotto beast tournaments
I that's
I think I can dispel it. I don't it's hard to say any answers to these questions because
Don't know
Let's make sure that it goes. Well
let's make sure that people get things and
Uh, let's get through part one first and then we'll figure out if there's a part two part three part four part five
Yeah, I did it no don't yes
I who was I even talking to?
Are they going to be reprints?
We've already done
Well, I don't know. What do you mean by reprint?
because we went through
We went through the booster pack inventory and needed to do a second print. Is that what you mean by that?
That's what you mean, right?
Because we already had to do that in the during the presale
And we think and we hope we have enough inventory now just to kind of have it
For as long as it's uh possible as long as it's available still
After we get out of presale
This is on the veteran difficulty
I mean re-release. Oh, I don't know. You're just in time
Beyond this lake lies. We don't have any of the first ball. I I I don't think I know
Reprint
But I could not pass through with her
I I
Black divine element, you see stop but I can find it. I'm so close
I simply need mother stop
Look at what Lilith has done to you
You're writing in your own blood
my little magpie
She awakened me
She showed me things
Can't even put into words
Once I finished
You will understand. I don't care what she showed you
Please let's just get out of here
Oh, I see yes clever magpie
Trying to lead me away so you can take all this for yourself
I discovered yours. I will finish these rooms
You must stop this
Look at the gifts she's given me
You won't take what's mine
Uh-oh rip them up now. Oh shit. I'm also potions
Oh pit lord
I'm not ready yet. This is so out of place
I'm not ready yet
I need time
Get out of my ears
Stop, why can I cast?
I need time to prepare that. Oh, i'm not ready yet
How are you still alive
You were
Any drops who are protecting me?
I don't want to hate you
i'm trying
I really am
We're going to make lilith pay for what she's done
So we need blessed blood
Go back to your prover
Get that blessing
beg if you need to
Whatever it takes
My mother started this damn ritual
I'm going to finish it
Meet me in the mistral woods
Why there?
The horodrim hid a vault there
Finding it was her life's work
So much for that
Maybe it will help with the ritual if not
At least I can bury her where she'd want
I need time
I'm sorry. Just leave me
And it really feels like the ritual didn't even work. I mean, there's nothing that like happened that was
Oh, no
Ah
Where's the loot?
Where's there's no there's no box or chest or anything
There's no box
Well, look at your inventory
Oh, I did get this
Let's do to all stats
I'll hold on to it. That seems pretty good
I need to look in town at all this stuff
All right, so if somebody here we go
So grotto beast rerelease as in will you be able to buy the game in the future after presale and stuff runs out?
Will it be a continuous item that you be able to purchase from the store?
So the way that it works with the printing
is
We have to be able to order a certain quantity for it to make sense from my understanding
and
I don't there's no plan on us doing like a year or two from now. Like oh, yeah, by the way turn it back on
um, I think the idea is that we have a lot of inventory now
and when it's
Done, it's done and it's a limited run
and then the digital version
Will be a thing that
Exists pretty much indefinitely
But I don't know it really I guess depends on demand too really depends
We we went into this as this uh being a limited run project that was supposed to be merged for the channel
um
And then the actual game portion of it can probably live pretty indefinitely through the digital version. So
Yeah, that's the idea
But we don't know we don't know how it's going to work out. We're
We're operating on it being a limited run piece of merch
That is going to exist until it doesn't and we have we have plenty of inventory
Let's see how it goes. I need to upgrade. I need a third spell
And I think it's going to be
All right. I need to slow people down
What about should it be flame shield?
That seems kind of good
I'm doing it
So you're immune when it's active. So if there's a bunch of enemies I can just press it and just go boom boom boom
Now these are the players I think
Oh it is these are other players
I need to go to the
Blacksmith what else is in here?
3,500 I wonder if it's always salvage
Let's have a look at you. Hmm
Buckets need reinforcing
This leather's cracked
What have you been getting yourself into? Huh?
Look you live or die by the quality of your equipment
If you have the coin and materials
I can improve it for you
Okay, so need something for
All right. Don't do this yet. Let me see
All right, give her to that
Get rid of that. That's good salvage
Hmm. Yeah, I just don't want to accidentally give her something I can use
You can take what's left like that. Okay
Let me get out of this menu
But this is more if I have 1.5 percent of 60 damage is like point like two or something. Who cares?
All right
Can't salvage that one, huh?
upgrade
What? Okay. Hold on a second
This is probably a bad idea
What about nancy drew? I oh my god nancy drew is just sitting in the cold
I don't think i'm gonna do this. You replace so much stuff in the early levels at what's the point
Is there a stash?
Where is it? There it is. I wonder how the stash works. Is it account found? Is it account stuff or is
Is it between characters? Is it just individual? Is there a a shared tab? How does it work?
What about sorcery?
Yeah, I know
I got to finish breath of the wild before sorcery though. I feel like that's more
Necessary because the new one's coming out soon
So you can buy
more tabs i'm assuming
Do I give these two?
Ravenous dead
Oh, it's part of the quest. I have to upgrade one thing
All right. I'll go i'll do it healing potion upgrade
Interesting. I'll do this first. Wait, hold on. You're not gonna play tears of the kingdom for years
excellent work friend
Ghoul hearts seem to have captivated the clergy as of late
It's no surprise really
Understanding your enemy is the first step to defeating them
What would you do if your soul was trapped in a cube?
Uh, I would wait patiently until some random dumb adventurer let me out
It might take a few thousand years might take a few million, but it would probably happen eventually
I could be patient
My husband feodor left our home in the middle of the night. I heard him talking to someone another woman
I went to confront them, but they fled towards a strange light in the forest
They have been gone all night
I think it's time. I went after him, but the forest is dangerous
Would you accompany me?
Hmm escort quest
Sure, let's go
Let me try my new move
That's fine. How does the new move work the radius?
Jesus
Uh, that's the case down here. I'll help the lady. Why not?
I wonder is magic find in the game
Because that was always fun in um
Diablo 2
All right, that was pretty good
That's pretty good. You group them all up and then just do the big fireball
Remember, would you go back to cuphead for money?
No, just out of curiosity though. How much money i'm just curious
What do you mean by that?
No, I got everything I wanted at a cuphead
It was a very very fun experience. The game was great
But i'm done with it games like that. I probably go back to every so often usually like a year or two will
Cuphead's one of those gamer cooldowns
You know what I mean? You got like a gamer cooldown
Where you play it and a year goes by and it's like, all right, i'm ready to do it again
that happens to me with dark souls it happens to me with
pretty much any
Game that requires
very intense focus
You get the gamer cooldown
I said, oh come off it. What do you mean? What's that? That was very
Oh, come on
Come off it
Is he drunk?
No, what?
Why was that such a weird that was a weird take to some people what was it?
It's kind of like a movie or some really really
There's a lot of movies that I you know, movie cooldown same thing. Do I have to stand still for that?
Wait, will neff wants to play bill wants to play
Oh, hold on. I think wait is that what I I got a notification over here. Hold on a second
Oh, no, the dru the dru crew is about to be very disappointed
Oh
But that's not hold on that's not accurate
It's very possible that I get booted and have a 20 minute queue
How about this dru crew? Let's let's do some bargaining here
dru crew
I've come to bargain
I want to play
nancy dru and the ice wolf
on
Thursday of next week
You understand me? Oh, no, that's resident evil 4. Um
Fuck you think you guys might be in a little bit of trouble here. How about this dru crew?
I'll tell you
If I don't play nancy dru and the ice wolf, whatever that game was that we were playing earlier
By the end of march 31st, I will delete my twitch channel. Okay, there you go
If I do not play dru crew in the icicle wolf, whatever that game that we played earlier, I will um
That's a bad thing to say
Okay, yes
I'll just play it before the okay wipe that bet wipe that deal
I will just play it before the 31st
Of march of this year. There you go
Dru crew accepts
Uh, what was I supposed to do?
Oh find her husband
It might be worth checking out the multiplayer say at work
Although i'm gonna have to add a few people though
Did I level up again?
Oh, I like that more damage more duration
What do you guys think? I think it's a pretty good escape wills in a party right now
Uh, well, whatever figure it
We'll figure it out. I think I want more damage
Because this move actually and you don't have to stand still that's okay. Just just checking to make sure
All right. Where is your husband?
Are you really gonna go all fire?
I'm gonna go mostly fire
Fire sorceress is one thing I never really did in diablo 2 so i'm going to fix that and do it in diablo 4
Are you gonna explain to the that group that you only have three skills?
I'm not gonna
I'm not gonna say that
But who cares if I only have three skills. They're very powerful
It doesn't matter. You know, hey here's the nature of diablo
This I make my build you make your build if you want
You want a whole hot bar of moves and you don't just want three fire abilities in that then you do it
Good luck
Good luck. Oh my god
My sweet fedor
May you know bliss fedor
What has happened
Well, don't let don't let her run
What did a little run?
Such sights I have witnessed
such pleasure
such pain
I must have
more
How is it that you more please go after that woman who did this to him
More more more
I'm gonna leave you two to sort this up
And i'm gonna go this way
It's no surprise fedor was drawn to me
But I have given only what was desired
His petty soul has been torn asunder by agony and ecstasy
But his flesh is unyielding
He will not interfere
Uh, i'm gonna go back over there. Uh, I don't I don't really want to know what's over there
You you deserve much worse than the mercy I have just shown you
That woman was demon. I have dealt with her if it's a reward you want
Take the dagger from his chest
And leave me be
Oh shit
Help him
10 more damage to injured enemies 10 11 is a basic skill damage. I don't think it's better than this
Neither this staff is actually really good. I get a plus damage increase to anything
Doesn't matter how close or how far away. I think i'll hold on to that. Yeah, I think that sounds good
That was an interesting quest
Any advice on how to stop slouching?
Um, not really but i'll tell you a little tip every I would say in between
Okay, let's say you're playing let's say playing apex legends, right?
drop
Got 100 people that you have to fight
You get that guy you get that one you get that person boom. You're in the top 10
you got
Set nine people running around
Ah, you got sniped from the window, but you nice nice fucking work. Nice job. You did it
After every round just sit up
Sit up after every run
Just make it clear that every time that you are gonna get and that was a who cares
Okay, all right going this way just make a conscious effort
every so often
Every 20 30 minutes or so or like 40 minutes
Correct it. That's what I do. You see it happen all the time
How many times you see me just kind of move and go wait a minute. Hold on
Re-adjust and stay that way
Who cares? No, I didn't mean that. I just mean like who cares about that story. I was telling
All right. The fireball is kind of destructive
A lot of people didn't believe in that
I'm a dental assistant
Um, so yeah, does everything just after you do the teeth?
Um work then just kind of sit up for a little bit stretch a little bit you get nice target ass shirt
Don't know where I got this shirt
All you can do is speculate
Ooh
Ring
Do anything with this?
So it's close range this far away range. Is there a medium range?
Got that shirt kids are us
Rafflecopter
Behold the truths that lie within
Try to do anything with this stuff. There's something strange going on here
They around must be nearby
Who the fuck just said rafflecopter?
Come on, dude
All right search
Am I the right level for this place? Yeah
Oh somebody wanted to see this i'll show it to you
You're still here
Is there a place to see the?
Um the difficulties or is it a different menu?
We've had the mcdonald's shamrock shake
uh
Yeah, i've had a sip or two of it
one of those items where you can only have one sip or two sips before you just like
Just never want to drink it ever again
But those three or four sips
Are delicious the first sip of a shamrock shake is
This is the greatest thing i've ever had in my life
There's nothing nothing will ever compare to how good this tastes
sip two
Is kind of mostly just sugar flavor
Sip three is this is the best thing i've ever had in my whole life again
And then sip five hurts and makes me kind of want to like put it down
mist for
Exactly
Sip four is between you and god
That's right
We don't talk about sip four
We don't discuss sip four
I do appreciate that that thought
Shows you if it's going to kill them
If you're not out of shake by sip four you're doing it wrong
That depends
Sips or gulps
Well, that's what I was saying to you guys earlier
drinking water
Sometimes I can drink a water
Faster than anything
All right, where am I going here?
All right this way what temperature do you like your water at water to me needs to be
Just above room temperature
It's not cold
above room temp
but maybe something like
Oh, no, no, no below below below. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry below just below
Just below room temp
So let's say room temp is somewhere between what like sixty eight seventy
I like a like a sixty degree like fifty to sixty degrees created by the horror
The portal will lead you through this crude nancy
the ice wolf
Okay
chest
Relax no harm will come to you here. Who is this?
Who are you n of sorts?
I saved you in the mountains
You'd lost your horse and crawled into that cave
Would have frozen to death if not for me
Why are you helping me?
Oh, it's very simple
You want to stop lilith and I want you to succeed
But you'll never do that by following the whole rotrim
Their path always ends in fire and death
So what is this path exactly seems pretty fiery and seems pretty deadly seen enough
Open the door. Uh, you don't bring people here
and say that you know, you gotta
You've got to clean this place up a little bit before you say it's not fire and death over here
It's a cool looking place though
Why are you telling me all this?
to warn you
A day will come when the horodrum stumble
Don't be there when they do it's gonna be diablo
The portal will lead you to that little girl you're looking for
I like the world the way it was
without lilith
A little game of rebellion will only lead to chaos
You've already seen visions of the damage she can do
Yes, I know you were fed her blood
Do you feel it changing you?
Perhaps not yet
But as long as lilith walks in your world
It is only a matter of time
Tristram
The horodrum of old imprisoned diablo the lord of terror beneath the earth
And then they built this town nearby
You can see how that turned out
This worked
Okay, let's go back in the horodrums illusion
illusion
What are you hiding?
nairo
There you are. All right, let's go
I think i've lost my way the same thing happened to my mother and me earlier on
The trail to the vault ends here. So it should be somewhere around in these woods
Find the way to the horodric vault
Someone toying with us. This place is amazing. Oh, I should have held on to that
We need time to prepare
Where they go
All right, punch everybody up punch everybody up punch punch punch punch
You actually despawned them. Oh
What the heck?
How does it feel so far?
It feels good to play
I do like
Okay, i'm gonna give you a take
one of the things I really like about these kinds of games, especially like d2 and
um others
I played grim dawn. I did
and
I'm gonna pick my nose on camera
I really didn't like in d3 and I know this is people are gonna say what's the difference
It doesn't matter. You can just respec or whatever
But having access to every single
ability
Every single one and you can just kind of if you make a barbarian you are every barbarian if you want to be
And it's only you diablo 3 really relied on you finding
a set
That had some crazy modifier to something
But I like so far
That you have to pick stuff
And it's
I guess permanent unless you refund it which it looks like I wonder if I do this. It's four gold. It probably
Will go higher i'm imagining so I don't know if that's the accurate who knows but I like the fact that if you make a
a sorceress or wizard or
A barbarian
It's not not every barbarians the same barbarian because I can just do the moves you're doing if I really feel like it
I can just swap them out. Um, I like building characters. I like making a wizard for instance
That I have to make two I have to make three I have to make five
I have to make 10 to experience some of the all the builds that I would like to experience
I like it more that way now. You could say well, you're just kind of adding more unnecessary time
But I like that. I kind of like having permanent decisions that maybe they're not completely permanent
But they're permanent and i'm talking to my channel. I wanted to be permanent this dude's waffling
I don't think so. What is right here because I can do it. He's talking to his kids. Is that rare?
That was like bold letters. I kind of like being able to make
Mistakes or make characters that are kind of maybe unconventional that are just strange
That maybe they're not the most powerful but you can still do it and maybe you find items that make it fun to do
the ruins in d3 were interesting, but it really did feel like
and this is probably likely to happen here, too, but
It was there were a few ruins that were just so good. It was unbelievably good
And why would you pick anything else? Uh, what I have to do pray give thanks. Hello. I appreciate that
Nice, what is this?
elixir of what
Increases lucky hit chance by 30% in an experience gained for 30 minutes
Oh, I can't even use these
That's pretty cool. I like unique gear. I like collecting stuff and I like making characters that other people might not have
Yes
Diablo 2 shout barbarians come to mind
Ocean find barbarians come to mind if you got into a game where there was a potion find barbarian
It was just like
Ah, you're okay. You're a weirdo and that's okay. That's all right
It was it was kind of interesting. It's a grandpa take. That's fine
now obviously diablo 2 was it with things that you should do it with things that were just crazy and
you'd see a lot of sorceresses running around with frozen orb or
Like nova was
unbelievably good for a while
But you still could do the other stuff and it was still
You're muted
What I just said a bunch of stuff
Who we're going in here?
Summoner was op
Like we're gonna boot it now
Summoning necromancer was so it was just so goofy
I don't know how you do that now
Because I think the technology might not be able to handle
Hundreds if not, you know two or three hundred if you got three or four necromancers in a game
Maybe it would just break the server. I don't know
How is he not noticed what are you talking about everyone say one I win is that the only thing in here
missed experience
Featured peaks total real never known
Whoa, what's this?
Just got 3 000 gold in the skill point. Holy shit
All right, one skill point is way way way way has been added for all characters on this realm
I did that want the movement speed. This is good, too. It's all your characters, too
How are they gonna handle that?
Does that just cap out at some point?
I have to imagine that that would get kind of weird after a while only a certain number per region
It's just the characters you own
You did that I did that so you don't have to replay everything
Compound. Oh, okay. Is there a town hub? Looks like there's quite a few of them show the map
We might be getting booted here. I think so. I think we're getting booted
I'll give it 30 more seconds. So then i'm gonna restart it 10 seconds 10 seconds messed up
Uh, I hope I don't lose progress or something. I was wondering why my room was hotter
It's because I have two games open running at the same time. I was wondering like why is it so hot in here?
Let's try to get in the queue again
Nancy drew is definitely not running the gpu hot. Yeah, but it's still operating. We've got a long one here
In fact, we might not even
Do this anymore. It's 20 minutes in the queue. We might just be doing drew crew for a little while
Let's see. Can you see nancy drew the problem with playing two games at the same time is I need to remember what the hell
We just did an hour and 25 minutes ago. That's the hard part
Hmm
I'm just gonna tell uh, tell will and I just got a big pretty big queue. So
I how do you spell queue? It's such a weird word to spell then i'm gonna i'm gonna do an emote
What's a good emote to do the sideways crying laughing face?
Zany
I was gonna put bugleberry in here. All right, nancy. What are we what are we doing? Where were the those?
They were playing that game and they were saying hey fix the lake, please
Where was that wasn't it here? It was here. Maybe they went out to the lake should I go upstairs going to their rooms?
This shoot is for dirty laundry. Do I have to do the match the colors or something? What was it red?
Red blue then green it was it was like certain colors, right? Definitely to get this right. Nobody has an actual
Key thing on their door emergency exit only cold warning
I shouldn't open this door unless I absolutely have to put the key in your bag and use it on the door
Oh, okay, what do you got in here rudimentary geology structural engineering
Large machinery safety protocol make the bed. What about this? Wait a minute. Hold on back over there. We're coming
Shoot, I can't clean this room yet. I don't have anything to put the dirty laundry in the chute
What do I need a basket?
That's not scary music
The diablo q
Can I open this? I cannot well, what about whatever's going on? I need a laundry basket or something, right?
I've been so itchy today hates to lose expected to win and I always did
Knowing your enemy is the surest way to defeat them. I know some of my competition is better than I know
Myself
Some believe he studies his competitors so he can eliminate them. Why is she on a rifle?
Environmental champion. I have long bobs tip of the month. Shoot. I can't clean this room. I need a laundry basket
I'm not doing this till I get a laundry basket. Is there a staff room or something I can get to
That's not what goes here
I need a laundry basket. Is there like a staff room or a
Contents deleted
Wonder why from last year? Interesting
Okay, pick up laundry bag at the front desk available after 5 45 a.m
But I took too long. Well, isn't this the front desk? We're sorry. I won the jackpot
Check the number and dial again might as well leave a message. Hi sheriff. It's Nancy Drew. Nothing urgent
I'm just kind of checking in. So if I don't hear from you, I'll call you back later. Bye. Okay
All right. What about uh, Tino Balducci?
That was a pointless message
I didn't catch you but whoops, I'll try again. I'm not sure helped is the right word. Mr. Balducci
In fact Tino i'm a little surprised you're still in law enforcement considering some of the unethical if not illegal stunts you pulled back then
looks like
I'm curious. How do you know shantel? We're gonna get intel. How many clients do you have?
One large pepperoni
Okay
I better go. That's a lot of pause. No get I want to leave the phone
How do I put the phone down?
This please call me five five five
Okay, two three eight three two three eight three. What's the area? What's the code?
Can you do mario? I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I got I did it. We're sorry. Your call cannot be completed as dialed
Please check the number and dial again the recording. I did it. I'm really high. I don't understand
Why does he keep dialing numbers? Oh, no
Oh, no. Um
Let's relax for a little bit
Just just chill. There's no reason to
Looks like elsa was having major boyfriend problems
Dude, I can't watch it
Sorry, this is a laundry basket. How is this not a lot? Oh
Give me this
Dear elsa
This time when I read it when I this time when I read in your letter saying you weren't coming
I didn't get sad. I got mad
I can't believe you think working as a stupid
Made it some stupid lodge for some stupid lady whose name I can't even pronounce is more important than spending time with me
If I didn't love you so much I tell you to go
Take a flying leap
But since I love you more than anything i'll just have to do something else like maybe take your precious collection of troll dolls out
Of the box you store in my garage and dump them down the disposal or maybe i'll sell them on ebay for a nickel
I have a piece
I don't know how else to make you understand that I love you with all my heart and I always will
That was a review for valorant. Okay, I need to go upstairs. All right
Jesus what happened? They have to have the thing on the door. There we go. All right, let's go in here
I got the laundry bag now clean up the room put the laundry in the laundry bag
Okay laundry very nice you want laundry done as well
Everybody else have any laundry it was just these two. I think that's it
It was only people that had the thing on there. That's it. Right? There's two more rooms for you to do
How do I go get that thing back? I got this. No, no, no, no, this is correct, right?
That's not what goes here. I gotta go. I gotta go get it
Whatever. I don't even care. What's the what's the next task to do? What's the task need something? You look busy. What are you making?
I'm building something. It's gonna solve all our problems a wolf trap one
That'll finish off that thing out there once and for all you think the wolf is causing the accidents not a doubt in my mind
Everything was a okay till it showed up and started howling
It's bad luck and something's protecting it
Something unnatural does mizma weakway know you're doing this
She knows she doesn't want that thing around her guests and you heard her i'm supposed to do whatever I think is necessary to get rid of it
But it's not like it's attacking people what's wrong with this wolf yesterday. I went looking for it
I tracked it and finally found it sitting across the creek not 20 yards away from me. Just staring at me
So I raised my rifle drew a bead and fired
Easiest shot i've ever taken in my life, but why though missed so I fired again
And I missed and then I missed again and again and all the while it just sat there staring until finally it just stood up
Walked toward the brush just as calm as could be and disappeared wild animals
Just don't act like that and I just don't miss like that
There's something real weird about that wolf and I ain't gonna rest till I get rid of it
So maybe we should just find something else to jaw about you met my little girl yet
No, but you mentioned that her name is freddy. Yep spends most of her time outside
She built herself a little snow for it
Just sits out there waiting for somebody to go by so she can pick a snowball fight with him
I keep asking her how she manages to stay warm all day, but she won't tell me
Says she's got a secret weapon
Yeah, she's something
Why do we care about this wolf who's
Who cares?
Do we think the wolf is the one dropping the grenades?
It's a magic wolf
Why do we want to kill the magic wolf? I mean it growled at me. Yeah wild animal would do that if you approached it
Why are we gonna kill a magic wolf?
Why wouldn't we want to how long have you worked for shantel if it grants us wishes or something?
I was her first hire best hire too. I could run this place
I'm telling you you just take you throw like one raw chicken at it and it'll grant us all wishes
Just one just one like raw turkey and the thing will be like, oh, thank you
By the way, how much money do you want in your bank accounts tomorrow?
It's a magical wolf
Have you ever been in the guest lodge business before I tried my hand at it once
Long story short didn't work out, but i've learned a whole lot since then I could make it work now
Just need to find the right property get my hands on enough cash to make a down payment
Is your wife freddy's mom does she live here is your wife freddy's mom does she live here too
In the summer she does but in the winter she goes south though
I don't know her name this nerve condition that makes her real sensitive to cold
freddy'd like to go with her but until shantel stops putting off giving me that rage
She promised me sending freddy south too is out of the question
Can you tell me more about the accidents that have been happening around here? Nope sure can
Hmm you can't or you don't want to shantana those lawyers or her said I couldn't talk about them supposed to direct all questions to her
Sorry
Have you seen that strange concrete monument thing that's out there on the trail kind of weird
course
Is there a way to get into it? Do you know don't know don't really care
Maybe something in that display up in the lobby will tell you what you want to know
Did you know there was an avalanche at chicken ridge sure didn't not surprised though you call the avalanche patrol
I thought I'd tell you about it first
You better give those employee instructions I left in your room another look report
Oops, sorry
No, my bad
And you should probably start drinking fucking four fingers of whiskey before you go out to hunt the magic scary wolf
Looks like we both have things to do. I'd better get back upstairs
By the way, you dumped the laundry bag before all the rooms were cleaned. So I'll put it back up at the front desk
Oh
Okay. All right. All right. All right, so I have to call the avalanche people. This is so invigorating
This is so invigorating
Um, I don't know why this keeps happening. All right, I had that was
Nancy i'm glad to see you
Are you all right? You're okay upset. You must listen. I was outside skiing very fast
As usual and suddenly boom snow dirt rocks everything went flying into the air right in front of me
There is a mad bomber on the loose
Was anybody I saw no one not before not after
My competitors bombed the bunkhouse thinking I would be so frightened that I would abandon my training and leave only I wasn't frightened
So now they are trying to bomb me
Uh, okay, do you think they're responsible for all the accidents that have been happening around here as well?
My competitors and the governance behind them. They are as desperate as they are ruthless. They're capable of anything
They can operate anywhere in the world under all conditions
It would not surprise me if someone right here in the lodge is right now under their employ
But to them I say pa they do not scare me. I'm the best cross-country skier in the world
I will neutralize their petty threats with my excellent strength skill and speed
What is this very why are you so mad what are my problems did you want
All right, have you seen the wolf in the wolf while you were out training? No for which i'm very grateful
In my country in fredonia. It is said that the gaze of the wolf will make you go blind
Really they are creatures of infinite evil and that is all i'm going to say on the matter
You're busy. So i'll let you go keviche naya
i'm telling you it's just
I hate this sound effect
All right. So we have to go do the laundry thing. I got a call about the avalanche
I don't think I think diablo is is completely done by the way
I've been sitting here and it says queued and it's just not doing anything. So i'm just gonna close it
So we're not gonna play any more diablo
unfortunate
I had it was fun. It was fun. I just
Obviously wish it worked more often
but um
I enjoyed it. I think it's gonna be
I don't know. I can't tell you only know is that it was fun for the
Three or four hours. I got to actually play it
I cannot give you a judgment on it because it's hard to do that so early into a game that is
Potentially hundreds of hours of things that you need to do in it
But I will tell you that it felt a little it felt better than the way that I felt about d3
And way better than I feel about diablo immortal. So
It was good. I thought it was fine
We'll see
Okay, I need to go back to the front desk
I gotta make a few phone calls
All right. What was it? It was
Who do I call?
I called the sheriff and it was just like oh, I don't care. Leave me alone
What what I have to call the who do I call ghostbusters? I actually watched afterlife, uh very recently
Who do I report this to is there another number lying around somewhere? I'm a senior detective
I don't need a task list phone numbers. There it is. Okay 403. It's been an avalanche
I'm calling from the icicle creek lodge, but I wanted to report an avalanche at chicken ridge
Uh, not anymore the handyman here at the lodge. He's also on the patrol explosives training
Sometimes the patrol has to i'll tell him appreciate it one more thing
Have any of you guys been setting off explosives anywhere near the icicle creek lodge recently? Liar. Thanks. Bye
He has an old-timey radio cadence
Okay, so we did that now I need to
Close this
Get the laundry bag again. Is it lunchtime or is dinner? I don't know. I'm not who cares
I'm not gonna serve any food. Okay start at the very end of the hallway you make the bed
Already made get the laundry leave across the hall same exact thing turn around this bed's made, right?
It is leave down the hall. Nobody else has the the we want room service thing
Is it just everybody? It doesn't I thought I said only if they have the thing on their door
Does that just count that's all I don't have to do the whole thing again, okay
That's done
Now what now what I kind of don't know long as it's not time to cook. I might as well stay out of the kitchen
Can't do anything here. I'll go back outside. I will go to uh the needle. Can you confirm that corn pop was bad?
um corn pops
pops
How do I open this? I like I thought the corn pops like the god half my pops, right?
I need to open that door
Wrong wrong wrong. No more avalanches for me. Thank you very much. So where do I go?
No more avalanches for me. Thank you very much. There we go. Why don't we talk about a landfill?
Book in more rooms
It's a simple question. Um
I don't have a simple answer for you
The speed run for this game is 21 seconds. Is it actually that seems ridiculous?
Have I been to a landfill before? I cannot say that i've been to a landfill
Ah much better. That's really cool. I've been to a landfill
Look up the video of the speed run
No, no, I want to beat this. I don't want to see the 20 second speed run
Okay, what about what's going on in here? It's locked nothing in here. All right, what's this weapons?
I don't know. These are locked up completely locked up locked up. Really just open it. I can't how do I get in here?
I don't understand. You got a picture of a wolf in your room
What the hell was that? Is it dinnertime? No need to go in there till it's time to cook
No need to go in there till it's time to cook scary. Okay. Oh this thing. What's the deal with this?
What's the deal with this? I think I know the deal with this
Does it do I have to put the is it about the edges here? I don't get it because you see how these
I just yawned and I want to yawn in front of you like
Okay, do the all the raccoons have to be with that line on the left?
See i'm saying I think it's probably that and then
No, thanks for taking your disgusting bodily function off camera. That makes like sense to me though, right bottom line right line top line
But what about the mill you guys want to you know something interesting?
What interesting I started to do recently that I got I got really into i'm curious how much I care about it
Uh, I bought a bunch of clay. I'm just making a bunch of weird shit with it. That's all I thought at first
It was just match everything but maybe it's not this is a clue somehow
No, I have no idea what the solution of this is but I feel like I should know it at some point
You're suing right salmonella and the potato salad. I didn't do this. Did I I didn't do this
I'm gonna go trying to turn the lodge into some kind of ody-tody spa while she still can first the wolf now this i'm leaving
Okay. Oh, they're back. What's up? Do you ever see anyone else when you're out there snowshoeing?
I see that yanik guy sometimes
I'll be plodding along and he'll go zooming by those skis of his are like rockets, man
He's all like zippy zoom
Do you ever see the wolf never sometimes I hear it howl though bad news, man
It doesn't take a very big sound to trigger an avalanche
And when you're out there by yourself
Nothing will ruin your day faster than a couple of tons of snow roaring your way at 100 miles an hour
Tell me about it
What do you think about all the weird things that have been happening around here? I think they're kind of cool
Accidents make life colorful, you know
You wouldn't be saying that if you were the one who'd slipped on those ice-covered stairs or eaten that bad potato salad
Or had those four flat tires. Say that again. Hey, I had that broken window broken window
I went snowshoeing on like the third day
I was here and when I got back the window in my room was broken glass was all over the place
Why is he wearing vault dweller clothes who broke it don't know don't know what true get either
There was no rock on the floor. No bullet. No nothing
It was the wolf tried to jump up into your room, but didn't quite make it
That's bogus dude. My room's on the second floor and besides wolves don't do stuff like that
Hey, that wolf does a lot of stuff wolves aren't supposed to do. That's why it needs to be hunted down
Nobody even knows anything about this wolf man get off its case
Anyway, my window broke and nobody knows why
It's pretty awesome. Huh? So you like to snowshoe. I like doing stuff outside
Snowshoeing is about all I can afford
Think you could teach me sometime. You don't learn how to snowshoe if you need to get through snow
That's too deep to walk through you slap on some snowshoes and you just do it
Okay. Well, i'll let you go ditto, dude
Hey excellent job on the snowshoeing. Eh, we had ourselves one fine time out there because of you, especially lu here
I beat him five times
By the slimmest of margins. What's up, kiddo?
Are you by any chance related to ralph kessler the guy who used to build carousels around the turn of the last century?
No idea
Is this the first time you've been to the lodge? Yep sure is
Well, I better get back to work glad you dropped by
Then it's fucking backflip
All right, maybe if I talked because this guy was like, oh you didn't do your job
But now I did so now does he have anything else to say?
Where where is he by the way?
There you are. What you need the avalanche patrol asked me to tell you that the explosives training session in calgary has been postponed
Till next month. Well, hallelujah. I didn't really want to go anywhere until I finished off that wolf now. I won't have to
So you're on the avalanche patrol, huh?
Yep, dang
I just remembered patrol wants me to keep an eye on skookum ridge for the next couple of weeks. Okay, skookum ridge
There's the key to the snowmobile
And see if there's been an avalanche
You want me to check it out?
So you don't have to worry about the cold
Make sure you call the patrol and give them a report when you're done
You can handle that cold. It is a little chilly in here. Let me go ahead and get that fire started over there
Nice
So where we going now?
Okay, you bet. You bet good. I think that's enough. I'm sweaty
So now where's this snowmobile two more things that bill kessler guys getting bored. He's checking for plus
He wants competition, you know me too. Well, that's why the cam can't be on
Oh, I did something and
Other thing is a cold snips on its way
You think okay, they like it good. Just wait got to be real careful anytime you're outside
So we're done here
Okay, i'm gonna take this normal questions. I had by the way
You dumped the laundry bag before all the rooms were clean. No, I didn't this guy
I don't get it because i've done that like three times now
What's this guy's problem? All right snowmobile. Let's go
actual progress
Where is the snowmobile nancy drew?
How does she do that
She's talking to herself what are ice balls
I feel like she has her hand up right now going like this ali's daughter freddy
She's like talking
She's just kind of bored. What the hell fucking destroying this kid right in the face, too
If you're gonna have a snowball fight, you don't ever don't ever aim for the face. You know what I mean?
Especially like a little kid
You I'm not trying to pinpoint throw this
Snowball at a kid's face, you know you throw it like oh
You throw it like towards the ground over there and oh you miss that way and oh, oh, no, you got me
Who is throwing fucking baseball pitcher throws of?
Snowballs at a little kid's face. No, you know, you're just like, oh, yay
I we flip-flang and I lost who is who is doing that?
Nancy nancy slow down. Holy smokes. All right, there's a
Let me wind up
Just like if I don't get warm soon
I may not make it what?
A nice fishing shack a nice warm one at that. Did I walk here? I don't understand how this works
What kind of weird shit is that?
I'm sorry
I was trying. Wait, is it over?
No, we're good. How do you catch a fish?
Hello
Do I not have bait on the line? Is that the problem? I need a worm nice i'm measuring it with a ruler
16 inches
How big I think I have to get like a big one, right? That's a big one right there. That thing is huge
Am I am I i'm not holding on over what do I do? What's the point of this?
Oh my god, that's a huge fish got it a sturgeon chewed right through my line
What am I supposed to be doing though? Okay
Get the boot
I'm just imagining somebody tying a line to a big piece of driftwood like putting it in the water and then
Being insanely excited just pulling it up being like oh dude. Oh, what did I get?
Driftwood and like everyone that you're with is like cheering and they take pictures of you with it and stuff
Am I supposed to pick up the boot?
Well, that has a target on it. I didn't pick it up though. I think I have to get whatever that is
Just staying up here
That can had a target on it. Where is it? Come on. Come on. Where's the can?
It has to be a reason to be down here
I snagged a log there goes my line
No, I didn't just keep getting random fishes and stuff
Is this just a fun mini game to play does this mean anything?
Does somebody even know the bomb? I already got it. It blows up the shack
I want to see that can again. Maybe there's a certain type of fish I have to get the sturgeon was huge
I'm surprised that wasn't it. I mean, why are you asking us questions about your favorite game?
There we go. I got it. That was exactly two feet. Yeah, I couldn't pick it up
No, what why did it not let me do that?
You need the can you need the can you need the can you need the can I didn't need the can
I think I need a basket or something. Yeah, I need I need like a basket. I need something
I can't carry anything. I need to come back here later
I'm gonna have to come back here much later because that's the end of the stream. Here's what's gonna happen
I'll see you guys on sunday sunday. We're gonna finish this nancy drew game
I'm gonna see if the diablo servers are fine. We'll do this maybe a little bit diablo 4
But we will complete this on sunday. Thanks for watching. See you sunday
I said till the 31st, but I kind of want to play it these games are very they're just really I like them
They're nice crew crew lives. Yeah
Uh, oh keep an eye on the grotto beast twitter because i'm gonna take a picture with the glow in the dark on
I'm i'm i'm surprised it wasn't showing up. I want you to see that it actually does glow in the dark
So we'll take a picture i'll go and like pitch black rubbin will light it up keep an eye on the grotto beast twitter and
What else I don't want to tell you what time sunday finding a time. I'm just i'm searching for six o'clock pacific
Uh resny before yeah, that comes out on the 22nd 23rd. I'll be playing it on launch
I don't know exactly when it comes out. But whenever I stream on that day, we'll play resny before
We'll probably be playing that for a couple days in a row
I imagine at least because I want to just beat it and play it because the game's awesome
I need to save this. There we go. All right, it is saved it is ready and that's it. Thank you for watching
D4 was pretty fun. It was i'm
Looking forward to playing a little bit more to give you a real assessment of it
Uh, jimmy neutron game is required reading well as we settle here after stream rewards
Obviously after grotto beast is out in the wild and people have it and we can um
Because that's been something i've been paying attention to a lot recently
So once we get that done i'll be able to play a lot more random stuff
My grotto be shirt is coming this weekend i'm hyped
Yeah, the apparel should do I think the apparel is going out to people
So people I think from my understanding I think that that's shipping before that's going to ship before all the uh cards and stuff
So you should get that first or at least maybe if you ordered individually apparel. Yeah
Most of this stuff is at least the first batch
Is um, it's coming soon. It should be shipping at some point in the next couple weeks. Thanks again
We'll take a picture
We'll go do it right now to show that the thing actually glows in the dark so there's no
Um, what did somebody say earlier the tesla truck incident?
I whatever it's midnight. I'm allowed to like snort like a fucking weirdo. It's fine. Nobody's even here right now
It's nobody's even here watching. It's just me in the room. It's me in the monitor
That's the only people that heard that only weirdos snort. No, I
No, no. Good night guys. See you soon. Call your mother. Take it easy
That hopefully d4 turns back on because I want to play it take it tonight