Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary and tonight I'm going to be playing as the Spy with the default invisibility watch, the Ambassador and the Spycicle.
This is on King of the Hill Lakeside and I get a bunch of kills. I think I top frag too. I'm not exactly sure, but this video is not going to be really about the gameplay.
I want to talk to you guys because it is finals season. Beginning of May, end of May, between the May to May is when a lot of you guys are taking your finals.
A lot of you guys are getting into study zone where you have to really pay attention in class.
And I figured I'd make this video to try and give you some of my experiences, some of my tips to help you cool off, I guess, during the stressful time.
And do you like that pun I just made? Spycicle cooling off? I know, I'm terrible. But here we go. Here is Jerma's epic test getting ready for strats. That was in quotes, by the way.
Number one, the number one most important thing you need to remember is do not stress yourself out. This is the most important thing about finals weeks.
Do not get into that mode where you're like, oh, how many questions are going to be on the test? How many answers am I going to get? Am I going to be able to know every single answer?
Do not get into that mode. The best way to study for a test is not to stay up till nine in the morning overnight studying and then go into the class the next day and sit down and have no sleep.
No, no, no, no, no. The best way to do this, guys, is get as much sleep as possible. You want seven to eight hours at least of sleep to get your brain ready to go for the next day.
And for studying and cramming-wise, don't do the majority of your studying the night before an exam. Do it in spurts, do it in a relaxed setting, have a little bit of music behind you somewhere over the week period that you're supposed to be studying.
Never get into that mode where you're like, Joe, my dear, okay, this question and answer, got it, got it, got it. Your brain can't handle it and you'll end up forgetting a lot of the information that was supposed to be stored to begin with.
So do it in spurts, do it in a relaxed setting, just sit there, get a cup of tea or a cup of cocoa or something, read for an hour, get some of the information in your head, go watch some TV, relax, get it stored into long-term memory.
That is the big thing, long-term versus short-term, guys. That's how you remember information. It gets stored into the long-term.
Epic strategy number two is on test day. When you're actually taking the test, you're actually sitting down in the seat and you're answering questions.
So you get to question one, you say, okay, I know that question, I got that one right. Question two, know that one too. Question three, you have no idea.
Skip that question and move on to the next one and at the very end, go back to it. Don't sit there for 45 minutes with your hand in your head going, I don't know these next two questions, hold on, let me try and remember, let me sit back and really try and pull it out of my brain.
Because when you do that, you're kind of screwing up your rhythm and you're kind of messing up the way that you're going to take the test.
So just skip those questions and get on to number five or number six and you go, oh, I know these answers. Get every answer you know before going back and trying to find and pull out the information from the ones you didn't.
It is really important for your cognitive brain to be in a rhythm rather than to just sit there with your pencil in your mouth going, do you know what?
Now that does not mean to blow through the test as fast as you can. No, that just means keep your brain active and keep a good pace.
You don't want to blow through a test that is not, you don't want to go as fast as you can. Do not do that.
So the third and the final tip I'm going to give you is as important as the first one and pretty much what it comes down to is eat a very good breakfast the day of a test.
And that does not mean don't walk out the door with a bagel in your mouth chewing on it and then you throw half the damn thing out the window on the ride to school.
You need to eat a good balanced breakfast, have a full glass of orange juice, have a good like scrambled eggs and bacon and toast and everything.
Fill your body. Don't overeat, but just get a very good quality breakfast in your system that will keep you active, that will keep your brain fed.
Your brain will not be hungry during the test and you will see better results.
So that is going to wrap up this video, guys. Hopefully you got something out of this.
These are the things that I used to do and they did seem to work. I mean, I wasn't the best student in college.
I didn't have like a 4.0 grade average or something, but it did help.
So keep this all in mind, guys, and good luck to everybody on your finals. Hope you all ace them. Hope you all get A pluses.
Don't stress. Don't overdo it. Just keep relaxed. Keep happy and all that good stuff, everybody.
So I'll see you guys all soon and take care, everybody.