Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with Grandpa's face cam video, and it's also my 400th upload, so thank you so much, everybody, for sticking around for this long on the channel.
Um, I hate to break everybody's heart with this, and I know a lot of people are going to be probably pretty upset with this video, but Grandpa is not real.
Grandpa is in fact a-
Yeah, you did scare me!
Seriously, I've been sitting in this chair for like four hours. You've been sitting in there for that long? Have you even eaten today?
Nope, not one drop of food. But plenty of this shit right here.
I did see.
Because I-
Shut up! I'm trying to scare you! I wanted to tell you a story about how I scared you. Which way is it? Is that a camera?
Are you done? Are you done?
Where's the camera? Is the camera right here?
The camera's right there.
See, I got this. Hold on. Hey, everybody.
Well anyways, guys, this is Grandpa.
Yes.
Um.
Fuck you, everybody.
I don't know why. I'm going to have to redo this video.
You're not redoing shit. You're uploading this as soon as it goes live. I'll tell you.
I can see myself. Look at that.
Alright, well I'm going to go shit in my hand and throw it at you. In like an hour.
Fantastic. I'm really happy that you just did that.
And I can't really edit that, so.
You are perfect. You can edit anything you want. You're a good editor.
So anyways, are you-
Those are my shoes.
No, those are not your shoes. Those are my shoes.
These are my fucking shoes.
They're not yours. Those are my slippers. Do you know why?
These look good on me. They look like shit on you.
Anyways, um.
That's going to wrap it up here, guys. I was going to do like a quick little vlog telling you guys that he wasn't real.
You were going to do a vlog.
And I was going to vlog you.
Thank you guys so much for watching. I want to say goodbye.
I want to say bye to the fans.
Alright, come on in and say bye then.
I want to say bye to the fans and I want to say one more important thing.
Take care everybody.
And that's it.
See you later, guys.