Oh god, oh dear god.
Alright, let me open this game. See if I can do it.
It's called... I think it's called Super... Psycho Baseball or something.
MVP Baseball 2005. Well, that's actually the greatest baseball game ever made, so...
You know what sucks about that? Do you guys remember?
So MVP Baseball was the best baseball game that's ever been made,
and then 2K sniped the rights to all of baseball, and they couldn't make it anymore.
A few years later, they made an NCAA version of the game, which was still amazing.
It was still really good, but they couldn't make baseball games anymore,
because there was a feud where, if you remember, EA made MVP Baseball.
EA also makes Madden, and they got the exclusive rights to football.
Nobody else could make an officially licensed football game, right, unless you were first party.
So, right, third... I believe third-party game developers couldn't make them.
So, I think that 2K was like, hey, fine, you want football? We'll buy the rights to baseball.
And I remember being very, very sad, because I actually did not like Madden at all.
I liked the EA baseball games, not the EA football games.
And I would have much rather they did it reverse and just bought, you know, the rights to it,
for the baseball games that are football.
But Madden is way more popular than MVP ever was.
What was it? What game were we playing? Oh, yeah, right.
All right, this is called... Yeah, Super Psycho Baseball.
This has been recommended a few times in the recommended Discord.
By the way, if you don't know, the Discord has a recommended channel.
I look at it all the time, and here's proof.
I think I need to capture it a different way. Let's see.
Uh-huh, there we go.
All right, so I don't know, this... Let's give it a try.
Can one of the mods change the title?
Hey there, nice to see you again. You lost the game? Figured.
I haven't even played.
Play ball!
What? How do I hit? Why am I so small?
How do I hit the baseball?
Oh, I have HP? That's got to be out.
God damn it. How do you hit a home run?
I'm going to lose. I don't even know how to play.
You got to get just under it.
Let's go on. Go on!
Good. All right. I get it. I get it. I understand. I understand.
Let's go. Go on.
Go on.
That's how you come back and you win.
Five in a row.
At the very last out.
Unbelievable.
That's one inning down. Two to go.
All right, first inning.
Do I still have only 10 HP? Whoa, hold on.
112 coins.
Heal 20 HP.
Devil's Pack.
Sell your soul.
Regain 5% of your max HP with every home run.
Nerd glasses.
You put on a pair of specs.
Increases range of a perfect hit.
You have an even bigger heart.
You might want to see a doctor, but HP is max HP by 30.
I mean, I think it's the nerd glasses, right?
How much do I have? I need to heal.
You only get to pick one.
He's throwing a lot faster now, but I think that's still gone.
That makes six in a row.
He's throwing so fast.
I picked the shittiest upgrade.
He's on fire. That's seven in a row.
That's gone. Get out!
Sorry.
He's throwing, so I...
Whatever.
It's okay. Sometimes you lose in level one.
If you're bad.
You get that first time somebody plays.
You're supposed to say, hey, try again.
That was the tutorial.
Now you know how to play.
So now don't click one power up.
All right, let's go.
Okay, I understand how it works.
I'm going for it now.
Sorry if I hit you.
I've had a bad day.
Play ball!
Started off good.
Goodbye baseball.
You got to get just under it.
Three in a row.
That's good enough, right?
Four in a row.
All right.
Good start.
Shit.
It's okay.
That's a moon shot.
All right, now let me...
I got...
Honey hell, let me not waste this.
That's one inning down.
Two to go.
Okay.
Your bat grows in size.
Hitbox size.
I kind of want that.
More HP.
You know what it is.
Power boosted.
Oh, I think I might go for the power.
Should I take the steroids?
All right.
Go ahead.
Call me a one-pitch Andy.
No, this is going to work.
This is going to work pretty well.
One-pitch Andy.
Don't get over it.
Goodbye baseball.
Home.
All right.
Jesus.
I had...
That's enough, I think.
Three in a row.
There we go.
All right.
What am I buying next?
Four in a row.
Another inning in the book.
One more to go.
Hundred and...
All right.
Steroids two.
I don't have enough.
Should I hold it?
I think I buy this and hold this one.
Because I'll get this next.
Psycho mode activated.
What does that mean?
One last shot.
I'm going to throw really hard this time.
No fucking way.
It's literally impossible.
Come on.
Get out.
Home.
Come on.
Up.
That's a loop.
Goodbye baseball.
We had a raid?
Hold on, hold on.
Oh my goodness.
No.
No, no, no, no.
Not in the last pitch.
Thank God.
I fucking actually nailed it.
It's out of here.
Oh no, I lost and I have to go home to my super hot girlfriend.
You...
You completed...
You advanced.
I advanced?
We had like three raids come in.
Bruce Green,
Sideshow,
and Bren.
What's up?
Thanks a lot, guys.
Thanks, everybody.
Welcome to the channel.
We're playing this baseball game.
It's pretty cool.
It's called Super Psycho Baseball.
Hope you had good streams.
I'm ready to rock and roll.
Raid songs?
We don't do raid songs.
All right.
I'm definitely doing steroids, though.
Hope you guys are fans of baseball.
Or should I be conservative here?
I feel like this is a big deal.
Uh...
So many of my brothers chopped berries.
Play ball!
I only have 10 HP.
Adios, baseball.
That was fucked up.
Now you, too, have experienced loss.
They made Super Psycho.
Do I start at the beginning,
or do I start at the tree?
Shit.
Let's hurry this up.
I've got a pit.
Play ball!
Oh, come on.
That was perfect.
It's out of here.
That's a moonshot.
So I need to do accuracy.
I think it's more important.
Three in a row.
Four in a row.
Rogue-like baseball.
I...
How did I swing through that?
Um, I lost it.
I'm playing really poorly now.
Oh, come on.
Come on! Restart.
Hey.
My name's Pitchy.
And I got a hell of a fastball.
Keep your eye on the ball.
I'm trying.
Play ball!
Goodbye, baseball.
You got all of that one.
Perfect.
Shit.
That's a moonshot.
I don't have more than 20 coins?
Three in a row.
Four in a row.
Okay. Next inning.
Count it.
Five in a row.
How did I get more coins for less distance?
That's one inning down.
Two to go.
All right.
Can you talk a little louder?
Vinnie's stream is a little loud right now.
What...
What are you doing?
Five percent does not sound like...
It's not very much.
These two are effectively the same power-up.
Technically, right?
I'll go ahead and tip you my next pitch.
It's a fastball.
That makes six in a row.
I need health.
That was a really hard pitch to hit and I got it.
I didn't get under it enough.
Goodbye, baseball.
It's out of here.
That's enough.
Three in a row.
All right.
I've got 70 percent.
Another inning in the book.
One more to go.
Breath of the Wild.
I don't have my switch set up over here.
It's definitely this one.
I need the health.
Five percent HP every time you hit a home run.
Psycho mode.
It's the final inning and I'm all oiled up.
Let's go.
Is that enough?
It's out of here.
That's got to be enough.
Yep.
Home run.
What a... That pitch was so...
Adios, baseball.
This game is hard.
That wasn't even in the strike zone.
It's out of here.
There you go.
All right.
Next inning.
Next.
Adios, baseball.
You're just bad.
It's not my fault I was only programmed to throw a fastball.
Move the camera to the top right.
Uh, hold on.
It's this.
Right?
Big bat.
That's 10 health every time I hit a home run.
But this means I'll hit more home runs.
I'm going for this.
All right.
Come on.
This tree throws curveballs.
All right.
Just zone in.
Walk in and go for it.
That's so fucked up.
Goodbye, baseball.
Give me the health.
Hit the pole.
Goodbye, baseball.
Thank God for the heal.
All right.
Now we're working.
Three in a row.
Okay, inning two.
How did that not go out?
All right.
Good.
It's out of here.
I have to hit two or three home runs right in a row.
That's one inning down.
Two to go.
Both of these or...
I can do both, right?
No, I can't.
It's either both of these or the health boost.
You don't need the glasses.
Yeah, I do need this though.
I could do this and heal, I think, right?
That will heal you.
That's true.
Yep.
What do you mean, you smoke?
Hit the pole.
Fuck off.
It's over.
Okay.
I think I still have a one.
I can do two outs.
That was really hard to hit.
I think I got it.
All right.
We're good.
Three in a row.
Pull it all the way back.
Back to 100 health.
Four in a row.
Get over.
Shit.
Sorry.
Get up.
Come on.
Don't do it like this.
Audio.
All right.
This is very important.
Another inning in the book.
One more to go.
I can do both.
I could heal, but no.
I got to do both of these.
I have to do bat and steroids.
I don't think I can heal roids and steroids.
Okay.
Yep.
Let's go.
Psycho mode.
One more inning.
I'll turn you to logs.
God damn it, dude.
No way.
You made my cousin into a rock and you sold him at Cracker Bear.
Super.
No way.
That's so hard.
It's ridiculous.
All right.
One more try and that's it.
And I'll move out too.
I'll play something else.
Sorry if I hit you.
One more try.
That thing comes in so fast.
It's out of here.
What a failure already.
What's the stream title?
Adios, baseball.
Baseball stream 2.0.
Wallet is a bit tight.
Wait, what are you talking about?
Featuring fishies with that face.
That's a loon.
Get up.
Goodbye baseball.
That should have hit.
That's a loon shot.
All right.
If the heel pops up, it's happening immediately.
That's one inning down.
Two to go.
That heel is necessary for any run.
It's not here.
So I'll take this one then.
Hope you don't mind if I throw a little harder, kid.
Adios, baseball.
Stay fair.
Home run.
Three in a row.
Four in a row.
Need the heel.
Charge the mound.
Count it.
Five in a row.
This guy just throws fast.
The other one has curveballs.
Another inning in the book.
One more to go.
There it is.
All right.
Now we're in business.
Psycho mode activated.
One last shot.
I'm going to throw really hard this time.
That makes six in a row.
Need to get this health back.
Those pitches are such bullshit.
And they go down like that.
Again.
Ah, yeah, yeah.
I got to keep the cursors down.
Yeah.
It stayed down.
I was thinking stay right in the middle so you can have equal place to go anywhere.
Still sticking with it.
Yeah.
No.
Lower thirds of the strike zone.
All right.
Let's go.
Now that's a dinger.
How much health do I have?
Jeez.
Maybe my x-line was right about me.
Reduce the speed and bat size.
How many trees died to make-
All right.
I got to focus.
50 health.
Play ball.
Come on, man.
Home.
That's got enough.
Three in a row.
Four in a row.
That was a weird pitch, but I still got it.
Nice.
Does the game account for where you click on the ball?
Does it change the angle it does?
So you have to get slightly under the ball.
All right.
Slower pitches, I think, is the way to go.
Because that's 12%.
Although it might mess me up.
Yeah, I'll do it.
This time, we'll make it.
Home.
Three in a row.
Over it.
Goodbye baseball.
Nice.
All right.
Home.
I've got a good amount of health.
I've just got to be very, very early to swing.
Another inning in the book.
One more to go.
Are you mad?
Oh, I'm not.
I'm just focusing.
Gravity.
5% of 30 is more.
Or should I do, I don't know.
This is important, too, though.
Gum or gravity?
I'll go gum.
Because if I just have to hit, I just need to-
I'll heal.
All right.
This is very fast.
Good start.
What?
That's a loonshot.
Oh, ball behind me.
Way under it.
It's out of here.
Grr.
Fuck you.
Oh, man.
That's it.
I thought that-
Whatever.
It's so hard.
Now you two.
They made my uncle into a super psycho.
That was fun.
That was a good-
This is hard.
Is this supposed to be a chill stream?
It is.
But I can't say F you.
It's so fast.
One more?
One more.
I have to beat the tree.
Hey there.
Nice to see you again.
You lost the game?
What's your refresh rate?
144?
Play ball!
All right, the real stupid thing here is to lose any health against this first two innings.
You know, right?
This first inning, you should not lose a single health.
It's out of here.
Three in a row.
My mom just heard you swearing.
She said, my germa privileges are revoked.
Four in a row.
Well, I'll tell you something you can do.
You got to put something on the table.
You got to put some type of bargaining chip on the table.
Oh, like, yeah.
I mean, I'll clean my room.
I'll help with some chores around the house.
You got to put some bargaining chips up.
I'll help you move furniture, right?
Be like, I'm sorry that the guy that I watch sucks.
There it is.
No, that's not what I want.
Isn't this just better?
This is just better.
Go ahead.
Call me a one-pitch Andy.
That makes six in a row.
Guess what?
Next time your mother comes in with groceries,
get off your ass and go help.
He's on fire.
That's seven in a row.
And then, I don't know, maybe it's like, oh, OK.
Maybe you can get some theater privileges back or whatever.
Dad?
Hey, next time your mother shows up with groceries,
get off your ass and help.
Yeehaw.
Thanks, dad.
Another inning in the book.
One more to go.
All right, this has been good so far.
I got a lot of money.
Steroids and bat.
Psycho mode activated.
Inning three.
Time to throw even harder, I guess.
Eleven.
Holy poggers, there's eleven in a row.
Did he just say holy pog?
I'm getting more money with the multiplier.
I'm getting a lot more money with the multiplier.
This guy's quick.
Oh, that was out of the strike zone, whatever.
Adios, baseball.
You have to get them in a row.
That's how you get the money to buy everything.
Adios, baseball.
Pray for our heel in between innings here,
because I need it.
Goodbye, baseball.
It's not about winning or losing.
It's about something else.
Nice.
All right, there's the first heel.
Five percent every time I hit a home run.
And steroids.
I can't afford it.
Should I just hold?
I'm going to hold.
I don't know if I want...
I think I want accuracy.
I don't think I want the...
You didn't hold?
No, I may hold the money.
I don't think I want...
Goodbye, baseball.
I think I want accuracy.
That's got to be enough.
Come on.
I need to heel to full health right here.
Adios, baseball.
Five percent of 130 is a lot.
Get under it.
That was like scripted talking.
Adios, baseball.
Get under it.
Stay fair.
All right, good.
Adios, baseball.
Going to be faster.
I got a lot of money.
One inning down.
Two to go.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, man.
This is a big deal.
This is huge if I could do this.
And bubblegum.
What do you mean you smoke trees?
Jesus, those are two bad ones in a row.
So how much am I healing for right now?
Does everybody pay attention?
I can't look.
How much am I healing for?
A lot?
13.
That's awesome.
Oh, back to fucking full health.
Let's go.
Just don't blow it.
Never mind.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to choke.
Oh, thank God.
Stay fair.
I'm all right.
I just made up all the health I just lost.
Yes.
Okay.
Full health.
Another inning in the book.
One more to go.
I have to win this right now.
Oh, I don't know what to pick.
All of these are very important.
I it's probably steroids though.
I don't have enough for devil three.
Oh shit.
I don't have enough.
I have to do.
All right.
I don't I didn't have enough.
I had 122.
I'm going to hold this though.
All right.
Psycho mode activated.
Curveball could come, but I would.
On good start.
Four in a row.
Jesus Christ.
It's so hard.
Get out.
It's out of here.
Shit.
Get out.
My hands are sweating.
Now that's a jinger.
Oh, that's it.
I got it.
All right.
Now what?
I am but a tree.
There's another level after this.
How many levels are there?
I don't know what to do.
Should I boost the HP even more or do power?
Power I think is what I need.
I'm going to hold this because I got to buy.
I have to buy this next time.
Wake up.
There are baseball tryouts to go to.
Harry, he's a little crazy.
Look at the size of this wall.
What?
What just happened?
The ball didn't even come out of his hand.
Excuse me.
Where's the ball?
Dude.
By the way, any ladies watching?
I am single.
Well, we got to the end of that one.
That was fun.
You can't call that a skill issue.
That was.
Good luck if you want a super psycho baseball.
Good luck if you want to play it at level three.
It's very difficult and good luck.
Do I have anything else I can start?
Let me see.
That's fun.
What else do I have here?
I don't know if there's anything I could really do for that much longer.
Let's see.
If you're wondering what's happening tomorrow,
Ster and I are going to play this game called Ember.
Firefighter game.
Like a wacky firefighter game, I think.
I don't know what time we're going to start.
I'll talk to him tonight and see.
That game is amazing.
Yeah, I think I'll probably just call it here.
I think it's a good time.
I have a lot of games to play,
but a lot of them are not like 45-minute experiences.
Go back and finish the other game.
When are you going to watch Biodome?
I don't think I'm going to watch Biodome, man.
Yeah, that's...
I'll call it here.
I'll see you tomorrow.
And then the plan going forward from here is
Driver 1 is going to be a part of a bigger PlayStation 1 Xbox 360 night.
There's still probably five games down there on the Reddit shelf
that I never played.
They're kind of just sitting down there.
There's like at least five or six games that I never played down there.
So definitely going to play them.
What about the Ace Attorney games?
I did hear that there's a new Ace Attorney game that released
and there's no white flashing.
So, I mean, I could probably play that now.
Or you can disable white flashing.
PS1 and 360 are 10 years apart.
Well, I'm going to have a range.
I'm going to play Driver 1, a few more PlayStation 1 games,
a few PlayStation 2 games.
The rest is some of these stragglers of Xbox and Xbox 360 games
that we never played from like, I'm talking five years ago.
Four or five years ago.
They're here.
The new trilogy has an option for that.
Okay.
Yeah, that's the plan.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
I don't have a time, but I'll make sure the sauce is updated.
And I'll see you tomorrow.
Thanks for watching.
Take care.
See you soon.
It's a chill stream.
We just kind of hang out.
I do want to do a lot more of these.
I am very much in the market for doing more just kind of play games
and hang out streams.
2023 is going to be the year of just streaming games and hanging out.
We're going to be kind of going back to the basics here.
What about Sorcery?
Yeah.
I'll fit everything in.
I definitely do want to incorporate way more streams like this,
but we can just kind of fuck around and play something.
It doesn't have to be anything, you know, in particular like,
oh, it's got to be this.
It's got to be that.
It's just like, you know what?
I'm going to open up Super Psycho Baseball and play for an hour.
I'm going to play this game for like four hours.
Whatever.
That's what I'm going to do.
Which also, I'll be honest, that means that each stream is...
I will not be against now, not like I was against it before,
but actually starting games and playing through them and finishing them.
I know I abandoned one literally an hour ago.
But, you know, there are games that have been on this list of,
I mean, like Paper Mario, for instance.
It's just like, do I really want to play Paper Mario for like the 20, 30, 40 hours that it...
Yeah, probably.
Breath of the Wild.
Oh, yeah.
No, I'll go.
Don't worry.
I'll go back to it.
There's a lot of stuff to do.
Finish Yakuza.
Honestly, Finish Yakuza has got to a point where it would be restart Yakuza,
because I have not played it in two to three straight years.
Is Battle Axe still happening?
Oh, yes.
It very much is.
Alright, I didn't have the music playing.
Thanks for watching.
Thanks for hanging out.
Have a good rest of your night, guys.
See you tomorrow.
The game is going to be Ember.
Take care.
Call your mother.
You know.