Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with some Rogue Legacy.
You can go get it on the Steam store for $15, $14.99 USD, and it's a fantastic game.
I know a lot of you guys probably have already heard of this game, but if you have not,
this is kind of in the same ballpark as Binding of Isaac, where you get one life.
If you die in that life, you start over from the very beginning.
Now the difference with this game is that it's called Rogue Legacy for a reason.
You pass down all the gold and all the upgrades that your last character made to a child that you have.
And it gets pretty ridiculous, the things that your children have, the different ailments and the different traits that they have.
But this is a live commentary. I'm going to let it speak for itself. I'm going to let it get right into it here.
Just want to briefly introduce this so you know what this kind of is.
And also to say, if you want to see a Rogue Legacy series where I play through and kill the bosses or do some live comms,
if you want to see this as a series, please let me know, because I'm trying to gauge if you guys want to see this more or not.
So with a comment or a like or anything like that to let me know that you want to see more of this game, then please do it.
But that is going to wrap up this little intro here, guys.
Enjoy the live commentary, and I'll see you all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.
Ow. Ow. Ow.
Oh, lightning!
Alright, so let's go.
I should probably show you guys my castle first, because I guess I've been playing for at least a few hours.
As you can see, I'm working on spellcasting, having my mages do more damage.
I'm not too good with the spell sword people, but I hear they're really good.
I love using the miner. Miners are amazing. If you don't know what miners do, is miners can pick up more money.
So when a coin drops on the ground and you run over it, you get a higher percentage than anybody else in the game.
I love using miners. They don't do very much damage, and they're kind of weak as all hell, but I love using them.
And plus, you can see through walls and see where all the chests are and everything, so let's see if we can grab a miner after this.
Well, who the hell am I using right now? I think this is a knight. Yeah, this is a knight.
Alright, don't need any new equipment, don't need any new runes.
I would love to really expl- actually, wait a second.
I would love to really explain everything about this game, but there's just so much going on, like the rune system and the item system.
It would be a pain in the ass for me to explain, but you know what? Can I even unlock any of these? I'm about to lose all this money.
Maybe not. Yeah, I am. Whatever, let's just go. I can't do any upgrades.
So anytime you start a new castle, well not a new castle, anytime you randomly generate a new castle, you have to give away all your money.
And the only reason why I didn't just give away 100% of it right there was because I bought an upgrade to make it so he doesn't take as much, so death doesn't take as much.
But see, look at this coin. Yes. See, I got 12 gold.
And essentially, what you want to do in this game is you want to break friggin' everything.
Like, you want to smash every single thing there is, because there's always a chance something can drop money.
And it's got this cool little, like, super Metroid feature where you can see the rooms you're going to and where you are and stuff.
It's pretty awesome. Let's just go. Get out of here, you spooky bastards.
Remember, Jerma's Tip. Smash everything.
And the goal hill, the ultimate goal, I mean, of course the ultimate goal of any of these, like, weird action, role-playing, rogue-like...
Why are you shooting through walls? Is you want to get as much money as you possibly can before you die.
Because in the intro, which I'm assuming I did do an intro to this game, you have to, you have heirs, right?
So every time I die, this is not the character I'm going to be playing with.
It's some child of this, or of the guy previously that had kids, that had, like, a wife.
When did I get to see the wife, though? Don't ask me why.
Wait a minute. I just had, like, a really weird revelation.
Are they, like, all inbreeding? Is that why there's no, like, father and mother?
I know there's, like, a journal you can read, but I'm more about the action, more about the gameplay than I am about the storyline in these type of games.
So let's just go!
This is a random teleporter. It will take me randomly somewhere. I don't want to take it right now.
But I'm just smashing through enemies, and you just want to collect money.
Collect money to upgrade. Collect money to upgrade.
Rinse, repeat, rinse, repeat. Last as long as you can inside of the castle.
Money! Woo, yummy!
Probably should show you this, too. Each person has, like, a special ability.
This, the knight can block attacks, as you see there, by holding down.
I'm using a controller, so it's Y on my Xbox controller.
Open.
I have beat the first boss already. I've played for about five and a half hours or so.
And I really just want to get familiar with this game, because like I said in the beginning, it is pretty, it's pretty confusing and hard to grasp right when you start playing.
So I wanted to make sure that I put a few hours into it first before I really want to start talking about it.
So right now, if you notice, we went from the blue area over to the green area, and the blue area is the low level area.
It's like 1 to 20 or 1 to 15 or 1 to 30 or something.
Over here, if you'll notice when I smack an enemy, they...ow.
See how this guy at the top, level 19? This forest area is the second area you should be going to once you beat the first boss.
And I already did beat the first boss, as previously stated.
I'm actually not doing too bad. I'm not getting a whole lot of money, though.
I gotta spend more time focusing on where the chests are.
Not so much progressing in the areas. I want to just upgrade the hell out of this whole entire game.
You guys know me, man. I'm a psycho when it comes to upgrades.
If a game has an upgrade system, and I really don't know why this is.
I think it's maybe something in my childhood.
Maybe like I dropped like my Spider-Man on the ground and I couldn't like fix it.
So I'm always like for the rest of my life wanting to fix things and upgrade things.
I don't know why, but I have this insatiable need for upgrades.
What am I doing? I'm just like standing in this room.
Any game with an upgrade system drives me insane.
It's like a sick thing I love.
Okay, hold on a second. Try hard mode. It's gonna be tough.
It's also good that I have a lot of life leech on, equipped.
I'll go over that in a minute. Let me go over this first, though.
So what this is, okay.
So this, this is a fairy chest and they have very weird objectives.
So let's say I have to like defeat all the enemies and see that in the top right, that little objective thing.
I just did it so I get to open this chest.
Some of these are almost impossible.
Like some of them are like don't take any damage from spikes around the entire room.
But once you complete it, you get to open it and look what's in here.
There's a rune that you can socket into your various gear.
And this is a bounty rune, so I'm assuming it's gonna be more money drops.
But we'll just keep going.
Break your vase.
Okay, so I made it back to the blue area, which is the lower level area.
I'm actually gonna stay back here. Watch out for the spikes.
I'm gonna stay back here for a little bit.
Because damn it.
Because I could use the money.
One cool thing about this game, something I really like, is the developers.
They snuck in a bunch of hidden rooms because everything is randomly generated.
All this stuff is randomly generated.
They snuck in a bunch of rooms that have their like development history.
Like oh, this was our first game. This was our second game.
And it's pretty cool how they do that.
This room is a pain in the ass.
Get linked. Get Zelda linked, bro.
I'm gonna drop down.
I'm not too happy about the amount of HP I've lost in this run so far.
But there's a chest up here.
See the top right? See how that is a blinking chest?
If you play as a miner and you unlock the spelunking,
you can see every chest all over the map, like everywhere in the game.
So it's pretty awesome to go as a miner.
That's a fake painting, but let's open it up.
It's all about that money.
And at this point right now, I need a lot of money to be able to really do anything.
I need at least like this...
If I don't get at least a thousand gold in a run before I die,
then it was pretty much a wasted run.
Because I...
A lot of my stuff at this point is pretty difficult to upgrade.
But if you're a big fan of stuff like Binding of Isaac, this is...
Ooh, okay. Okay.
This room is interesting.
So what I have to do with this guy is...
This guy takes 25% of my money I have right now,
and he gives me a chance to open one of these chests.
If...
In one of these chests is triple the amount of money that I just gave him.
And the other two chests is nothing. I'm gonna go for it.
All right. Left, middle, or right?
I want to go mid.
No!
Ugh!
You know, this has happened a couple times.
I want to be able to kill this guy.
So developers, if you're watching right now,
let me bury the back of my sword in the back of this guy's head.
Like, let me just bury it in his head if I lose,
because that guy's a shithead.
Hey, thanks for the 325 gold, haha!
How do I get up? Oh, it's over here.
And like, you can always see where you haven't gone yet,
seeing the top there.
That little blip, that little blue blip.
That means I have not been up there yet.
Defeat all the enemies, okay!
This is gonna be tough. I might die here.
That life leech is so important.
That life leech.
6 HP every time I kill somebody.
What's in the box?
Spirit rune for a helm.
And I'll make sure before this video is over,
I will make sure to show you that,
like, what that is.
Because it can be kind of confusing.
How much money do I have?
If that asshole didn't take the 25%,
I'd be fine right now.
Hey, buddy!
Woohoo! Where am I going?
Ooh, another journal entry. Journal entry number 17.
I must be going insane.
I stumbled across a carnival inside this castle,
complete with a sad clown and everything.
He's sort of an ass, but I guess you can't be too picky
with your friends in a place like this.
Getting hungry again?
Good thing I topped on the chicken legs
and I found these in a chandelier.
This castle, sometimes I wonder if it's all just a big joke.
Probably is.
What'd I say, I need at least like a thousand gold
for this run to be okay.
I'm gonna try and make my way to the right.
Oh boy, no, this is like the harder area.
The dark blue is, if I'm not mistaken,
like level G.
These things are like level 38. I can take them.
I can take them.
They do a lot of damage though.
And how you level up in this game, you're probably not noticing
any experience bar.
And that's something I was pretty confused on myself as well.
You level up in this game
by doing upgrades
to your castle.
So for each upgrade you do to the castle,
defeat all enemies.
Oh, I can't, yep, I can't kill them.
Unless I had one of the different spells,
I cannot do this.
I have a randomly rolled character like you get in this game.
And I want to show you that,
because it's pretty hilarious.
But I can't do anything over there.
We're gonna stay up in this harder area,
because I feel like I'm being a wuss.
I have a level 65 right now,
and I'm staying away from the higher zones.
Yikes!
Get away!
Critical hit, got plenty of money.
Get outta here, Skellington.
Get outta here, Jack Skellington.
The Nightmare Before Christmas 2, Jack Skellington returns.
Level 44, this guy's gonna be a pain.
Get over here!
Come on, I'm a knight, you're a knight.
Let's knight it out. What? What?
Whatever, I'll just magic you to death, you punk.
I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die.
In this next area. Yep.
Goodbye. Oh, if I kill him though.
Nooo!
What the fu-
Okay, so we died, so now let's talk about death,
because death is actually pretty important
to progress through this game.
So that character just died, that was a knight.
And I'm back at the title screen now.
So I hit A, choose your heir.
And here are all the people that have died.
These are all the children before these children.
So this is the new blood, so to speak.
And if you look at them.
So class paladin, traits none.
Class archmage,
like I said, I've been building up some mages.
A powerful spellcaster, every hit gives you mana.
Trait, colorblind.
Now this is really important.
I can't see colors with this character.
If I pick this character,
the screen's gonna be black and white.
And everything far away is gonna be blurry.
All of your children,
after you die,
some of them can have, like, diseases.
And some of them can have, like, quirks.
And some of them can be different.
And that's one of the coolest things about this game.
Is the randomly rolled children you get.
So this guy, this guy has tunnel vision.
No peripheral vision.
And he has IBS.
He, like, FOTS.
Like, it's just so cool.
So we're gonna go ahead and pick, cause I cannot handle
playing the game with no colors.
It drives me insane.
I gotta pick one of these three. And I don't wanna pick the paladin.
Cause that's not really what I'm building.
So I wanna build the mage.
Let's pick that mage with the diarrhea.
And let's upgrade something.
So, probably use a little more HP.
Or I could do some more magic damage
for my mages. Let's go ahead and do that.
So right now, this is gonna upgrade.
Out of 75, by the way.
I got five points in here. Boink.
So that means my mages are gonna do more damage
with their spells. Pretty cool.
Okay, so now let me show you what I was talking about before.
I go up to this lady. This is the rune lady.
And I found some of those runes.
Here are the good ones, the new ones I found, apparently.
So spirit rune, this is a dash.
So if I equip this, I have this one.
You can only have one equipped per slot.
So I can only activate one of these.
And of course I have to buy these.
I have not bought them yet.
So this one, for instance, is when I kill someone
I get its life leech. I get health.
I get a couple HP points if this is turned on.
But if I turn this on,
that means I do not have this turned on,
which is a double jump.
And if I don't have that on,
that means I can't turn this on,
which makes the enemies scale slower and make them easier.
So there's a lot here.
Coins give more gold. Oh my god.
I want this so bad. I'm gonna have to unlock that next.
So it's very, very deep.
For as simple a game as it pretty much is,
there's a lot to it.
And you can stack these runes.
So let's say I have
all my bracers here.
These are the bracers I have on.
Vampire rune.
And I have Vampire rune on my helmet as well.
So that's even more HP per kill.
And if I have it on my sword,
that's even more HP per kill.
So you can really build cool characters.
And this guy,
what this guy does is he makes it so
the dungeon, like I said,
is randomly generated.
He makes it so the dungeon is not randomly generated.
But I get 70% money.
I lose 30% gold.
So he locks down the dungeon for you.
If you know, if you remember where everything was,
and you don't care about taking a money hit,
you can talk to that asshole right there.
But we're gonna keep moving.