I need to wait for you to disable that camcorder. You take out that camcorder. Hold on
Figure it out. There's a lot more to hacking than there is walking down an alley and getting caught
My screen is four different windows of views and each one has a tutorial on it right now
Put the pager. Martin can lure enemies away from their post by calling a throne pager. A throne pager.
So apparently I can throw this pager and this guy's gonna go get it
Can you make that thing buzz?
Oh shit, you just did that, okay? Yeah, I just called it. So I just sprint by this guy. Oh, he turned. It's okay
Is he still turning?
I think he's fine
Stop calling that stop that
Okay, you just know you idiot you like
Are hammering my brain
Yes
Well, there's a gun in here too, hey plug me in plug me in oh fuck was that the computer we were supposed to use
No, there's three people in here they'll all hear you
Throw your fucking pager. I don't have I don't have my pager anymore. Oh no
I'm running
I'm running, I'm running, they don't see me. No, he's hurt. He's running towards your door. He's running towards your door
He's about to go through the door. He's walking through the door. Just sneak over here. His pathing is bad. He couldn't do it
No, he's coming. He's coming. Oh shit. I'm hiding. I'm hiding. I'm hiding. He's in. He's not gonna find me
You gotta shoot you gotta shoot him
No one heard that
You're clear to go ghost rider. All right. Thanks a lot tango bango. He's coming up the stairs
He's coming dude. Shoot him in the fucking face. Hold on page page him page him page him page him
Page page. I did I paged keep doing it
Just keep paging it this page
Page quick
Make it a break make it a break for it
Can I please stand the fuck up that'd be great stand up I saw you
He's coming around he's coming around figure it out right now. He's looking at the ocean
You can snap his neck snap his neck. He turned he heard you walk
No, all right. Where am I hiding? Where is he gonna go?
What the fuck was that? You scared the shit out of me. What'd you do?
What happened? What did you do?
What oh god
You're not gonna keep an eye on these cameras, oh, I there's people there's three people coming for you. Oh, come on run run
Where am I running to?
Right, right. I don't know where to run to right?
I've got hiding up there. Stop there. Stop there. There's a guy coming in for you. He's marked three
Three people are coming in here right now. No, he's marked as three. He's close three is close to you. They're walking away
They're all walking away. By the way, I'm holding down G. I have to let go of this and throw this at some point. I
Can't let go of this
I have to let go of G to open the door with ease. I'm going to flashbang myself
Can't even open the door
I
Can I take okay, give me hammer. I want a hammer so bad. I don't know
How would you not know I'm behind you?
Trying to reach for your desk hammer. Yeah, I'm trying to get his hammer off his desk. He's still are you serious, dude?
Oh
God what the fuck what I
What?
All right, hold on hack his computer while he's on it I just I are I'm already hacked. Yeah, I'm on his computer
I'm looking at his emails
Okay, I let me browse it. Let me hold your mouse and browse your emails. Oh, thanks, dude
So there's a guy here I can if I can get three and at least the guy next to three
Mark the guy next to three so I'm gonna flash them. I could all they have three marked at a time. So that's why
You gotta be fucking kidding me
Turn around open door turn on door open
Got it on your right. Open that door door, right open it
This guy sees you down the hallway. Keep going down the hallway. All right, open this door open door. Don't leave. Don't leave
Okay, wait, wait guy hands the hallway guy and I'll run out of this door. There's a door on your right
That guy's checking the wrong room for you
Turn turn to your right. There's a door door. All right
Go back in the room
And right right door go got it
Forward forward forward forward forward forward you got it. Keep going. Keep going. Keep going. Right?
No, right
Inside
Keep going down this in this room in this room back right hand. There's a guy
He's not still alive
In front of you they're on your tail go go go go run run run door on your left left on your left get in
There run for double door right front front front front
What's going on?
Keep going keep going keep going there's gonna be a door on your left. You've got it doing left open it up Roger that
Okay, there's gonna be a guy around this corner. You're gonna want to kill him turn this corner. Shoot him in the face
You got a captain
In the face
Open this door. There's gonna be about three guys and you're gonna die. So immediately turn left double door. Okay
Hold on. Let me just open the door with my
Door
Turn around there's a man behind you fuck fire
Which one
That was the right guy
He's looking at the wall get this man. That's important crucial
Right here, right here. This is stairwell down here. I want you downstairs. You got it
Open door. Okay, come out this door. Come out this door and you're gonna go left double door double door and
Snatch it. Okay, keep running forward. No second. Oh, it's one. Oh, it's one. Oh stickers stickers stickers
All right
Okay, you're gonna want to go kill him. Oh my god. I can't
He wants your Snickers got him
He's done. You got it. Okay
Okay, through the run through that doorway. There's a guy back there in the cafeteria
All right, sir, which one just two double doors these ones this one no other one back
Yeah, yeah hide in this room hide in the corner behind the door
This has happened so many times