Hey, how are you? Welcome to the stream. Good afternoon. Sorry, it was a little tied up.
Available now. Today we're going to be playing Nancy Drew, Midnight in Salem. You're probably
wondering what's the bet that I lost. One guy strikes again. And this is actually one guy
from yesterday or the day before. So somebody said this and it just, hey, do Nancy Drew. I would love
it. I'm like, oh, why would I fucking ever do this? And the two days went by or day went by. I slept
on it and I woke up and I'm like, yeah, okay. I mean, they are, let me be fair. They were at least
another like 30 or 40. One guy is in the game. Uh, not in the game, in the chat before the stream
started that also said this is a good idea. Why did you pick the worst Nancy Drew? This one just
released. This one just came out. This is the brand new one. This is the one that came out literally
two days ago. This one sucks. You guys act like I don't have at least three, four to 10 Nancy Drew
games on backup, ready to go. This one sucks ass. This one sucks ass. That person was not happy
about it. There's 32. There's, there's, there's, there's as many Nancy Drew games as I've had
birthdays. Just play them all. Why would I, that's not, that's not going to happen. It would have to
take something extreme for me. I would have to play for 20 minutes in this and go, yep, we're
doing all of them. Play them all. Play them all. Stream. Money stream to force German to play them
all. No, that would not work. I'm going to tell you right now, those of you that are like, oh yeah,
money, let's money stream and he'll do it. I'm not going to do it. So if there, if you do a money
stream, just be aware that is not going to do anything. That's not going to do anything.
That's not going to make me play Nancy Drew one for 32. Just to make sure we're aware of that.
But now this continues of our non-canon week. And what that means is every stream you've seen this
week didn't happen. None of these are canon. They've all, they're all in the extended universe.
So knowing that it's like, fuck it, let's play Nancy Drew, Midnight in Salem. You know,
fuck it. Didn't miss anything canon. No, not yet. So this is the, this is the one that came up two
days ago. And here's the thing about this. I have never played any, a single second of Nancy Drew.
So this is all new to me. I haven't played any, I've been one time in college,
Nancy Drew two. I do remember friends of mine were actually playing it in the dorm rooms there.
So they had, they had the hookup where they could do more than three, four computers together. So
I got to see it. I sat down and I did a little bit of a puzzle for like two minutes and I was like,
all right, whatever. And there's a lot of these, I know this is a really, really established
franchise, but I've never done it. So, and this is a scary one and somebody's house is burning down.
Somebody gave $50. It's not going to do anything. It's not going to do anything.
I'm going to, okay, let's put a bracket here. Thanks for the $5,000. It's not going to do anything.
Thank you for, no, 5,000 bits. But if you tell me to play Nancy Drew four,
cause it's your favorite one, I'm not going to play it. Did someone say money stream also heard
you were offering private streams for $5,000 in McDonald's gift cards. I'll get on that,
but this is non-canon. This whole week is not canon. So that's not real.
Something that you should know about Nancy Drew, midnight in Salem, which is actually very,
very interesting. Um, there are like FPS game graphic settings in this game, real time
reflections, anti-aliasing, post-process shadow, shadow quality. There are more options in here
than I've seen in a lot of actual FPS releases, right? Look at this. They weren't fucking around
non-descript civilian. Thanks to the five community subs, this is more options than halo reach.
No, it doesn't. They have all these options, but it still has unity grass. Well, just let's give it
a, just let's give it a little bit. Okay. Unity. Yeah. All right. Here we go. New game difficulty
amateur sloth, master sloth as sleuth. And I feel, okay, this is, remember, this is a game for,
this is a game for like 15 year olds or something. This is like a 12 year old game, right?
So an amateur, an amateur 12 year old versus a master 12 year old. I think this is, this is like
for an adult like me, this is like, no, I have to do master. This is a kid's game. British accent,
British accent, British. Fuck. Get an old relic.
That's fucking terrifying. You don't want to go here. Oh, the place is supposed to be haunted.
So yeah, I might get killed in here. I might get fucking eaten by a demon, but oh,
I'm looking forward to the scares. It feels like ages since I was on my last adventure.
So are you coming in? Miss Drew, I prefer to stay out here. Is it an FPS? It's so
warm and inviting in here. Where am I? Is this my house? Suel's effects are there. Just as your
father requested. This house is fucked. I just write letters in my fucking crumbling house.
I haven't been to the grocery store in like fucking years. Click to move. No, it's a click.
What is this tablet version? Hey, it's like, hey, just to let you know, get this on your iPad.
It's probably better. Oh, that was easy. That's not a good view. That's a terrible view. It's
just trees. I mean, I guess that the mountain's kind of cool. Click on the screen just to turn.
Yeah. What's going on in here? Is this person talking to me while we're both in the bathroom
and they're in the stall while I'm washing my hands? And then somebody else comes in the
bathroom and you're like, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck. Hey, hey, stop talking. It's odd what we're
doing because they don't know that somebody just, oh yeah, we just came into the bathroom, but
like just us two, it's like, nobody says Alice is here. You're in the stall. I'm like just
doing my, I'm just like fucking shaving. I'm like picking my nose hairs out and you're just
talking. You're just monologuing to me from the stall. And then some old guy walks in
and I don't think, just slow down. All right, interact. Hold to look. I found a letter.
It's addressed to Abigail Hathorne Woodley. What does it say? I do regret to write to you in this
state. I have been wracked with guilt as my fervency of spirit was too great to determine
a conviction. Just Nancy, just sell this. This is probably worth like eight grand for gods.
Somebody else will read this way. I have to read this, don't I? I regret to write you in
the state of wracked with guilt as my spirit is too great to determine conviction. Just
relentlessly have I cried at his mercy, longing for his light to bathe my conscious clean. Wait,
read. You read it. To write the wrongs I made in zealous blindness, I'm writing a book I call
the Book of Apologies. To be worthy of his mercy, I'm traveling the world to note down all the names
of those wrongfully accused of witchcraft. Let this be my final legacy, my only way to write the
wrongs I've helped create. My guilt allows me not to ask for forgiveness, though know that my soul
remains forever tortured by the knowledge of what I have done. All right, any like fucking codes?
Ooh, here we go. You didn't think I was gonna click on this shit, did you?
Press the secret button, go into grandpa's secret compartment. I wouldn't do this. No, I wouldn't
do this. I wouldn't. Because if like, I don't know, if like grandpa has like a secret fucking door in
a compartment and shit, I don't know what's in here. They could be drugs. They could be like,
I don't know, this is like porn collection from like fucking like the 40s or stuff. I don't want
this. In fact, I would probably I would just burn this thing. I don't know what's in here. I need
a key that shaped like a U. This is on master difficulty, just so you guys know. I'm going to
examine. Okay, that's scary. Dr. Hurst? Yes. Yes, I'm here. Just come in the room. Why are you
standing outside the door? Just come into the room? And why is there dialogue options? What else can
you tell me about the book of apologies? I want to know. What else can you tell me about the book
of apologies? As I mentioned, it's the book written by Judge Samuel Sewell himself, detailing
the names of people accused of witchcraft. Sewell was one of the very few judges who regretted his
actions. You take a long time in the bathroom, by the way. You have places to go. Sewell himself
was originally from England, but acted as a judge in the Salem witch trials. Do you perhaps know why?
The whole game is played with the vote. Just out of curiosity, of course. It's
just such a very unusual request. He's looking into it as a favor for the current judge in Salem.
Oh, how much is that fucking making you guys angry? Not only is there a cursor on the screen always,
but it's moving. So I have to look at it. Humans are like cats. That's why nobody wants a cursor
on the screen. Because if I go over here, you know, me, I just went through the right. If I go this
way, you're following it right now. I am. So are you. You're looking, right? Ready? You're looking
in the lower left portion of the screen right now. And by the way, we're going to take it. We're
going to do a theory here and we'll see in like, in like 30 minutes, I'm going to tell you exactly
where you're looking. And it's going to be that one of those magic trick shows where like you got
to participate. All right. Who cares? Let's go. All right. Every desk, there's going to be like
one ring. Wow. The hammer of witches itself gives me chills knowing what it did. Yes.