I was muted for a long time. Usually I don't take that long. I know that a lot of streamers on this platform
Sometimes don't a lot of people do like a 25 minute countdown or something. I couldn't do that. I just sit here and
Two three minutes go by and i'm just like I i'm supposed to say something, right?
I could never do like a 20 minute countdown to start the streams
It would get to 17 minutes and I would just scream and press the unmute button and be like i'm guys i'm here
I haven't been i've just been here for 15 straight minutes. He sounds different
I got I got a little bit of a nose bug. It'll clear up wasp
Here comes the end of the stream. No, what?
That's not what's happening
i'm ready to play
end of the stream voice and so okay, first of all, I
Somebody just clipped to that
what
Why?
What did I do there?
Somebody just clipped whatever I just said
It was me
Why he doesn't know it's kind of funny because I see in real time when somebody takes a clip
It's a little thing on my dashboard
And i'm always sometimes I get self-conscious because i'll be like blah blah blah. Yeah. Yeah, yada. Yada
Can I look over a new clip and i'm just like what happened?
What did I do?
Should I not have said that what?
Who are you sharing that with?
Nah, how you guys doing? Hope you had a good relaxing
A couple of days. Hope you had uh had some fun. Hope you did some things. Hope you were productive
Probably you were productive as well, you know
Today we're gonna play vista or cleanup detail because you know, I just feel like cleaning shit up
I'm in the mood for kenshi
Yeah, kenshi is a lot of fun
But i've been away from vista. I played it once
And I had a shitload of fun. So I want to do it again
I just like cleaning things up sometimes
It's my guilty video game pleasure
house flipper
Vista or cleanup detail. It's easy just to mop stuff up on the ground and talk about chrono trigger
You know what I mean?
Anyways, uh, i'll be right back
Give me two seconds. I just want to make sure the game opens and doesn't crash
We're right back. It's not a guilty pleasure if you share it with 5 000 people. What?
That could be a guilty pleasure still
Okay, how is that not still a guilty pleasure? All right, you know, whatever we're right back
Like if I robbed a bank on stream, that would be guilty. That'd be a guilty pleasure, right?
Like i'm gonna i'm gonna go i'm going to jail
All right, we're good
No, that's not what i'm talking about. You guys know i'm talking about like in grand theft auto 5 when you do a heist with
Your friends
I would go to the in-game video game jail context. You gotta have the context
Otherwise, wait, what the hell does that mean?
Gotta do revengeance dlc. Yeah, there's a lot of things to do
I like cleaning by myself. I don't like I don't like other people cleaning with me
I don't want somebody to clean my room with me because what if they find like the dirty underwear and
crushed up fucking
Hot pocket wrappers. No, that's my it's a guilty pleasure of mine hot pockets, you know
They're disgusting. I haven't eaten one in probably four years. Don't take that as an endorsement
Uh, save file. I don't have any on this one. This is okay. We're gonna do
Clean up
So now we get to pick
Which one of these should I do today one hour one hour two hours 30 minutes evil science looks kind of cool
zero g therapy
incubation emergency
up rinsing
Do a straw poll this so there are too many things to choose from I can't do a straw poll
But this will take like 30 minutes to write all these
I think uh evil science seems like kind of fun
either that or
What is this one penumbra ice moon research outpost?
Smart click smart click ain't gonna work here. Don't let dumb chat choose for you
Like these only take like two hours. Okay. I'm gonna get through look. I know how to play now
I'm gonna do evil science
The two hours and 30 minutes add like two hours of germa time
So it's gonna be like four hours and 30 minutes and then I could do another one
That's like an hour, which is like add like add plus one hour of uh of time
Yeah, I can do two
Evil science. Let's see if I can get this done in like three hours. I think I can
Worksite game rules, uh foot. No, we're gonna keep it here
Time limit. What is that 300 minutes?
No, no time limit that'll that'll get that'll fuck me up
I'll get to the end and it'll really that'll get under my skin so much
Disable the sniffer. No, keep a sniff. I want that footprints. That's fine. I can't make mistakes
I'm ready
Start work. Why are we still not playing big? What?
What what is that? What word did you just say? Okay, we're gonna start work
I'm gonna do it till my hands burn. I'm gonna do this until my hands burn
Oh, okay
Name janitor age 25 junior executive janitor given the nature of the janitor work that was carried out within the last facility
Your absolute discretion is paramount. Didn't I have a computer and shit on the other safe file?
Federation representatives will be arriving in a week that it is imperative that the facility be cleaned and organized before said time
Failure to perform your duties within company protocol on time will result in immediate termination
You are most assuredly an expendable piece within an organization that is in your best interest to conduct yourself
Admirably be absolutely certain that the facility is spotless
Guaranteed hygienic and in working order. All right, welcome back to viscera cleanup detail. My name is german on a5
Let's get this party started
Uh, where do I go? Let's take a look first
Is it aliens in here?
Hold on. Let's take a look at the big hallway. I'm gonna get lost in here doesn't look too bad
big hallway leading down to
uh
Uh, I can always tell when i'm really mouth open have no idea. I just didn't think the butt head
Uh-huh. So these are all locked
Am I gonna have to get all right? I just need to look first
Shave us. Okay
Maybe you should buy yourself a narco
Let's get the music on here. What? Oh, how do I how do you pick items up again?
e
Well, right need the hands right and then there's a way to whoops
Is it shift?
z
alt
right click
Hold left click. There it is. Look at that
Okay, what's on the music file here?
Oh, that's right. I turned it all off because we were listening to chrono trigger
What's the music on this one? Uh, I listened to that for like three hours
Okay
That's all right. That's what those are both the same song
That's too intense for me. I didn't I need something less intense
now that's
Too quirky for me. I don't like the generic cassio keyboard drum beat
No, all right. Sounds all right
No, no skunks in the machine
No
No, no, no, no
I think I want this one
All right. Let's take a look. We got a lot of ground to cover
There's a lot of ground to cover
uh
Upper level is this an elevator?
No, it's not how big is this? Oh my god. This is gonna take me like 12 hours. Look at this mess
And there's multiple locked doors
Oh
Okay, I need to still we got i'm gonna start up top
Yeah, i'm gonna start up top
Because i'm gonna work my way down
What do we get water in this one? The other one was like had elves in it and there was a funny elf machine
Do I can I do I have to bring buckets upstairs for this shit?
All right. I'm ready. No, i'm not ready. I'm so overwhelmed right now go out outside and down
Okay, here is the trash machine. Let's just start in front of the elevator
I don't know what to do. This is what happened in real life
If you walked into a scene like this
And you were told all right, you got to clean that up. You'd be like, okay
You don't know where the fuck to start
Okay, let's go
I'm gonna start right in front. I need to throw i'm so overwhelmed. I really am this is like hey Jeremy
This is why you play it with like five people
Not me. I need to clean alone
All right, we made some progress
Look at we already made progress. I didn't have to do anything. No, I have friends
But I don't
I I like to clean alone
And plus like somebody would say like a funny joke and I would miss it
I'd be too busy going like this
Oops, I have friends of it. I don't well, come on man. I just moved to vegas
I don't know anybody out here
How am I supposed to connect with my friends? I moved to vegas
We bought the internet. Oh, that's right. This isn't that we're on the internet
I can just call them on the internet phone
I love this game. It really is so much fun just to do nothing
Does anybody else feel that way too?
Is it weird that remember we were talking about
Stuff. Hey, Jeremy, what would you do if you weren't like screaming?
this
I would probably want to do this dude. I would do you know what i'm talking about. I would just sit here
I would just put on the joe rogan podcast man and just like zone the fuck out
I like this idea though, because then i'm gonna make sure there's nothing on the ceiling. Nothing anywhere. You kidding me, man
Oh, I would just open up children's surprise egg videos
On repeat while I just did this it'd be amazing
Because I don't know man. Like what's what's in that egg?
Open it
Oh, it's a mini spider-man. Whoa. Awesome. I don't know. It was in that egg. It could have been anything
What's in the next one?
A hatchimal. Oh, yeah
I've seen those before. Hey, what do we got binoculars?
Can I look in them? No, I can't even can't. I love fuck you a lemon lime binoculars
What's this biohazard material?
Hey, you know, I had one of these
No, no, no, not a bed pan. Not a bed pan. I had
I had one of these
I did I owned one of these
Who'd somebody just gave a shitload of subs?
Uh, jinxibo just gave five community subs. Thank you
Thank you so much jinxibo
All right. Now come on. I need to bound
Where's the where's the fire for this thing?
In the christmas month, there was a big giant fire. Where's the giant fire?
Is this a fire?
If you are attacked or severely injured, please report to the nearest medical facility treatment. What do you mean attacked?
What the hell is this?
toilet seat pizza slicer
What?
Why are they giving out toilet seats?
toilet seats
I got a feeling
That i'm gonna have to replace toilet seats
Okay, that's fine. And I might no i'm not tracking. All right, we got this place almost clear
I need to I need to find the big fire in the middle. I need to find where the santa comes down
That looks like where santa comes down. Oh, yeah it is
Mm-hmm
Uh-huh
Mm-hmm. This guy's not still alive is he?
I don't know if I'd want to fuck with that guy that guy had on one of the backpack super soakers
Remember you were when you were a kid
You got in the super soaker fight
You got your
And it stopped and the little the little p came forward
That motherfucker rolls up with the backpack on
You're all in trouble. Oh that just scared the shit out of me
All right, hold on I gotta I gotta put the I gotta put the giant maggots in here
Are these gonna fit?
That fits right? Yeah
I'll come back later
I hate this music
All right, we got some cells here
I don't want to listen to this but i'm going to
Holy shit
Is this an alien?
All right. I don't like that. I don't like that
I don't the eyes. I don't know what's going on with the eyes
those eyes
You know what i'm saying when i'm talking about the eyes
They're like perfect cartoon eyes
All right. Well
I found the incinerator
I don't like that one. All right. So where was I? How much time has elapsed? 21 minutes. Oh boy
I'm never gonna get this done in two hours. Yes, I am
It's so big
What is this?
A box? Okay, I can put some stuff in here and then put this in the fire
No, no, no, no get
All right. This is a whole nother. This is the exit
Yeah
I need to bring some uh barrels around here
I've got shell casings everywhere. This was an fps. That's for sure
One of the funnest coolest parts about this game is just figuring just seeing it out
What is this? Is this an fps or was this like an rts or an rpg? It's real like this is an fps
So cool. All right. Can you stop please? What why?
Why what?
Why is this still happening?
Okay, we're fine now apparently I need a bucket. We gotta go middle out. I think there's no way
I'm gonna walk across this whole time
Can I pick up the?
Can I pick up the thing that generates?
No, no, just start just kidding. I'm getting distracted. Stop getting distracted. Give me one of these
Give me like five of these
Does dynamite come out of this thing?
What's the joke for this one?
What's what's like the the thing that pops out of here? I mean, so here's a joke right here
But that's I mean, that's still kind of funny
All right, let's put this one back here
I don't get much to do over there. I gotta incinerate that
I gotta get a mental mapping of where that incinerator is fucking is
Okay mental map of where the incinerator is here we go ready
Straight and then you take a right. Nope. You don't straight then left. It's right there
I got a mental map now mentally decoded into my brain
I'm gonna leave it open. Why even just leave it open?
Okay
We got to go from back here
I'm gonna do this now
All right, get in there
Toasty that wasn't even funny
That wasn't even supposed to be funny. This was filling air
I was just filling dead air
Oh well, this has got to go too
Play the super mario brothers ost rpg. No, no, that was super mario brothers
All right. I'm ready. I need another one of these buckets not tracking. No, i'm not
Beautiful beautiful come up this way. What are you doing to me? Oh, by the way, does the audio sound better today?
Am I a little louder today than I was a couple days ago?
I should be
I boosted myself a little I don't think this is gonna fit in here. Is it gonna fit in here?
I think it's gonna exactly fit in here
It fits. All right. Good
Now I just need a few more buckets. Oh, yeah
A spill joke plus three
Yeah, go ahead keep track of all the times that I spill
Do it
Because then we're gonna do we're gonna go through and do some deductions
No, why would I tell you to count in this chat?
That's something we don't want people doing
Every time that channel meme has a chance
To just go away
What do I do?
What's the first thing that I say after about two weeks of that meme people not doing it?
Take give me like a counter. That's my own fault. This is gonna explode
No, I need some new buckets. I need none of these just put them in a pile over here
So I can keep dragging them. You literally know i'm was counting until you complained that everyone would count
Do you see the vicious cycle?
It's me. It's my own fault. I'm the outlier here
I'm the issue here
It's not you guys counting. It's me
I'm the problem
All right
No blood no bullshit over here. This is pretty clean
Just make sure the green is not alien goo, right?
See i'm the one that's counting
On you guys to be good in chat
I can do it. All right, get that out of here. We're almost done guys. We're getting close
We're almost done with the entry way
of the level
Which is designed
For an 11 year old to do it
And no, I know 11 year old is playing this game. This is not like a game for kids
Why would I even make that comparison?
No, like 10 year old is playing this that's not happening
They are
No, they're not
There's only one game that a 10 year old is playing right now. Can you guess what it is?
ooh
Wait, what fortnight?
Minecraft, what are you talking about?
You guys are way off
Oh, that's not a computer. What? Come on. It is a computer though. Is this a computer?
I need a computer
Is this the computer?
Where's the computer where this goes?
over here
I don't know where these go. What's that?
Is it upstairs?
It's probably in a different room
Got it
Nope, that's the elevator
Where's it gonna put it over here?
It's where I spawned though. I just can't believe nobody has said the games at all every 10 year old is playing right now
I'll give you a hint
It's on a phone
mafia city
What the hell is mafia city?
I've been asked again to reinforce the cell doors. I really don't see the point. They're strong enough
I mean we could possibly get through those. I've got more important jobs anyways
Yeah, mafia city. Did I play that like four years ago?
I think I did
Isn't that one of those games I played?
It's some stupid game
Sponsored mobile stream
All right. I will I will get I will guarantee you guys something
If there's ever a sponsored mobile game stream on this account
It's not me
It's not me and and somehow they've impersonated me. I don't know how
I think if you if you see that on this stream, this is sponsored mobile game stream
And i'm like, hey guys, what's going on? Welcome to the stream. I'm in trouble somewhere
Like i've done
I don't know
Who would sponsor you?
Yeah, that's a good question. Hey, you know, that's a good question
PUBG mobile stream, but that was me on my own free will
That wasn't me sponsored to play that
Oh
I'm in trouble somewhere
It's up the ruiz is up
That was the last stream I I ever did is me
Wait, I played pubg willingly. I don't know. Not really
Yeah, I did what I played pubg on mobile for like 10 minutes
Because it was a joke
That doesn't count
Yeah, that doesn't count though. I played it on stream with you looking over my shoulder
It was almost best gaming moment of 2018
We all know that
I played an entire game and I won
Someone help him
Oh his dinosaur tracks gotta be careful
I got killed by bots. What do you mean got killed by bots? I played one game and won
I got the chicken dinner
I didn't I I got I played it once
You play with bots until level five and I was level 14 in that video. Go look at him
My I know my username. It's like aragon or something. I did like a look at me lord of the rings thing when I was lying in bed
You can look that up
I was a little 14
So I was playing with
Like can I use this?
What in the whoa? Okay
Should I put should I hide this?
Why would they give this to me? Are there monsters in this level?
Uh, okay. Well, I need to make sure I know what this is
I'm gonna put this right next to the slosh of matic
Because I will forget what that is halfway through this game
All right, i'm not looking too bad over here
Except for right there, but I got it
Uh-oh
No, I got i'm fine. We're good
Fix his bullet holes. Okay. Okay
Thanks for the tip man
Read chat read chat. I I I am what i've been reading this whole time
I've been reading so much of the chat room. Yeah, one would say I might be reading too much chat
So i'm gonna go on chat restriction i'm not gonna look at chat for like a full two minutes I promise
Okay
All right looks good
This thing I don't know what the hell this thing's for. I'm sure i'll find out somebody will be
screaming at me
I'm gonna walk by the thing. I'm gonna walk by the toilet seat thing like four times
How do we look? All right. This is not bad
Does this count as trash? It probably does
There's uh, there's paint cans over there. All right. Hold on. Let me clean this up
Get rid of this
Mike muted. Oh, he's reading chat again. That's been two minutes
Look at me. Look at me. Look at me. Look at me. That's the one thing I read the thing that I know is not real
If mike muted, that's the first thing I read
Let's get it. Sometimes I look over and the chat's just sprinting by so that's why I have to pick something out and read it
Like for instance somebody just said say banana
Okay
Looks good. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
Oh, yeah, right. That's keep that there
Toilet seat, uh, I don't need this
What is this stuff?
warning cryogenic storage
Okay
I don't know why that's making me laugh. It shouldn't that's not even I don't know why that's funny to me right now
If you're fast enough, you can read us all. Okay sour, please burn gun. Don't burn. No. Okay cryogenic. Haha
Do tongue twisters while cleaning stuff. Jeremy you have
Uh, no buttons Joe. Okay, sorry got it. That's as much as I could do
Can't do any more than that. I'm gonna take this down the hall
All right. Speaking of ipad music, that's ipad game music. I need something else
Is there monster noise?
Doom ost now i'm never gonna play the doom ost ever again
I've played the doom ost more than anyone on this whole website. I could probably bet any amount of money
If you take a look at twitch statistic somewhere
Who has played the doom soundtrack the most on on every between every account
I would be probably up. I would have like a huge advantage already
German mustard ost. What was that?
Play the persona 5 ost. No. All right. Hold on a second here guys. I need somebody to tell me this because I
Did I ask this question already before?
I think I may have asked this question before
What the fuck is persona 5?
Did I ask this?
Is it it's like a life simulator. I tried watch the trailer and I couldn't figure out what the game was
He's hitting
Balls in a batting cage. He's talking to somebody like a coffee shop
I don't know what the game is
It's a turn-based fighting game with social stuff
because
Persona 3 was a full-on
turn-based rpg
Is that the same game?
Is that the same like are they the similar genres or they different persona 3 had social bits
Same game but better
Oh get in there
Get in there
Why what's in the way?
There's nothing in the way what?
Get your body in there. Okay
Mafia city ost that's not gonna happen. Whoa. Hold on a second medical
I don't really need to get rid of this. There's nothing wrong with it
I you know, I would put on the star wars ost, but i'll probably go to prison so I can't do that guys. Sorry
You know, it would be like funny like somebody play like put put a youtube video up
you play
oh, here's the uh, here's the full ost of
star wars
Just start with like the empire strikes back music the empire music
And then intercut in the middle like a siren
That would be kind of funny. That would be like a really really funny joke. I think
so it'd be like
Uh
That would be a bad joke that's the worst joke of 2019 that's worse joke in the last five years
That's the worst joke in the last 10 years. That's the worst thing i've ever said
Ever and I mean ever and i'm talking about in my life
In my whole fucking life and 3,500 people just heard it
Oh, I just spit all over my mouth because in the middle of that. I was like abort. This is not good
This is not funny, but my brain was like no just keep just try to just try to hash it out
Nope, that's the worst thing i've ever said
It was such a better way to do that too
Oh
All right. I'm gonna like turn the stream off and turn it back on and pretend we just started
It was the whole package
I knew it was gonna be bad too, but sometimes something you gotta commit
You can tell that I was having strong conflicting opinions of it, too
After the first like dun dun dun dun you can hear my voice like stop and then to say something else change it
I didn't change the channel. I stayed on fucking qvc. What am I doing?
No, no, hey, all right, it's time to start it over. Hey everybody. Welcome to the stream
I'm peeking the microphone right now
Did I have I've been peeking?
Who just gave money?
Stormy chew just gave 50 dollars
Thank you so much stormy chew
Hey german chat been a while since i've been able to watch your streams due to my new time zone
but just wanted to say
Uh, keep being great. You deserve this. I also hope you and chat had a good new year. Thank you
Stormy chew. Hope you had a great
New year's eve. Hope you have a great new year
Thank you so much for the 50 dollars
That's a lot of fucking money
No, i'm not doing the joke again
no
50 dollars start of the stream. Yeah
I'll say it. I'll say it again
Sometimes people come in here and they just drop fucking huge money
And you know, it's been not even 45 minutes
Thank you, that's fucking ridiculous. Thank you weird flex. No, no i'm saying i'm saying that I can't believe it
You know what it's been a few minutes i'm starting to like it I think I like that joke though
Yeah, don't delete the spot. Keep it up
Mitchell just gave five community subs. Thank you so much. Mitchell. I'll pay 50 dollars if you never make that joke ever again
Well, I can promise you that i'll never make that joke ever again. Why would I do that again?
I'm not gonna double down on the embarrassing fucking terrible dumb shitty joke. I just made it
That wasn't even a joke. It was me pretending. I was watching a youtube video, but there's no context there
I tried to give context in 10 seconds
And it just that don't work like that if I made that video and played it on stream, that would be funny
It'd be really funny if I actually made that video and like put it. Hey, there's here's like an ost for star wars
Now that's funny
No, it's not
I think that's kind of funny if I didn't say anything about it before
I think I'd get a few
I would get two L's and then a circle in the middle from some people in the chat. I think
All right. This is looking this is looking good
I like this so far
Let's move this up
Put on some music. All right. What are we gonna put on for music? Let's get something good
Something that we can all hang out and enjoy
By the way for every doom ost I see in the chat. I'm going to repeat the siren joke
A full cycle. I sometimes I forget. Oh, yeah people want me to like embarrass myself. Sometimes I forget about that
Put on plock
Plock ost what?
Holy shit. That's like a decade ago. I remember plock
Plock ost
This is an old one. This is this is the the
You throw your limbs, right?
Okay, is that a good volume? I think so
That's rocky
This is just rocky
That's cool
I have a siren place
All right, was that the intro can you recreate an acapella version of the song that you just heard
What no what?
Pretty good banjo kazooie song
I need that thing in here
Oh
How fucked up is it going to be when they finally make banjo kazooie 3
And it's fully voice acted and they ruin everything
No, no, no, don't pick up the torso
Banjo is gonna be fucking chris pratt
Oh, I needed that
Am I no i'm not tracking now i'll do banjo kazooie. Yeah, i'll do banjo kazooie ost
Get these limbs in here
Somebody got a uh
Somebody got the rocket launcher in the other room. This guy is in a hundred pieces
I have you muted and i'm playing the doom ost because you refuse to
why
Why can't
That's such a
That's such a passive aggressive thing to say
Or is that regular aggressive? I don't know
Can I play chungo ost? I don't know what that is
I like I don't cronk pull the lever. I don't know what that is. Like I don't get it
All right, I think this can fit in here
What do I do with the stinger?
That's too awkward. It's gonna go in by itself
Any more little bits?
I'm gonna play this song at my wedding
and now introducing
Mr. And mrs. Elbertson
I'm gonna really fucking piss off my grandfather
What the hell?
Unbelievable. What is this music? This is not closing time from green day. Oh terrible wedding
Oh, this is dirty. No, they're not closing time. What's what's the green day song?
The song does not even please fall if he had it why I hope you have a high high
What is that one?
That one's called good riddance
No, no, no, it's called time of your life, right?
That's what i'm talking about
Wait, actually, maybe good riddance probably doesn't sound like a good song for a wedding
good riddance
What's like the graduation one? No, it's closing time
That's the graduation wedding
You did it celebration song. Yeah closing time
Graduation is good riddance
What?
No, no, there's two different songs here. There's
And then there's
I'm sorry this music started playing and it fucked up everything
It started playing that fucking alien music
The alien music really screwed it up
Didn't spill it. I win. I win. I win
I remember this level jojo part five ost
Now i'm not going to play anything jojo related on the stream
Nothing to do about don't
That is actually
Really really cool painting
Get a frame on that frame that up one, two, three four
Give it a good title and sell it
You'll make some fucking money
Really?
Actually, I really do like the way that looks that's what my new desktop background
I said that really weirdly desktop background
Should have screen shot of that. Yeah, I know fuck
You're right
fuck
Put on mother ost don't talk about my mother
I got I got a rhythm here. I got up. I got up. I got up
Great. Thanks. Thanks for nothing
The incinerator has two doors. Yeah, but then you're losing the
does the
You have to have one side closed. Otherwise all the air and the oxygen gets all fucked up. You need to have
This doesn't make the fire too crazy
Two doors open and let's all the oxygen out and then the fire goes out
Have you guys been camping before?
What do you think that accordion does when you stick the accordion in and you go?
The billow I need to bring in some
You bring it in
Yeah, what are you gonna do about the trash
What are you gonna do all with the fucking electronics the ipods?
All the takeout
Well, you guys don't order postmates to your tent
You're not doing it, right?
I forgot to get a bucket
nice
Quake bunny hopping that was an extreme spill joke. How's this for extreme? All right, it's right here. We good
Don't you guys understand? Here's the here's the thing
So a lot of people that are coming in going like what the fuck is this guy doing?
What's wrong with this person?
When I do when I sit here and I get to just I don't have to pay attention to anything
You know, this is just cleaning we can just hang out and just talk shit. This is what happens
My brain gets contained
When I have to focus on something else
My hair is up in like a fucking bun
When i'm streaming like a normal video game, my hair is down right now
Don't on the face cam. I don't have any clothes on I can't do that again achievement right there
Uh, how many more buckets do I need you think?
At least put on the ost
I'm not gonna put on a meme ost guys
You want me to solidify myself?
In the he did it
No, I don't want to look over and see he did it
Or no, it's all right. We did it
Come here
Uh, do we need to do this? I'll get rid of the barrels too. I'm gonna fuck it up. I'm getting rid of everything
Yeah, what the fuck is in the way?
Get in there
What? Oh, they're going off the other side
All right
We're almost the clock is almost done
Bring this over here. Just fucking whip it over there. No, don't
No, no blood. We're good
Mafia city ost. No, I haven't seen any good. I have not seen one good ost
You guys can do better than this. I know you can near automata
No, I don't want to do near automata
I'd rather play it
I don't want to experience the music yet until I play it
Damn, this is dirty mother three you wanker
easy
Easy, it's gonna be puke again. Yeah, I knew it just just storm over here
Yeah, this should be enough. I'm really feeling this
No, I don't want to play any copywritten. I don't want to play any actual real copywritten music
I'm not going to play star wars
I think you guys understand that
The disney ceo has an alarm clock
that just
buzzes
And somebody is watching or viewing star wars or listening to star wars music illegally
And he has a speed dial
from one of the five thousand lawyers
He doesn't even give a shit if it's the middle of the night
before in the morning
Who's watching star wars his wife just turns over and it's just like
Hold on. Sorry, sweetie
Some dudes playing the soundtrack
Play the celeste ost but I haven't played the celeste game
Then that I can't you know what I mean?
I need to know what it's like first. I have to experience it first
We got to go with stuff that i've experienced
spill joke ost
Yeah, just cut together the three times the two times I played this game
and then
Use like one of those auto tuners to every time i've spilled something
There you go
Play the stormwind entrance music and I don't hate that one
I don't hate it
I haven't heard that song in a long time
I got a better idea
Why don't we play?
WWF the music volume 2
That sounds like a pretty good idea
Oh don't break anything
Actually good. Uh, yeah
All right. If a magician can do it I can too
Apparently not
I just rolled that no open it
open
We're gonna play a game. We're gonna play every wwf the music volume
And we're gonna see if I can tell you who it is
Just based on their entry music now i'm curious now i'm curious as to hold on. I just got
I just got an achievement for doing that. I need to see something here
I let me save this because if there's a I don't they might be a problem here
So I need to save this
That was plock. That was pretty good. Everybody loves plock
All right, wwf the music
volume
One are you ready? Uh, let's see if I can get these all you're playing
Uh, this one's coming out of like one ear. So let's try the other one
Okay, let's see if I can figure all these out
This is the undertaker. All right, I already know it's the undertaker
I already got it and he goes
Told you
I miss old undertaker
Give me a couple of these
I miss old germa
Do you though? Do you really you miss modern warfare 3 and minecraft and speed?
Be certain about this
Well, at least no don't make that not funny
Clean clean dirty ceiling not clean i'll take care of that right now
So I know close this side. I don't need it open
Yeah, this is before he had the uh, like the rock music. This is original undertaker
paul bearer
Oh, no, don't don't if you if you're in the chat right now, don't look at the chat
Don't even look at it, but i'm one for one right now
I wonder who's next the stone cold is gonna be on here. The rock's gonna be on here volume two
This is 1997 98. I wonder who else is on here. It's definitely gonna be stone cold. Who's next?
You are completely pathetic
All right, it's stone cold, I don't remember that part
I don't remember him saying that I didn't that didn't sound like steve austin
This shit's fucking loud
That's a little bit better
Decibel volume this room is pretty much done. I gotta get off the top there though. Don't I?
Look at the spot i'm missing over there. I can get that watch this
You know you can start begging for some mercy right now
Because you ain't got what it takes to stay in the ring where stone cold steve austin from bell to bell
When did he narrate this song? I don't remember that
I'd no I could I think I could
I think I could take one full closed fisted punch as hard as he could in the face
And then that would be it I'd have to go to the hospital but I think I could do it
Like i'm talking he goes off the ropes as fast as he can and double crow hop sprint punches me in the face as hard
As he can
I think I could do it
How does that why can I not be like you
What the fuck stop are we gonna get any more?
Oh, okay, we're gonna get any more like pull the string on the back of the toy and give one of my four catchphrases
Got it. Fuck is that enough?
That's the bottom line
All right. Yeah, that's that's why he actually had things. He said he didn't just go what?
What?
I don't know who this is
Who is this familiar? But I don't know who this is not john cena john cena wasn't even alive right now
John cena john cena was like four years old
All right, almost down with this room. It looks very clean
Oh fuck there's knives
Shit, can I reach this?
Did I ruin that forever? No, I didn't right?
I got it one little knife
That's matching up with the music
Looks pretty good. I'm almost happy with it. Not quite
This is a watch. That's a nice pocket watch
Did you know that i'm three years?
Three years older than john cena
Uh john cena is like 41 so I don't think that's correct
Three years older than john cena. I know
I know john cena is older than me
because
You don't do the i'm in random christmas movies with mark walberg
Unless your career is now turning into like you're older and you don't do what you used to do anymore
Uh, he's he's not like 32. He can still shoulder block the same way
What
I don't even know what that means. I haven't watched john cena wrestle
I don't know what he I don't even know what he looks like
If you had like seven john cena's in a lineup, I don't know if I could figure out which one is the real john cena
All right. Well that was that was not john cena. Is this uh, oh who is this? This is uh
Who the fuck is this?
I think this is
sable
Is it?
Like cat screams
Did I get it right I don't
No
Nobody knows a run
Uh, i'm not listening for anything
I
Oh, all right
I gotta compose myself here. I'm fucking losing my mind
Oh, look at all this trash
No, there's too much trash over here. Hold on
I don't even know what to say
I gotta play the game
Oh nobody don't even whatever i'm flaying
Did I tip it? I did
oops
Okay. Well that was uh, I don't know who that was
I thought it was sable
Uh, is this the undertaker? No, this is the undertaker's alter ego like the overtaker
And he's like nice
He's not like a demon. He's from heaven
Mustang sally
What?
I don't know
I don't know who the hell this is
This is the era that I watched the most
And I don't know who this is
So much copywritten music
I don't think anyone's gonna dmca this
Who even has the rights to the music volume 2 the company's probably defunct at this point
This company probably went bankrupt in like
WWE well wwe is licenses it out. But who dmc ww doesn't dmce claim
They do
This song goes on for
How long is this song?
Okay. Well, let's turn that off then
Mother three ost. Nah
Nah
Oh, let's see
Jenga ost. I don't understand. Is that just like a family playing jenga in the living room?
Banjo kazooie. There it is
Absolutely
There it is full banjo kazooie soundtrack
Oops try that again. Let's try that again
Okay
All right, let's do it. Let's try it again
That's right
I thought the whole thing was on fire for a second sauteed fucking money so much
Where the fuck were they this generation with another banjo kazooie? They don't like to do anything
But have crackdown three take five years
Remember when you could drive her out of the car in the last one
This one's done
Ha ha
Shouldn't be ha haing me. You should have yeah, you should actually
You should
Uh, but we're honest to god though. Let's let's
stop fucking
Talking for a second and talk
uh
Microsoft buys rare
They make a lego build cars game for banjo
Microsoft then teases a joke about conquer's bad for a day in project bankrupt spark
Why what happened?
I don't understand
Why would you even buy?
rare
You have all these insanely amazing beloved licenses
And they've turned them into like serial characters. They don't what what have they done?
Cage in the corner cage in the corner. Hold on
I got it. I got it. I got it because Microsoft hates fun
If there was a real banjo kazooie 3 that came up
And it was actually just banjo cuz and look i'm not even i'm not gonna tell you that
Oh my god, I love banjo so much. I'm a huge banjo fan. Not really
You know, it's fun. It was really interesting for the time. But
You know how many people would buy that game just because it has the number three on it
That'd be the probably the fastest selling console game in the last probably 10 years
Can I get in here?
No, it wouldn't are you sure about that? You know, I think you underestimate just how many people are starving
For another game like that
They might not they might be looking for rose-colored glasses there or whatever, right?
Is he high?
me
Or phil spencer
Both of you
I just got gnomed. I told you you guys find it everywhere now
anytime somebody says or makes a utterance of the word like
Or like oh
There's thousands of those instances
All right. This one's done. We've got a clean room here
At least I think so. I might be wrong, but just triple check and give me out the
meter
Looks good, right?
Yeah, I don't want that. I don't like this anymore
Uh, what am I gonna put on?
mario kart 64
We need something that just sits in the background
Something easy that sits in the background that could be dropped to like minus 20 decibels
ry star
That's an old one. What is with you in decibels? That's how
Db that's the termination. That's the how you gauge how loud something is
Especially when you have audio editing over here. It's db decibels minus five db zero db
Minus 50 db. How about um the ps4 background music? No, I feel too trippy
Audio is measured in volume
um
well
Sound is measured in units called decibels db the higher the decibel level the louder the noise on the decibel scale
The level increase of 10 means that a sound is actually 10 times more intense or powerful. It's the decibel scale
db sound is measured in a unit called decibel. All right, donkey kong country is good. That's good
You can just sit in the background
Well, actually
Hey, you gotta speak up man. The decibels are low back here
Finally some real music, but the music's fine
Meter it's meters cubed
Louder louder. Ah, fuck. It is too soft, isn't it?
That's that's a good
db level
All right. We've got an hour and 30 minutes. I'm like almost done
And i'm gonna eat a whole pizza on stream. That's not gonna happen. Why is this thing broken? What's wrong with this thing?
I don't make sure I got everything over here. Yeah, I have to bring this bucket back here
Then there's no straight pieces in this room, right?
I think it's good
Close that up
Still on the first floor. Yeah, I know
Perfect looks pretty good
It's still up. There's one. There's still a protractor here
I think that's it though
That's it, right? Yeah
Good to go
Move on to the next room
Right here open it up
All right
Let's go
Is there an incinerator in here?
Do I have to actually bring the all the way back?
Oh, this is gonna suck
This is gonna be so horrible. I have to put them. I gotta bring a bunch of shit in here
Can I open this or something?
What is this for? Whoa. Well, that's really useful
I could have used that
What was this in the santa level? I could have used that a thousand times
Really could have used that
All right. Uh, I need a couple of the
I need a couple of these
and
Um, do I want to do this room? Yeah, I probably do. I'm gonna bring three of these in here
Look at how much shit is in this. Ah
I gotta fill every bucket. I need like five buckets
I'm gonna do this. Correct
Lake thank you lake drinker for the five community subs
Lake drinker
Thank you so much
Look left
Okay, we can clean up that we can do the little cleanup later
Look left look left. I just I gotta get this set up
Just give me a minute
This is okay. I gotta designate this shit
This is for this corner
All these body parts need to go in these two
Should fit
Okay, derma your feet. I'm i'm fine
I'm fine. I did it demo this
You want to get rid of this?
Look left. Oh, I oh this is horrible. Oh, what have I done?
Just throw them in here. I'll get them later
Take your socks off
I don't think i'm gonna do that
There's another room on my left is there
I mean I say I know this room here. What's wrong with this room?
Holy shit, that looks kind of crazy. Can I activate this?
They could they don't come out of there. Did they those guys come out?
Uh, give me the gun
I'm not fucking around in there
Come on out. That's a display. They don't come out
Right. What the hell is this?
The results are more than I could have hoped for my creation is showing a great increased pain threshold and soon
Would be my crowning achievement ultimate proof that I was right
This is the critical phase of the experiment one. I cannot afford to get them wrong his siblings grow restless now. I must tend to them
Okay
Uh, I don't like this room. I really don't that just scared me. I thought he got up
I thought he was gonna just plop me right there
Uh
Okay, close this room up. Don't block it
I don't want anyone coming out. I need a gun. So somebody's saying laser on bodies
Oh
Does that destroy them?
Okay turns into little meat chunks
That's very helpful
What happened? What happened? What happened? What's going on? What's the spell that's happening?
I'm overheating the gun. I'm overheating the gun. I'm overheating the gun
Stop it. Relax
This is gonna be a really easy cleanup though. Once these are all turned into like meat nuggets
All right, cool
That is a bigger mess
But no, it's not it's fine
It'll be easier to clean up. Trust me
Just cook the whole room
Okay, now this room's ready
I can't I gotta
Okay, we're good. Give me a bucket
I'm i'm cleaning my feet
What do you mean stop what i'm trying to just torch the whole room so I can uh
Not if we're just coming here and just go like this on the ground and the ceiling and everything would be good
And look at this. This is easy with these chunks
Take a bubble bath on stream
Uh, no
Sorry
All right. I need a incinerator cube
I didn't knock it over
I knocked that over but that doesn't count
See this would probably hold it all
That's why I just torched the whole room
Because now I can probably fit 90% of these in the cube
And then just have to worry about this one cube
You want to take a bubble bath with clothes on i've done that before
It burnt my skin, so i'm not doing it again
Watch out don't knock it over
Okay, i'm gonna need quite a few more of these but now at least i'm not gonna step on this
I this I love this game
So you wouldn't recommend taking a bubble bath with clothes on
No, probably not it's too hot
One last staple
Okay, what's this do?
I don't know what that did
I just yeah what I don't get what that is. I need a new bucket. I need two or three buckets actually
Where's the bath video?
Uh tf2 crates video. Yeah, i'm in the bath
That's the one right?
Does every room have a lever?
Be careful here. I don't want to fuck this up. Is there a lever here? Okay. Is this gonna okay?
Hold on does this open the tubes and do the aliens come up this turns on the saw
That doesn't do anything. I can't touch the saw
Well, okay, it's just for fun. Well, that was fun. You can have the saw spin around
This is some dense dense dirt
I'm gonna take a little bit of chunk
Get it in there
You know, you know, i'm gonna get the chunks first
I know i'm stepping all over the place, but I have to get rid of all this bullshit first
Keep an eye out for chunks
You made those scorch marks, by the way. Yeah, I know but I also made the chunks
I would not be able to fit this dude in here
I mean his leg's a little unruly but we can fix that
Yep. All right
Oh
God damn it that hurt. I thought I was gonna be able to get it over there. That sucked turn off the stream
I'm gonna get the uh
Okay. All right. I fucked it up. No, I didn't i'm fine. I'm good
This is a dirty floor
How did it get so dirty?
Fuck I screwed it up. Now you can say I fucked it up because I did
What's the purpose? Where am I?
uh
The purpose is there was an fps video game that was played here
And you have to clean up after it because nobody ever thinks about what happens after you leave a level
Pretty fun concept for a game funny
interesting
Why am I getting minus two?
I just read you the back of the box
That's like the description on the steam page
What?
I'm trying
Now now it's gonna happen again put it down it's gonna happen again
Is it really still happening? Who cares?
I need like seven of these
It's the bonus room
Where's that bucket giving me? I don't what if and I don't even care if I track
That's I just hit my mouth on the door. All right, I need like seven buckets and i'll be happy
One in each corner one right here
I'm gonna he's tracking. He's tracking. He's tracking. I know it's fine
I'll take care of it
I wanted to get the meat out of the way. I didn't want to pick that up. You understand
Get over here
Four buckets one in each corner and then one in the middle and i'll be good to go
one
two
This is what rock bottom looks like
He's gonna hiss at us
Now that's four we're good
Derma is basically adam sandler
What are you talking about? Adam sandler. Yeah
Adam sandler. Yo, are you talking about the guy that was on saturday night life?
Made a bunch of funny movies back in the 90s
But just didn't know when to stop
You compare me with a guy that's won an emmy
Two emmies
Now we're good. Just a question of getting these tools off
Happy gilmore was an okay movie
Yeah, it was it was yes it was it was fine it was
What was wrong with happy gilmore? It was fun. It was funny
I mean maybe it was like a little
Shitty but a little don't drop it pick it up pick up
Why are you so large get in there? See we're we're almost done with this room
It won't be long won't be like it'll be like another two hours tops
This is getting full give it a jiggle
It's all right. I'll just i'm gonna take this take it out now
I know i'm tracking. I know I know I know I just saw it in the chat. I get it
I get it
Wash the entry no
Wash the entry i'm not going to
All that down there. Oh, there's so much
There's so much left
All right, just stick with the plan
wrong room
Fucking piece of shit streamer
Hey relax, man
Whoa
Oh my god
I just need to get it out of the way
Where's my incinerator? What is this?
It's fucking gold
Can I sell this? I don't know what it is about these streams in particular
But I just I just love I don't know why i'm having so much fun doing stupid shit that everybody hates
It's it's like a weird thing with these streams. I don't know why I do it when I play this game
When am I getting bt tv never i'm making a volcano
Uh, yeah, I just did that i'll take the credit for
All right looking good looking good
Watch out for the super volcano
There's no super volcano
No, okay. There is this okay. There's a little baby volcano that sits underneath
Scientists are predicting that it could blow any minute, but they're talking about the scale of the universe
So any minute for the scale of the universe
You know, we've only been here humans have only been around for like 600 years, right?
so
I mean you're talking about like potentially the million years before that blows
I mean a bucket
I gotta get rid of this thing
I know I fucked up the volcano, but I need the box. I need the box
I hope new viewers are coming in and hearing this. I know I don't know what i'm doing
If that's the first thing you hear you're probably just like, whoa
All right. See you
I need
Getting there getting there getting there almost done
But all right, i'm gonna be completely real no jogging around
If there is a giant super volcano under the earth
Whatever
You know
What are we gonna do about it?
What's what are we gonna do?
live your life
Try your best
Look, I don't want I look here's the problem, right?
You never want like it to be a situation where it's like well that thing could explode
So let's go down and send a nuclear bomb into it
No, no, no, no, don't do that
Maybe if we dig down and put a giant drill and let out the air pressure. No, don't do that either
Be careful
What is this because nobody knows what it actually is
What if they go down there and it's a giant monster?
And the monster finally just is like, all right. Well now you woke me up
You know that movie godzilla. You ain't seen nothing
Don't knock it over. Okay, just trash
Why is the monster up to date with pop culture?
What the hell else are you gonna do down there?
Not much you can do when you're surrounded by fire
And you're locked in the center of the earth
You you're probably gonna watch friends
Every season 10 times you've had thousands of years to do it. I did that. Yeah, and look you're talking about
Oh like how what would he be doing down there? Are you serious? You're not even a monster and you did that
How many times have you loaded the full metal alchemist brotherhood season two intro?
And listened to it, you know how many times he's fucking done that
Let's get the rest of this shit. I gotta bring another box down here. This is a big box level. I would say
I need like four of these down here
I don't know how I got to this germa stream, but I guess i'm gonna stay on this germa stream. Well, hey, welcome
Thanks for sticking around
Yeah, we like we do this thing here we talk about like like topics
Like what if kind of what are scenarios?
But what if godzilla was real, you know, I mean, that's what that's in
Cheater console. I just I accidentally hit the till day
What do you want from me?
I'm gonna report this stream for trolling if you don't make a good joke soon
You can't what do you mean report me for trolling?
Who am I trolling you me?
Am I trolling myself? I don't understand
You said there's gonna I when have I ever said that there's gonna be a good joke incoming
I've never done that
There are no expectations here
Leave them at the door
Do the siren joke again. I probably will like three more times. Don't worry
If you hang out here long enough, you'll see that like probably five more times
Okay, I need two buckets
Oh
I just tony hawked it. I've given myself landmines in every corner. That's not a good idea
Uh, do I need this thing? Probably not knife get it in there
Blood on the ceiling. I'll get it. Don't worry
I'll take care of it. I just realized something. This is a huge soundtrack
How long is this soundtrack?
Seems pretty long
Wait, this thing has wheels. Can I
Caught it. Yep reflexes like a goddamn
cat
Unfunny spill joke
Oh
When did this soundtrack come up? This is 94
94 right? Yep. That's pretty damn good
They should do another one. No, and i'm not i'm not talking about donkey kong country 7-eleven fucking icy freeze
I'm talking about a donkey kong country game
Shitting so much over here. Did they do one for the switch?
Tropical freeze was composed by the same guy. Oh
whoops
Sorry about that
This hurts my eyes
Is this can this show?
Maybe that's a good thing to have was a tropical freeze a good game
I think I actually bought that a long time ago
It's great
It's very hard. But yes
All right, if nintendo is smart
Don't you think?
Because let's face it
Like 42 people bought the wii u
Don't you think they should just bring some of those games over?
What's this thing? I'm just checking to see if it
Was worth keeping
They have been
That was a perfect throw
I couldn't have tried to do that
I hope you understand
Tropical freeze is on the switch. That's kind of cool nintendo was smart than starfox would
Yeah
They probably tried to make a couple of didn't they try to make one a few years ago?
and
The wii u was really hitting the bottom of its life cycle and they maybe just were like nah
Probably not worth it
Why did the wii u fail?
because
They named it
The same thing as the other console with a u in front of it
And they had a giant game gear for a controller
It was a clunky mess
Maybe with some decent titles on it
But the switch has the joycons and then oh get the pro controller you would you would have a box
Of controller peripherals for that system
Because holding on to that giant brick ipad game gear thing was no way
Could you do that for more than like an hour or two it hurt?
The switch is the wii u with detachable confronted. Yeah, but it's also more comfortable
The wii u pad was thick it was thick
And chunky
Like the wii u was pretty damn chunky. I wouldn't be surprised if it was a murder weapon at some point
That thing weighed like four pounds
Get rid of this. All right, this one's pretty much done and the news outlets would have got it all wrong
it would have been like
local man smashes a brick into a friend's face
They don't have to fax, you know, that's a way that was a wii u this one's done. I just got a couple more little pieces
out
Why do you know so much about this?
covering my own crimes
No, sorry guys. I didn't like I didn't like wii u brick pad somebody in the face
Good thing that wasn't a bucket. It can't be spilled
German behind you
What the heck okay
No, that can stay
Any more pieces I need to pick up besides this
I'm just gonna let's try to spin it out of here ready
Ready for a paw camp
Oh imagine if it had bounced up there bounced into the incinerator. That would have been a clip of the week
Ceiling what's wrong with the ceiling?
It's pretty sleek. Just got to move some stuff around
Some over here
It's still red
Oh that was close
Don't forget about the bullet holes
I will
I'm just gonna be frank with you. I definitely I absolutely will forget about that until the very end of this level
And the chat is just gonna be spamming with lul
idiot
You're gonna see it fail fishes. Yeah, that'll happen too
Corner here
Close this up
Mm-hmm. This room looks pretty done all around the alien
Containers looks good
I think we're good
Looks good
Ceiling. Yeah, that was a little bit on there wasn't it a little bit
This up just to have it dust
Okay, let's move on
I need a med kit
Is that what this shit is for?
first aid supplies
Let me see it
Do I have to actually put this fucking thing in?
Damn, okay
Just put it I did I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it
So what is this stuff for?
Solar flare wet floor sign pizza slicer toilet seat lantern
What are these for?
This is gonna be bright
How bright is this? How do I turn it on put it in the fire?
Okay
Oh cool. Okay. Well, I need it back
Well, all right. Well, at least I know what it does who cares what what's the point of that?
All right. That's I mean, that's cool. I guess
Make 20 of them. No, I don't want to melt everybody's eyes
I just want to see what it looked like. All right
Let's go
This room's done
Close it up just I i'm I gotta close the rooms that are done
Because I will forget now walk around in circles. I'll come back in and chop. I'll double check it
For now, we're gonna seal it up
handprint this hand
How did you even see that I don't know how you even saw that shit
We got two hours and 15 minutes
Maybe like another 10 minutes. I got so many buckets. So we go
That's the way up. I'm almost done
I'll get a rhythm watch the rhythm
I'm gonna make a Hansel and Gretel trail
Of buckets. Oh, yeah. Wait, I forgot about this room. I was supposed to do this one first
Haven't even been to the basement or the second floor yet. I'll be all right. Does it wait as a basement?
That's fine. I'm gonna and i'll be the first person ever on stream to beat this level
I'm okay having that
Like look at how many buckets I got it's gonna take no time at all. Once we set it all up
Fix the bullet holes. I'm gonna don't worry. I'll get it all
I will get it all this is off right? Yeah, just need a couple more incinerators
I'm not tracking
I'm gonna stack them four should be enough. Can I do this? I could probably do more. No, I got it
Everything's fine
Put these around the room. Don't fucking watch the bus. There's so many landmines around me
All right, move this down here
Don't step on a landmine
You come this way
down here
right in the middle
Look at all this junk. I think we're in a decent spot to start picking up the chunks
This can probably go over here. Yeah
Okay
corner to corner
Uh, we got a whipped cream canister
co2
That's another another 50 dollars just coming
Yeah comfort evil eagle just gave 50 dollars
Oh my god. Damn it. It's okay. I stepped on one landmine. I didn't he did he stepped on the landmine
I didn't touch it
But thank you so much comfort eagle if you stack the buckets inside each other you can carry more than one
To and from your work area
Yeah, I don't know if i'm gonna be able to handle that
Make a pile
Thank you comfort eagle
I could try
Cut up the bodies with the pizza slicer
What?
The pizza slicer no, I need the laser gun
Great canadian
It was nothing in it didn't even spill i'm good great canadian fuck club just gave out five community subs
Thank you
Thank you so much
All right. I gotta cut his
Can I do it in the bucket?
All right. I got it. I turned him into a blood-borne enemy
All right with those can fit
No, no, no, no
All right
Now let's chunk it up
Somebody said you have at least three more hours here
This is well, this is dr. Phil and you uh, are having a problem at sea
I'll take the fucking plus five for that one
It's 500
Shit, i'm usually good at timing that
It doesn't fix the bolt holes. I'm gonna do that at the very end
Because then I can
Just go look at them all and want to track dirt everywhere and all that shit. I'll get them
Because I need to use the gun for that
Put on a dr. Phil ost put on a dr. Phil episode
No
I'm not gonna put on dr. Phil
Dr. Phil doesn't have an ost
He does
This is his theme song
It's when yeah, no this is when he comes out. Yeah, okay
The audience is clapping
He walks out sits down in his big chair
Okay, so, uh, what's next on the autoplay? I don't know looks like dr. Phil theme music hd
What's the difference how is how is this one high quality
It's the same song
Does he have an outro or is the intro the outro?
It's probably one of those scenarios
Are you certain?
Are we sure this is not like sonic tennis?
Choose your character screen. That's what it sounds like. Oh my god. I gotta move this shit out of the way this
dirt
Bile puke all over the walls
Dr. Phil in the chat
Are you serious?
What's up, man?
Oh dr. Dr. Phil raid here comes a dr. Phil raid
Six and a half million people just showed up. Oh, hey, whoa
Hey, thanks for the raid man. See you at twitchcon
This is not like a 10-hour version of the song is it?
This song is gonna make me lose my fucking mind
I don't check
I have to check. I think that's it
Yeah, that's it. Here comes another one. This is a different theme song though somehow
This is I don't know how to see this has a theme song
This is the wheel of fortune ost
I like this one. Yeah, I do. This is good. I have some dirty buckets
This fits too. This is pretty good selection. Who picked this?
YouTube's auto algorithm bot
Hey, I see it twitchcon
Twitchcon I didn't go to twitchcon
save
Good idea
Am I already?
122 14
Did I only save one time in the middle of santa's workshop?
I would go to twitchcon if uh vanna whiten. Yeah, if if if the cast of and the crew
Of wheel of fortune went to twitchcon and they had like a panel I would go
And let me try the stacking thing that that person was talking about
This is the dirty. He's gotta go
Raid a wheel of fortune raid incoming god. I would love to go on one of those shows
And just blotch the absolute hell out of everything
Spin the wheel the wrong way every time
No, no, no jeremy stop doing that you're spinning the wheel the wrong way
I'm sorry. Sorry
Uh any vowels?
Uh, you have to ask me for a letter
Oh, uh d
D is not a vowel god. Damn it now. I'm gonna get him to scream like a swear on the air
And like end his career
Why would this come up next? I don't know why this would come up next
But apparently we're gonna see this
This is not connected to
Is this gonna be tv we're gonna go from here
I buy I bet you I bet you graze anatomy is next
on the autoplay
I wonder
Oh
All right
Holy shit it works
No, this one's fine. All right. Is it graze anatomy?
Well, I think this is extended
No, it's not graze anatomy. It's something else
Yeah
This is a different version
I think this one might be hd. Yeah
It sounds like an hd version
This thought is going to get nuked
Yeah, oh god the screams the sound of saws and machinery the roaring and restless groans from the cells is too much also wrong
It's so dirty back here
I gotta get rid of all of them
Can we get something else besides the breaking bad theme?
And then after whatever the next one is I gotta turn it up before I get like before I get deleted
I'm i'm gonna get deleted on the air. This is gonna be stream offline for about 35 seconds
All right new buckets. Let's go new buckets new new
Don't spill it
Don't be a coward
Well, I want people to be able to watch the vods
Okay, we'll get one more
Holy shit
Oh
I've never even seen this show. I'll clean this up later. I've never seen this show. Is this a good show?
Mega spill
This one's very low. It's not that audible. It's modern family
Thankfully, it's only 30 seconds long
Um, what are these shows that i've never heard of mom cbs tv series?
This is a six minute video. How could you have an intro for your show? That's six fucking minutes long
What have I done over here?
Uh
Yeah, I have to next this no i'm not gonna sit here and listen to this
I'm nexting it
By the way, this is I believe this is the song
This is an orchestra version of the song that we're just hearing
This is the mom song but it's an orchestra doing the actual song
All right next again
Okay, this is
This is the same. This is the same song, I think
No, let's do it again
What is it is this no, wait a minute, oh this is star wars i'm gonna get out of there
Wait here
No, don't wake up
Get off
I I almost just turned off the stream for the joke. I almost just turned my fucking stream off
But I want I don't want to do that. It's been like two and a half hours. I want to keep playing
I can't just like delete the stream
That would have been worth it
maybe
Not after two and a half hours if it okay if it had been like seven hours
I may have done it still early. Come on. All right, let's uh clean this up
No, no osts. I want I want to be able to have a non muted vod for five minutes
parks and rec
Nah
My vods never get muted. Well, I don't really play music
I very rarely play music usually when we're just hanging out
Just being dickheads in a game like this is when I play music on the stream
Put on binaural beats
No, i'm not gonna like mind control everybody in here
binaural beats
Doesn't that the shit that just goes like
No, no, we got to play the play the low one too. Yeah it goes like
Get off, you know what binaural beats sounds like
Uh, you know when you have your cell phone sitting near a computer and your phone is about to ring and you get that
Well, my phone's gonna ring
That can't be healthy, right?
The fact that we can hear that when your phone is near a speaker or a computer or something. That can't be good
El fatso crisps
It's interference
I mean it is
Uh, i'm most certainly pleased with the progress we've made in recent months the dna harvested from the captured alien creatures
Has allowed our creation truly blossom into a vessel of unprecedented strength and malice with further treatments. I'm certain
We can realign the creature's mental capacity as we need
And on a final note who is responsible for the continued theft of my gloomberry doughnuts
How do you fast forward a stream?
Uh, there's a button down there. It's uh, it's play
Fast forward and then next and if you press the fast forward button
You uh, you can get it to work
But everybody has to collectively press it at the same time
And if you don't that it's not going to work
so I mean it needs to be at least five to
Like 500 to 2000 people have to all do it at the same time
So if you uh
Yeah, I mean i've never been that's the first time i was ever naked. So
It's hard to be naked
When you're naked, you know, if people can just see you they can see who you fucking really are
So that's why I don't do it anymore. But uh, thanks for the four thousand dollars. Uh, appreciate it
Somebody that you know, over the course of the last four hours or so. Thank you
And I fucked it all up again, didn't I?
I you guys seriously have
No, you know, don't rewind me. Don't do it. Don't i've been sitting here for so long
It's been four hours. No, you're gonna delete the four thousand dollars that the guy just gave me. Don't do it
No, I want that four grand
Don't bring me back
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, don't do it. Don't do it
Stop get your finger off that button
No
Oh
It's pulling me in three different directions. I'm going across dimensions
Fucking buy neurobeats
Don't do it
No
No, don't let me you're killing me you're killing me
Don't do it
Blood coming out of my eyes I can fight it for another minute or two. I could fight the whole thing
It's blood coming out of my mouth
So I think this box here I can um, I can use this right fill up the pieces and bring it down
How long do you think it's gonna take me to do this? I would say probably
Was it two and a half hours? Well, no, okay. Nothing in there
Fuck this is gonna take so long. Is it what's this? Is there an upstairs?
There's not an upstairs. No fucking way. Well, whatever. Uh, can I open the doors? I don't think I can this one
This one looks already clean. I don't get it. Where do the buckets come from?
This feels kind of weird. All right music. Uh
Zero the volume's all the way down from the last stream, right? That's not okay. Well what we got
Um, that's that that that I don't like that one. That's the same
That's the same one
Dude, I don't like either one of these
No
Um, I don't think so
Doom os i'm not gonna play doom ost. We're not doing the ost thing. I want to hit the actual end game music
No, no
No, no, no
No, no, no, no
No
There we go. So where should I start?
Fuck so what's like the dynamite thing here? Is it dynamite gonna come out of there?
What's like the funny thing for this one?
This room is clean
My fucking game is bugged. I think somehow
And this must be dirt in here
And uh other strange thing that i'm kind of noticing at the moment. Why am I covered in blood me in real life?
I blinked a couple times and I just i'm seeing red
this is uh
Maybe I was doing like a funny. Hey, look i'm in the game joke or something
Did the web did I turn the webcam on did I
What fucking time is it?
Did you see a doctor about that? Did you see a doctor about it? Should I what doctor are you referring to?
Talking about the good doctor phil
What even is what is this sound what is this fucking song
What an awful fucking sound this what is this? Uh, what is this like fucking sonic tennis?
Dr phil's rating
Oh, hey, dr phil. See you at twitchcon man. I'll high five you
That's so funny. What's next on the auto play? What the fuck is this?
Are you shitting me?
the hd
That one's even louder somehow. All right, let's continue cleaning. That's this fun game
Oh, what's the dna? Oops. This room is almost done. I can I pick this up move this over here
ha
Fill it up. Hey
Dr phil it up. I want to get rid of this. I never what's the point of this?
Bring him further back. I don't know what you mean by that
I can taste his blood
All right, speaking of blood. I gotta go pee
Fuck all right. I'll be back. I'm gonna grab another drink get some water and take a piss. I'll be right back
Hey he's back
That's enough of that thought I just turned on the camera that would have been bad
Is this the joke of the month
Well, it is it is it's barely january so
And it hadn't even been one full week. Let me open this back up and let's keep going. Let me uh,
Let me fix all the shit that I just ruined in the game. What's going on?
Oh, right. Okay
Uh, I kind of ruined everything so just added like a 45 minute plus timer
to the
Get him to the 23rd
Quick get him to the 23rd
you know part of that is
Really really really morbid of some of you guys
Skip to the 23rd
Why?
Because that's when you're supposed to die
Okay
My goodness
That's gonna be the worst stream of the year. I hope you guys understand that and I there's no
Oh, I wonder what he's gonna do
You I told you what i'm gonna do
That's the stream
I'm sitting in the room in a fucking goalie outfit
And just i'm just gonna survive
is it
What room was I in?
What am I talking about?
Like almost a year ago. I played a game. It was a game about like having illnesses and you could play as yourself
And I named the character me and the game told me that I was gonna die
on January 23rd 2019
so
That's coming up. So i'm gonna final destination my room
I'm gonna be drinking out of sippy cups
I'm gonna be covered in pads
Am I gonna go back to kenshi?
uh probably
Probably this weekend
Because the plan was we're gonna do this tonight
Because I love this game
And then after tonight tomorrow either get back to kenshi
for simpson's hit and run
That's the plan
Either one of them will work because whatever one doesn't happen the other one will happen the next day
so it depends
the reason why the simpson's hit and run was not tonight
is very very specifically because
I have it for playstation for playstation 2
I've
Can I like say a word with an f?
I have it for
ps2
and
I was told that it actually exists for pc
And there are mods
And the game is way better on pc. So I don't know how the hell i'm gonna work that out
But that's why I didn't do it tonight because I was gonna play it on ps2
And it turns out that probably shouldn't do that
If for some reason I can't get the pc version with the mods to work
Then i'm just gonna do the playstation 2 version. That's the plan
I need another I need to get with the program here. Give me some buckets
And then 700,000 games part two. Yes
In probably in that order i'll probably wait for uh next week to do 700,000 games, too
Give me a break
Rng
Okay, just make all right. That was pretty cool
Yeah, there is a 700,000 games part two
The company made another one
And we need to see what it is
So that's gonna be a whole stream
I just kick flipped
Yes, I did
Do these fit in here?
No, i'm gonna have to stack these and walk them just stack them up and walk them
What's the best way to stack these?
like this
but this
Fuck actually that's a better way to do it. I think
I could play this game and be in a meeting
I wonder how many lawyers own this game and they're on the phone with a client just doing this
I'm doing these all upside down, huh?
An idiot fucking idiot idiot that this one i'm see if I can even do this
Somehow magically they haven't fallen
Whoa
Yeah, hold all my calls. I got a meeting. I got something else important going on
Can this even fit in here? I can barely fit the fucking printer in here
Okay, close it up. Well, i'm gonna have to put these in. Oh my I I didn't even spill and I picked it up
I picked it up. It didn't spill. I picked it up. It's a lot of work. I got a lot of meetings to miss
Okay, we're good. Hold on to the box. Fuck it. Just don't let me forget about these. All right
Okay
fun
Persona 5 ost. No, i'm not gonna no no persona 5 i'm gonna play that game if if anything
All right, I got a full bucket here. Now i'm gonna play it on stream mine sweeper ost
All right. I'm not gonna say the word ost for another year. Okay
We're gonna hold you do that. Do it do it so many more rooms
Uh 24 hour stream apparently confirmed because this is how the fuck am I gonna do this do it
24. All right. So those of you that are internet connoisseurs
There are there are 4,300 people watching this stream right now
Another doctor fucking phil how
What would the view count be?
If I put on repeat the doctor phil theme song
For a full hour
What would the viewer count look like?
One hour from now. I would yeah, I would say somewhere around like 1.4 like 1400
and
follow-up question
Would any of those people come back?
that left
Ever again, I don't think so
Even some of you guys that are saying
Oh, yeah, no, that'd be so funny. Do it you'd leave
You'd be here for 20 minutes and then you'd go fuck man. That's something else
I could probably be doing right now. You'd leave too. I'd leave
And this is I have the stream turned on I would just get up and go
Like walk my dog
I would report the stream if you did that
What's the drop down menu and you report a stream? Oh, okay. We got a offensive. Uh bad. Uh, he's naked
He's playing doctor phil for 10 hours
If you want you can file reports
Describe how you think certain people were murdered if you put people's id tags in your chest you get extra cash
What?
That's so cool. Is that real?
All right, so we have successfully cleaned up
this area
The area that I caused a huge problem in
Nothing in here, right? Empty. Oh a couple of blitz
Just dump them out in here
That's stuck
Whatever I can get another one. When am I gonna go on the doctor phil show?
I'm not I don't have any plans to
How's this for him looking?
Not good
That's stuck in my head no what
He said he'd love to have you
What would we talk about? What's why do I have to go on the show? There has to be a reason
Jeremiah i'm done with you not listening play the portal 2 soundtrack
What?
I'm done with you not listening put on the portal 2 soundtrack
Like give me a minute make sure I cleaned up all the blood in the guts
I think I did ceiling doesn't have anything on it. Do it. This is my stream
Oh, is it?
Oh, I was unaware
Is it now?
dump
Dump it. I missed under the bed. I know I could have dumped this
Blood behind you idiot idiot stupid idiot
There's blood there dumb idiot stupid dumb idiot
Where I don't see any blood. I don't see
Relax are you mocking us? Yes. Well, I can't mock you guys sometimes
You know, I look over in this chat and sometimes all I see is a mo ck ing
Sometimes that's the only thing I see
So if you can't take the heat and take a couple of cooking classes and maybe you'll get better
Hey, you know how many times I'm gonna have somebody have somebody doctor a fucking photo of me at five feet tall
I can't do an elvis. Uh-huh impression making a little joke. Well, that's not allowed
Met what meltdown what this is not a meltdown a meltdown is start talking fucking talking like this
No, I mean, it's um, it's like just it's fucking stupid and I just I don't I can't fucking do it right now
So that's it. That's how you know
My voice drops
It's like this and it's like fucking I don't know what the fuck and I swear a shit every other sentence every other word
No, this game just wasn't fucking so stupid like
Whatever. It doesn't matter like I don't I fucking don't like fucking even care about this fucking stupid game
Oh, it might be time for a break because I don't know man. Like i'm fucking
You know what i'm saying? I might be time for a fucking break
Is that really loud i'm sorry guys seriously did I peek the mic
Shit, i'm sorry
I actually i'm sorry. I hate when that happens. I just forget
Sorry, i'm like peeking the microphone
All right, so let's fucking dump fucking game in
It's like funny. It's fucking the first five times which is seriously
It's getting so fucking irritating
Fucking give me a break
Give me a fucking break
Fucking jesus. I don't like this joke
What's he what's he so mad? No, i'm doing a pretend mad
When sometimes i've been actually mad that's how you can tell
What would possibly be causing me to be mad right now for these pretending in quotes. I'm like picking up thumb drives
What no i'm just kidding. You guys know i'm kidding
What the heck are you talking about?
Bad elvis impression. Oh now you got me
boiling
Be real for once in your life. What?
I wouldn't be real for once in your life
This guy hates his viewers. I don't that's not true
Don't say such incorrect things so this room is pretty much done
Yeah, okay
What's wrong is he talking about the broom
Do I have to throw the broom away?
Med kits med kit. What what are you? Oh, are you putting in the mad?
No, if you clicked on this and you didn't have any context funny it fucking the first five times, which is seriously
It's getting so fucking irritating
Fucking give me a break
Give me a fucking break
fucking jesus
And who says i'm not a good actor this text to speech in the game. Oh, yeah forgot about that
You're gonna fight it dog. I'm not even gonna read that out loud. All right, i'm gonna pay attention
I'm gonna pay attention for another mouth down comes up
I was looking over at chat
Oops
Ah, and it's everywhere now, come on. It's this dump room
Unfun it's not a spill joke. It's me looking at the chat. I fucking see fucking fucking dumb fucking game
He spilled the thing. Yeah, I know and I know you're giving me the I know what that means now
I know what the forehead emote means now
I thought people thought it was hilarious some of the shit that I was doing. Nope
That's the kappa
of lul
I get it now
Okay, let's bring this
Okay, we're almost done
Come here. Come here. I have to like knock those around. Don't I crap? Oh crap
I can reach this one
Sounded out what do you mean sounded out sound out what everyone people used to do kappa
People still do it. I see it from time to time. I need some more incinerators
You didn't clean the outside of the building
Fuck you. No, no, no
No, that's not stop taking me out of context. This happened two days ago, too
All right, clean clean clean. We're almost ready to go to the next step. What the fuck are you doing, man?
There's body parts in here
He's losing it. I'm not losing it. I'm not losing it. He's losing it
This feels like a vr game. It is
You didn't know I was in vr. I'm doing very well for how goofy it is to hold these move controllers
I hate when they like that. I gotta get on top and knock them this way. Is it out? Shit get out from there
Can I can I pick you up over this way? I hope so
Ah, that felt good. That was like removing a rotten tooth
Play a more calming tranquil game
That this is kind of the epitome of a tranquil just calm game, isn't it? It's not gonna happen. I'm gonna
Bring it out here sit on the gurney
Bloods everywhere. It's totally calm. I mean, it's relaxing to just clean. I'm just relaxing
How much of the upstairs have you done?
Um
90 maybe
Something like that
Maybe 95 percent
If it's so tranquil, why are you losing your shit?
This is just what happens when I play vista or clean up detail. We just start talking about anything
And that's it. We just hang out
Have fun. All right, that looks good
Under the table under the table
There is a meat chunk that's sitting there
And where's my bar? There it is
missed two on the step
Missed step two there pal
What?
What's step two?
Pal, I don't know what you mean. What do you mean? Looks good
The ward almost done with the ward
Okay, I wish I could turn this is gonna give me
Anxiety, man. I gotta turn that over. I wish I could pick it up
Nothing on the ceiling
Okay, did it miss any other blood? I don't think it did looks good looks good looks good looks good
Yep, 30
Or is it reflection? I think it's a reflection
portal to ost
Ah
I just said it
Shit i'm supposed to not ever say that again. It's gonna set this down over here
I need some med kit go right there
gimme
Got it clean that up
You the incinerators right here might as well just drop it in
New year's resolution failed. I don't think so
What was my actual new year's resolution? You guys heard it. Wasn't it something different?
Something else
But then I say like two days ago
Oh installing a better twitch tv. Yeah, that's right
Yeah, as long as I just do that at some point during the year, then it's fine
I could do that on
december
29th 2019. I still did it. This one is done, right? Just want to make sure done
There's a bucket in here though
Let's just double check
You think we'll forget? No, it'll be fine
I'll get it
Derm has been live for four hours and this is not even halfway done
Well, we're going to have to finish it
Regardless of how long it takes
And how many things we do this game has nudity
That's not what you said. You said was this game made in unity?
I'm not sure where my mind went there
Clean clean clean. We only got the one little upstairs area
Clear out the downstairs
Press a couple of buttons
All right. Wait, let's I gotta go
Missed a spot we can triple check
I'll come back down here. We're gonna do all the good to go through with the
Ghost busters meter. We'll find whatever needs to be found
This on the other hand needs to be cleaned up bad
Uh, what are the empty ones? This one's kind of dirty stick it in there
Okay
Empty stick it in there
I need a med kit
Let's go one more pass to make sure I didn't miss anything
Might as well pull it out just to look
There ain't nothing here
Just spotless
Guaranteed
All right stack this up and let's get the hell out of here and move on
I don't like how this is
Tip it this way. What the fuck man
Tip it that I wanted to tip it the other way that didn't even tip over
I'm gonna be real with me that didn't even tip over. It was just barely. I was moving it around
They're all empty. Anyways, don't fucking matter. No. Hey, he very funny
I mean, I honestly was just trying to get it so I wasn't gonna tip over but
You know, oh what a silly what silly stuff. He's doing right now fresh buckets
This is new, but I don't want I'm wondering I gotta bring them over there
Okay, nice and clean get in there
All right. I'm about to play the portal to ost for the as long as it takes to get the fastest gnome in the world
You're gonna get like a whoo, but except it's the first song in portal to but here live it over here on the wall
But almost done
There's only about five minutes left
This looks good. I need a med kit
Done good. Goodbye. I need a health pack for that room
I'm gonna go through at the very end and make sure to change everything and fix everything
So don't worry
Moving on what do we got here?
This door cannot be opened
There's nothing even here. It's just for show
further down
Also, this door is locked nothing even in there. So that's good. I thought I had way more to do
I need some buckets
The gun is right here. All right, i'll do the bullet holes. Okay
How do you do them? I'm about to start a fire. Hold on there now everybody can exhale
What do you mean? We got him. Well, we got him. He's doing the thing. He's supposed to do
We'll do the rest later. I know there's more
All right, give me the bucket
How much real estate can I clear with just this little bucket that people need the portal to or we're gonna starve
What's that have to do with you eating food?
this
Not uh
Okay, not gonna do it yet. I want to clear this out and then get a few new buckets
I'm not gonna spill them. I'm gonna try as hard as I can to not
I promise
I'm not gonna spill it run too fast. I'm gonna walk with like four or five buckets
I'm gonna take it slow
Because this is now clean. I don't have to worry about this little corridor anymore. Good
It didn't even happen. Oh, hi. Yes. So funny
I'm sorry to the people that might be new to the stream that think that this is i'm doing this on purpose
It's not on purpose
Why give me
You are i'm not
There are people that there are people who aren't
Knowing that wait what i'm gonna get in there. Don't do this. Did they all spill? No, okay
I got four. All right
I'm holding shift. That's
That feels like it's gonna spill right? Is it? No, it's not. Okay
Whoa
Okay, put it down gently see I told you I was gonna try not have that be a thing
See, it's so bad. He wants to do it. Don't do it though
This should take me all the way up to the stairs. It should be good feels pretty good
Please play portal to i'm so hungry. I don't even I don't have a response to that because that is so dumb
I have no response to what you guys are saying to this. I can't even think about it here. Eat up
Thank you. We can eat
Good i'm glad i'm glad you can eat eat it
My ost is a little dry. Can I get a refund?
No
No refunds
Look at how close we are. Okay. How do I how do I say look at the guy got employees on site?
No, what?
Okay, i'm full stop. No you you eat it you finish your vegetables
You're gonna eat it all and i'm too full
It's the first song you ate like one carrot
You have a full plate of food right now
Worst joke contender. This is not my I didn't do this. This is
Are you talking about for chat? Because this is a chat thing. This is not a jeremy thing getting close
So close
Uh, i'm not gonna be able to take that. Let's just go dump it
And then bring another one. I'm gonna get i'm trying I can only drink one
Good good get rid of this bucket too
I don't need it
Can't believe i'm watching this guy live
Welcome to the stream
Hope you're having a good one
Is it gonna work?
Yep
Is this pre-recorded?
No
Is it?
No shit it is
No, it is
I'm at the beach right now. I forgot
I made sure to have a pre-recorded stream because i'm at the beach
I want to make sure I had something for today, you know
Um, I can't pick this up. Can I not pick that up?
I'm not my hands are off the keyboard right now almost to the spawn and then we are done
With the verse floor good good good good good good good
and then I can take the elevator up and
We can do the
Doppelohr
I'd love seeing the progress
This is where I started
There's the spawn. Look at how clean it is down here. There's no blood
Remember this shit how bad it looked
You get to really see your progress. It's great
At the limb box
I think I can just bring this over there now. Wait. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet
Good I gained 62 viewers from the dr. Phil music. That's incredibly specific
That's very okay. Here's the computer
I'm gonna put the thumb drives in there eventually
Maybe I should turn this into a thumb drive box
No, no, no, no dump it in here
That was just a dog
Running with his bone into the door. Fuck. I'm not sure I can put this in here. What the fuck are you doing? Open
Can I you can I close the lid on this thing?
Okay, I didn't know it had its own animation
It's gonna get a little sloppy over here. Anyways, don't worry
No, no. Well, what do you mean? No, don't do that. Don't do that
Why?
What why?
Don't burn that I needed that did I though?
Let's get another one
Use it to save items. All right, it's okay
Isn't there one of these in here?
I didn't know
Everything there's a everything in this game is a box. It can be used
All right, almost time to go upstairs
clean clean clean all right time to go upstairs we'll find the little bits that are still
around later might as well put this in got it okay i missed a spot at the end it's okay
i i think i can clean it all up take care of it later that's locked up
yeah i need a med pack for that let's get this get another one i'm just gonna dump it
i missed a $50 donation earlier did i really where did i miss that comfort eagle we touched
upon comfort eagle didn't we i missed 4 000 donation when somebody gave four thousand dollars i don't
remember that oh jebaited oh funny all right uh i didn't even dump this shit that's what i came
in here for new box fresh box fresh water i can't do it again fresh water fresh box and let's
take the ride upstairs thanks for nothing no i'm gonna put we need to bring a lot of stuff up here
i need to think about this logically because i have to come all the way back down we're
gonna do eight buckets and three eight buckets and three now i can only do one
are there no buckets upstairs didn't look like it when we were there before
save the game thank you turn footprints off that's too late now all right two in the other i
gotta make sure i can fit can i fit a couple of boxes in here still we'll find out in a minute
please two more here comes a meltdown it's no no that's gonna be fine two more and then
i might as well get that animation going so i can do this one two three style there we go
get it in there yes can only fit two in here
oh what the hell
jesus that's too much raw meat for me to take in okay now if i just get in here
close the door here we go up oh there's so much up here how much is up here
okay no it's not that much it is not that much it's just a lot it's not that much
it's a lot but it's is it it's not a lot primary objective eliminate the crazed doctor ward make
a big fucking mess this area of medical facility is where dr ward and his associates created the
mutant hybrids find and eliminate the mad doctor and all his creations what okay this
one's not going to be that bad i'll tell you for one very specific reason why i'm who
am i kidding it's gonna be horrible i'm gonna put every body part in a corner and then i'm
gonna come up here with a gun and i'm gonna light the whole fucking place on fire we're gonna
make a bonfire of body parts imagine the smell i don't even want to be fucking horrible
uh door control locked can't go in that one this door door control please enter code
oh no well you got why would you guys do that i just cheated all right back to what i was
doing over here i got so many buckets we're gonna clean it all so quickly just get
everything out of the way and we're doing i'm gonna make a trail of buckets and i'm going to do
this faster than that guy was broken into a million pieces i've burnt the code you make
a mistake sometimes any more pieces yeah this shit is over here hold on i gotta put the
bullets that's too many of them there's no vacuum cleaner i can use i have to pick
each one of these up individually no i'm i'm gonna get out of this very quickly it's
we're almost at the four hour mark this is gonna take less than 20 minutes 20 minutes from now it's
gonna happen because i'm gonna do this so strategically i'm gonna line everything up
i'm gonna do it very fast just watch i will get it i'll it'll be right this time i'll
get it this time i'll be ready to get out of here it's in the elevator just gotta get rid
of all the stray shit everywhere corner to corner yeah i'm gonna do the whole thing
and then we're gonna take all the dirty shit down in the elevator i need the gun though all
right 30 minutes add 10 minutes but i gotta go get the gun just sweep it all under a bed
they're gonna dock points for that all right alarm let's just take it so i don't track blood
everywhere let me take care of this shit first i'm gonna start in this area here and
we're gonna go in so i won't run blood all over the place all right need my buckets
i'm gonna go one bucket at a time first bucket right in the middle bucket number two 10 feet
15 feet forward bucket number three another about 10 15 feet forward so i'm and then the
next one will be down there that's four buckets should get the whole thing done with that
so i'm never more than five feet 10 feet away from a bucket here we go check it one
two three begin rpg planning i'm gonna play rpgs i downloaded the witcher three all right this
one's done i'm gonna have to set it here for now keep going holy fuck it's so dirty up here
i'm gonna have to use all eight buckets here damn nothing moving who's talking
um okay over here if i can just get this whole thing i don't need to come because i
don't want to track shit everywhere there we go somebody left their xbox mic on and their
mom came into the room all right it's almost getting to the point where i need four more
buckets yeah oh this is bad i wasn't even close i wasn't even close that's not in right
when i pick it up it should straighten itself out all right i've got one more bucket over
here don't i yep right here omega spill is incoming no there's not gonna be no mega spill
i told you 30 minutes it's gonna take the other buckets but that's why i brought eight
and then we're gonna bring them all down stacked into the incinerator could you please do it on
purpose like last time all right we're almost ready to get the next set of buckets out here
not quite almost all right we need to replace wait i think i can do one more yeah last one
that's it he didn't deny it i didn't deny what that it was an intentional spill
it wasn't an intentional spill perfect all right well before i go i'm gonna get this out and then
get these out too no get this in get these in fuck it's tipping it's tipping it's tipping
it's tipping which way do i have to do it i'm ready don't take them out like this i'm it i'm
fucked i fucked it all up i think i fucked the whole thing up nope thank god time check how
long has it been 10 minutes it hasn't been 30 minutes no way it has not been that long
you ever have bad this looked not even five minutes ago i still got three buckets it's been
eight minutes would you look at that i still got plenty of time nothing spilled nothing
fucked up nothing stupid happened this place is almost clean all right that one's done but
i can get the ceiling hasn't happened yet why do you think why do you think it's going
to happen it's not going to happen look at how much better that looks i've only been here for
few minutes i spilled them up now here's the real question i gotta just keep these over here
in the corner that's okay it's not that's not the end of the world it's not it's only two
buckets don't worry it's not the end of the world not the end of the world why is it
bubbling why is it boiling in there it shouldn't be why is it doing that why is this
bubbling around sit in there set in there good it's so dark i can't see that's not gonna work so
i'm just gonna put it down like a normal human all right i still got a bucket still one bucket
remaining everything's fine it really is not that's what i wanted i wanted to get at least
this part done now we can clean up a little bit get the last little bits be fucking serious
you can use the toilet okay that changes everything no i'm not supposed to be doing
it like this no i'll get this out here i'm not supposed to be doing it like that
no the bullets were in there shit
it's all right give me that thing i need to bring it back it's a good transport
replace the toilet seats in time in time and give her the trash first 15 minutes left i got
plenty of time i'm almost done and now it's just a question of just dunking it this is
good just gotta replace the seats do i why would i i don't even need to do that looks pretty clean
to me leaves us with this room i just want to get the blood and shit that's most important
what that what's that doing not very much blood in here though so that's good yeah this is
clean this shit is clean clean clean just gotta pick up the body and throw him into the body
let's bring this okay um the whole thing's getting burnt so don't worry there's something
flickering yes it's a light it's this light look at vent look at vent what there's something in
the vent which vent oh there is something in the vent you're right is that alive is this
thing still alive do i have to i have to burn this don't i is it alive no it's dead there's
blood up here now though i gotta go get the gun i don't want to pick this up
disgusting that actually i hated that okay clean clean clean now we just bring the
fire gun up here and burn the whole thing so what does that leave us with i need to make
sure i have enough of these here okay so i need to bring up how many med kits one or two
two there's one two and i have i can clean my brush in the toilet so i should be able to clean
the rest of that don't think i don't think i need buckets i am going to leave this one up
here though because this one still has some water on it so i'm going to leave it take this
get it over there and get this fucking thing out of here too come up with the gun burn
this whole thing clean it up and get out of here flush the toilet can you flush the toilet
oh it was a lie it was a lie all right let's go back down i need two med kits and then the gun
let's do it whoa easy i cleaned all this shit up already what is what is this all right now i
remember all right give me the gun i'm gonna deal with this shit later who the hell is the
gun where's the gun what song is playing right now oh the portal 2 ost it's been on for so long
i thought it was an in-game song and i wanted to turn it off all right that's enough of that
yeah here's the red dead redemption 2 ost why does everybody hate this hold on you guys don't
like this don't you don't like this i'm very i can't believe it where am i going i need an
elevator i need med kits too i picked this what is all this shit oh yeah that's okay hold on i
gotta get hey hey all right there almost spill joked almost all right you try to tell me how
that was possible that i didn't do it there okay i don't know how but it's gonna it's close
oh here comes the giga spill no not gonna happen ready
it's all right this can be cleaned easily oh i'm tracking mud everywhere no
there's so much mud nice excellent nice great cool great fun all right i gotta get all this
shit out of here did that spill it how did that spill two spill jokes it's getting old
i'm not trying to do it i'm carrying like four buckets at the same time upstairs is pretty much
done just need to bring some toilets i need these i'm stashing them right here i need this
boomer music hey get god get real all right i know how many toilet covers do i need just two
what the fuck is this it gave you an ad oh okay yep all right how many toilets do i need
i need two i need four no only two broken toilets in there all right um you mean light
i didn't know it can do that fuck i thought this was an led i don't know it was like
place it gently all right that's where the toilets toilet seat one toilet seat two
two two gun light let's go i don't need anything else right i don't think so let's go
play lisa i've never even seen i haven't played lisa is that on it's on right okay it's on
i didn't even need these all right let's go ready i'll give you a fucking ost here we go
and what i fucked that up there whoa easy okay here we go you're curious of why the hell i just
did that well it's a very very very easy answer there's so many body parts that just burn lighten
the whole fucking thing on fire i can just look at all these little meat cubes it'll fit nicely
in here bring them both over here that wasn't even the right version there's a correct version
what do you mean use the broom what why am i doing this how the hell how is this gonna do
anything for me wait a minute i don't do shit now i get this like so many fucking dumb canisters
on the ground play the busting version no no no more osts i'm not gonna say that word for
another fucking year see this turned out to be a good idea i got toilet water to clean the
walls and we can be done that's it and is there a basement there is one little basement
what was the uh the estimated time 2.3 we're at 4.3 it's not bad he's not doing it he's not doing
it um why would i want to play that not right now in like 10 years almost every piece of
meat is good to go i would have the exact correct amount of boxes that i needed for this
job now a a spill here would be a catastrophe so i have to make sure that doesn't happen
actual catastrophe this would cause a huge problem this might be too big to put anywhere
um i don't know if i'm okay with that but whatever good exactly what i needed so let's
just go over here i have the bucket still i oh riot riot riot he's not going to do it
you know what to do uh i need buckets up here there's no way i'm going to do this
with toilet water no there's no way this is why is this so dirty what what else oh med kits right
get these in here do this now so i don't forget about it get in there ray parker jr here we go
give me this
i forgot all right i'm gonna put the light down i can't even hear we're gonna bring
this shit down no way where's the toilet where's the other one let me tell you
what i forgot how these this soundtrack is that's right here sleeping yeah what this is all dirty
let me sleep in you that stupid line
that line get me out
no
where's the incinerator i ain't afraid of no bad what do we got a little bit of not even
a big skill it's fucking with my brain i gotta turn it off it's fucking with my brain
i can all i can hear is that that was the end of the song anyways we're fine
oh my god there's like five seconds left there you go well there it was mine's my job my
jaw hurts after that for some reason this would be the final cleanup bucket of water i need
a bunch of water because there's no way i'm gonna get through that final cleanup but we'll
do that final cleanup that's fine okay get that out of here like seven buckets i'm going so fast i
know am i i can't this is this is where i spill something i just need like four or five probably
that should be it and we can finish it play feel good ink no that's a legit full-on copyright
song i'm gonna go with six that should be enough age of mythology already did that
we already did age of empires age of mythology didn't we do all that already
all right what else do i need there's no there's nothing else up there i got all the meat
i just need to clean with the mop let's just get up there see if i can do it with three just
don't back the fuck up into these like an imbecile is that enough for me to walk by how
thick am i jesus oh my god that's so hard to do you do it twice and it's gone am i ever
going to be able to clean all this i don't think i will oh no oh no three sweeps and it's
completely and totally filthy somebody in chat said good luck cleaning that now i understand
what the hell they talked about so many layers i have to get like six more buckets maybe not
maybe maybe i can do the rest of toilet water should have just bought a pizza cutter
well that's my own damn fault in it well that's i got maybe five feet oh yeah yeah two trucks mr
streamer what is two trucks two trucks let me see the hell you guys talking about two trucks
what am i gonna play this for no i don't know what the fuck that is i like why am i gonna do
that is a good song no we don't we don't play every single request um what's it what's
a song i could put on right now look at this wow there's like literally only are two options
here apparently one guy said this so it's going on so loud for careful yeah this is louis g's
mansion official sounds like that i might do it it's possible this is gonna be okay maybe
because it's getting a lot thinner over here i think we got it it's the last bit i can do
there what are these random duck sounds
this is freaking me out because i feel like somebody i'm walking with not the right sounds
when is the new one coming out aren't they making another one mario no louis g's mansion
aren't they doing another one for switch i think we're gonna get it this would be so
satisfying if i can get it in just these last few buckets ah i think i can do it
i think it's gonna happen you stupid fucking game i'm fine it would have happened too no not
quite just give me the toilet excuse me excuse me fuck i'm dragging this around everywhere
i don't want to hear louis g anymore that scared the shit out of me i actually just like
my face twitched when that happened is this an ost or is this somebody playing the fucking game
oh
fucking breaking toilet seats i have to bring no i'm not i don't care we're done i did it done
it's been done it's completed we're fine just gotta get all this shit out of here
and then we're done i can go downstairs throw the lantern into the toilet fine
i hate to crack the egg wanted to see what was in it i was never here you're fine everything's
clean everything's good just gonna put this back on here that's fine fine foo i don't think i'm
getting it back whatever i'm not gonna miss it upstairs is done let's go get out all the junk
just throw it in here it'll be fine that was fucking crazy i just jumped i tripped over this
that's what happened i didn't jump the gun i need all this oh my fucking god i was trying
to pick it up you idiot are these all empty anyways why why god no i need the gun both
no why are you still here burn the buckets no that's gonna cause a huge problem i just
cleaned it up all right is there any more bullet holes i don't see i thought i just ran
into something you know the thing is there are probably a few people here that are like i
hate this this in the song i'm talking about they're all dirty i can't flush either
and i'm fucking tracking this everywhere all right we got uh i can finish it up later i'll
i'll look i'm gonna come back up here later we're gonna do our final pass through anyways
i don't see any bullet holes in here a couple here so that's one two one two one two
one two looks good be sure i didn't miss any light in the room up so i can see
i think i'm good i'll come up here i'll finish this later they gotta good i gotta go down
let's go let me take a look what if is there another one lower level no this is it this is
it this is it this is it this is it there's no basement this is it it's done i just gotta
throw the shit away clean it up do a final check okay let me just let me i gotta we're gonna do a
final pass through clean up bullet holes make sure everything's done this everything's fine
and i'm gonna get the it's gonna happen footprint don't worry we're gonna get the final
pass through we're gonna start over here i don't know what that does all right there's
bullet holes here all right i gotta no we're gonna end here because that's the that's okay
end there we're gonna end there that's the final pass throughs i gotta get all the way over here
i hate myself you guys are in my head so much i'd all i can think about every time i pick up a
bucket is i'm gonna spill it no i'm not don't do that people gonna think it's like on purpose
all right start from here give me a couple buckets we're gonna clean this up i'm gonna
get four new toilet covers and then i can be at the end of the game this level at least
this guy what a great game it's just so much fun you just feel really accomplished
it just scratches a ton of itches make sure i'm not tracking anything not all right i need
some buckets that's not a bucket it's going immediately into i can't even pick it up that's
fine that's great don't don't he's rushing slow him down okay yeah i get the arm this is all
bullshit i didn't even do this again that scared me again i'm i'm done with that one
gta vice city my favorite part about this whole stream so far has been when the music turns off
i look over at the chat room and it's just a million requests that's the best part
the room is silent hurry up scream we've done earthbound too many there's too many
requests here i don't know what to do i was supposed to do this a long time ago okay where
is my bucket these are dirty whoops a daisy didn't matter all right this is clean corner
to corner just last cleanup this is not i need to get this arm out of here this whole thing
doesn't fit at all this is bringing back such weird memories that i don't think i want
to have right now just hanging out in stormwind you know i don't want to i don't really want
that was i don't want to think about that junk this is just bringing back memories of idling
and trade chat trying desperately to sell this one item that i was over pricing the
fuck out of got like a boe epic and i probably sat there for like four days trying to get like
400 gold for it and this this song played in my sleep all right let's burn it uh can i get
it over there without spilling door needs to be open no no no no no no clean this up first
this is a fucking joke that's a joke resident sleeper sour please how does that make any sense
that's funny that's funny it is get this in there it's looking good just easy i'm
gonna probably drop a piece of meat but it's okay get in there thank god there's no dynamite
in this level the hell is that oh it's the incinerator close that up uh toilet seat go on
the incinerator a little piece of blood it's almost at that point where i can pull up the
blood detection unit shit on the walls looks pretty good to me look at that it's beautiful
it's absolutely stunning absolutely stunning go to go forgot about the basement where there's there
where's the basement there's some bullshit over here i have to take care of alone
where i don't see this magical basement level that everybody seems to know where it is with
me too dirty shit don't have any stray buckets just sitting around somewhere
it's behind the secret door last time everyone told me to do a secret door it was it was dog
shit and wasn't real and i spent about 20 minutes trying to figure out how to get inside of it so
i don't know if i believe you right now all right so far so good one bucket any more blood
or shit anywhere i can see not really doesn't count on the other side it's a note here
today so something weird they have me and again to repent and it's uh bad demolish
oh thank god there's nothing in here no liquid doesn't count no liquid doesn't count
i'm just trying to go too fast he's pretending to spill i was i had i blocked all of my vision
if you fucking seriously don't go in there okay one more spill and you have to play death
grips hey well that's not gonna happen so i'm fine
anybody see anything else i don't i think i'm almost ready except for this my god just
fucking throw it over there i'll get it in a minute there's a fucking incinerator
it's i am so close to being done spill spill spill what spill the bucket
that one that's over here on the ground over here this wasn't this was already spilled
that doesn't count see look there's two of them here got it okay good blood in the cage
thank you you guys are always looking out for me appreciate it this is it i just have to go
upstairs i'm gonna take out the meter and that's done i don't there's no secret level
i don't know what this is for though that has to be here for a reason right
have i stacked the crates and barrels uh there was a door i had to go into earlier
little crevice in the top corner that i had to go into and i stacked a couple things
okay ladies and gentlemen i think that's it let's take let's get make sure one
pass through the whole thing take out the meter well ah what's the problem over here
there an issue that i don't see i need to get the uh gun i need to get the gun wherever
i put it boomer laugh i just made a little bit of noise with my mouth you know you know
because the boomer's gone forever okay broken toilet just trying to keep my eye out and then
i'm gonna go through i'm gonna do the bullet holes i gotta bring a bucket upstairs
that's pretty important give me a new bucket let's get that over here throw you away and
that should take us to the end just gotta go upstairs and fix a few things i mean that's
spilled with enough minutes so that doesn't count i already went up there no that doesn't
count that has to be something has a spill on the ground nothing spilled on the ground
it was air all right it's time to get the gun is it on here where is it upstairs is the gun
upstairs blood on cage door i'm doing my best ah i still need one of those is this still the
storm wind music ow what am i supposed to do with this oh this is the cataclysm version
okay i see i feel you i need that gun i need the gun then i don't know where the hell i put
it then i leave it upstairs well all right we're gonna go top to bottom then because
there's bullet holes down here i guess it's a health pack thing here i mean there's an explosion
that just happened right don't do that it's already clean don't fucking do that okay
i'm gonna go top to bottom i did bring one bucket up there and okay let's get it bullet
holes i know i know i know i know i know i'm gonna bring them i'm gonna bring the gun down
here one guy the car is upstairs guns upstairs the gun is upstairs right now i got a fresh
bucket to clean up the little residual shit on the ground let's die toilet seats
no who cares just sit on the fucking raw seat doesn't matter looking good that's it
that's what i needed to do bullet holes taking the bullets rat's birthday mixtape i'll do that
at the very end good to go blood in the other room i'll get it there's some trash in here but
at some point you kind of have to give up no well let me at least just set it up in the
right spot so i can eat there's so much stuff i don't have a box up here it's just tools
anyways this isn't kind of cleaning this is equipment that's not dirty this is there
okay thank you there's a note i need to read this in the light manage to breach security
protocols by avoiding my personnel my secret has been discovered and as a result i'm in
deep trouble auto came for me luckily i managed to hit him with my mop but now i'm on the
run the things i've seen in this facility and in so many other is truly horrible sooner
i get out of here the better if anyone happens to find me i'll need a better weapon and soon
i plan to make it for the cryogenics lab and hopefully sneak through undetected
and does never find me sorry about that okay done let's go out stick it in one of the pots
you've got to be kidding me what why thank god thank god all right don't do it all over
again thank god i have to play death now i don't feel good i can't i don't feel good today i can't
like do that like the sum of curds see that's what happened last time i just popped up for no
reason done nothing else up here cleaned all the toilets cleaned all the rooms i want to
they're all empty anyways i don't think it matters all right let's go nice gym class
excuse no i don't feel good uh my stomach hurts elevator blood on the ground i'll take
care of it all right goodbye i'll never see you again top floor we're done here we go
time for the bingo bullet holes cage in the upstairs room just wait crushed okay gonna move
this out of here all right now let's do bullet holes and i'll get a box to put the those
things in bullet holes let's try the bright room i'm sure don't miss any ton of blood in the
elevator shaft one thing at a time hold on put on the rat's birthday mix oh my god fine
the fucking rat's birthday mix
this is just turning into a shit post that's good for bullets good this room
check this one make sure don't miss any bullet holes here good let's move on i don't know
how much i can take of this this is like i'm like a fucking i'm in like a dream
oh my god there's so many bullet holes in this room one two don't i gotta wait
that's a cool fidget spinner gun all right there it is michael's been such a great boy
this year i'm gonna dmca myself too and two again no i'm not no no you can put your own
soundtrack on dude open it up right now let's go to youtube type in rats mixed birthday mix tape
and you can hear it right now it's not the same well that was a lot there was so many bullet
holes over there i think that's it for the room here uh is it hmm just to make sure
got it looks good next room this place needs a med kit let's go get that done right now
yeah i know i know how that works i've been here for like five hours got done done done done
done everything's done give me back that the only few more bullet holes and then we can go
upstairs fix the bullet holes up there and i've completed this level i'm gonna say i'm gonna say
probably somewhere around like a 95 percentile 96 make sure i didn't miss any back here i did
didn't i already get these no that's it thank god there's the end the end's inside
i can see it i can see the end there's blood in the middle of the elevator i'm about to go
back to the elevator don't worry looks good looks pretty clean oh yep no
there's a usb upstairs i'll get it i'll get it don't worry all right lock it in yeah lock
it in bullet holes upstairs and then uh go ahead and lock it in new seats free now they
can sit there they can sit on the cold seat for all i care i don't see any more bullet holes
up here no uh ah ah who the hell is this all right fuck it here we go can't get up there
from here get the lift yeah but who cares i'm not even sure that's what it's looking at
oh it's talking about right here right come on okay fuck do i really have to go get that dumb
thing downstairs there's blood still up there in the god damn it all right well makes everything
else in here is fine yeah everything's good now just get this thing back downstairs i'm
gonna get the lift up there and then i'm truly done was the usb somebody said there was a
usb up here there i get it let's go clean clean that up no i don't need to clean that
up it's not dirty now it's very quiet all right go down get the lift put this downstairs
i don't think i need this anymore i need to lift do your job i am doing my job did a pretty
damn good job there is a basement i'm serious well where is it then probably down yeah but
uh i can't take an elevator down okay okay so here we are what the fuck this is a problem
up here okay don't i gotta be careful i don't want to let this go because i don't want the blood
i don't see anything else i'm not sure there's anything in there fuck there is mop is dirty the
mop is not completely dirty yet though can i pull this off it's the meat okay well let's go
what the hell was that fucking dumb thing unbelievable come on one more son of a oh god
that was such bullshit come here close it up all right very very good let's take care of that
again looking at the elevator left side of shaft going up is dirty well there's no i let
me try this one last time because i don't know if i'm getting let me see what happens when i
do this because i feel like i can get in there we're almost done i don't think there's
anything in there that's it it's done that's it let's go whack it i can't do anything about
whack it twist it all right that's it i'm up goodbye goodbye upstairs it was fun
shoot it the gun's downstairs how are you okay so when we're going down is my finger on it
let's get out of the way okay here we go did i get it oh wait got it there's more
how does it even get down here getting the fucking sense
all right spill buckets oh that's right okay that's it is it detecting this
come on get up that one's done okay now i'm gonna put in the usbs and i'm out of here
you missed the basement lower level basement basement there is lower level there is no i
can't go anywhere see there's no there's no basement there is no basement don't go in send
it up otherwise this is a dark soul send the elevator up open the door i can't open the door
all right i'm out of here i need a bucket that you know why i did that so don't even
tell me that was on purpose i mean it was on purpose but you know you know what i'm
talking about feels good feels good to have a fully clean room everything's good over here
the time is up just jam the door with the lift no i did it i did it all everything's good
to go it only took six hours see we're good jam the door burn the usbs no i'm gonna dump them
all out there's my halloween candy i'm gonna dump the whole thing out death crypts now
no no death grips okay hey thanks everybody for watching the stream we just did a full level
of this or clean up detail move this all right i'm gonna jam the fucking door
because everybody won't stop with this jam the door bullshit so all right here you go jam door
you can't jam the door no you can't use a bigger object this is the biggest thing in the whole
level this is the biggest object there ain't anything very much bigger than this stand in
the doorway where's the body isn't usually a body when you die extend the lift oh my god
i'm gonna just end this why i don't know extend the lift this doesn't matter i'm done i did it
it's obstructed i can't even do it look watch i'll do it again it just ate it it just
swallowed it is it in there oh thank god who cares i'm done i win bye hold on good to go
this is usb on the ground well there's no usb on the ground that's not a usb this bullet all
right oh there is a bucket right there good call all right that's it into the incinerator it
goes and we're gonna see how good of a job i did it's not gonna be 100 but you know you
can't choose for 100 look at this looks nice remember what this shit looked like before
good to go thank you choice i wish i could do more for my company give me some paperwork to fill
up for extra marks yeah let's do it uh please tick the box that best describes the severity
of the incident you worked on wait what oh easy moderate challenging severe that was moderate
painful horrifying i'm afraid to sleep it's kind of painful i browned out i don't know
what that means please describe your method for completing the job what was your work style
okay um please take the best described so efficiently you believe the job was completed
evenly that was probably rationally incident particulars please take the box the best
described the particulars of the whole incident uh aliens mutations chemicals
guns guns personal account any relevant info you wish to report describe the day's work
please enter the number of alien entities presumed dead on site that's probably five
estimate a number of spent shell casings uh 20 estimate number of bullet holes unfound
on site that's probably like at least 25 please indicate the estimated amount of items
incinerated on the site uh 180 peer report if applicable describe the on-site work relationship
with your fellow employees union please enter your union identification number so we can add
to your last okay union id what is that it's on your pad oh whatever i don't know like clock
off i'm actually oh wait a minute oh it's all right promote it let's see you left the worksite
feeling confident that everything was in order a good job on your record is sure to earn a
favor with your superiors you feel a sense of fears you realize your colleagues are sure
to punish you for your efforts at ascension in the end you decide they can go to hell you
lazy losers you periodically gaze up at the wall in front of you smugly in between attempts to
beat your brum high score of level 13 and imagine your picture framed on the wall with the words
employee of the month beneath it nice but there we go look at that okay what's this thing
what percent was that though i don't know my workplace reports how do i see it fool behind
you fool fool fool oh 99 what happened here concerning evil science incident reports the
services company record people uh proximate data completion workforce size report particulars
report accuracy 60 death report zero i browned out confirmed articles oh this is just me okay
read the notes for what you did wrong jesus didn't do the basement who are these people
dr phil was here yeah this is all that santa's workshop that's funny 99 you left one shittier lid
read the paper notes um where are the paper notes it was the toilet seats
disturbed man consumes blood it's probably on paper maybe satisfactory job done despite
searching the back with the top the bottom i was able to find fault keep a watchful eye on that
station there look at the cat pictures nah five percent salary including okay cool
they're basically perfect yeah no i'll take a 99 percent and that's it and that's it read
all the notes one more level one more all right fine fine all right you know what fuck it we're
gonna do one more we're gonna do one of the easy ones what's the easy one is there one for the
was it is it one that's like 10 minutes where's the one that's five minutes be the same level
again no no no we're gonna do how do i get out of here what is it what's a quick one
i want one that's one hour one hour and 30 minutes hour and 30 okay this one frostbite
one hour unrefinery one hour oh 45 minutes that's a quick one section eight all right
which one unrefinery or frostbite frostbite looks like it could be interesting yeah let's
do frostbite one hour you got it i'm going let's go you think i was gonna come on this dreary
research and storage facility has a long record of minor psychological incidents due to the
isolation and cold but even so details regarding the events that decimated the
facility are sketchy at best an extraterrestrial organism is suspected involved however
the junior recon team is certain that no poses no threat there's nobody here
already there are multiple conglomerates interested in acquiring the installation
and collected data once you have executed your sanitation duties work diligently and with speed
as the facility is expected to be swept over via orbitable bio bomb to ensure security good
day all right one hour one hour one hour that doesn't need cleaning all right where are
we going nothing dirty over here easy i'm with the buckets buckets are over here the outside is
pretty clean you mopping snow yeah why would i need to do this they would just melt into the
ground i'm gonna try to get this one done in less than an hour no fucking around we're
gonna get this one done in like the next 40 minutes okay look at we don't got look at it
we don't got much where's the incinerator down here no no spill jokes we'll get this done
right fucking now this is clean clean whoa okay well that's kind of fucked up start right here
down in the corner this is fucking huge this map is on the hour this is going to take like six
now i didn't notice just deal with it look at all this shit an hour an hour is dynamite
down here i need okay i'm gonna plan this out i'm gonna block this out just wait
there's a bullet hole shit here one hour huh so incinerator here we're gonna start in the corner
this way i'm gonna get some of these the gun i need two of these for right here give me that
gun we're gonna melt everything over here don't start a fire these big chunks we need another
ost all right and this looks like it can be done now now there's one big chunk here that
needs to go i think that's good enough i'm glad to go outside in but if you're taking off
see you tomorrow a lot of people probably go to bed now so have a good night i'll get this one
finished god i'm trying to go to bed one hour fuck oh i was getting a little tired now i might
have to uh i might have to scream another day you know it's a little sleepy at this point in
the uh in the you know i'm getting a little sleepy fuck where these go i'm gonna put them
over here okay i need another one trying to get these all done right now there's really
not that much more did these explode i don't even want to know put the fucking etch a sketch
in there i'm just gonna stick them all over there how would you even do a speed run with this
you need to be on the ball the gun does not affect the barrels that's good to know all
right incinerator is where is it down that way let's just do it now goodbye this is
definitely the dirtiest place bye without a doubt okay well i don't know what just happened
something bad happened there it's all right i need some water oh a couple more boxes i can make
them level two messy that's possible put on the thing ost no peter god damn it whatever
get a couple of buckets you can get out of the way i'm gonna move these because that'll
look nicer if it's just over here just get this shit out of the way now we're not going for
like sexy with this one you know what i mean we're going for clean then that'd be like
perfect it's fine all right not doing so bad i need to where's the thing that generates the
what the hell is it there it is it was sexier before that's all right i've put it down too
just don't rush just give me a couple of them three should do it just like a puzzle
pick it up let's get it over there walk when does the game start right now
is that i don't know it is but it's okay easy that's gonna fuck um we're good all right
quickly let's go let's go let's go i'm angry i'm really not though dumb motherfucker what
are you thinking getting there i'm trying to go too fast that one hour estimate man who is playing
that what do we got right now it's been like it's been like 20 minutes already how do you
physically do this in one hour especially by yourself that just burnt me and turned it upside
down 30 minutes left it actually my way i might surprise myself and get it done pretty
quick this was the big holy shit moment here this was the worst one it was like 30 or 40
pieces of person here okay there we go a couple more pieces i'm gonna lose some of these
i'm looking if i can get an 80 here i'll be happy that's all i'm looking for
i'm not looking for 100 i'm looking for 80 hey hello pull it up nice close
put this in the burner really not much out here so that blended in with the fucking fauna
ah
i might be getting too tired for this shit oh i think i've lost it okay i just laughed like
i was at a comedy club and i was like 60 that was like a 60 year old fat guy at a comedy club
in the back laughing his ass off why does he have to be fat i don't know because he just
apparently does i have to come back and fix that later that's just okay this place is done
done done done so you take a look around some blood this way and there's a earthworm over here
we gotta get rid of it and good nice pick you up come with me i need water again i don't think
there's very much outside there's these two little research facilities and out here that's
it meltdown what where's the meltdown i'm fine meltdown i don't agree with you at all
all right there's the other one is check out make sure you get everything outside
get some footprints there's gonna be a dead body back here probably yes there is and note
let's read it i think i'm the last one left they killed each other one by one or it killed
them i don't know this thing whatever it is we unleashed it and now we're paying the price
i can't get to the mess hall and i haven't had a drink in three days i don't feel so hot
huh did i just make a joke god damn it sorry the thing ost no i'm not gonna acknowledge what
happened i need two more why is our office chair out here what the fuck is this doing
all right wrong good time 20 minutes left but but seriously though okay we got over here
this little corner the two research facilities and that's it snack box person person
yeah i'll get this done in like 30 minutes you bet your ass i will carpenter makes good music oh
yeah the thing's a great movie really good movie actually it's one of the best one of the best
thriller horror type movies you could probably watch out here nothing this way right just
check in to make sure i don't get i gotta get at least 80% done with that guy walked over
here i'm gonna need to clean that up a little bit it's probably blood and shit up
there's probably a dead body up there too it's all right it's all good uh buckets i need six
what anything in there is this empty it is get this down here i need six buckets it's gonna be
easier on me if i just do this one by one got to finish cleaning with where that guy was
yeah that's all right i will i won't forget it all right i need i need that gun probably
this is actually not as bad as i thought it was it really isn't it's down here i mean there's a
shitload of people random body parts but it's all right bob the builder ost there is no way that
bob the builder doesn't have an ost good thing i have another one of these down here
uh i'm not gonna bring the dynamite because that would be bad i'd explode myself
just tipping i'm gonna lose a piece probably but whatever let's bring it up please do it
what do you do what bob the builder nothing spilled good one hour yeah maybe if you have
maybe play with four people i don't understand what's going on right now because i can't lift
them up you know you know what let's go just take them you're still waiting for that apology
i didn't do anything i'm not even gonna look all right now i can start the cleanup process
down here it's because i didn't play death grips i'm sorry i'm sorry guys put my own
music in the background i'm really i'm really thinking bob the builder ost something like that
okay i need a bunch of these this is not on the this is not a level surface this is not
gonna work i need to pick this up and put it on a level surface like right here i need four
we'll go i'll try to pick up four i can't do any more than that any more than that is
a disaster waiting to happen look at how fucked up this is this is all fucked up beautiful all
right one more did that spill i don't think so right straight ahead no not straight ahead
this way thank god it's just barely tall enough to fit under here beautiful set it down nice and
easy okay nice oops oops i don't know what to do i don't know what to do i don't know what
to do okay fine you can't tell me that that was my fault that was so fucked up that was
the water was alive at that point what the hell was that i didn't i did not that was you know how
much bullshit that was i'm trying to take the top one out and the whole thing just starts to
come alive i was being so careful you can't tell me i wasn't being careful there i was
being so careful stop stacking four fuck no i can't it's not gonna take me like three hours
where are they they have to take up across the whole game i did that on purpose because i was
fucking angry i may as well just kicked that bucket as hard as i could let's go with two now
there's blood everywhere what are you doing what are you doing you're like falling it's
jumping out right now why are you falling out stay right there my carumba my god okay can we
please start cleaning up i'm gonna knock this fucking thing over i swear to god all right
i gotta put this guy in the bathtub just go in the bathtub for now i'll deal with you later
oh my god get in there i'm ruining this whole thing oh my god just take him just fucking take
the goddamn guy and put him in the fire i should have even moved him the place is filthy
you'll be fine 35 minutes left i think i'll get it there's really only the other place
after this and that's it i wish i could put the camera down because like you can't even see
like i can't aim this down because what the hell i want to look down but if i look down i have
to put the fucking tube down here comes a meltdown no there's no meltdown is this you
can't melt down this game it's almost done there's just dynamite a couple of bathtubs need
cleaning okay looks this looks much better i need i need to step on something for this
i stand on this apparently i can what is this three life forms in the ice specimens been thawed
so they were these aliens in here okay now this is going to be impossible i need to bring this
over here and i did close don't knock that over okay can i fit it all in here let's find out
i think i can no i can walk this one back so let's even get the little pieces in there
is uh do i have another one down here no this on the other hand i'm just gonna walk it back
it's too big that was no way those yeah i got to come back my shit face what's going on here
am i drunk where'd that go okay well i'm going to walk this back there there's the
99 watch out for okay there are no buckets in the way speaking of buckets what happened here
i'm gonna need like two or three more stack up two here comes the bad ending i think i can do
three four is pushing it but three is possible this might not be the best place to do this
i need to move it a little bit so it's on the flatter ground five no way i can do five
if four is pushing it five is dumb i'm walking nice and slow
what which one does i don't think that was anything that was not none of these spilled
oh my god it's doing it again fuck it's gonna do it again i'm not touching anything
how did this happen it's stuck inside the second one is stuck inside it's wedged in there
somehow i'm trying to turn it please help me salvage is that gonna fall let me salvage this
one thank god that's not a good spot for that i didn't do anything it just shot me up here
what the hell why am i up here what am i doing up here why am i up here no more blood bloods
in the front door you're doing this on your own yeah i know and that's part of the estimate
one hour uh-uh where i don't think i have no i got one i think it's full though isn't it
speaking of full this i gotta get this shit out of here this one's full this is just a hazard
waiting to happen this is a piece i need to take with me just look at all these buckets
that are just asking for me to tip over is that in kind of i gotta get this out i need
another one i gotta bring this back or get another one that sounds that's very loud for
what's in here did i what did i bump into those parts are alive i hope not all right
so close to being almost ready to play what am i i am playing what am i talking about
it's just this is really really dirty i gotta mop all this up i got plenty of buckets for
that though just make sure i get all these little bits and pieces down here
there are a couple more alien hands can i reach how's that i'm reaching hey there we go
give me this uh put that down forget about the i don't care about the dynamite and
shit what is what the hell is this med kits that's somebody else can come and figure that
out clean clean kind of this has got to go bucket bucket bucket bucket buckets everywhere
piece of meat it's a leg two over here remember when he promised us death grips
did i did i promise death grips though did i say wouldn't that be fun
if you saw death grips i don't think i promised it all right that's good
any more limbs there's one over here pretty good all right this place is almost done need
to stack up some of these that one needs to be stacked and we can get the hell out of here
and go to the last part this is dirty look how many buckets are down here you gotta be
kidding me it was at least 10 to 12 buckets down here is that what do you see 4k what do
you mean uh i don't think i'm getting this one well that sucks well it's technically clean it's
not there anymore all right little doodads put them in here get this can this fit in here too
maybe yeah with a little jiggling it should be all right no blood in there clean no blood
in there clean clean clean just the stairs i'm gonna go do that now pack let's bring this
bucket up with us because you know like it's not gonna fucking get any better
there are pieces up here i might as well pick this up bring this too this is full though so
i'm not sure how well this is gonna go can i fit these little pieces in there no just
saying i'm just gonna have to clean just gonna have to go like this on the walls and slowly
go up here and then be done and there's only one more little spot left and that's it i beat
that's done where's the clean bucket clean bucket i need one is one right here right
yes durami i'm so proud of you hey thanks thanks really are you really thank you
that means a shitload i always have the bloody hell achievement 10 000 i'm not sure 10 000 what
blood mops let's get actually let's get this out of here i'll fucking trip over this
there's still bits of people all over the stairs yeah but this is the big one the one right there's
one other facility over there and then that's it we've got community subs great canadian fuck
club thank you for your five gifted subs thank you adding to the absolute ridiculous amount
that you have gifted hundreds hundreds of gifted subs hundreds of them dirty dirty
all right can he do it is he capable of doing something like this to save a little time
yeah i'm fucking glad it happened how many buckets so many of them more community subs
kazi just came in with 10 community subs thank you kazi 10 more community subs yeah can't spill
them you can't spill when there's nothing in them i can get it it's hard to see thank you
guys so much seriously tons of subs have come from community community subs recently so
okay i saved it saved it it's too heavy i can't pick it up it's too heavy
it's too heavy i can't do it wait maybe i can no just take the top take the top three go out
this thing would just tip over it's too heavy spill joke no that's an intentional pick it
up joke that wasn't even a joke why am i calling it a joke this has liquid in it just
don't be a dumb idiot and just put it in there and get it in and then pick it up
dispose of it put on the english lessons what is this game about it is a game where the
goal is you just clean up a battlefield you get a mop you get buckets you have to pick everything
up you got to mop everything and that's pretty much all of it that's the whole game make sure
i'm not tracking this but it's okay all right so close just need to bring another one or two
buckets down here all right somebody got to get me a good english lesson i'll put it on
just barely wedged that in can you do a fortnight dance after the stream yeah sure
okay i can't i gotta pick these up let's go one two i'm gonna say three will be all right
oh yeah yeah oh oh just fix it flat surface that's the problem slowly don't be stupid
what's the best fortnight dance um i don't know oh boy don't do that pick it up don't
please don't i can't put it here lift it up lift it up pull it back right here relax
it's just like tied up somewhere i don't know anything please we can move on from this area in
just a moment time for the looping dr phil joke no it's get it's late is it getting late for
that that was like a four hours ago type deal people are getting tired that was a lot of blood
there and now it's almost gone looking good all right a couple more footprints there's some
body parts down here still though unfortunately everything else looks pretty good he's doing
another level yeah this is just a quick one though well it's supposed to be it is gonna be quick
because we're pretty much almost at the last spot i do i do need one of these there were
some body parts down here still that i want to make sure i got like this one here and then
i'm gonna crush it with the nuclear waste mop up the last bits and leave and leave stop stalling
i'm going as fast as i goddamn can stalling i'm trying as hard as i can to do this in like less
than an hour and a half faster i'm good i'm trying that's it pretty good ceiling walls
everything looks clean gonna get this out of here burn it all right wait this is dirty too
these somebody said that's dirty it doesn't matter they can be dirty let's go watch out
for the bug there's a couple those two buckets right in front of me don't ram into
them where are they right there okay drain this what do i got 20 minutes 12 minutes left
it's gonna be close it will be because this is that's the only thing left hold on i'm gonna
bring bring this one with me because it's still some shit on the outside let's finish up the
outside i gotta pee but i can't go to the bathroom right now i got 11 minutes left i can't
go pee right now that looks good some blood in the corner over there i'll get it hopefully
i'm gonna be able to do it with this because it's a huge spill got it nice okay good great
almost there close i just gotta get on top okay i see a body right there
god damn it there's so much up here only all that right yep only right here
shit um i'm gonna have to do this i'll have to clean it up later i just gotta get it off
i know i'm causing a mess but it's better than nothing got it damn it don't i got it
don't move i'm gonna i got i'm making footprints i got it's clean here we're gonna jump off
backwards that's the only way this is gonna work okay we're good okay this is gonna
it's a disaster over here it's an absolute disaster it's okay i getting that's the last
thing i'm gonna do give me some buckets we're gonna go down here i need what do i need i need
an incinerator right yeah yeah yeah i think yeah yeah yeah give me i'm gonna say five four we'll do
three there's plenty of dog shit over here anyway it doesn't matter that means i got four over
there i don't know how dirty it is down there but i'm sure i'm about to find out pretty good
first try stack it walk all right work down no bring it down bring it down to like this
spot here bring all the way what's down what the hell is even down here all right not bad
not bad it's almost done we got it there's really not that much blood down here see what i can get
with one bucket this is actually fairly clean already i need one of those hold on i need a box
30 seconds well i'm not going to get it in the hour but i'll get it in the
in within the next 20 minutes i need a box i need two boxes stack these i don't need them
anymore it doesn't matter if they spill it doesn't i don't care one for this way i'm just
gonna do it now get it out of the way fill this up this torso is so big you're gonna have to call
it a night well good night have a good night i know we're going kind of long into the evening
here but i had to do another one i'm addicted to this game this game really is just too much
fun just to do this it just is i don't know why something's gonna get lost over here what's
happening next year oh by the way so tomorrow tomorrow we're gonna play simpsons hit and run
either it's gonna be on the ps2 or pc whatever version i can get to work
this is not gonna work yeah speaking of working yeah that is the plan for tomorrow
need a bucket and depending on how long we do that i don't know maybe i'll like it and
i'll play the whole thing how long is the game six hours or something how long is it
50 hours no it's not it's a 50 hour game how is that even possible there's a playstation
two game i gotta dump this just this there's so many body parts over here how the fuck am i
supposed to do this that's it i need oh yeah there's so there's so many body parts over here still
am i supposed to put them in the i'm putting it in the bucket i don't care why was it where
is it can i reach from here what do you think close clean right just this little intestine
put it in here and i'm ready to move on in fact i almost i'm almost ready to clock it out
not much longer and yes i almost just ran right into that bucket that would have been terrible
good these have water clean water just got to get a bucket down there and then i'm clocking
out i'll have it all it doesn't look too bad just need one of the big uh incinerator buckets
nothing else all right nothing else nothing else no i'm good it's time to go uh yeah so after
this after doing this as fast as i can pretty much i wonder what i wonder if i'm gonna have
like 80 what do you think 75 80 i'm gonna say 85 after doing down here and then throwing all
the buckets away too speaking of buckets let's get this down here i need to fill this
with all the junk that's down here all right i got a bucket down here okay i just i just
set you down why are you broken chunks get them in let's take a look quickly more chunks
that's a big chunk i'm gonna take that by itself there's an alien in the room that's that's fine
the alien's gonna get dumped in the incinerator anymore no it's just
i'm just like fuck it i don't even care to do it looks fairly clean look left look left
look left oh that's bad oh my god why did i just do that i could have picked him up why
did i just stick up like a fire poker god damn it i gotta come back down here again now oh
oh well all right blood is all clean easy walk it out is there a pocket in front of me
no i'm moving to the i wasn't an idiot and i moved into the sides okay clean the basement
there ain't no basement i know okay what else is down here there's a couple of pieces i can
put it in a bucket i'll be fine head in there who cares about the usb's can i get
the head in there too it's gonna be tight and then the asparagus i don't think i can get the
asparagus in there oh yeah i can don't tell me i can't do anything let's get it out clean the
roof oh my god the roof is clean i had the asparagus in there already the roof is clean
the roof is clean god damn it it was ready to go i had to look over a chat for that one
second that's gonna fall out i don't give a fuck about the chips i'm not gonna dock points
because of potato chips all right i'm out of here looks fine i don't who cares about the
dvds no the body bag right the big body bag i'll get i'll get the big body bag the big chunk
got it all right big chunk gone these two put them together i'm not gonna leave a huge mess
these are gonna spill potentially but it's okay that huge fucking thing isn't it just close it
just burn the thing for christ's sake come on come on come on are you done
he's losing it i've lost it a long time ago probably this doesn't seem very relaxing
well this one has been stressful because i'm trying to get it done as fast as i
humanly possibly can okay that's it check around hold on okay what about the med kits
everybody's dead anyways one two you know i'm looking at it already might as well just do it
what are there two three that i can see up here there's a ladder and a shipment container
let's take a look because i'm done why is that even a feature you know that don't add nothing
that adds nothing you're gonna press the button again anyways where's this ladder
he has an air strafe that's it let's see if i got 80 or not what do i clock out over here
activate i'm proud of my work tell me what i did that's an 87 i'll take an 87 trying to
in an hour 87 is demoted apparently so i think maybe because i did 99 last time
it's probably something like that that one was pretty cool and that's gonna be it
we're at the seven hour mark i'll see you guys tomorrow for some hit and run mr cleanup detail
uh the game is really really fun it's really interesting i love it i will see you guys
tomorrow for simpson's hit and run have a great rest of your night if somebody were to
shit all over your bathroom and then you cleaned 87 of it yeah i guess you're right
there's still be some that's still be some shit in there you're right i'm gonna do the bits we'll
do the subs but i gotta pee real bad so i'll be right back we'll finish up if you're taking
off see you tomorrow or maybe see you when you come back whenever take care see you real soon
i'll be right back all right exit this game close it up i've been doing some long streams
lately oh you kind of i mean i'm i'm just having fun let's put this on because that's
where we are let's go to while ago about seven ish hours ago have a great night everybody
and let's do the bits thank you dennis for the one dollar thank you divas for the three dollars
mr pigeon for the one dollar a girl said she wanted a thick boy offered myself and she
responded with an oof i i don't know why i read it like that but i did thank you binary man
for the six dollars thank you binary man uh hey germa i made this while you waiting for
the stream to start there's a gnome well why would you tell me there's a gnome is that it
it's i don't i did you make that i'm not sure you made that did you thank you for the six
dollars oh here's a link to it if you want to you want to look at it let me get it up
there listen to the whole thing i don't want to listen to the off well ah ah i can't even
do it i'm too tired hey snooze and cough for thanks for the one dollar hope you played some
nice classic snes osts this stream we did donkey con country right also is it true that you
finished red dead 2 and monster hunter world off stream yes what's the final verdict uh i
thought they were both great monster hunter world is really really cool i got to the point
where i completed the story and kind of they were still monsters to
hunt but i didn't really play much after the story ended and same thing with red dead i did
all the side content side stranger missions and the main story and that's kind of where
i left it i thought they were both good i had a lot of fun with both of them thank you snoozing
copter for the one dollar demonic cucumber thanks for the one dollar summer lovin i've heard
this already do you eat ass i've heard that didn't we already play this before we already
played this before did we am i my brain cannot remember that shit but i think we did
thank you demonic cucumber thank you uh timmy tim tan for the three bucks uh love you germ
the only reason george rr martin hasn't finished game of thrones is because he's too busy making
daily english tv cameos on the phone a less formal call good afternoon scott and smith may
i help you may i speak to mr scott or mr smith please i'm sorry they aren't here right
now who's calling please george martin is there any message i can take mr martin no i'll call back
later thank you for calling that's weird that's very strange why did this come out this came
about in 2018 so somebody's making a funny thing there but thank you uh timmy tim tan thank
you for the four dollars total here timmy just uh i just donated three dollars in the bot
deleted my message because i linked a daily english tv video no i went through it's there
we saw it i don't know why i deleted it it's up here right here thank you ilm sal for the one
dollar i love this game but please use speedrun mode it adds a timer and removes random body
parts from the bucket dispenser that's actually really really cool to know because i did not
know what that did so that's pretty cool thank you for the one dollar thank you i'm
monk for the one dollar i watched ads to get enough bits to say i love you jerma heart
thank you so much hopefully you're not suffering through these ads too much for me thank you
though hey smelly boy thanks for the one dollar hey jamie pull up that video of that weird
streamer talking about watching the podcast look at this goofy motherfucker what the fuck
is a spie joe rogan all right because we talked about joe rogan that was like seven
hours ago i don't even remember what happened 45 minutes ago who's jamie i've never watched joe
rogan's podcast i don't even know what joe rogan's voice sounds like hey demonic cucumber
thanks for the one dollar jeremy the blue boxes used to save items like souvenirs from the
level and take them to your office stop burning them also stop just throwing shit around it's
not funny and this is the exact same thing that made the ceiling dirty last time i don't
think of i don't think i was trying to be funny throwing stuff i was trying to get it out of the
way thank you though uh thank you extra cheesy for the one dollar mafia city there it is
the guy turns into level 30 did people play this game
how many downloads does this have hey thank you mr sneak man for the dollar 60 hey jerma
spectrum decided to die in my area so i missed the new year's eve stream but i
wanted to say that 2018 brought an amazing year of streams and i hope 2019 will be even
better keep up the slightly questionable content viva las vegas ps vegas food of boston food
uh well vegas just has so many there there's hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of restaurants
around in vegas boston has great food boston has great seafood but if you're looking for
variety vegas is i think just where it's at he's a questionable streamer but thank you
though sorry you missed the new year's eve stream i had fun hey zack play a game now
thanks to the one dollar play royalty-free christmas music no you can't do that in january
you can do you start doing that in november you can't do that in january after first
i can't do that hey bake me home thanks for the one dollar bits thank you
we also had a dollar from katayusha alexandra for the one dollar so my birthday
was recently and i thought i'd give a bit of money that i got from family well i can't
make it to every stream i do know i can always enjoy watching and interacting with
everybody in the community germa hart hey thanks a lot happy birthday hope you have a good one
don't worry about not being able to make it to every stream there are there are a lot of them
and they go a long time i can't expect people to make every second of the stream
it's a long time thank you though ten dollars from cyprus thank you cyprus for the ten bucks
germa you reminded me of this game thank you so much the game is awesome it's fun just to
clean shit up make a mess have fun it's awesome i love it thank you the ten dollars hey katayusha
again for the one dollar the yakuza boss just busted into your house and is threatening to
smoke you what do you do uh what is what boss is this the mustard family lieutenant mcdonald's
i i would probably just i don't know they'd probably just close the door
and be like no i'd be like i don't i don't think i want to fight anybody
uh thank you c4g for the two bucks pogchamp thank you thank you kill code for the one dollar
plock ost germa fireman yeah plock is where it's at you promised a fortnight dance what
i have no idea what you're talking about fortnight dance sounds interesting whatever it is
hey superintendent chalmers thanks for the one dollar uh just wanted to let you know that
vinnie's chat uses the minus two joke every time he plays this clip what is this what my
minus two all right then keep your secrets all right i don't know what that is that's harry potter
and harry potter that is uh frodo that is frodo and tall wizard what's his name gandalf
thank you uh traumas for the one dollar thank you glyph bin for the one dollar i'll be
driving through vegas in an hour wave ah shit i missed you demonic cucumber thanks
for the one dollar you need to stop using the i'm naked excuse for your webcam since you
know you live with italics now what do you were you here when he told when he talked about
on stream that this is real he by his own admission i've he you can ask him we talked
about that during edf be him and star i don't i have no clothes on right now i'm not wearing
a shirt i wear pants yeah he he already talked about it that's alpha naked while he's wearing
pants uh thanks a lot though uh yes is online thank you the 15 dollars uh yes is online thank
you for the 15 bucks thank you your streams combined with mbv's lovelace have kept me sane
while working on projects i'm even flying to boston to film on location with your green
screen footage thanks for inspiring me plus cheers from pittsburgh what are you going
to do with me on location with my green screen footage thank you for the 15 dollars and
good luck with uh good luck with whatever you're working on that sounds pretty cool
thank you for the 15 bucks hey optimus thanks for the two dollars optimus hey germa thanks
for the great christmas stream and new year's stream is wondering if you have seen
into the spider verse yet oh so i thought the world needed to see the best joke of 2019
i have not seen into the spider verse no see the best joke well no i've not seen into the
spider verse that was an air raid siren no i'm looking forward to seeing it though i'll let you
know what i do thanks for the two bucks captain worgen thanks for the one dollar hey germa saw
you in las vegas the other day i wanted to say something but you knocked me down and
started throwing pocket rats at me italics tried to help me out but you shoved him aside
started throwing rats at him despite the ordeal i'm glad you signed my t-shirt you know
your signature looks like a footprint hey thank you the one freeman for the two bucks hey germa
if you ever do that ost cop joke i recommend buying and renting binaural audio kit for it
so when you break into the house as a cop it sounds like you're really crawling through the
listener's broken window shouting about copyright what is going on what we talked about binaural
audio but when when am i i'm breaking into somebody's house thank you uh the one freeman
hey manny the ripper thanks for 10 bucks manny the ripper hey what's up germa i'm a new subscriber
and this is my first time donating i love the vids keep up the good work thank you thanks for
the 10 bucks welcome welcome to the subscriber club no it's not a club but thank you for
your 10 bucks too uh dwarfs thank you dwarfs of the one dollar this is germa's art exhibit
i'm not sure what it is that's that's pretty good actually
all right that's i like this a lot thank you for that um manny the ripper again 20 bucks here
total play smash brothers on stream i probably am not going to i've made the final decision
that it's probably not something i'm going to do on stream i don't really play it
i played it for a little while and i just i just couldn't get into it my brain couldn't
lock into playing it so probably not but thank you for the 20 dollars manny
marvosh mcgalley thanks for the one dollar worst joke in 2019 is this the
sire's the uh here's the full ost of star wars no that would be a bad joke that's the worst
joke in 2019 that's worse joke in the last five years that's the worst joke in the last
10 years that's the worst thing i've ever said ever and i mean ever and i'm talking
in my life not wrong uh hey gatsio thanks for the 10 dollars no message thank you for 10 bucks
gatsio germa is the best thanks for the 10 bucks and what an interesting username that is
thank you for the 10 dollars sorry for bringing it up jojo in my last bit donation i realized
i was just beating a dead 2018 meme horse however i'm ecstatic to hear you are going
to watch one punch man which is a much better watch also did you know that it's getting a
season two in march i'd recommend you watch it too i did hear about the second season of one punch
man so i'll be primed and ready for 2020 when i watch season two thank you germa is the best
for the 10 bucks uh thank you that is like a keyboard mash uh thanks for the one dollar i'll
something this is not appropriate for me to read on on the stream thank you for the one
dollar though i appreciate it marvosh mcgalley thanks for the one dollar this is the secret
bit that will show up after the outro in second germa you better do something funny quick
um i don't i don't think i can i don't think i can fortnight dance so sad what why was it
sad what's so what's sad thank you errorless for the dollar 23 i love i love how recent
games have turned these into ost streams also this is a perfect laid-back cleaning stream
for my sick day so thanks yeah this game is great i love just dicking around in this game
hope you feel better also potato wizard academy thanks for the one dollar you're gonna play smash
ultimate i am not let's see let's just put this to bed right now i am not going to play
smash brothers on this stream let's just put it to rest bury it but thank you the rewind
joke was not very relaxed no it wasn't blood was coming out of my eyes yeah what a relaxing
day blood came out of all of my face thank you potato wizard we also had uh comfort eagle gave
a shitload of money tonight talked about the 50 dollars already but another 25 dollars from
comfort eagle hold shift when carrying stacked items to avoid mega spills i have i did try
that i was doing it but sometimes i just tip over the shift is walk but thank you spilled stuff on
purpose that's the thing i i can say this a thousand more times but those of you that think
truly that me like throwing something down a hall and knocking over the bucket
or bumping into a bucket is me putting on a joke no i got news for you you know it's
maybe it's like better that way that people think that because if i'm doing it on purpose
then like i'm doing then like i'm not really that stupid right and not really that careless
so it took off he's just made he's making jokes here he this is a joke then you there's
no way he's this careless that's what your mindset is if if i'm doing it on purpose
so i mean i guess we could maybe keep that going someone came in during the green screen
self-centered all right well i mean how could you not think that if you do i'm doing a night
where look at me on the screen but i mean could it really be self-centered if i show on screen
me using a stepladder to get groceries wouldn't i want to have like stuff that makes me look
good he made all of these and laughing at them oh i see that would have been a lot of work
holy shit imagine if i made all 400 fucking of those videos in two weeks
that's not even humanly possible number one jojo fan yeah i made all the jojo videos why
not but it's all good but thank you extra cheesy for the one dollar you say you don't
like being naked but you're naked constantly i'm just like half naked but i don't want to put
clothes on because then i have i could put turn the camera on turn on the cam got to have a
shirt on and shit no no i'm gonna sneeze so i'll see you in a minute okay i think we're good
yeah wait no another one coming on maybe hey optimist thanks for the one dollar optimist
that person was right jerma you really are adam sandler you even performed click
live on stream i didn't i don't think i did that thank you jamie for the one dollar that
rewind joke already wins best joke of 2019 don't be so sure william thank you william
for the 15 dollars that was an a plus bit thank you william if you're still here demonic
cucumber thanks for the one dollar chat we need to fix the timeline like seriously it's
fucking with my ocd it went its own way we went back and we went it was a different way i
guess so that's from what i feel to what chat told me but thank you so much demonic
cucumber for your at least three or four or even five dollars tonight thanks a lot
solid milk thanks for the one dollar jerma if you die in the 23rd can we rewind you
we can rewind you until you survive yeah we could if more than 500 people have to press the
button thank you solid milk thank you egg in my egg for the five dollars jerma please play
peter gun uh is that too late for that sorry i missed it but thank you for the five ducks
egg and five ducks i'm gonna like go eat a tomato after this i need something like
vegetables thank you egg and my egg for the five dollars demonic cucumber again for a dollar
you need to go on dr phil to sort out your relationship with this chat i think we have a
great relationship what are you talking about imagine a dr phil with chat is the actually
that's kind of a funny idea sitting there being dead serious talking about chat and all
you see is like owos and fucking smiley face i made this and shit like that well i'm
trying to have a deep conversation on dr phil with you guys thank you crow crow gar for the
one dollar hey jerma i liked your videos for a while now you're funny take some of my money
i will gladly take your money if you'd like to give it to me thank you alec four by four
thanks for the 27 dollars thank you for 27 bucks this meltdown is going to be one of
dr phil's main points in jerma's arrest why would i ever be on dr phil for real
thank you so much for 27 bucks double d thanks for the one dollar not a day goes by where i do
not enjoy a good spill joke i last my i left my ass off every time it's so funny i'm crying
laughing as i'm writing this message i don't know if this is sarcastic or not that might
be sorry i don't that might i'm not sure if that's sarcastic
thank you double d gozu thanks for the ten dollars gozu thanks for streaming kenshi those
past few days watching the stream reminded me of your monster rancher and oblivion streams
and playing it myself has been a blast it's a great game it's very uh deep there's a lot to
do thank you for the ten dollars i will be going back to it this weekend so probably on
what's today probably on monday i'll probably be going back to kenshi for a little while
maybe ferodian weapon thanks for the 250 ferodian put webcam on thank you for one
dollar hey it's me john cena you left your number one dabber trophy at my hair growth laboratory
uh all right thanks thank you jack the prick of two dollars and 45 cents
oh up in smoke thanks for two dollars and 45 cents garfield the monday killer thanks
with the one dollar for new year germa i should say something nice garfield thinks
you're the greatest online personality out there humble daring courageous and caring faithful
and friendly with stories to share all through the forest we sing in our chorus
marching listen gummy bears you're doing the gummy bears theme song
anyway here's a fan made pac-man track from super smash brothers we want fortnight we want
fortnight we want fortnight i'm not going to play fortnight fortnight dance well where are
you getting this fortnight dance from i don't know why everybody's doing this fortnight dance
what is this can you do a fortnight dance after the stream yeah sure i don't know when
did i say that oh you got that's a clip from like four months ago it was two days ago
now people like do shit to me all the time i'm like if i say like oh like shit ass i eat you
know what i mean if i say any of those words people will put it into a clip and just fuck
with me i eat ass right it's not hard to do hey i eat ass it's not hard to do that
you just it's sentence splicing it's that's hey german how many people sub to you
seven at least seven no how many subs are there now let's find out
an absolute shit look there are more than 5000 subs on this channel it's fucking ridiculous
yeah it's insane how do you think how do you think i keep renting out this studio guys
i mean think about it i told you guys i told you whatever money comes in
at a certain point it goes it you know it goes right back in fuck the studio how much of the
money goes to soylent um it would be way too much because soylent is incredibly expensive
yeah i got a stacked fridge of soylent no die die that's not true i can't say that
that's a fucking lie that's a joke i don't want to see i don't want to go down this
road what i just said right there was a fucking lie it was a joke i have no affiliation
with any company especially ones that i may have just said it was a joke it didn't mean anything
thank you welt for the three dollars thank you st jar for the two dollars
i was wondering if you even wanted to do merch i would buy oh what that's oh my god i
completely forgot i was supposed to talk about this during the stream shirts are coming in a
couple weeks the glue man shirt is coming back and the solar system shirt the new shirt
is coming too at the same time so at some point before january is over there will be two new
shirts that you can purchase how limited is the run if it's possible i may just make it permanent
so if it's something i can do if not then i'll run up as long as i can have a campaign on
teespring i will find out those details in the next couple weeks so those are the two
shirts that you will see but thank you st jar hopefully that answers the question attack of the
hank thanks for the one dollar when you first started carrying around four buckets of the
top floor i said as a joke chat i fast forwarded and he drops four buckets trying to fit them
all in the incinerator at once and when he did exactly that later in the stream i freaked
the fuck out yeah yeah yeah that's i'm not far i'm really just dumb i'm not done look i'm
not dumb okay i am not a dumb person i am a clumsy absent-minded person i'm not dumb okay
this like this thing about like i'm how he's dumb i'm not dumb i just walk into fucking doors and
bump into tables and knock over fucking buckets and shit i'm a little clumsy i think you are
smart germa you once bet that corn grows on trees if that okay you are talking about a
quote and a picture i was drawing in the middle of the of a gerbil video game the
really i was playing the gerbil disney game we weren't having a an intellectual conversation
i was rolling around in a gerbil ball g force that's the one right
oh i'm just kidding all right thank you super sale for the one dollar wow what a clean
streamer and opal and you could clean that dirty mouth of yours ha ha yeah that's true
matters of darkness thanks to the 17 dollars and 50 cents nearly 20 20 bucks play the curb your
enthusiasm theme or riot but during when i was dropping all those stupid tools what am i going
to play swat for um probably pretty soon i have to imagine it'll be in the next few weeks
but thank you for the 20 dollars matters of darkness it's a lot creel thanks to the five
dollars death grips has given out most of their albums for free on their site so i don't think
they care that much about copyright just a smudge uh a smudge pogchamp and then pogchamp like five
times did they really do that they gave out most of their albums for free that's kind of
cool damn but thanks for the five dollars it's uh too late for me to play pure bread thanks
for the five dollars extra cheesy thanks for the one dollar alec again thanks for the one dollar
if you were an anime protagonist your ultimate power would be the ability to turn one stain
into 50,000 stains and then take five hours cleaning up your own mess that didn't happen
thank you alec it was my 50 dollars you missed earlier but just play the super mario
galaxy ost did i i did did i really miss a 50 dollar bit donation from you did i
holy shit i touched upon it a little while ago right like not like half an hour ago yeah i did
didn't i because i'm hold on i'm scrolling back here from i'm back like eight i don't want
a minute because i i'm at because i see three days ago which is the last time i streamed
then eight hours ago i swear i touched upon it let me just make sure no i don't see it here
it was way back into the stream start because i see did the extreme labs eat this donation
because i see stormy chews and that was like seven and a half hours ago yeah i don't know
that's weird well sorry that happened because yeah i don't see them anywhere on here but
we're almost done uh let's go back to your original message original message here let's see
uh i'm just checking it one more time because that's really not cool if that happened uh but
thank you alec play super mario galaxy ost save it for next time i'm sure we'll be playing that
game again but thank you so much thank you c4g for the one dollar did somebody say thunder
fury blessed blade of the wind seeker i remember that those are the days mr avocado man thanks
to the three bucks happy birthday to us happy birthday to us happy birthday i remember that
yep i remember sitting there and having people spam that because only like one person on the
server ever had that thing so they would log on to world of warcraft and the first thing
they did they got like their morning coffee they take a couple sips and then they just
spam that in the chat every day all right getting close to the end of the bits we are
at uh the true thank you the true michi for the one dollar thank you for making me laugh lul
oh and also uh discord seems pretty empty i got no message from somebody
who wanted to message me i'll fucking i'll give him a i'll give him a stern talking to
after the stream sound it out jerma lul i'm gonna i'll give him a stern talking to after
the stream about that thank you true michi miss pence thanks for the two bucks you want
to come clean my place no i'll knock over all your stuff somehow your fridge will tip over
uh platid platid to donius thanks for the five dollars hey jerma you're doing a great
job of quickly and effectively cleaning just want to make sure you saw this fan art by
angus becloud on your subreddit oh yeah yeah that's fantastic thank you that's very good
a spill joke thank you e dragon for the eight dollars hey jerma are you ever going to do that
music making stream you planned before you moved yes it is on the distant cards and by
distant i mean at least a couple months because there are very very specific things
that i want to do for that stream that need planning need a lot of planning so yes you'll
see it pretzel foxtrot thanks for the 15 dollars sorry that the goonies stole all your
money pretzel foxtrot by the way you still here thanks to the 15 bucks uh pretzel foxtrot
is somebody it's uh me kim and it's alex were out a couple nights ago and pretzel foxtrot
happened to stumble upon us hung out talked for a while took a picture or two uh yeah
just good dude that was a pleasure that's where the picture uh comes from if you saw that on
twitter it was super fun that's i'm good that's glad glad to hear that it was great
just sitting there like sipping a wine hanging out you said how drunk you were what but thank
you so much for the 15 dollars i did lose well i i gained like 30 bucks and then i lost 25
dollars i think in the goonies machine and i said i'm never playing ever again
you were right there for that but thanks again dark soul 115 thanks for the five dollars
have you played near yet uh automata if not i would love to see you play it on stream
even though i understand if it doesn't seem like your kind of game
hmm i don't know not yet i need to space those games out games like metal gear rising super fast
pace action games i kind of need time between them does seem like it's pretty fun and also
i'm buying a fireman shirt and can't wait to wear them around everywhere and be shunned
for watching the streamer who made the star wars siren joke i mean it is embarrassing
no not to wear the shirt but what i did what is with me in saying things that out of context
are just bad the last couple days the last three days thus two streams i've said a couple
of things that just were not in the correct context but thank you hey a plastic spork thanks
for the two bucks hey german just want to take this time to thank you for getting
me through a really hard time last year i had to deal with a move from idaho to oregon
lasting grief from a late pet and getting my driver's license quick before the move
all at about the same time it's because of you and your amazing fan base that i stayed through
saying through that time the community is so welcoming and sweet and we're all here to
see the same funny caring amazing streamer germa hart thank you thanks for the two dollars
and yeah it's always a good time here always yeah we fuck around a lot and we i do dumb
shit i say dumb shit oh but just jokes you know what i mean we just fuck around
it's a great fucking community you guys are amazing good shit all around for real am i
gonna stream secure oh absolutely 100 yes and then uh plastic spork again for the three dollars
they say uh pride 100 pride 100 pride 100 anyway enough of that sappy shit damn germa
are you a donkey in a desert because that ass is thank you okay okay thank you hey uh bingo
bingo thanks for the one dollar thanks for the laughs the goofs and the the gaffs as a
streamer you add a lot to the community and you deserve to know glad you're here my dude
uh i could say the same thing to you so thank you so much the serobert thanks for
the dollar 14 my boyfriend has been watching you since he was in the seventh grade
he's in the 12th grade now and he introduced me to your channel and you're one of his favorite
streamers one of my favorite streamers we sing the birthday mixtape at his birthday every year
can you say hey philip hey philips so i can send him a video of you saying and he loves
your videos and shows me the tf2 classics well i gotta say something more than hey philip
hey philips hey congratulations no hold on that's that's too generic hey happy birthday
philips every year you're gonna listen to this until you're 70 happy let's let's go over all of
them happy 20th birthday 21st 22nd 23rd 24th 25th 27th 28 29 29 30th and then just like you you
don't know happy birthday every single birthday after that philips have a great day thank you
the serobert for the dollar 14 somebody just ha ha'd me what come on i'm just doing a birthday
thing i'm just doing a birthday thing i got like the ha ha'd for that did you
did you ha ha me at all during the fucking dog shit jokes i was making during the stream
there was at least one or two opportunities for you to use that not here
how dare you hey noby thanks for the three dollars 33 spence german what is your liquor
of choice other than johnny walker blue i'm looking to branch out johnny walker blue is
insanely expensive but it's my favorite whiskey ever uh so if you don't drink cider forget about
liquor cider hard cider is great my favorite cider ever is down east it's hard to get though
i think you can only get that in new england you might be able to special order it but it's
my favorite cider if you're talking about more hard alcohol i don't know i don't really
drink that much hard alcohol not anymore i'm more of a light kind of cider a little bit of red wine
maybe a cocktail or two but i'm not i don't really drink that much hard alcohol anymore
wine gives you a headache yeah it can you've actually seen down east in a liquor store here
in oh yeah get it if you're of age and you can drink absolutely it's great all right coming
down to the final 10 uh alex four by four again 11 dollars i must have only given 20 earlier so
here's another 20 my bad don't don't worry about that that's fine thank you so much for even
considering giving me money don't feel bad if something happened and you need to give it don't
you don't have to worry about that thank you thanks for even even any amount of money and
they say get some sleep i will i'll see you guys tomorrow demonic cucumber thanks for the
one dollar hey germ just wanted to give some more bits tonight because the stream always
gives me a smile i'm staying with my nan now so it's looking up a bit but you still help me
get through the tough days thank you handsome streamer thank you demonic cucumber it's always
a pleasure glad things are looking up much love to you take care of yourself handsome
streamer oh i was laughing i don't know why this made me think about this but i was laughing
really hard that is a picture that kim took kim like kim came in to give me like a kiss
and she snapped like a photo right and i was like oh whatever that's fine that's
that's cute i guess it's all right that's cool somebody somebody doctored the photo and
made me kissing me i was like what the fuck is this it's so it's it's so odd it's the
oddest thing ever it's just so uncomfortable to look at is that right there yeah look at that
look at how strange that is that's so strange
it's me and me kissing each other i i don't even know i can't even it's after a minute
after like 10 seconds i have to click off i was in bed last night looking at that and
i just shook my head back and forth i was just like what on earth is this cursed i was
laughing so fucking hard at it though but i don't know what made me think about that
uh uh thank you sir tardy grade for the one dollar hey germ i've been watching a youtube
channel since the tf2 days and just recently started catching streams these things are
carrying me through high school and i always have a good time thanks thank you since the
tf2 days i'm glad you guys still think it's worth watching after all that time demonic
cucumber again thanks for the one dollar final bits of the night i at least try to keep a
limit don't tell my mom that i gave you more than five dollars ps i can't help but think of
this whenever you rant about us making things up using audio clips you're doing that thing
again where you take everything i see out of context we're trying to make it look like i
think cool's bill sucks no don't record that thank you dr clay for the one dollar i actually
have a clip of you doing a fortnight dance already see i already did it oh yeah before i go please
do a fortnight dance i already did this i took one fucking kid with the backpack on this one
see i already i did it already see i told you that clip was from four months ago
i'll put webcam on thank you for the bits i'm fighting words sena have you ever seen that
man's new hair i have not seen sena's new hair i don't even know what he looks like
mostly lost thanks for the one dollar paper mario the thousand year door has the best
ost don't at me i never played it hey musty face cloth thanks for the dollar oh two
hey germa if you go with the pc version tomorrow check out lucas's simpson's hit and
run launcher has some good fixes and tweaks i'm going to copy and paste this because i'm going
to be looking up stuff like that before the stream so thank you musty face plus and i know
i just said your name wrong but i'm sorry kxc 501 thanks for the dollar 50 no message thank
you kxc flank tank thanks for the one dollar hey just curious don't remember if you walked
about it before but will you ever play nintendo 64 super germa 64 might be fun to
watch maybe a modern version or something yeah in due time i've had the dreamcast for
six months now and i still haven't found an opportunity to block out two or three
straight streams to do all that so once that's done kind of have to and i got playstation 2
add it to the list i still have the dreamcast but thank you hey casey thanks to the one
dollar here is the fireman t-shirt link they still this still i'm surprised that they still saved
this this still is here did they stay there forever i already have one i bought one i already
got one but thank you casey thank you lazy look for the one dollar what healthy food do
you recommend salmon salmon asparagus and like a little dollop of mashed potatoes you'll be
good to go for the rest of your life that is the end of the bits here come the credits
all the new subs and old subs thank you guys i'll see you guys tomorrow probably around
the same time around like three ish pm pacific i did update the offline screen same time
simpson's hit and run we're gonna give it a go and thanks for sticking around as long as
you did tonight i had a blast as always this or clean up detail is just it's just fun to play
and dick around in i was a little ill earlier i still am like a little stuffy but i'll be
fine tomorrow i'm gonna have some vitamin juice and we'll be good to go eight hours just over
the eight hour mark i'm taking boomer vitamin supplements nah i'm not sick or anything i just
don't know something about i've had some like nasal issues recently just dry irritated kind of
nose and it might have something to do i have a humidifier so i'm not sure if it has to do
with the fact maybe it's just drying out here recently let's see vegas weather let's take a
look at the what do we got for humidity over there actually it's really fucking humid here
right now it's because it's apparently raining but last couple of days it's been really dry
so we'll see what the fuck are bits uh it's a fake twitch currency that translates into money
it's the best way to describe it v bucks yeah have a fantastic night catch you guys tomorrow
will you ever think of accepting direct donations uh yeah this this really here's how
that plays out right i think that is the t-shirt sales you know what i mean that to me is that
paypal chargebacks yeah there's a lot of weird issues that have never really been solved even
though a lot of people say that they've been solved how about ethereum now that's been
deleted from the bio as you see so i i don't like to take direct donations because
bits are through twitch subs are through twitch i don't have to really worry about
having to keep track of that and no oh wait a minute you have to wait that was disputed
yeah yo did you just did you use any of that money yeah well hold on a second here has been
disputed you gotta give it back you know he's gonna be careful so having a t-shirt sale is
very similar right i'd rather have something tangible something you can really hold on to
bits cost more though yeah i know i i know bits are more expensive than actual money it's
quite a bit cheaper on our end if you enable paypal as long as you're careful not to spend
everything right away chargeback shouldn't be a huge issue but also here's another thing for
tax purposes it's it's a lot easier for me to be able to have something from twitch that's a
tangible thing getting straight up monetary donations through paypal is i don't know it
always kind of freaks me out because then it's just a pot of money that for tax purposes looks
a lot looks kind of strange but i am sorry that bits are as the way that they are if i
could put like feedback into twitch partnerships you know it would be something like that the
percentage i don't think has to be that high although i don't know what the overhead is
it's just my opinion right doesn't your job already look strange for tax purposes
not so much anymore because twit you know twitch is owned by amazon now so if if you get tax
documents from twitch it's amazon so it's not it's not really that out of the ordinary
i work at amazon no i don't i don't no i don't that's not true but that's my time i'll see
you guys tomorrow thank you mostly lost for the dollar thank you novi for the three dollars
three three three that's your name fuck it i'm drunk and i want the bit badge thanks for
all the years or laughs thank you see you guys tomorrow get some rest maybe we'll see
you tomorrow take care guys have a great night