Oh, don't worry, we can do it. What does that look like?
Oh, do you need some help? Don't worry, I'll help you.
Hey, what is going on guys? Welcome to my first ever quest tutorial video.
And what's going to happen here is we're going to teach you how to do a quest.
The most important thing in this is you want to get the quest, which is really easy.
There's a quest giver around the world. So after you get the quest, you do the quest,
and then you complete the quest. And that's really all there is to it.
Quest.
The thing in this game is really, really fun and interesting.
Quest, quest, quest, quest, get the quest.
What a beautiful land this is, wouldn't you say?
The sights, the sounds, the smells.
Oldham is full of treasures, my friend.
Treasure. I like that.
Yeah, some are easy for even simple men to discern, while others require wisdom to see.
Ah, what the hell am I doing? I can see that, oh, why am I doing this?
I knew that for that last one, you were literally just going to do what you did and just shout.
Well, no, because on my screen, I'm sitting next to this guy,
and he's telling me his life story, and I just don't care.
Well, not that I don't care, my character doesn't care.
At least he would. He's sitting here like stone.
Dude, when you see this video, look at my guy's hands.
He is like, he's sitting there like he's holding on.
Dude, it looks ridiculous.
My guy's hands.
Oh, he's like, it looks like he's got broken arms and he's in casts.
What?
This is a bumpy ride, by the way.
Who's manning this son of a bitch?
Okay, so they're weakened.
They're weak.
Oh, man.
And it only took like an hour and 10 minutes.
All right, you better queue up.
Hit that button.
Oh, you son of a bitch.
This guy better queue up or I'm going to be pissed.
It's probably the same guy.
Oh, thank God.
I was about to freak out.
Hey, look at that.
Where the hell are we?
Grim Batol.
Oh, our healer lagged out.
Oh, joy.
Look at this face of disappointment.
He is disappointed right now.
When the hell did I make my guy look this ugly?
He looks like Santa Claus Hulk Hogan right now.
When the hell did I do this?
Hello.
Hey, sorry I can't get in.
How?
He says I need to do the stupid quest before I'm allowed in.
What?
You can run?
Really?
Yeah.
Jesus.
Okay.
But you could get in this one without the quest.
Yeah.
Oh, and here we go.
This is the journey.
This is what it all comes down to.
That guy is huge, man.
Can I just...
I'm going to start attacking this guy.
Oh, that guy died.
I killed one of those marines.
I have to fight this guy?
How the hell am I going to fight this guy by myself?
I think those marines helped me.
Let's hope so.
Come on, you.
Don't worry.
I got my dogs.
Whoa, lasers everywhere.
Get him.
Kill this son of a bitch.
Kill him.
Everything you got.
Heroism.
Super bomb move.
Oh, man.
Intense battle sequence.
Get behind the colossus.
All right.
He did like a super smash.
This guy is toast.
Are you kidding me?
He is really, really cool looking, though.
I will say this is one of the coolest things
I've seen so far in the zone.
Ow.
Bitch.
Oh, and that's it.
See you.
See you later, dude.
Why is he not dying?
Oh.
He needs like two more DPS done.
I did it.
Wait, these guys are attacking me now.
Oh, no, they're not.
I'm wrong.
No, I can't use any of it.
I'm just going to take away.
What's the most expensive thing?
This.
Why?
Not very much.
Oh, oh, I did it.
I did all the quests.
I am the quest master.
I am the master of the quests.
And you cannot defeat me.