Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some trouble in Terrorist Town, the mod for Garry's Mod and Counter-Strike Source.
Just wanted to briefly introduce this before the live stuff kicks in, because it can be very confusing if you're just watching this and have no idea what's going on.
So I will try to clarify this a little bit before we get started.
So essentially, it's kind of in the same category as Jailbreak, where it's just this enormous social experiment.
And I love stuff like this. It's one of the reasons I love Jailbreak so much.
And you're gonna see a lot more Jailbreak. You'll probably see a lot of this as well, this TTT. I think that's what people call it.
But so this is how it breaks down, right? You got three different people, three different types of people in this game.
You have innocents, traitors, and detectives.
So what you do, the whole point of the game, is to just stay alive.
If you're an innocent like I am in this game, the whole goal is to just not die and to try and get rid of all the traitors.
The traitors, their goal is to try and kill everybody without being seen and without being found out.
And the detectives, they are the exact same things as innocents, except they have a couple of things at their arsenal to try and track down the traitors.
They have something, they have a DNA scanner and stuff like that.
So it's cool to be either one of these things, because it really is just a giant show.
It's just a giant acting lesson. If you're a traitor, or even if you're an innocent, you have to try to find ways to convince your fellow man to not kill you.
So again, you have to have Counter-Strike Source and Garry's Mod to be able to play this game.
If you have these two, go check it out. And here comes a live session right here of just absolute nonsense.
So I'll see you guys all next time. Enjoy the live commentary and take care, everybody.
I'm with ass face and abusive.
Okay, who's on the other side of that door?
Dude, you can trust me, you can trust me.
It's one of the detectives.
Who just shot the detective?
I don't know.
This is the scariest thing ever.
Get him, get him, kill him.
Kill Broby.
There's a chair out of the way.
Seriously, there's a chair out of the way.
Don't shoot, don't shoot, don't shoot.
Get the chair out of the way.
Broby killed the detective.
Cover me, I'm going to do some DNA scanning.
Was Broby a terrorist?
Yeah, Broby was a traitor, and she killed Rainbow Kitten, who was a detective.
Me and Jeremiah opened the door.
That's a DNA scanner.
I have DNA on you, too, if you did anything here.
Yeah, I killed the detective.
No, I mean the traitor.
I killed the detective.
No, I didn't do that.
I'm with abusive.
This Renegade, why is he badly wounded?
I'm with abusive in German.
They're locking me in.
I picked up a DNA scanner.
Renegade, Renegade, why are you badly wounded?
Where have you been?
Alright.
Alright, Jerma, try to pick up this AWP right here.
Drop your primary.
This doesn't work, this doesn't work.
Traders don't get it.
Really?
Yeah, this doesn't work.
Are you sure this doesn't work?
What the hell is going on?
Oh my god, that's morbid.
I think there's someone missing.
Renne, why are you hurt?
I already asked him.
What?
I'm alone with Renegade.
You're not alone with anyone.
We're all here together.
I'm downstairs with Renegade.
We're in the bank.
He's trying to get away from me.
He's got his pistol out.
Jerma, you're alone with abusive now.
I'm alone with abusive right now.
We're being followed by abusive.
The man he's carrying.
I'm so fucked.
There has to be a traitor here.
I'm going to say that.
I think it's Jerma and it's not me.
Me too.
Nope, he's innocent.
Damn it.
Wait a minute.
Alright, well.
What the fuck?
Where are you guys?
He was carrying around that body like a real creep.
Come on.
Like it was a prize.
I do not think that Jerma is the terrorist.
He wouldn't have reacted that way to a detective dying.
Believe it's stealth.
No, that's only when you're dead.
You can only see that when you're dead.
It's a real case of who done it.
Second floor.
You guys go.
Body here.
Is there anybody in here?
No.
They're not here.
We have to go downstairs in the elevator.
Let's get in the elevator.
We're going into the elevator.
I don't know where we're at right now.
You want us to get in the elevator so bad.
Good place to drop some C4.
Come with us.
I would instant die if I did that.
I wouldn't even be able to arm the C4 before you guys kill me.
What the hell is this?
Let's get in the very confined elevator.
I believe that the map is bigger than we think.
If I die, she's dead.
Don't leave yet Renegade.
Renegade, don't you dare press that button.
I'm shooting you.
We're going to wait for the others.
No, I lost you guys.
I don't know where you guys went.
We went back downstairs.
Don't you dare press that button Renegade.
Hulster your guns.
Hulster a gun.
We're all dead if we do that.
I did it.
It's alright.
Crowbar doesn't do any damage anyways.
What if this door opens
and people have guns in the other side?
What was that?
It was him.
It was Renegade.
Renegade.
The second the elevator doors opened
he shot Tio in the face and just ran.