Oh, what the heck? What the fuck? A raid. Raid coming in. I just turned the stream on a raid coming in.
What? No way. Who's raiding me right now? I'm getting a raid. Oh my god. What the heck? Raid.
Do it. Where is it? Oh, what the fuck? Raid. They're not gonna do it? Oh, what the heck?
Are you kidding me? A navy bog with a raid. No way. They all left.
They didn't. I caught that in pre-stream. You don't think I... I can see what you're doing.
Sing the raid song. No, I need a new raid song. I didn't even tweet the stream out. Just wait a
minute. Thanks to the raid though of everybody that like planned to do that. Only 157 of you
went over there. It's like 60,000 people in pre-stream chat. What the hell? Show video. I
don't understand what's going on here, by the way. Let me be really, really clear. I made a
Thanksgiving... Happy Thanksgiving video last night and people all lost their minds. I have no idea
what's going on. I just said, hey, Happy Thanksgiving. I just... I don't... I wanted to do more tweets. I
wanted to get more stuff out there. They'll say tweet more. Give us more updates and shit. So
I don't know people... That tweet has been seen like three million times. I don't understand why.
I don't get... I just like... That was for you guys. Whatever. It's because of what? Vinny saw it,
by the way. Yeah, I know. I also heard that there was a little bit of debate of how much that was
going to shave off the debt. I wasn't even doing that to shave debt off. I did it because I felt
like doing it. None. None. I was going to play Sly Cooper today, but that didn't end up happening.
I bought it for the PS3 and I noticed that I started downloading Sly Cooper and the Thievius
Raccoonius, whatever the name of the... I don't know, whatever it is. So I leave the room. I come
back after like 15, 20 minutes and my room just smells like burning plastic. Just burnt plastic.
It was disgusting. And I remember talking about this before. I brought this up. I was like,
why does it smell like burning plastic? Remember that on Saw 2, right? This is not the first time
this has happened, but it was way worse this time. It was gas. Well, it was bad. It wasn't very good.
So I'm like, I don't want to smell this all day. No, we're not doing that. So I was like,
maybe I'll do an emulator or something. And I tried it. I couldn't get the emulator to do what
I wanted. Didn't like the way it looked. So Sly Cooper's going back in the bag for like another
week. I don't know. I'm sorry. I know so many people wanted that and they were like, oh,
I can't wait for Sly Cooper, dude. Sorry, my PlayStation 3 was burning. So we're going to
pivot. We're going to play Cooking Simulator today. Specifically the pizza update. I made sure to eat
a lot of food before this stream. Do it on PS Now. No, PS Now is no. PS Now, remember I tried to do
Red Dead on PS Now? It's not, I don't want to stream through PS Now. It kind of looks like
not very good because it already gets compressed and then I compress it again.
There's a little bit of input lag too on PS Now, which I don't, I'm not going to play a platformer
with like a quarter second input delay. We're going to see Bugleberry today. Why would Bugleberry be
here today? Stop streaming please in 720p. Your streams look so low quality. I know. Wait, I'm
going to do 900p. But I need a 3080. I need a i7-99000K, whatever it is, or an i9. Oh no,
we're going AMD. I forgot. I'm going to get a Risen like Threadripper 64 core monster PC.
He's going to AMD Omegalel. Yeah, AMD has surpassed Intel in technology from what I've been told.
I've been told that AMD is rocking it right now. How true is that? I don't know.
Get away from me. Okay, I don't know why somebody, did somebody just say just watch the AMD
CPU video on YouTube? Like this is the ending of a video game? Did I read that correctly?
Ha, dude. Oh yeah, dude. Just watch the AMD CPU on YouTube. Oh, okay. I guess that is the same.
All right, it's pizza time. I had to mute this because this has just been going on.
I can't turn this off. I have, my desktop audio has been at zero for the last 10 straight minutes.
Yeah, it's pizza time. We're going to talk, we're going to talk a lot about pizza today.
My favorite pizza, your favorite pizza. What is my favorite pizza? You guys already know that.
Do you know what it is? Do you know? I hope you do. It is a thin crust pepperoni pizza
with no bullshit. That's it. Thin crust, crispy, crunchy, delicious. That's based.
That's boring. I don't like a bunch of stuff on my pizza because it weighs the pizza down.
And then, all right, hold on. I got to turn this down. Like,
dude, I can take my headphones out. So I don't like when toppings weigh pizza down. I don't.
I only like one or two toppings per pizza and they got to be light. All right, bring it back.
It's boring. No, why is it boring? It's like, I want sausage, eggs, peppers, onions. No, I want
a croissant, eggs, and cheese on my pizza. I want a croissant with pizza. Like, what are you talking
about, dude? Don't order that. What are you doing? No, I like simple pizzas. Peppers and onions.
Sounds good. Pepperoni. Sounds good. Garlic and onion. You got me. I'm on board.
I almost just wrote what I said the word.
No, sorry. We need to do a pizza tier list today. I don't know, in half an hour.
All right, let's go. Pizza Simulator. I will try pineapple on pizza the correct way. I've been
told I've been eating it wrong and I'm willing to go for it. I'm willing to try it. New order.
Margarita. Press T. Hello and welcome to Papa Pepe's Pizzeria. I see great promise in you.
So much so that I'd like to share some of my secrets. And if you prove yourself, I may even
let you run this pizzeria. Your training begins. Imagine going to work for Coca-Cola and Mr.
Coca-Cola walks up to you, the CEO. Oh, you're the new hire. Yeah, that's a good handshake.
The secret is fucking, is castor oil. What? You're going to do really good here, kid.
Okay, let's go. I'm sure you already know this, but let's cover some basics. I'll show you how
to assemble a pizza from already. All right, let me see if I know how to do this. Bake it in
the oven and finally serve it. Why it's so bright in here. Is my, what? Yes, and put on your company
pizza headphones while you're working. Name and address. Why? What do you want to name it a dress
for? What the hell is this here for? What? Okay. 60 FOV. Yeah, right. Okay. That, why does this feel
way worse now? Name and address. Why does it want your address? That's fucked up. Okay. Here we go.
Let's begin with the base for our pizza. They can't be pizza without it. To make a base,
you'll have to roll out the pizza dough, get some dough and place it on the bake board.
Dough. Okay. All right. Place the Neapolitan-style dough on the bake board.
We're going to roll this out. Okay. Enter the creation view by pressing on the lump of dough.
Okay. This is where you can roll out the dough and decorate it with ingredients.
You can have up to three pizza bases at the same time on the bake board. Use A and D to switch
between lumps of dough or pizza bases. So you use to roll the dough. That looks pretty good. Oh,
no. What? I don't want the edges. Okay. W to switch to the GN container view shelf.
You'll find some ingredients and some sauce that I prepared for you. In the future,
you'll have to prepare the ingredients yourself. Okay. So this is the shelf where you keep all the
pizza ingredients. No edges. I like a thin crust. I don't like the big, I like a thin crust. This is
too big and bulky. Make a stuff crust. If you can make a stuff crust, I'll do it. Okay. A and D to
switch between ingredients. Right. Okay. Remember, you can only use the ingredients that have been
stored in a GN container beforehand and slot it into the shelf. You use to choose the sauce.
Nice. Oh, yes. This looks small. Now click on the pizza base to pour the sauce on it, then move
while holding to spread the sauce around the surface. I know I've, I've seen the pizza hut
training video from 1985. I know how to do this. Oops. Didn't do anything. Oh, there we go. Okay.
All right. All right. All right. You stop at the edges. You don't go any further. But wait,
I need to get a little bit on that crust. He did it too much. It looks like a coiled up turd.
Okay. Now to add some cheese.
Somebody said, stop dragging the ladle. I'm all right. Everybody relax. Okay. That's enough. Now
time to add some cheese. It has to be placed evenly so we can cover the whole surface of our
pizza when it melts. Remember that you can use Q and D to rotate the cheese slices. Really?
Is this cheese? Okay. We can rotate and this is going to, I don't, I actually prefer when
it's shredded. Okay. That, that's it. Finish. Add some basil leaves. Oh, okay. Here's the herbs.
All right. Now just put it on there. Used to place basil leaves on the pizza on the template. Okay.
All right. Now we have to bake it. Our pizza is ready to put in the oven. However, the oven
needs to be prepared to fire up the oven and place a log, a log inside the firebox. How do I get out
of here? Wait, we have to actually feed the fire? All right. Oven. Okay. Before we can start baking,
the oven needs to reach the optimal temperature. You can check the temperatures in the thermometer
on the left side of the oven. As time progresses, the oven will slowly run out of fuel. Make sure
to add logs from time to time to keep the fire going. Get it in there. All right. Get it in the
green. How much wood does it take? A wood-fired pizza? Yeah, that's the best. Okay. Now let's
shove the pizza into the oven, but don't try to do it with your bare hands. Oh, okay. I need to pick
up the pizza peel. No, that's not a pizza peel. Get rid of that. Whatever. Okay. Where's the pizza
peel? Oh, that thing. Precise handling of tools in the kitchen is crucial. Holding out shift will
open up new ways to manipulate whatever you are currently holding in your hand. All right. Let's
get it. All right. I got it. And we put it inside of here. Slide it in. All right. Then we just let
it sit in here, right? Pay attention. If it's too low, add logs. If it's too high, close the chamber.
All right. Oh, I need to add logs. Logs. What if I know if it's done? I never understood this shit
because you can't even see in there. You know what I mean? I can't see in there. There needs
to be a camera pointing down inside of these ovens. Okay. It's hot. Nice and hot, hot, hot, hot.
Okay. Give me the tool. And it's ready. Get it. Take out the pizza. Oh, that looks pretty good.
Doesn't it? That looks pretty good. I'm so glad I ate before this stream. Boring. It's a tutorial
pizza. Serve it through the window. Serve it through the window. If you just like freeze
out at somebody. All right. Pick it up. Oh, wait. All right. Here you go. Come get it. I can't fit
it out there. This plate is so big. This is a mess up. This is a small pizza on an extra large
pizza tray. What the fuck is going on? Can I get out? Can I get out the window? Okay. It's ready.
I need to make another pizza. Serve it through the serving window. That's not the serving window.
This is just a regular... Why can I open this? I didn't soft lock it, did I? No. We're going to
make another pizza. Fuck. I think I did soft lock it. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I can't get up there. Shit. No, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait. There's dough in here. There's dough.
This is the dough machine. Insert container. Wait. Where's the dough? Dough. Fuck. I actually have
to start the whole thing over. I have to make the dough from scratch, but I don't know how to do
that yet. They didn't tell me how to do that. Okay. What if I just put like a... Okay. Hold on.
Can I just put the tomato on here? Shit. I have to... Pepe D? All right. We're good. Oh, come on.
Yes. All right. We're fine. We're fine. Everything's fine. Everything's fine. All right. Get it in there.
What is Pepe D? All right. Let's get some wood in there. No, don't do this already. What did I just
do? All right. That's fine. I have to reinstall... Oh. All right. Let's get it. Get that pizza out of
there. Eventually, I'm going to have wicked cool pizzas. Just you wait. Okay. Now, this time,
I'm not going to mess this up. Here we go. Too early. Just a little too early. I kind of like
underdone sometimes. Be done? That was done, please. That shit was done. I don't like it raw.
Sometimes it can be nice. All right. On to the serving tray. Margarita pizza. All right. Nice.
Ingredients. Basil leaf. Triple check mark. Okay. Cool. You've proved that you can prepare a proper
Italian pizza. Now, it's time to prepare your pizzeria for tomorrow. Let me show you how to
prepare the dough, sauce, and other ingredients. Okay. You don't have to rush. Take your time. The
preparation phase has no time limit. You decide when to finish and when to start a new day.
I like that feature. Let's start with preparing some Neapolitan-style dough.
The first step is to familiarize yourself with the recipe. Launch the pizza pro app. I'm sorry. I did
the mid-sentence. That was weird. Launch the pizza pro app and find the recipe that we need.
Pizza pro app? What button is that on the keyboard? What button is that on the keyboard? Tab?
Okay. Pizza pro app. So now we need to open pizza pro. Select the recipe. All right. Here you find
a list of necessary ingredients and their quantities needed for the recipe. Clicking on the pin button
will allow you to view the recipe without well working on it. Yeah. Let's go back for a moment
to the quest villa app. Bring up the smartphone's main screen once more. Click on the app icon.
Don't worry. The recipe is going to stay pinned. Okay. The quest villa. This villa is an application
dedicated to the elite world-class pizzalios. Is that a Warcraft zone? No contract today!
Here you'll find some challenges. It's a battle pass. It really is a battle pass. It was a bad
joke. Oh, I'm not trying to make a good joke. I was just trying to make a wow reference because
I get to. Jerma bought Shadowlands. Time that guy up. I don't want to hear him. Here you'll find some
challenges and tasks that allow you to improve your skills and gain new abilities. Battle pass.
Completing these quests will grant you fame, respect, and skill certifications.
I need to learn how to do dough first. We're not getting involved in this. Hide him, hide him,
hide him. No, no, no, no, no, no. I will grant you the title of novice pizzalio. How do you even say
that word? Let you run the pizzeria by yourself. Additionally, by completing tasks from the app,
you'll unlock new recipes and ingredients. So it's well worth the effort. Okay. At the bottom
of the screen, you'll see a key that describes the elements of the app. After you familiarize
with the app, press tab to put the smartphone down. Okay. Quest progression. I just want to
make a pizza. Okay. Necessary ingredients and tools. So I need flour, water, sugar, salt, oil,
garlic, butter, and baking soda. I don't know. Whatever it is. Before you turn on the machine,
you must add the ingredients to the machine's bowl. Let's start with flour. You'll need it.
You'll find it on the shelf behind you. One bag of flour should be enough. Try not to go bankrupt.
Everything in the kitchen costs money. Plates, products, especially repairs. Don't take more
than you need and keep an eye on your balance. You're out of business if you run out of money.
All right. Let's dump it in there. How much do we need? 3.5 kilograms. All right. Add to the bowl.
Holy shit. How much did I just put in? I thought I put in a lot more than I needed to. All right.
Easy, easy, easy. Easy. Come on. Do it. 3.5. Yes. Okay. Put this away. Now, flour is very important.
It's not the only one. You'll find the rest in the box. Buy them and add proper amounts of each.
In the box? You'll find the rest in the box. What box? Oh, okay. Yeast. Do I need liquid? I need
water? Okay. How much water should I buy? A lot. Okay. I need water, salt. Water, salt, and yeast.
Buy it. Okay. Use piss. We're not even 10 minutes into the game. Just hold that thought.
What was it? Water, yeast, and what? What was it? Water, yeast, and what? Salt. Okay. So now we have
to put in... I can't see what the... I want to see the recipe. Okay. Salt. It's 2.4 liquid milliliters
of water. That's all that's in here? Why is this... That's only one liter of water? Oh, god damn it.
Come on. How many... Why don't I have a bigger... Use the sink? I could... Yeah, but that's low quality.
I need to use... I'm not gonna use tap water. I'm using bottled water. That's the secret recipe.
You're in Europe though. Oh, oh, okay. Yeah, yeah. The water's clean here. Is there water in this? No.
How am I not even... I don't even have a bottle I can put this in. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I already paid for this. Whatever. 2.4. Good. It's okay. All right. Now we need salt. How much salt
do we need? I don't... We need 125 grams of salt. When preparing sauces and doughs, we often use a
lot of spices. That's why our shakers are equipped with double action covers. You can pour one gram
or 10 grams of spice with a single shake. All right. So I want... I want 10 grams. 125 grams.
Bingo. Yeast. Yeah, it's like a cube. Okay. This is 10 grams. Just put it in. Now mix it up. Oh,
this is my favorite part. This is my favorite part. All right. Now ready. Be careful now. Do not press
the red button. It will clear the bowl of its stored ingredients. Use it only if you make a
mistake. When preparing the dough from the recipe, or you've accidentally dropped something in the
bowl and can't remove it. No, chat. Chat, I'm not gonna press the button. I'm not gonna press the
big red button. No, chat, I'm not gonna do it. Press the green button. Nice. Okay. Let's discuss
sauces. Sauce recipes are located in the same app as the dough recipes. Just navigate to the sauces
tab and we'll make classic marinara. Okay. Sauces. Marinara. What was that?
Did we just throw a rock at the restaurant? Let's pin this. Okay. Quest tab. Okay. Okay.
Okay. What do we have here? We need some fresh vegetables. Time for a trip to the pantry.
Gas. Do not mix gas in the mixer. Not now. Oh, look at these little... These little poops.
These little bread poops. Okay. Hold on. Pick up the basket. Gather 16 tomatoes. That's a lot.
Four garlic and then go back upstairs. Okay. 16 tomatoes. Okay. Holy shit. It's a 3D tomato.
Now how do we do this? No, no, no. Easy, easy. All right. Now what? Before you place the basket's
contents into the cooking processor, make sure you have the right ingredients in the correct amounts.
After you fill the cooking processor, you will not be able to remove anything from it.
It's the cooking processor. Okay. Dump it in there. I need olive oil. Where do I get olive oil?
Just fill it up from the sink. No, it has to be oil. Okay. How about 200 milliliters of olive oil?
Where did the ingredients go? Oh, fuck. That comes out fast. It's okay. It's gonna be a little oily.
Salt. Okay. Salt, oregano, basil, and garlic. Salt, oregano, basil, and garlic.
Put down the basket. Look at it. You should see a list of contents. If you notice something that
shouldn't be there, take it out. Okay. Here's basil. We still need olive oil, herbs, and spices.
You'll find herbs in the herbarium. Since we're preparing almost two liters of sauce,
we'll need a lot of sprig. Okay. So we need how many sprigs of basil? 30 grams. All right. Put it
in there. Salt. Where's my salt shaker? I just had it. Right here. 35 grams. Open up. One, two,
three. One, two, three, four, five. Okay. Fried oregano. I don't even have any oregano. He didn't
give it to me. Can't put the sponge in there? Come on. Where's the oregano? Get it from the sink.
The herbarium. This is the herbarium. I only have basil. I have to buy it? Where is it? Basil,
oregano. Okay. There it is. All right. Let's go. 25 grams. One, two, one, two, three, four, five.
All right. Let's blend it up. I can't wait to make my secret fucking sauce because I have no idea.
We need to insert a GN container. Except for the dough mixer, all machines require an empty
GN container to be inserted where they can be activated. Take one of the empty GN containers
that you find lying around the kitchen and insert it into the cooking process's dump chamber.
Okay. Turn it on. That sounded like it hung up a little. Okay. We don't need any more recipes.
Unpin them. Okay. It's going to take some time. Don't stand idly by here. Pick up the basket
and let's go back to the pantry. Okay. Where's the green line leading me to over here? All right.
I need olives, corn, salami, white onion, mozzarella. Is that good? Okay. Mozzarella,
white onion, salami, sweet corn, olives. Where's the sweet corn? Where's the sweet corn?
Where's the sweet corn? I thought that was a big thing with cheese.
Garlic? Where's the sweet corn? I don't see this anywhere. Do I just keep glazing over it?
Corn? Onion? It's right there. Where is it? You just did it again. It's on the shelf?
Oh, I'm looking for ears of corn. I'm not looking for canned corn. I'm looking for ears of corn.
He's throwing. No. No. Stand back up. Okay. The sauce should be ready.
Let's see what it looks like. Oh, it looks like raw meatloaf. What do I want to do over here?
Wait, wait, wait, wait. This is... Oh, this is from the other side. That's how they do this? Wow. I
didn't know that. Okay. Pick up the salami. Just put the salami over there. Put the salami into the
cutter. Cool. All right. Turn on the salami cutter. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. Use this one.
God, I wish that was me. The salami... You want your salami to be cut in the salami cutter?
What the fuck are you talking about? God, I wish that was me. Somebody...
Somebody... No. You know what? Time that guy out. Okay. Into the cheese grater.
Into the salami cutter. What the fuck? All right. Turn it on. Turn it on. Turn it on. Turn it on.
We're going to have our grated cheese. Nice. Nice mealworms. Pick up an onion. One onion.
Drop it up. Oh, shit. I need... I'm going to... I'm in the onions. Look at the basket. Shit. Wait,
wait, wait. I need... Is this a jar of pickles? I... Wait, wait, wait. I lost. I lost the...
Game thinks I did this already, but I hit the red button. All right. Here's another trick. Put an
ingredient into the automatic cutter. All ingredients of the same type in your basket will also get
thrown into the machine. Whatever. Okay. All right. Wait, wait, wait. I need to... Okay. Pick up the
basket with the ingredients. While holding the basket, use on the automatic cutter. Oh. Save a
lot of time and trouble with cutting large quantities. I'll turn it on. Wait, I need to...
I'm going to have to buy like a thousand of these. Wait, pick this back. I can't get rid of the
onions? Pick up a can of sweet corn. No, I have to get rid of these. How do I get rid of this?
Okay. There we go. Pick up sweet corn. While holding the can, use it on the container.
Okay. Cool. Insert the GN container with sweet corn into the GN container shelf.
Okay. Hover over the jar of black olives. Try not to throw up while you do that. Okay. From left to
right, the icon... Wait. Put this... Okay. From left to right, the icon represents dough mixer,
cooking processor, electric grater, automatic cutter, and GN container. The last icon means
that the ingredient can be stored directly into a GN container without the need for any further
processing. Insert a GN container with 500 grams of black olives. Cut into the GN container shelf.
Shit. Okay. Now we need a GN container. Chop them up. Put it into the GN container shelf.
Very cool. Pick up a dough tray with click. All right. Follow the green line. All right.
Now we can prepare our dough for the day. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't waste time.
Pull the GN container shelf back into the yellow room. Hey, look at that. That's all my stuff.
What are the marked area? Oh, that's it. All right. Let's finish this up.
That's not what I wanted to do. I was trying to drink it. Are you throwing glass at people?
There's nobody out here. There's no trash can. Yes, there is. Well, whatever. I'm prepared.
All right. How do we do it? Click on the clock. What time is it? I don't know.
Call an ambulance. I'm bleeding. That was a pretty good first day of preparing our pizza show.
All right. Here we go. Time to make pizzas. Complete the tasks that I've prepared for
you today and I'll grant you a novice pizzioleia certificate along with this pizzeria. Let's start.
Okay. Quest. Finish all the quests to unlock quantity, quality, and speed specializations
in their respective challenges. You must fulfill an order. Accept a new order, prepare the pizza
according to the client's expectations, and serve it. That's all there is to do it. Don't worry.
I'll give you a few tips if you have any problems. Okay. Notice you're only 50 EXP away from the next
level. Completing this quest will result in leveling up. Hover over the basket to check
out the rewards that await you for achieving the next level. Put down the smartphone. Stop
using your phone. Put it down. In life. Don't lift it up at a restaurant. Don't lift it up
when you're just sitting around. Way less screen time. I have a screen time thing now on my app
and it's like, holy shit, I look at this phone like for three hours a day. That's way too much.
Put it down. I'm going to try to cut back. That's a minus two. That's not a joke. That is a public
service announcement to put your phone down. Each star can be bronze, silver, or gold quality,
depending on how well you prepare the pizza. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay. The timer starts the moment you
accept the order. If you manage to complete it within 30 minutes, you'll earn a bronze star,
or else it's free. 10 minutes? That feels like I can do that pretty easily. While you're still
learning, do not worry about the time. All right. Well, whatever. Just give me a fucking order.
What is it? Orders can be accepted for only half an hour since the new day starts, but the guests
won't leave until they receive their pizzas, even if that means waiting. So wait, if you order a
pizza from this window at like 11 o'clock in the morning or 12 o'clock in the afternoon,
and you don't get it till like 10 o'clock at night, I feel like you'd complain about that.
That's not okay. This pizzeria is really busy, so don't worry about running out of orders.
It's never happened. Okay. Okay. Let's go. New order. A pugilis. Your first order. Launch the
Bellapizza app and check it out. Pugilis. The timer's already running. Okay. A pugilis is a
medium pizza. It's a Neapolitan style. Hold on. I gotta read this. How much of those the client
wants? Sometimes some of those categories will be blank. That means that a customer does not want
cheese on their pizza if it's blank. All right. Let's go. The arrow buttons next to the dough
and sauce type will switch your view to their recipes. Unfortunately, we prepared everything
we needed yesterday, so we don't need recipes. Okay. I already made marinara. I already have
Neapolitan style dough. That's a lot to remember, but you can pin the order. Yeah. Okay. Will you
fuck off, Chef Boyardee? I'm busy. We start with the dough, and as you might have noticed,
the order specifies a pizza size. That was rude. You won't leave me alone. I'm trying to run a
pizza place. You're rude to tutorial guy. He's helping. I just want to make my pizzas. You need
him. I don't need him. Toxic streamer. I'm not toxic. I'm not. No. Turn that toxicity down.
He invented the pizza. I got a timer running. I got a timer, and I got to go. Okay. Where's my
dough? Where's my dough? Where's my dough? Where's my dough? I've over a large lump of dough. Where's
my... Okay. Press Q while hovering. Press Q. What? No, this is large. Oh, shit. This is too big.
Give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me,
give me, give me. Okay. Q, you can split it. The order requires you to make a medium-sized pizza.
Combining two small lumps will give you a medium dough lump. Okay. Let's go. Rolling into a medium
size pan pizza. Okay. Needs well-baked to achieve a gold star. All right. Customers usually do not
like dry, sauceless pizza. Why would I serve sauceless dry pizza? Those are crackers. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay. Good. Cool. Sauce. Marinara. How much marinara do you
want? Well, this is how much you're getting. Really bad place for a save point. Okay. Good,
good, good, good, good, good. All right. That looks good. The cheese rating consists of three
factors. Saltiness, creaminess, and suppleness. Don't worry. If you lose a little too much cheese,
the customers will be happy either way. Whatever. As long as they don't go bankrupt. Sure. When you
shove the pizza in the oven, the cheese will begin to melt. Customers expect that the whole surface
of the pizza will be covered by melted cheese. Okay. What kind of cheese do you want? All right.
Mozzarella. You want cut mozzarella? How much mozzarella do you want? 100 grams? How many do
I have? What do I have my hand right now? 20. There. Now you're gonna be really happy when you
eat this pizza. Okay. This is just how they serve food at like the Disney resorts.
Spread out evenly on the pizza. Maintain the proper quantity of each ingredient. You'll find
this information in the details. The final score is an average is value based on the quantity and
the distribution of each ingredient. The better you fail, the better the star you'll get. Let's
start with the onion slices. Some ingredients are too small or used in such large quantities that
the exact placement doesn't matter. Instead, we just scatter handfuls onto the pizza. Okay.
Onions. What the fuck? Pop the pizza with 32 grams of white onions?
That doesn't look good. All right. That's 32. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good.
Decorate the pizza with with some olives. Olives. Is it going on the pizza? Oh shit. Okay. Gross.
Gross. Gross. They look like Oreos. Now we have to bake it. All that's left. Raw pizza with solid
chunks of cheese will be rated poorly, but burned pizza won't steal any hearts either. It's best to
prepare a plate for the pizza. Take on from the stack. The pizza size is medium, so we need a
medium plate. Okay. What? This is going to be good. This is going to be real. It's going to be good.
Oh, fire it up. I didn't fire it up. More. More. More. More. More. More. More. More. More. More.
All right. I don't want it to be too hot. Do the stream in Italian. I don't. I can't speak
Italian. Why do you think I can speak Italian? I can't. I don't know. I don't know any Italian.
Oh my God. I can't wait. Oh, it's going to be so scrumptious. You can't speak Italian. Why not?
Because I don't know. I didn't learn Italian. I've always wanted to go to Ili. Okay. It's not. Get
it. Get it. Get it. Get it. Get it. It's going to burn. Get it. Ah, looks pretty awful. Bravo.
Let's see what the customer has to say. What do you think? Here you go. Eat up. I did it in seven
minutes. Oh, I can unlock prosciutto. Mm. Mushrooms. Chicken breast. And sausage. Allows you to
replace a quest with a new random one up to three times. Uh, yeah. Bravo. Can I not choose a new
perk? Let's see what your customer is. All right. How do I get out of here? What the hell is going
on? All right. I previously mentioned you will choose a perk every third level. Okay. Unlock perks
can be activated and deactivated at the perk app. Okay. Take a look at the wall next to the serving
window. This is a certificate proving that I granted you the rank of a novice pizzialio.
Magnificent, isn't it? I made it myself. Oh, okay. Thanks. Thank you. All right. New things in the
quest app. Now, instead of just one quest, you'll have three active quests, each one of them belonging
to a different specialization. Um, okay. You got a participation award. It's kind of- whatever.
The speed specialization focuses on, you guessed it, performing various tasks very- why is there a
talent tree in this game? We're making pizzas. There's, like, skill points? All right. There's
speed. There's quantity. There's quality. Okay. There's quality. You can- you can- you can unlock
different skill points. Complete all three master tier challenges to become a pizziollo supreme.
I never did it myself. All right. We finally made it out of the tutorial. Let's go. What do you got?
Any orders? No orders. How do I get an order? Waiting. Didn't you say this place was busy?
I ordered two hours ago. Oh, wait. I want a marinara pizza. I want a marinara pizza.
Medium dough. Marinara. Garlic and basil. You got it. Garlic and basil. Medium. This is going to be
quick as hell. Okay. Marinara. Why is it green? Okay. Marinara. And- oh, give me that. Garlic.
Do I have any garlic? Oh, should I have sweet corn? No, I don't have any garlic. Oh, no. I didn't
prepare. I didn't prepare. I didn't prepare. Where's the garlic? I need garlic. Oh, shit.
Hurry up. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Garlic. Give me one. Give me. Okay. How much does he want?
Dude, how much garlic do you want on this pizza? I gotta cut it up too. Shit. Oh, no. I need a
basket. This dude wants like 10 cloves of garlic on his pizza. Give me the basket. All right. I
got- I got a lot. I got enough. Ow. All right. Chop it up. Put it into the cutting machine.
Way too much. No, no. I'm gonna put it in a- in a GN tray. I got this. Oh, I got it. I got it. I got
it. I got it. I got it. Where's the GN tray? I need it. Oh. There's like none in here.
Okay. Let's go, go, go. Where's the basil leaf? Basil leaf. 30 grams. Give me one.
Here we go. Garlic. He wants 24 grams of cut garlic. 32. All right. All right. We're good.
We're good. And then he wants basil leaf? Do I have to cut the basil leaf? How do I put this on
here? I have to cut it? How do I cut the basil? Don't cut it. Well, I can't put- I won't let me
put it on the pizza. Basil leaf. Hold on. Okay. Basil leaf. With a knife. I don't- I don't think
I can do that. With a knife. That wasn't in the tutorial. Grandpa didn't tell me how to do that.
Where do I- Where do I get a knife? It's on there. All right. Does he want cheese on this?
No, he didn't even want cheese. Get it- Okay. Go, go, go, go, go. Give me this fucking thing.
All right. We're- Herb selection? Oh, Jesus. Get it in. All right. I can take another order.
How are we doing on heat? Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait. Just leave everything in there until I'm
ready to heat everything up. Where's the garlic? I covered- I smutted it in garlic.
There's so much garlic on that pizza. You'll throw up if you eat it. All right. What we got?
That one's going in there. That one's good. Next up, we got a salami pizza. Small salami- All right.
Get away from me. A small salami pizza with just mozzarella, salami, and basil. I got it.
Small. I want a small. How do I get- How do I make this a small? Oh, shit. I'm losing heat. Hold on.
The pizza's not burning. It's fine. I thought there were bugs on it. All right. Here you go.
That's not what I wanted to do. Oh, Jesus. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I gotta put it on a plate.
Just pick it up with my hands. I don't even care. You fucking stupid ass. Oh, my God, dude. Stop.
Stop, stop. There's no counter space. Oh, what the fuck, man? Come on.
All right. We're good. We're good. We're good. Here. Serve it. Ding. That is the marinara pizza.
How'd you like it? All right. I gotta get to work on this. I need a small.
I unlocked Alfredo sauce. Oh, shit. Oh, gotta get the bacon. Buffalo mozzarella. All right. Close this.
Medium dough. I can't split it to a small. Oh, there's a small right there. Okay. Let's go. Okay.
And you wanted what? Let's pin it. You wanted a little bit of mozzarella cheese.
I guess. Mozzarella cheese? Only 16 grams. That seems like not very much. Oh, shit. Oops. Okay.
Hold on. How much marinara? Marinara. It'll be a surprise. Okay. There's your marinara.
There's your mozzarella cheese. You need some salami. I know the salami in here somewhere.
There it is. Cut salami. I'm gonna do it this cool though. No, I need to be able to put more
than that. And then basil leaf. Okay. Basil. How much basil? There's more basil than salami on this
pizza. Oh, we want a grated mozzarella cheese. Uh oh. All right. Can I take it off? He won't even
notice. Thousand kilograms of mozzarella. That sounds like a really cool band name.
You don't think that a what? A thousand kilograms of mozzarella is not a cool name for like a band?
Why not? How do I clean this? How is it a band name? I don't know. Name a band. Let's find out
how weird the names are. Fallout boy. The Beatles. Oh, this is burning. Get it out. Get it out. Get
it out. Okay. Put it on a small plate. Coupleware remix party. If that's a real name for a band,
then how is mine any stranger? Jimmy eat world. Okay. Here we go. Take it. What do you think?
It's next one. Oh, what's wrong? Oh, the cheese is wrong. Right. Whatever. Another marinara pizza.
This one is medium. Roll it out. So what did you want? I mean, I'm gonna, this one's gonna be
perfect. You want, let's pin this. Marinara. Let's get the marinara. I'm gonna do this as best as I
can. I'm really gonna try as hard as I can. Okay. That's not bad. That could have been,
that could have been way worse. More sauce. Extra sauce. That looks good. Okay. Garlic.
Garlic. Get out of the way. You're in my way. Please get out of the way. Out. All right. I'm
gonna do this the way that I would want it. I like it in little clusters. I can't do that though.
I have no more garlic left. Shit. Uh, give me this goddamn basket. We're gonna fill this thing to
the brim with garlic. Raid, grate your, I'm not, I'm not gonna say that out loud. That's insane.
What you just said. I love garlic though. I'm totally cool with this. Uh, I need one of those
things. There we go. That's much better. All right. Garlic. That's it. No cheese or anything, huh?
Okay. That's fine. Not much more, right? 32. Okay. And then a little bit of basil. 24. What are you
doing? What are you doing? Can I put one more? So I'm gonna put one more. I don't care. It looks
better. All right. Get it in there. Do you think the person's really gonna complain? They're gonna
get their pizza and go, excuse me. There was an extra basil leaf on here that I did not order.
Guys, if you order a bunch of shit on a pizza, they could probably hide bugs in it and you
wouldn't even know it was on there. You're not going to notice one basil leaf. Okay. Let's,
this is going to cook fast. I hope you never prepare food for anyone. I mean, very, come on,
very clearly playing cooking simulator, pizza sim. I, what just happened? I pressed, I pressed Q.
Oh dear. Oh well. Burnt to fuck. Yeah, because I pressed Q. Why, why, why is there an instantly
burn the pizza button? What, what's that for? It was a zero, apparently. It was a zero. All right.
Do not mess this one up. Just do it. Just pin it. Let's go. You want a medium sized dough.
Shut the operation down. Okay. Baron arrow. We're closing for today? What? Oh shit. Hold on. I
forgot that we're at a restaurant. Okay. Let's, uh, mozzarella cut a hundred. Not bad. Okay.
What's next? Basil done. I'm going to see one 24. All right. Get it in there and don't screw this
up. The freezer has been open the whole time in the basement. Did I open it? Did I do that? I did.
Oh shit. That's not good. It's done. It'll be done in a minute. It's not going to burn.
Just don't press the incinerate button. I just had, I just felt a sneeze coming on
and I panicked and pressed every button on my stream deck. It's not burnt. It's fine.
I muted the game. Yeah. I press. Oh shit. It's still muted. Sorry. Yeah. I felt the sneeze
coming on. So I was like, I don't want to sneeze on camera. So I just went, I mashed my fingers
all over my stream deck to try to turn everything off. How is this burnt? It looks perfect. I was
going to just whip it over here, but I can't do that. All right. First day of my new pizza job
completed. Now prepare the ingredients for tomorrow. Ooh, this part's fun. Okay. Here we go.
Where's it clean? Can I, how, how do I clean up? There's no trash.
You only made two pizzas in a whole day. Yeah, but it's quality though. All right. Let's make some
dough. We need flour. Let me clean up first. This is hell. Make glass pizza. All right. Hold on.
I'm not going to serve glass pizza to somebody yet. And I say yet because you know, I probably
eventually will. Psycho. You all know I'm going to make a glass pizza. What do you think? That's
like a rocket scientist that's at the stream for more than 10 minutes to know that somebody's
going to eat glass today. All right. Flour. Open. All right. What's it? I need the recipe.
Where is it? Okay. I want a dough. So it's, let's pin this. Okay. All right. It's 3.5 kilograms of
fiber. What if I just make a shitload of it? I'm going to do a double batch. So what if the,
let's do double, just double the whole thing up. Okay. So 3.5, 3.5, so that's seven. Don't, don't,
don't, don't, don't. All right. Well, let me, let me, I gotta use tap water. Can't pick this up.
Okay. I need a container. Fire extinguisher into the dough. No, not yet. Put soap in there.
Oh, here we go. Jug. Get down there. Don't break it. Do not break it. All right. Pour it in.
2.4. That thing, that just turned into a blooming onion from Outback. Whatever. All right. I need
salt. 125 grams. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Easy, easy, easy. Not that much salt.
We want a blooming onion. You really don't though. Cause it sucks. You order it. You eat three or
four little cloves and then you, nobody else at the table wants to eat it. You eat it with that
delicious blooming sauce. You eat five of them. And for some reason, you're one of the only people
at the table that's eating it. Cause you go to the Outback and you get the meme order
and everyone's like, I don't fucking want to eat that. And then like, oh, but let's get it.
Okay. Now I need yeast. And then you have that awkward moment where like the waiter or the
waitress comes over and two thirds of the blooming onion is still there after you've eaten your
entrees. You guys are still picking at that? No, but I'm going to take this thing home.
I'm taking this thing home and I'm going to eat it in the microwave later.
I want to hit the red button. The green one. Okay. That's dough. I need, how much sauce do I have left?
I think I have enough sauce. Clean this place up. Close the windows. I don't want, I don't want
anybody looking in here. Okay. I have, I need some more dough. I need to really, I got to clean up.
Let's make this place look like shit. I need to pick that. I have to pick this up. Hold on.
What are you doing? Come here. Where did they go? Go back to normal. Go back to normal.
Go back to normal. Back to normal. Why can I not pick this up? All right. No more advanced controls.
Just give it to me. I'm trying to pick the dough up like this. No, just I'll pick it up with my
feet if I have to. Okay. Right now I'm doing the thing that, okay. Let's say, let's say you're like
a blanket falls on the ground or like a pillow is on the ground that you want, but you don't want
to bend over. So you just reach over with your foot and you scrunch your toes around the blanket
and you pull it up. I'm not actually doing that with this. I'm just saying that's like what it
reminds me of. I got plenty of dough now. Plenty of dough of various shapes and sizes. Lots of dough.
Let's put this back where it belongs. Okay. I already have one. I have two now. It's covered
in dust. How do I clean? That's what I want to know. I think I have enough marinara sauce for
tomorrow. I need a little container here. Can I put glass in here? I can't. I definitely I'm
going to get cut by this. Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? Throw it away. Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? D minus
rating from the inspector? Oh, I don't think so. I haven't poisoned anybody yet. Come back next week.
Okay. Let's go over here. Note to self. Let's make a really clear note of this. No more breaking stuff
on the ground. I don't care how funny it is. No more breaking shit. Because look at how much I'm
painting the ass this is. Where's the sponge? Sponge. Oh, nice. Very nice. Very nice. Very nice.
Clean up the pee. I got a clean area. Make sure to clean those vegetables. Clean the meat. I think
I'm ready for tomorrow. All right, new day. New day. I'm 800 in the green. I'm doing fine.
All right, I'm going to try to get at least five pizzas done today. Here we go. Let's go.
Give me five. Give me five. Let's go. Go, Go, Go. Give me the app. All right. We got
two margaritas, marinara, we've got medium dough, medium, medium, medium, small, medium. All right,
All right, we got four mediums and a small.
Medium, medium, done.
Medium.
Is that a small?
Okay, we're good.
Ready?
Go, go, go, go, go.
They all have sauce.
Why is this one small?
Shit, can I just like bunch up dough and throw it on top?
All right, with the two smalls?
Sauce.
The sauce looks like brown.
Done?
Sauce.
Sauce it up.
Pull it back.
What else?
We got two smalls.
Unpin this.
Why is it still here?
All right, so this is a medium.
We got marinara.
We need garlic, basil.
What are the other ones?
Garlic, basil, mozzarella.
So, okay, we need garlic, basil, mozzarella, cut.
Garlic, basil, mozzarella, cut.
All right, put your head down here.
Garlic.
Where are you putting your head, man?
Okay, garlic.
24, right?
32.
Garlic.
Is there garlic on this one?
Garlic, basil.
It's rosemary.
This person didn't even want cheese.
All right, we have garlic, basil, marinara.
Done.
This one's done.
This one is mozzarella, cut, basil.
That's a lot of cheese.
All right, and basil.
Done, done, done, done, done, done.
What is this one?
This is the second small.
What's the other small one?
Medium, medium, medium.
There's only one small.
I can't.
I'm gonna, who cares?
Fucking free pizza for the seagulls.
Okay, medium.
Can you imagine being at a pizza restaurant?
You're out like on the pier or something in Italy,
and all of a sudden, the guy's screaming in the kitchen.
The fucking windows fly open.
Fucking small.
He's like, this one's for the seagulls.
And he just slingshots a pizza out the window.
Holy shit, this guy's nuts.
We gotta get out of here.
Why?
It said medium.
Pick it up.
Wait, add, add, add, add.
Oh my God.
Why?
Is this a medium?
What the fuck does he keep doing this for?
It's for the ants.
Okay.
Medium, salami, right?
This is marinara, grated mozzarella, salami, and basil.
Grated mozzarella, basil.
Grated mozzarella.
More, more, more, more, more.
That's it, 64.
Get him in the oven, I'm done.
Oh, I forgot the salami.
Hold on, hold on.
Forgot the salami.
How much salami did you want?
All right, get him in.
Damn, you're thicker than a bowl of oatmeal.
Thanks.
That's a Reddit joke?
I don't know.
I'm just, I don't know what that is.
Wait, what?
I can only have two pizzas in the oven at the same time?
All right, well, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
There's three, I have two more pizzas to make.
All right, just low and slow, low and slow.
Low and slow, low and slow, low and slow,
low and slow, low and slow.
Medium, medium, medium.
That's not how pizza works?
It is here.
Okay, everybody, it's all marinara.
Fuck it, whatever, I don't care.
You're gonna eat it just, look,
you'll enjoy the Nickelodeon splat of marinara sauce.
I don't care.
Now what?
I lost track of which one is which.
Marinara, this one is garlic.
Oh shit, hold on.
They're all garlic and basil.
That's all we make here.
It's just garlic and basil.
We don't make anything else.
All right, just put garlic and basil on everything.
Who cares?
Wait, the pizza's burning?
No, they're not, low and slow.
All right, garlic.
That's onion.
Okay, basil.
Okay, that's good.
Garlic, basil, garlic, basil.
I did extra garlic, but it's okay.
All right, get them in there.
One needs cheese.
This one.
One of them wants, okay, that's garlic and basil.
Cut mozzarella, 100.
Okay, how are we looking?
All right, get it out.
These are two mediums, two medium-sized pizzas.
Why is there a sponge in the way?
Get the sponge out of here.
Okay, here they come.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
All right, they're ready, go.
Looks good.
It looks good, it looks good, it looks good.
Let's go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Okay, get the other one quick, quick, quick, quick.
All right, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Let them cool, they gotta rest.
It's like meat that you take out of the oven.
All right, next going in, we have the small.
Where's this pizza go?
Where's the small pizza that I made?
Oh, whatever, fuck it.
The rats took it.
Oven's still hot.
It's funny how stupid I am.
This was resting on the stool with the pizza on top of it.
It's just not there anymore.
This shit's gonna be cold.
Fuck, okay, let's go.
This is pepperoni, basil, and salami.
Take it.
This one is, all right, level up.
I can move faster.
All right, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, I don't care.
This one is garlic and basil, medium.
Medium garlic and basil, go.
All right, thank you.
What happened to that small pizza?
I don't know, why I thought it was gonna be under there,
like a chewed gum.
What am I doing?
It went and it fell into the trash.
Well, whatever.
Okay, so now I have,
I gotta make that small pizza again.
It's burnt?
This looks like shit.
It looks like somebody bled on that pizza.
Doesn't it look like sauce?
It looks like cat puke.
That's my special.
That's my cut arm and cat puke pizza.
This is like how I slipped my hand open
when I was making the pizza.
Shit, all right, all right, all right, all right.
This one, what even was this one?
You have to make the noise now.
No, I can't.
You know what's weird about this pizza?
This pizza looks like a lot of buffalo chicken pizzas
I've had before.
Why is it that people just can't do that?
Putting it back in.
It was ready.
Oh shit.
This just looks like,
this just looks like you hit M in an open world game
and look at all these quests I have.
I need another plate.
Give me this damn thing.
Oh my God, what the hell am I doing?
Just, I just smashed that, don't.
Okay, I smashed that plate into my face.
I don't even know what this pizza was.
What was this pizza?
I don't even know, who ordered the chili?
That's disgusting.
I guess it wasn't margarita.
Okay, it was this one, I guess.
Oh, bon appetit.
I enjoy your chili on your pizza.
Oh, prosciutto, eggplant and cherry tomato.
Hey, you still ate it.
Oh man.
Okay, what was the blood pizza?
That's just basil and garlic?
All right, let me take a look and see.
Let me just make sure I'm doing this right.
This one is the medium that wants cheese on it.
Fuck, get that over here.
I mixed them up.
Just put it on low, wait for the cheese to melt.
All right, is it ready, is it ready, is it ready?
All right, it's ready, get it.
Oh, look at that, look at that bubbly cheese.
Oh my goodness, the ooey gooey bubbly cheese.
Actually kind of looks kind of good.
Looks frozen, doesn't look frozen.
You know what, whatever.
Here, here, here, happy birthday.
No, that was the, oh.
This is dough on top of, wait,
can I do dough on top of the dough pizza?
You take like, you go out for like a nice dinner
with like a significant other
or mother or parents or something or whatever.
You order a Neapolitan pizza
from a place that has apparently rave reviews.
This is like when we're in Italy, this is in Italy.
This is gonna be delicious, we're in Italy.
This is where you get the best pizza like in the world.
And this dude just gives you a burnt piece of bread.
Actually, Italy pizza is shit.
What?
I've never been, I don't know.
This place is a mess, I gotta clean this up.
After I put this in there
as long as it can go in there for.
I'm gonna give it an extra toasted bun.
Oven is blocked, what?
I mean, oven is blocked by the bread?
All right, let's get it.
It's still in there, looks like a pie crust.
Can I buy like cherries and blueberries and stuff?
It's, who ordered the caviar?
It's my special caviar pizza.
But it's the children's version
where it's not actually caviar, it's olives.
This is, okay, remember when like there would be things
where food would be gross for kids?
Like, oh, it's brains, it's brains pizza.
That's just on the menu.
I have one of those like weird fucking menus
where it's like you just get a bunch
of olives all over pizzas.
This costs me, this is a piece of shit to make, right?
Well, like I can sell it because it's like,
oh, it's like bird shit, bird shit pizza.
Hey, hey, do you guys,
hey kids, do you kids want to order the bird shit?
Oh, gross, yeah, here you go, here's one bird shit pizza.
Why do we do that?
Why, what's, I don't understand that, by the way.
Why do we have like a gross shit
for like funny for kids menus?
Oh, look, it's worms, you're eating worms.
I don't want people to think they're eating worms.
When you eat spaghetti, why is it like, oh, hey, no, no, no,
hey, I'll make it cooler for you, kid.
You're eating like fucking worms out of the ground.
Oh, yes, mm, it's called spaghetti.
Here, who ordered the mussels?
Would you really be pissed about that though
if you bought a pizza that was,
if you bought like an $8 pizza
and it came with like $70 of mussels on it,
are you gonna be that upset about it?
I'd be like, are these cooked and are these good?
And whatever, let's have to make the pizza.
Oh, I kind of trashed this place.
Meat and veggie pizza.
Uh-oh, the game crashed, but it came back.
All right, I don't have any Alfredo sauce.
What the fuck, I gotta make Alfredo sauce.
Butter, hold on, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit,
butter, butter, I need one of these.
Okay, butter, 150 grams of butter.
Was the label still on?
I think the package was still on, the wrapper was on.
Okay, butter, what else?
Milk, okay, universal flour, 150.
Oh, fuck, okay, whatever.
We need salt, pepper, okay.
How much pepper though, 10?
We got a link, hold on, wait, wait, wait,
I'll click, whoops, I clicked it too much.
And Parmesan cheese, I love Parmesan cheese,
that's like my favorite.
All right, Parmesan cheese.
Wait, that's downstairs.
That's a lot of cheese, okay.
I gotta grind it up, can I just put it in there?
Oh, shit, okay, what, what?
All right, there it is.
Who wanted this?
Let me see what the link is, what's the link?
I've seen that before, this is old.
This is old, I've seen it.
Okay, now I need to make a,
let's go back to the guy that wanted the actual,
what does he want?
All right, meat and veggie.
You wanted meat, what kind of meat?
Why can't I click this?
It's crashing again, wrong link?
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Don't crash, don't crash, don't do it.
Don't crash, don't crash, don't crash, don't, no.
No, yes, I think it's changing soundtrack.
It's heavy, huh?
Is this me lifting up like, what am I,
whatever, okay, I'm moving, I'm playing this,
I'm making pieces, I've got a timer.
All right, Alfredo sauce, mozzarella, chicken breast.
I don't even have chicken breast.
Oh, God damn it, okay, hold on, chicken products.
Where do I get chicken?
Oh, okay, okay, cut this up.
Wait, can I do grated chicken?
That's disgusting, like little shredded cheese chicken
pieces, actually that's, that isn't disgusting,
that's fine, there we go, okay.
Now, SpongeBob, why do I hear SpongeBob's music?
Stop crashing when I click this info link, stop, why?
Stop clicking it while I need to see, I gotta pin it.
You're making the subway trays.
Just turn this place into a subway,
don't even do pizzas anymore, just do subway sandwiches.
Just line like four or five pieces of cold,
gross chicken strips, squeeze way too much mayonnaise
and way too much mustard all over it.
And then grab the container of wilted lettuce
and then be out of all the cool breads.
Can I have it on the herb break, the cashew bread?
We don't have that.
Can I have it on a wheat and oregano?
We don't have that today.
All right, can I have it on just default,
fucking like sub bread?
Sure, there's only cringe breads left, yeah.
The last time I went to Subway, I had the,
it was one, I don't know, it was the last experience
I'll ever have there.
And I'm sorry this is gonna come off as I'm gonna sound
like elitist or something, I really don't mean to be.
But when they take that, when they take that like
carnival fare container of chicken and cheese
that they melt in the microwave thing
and they dump it upside down onto the bread,
it's like in the French fry container from the carnival.
You know what I'm talking about?
It's this little paper container
and then they turn it upside down like three times
and it's just this melted cheese and chicken mess.
And it was still, it was like somehow cold
in the middle still, I don't know how.
We never went to the carnival?
Oh, really?
I love the carnival, you don't,
you've never been to the carnival before?
This is a medium, right?
No, it's a large.
This, dude, this is a large pizza.
This is a big one.
This is a meat lover's pizza?
Okay, you want Alfredo sauce, which,
what happened to my, okay, Alfredo sauce.
I don't know why, but this reminds me of egg yolk
and it's making me wanna just not make this anymore.
Okay, that's Alfredo sauce, mozzarella, cut mozzarella.
I think this would be too much, okay.
Chicken breast, 96 grams?
Hey, let's get somebody that's at this dinner party
the best bite.
You know what I mean?
This guy gets the good,
whoever gets that gets the good slice.
And then basil leaf, and that's it.
All right, wrong sauce?
What are you talking about?
What about, you forgot, I forgot onion?
We're closing for the day, oh shit.
I'm never gonna get that ever again.
I don't know why I did that.
Oh, good thing there's a backup.
I forgot onions.
Oh, white onion.
White onion cut, 64, okay.
All right, the next piece that I make,
I'm gonna make just one slice be,
I'm gonna have one slice have all the toppings on it
and everything else is gonna be bare.
I'm talking sauce too, by the way.
Let's get through this day and clean up though.
Sauce two waiting room.
Sauce two.
Why am I doing that?
I can't get them back.
I can't take this pizza out.
Oh, thank God.
It sucked to me, okay.
I'm ready.
I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready.
I want that pizza, give me the fucking pizza.
Give me that fucking pizza.
Almost ready.
Hey everybody, dinner's ready.
Come and get it kids.
It's not burning, it's fine.
Look at that cheese bubbling up.
Why is it frozen?
Every time I take a piece out of the oven,
it fucking freezes.
What are you doing?
Stop freezing, stop freezing.
Why is it frozen?
Oh my God, okay.
Are you, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, okay.
It's really thinking about if it wants to load
all the onions in the same spot.
Oh, wrong food, it was chicken, chicken breast.
That's correct.
And 80 omega low.
Yeah, I know, I know.
I was about to throw it out the window.
What?
I'm gonna go so slow.
Okay, cool.
Why won't it accept it, take it.
What the fuck just happened?
This is a major struggle going on right now.
Okay, okay, I don't know.
If my brain is a little fried,
but I thought that was the health of the pizza.
Oh, I took down like 10% of its health.
Okay, can we stop this nonsense, please?
Here you go, dang.
Meat and veggie pizza.
Do you love it?
You can't, you, I mean,
I mean, I did as good as if I guessed
on every multiple choice question.
So for me doing that, that did pretty good.
Was the sauce was wrong, how?
I'm gonna make my own sauce.
Yeah, I'm making my secret sauce.
Let's go, I'm making my secret sauce and secret dough.
Let's see, it's gonna be tomatoes.
Tomato, it's gonna be like a barbecue.
All right, here we go.
I want my basket.
I'm gonna make my sauce.
A little bit of garlic, a little bit of onion.
Lots of tomatoes, San Marzano tomatoes.
San Marzano tomatoes.
Okay, onions, garlic, oil, cheddar cheese.
Cheddar cheese in there.
Oh, that's gonna be cheesy.
Bacon for fat and flavor.
Milk for creaminess factor.
Prosciutto for the fat.
And then where's barbecue sauce?
All right, you know how many times
have you been in your own house
and you've done something like that?
Are you moving too fast or it's a little dark
and you just, ow, my face.
Oh, fuck, oh no.
Did I lose anything?
Oh, God damn it, just put it down.
Resident sleeper.
Hey, don't say that.
Don't say that right now, come on, man.
Why are 10K people watching this?
Because I showed my ass yesterday.
That's why.
True.
Okay, so this is what I wanted to go in here.
All these ingredients, garlic, the onions,
the cheese, the cheddar, the San Marzano tomatoes.
That was a good catch.
Now we put a little bit of milk in there.
Milk, just a little bit.
Okay, now I want the, okay, I got everything in there.
I want a little bit of oil too.
I want to make it nice and oily.
Liquids, sunflower oil, make it thicker.
Oh, I can't fit anything in there.
Wait, wait, there was already a bunch of shit in here.
It already was milk, butter, flour, salt,
pepper, cheese, garlic, tomatoes, cheddar,
bacon, white onions, and prosciutto.
Okay, sure.
Okay, what if I just do a fucking shitload
of butter and lard and that's the thing I put on pizzas?
Yeah, hold on, fuck this.
I don't understand.
You're making me angry.
Okay, butter, butter, butter, butter, butter.
Wasn't there a way for me to wipe out some of the debt
to eat like 10 sticks of butter?
That's, no one should ever do that, that's disgusting.
Like, why would you ever do that?
That's not even like funny or fun, it's just horrible.
There's mayo, yeah, no, why would you do that?
It would be so painful and horrible.
Okay, I have a sauce in here already.
That's my secret sauce.
All right, I gotta put my items over here
so I don't mix it up with the actual game items.
All right, let's go, butter, shitload of butter.
No, no, no, wipe it out, wipe this whole thing out.
Wipe it out.
Butter and oil.
Yeah, and I'm gonna put some like lemon in there too.
Okay, onion powder, salt, sugar, butter, sugar, flour.
This is just cookie dough.
It's a cake.
It's like milk.
It's just cake.
Milk, sugar, butter, flour.
That's okay, now let's get a tray.
Eggs, I don't think, I don't have access to any eggs.
More sugar?
Are eggs in the freezer?
Oh, that's mozzarella.
I mean, it looks like eggs, but it's not.
It's down here.
Nope, okay, close enough.
Okay, one egg.
All right, let's go.
Does it have to be green?
It has a green tint to it.
Okay, let me actually, hold on.
I need to clean up
because I'm gonna lose track of all this shit.
Hold on, I got these tomatoes.
I'm gonna make more, how much more marinara?
I got plenty of marinara.
I have enough cheese.
I got, I need more garlic.
I need more freshly chopped, cut garlic.
Gas in the sauce?
I can't.
I can't just add gas.
Can I?
Woo hoo!
Get rid of this, get this away from me.
Get this away from me, get it away.
Get it out, get away from me.
Do not throw it.
Yo, tray, gas in the oven.
No, I'm not at that point yet.
Sure, I will put the gas can in the bread maker
in like an hour or something, but not right now.
I wanna make a pizza for me.
Okay, let's get this open.
Where's my homemade sauce?
Okay, wait, what about?
Okay, butter, this is it, okay.
All right, that's the sugar butter sauce.
And you know what?
Oh, the jug is gone, nevermind.
I lost the jug.
Okay, now I want, now don't waste the marinara.
I need more chicken.
Why doesn't the streamer talk?
What are you distracting me for?
I just dropped all my walnuts on the ground.
All right, put, get them in here.
I'm just trying to prepare for tomorrow.
I have to actually make the Alfredo sauce too
because somebody said you didn't even make it, it's fake.
Lost the chicken.
This music's driving me insane.
Hold on.
It's the radio, where's the radio?
Turn off the radio.
Yeah, when I move around really fast,
it's like.
Where is it?
I'm playing empty folder.
Empty playlist.
Oh, turn it off.
What was I doing?
Oh, just stop this.
I don't know, clean it up, clean it up.
Clean, clean, I need to clean this up.
Clean this up, clean this shit up.
No more joking around, I have to, I need to unlock things.
Clean up this mess.
Clean it.
Why can't I?
I can't put, I have to have to do it piece by piece.
Didn't I say that I wasn't gonna break
any more plates anymore?
Why are there five broken plates on the ground?
Why are there that many broken plates?
It's like I said, I don't wanna do anything like that,
but that actually means I'm gonna do it 10 times more.
I really mean it this time.
I'm not breaking a single plate tomorrow.
Not one plate is breaking tomorrow.
If a plate, don't do that.
Don't say that.
Don't do that.
Just don't break one.
No betting.
Don't have to put any wagers on this.
Why, I don't, that's not necessary.
I do have to pee though.
That's something that we can all agree on.
No deal.
No deal that I have to pee.
You guys, can I go pee?
No deal.
Oh, well I just, no deal.
All right, if you let me go pee,
you can add a million dollars to the debt.
No deal.
No deal, no deal, no deal.
All right, we're almost at least somewhat clean.
Can you even use this?
Well, I mean, I'm going pee.
You're not gonna stop me.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
If I have to go to the bathroom,
I'm gonna use the bathroom.
I have to buy more wood.
Wait, I can't, I'm not allowed to turn the oven on
if the store is closed.
You have two trash cans.
Yeah, I can't put trash in here, watch.
No, I don't wanna roll that.
Okay, well, it wouldn't let me do it before.
I don't know why.
How much dough do I have?
Not a whole lot.
All right, this is where the tins are gonna go.
Clean.
A nice fresh surface.
Okay, what else?
That looks all right.
A little dirty in here.
It's super dirty in here.
What am I talking about?
How much olive oil is left in here?
A lot.
Keep that, that's fine.
Still plenty of flour in here.
I thought that was a bug.
Okay, there's still milk left in here, so that's fine.
We'll keep it.
And there's not enough flour in there
to justify holding onto it anymore.
All right, salt.
This looks better.
Just doesn't look like I'm messed up.
I need to make new dough.
Let's make the dough.
I need to do water, flour, flour, water, nothing else.
No, it's crashed.
It's crashing.
Go pee?
All right, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Go to the bathroom, Jerma.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
As you wait till the thing doesn't crash.
Oh, now, I can't, hold on.
The game is like hanging right now.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No!
Critical pee capacity, not quite.
It's getting there though.
The phone crashes this game, I'll tell you.
Please, don't do this.
No!
Song chain's not gonna fix it now.
Yeah, that's right.
Oh, I think it is done.
I think it's dead.
Come on.
When did it save last?
I'll be back, I'll be right back.
Hey, look at this.
I'll be right back.
Holy shit, I got back.
Look at this, look at that.
I missed it.
No, we don't say that here.
Somebody correct that person
that said there was a J word in there.
Isn't this awesome though?
No, not Jerma.
It's, how cool is this though?
This is only the second time you've ever seen this.
I love it, I think it's fantastic.
Sorry, there's been a seagull
in your left ear this whole time.
Holy shit.
That's terrifying.
All right, one more.
Rat Tsunemiku.
Sterling 3D printed fireman and it glows in the dark?
Oh no, glow in the dark version coming soon.
That's awesome.
You guys are so talented, it's unbelievable.
All right, one more, one more, one more, one more.
What the hell?
That's awesome.
All right, one more.
One more, one more, one more, one more, one more.
I kind of missed that hair, don't you?
I missed that hair.
I kind of liked it, even though like from the back
it looked crappy, it looked terrible from the back.
From the front and the side, I thought it looked pretty good.
There's the dry rub.
All right, one more and that's it.
One streamer tells truths, the other lies.
Hey, and oh, whoops.
And in the time it took for me to come back,
the game stopped crashing, would you look at that?
All right, let's make the dough.
I need to make, where is it?
Pizza Pro.
What, there's two different doughs now?
Oh shit, okay.
I gotta make New York dough.
New York style dough.
All right, we need universal flour, 3.5 kilograms.
Don't put it in there.
Something in there already, what's in there?
A water?
You know the next level are gonna need New York dough.
It's gonna happen.
A water, I don't have a jug anymore.
I can just buy one.
All right, 2.3 of water.
2.1, excuse me.
Excuse me.
I spilled it?
How?
Oh, 2.5, don't throw it out the window, this is expensive.
Shit, it's okay.
Whatever, turn this off.
Turn it off the water.
2.5, whatever.
All right, 35 grams of salt.
That's sugar.
Just make it water.
I promise that this wasn't my tooth breaking.
A lot of you probably just, oh my god damn it, Jeremy.
What are you doing, stop.
I have like a candy.
Too much salt, too much water.
All right, I need to add a little bit more flour.
No, no, just dump it.
3.5.
Is it a Sour Patch Kid?
No, it's a yummy Jolly Rancher.
It's not a Jolly Rancher, I just wish it was.
It's a CBD candy, nope.
It's a CBD Jolly Rancher, no.
How can there be water and then water in here?
I mean, water and then water.
2.3, perfect.
Get the salt.
Don't screw this up, please.
One, 20, 30, 40, 50, 60, 70, 75.
Yeast, just one thing of yeast, that's fine.
This is 10, throw it in there.
Olive oil with the sugar and New York dough.
Really?
I didn't know that.
Oop, I'm not, sprint.
Okay, turn off sprint.
Turn off sprint, no more sprinting.
Oh my fucking God, I even spent time not, ah!
I even spent the extra time waiting.
Oh, it's okay, it's extra oily.
I'm mad.
I am upset right now, I'm not happy.
Because I just dumped it 10 minutes ago.
Oh, it's fine, whatever.
Jerma's mad part, pizza.
A little.
All right, whatever.
Close it up.
Press the button.
Oh, I need a tray.
Cool.
All right, so this is a New York style dough tray.
I'm gonna put this over here.
That's gonna go right there.
Again, what's the point of having the windows open?
I need to make a regular, I broke the ceiling lamp.
I was gonna cheat when I said lights out.
Just put them in drawers?
Where did they all go?
Oh my God, what?
Why?
There's only three left.
I keep losing dough to collateral damage.
Other tray, no, there was more than this.
It was like three more.
What the hell?
Whatever, I'm gonna make more regular dough.
Shit.
Oh, it's regular, just Neapolitan style dough.
In it, let's go.
Flour, put it in.
Here's the fifth reminder for Alfredo sauce.
I got you, I got you, don't worry.
And water in there.
Just order a pizza, lol.
I have a pizza restaurant
where I just order pizzas to this restaurant
and then put them at the window.
The genius business strategy.
2.4, don't go too much.
Where's the rest of the water?
What would I name my pizza restaurant?
Flatbread, with no A in bread.
Oh my God, I went over.
Flatbread, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, not flatbread, flatbread,
but B-R-E, but flatbread.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It would be neither one of those.
It would be, uh, slap, uh,
flap, flap, crunchy crust, crunchy crust.
But it would be, instead of Ys, it would be Es.
So it would be crunchy, crunchy cheeses.
My mascot would be a big mouse.
Crunchy munchies.
How about just like, crunchies?
All right, let's go.
How about crunchitize me?
The Krusty Krotch?
No, I don't think I want a restaurant named that.
Would you eat at a restaurant
that was called Krusty Krotch?
What if it was like a 4.7 on Yelp?
Okay, I got my dough.
Don't just explode into the ceiling.
Okay, looking good.
Here's my dough.
Don't forget the Alfredo sauce.
I know, I will not.
Alfredo.
Pesto.
Shit, I gotta make pesto sauce?
Oh crap, okay, hold on.
First of all, let's, hold on.
I gotta dump all this crap.
I've made a bunch of shitty sauces
that it's gonna mess me up.
Oh, this is butter, sugar, flour, and mozzarella.
This one is butter, milk, salt,
Parmesan cheese, garlic, just get rid of this.
It's your sauce lab?
Welcome to Sauce Lab.
We make all kinds of different sauces.
My favorite sauces and your favorite sauces.
We take three comments.
You say a certain type of food
and we make a sauce out of it.
And the comments are random.
This person said peanut butter.
Jake1114 said peanut butter with a wicked, gross, gross face.
EatMyAss12 says, dude, water.
How are we gonna make a sauce
with water and peanut butter, guys?
What the heck?
And Anthony Jenkins6,
it's probably a young dude
because he did his full first and last name.
Don't do that.
Says blood.
Well, whoa, I guess it's gonna be weird, man.
Peanut butter, water, and blood.
You didn't say human blood.
Okay, ant blood.
Alfredo sauce, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, okay, right, right, right, right.
No, no, not ant blood.
I want Alfredo sauce.
No, I was gonna make ant blood.
Alfredo sauce, Alfredo.
Salt, where am I?
Okay, here.
What?
No, not salt, what am I doing?
Alfredo sauce is butter, is 150.
Okay, garlic, 50 grams of garlic.
Butter sauce, five, 10, 15, 20, 25, 30, 35, 40, 45, 50,
55, 60, 65, 70, he can go to all, he can go higher.
75, 80, 85, 90, how can he do that?
85, 100, 105, 110, 115, 120, 125, 130,
holy shit, 130, 135, 140, 145, 150, 155, 165, 175,
180, 190, 200, why is that chicken in here?
You wanna embarrass me?
I'm gonna do that with sixes.
Six, 12, 18, 24, 32, that's where it's over.
38, six, 38, 40, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 50, 56.
62, 68, 70, 74, 780, 86, it's over.
All right, let's do it with sevens.
Seven, 14, 21, 28, I don't know, it's over.
31, I don't know, how about eights?
Eight, 16, 24, 32, 30, 40, 48, that's over.
Nine, nine, 18, it's over.
How about four?
Four, eight, 12, 16, 20, 24, 28, 32, 30, it's over.
Three, three, six, nine, 12, 15, 18, 21, 24, 27, 30,
33, 30, it's over, 36, it's over.
Why is it always in thirties?
I can't figure, why is that, why?
What about two?
I can do two, two, four, six, eight, 10, 12, 14, 16,
20, 22, 24, 26, 28, 30, 32, 34, 36, 38, 40, 42, 44, 44,
yeah, I can do that one.
Is anything higher than your IQ?
All right, get out of here.
Once you cross over the first five or six tiers of,
I can't do it, I wish that was a joke,
but once you get over like 40, I don't know,
I just don't do math, I'm not a math guy.
I can fucking sprint wicked fast, you know,
I've said that a lot of times, but I can.
When does he play the game and stop stalling?
I mean, it's been three hours of stalling, man,
I'm sorry, that's just the kind of how it is here.
I don't know if you just got here,
but I've been streaming for three hours
and I haven't even begun.
All right, so what do we need?
Milk, one liter of milk.
I love the pouring, don't go hard, perfect pour.
That's a fucking perfect pour.
Wait, oh, it's because there's only one liter in here.
I need universal flour, 150, this is easy to fuck up.
It comes out really quick, 125,
just only 25 more, that's it.
Yep, got it, okay, good.
How many bags of flour?
I keep buying new bags of flour.
Okay, salt, pepper is just 10, that's it.
Pepper is also 10.
And then cheese, 500 grams of pie, it's just one cube.
Cocaine is bad for you, yes it is.
I've never done it before and I would say
to never do it, ever.
It's bad for you, don't do it.
I agree, I completely agree with you.
What you are witnessing is caffeine and neuroticism.
So, it's a little different.
Okay, I have those containers, right?
Okay, that's perfect, yeah, there it is.
Not eroticism.
All right, this Alfredo is junk, get rid of it.
Alfredo sauce made with milk is a disgrace to Italian, what?
I want the sauces, okay, I want toppings here.
I want sauces down the bottom, so we got, okay,
there's your, I'm gonna make the pesto too.
Okay, there's my, this looks kinda old, doesn't it?
When marinara sauce looks like meat sauce,
that's when it's probably time to get rid of it, isn't it?
Ah, fuck it, whatever, it's still good.
I need more chopped garlic.
Go ahead and put that in here.
Oh, there's chicken in here.
Why is there so much, why are there so many
uncooked potato chips in here?
Garlic, I don't like Alfredo sauce.
I like it sometimes, depends on what it is.
Why is there still chicken in here?
What is it, wait, what is going on?
This, what the fuck?
How much chicken did I put in here?
Why is it that much chicken?
Was it that much?
All right, let's go.
Plenty of garlic, I gotta make pesto now too.
Royalty-free pasta tunes?
Um, I don't know.
I haven't had to put corn on anything.
Now I need, I might need a little bit more mozzarella,
but okay, I need pesto.
Pesto is a bunch of olive oil, which I have.
That's 800.
Oh, that's unfortunate.
Do I have any more?
No.
Can I scrape it off the wall and pour it in here?
Oh, 7.99, that's horseshit.
Oh, it hurts.
It hurts to look at.
All right, now I need basil.
Okay, let me go, I gotta get my shopping cart.
Parmesan cheese, walnuts.
Okay, where's the walnut?
Walnuts, where the walnut down here?
Garlic, pepper, so okay, so where the,
I thought pesto was pine nuts.
Okay, where's the, where the walnuts?
It is, why does it say walnut?
Did I have an un-locked walnuts yet?
Blue can, oh shit, okay.
Garlic, salt, and then the basil is up there.
No, but seriously, I really thought that,
I thought pesto was pine nuts, not walnuts.
All right, let's get it in there.
Okay, give me the can.
This is only 300.
Green nuts are disgusting.
Oh, please, sucks at game, so I can laugh.
That's been happening for the last,
probably hour and a half.
And then it's a little bit of pepper and a little bit of salt.
Only five grams of pepper.
Two, three, four, five.
Salt, here, fun.
Oh, that's good, now I just need fresh basil.
240 grams of fresh basil.
Fresh basil, hey, don't break.
All right, more basil.
A little bit more basil, please.
Sing the raid song.
Raid, raid, sing the raid song.
We got a raid, who is it?
Raid song, all right, raid.
Who raided, I didn't see it, who raid?
Raid, raid, raid, raid, raid.
Raid, raid, raid, raid, we got a raid.
Raid, raid, raid, we got a raid.
We got a raid, we got a fucking raid.
Raid, we got a fucking raid.
You lied, there's nobody here.
Presto, Amelia Watson raid.
Amelia Watson, he said it, said what?
He said it, what are you doing?
What's wrong with you guys?
Did I get one guide again?
Did I read a one guy thing and I said,
what did I do?
Raid, raid from Marlon Brando?
Oh my God.
If only cleaning was this easy, even with glass.
God damn it, Avril Lavigne raid.
Oh, I wanna listen to that song so bad right now,
don't you?
Oh, how bad do you wanna listen to that song?
How badly do you want me to turn that song
on and just fucking jam out to it?
So bad right now.
But we're no longer allowed to enjoy music.
I have to pay a music executive like fucking $40
in a dark alleyway to listen to music anymore.
Why is it like buying drugs now?
Correction, 40,000.
Okay, so my basil, my pesto is ready.
I got my marinara, my Alfredo, my pesto
and that shit, that's all right, I'm ready to go.
Maybe, maybe I need to make some more cheese.
Let's go get mozzarella, running out of cheese.
Gordon Ramsay raid, salmon, tender.
Turn it around, crisp.
Off the pan, tender.
Why do I have so many bread pans?
Top this shit up.
I thought this was dough, I'm gonna roll it out.
That was bad impression, too quiet.
Sorry, my parents are in the other room, dude, fuck.
You fucking donkey.
That was just me saying that.
I wasn't even going Ramsey, that was just me doing that.
Shrek.
Do a different, better voice.
Hey, come on, what am I?
What is this?
Do a different, better voice.
I gotta clean my fucking castle up or whatever this place is.
Get this out of here, I don't even use it.
Why is everything silent?
All right, I don't even care if it's dirty.
Let's go, I'm leaving.
I'm ready for the new day, let's go.
Remember the three voices guy?
No, I've got at least six.
Negative 320, whatever.
New voices for us.
What do you want?
Call them, do Avril Lavigne?
I can't do Avril Lavigne.
Do Bill Clinton.
Let me just tell you.
No, no, no, no, sit down, sit down.
I did not have sex with that woman, I did not.
Okay, Michael Scott.
I, you know, I can't even,
you're all in big trouble, all of you here.
Okay, by the way, I've not seen one episode of The Office,
so I have no idea what he talks like.
I just was guessing based on like his face.
I've seen it in the Netflix trailer.
I'm not, I'm serious, I've not watched The Office.
I've not, that was Adam Sandler.
I don't even, that's just like Steve Carell.
I don't even know, The Office sucks.
I didn't say that, this person did.
Get him.
No, we're not doing impression speed run again.
It's a, okay, hold on, there's a pizza in here already.
They're right, I gotta get rid of this pizza.
Upset your stream any percent run.
World record?
No, I don't wanna cause like a bunch of problems.
I'm like playing my pizza game.
Do Goku.
No, no, all right, I'm playing.
I'm playing, I'm playing, I'm playing, I'm playing,
I'm playing.
Do Larry David.
No, let me ask you something, let me ask you something.
When you do, everything's just a version of Adam Sandler.
That's, I've noticed that.
It's just.
No, don't you want to die?
Oh, I don't want you to die.
I don't need, I don't need, I don't need Goku.
All right.
If the person that you like,
if somebody that you think is cool,
like a TV actor or something,
and they make a loud noise with the back of their throat,
I'm all for it.
All right, let's get a pizza.
You said Goku?
All right, pesto pizza, let's go.
No, it's not.
Okay, Margarita in New York, the game crashed.
Margarita in New York style.
Ooh, Yoda.
No, no, all right.
There was one person in the chat that just said,
shut the fuck up and play the game.
And I'm going to listen to that one.
That's a one guy moment.
All right, fine.
A final Garfield impression.
No, I was just going to go,
Yoda, no, no.
That guy was rude.
Rude, but he might have a point.
Which by the way, nobody gets to win on my channel
unless it's me, ban that person.
He's right though.
I am not stalling right now.
The game is hanging.
I'm waiting for it to come back.
Think he in the brain?
Same thing we're going to do every day, Pinty.
Try to take over the world.
Ah, ah, oh, Zoinks.
I don't know what he's, I forget.
I actually forget what he sounds like.
I know it's something like that.
Oh, it's something, I don't know.
It's Narf, whatever, not Zoinks.
It's Shaggy.
No, no, don't, you clipped it
and it's going to be embarrassing
for the rest of my life, whatever.
Why is it still hanging?
Do something funny.
Hold on, let me,
why is the game with the crash?
Do something fucking funny.
Hurry up, do something funny, dude.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
Uh-uh.
Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack.
Plus two.
No, you can't, it can't be that easy.
All right, seriously, why is it still hanging?
Shut up and play.
I'm trying to play the game right now.
All right, I promise.
All right, I'm going to add debt if I don't play.
If I do not make a full five-star pizza
by stream hours of three hours and 20,
wait, hold on, this has to,
this can't hang anymore, hold on.
If there is not a five-star pizza
by three hours and 30 seconds, 30 minutes of this stream
and I will owe six dollars to the debt.
But I would love to wait.
The game right now is crashed
and I'm waiting for it to respond.
That's a deal, okay?
Do the pizza tier list.
I might have to close the program
because I need to get on this now.
It took like a minute before it came back last time.
No, not six billion.
I said six, I don't know, six million.
And why is it opening the phone in this game?
Crash it.
All right, I'm giving it 10 seconds before I restart it.
It's the screen time.
All right, 10 seconds and I'm gone
and I'm going to restart it.
You don't have a TI?
No, I don't have a TI.
Here it comes, five seconds.
Come on, please, come on, do it.
All right, I'm restarted, close it.
I'm restarting it.
Come on, I can't even get out of the game.
What the hell?
Oh, okay, it took a while.
Pizza tier list.
No, no, no, no, no.
I like want to play this.
We'll do pizza tier list next time.
Otto, what's the matter?
You need something?
What do you need?
What do you need, Otto?
What is it?
What is it, Mr. Otto?
Let me, he needs something, hold on.
You need something?
He doesn't need something.
Let me see what he wants.
I'll be right back.
Hey, you get the VRB screen again.
This music does not really,
this music doesn't really fit with the artwork, does it?
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
It kind of does.
Face, I hate that face so much, more than anything.
Late night's, last night's chat logs.
Oh, but where's Otto?
How come Cheeto is in Otto's bed?
Love it.
What about Cat-Germa?
Cat-Boy-Germa?
What?
What about Cat-Boy?
He doesn't know.
Is the Nightwing shirt, I still have that.
Giant rat that hides all the rocks.
Did that show up?
Cat-Boy.
All right, I love this thing so much.
I just consider it all day.
What, is that a real gorilla?
No.
Look at the little shit post.
LMAO.
All right, let's get back into pizza.
Kind of like a cookie, kind of like a pizza.
I like to call it a cookie-tza.
Kathy, are you gonna feed me or what?
Oh, I forgot, nobody watches every infomercial
from like 20 years ago.
Sorry.
All right, let's make a pizza.
Okay, this one is just meat.
Don't crash.
Okay, small pizza.
You want buffalo mozzarella and Italian sausage.
Okay, I can do that.
Small New York dough.
This is New York dough right here.
There's a small right there.
Give me the small, please.
Small.
New York.
That's my tray.
Let me, first of all, hold on.
This is gonna get in the way.
It's actually gonna get in the way.
Okay, marinara.
Nice.
It kind of looks like one of those jelly cookies.
I love those things.
Okay, buffalo mozzarella.
I don't have, do I have buffalo mozzarella?
I gotta cut it up.
I need a tray.
I have so many trays.
Where are they?
Oh, that chops up.
What else do I get?
Italian sausage.
Do I have Italian sausage?
I don't, I don't think I do.
All right, give me the tray.
I need Italian sausage.
Do I?
Wait, I have chicken and salami.
Fuck.
Italian sausage, Italian sausage, Italian sausage.
Italian sausage, let's go.
What up?
I need another container.
And then basil leaf is already up there.
Buffalo mozzarella.
That's not that much, but whatever.
I'll deal with it.
Okay, here we go.
So I need buffalo mozzarella, 120 grams.
Let's go.
Buffalo mozzarella, 120.
Nice.
And Italian sausage, which is over here.
This is 30 grams.
Five, 10, 15, 20, 25, 30.
Okay.
The basil leaf, 12 grams.
Six, nine, 12.
All right.
And that's New York and that's small.
I think this is gonna be good.
This is gonna be a good pizza.
What is already in there?
All right, feed this.
What'd I say, five, right?
It might be five, it might be pretty good.
This pizza's been in there for a full 48 hours.
All right, the one that I care about is the small one.
I'm not gonna press Q, no.
Holy shit, I have a head.
Okay, almost.
And it's perfect.
Now, get it up.
Nice.
That looks good.
That looks pretty good.
This is it.
Okay, we've got a special.
Buy one, get one free.
Wait, we bought a small pizza
and you're giving us a large pizza for free?
Yep.
Okay, plate.
It's ugly?
No, it's not.
That's beautiful.
What's wrong with this?
I would eat this right now if I could.
Looks crispy, it looks done, it looks yummy,
it looks perfect.
That's a five-star pizza.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Five-star pizza.
Mm-hmm.
What's next?
Well, let's do the beginning two.
Double it up.
All right, we're gonna meet, I have three now.
We can do three.
This is medium, large, medium.
All right, so two medium pizzas, one large pizza.
A full pizza in the trash.
That's next level.
Okay, what's the dough?
This is a Neapolitan, New York, large New York,
two medium Neapolitan, large New York,
two medium Neapolitan, medium, and medium.
Roll this up.
Unique New York.
Is that a tongue twister you want me to do?
Why is this small?
Why is it small?
Yeah, you saw me pick up medium.
Medium.
What the fuck?
All right, are they all marinara?
Oh, this is marinara, this is marinara.
All marinara, let's get that one, two, three.
One, two, three.
Just tip the bag, okay, just tip the bag over.
Just like dump it on there.
Why do this with the ladle?
Is there not enough sauce on here?
Are they getting any more sauce?
That's all right, it's not bad.
All right, now they all, they all have cheese.
This is, what's with the double?
Okay, this is no cheese on one of the mediums.
No cheese on one of the mediums.
Okay, no cheddar cheese on the big one.
So cheddar cheese cut.
I don't have any of that.
I need bacon too.
I need cheese and bacon.
Cheese and bacon and what about the other margarita?
Also, okay, there's cut mozzarella and basil leaf.
Okay, cut mozzarella, basil leaf, I can do that right now.
Was it 120?
It was 120, right?
Okay, and then basil, 420, right.
It was 100, fuck, 124.
That's fine, whatever, a little bit extra cheese, it's okay.
This other medium pizza is garlic and basil, 32, 24.
Cool, garlic, that's sweet corn, nevermind.
32, bang, bang, bang, bang.
Good, that one's done.
Now I need bacon, bacon and cheddar.
I need cut bacon.
Where's the bacon?
Bacon, bacon, bacon, bacon, bacon.
Cut bacon, bacon, bacon, bacon.
Well, here's cheddar and there's bacon.
All right, well, cut bacon.
I need another thing.
Can I just mix them together?
All right, where's that cheese?
I threw it up here.
It looks like good bacon on the floor.
I don't see it anywhere.
Oh, there it is.
They wanted it chopped up, right?
Chopped cheddar cheese.
Make a little Caesar's pizza, just get some cardboard.
I love this kind of cheese.
I love when it's sliced.
I love the just cheddar slices.
It's my favorite.
All right, let's make this.
So this one is 120 of cheddar, 96 of bacon.
We're putting like Kraft Singles on here.
This is kind of weird, right?
Okay, bacon, 96.
This is just a Plinko machine.
96?
This is a very ugly pizza.
Okay, and then basil, right?
Basil leaf, 36 and that's it.
And then we're gonna start to just cook them.
Or it's a match three iPad game.
All right, let's get it in there.
Nice and hot, burning hot oven.
Ban the customer who ordered that.
Okay, cool, let's load it up.
I'm a shirtless.
Yeah, there's like two or three pictures of me
with no clothes on on the internet.
Okay, I'm making that sound like it's way more in
than what, you know what I mean?
Like, oh yeah, of course there's pictures of me.
They're like naked on the internet, they're there.
No, I mean like there's like a few stills of me
without clothes.
You nudes leaked.
Make a peanut butter and fluff pizza.
That sounds kind of good actually.
Okay, in three, two, one, they're done.
Get them out, get them out, get them out, get them out,
get them out, get them out, get them out,
out, out, out, out, out, out, out, out.
Don't, get it, get it, get it, get it, get it,
get it, get it, get it, get it.
This doesn't even look like it's cooked.
There is nothing to cook.
Yeah, I don't, I know that getting a pizza
without cheese on it, people do.
You know, you just get the sauce and the,
it's a little burnt, but whatever.
I don't, I'm not into that.
And almost done.
At link, please.
Hold on.
What, you made me like five times smaller?
Is that the thing?
I don't get it, is that the joke?
I'm just like, I'm 50% smaller than I was.
Well, I don't get it.
I look like, I look like dopey.
Did you mess with this image?
You did, you did.
You have alien eyes.
What, what?
Don't knock that over.
All right, these are ready to be served.
All right, we need two medium pans.
I like to call it making it great.
What's making it great mean?
Well, we here at Pizza Hut.
Making it great means we get it ready for the customer,
correct every time.
Don't forget the fairy dust.
What's fairy dust?
Well, it's another way for us to making it great
here at Pizza Hut.
You sprinkle the fairy dust on the pizza
right at the very end.
Sprinkle it right at the very end?
Yeah, it's a secret recipe.
It's actually just Parmesan cheese
and we just pretended something else.
Oh, cool.
What pizza, which one was this one, meat?
Oh, you waited a long time.
Sorry, you waited for perfection.
You know how many times they delayed Smash Brothers Brawl?
And that game was considered
probably one of the worst ones.
This is the Neapolitan pizza.
Boy, I need a, it is the worst one.
I enjoyed it though.
It was all right.
It was still fun to play.
Subspace Emissary blows World of Light out of the water.
World of Light was cool, but it was,
it was like too much.
This is the cheese one, right?
Nope.
They made such a, oh, wait a minute.
Chili Peppers.
Pepperoni, I'm gonna make my favorite pizza, finally.
Finally, it took like fucking four hours.
Prove alone on pizza.
I mean, I guess you could say that Smash Brothers
is more about playing the game,
Smash Brothers, like fighting game style
than doing a single player campaign.
And they just added a ton of shit to do.
So it's just kind of extra stuff, I guess.
But even Smash Ultimate.
What are they?
A hundred fucking characters in that game?
I didn't even unlock them all.
Fungi, Fungi, hmm, hmm.
I don't have mushrooms.
Time to get mushrooms.
How many mushrooms, I'm just gonna, let's chop them up.
Give me a basket.
Fungi, make a Bunger?
Now, I'm gonna make my favorite pizza.
We'll make my pizza and their pizza at the same time.
Let me make sure that I have everything.
I do.
That's gonna be so delicious, you have no idea.
You're gonna get fired?
Okay, you can't fire me, dad.
My dad owns this place, I'm not gonna get fired.
He's gonna walk in here and he's gonna put his hand on his
head and he's gonna go,
then he's gonna clean all this up
and then I'm gonna come to work tomorrow.
All right, what's like a good thin crust?
Would Neapolitan or would New York be better for thin crust?
New York?
Okay, so I'm gonna go with a large pizza
because I like, I order a large pizza.
Anytime I get a pizza, it's always a big, long, large,
thin pizza.
And how we start off my favorite pizza
is we're gonna start off with just,
this is marinara, just marinara sauce.
I like my marinara sauce to be very much
under the cheese, by the way.
I like the cheese to be really sort of
on top of the marinara sauce.
Oh, oh, that's just normal.
All right, yes, yes, yes.
I'm just doing my favorite pizza, okay?
That's just how pizza's made.
This is my favorite pizza, okay?
That eye is looking at me.
That eye is looking at me, did you see that?
That eye was staring at me.
I don't like this, I'm thrown away.
Okay, I'm gonna do it again.
A good layer of sauce.
I like the sauce to be tangy, too.
Some people don't like a tangy pizza sauce, I do.
I think it compliments the pepperoni.
Oh, I just told you what my pizza was.
Okay, so that looks good.
I don't actually like the thick mozzarella cut.
I like the shredded mozzarella.
I like it to be shredded all over it.
And none of this bullshit where you can sit,
no, no, I want it all over it.
I ran out.
I need more.
Get in the cheese grater.
All right, go.
Cat hair pizza.
It looks like that before it goes into the oven, all right?
Relax.
Nice and cheesy, really get a good layer.
Is it floating?
Why is it floating?
Okay, that looks all right.
I just want a nice good layer.
Then comes the pepperoni, which I don't even have up here.
Pepperoni.
And I like the small pepperonis, the little ones.
Not the mini mini ones, but just not the huge ones.
I don't hate the huge ones,
but I would rather have the smaller ones.
This guy's wicked horny.
Shut up.
I'm not, I'm actually not.
Why am I making a joke like I am?
I'm not.
Shut up.
What am I doing that for?
That's not, all right.
I'm making a pizza.
Then I put the pepperoni on there,
and then I shred the cheese up.
And then I like a lot more cheese than normal.
Maybe a little bit of extra cheese, not too much though.
Holy shit, this guy's wicked fucking horny.
I'm what?
What happened?
Okay, let's pepperoni.
Here it is.
And I like when the pepperoni is in a spiral out,
because then you get a piece of pepperoni
on almost every single bite of your pizza.
I ran out.
God damn it.
I'm trying to make my favorite fucking pizza.
Get back.
Why are so many things knocked over on the floor?
I don't know, man, because cooking is hard.
No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
Otherwise you wouldn't be paying people tons of money
at restaurants to make it for you.
Okay, we're not done.
I also like there to be just a dash,
just like a whack of garlic.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is my favorite pizza.
Oh, it's not done yet.
It's not done yet.
Stop rushing me.
Is he drinking it?
A little just drizzle, drizzle,
and I can't do it in this game, but you know what I mean?
You go wing, wing, wing, wing, wing, wing, wing, wing.
Okay, you know, you ever see unwrapped on Food Network?
You know those machines that do that to the chocolates?
They just go like blim, blim, blim, blim, blim, blim,
make like a little line up, down, up, down, up, down.
Olive oil.
Get it in there.
And you make sure that oven is hot, hot, hot, hot, hot,
hot, hot, hot, hot, hot.
500 degrees, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot oven.
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot.
Don't put it in there unless it's fucking smoking hot.
Hot, very hot.
Why is he talking to us like kids?
I just said the F word like four times.
What?
All right, nice and hot.
There it is.
Oh yes, it, magic, I was all right.
Get it in there, burning hot oven.
Yes, you let that, and you, and I'm sorry,
some of the people are gonna freak out about this.
When that bar fills to green, I ain't taking it out.
I'm not taking it out.
I'm gonna wait till it's a little bit overdone.
Just a hair, just enough.
Custom robo waiting room, it's been like eight months, dude.
Look, already looks good.
Already looks perfect.
All right, don't take it out, leave it in.
Get it out, get it out, get it.
Dude, take it out, take it out, take it, leave it in.
Don't touch it, leave it in.
Okay, all right, all right, all right, leave it in,
leave it in, leave it in, leave it in,
leave it in, leave it in, leave it in.
Hoo, it's perfect.
That's the best pizza I've made all night.
It's perfect.
And I don't put, no, no basil, no oregano.
No, no, no, no, no, you leave it alone
and you eat it just like that.
And you can tell when it's right,
when you go with the pizza cutter.
If you hear that sound, you've done it right.
And then when you pick it up and pull it out,
a little bit of the cheese is just running off the sides.
And you bite into it and you bite it.
It's a hot bite.
You get a little bit of that oil from the pepperoni.
The mozzarella flows in there, the garlic is there.
And you, the best part.
And then like after you bite into it, you go,
and then you spit it out.
You spit like the, you bite into it,
you let it smear out of your mouth onto the plate
because it's too hot.
And you didn't wait long enough.
And then you go, all right, whatever, whatever, whatever,
whatever, whatever, whatever, whatever, whatever.
Nice.
At least the pizza got out.
Whatever, at least the pizza got out.
All right, I need to make the other pizza.
Wait, should I make my second favorite pizza?
I feel like I should.
Okay, second favorite pizza, incoming.
Do I have it?
Do I have the ingredients for it?
I don't.
I need something else.
Plain cheese pizza, that's good a lot of the time.
I could, you know, I could do one of my favorite pizzas.
I could do one of my favorites.
Yeah, sure.
Okay, I already have bacon, what am I doing?
We'll start, we'll go with the medium.
What about the customer?
He's just sitting here waiting for his pizza
and he hears me talking to somebody on the phone.
And I'm making the person on my phone my favorite pizzas
that they're not going to eat.
Hey, it was like 14 bucks for that pizza.
Just hold on, I'm telling somebody my favorite pizzas.
You'll be up soon.
Okay, so the next one, use the same dough, we'll do medium.
Now we're gonna do a small because,
no, I'm gonna use the dough I have, medium.
Coming up next is one of my other favorites.
And that starts, it starts with,
as you probably could have guessed, marinara.
Only this time we're gonna do something a little different.
This time, we're not going to put the cheese on first.
What we're going to do, are you ready?
We're gonna put the, I want grated onions, not cut onions.
Grated onions, not cut onions, excuse me.
Well, okay, you know what I mean?
I want them like, okay, no,
they're actually already like that, okay.
Onions, onions, onions, onions, onions, onions,
a lot of onions, onions, onions, onions, onions, onions.
And then after that, we do the cheese.
This is mozzarella and a little bit of bacon.
No, it's not a toenail pizza, relax.
Fingernails and toenails.
God damn it, man.
Just, that's just what the game looks like, okay?
Don't make me turn the music back on, I will.
I need a, I need a, oh, there's one on the ground.
We got our onions.
Are you happy, how do you have the onions?
Are you glad you have the onions?
Crispy onions, they gotta be crispy.
Are you happy you have the onions?
All right, now I need the, wait, where'd it go?
Wait, what?
Wait, did I put onion in there?
What happened to the cheese?
Oh, it's not, there it is.
Okay, let's go.
So now the mozzarella and the onions
blend together a little bit.
I want little clusters too.
Clusters, clusters, clusters, clusters, clusters, clusters,
extra cheese, extra cheesy, cheesy, cheesy, cheesy.
And then bacon.
Although I'm not a fan of this style,
I'd rather it be like cubed or like finely chopped bacon.
Now, if there were peppers here too,
I would put peppers on this too, just green peppers.
So you get that onions, the onions get caramelized.
You get the bacon, you get the, I mean, why?
Well, no, no, Doug, you don't need garlic on here.
Adley, you tell me how good this looks when it comes out.
Cubed bacon, yeah, it's just easier
because you don't, it's easier to bite into.
I'm gonna make a fucking fucked up pizza next.
I'm gonna chop up, I'm just gonna make like a turkey,
I'm gonna make it like a chicken.
Put wood on it.
This isn't the fucked up pizza.
Oh, you know what?
Hamburger and onion's one of my other favorites,
but I don't have hamburger and onion,
so we're gonna do bacon and onion.
That's not pizza, what?
And again, we're not gonna take this out,
yet we're gonna leave it in for a few minutes.
Don't put hamburger on pizza, why?
Ground, the ground hamburger you don't like?
I always thought that was a, I thought people liked that.
There you go.
You see, you've got, this one doesn't look as good
because the game's like that.
What you have here is the onions are underneath the cheese.
You get like onion surprise.
It does look like little dog poops.
Dog poop pizza, okay.
Make that IRL.
Okay, let's make a super cheese pizza.
I wanna make a grilled cheese pizza.
Can I put two, I'm gonna put two pizzas
on top of each other.
Yes, that's what I'm doing.
Let us make the pizza.
You will in a minute.
I wanna make my grilled cheese pizza.
The grilled cheese pizza is gonna be,
I want just, I just want tomato sauce.
Right in the middle, tomato sauce, right in the middle.
And then we're gonna get the cheese slices.
I need a lot more than this.
In my basket.
Is that cheddar?
Making it, yeah, I'm making a grilled cheese pizza.
All right, slice it up.
What's wrong with this?
These bonkers, I'm making one, why is there bacon in here?
Get this fucking bacon out of here.
Grind this up, grate it.
No, I wanted slices for the, for like a grilled cheese.
By the way, people are gonna be like,
what do you, what the fuck is, this is like,
what, you think this is so weird?
I guarantee you there's like some weird,
stupid food blog channel that's like,
whoa, look, we got the weirdest thing ever.
We got a grilled cheese pizza.
You don't think this exists somewhere?
You don't think that they took like two bites of that
and then ate no more of it?
Ungodly amount of cheese.
More cheese, more cheese needed
for the grilled cheese pizza.
Oh, that's a lot of cheese.
Two kilogram, how much, okay, how much is a kilogram?
This is a lot.
This is actually like an extreme amount, isn't it?
100 pounds of cheese pizza.
If you walked in here and the person
that you saw doing this was doing this,
I would think that they were serving this
as an appetizer plate.
Like you had a, you were, this is like the amount
of cheese that you would expect on a plate
if there was a wedding party out here.
It's just cheddar slices.
What a shitty wedding appetizer.
Oh, I wonder what they're gonna have out on the serving tray.
Oh, bacon wrapped scallops.
Dates, no, no, it's slices of cheddar cheese
out of the package.
You know, a long time ago, I really wanted,
and I don't know, you might think I'm insane,
but like I've heard people doing like fun items,
like oh, like fast food items or like,
oh, we have a bunch of McDonald's French fries or something.
I was like, you know what, that's kind of cool.
If I ever got married, I think it would be kind of fun
to have like, I don't know, like a McDouble station.
No, not like, okay, and that is sort of like it,
but all right, listen, just for fun,
like it's not the dinner, it's not the meal.
You could just have one if you want.
Just a single, no, not a double, not a McDouble, sorry.
Just a plain McDonald's cheeseburger in the wrapper.
And like there's a person walking around
with a waiter or a waitress that has like a stack
of single McDonald's cheeseburger.
It'd be like, I don't know, if I was at a wedding
and they had like single McDonald's cheeseburgers,
because think of how fucking hungry you are
before the wedding is going on.
You gotta wait a long ass time to eat at a wedding,
a long time.
Sometimes you're starving
and you gotta wait another six hours before you eat.
And sometimes the people that are catering the wedding
take even longer and it's like a bunch of delays.
And then finally you get your salmon
that comes out, right?
I'm sorry, but after the ceremony is over
by like 11, 12 o'clock in the afternoon, I'm ready to eat.
And I'm not ready to eat like one shrimp
that's on a skewer that you walk by with.
That's not enough.
If you had a single McDonald's cheeseburger
just walking around, I'd be like, holy shit, this is awesome.
But this is the best wedding I've ever been to in my life.
This is incredible.
No judgments, no bullshit.
Just like, oh yeah, there's just single
McDonald's cheeseburgers.
Yeah, give me two of those right now.
I'll take two right now.
And then guess what?
I'm gonna eat the dinner later too.
I'm gonna eat the foals, salmon,
and whatever, the chicken breast.
You're a corporate, no I'm not, I like that idea.
How, that's not a shill.
I like McDonald's cheeseburgers.
What, what's so wrong?
Okay, sure, everybody yell at me.
I like McDonald's cheeseburgers.
I like them.
I like them, okay?
I really like them.
I like, and I like a lot, I like how they smell.
Okay, listen to me.
Okay, I gotta settle down.
I gotta settle down.
I'm adding more and more people to the list of,
is everything okay in Jeremy's world?
Yes, everything is fine.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Every time I talk about this,
I add like another group of people
that are like concerned about my well-being.
I would do the McDonald's thing, I would, for real.
No jokes, no fucking around.
Oh, okay, let me, wait a minute.
I want you guys to yell at me over this one too.
Forget about single McDonald's cheeseburgers, great idea.
What if it was Pizza Hut breadsticks?
So many of you guys talking so much crap right now,
you would know, no way would you be like,
what do you mean no, what?
It's worse?
What about the red lobster rolls?
What about the cheddar biscuits?
I just need one more layer over here.
Olive Garden breadsticks?
Yeah, I mean something like that,
like just like a breadsticks from one of those restaurants.
Is that, okay, would that be good?
What if the soup, salad, and breadsticks
was the appetizer before the meal or the cocktail hour?
That would be awesome.
Yeah, all right, well none of you invited to my wedding.
I'm gonna have a wicked,
I'm gonna have McDonald's cheeseburgers,
I'm gonna have soup, salads, and breadsticks.
I'm gonna, and by the way, we're eating dessert first.
We're eating dessert first at my wedding.
That's right, ice cream first.
This is the kid wedding.
The kid, child wedding.
There's a Chuck E. Cheese.
But imagine if all you guys got invited to my wedding.
Imagine if I had 10,000 people on the guest list.
We would have to have that wedding
in like a toothpaste factory.
We'd have to stuff everybody in a bunch of like a warehouse,
like a stadium.
We would need like a thousand acres
of like factory warehouse space.
Each chair has a box of toothpaste under it.
What?
Have a wedding at Chuck E. Cheese.
Maybe you guys don't understand.
Wedding at Chuck E. Cheese is like
one of the biggest marketing ploys ever.
You know how much money they would give me to do that?
You know how much money I would get
to have a wedding at Chuck E. Cheese on camera?
That's gotta be worth tons of money
because I'm throwing away a huge part of my life there.
I'm literally disintegrating
one of an incredibly major important thing
in my entire life.
It would just be going away.
Five nights at Freddy's, Chuck E. Cheese says poggers
and he would officiate the wedding and he better talk.
I'm gonna be real, he better talk
and he better give us free tokens for getting married.
20 free tokens to the bride and groom.
Okay, all right, all right, let's make the grilled cheese.
Three basic ingredients of grilled cheese
and you're forgetting one of them.
What's the other ingredient to a grilled cheese
besides cheese, bread, and a tomato?
What's the secret ingredient?
Butter?
Yes, sorry, I didn't coat it with butter.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Tomato on a grilled cheese is a staple.
What are you guys talking about?
What?
Hold on, wait, wait, wait.
Let me back up here.
No, I agree with you.
I don't like tomato on my grilled cheeses
but I know that a lot of people,
am I gaslighting myself?
I know that people put tomato on grilled cheese all the time.
I did it because if I didn't put a tomato
on the grilled cheese, I thought people would be like,
where the fuck's the tomato?
That's why I put it on.
All right, I need butter.
I just need a butter sauce.
Butter, it's a yeast.
I have to buy it, right?
I'm actually really glad that didn't break.
Oh shit, there's a bunch of crap in here.
Trash, trash, trash, trash, trash it, trash it.
Crap, crap, crap, crap.
Dang it, darn it, dumb.
There we go.
Here you go.
Here's your other ingredient.
Here's your butter that I didn't coat the bread with.
Get it in there.
Oh shit, is this still cooking?
No, it's not cooking, okay.
All right, grilled cheese, let's go.
Too hot, too hot, too hot, not that hot.
Lighter, incinerate this.
No, why?
That took so long to place at all.
All right, here we go.
Get over there.
Make it talk.
I can't make it talk.
Hey, hey kids.
You want me to make it say hey kids?
It just like scoop slammed it.
What?
Why did it bounce off?
Oh shit, it almost went on.
I'm trying just to flip it over so it's a grilled cheese.
Wait, okay, hold on.
Don't go in the trash.
Fuck, come on.
Actually kind of looks kind of good.
That's close, hold on.
Scrape it a little.
This thing's so huge.
I have to do this on the floor.
Oh, look at that.
Here we go, almost done.
Shit, it's almost there.
Come on, get up.
Get off.
I don't care.
Don't, whatever.
All right, what's an actual pizza I need to do?
I don't know, let's find out.
Oh, this guy's waiting a long time for this.
I hate this pizza.
Oh, it sucks.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
I've been waiting like two, three hours
for my mushroom pizza.
Right on that, sir.
Okay, I need mushrooms.
I gotta get mushrooms, mushrooms, mushrooms.
Closing.
He just has both of his arms hanging down onto the window
just waiting for it to close.
I didn't even.
This is like the super rich, rich kid
that wanted a pizza shop.
And instead of just bringing the kid
to like Plato class where they can just mess around,
his parents bought him a pizza shop
so he could make his own fucked up pizzas.
Okay, button mushrooms.
I need more of these.
This is like, it's like an old Macaulay Culkin movie.
Wait, was Macaulay Culkin in Richie Rich?
Or was that a different,
was that a different kid?
There's cheddar in here.
There's so much cheese in here, hold on.
You're a dinosaur?
I mean, Richie Rich came out in like 1995.
That's not that far away.
That's not that long ago.
I think I called a dinosaur.
What is this?
That's older than I am.
So?
All right, let's make this dude's pizza.
So he wants a Neapolitan marinara and some cut mozzarella
with a small, oh, look at that.
Perfect size right here.
And there's a two week old marinara.
Never coming back here again.
Ever.
Was it 60?
Okay, then we have button mushrooms.
Where the heck are those?
He wants 30 grams.
Okay.
And then basil.
Why does everybody put basil on all their pizzas?
What?
Stop, basil on everything.
Basil, basil, basil, basil, basil, basil.
No, don't do that.
All right, that's it.
Sir?
There you go.
It's a garnish?
Learn to have taste.
Oh, so it's a thing I remove from my food before I eat it.
I call that a waste.
You're gonna put parsley on the side?
No, no, no, get it out of here.
I don't want that.
You don't eat, what am I, eat parsley?
What am I, a rabbit?
Ye, I can't even read what you said,
but it's like, what?
You, I have to.
I don't even care.
Somebody says you fuck like one.
Here's your pizza, sir.
Thank you, I'm sorry for waiting so long.
I had to get frustrated.
I had to get frustrated making a grilled cheese.
The thing is, I'm gonna be like,
sorry, sorry, sir, here you go, sir.
It'll never happen again.
I'm really sorry about that.
Here's your pizza, free of charge.
He's gonna take a bite.
He's gonna go, give me that.
Oh my God, oh my God, this is unbelievable.
This is the best pizza I've ever had in my whole life.
It was worth the wait.
It's like a SpongeBob.
Oh, I, wait, hold on.
I can put, I can make a ketchup pizza.
Look at all these things.
Oh, here we go.
Time to make half the people mad
and half the people happy.
Lettuce, capers, tuna?
I don't know about all this.
I thought this was a loaf of bread for a second.
I was like, what is this doing over here?
Okay, it's not that dirty.
You don't even get points off for being dirty anyway,
so why do I even care?
Okay, I wanna go, let me see that stuff.
Spices, lick, oh my God, garlic powder, cinnamon,
brown mustard, oregano, paprika, ketchup.
Oh, gross.
On pizza, just on, oh, gross.
This really is gonna become like a kid,
like just a child's dream.
I need, what do I have for dough?
What do I actually have left for dough?
What do I have left for dough?
Not much.
Let chat make a pizza.
Okay, medium dough.
What do you want?
Let's make a pizza.
Click maps, click maps,
that's gonna be really, really hard.
Pineapple, all right.
What kind of cheese?
Mayo, I don't have mayo, I haven't unlocked it.
It's like a, there's a comedy prop.
It's not even filled with anything.
Why do I have this?
It's empty.
Oh, he's bored?
No, I'm not, I'm not, I'm just playing around.
I'm just playing around, hold on.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not,
I'm not bored, I'm not, I'm just playing around.
This is just dead air.
Well, I'm focused, I was focusing on dumping
a gasoline chamber into this chamber.
He hates streaming.
No, I don't.
Stop it, stop it.
Silence them.
All right, that's enough.
Holy shit, it didn't break.
And then now we need yeast.
Let's kind of see what happens, to be honest.
Okay, you've got salt.
Ooh, right, right, right, right.
Oh, it's actually stuck in there.
I can't make any more dough, I don't think ever again.
Unless I, hold on, bingo.
All right, I'm gonna actually, let's, let's, hold on.
Clean up a little bit.
I wanna actually do, I wanna do one more day of pizzas
and I'm gonna actually do it well.
I wanna do an actual day of pizza.
At least I got to make my favorite pizza.
Happy about that.
All right, I need, what do I need more of?
Let's see.
I have plenty of, plenty of chicken,
plenty of sweet corn, which nobody's tried to eat yet.
I could use more Italian sausages.
I could use more mushrooms.
I could use more bacon and marinara sauce
and just get all the meats.
So let's do a pepperoni, Italian sausages,
a prosciutto, a salami, more bacon,
some, whatever this is.
Gorgonzola, I'll take some gorgonzola, sure.
Capers, what else?
Some young artichokes, couple more.
I can have a tray of them.
Cherry tomatoes, just so I can have a tray of them.
Bunch of lettuce, shredded lettuce on pizza.
That's, I don't know about that.
That sounds kind of gross,
but I'm gonna get it nonetheless.
Tuna on pizza, that's, also I'm not a fan of that.
I don't think it seems kind of gross.
Like, just tuna, like raw tuna?
I don't know.
All right, now I gotta figure out
how I'm gonna wanna do with this.
I need counter space.
Okay, we're gonna do shredded lettuce.
I need a container.
I'm too lazy to go find one, so I'm just gonna buy one.
Well, I guess you can only chop the lettuce,
you can't shred it.
All of that's gonna go on the floor, mark my words.
Sure, I disagree.
Okay, that's enough lettuce.
Do you chop up the tuna fish or do you just,
what are you, shredded tuna?
I can't put this in it.
Why do I have, what's this for?
I can't chop it.
What can I do with it?
I can put it into the mixer?
Worst stream 20, what are you, wait, what?
What are you talking about?
You don't put it in the mixer.
What the fuck?
Why do you put it in the food processor?
So you just blend it up?
Wait a minute.
Okay, well, I lost that tuna.
But did somebody just say do something weird?
I just spent like 40 minutes
making a fucking grilled cheese pizza.
What?
Oh, there's still lettuce in there.
I missed the grilled cheese, do it again.
Oh, we're gonna make a second grilled cheese pizza.
Two, two grilled cheese pizzas.
And then artichokes.
I'm preparing for tomorrow, so I don't have to do this.
So I'm not gonna run around from place to place
and be like, oh my God, I need artichokes.
And I sprint down and pick up onions instead of artichokes
and I fuck the whole thing up.
That doesn't seem like a lot.
That's not enough.
That's just a can of capers.
All right, Italian sausages.
All right, let's go, go, go, all right, let's go.
You're making me wanna play this, it's pretty fun.
All right, give me a pizza.
I didn't even make any dough.
Oh, boy, I have this medium pizza here.
All right, I hope all the pizzas are mediums today.
You want Italian pizza.
Italian pizza is Neapolitan dough.
It's a medium marinara, salami.
I got all of that, let's go.
Roll it up.
Marinara sauce.
Do another comb stream, asshat.
Well, I'll tell you one way to make sure
that I don't do the thing you just said
is to immediately call me an asshat
after you request something.
That's the fastest way for me to go.
Nah, I don't think so.
That's like the fastest way for that to happen.
Okay.
Cut mozzarella, what's up here?
Hog.
Cut salami.
I think I still have, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
64 grams, done.
Italian sausages, I have a few left, don't I?
I do.
Sick.
50 grams of Italian sausages, do I have enough?
Please tell me I have enough.
I do.
And then cut chili peppers, I don't have the,
you want ketchup on there?
No, don't do it.
Pick it up though, disgusting.
Chili peppers, they are, okay.
How many does he want?
30 grams, he just want one, okay, chop it up.
Do another 3DO stream, asshat.
No, no, no, there's a fucking goddamn artichoke in there.
Fuck, this is why I needed to prepare.
Why can't I just reach out, reach in and take it out?
All right, I think I might have to put it on the floor.
They were right, all of it is on the floor,
but for very good reason, so I can see it better.
Just give me this, what are all these?
Stop calling him an asshat.
He's so mean, guys, why are you so mean?
What's with the meanness?
He's so mean.
Mean, mean, mean, mean, mean.
Artichokes, don't worry, I'm making it.
Your pizza's almost ready.
Play a children's game for three days in a row?
I think I've done that before.
So you want 30 grams of chili peppers, I can do that.
Should we put a ton of it like hidden
somewhere over here so he bites into it and goes, oh!
30, that's evil.
Is it evil?
You literally only play children's games.
That's not even accurate, you know it.
What do you mean it's not done?
Mozzarella, salami, there's olives on this damn thing.
I keep, anytime I see the word olive, I just glaze over it.
Quick, get it out, get it out, get it out, get it out.
Who even have, I have a jar of black olives somewhere.
Where is it?
Shit.
Olives, olives, olives, come on, come on, come on.
Oh shit, how do I take them out?
I, what do I, how do I, what do I put these?
I swear to God, if there's something in here already,
I'm gonna be very mad.
Thank God, okay, there's not.
We're good.
You're eating olives from the jar right now.
Nice, that's pretty cool.
Maybe they're good for you.
I just don't like them.
64 grams of black olives.
Holy fuck, that was too much.
Whatever.
Black olives on a pizza are bad.
It just, olives in general, I like, I love olive oil,
but black olives especially, they're very,
they're kind of, they're like acidic.
They have a super like soury kind of flavor to them.
They're like, bleh, not for me, not for me.
Black olives are better than green olives.
I actually kind of, I don't mind green olives.
Throw it on a chicouterie board or something.
That was a truth bomb, bro.
Thanks, I guess.
We have a new offer?
I don't click on new offer links unless it is confirmed
that it is a actual new offer.
It's official, official, official, official.
Okay, hold on.
We're saying it's official.
We're calling this an official, official.
Okay, let me look at it.
Let me see, what is it?
Limited time offer.
Sell as many pizzas as possible in one game day.
All profits paid 200 times off the debt.
How much?
Deal?
Is it a deal?
I got a deal.
Go.
It doesn't even matter what the pizzas are.
They're getting bread.
Oh no, I got my ketchup in the fucking onion tray.
What do you mean it doesn't count?
You didn't say I had to make their pizzas correctly.
You just said I had to make them.
And here's one right here.
How much is this worth?
How can I see the price?
Okay.
How much was it?
190 cents?
Oh, that's not very much times 200.
Okay, let's go.
Next up we have a mimosa pizza,
which is Alfredo sauce.
Is it a Neapolitan Alfredo?
It doesn't matter.
Give that back.
What are you doing?
Give this back.
What the hell?
Give my tray back.
What's going on?
Give me a fucking break.
Are you kidding me?
What's blocking?
Is something blocking it?
Something in the way?
Okay, mimosa.
You want onions on there.
You want bacon on there too?
I didn't even put any sauce on there.
Deal with it.
That's a turbo 985 special, onions and bacon.
What did you want on yours?
Oh, pesto?
You got it.
And way too many hot peppers,
so it's gonna burn the fuck out of your mouth
and you won't even be able to enjoy anything.
Pesto and hot peppers,
that's too much acidity in your mouth.
That'll be $12.
And I'm giving you a chicken breast.
You're just gonna have hot pie.
Okay, where are the potatoes?
You dumped out what was the contents of your shredder.
Okay, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Hurry, hurry.
Is anything gonna fit in there?
That's Timmy's school project.
It's like paper mache.
Yeah, you made a paper mache solar system.
It's like, Timmy, that does not look at all
like our galaxy, but you know, as you tried.
Hot oven, let's go.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Time?
Nope, no, hotter, hotter, hotter, hotter, hotter.
Take it out, it's ready.
Okay, it's ready to serve.
Does that go out the window?
Fuck.
I need to get the other one.
It's a tumbleweed.
It's like a chia pet.
All right, I need plates, plates, plates, quick.
All right, this is like a plant
that's in the corner of your office.
All right, who ordered the mimosa?
You just hear off in the distance.
$125.
Why would they eat it?
They didn't, they just saw it.
And this is a meat pizza.
What's next?
More, more, more, more, more.
Oh, no, I didn't like it.
I liked the sauce, though.
The cheese was not very good.
But I was a big fan of the sauce.
There was no sauce on that pizza.
It was just shredded up hair.
Oh, take it out.
Where's mine?
That actually looks so awful, for real.
I need another piece of dough.
Here we go.
Roll it.
I don't know what, you have lettuce, too.
And artichokes.
And I have a lot of sweet corn,
so might as well use it.
And I guess you can have, here, have some like,
no, have some Alfredo sauce.
And bacon, shit.
Okay, I'm gonna do the middle finger in bacon.
Can I?
Not even close, but whatever.
I think I could get it, though.
You've hit a bacon ceiling.
I still have a shitload of chicken.
Whatever, I don't care.
Do you like this game,
or do you just have Stockholm syndrome?
No, it's fun.
All right, I have to spell fuck you out on this one.
I need more peppers.
Shit.
Or do I, though?
Do I, though?
No, I don't.
I can't put anything on here.
Oh, shit.
This is done.
Oh.
This looks like a dead bird.
It's disgusting.
It is.
I just put a dead bird on the pizza.
That's disgusting.
Oh, that's disgusting.
That is absolutely revolting.
It just looks like charcoal.
Well, we ran out of toppings.
We ran out of meat,
so might as well use some of the wood,
the charcoal on the bottom.
At least it'll be smoky.
Dude, the health department would elbow drop you.
Is this one done?
It is.
I think this is the end.
I can't even process this anymore.
Oh, okay.
No, no, I'm not done with the day.
I'm just saying, I think this is it.
No, I didn't.
I need this all medium pizzas.
Whoa, that almost hit my head.
Wait, was that a...
What was in there?
Okay, one, two, three.
What even is this?
This is what I feel like it would look like
if McDonald's started doing pizza.
What about the shit in the oven?
Oh, whatever, I'll get it.
Oh, that's a Caprice pizza.
What's in here?
Okay, you sicko.
I guess he liked it a little.
He just didn't like the cheese.
It's not burning.
It's not even...
I need to put wood in here.
Okay, this one's done.
This just looks like what a baby's food tray looks like.
An infant that you feed, like Cheerios do.
Baby spelling out fuck.
I can't, I can't even.
This is a cheese pizza.
Is there even cheese on the pizza?
Everything but cheese.
You ordered a cheese pizza.
You sure you didn't want corn and olives?
Whatever the fuck it was.
All right, I'm like Mr. Giggles right now.
I gotta calm down.
You ever sometimes even just kind of sit there and go,
you know, what would I actually do
if somebody served me that?
Here's what I would do.
I would turn around.
If somebody put this in front of me.
Here you go, sir and madam, here is your pizza.
I'd go, okay, well the way that you're like
being like a waiter guy.
Okay, where's the camera?
I would look around and be like,
there's probably a camera back here.
There's a hidden camera there, a hidden camera there.
Like you're like an actor waiter.
You already did that part.
You came over and you were like,
sir and madam, I'm over here with your pizza.
You're obviously an actor.
So that part is, you gave it away already.
It doesn't matter, they still paid for it.
Ow, my hand.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It kind of looks like a little guy holding like a brick.
It's like a little rock guy holding up a rock.
It's like a little dude
and he's holding a rock in his hand.
He's about to dunk the basketball.
Whoa, okay, cool.
I like that one.
I'm keeping this one.
Nobody can have this one, this one's mine.
How many orders do I have?
Four, I don't have any dough left.
Let me just do this.
Is it ketchup?
I can't just serve ketchup on a plate.
Look for dough.
We're looking for dough on the ground.
You see it, let me know.
Oh, there we go.
Tuna and ketchup, that's disgusting.
Oh, oh, I almost gagged.
Tuna, ketchup and milk.
Sure, why not?
This caused me physical harm thinking about this.
Oh boy.
So we have our ketchup and tuna sauce with milk based.
Oh no, out of ketchup.
That might be bad.
I can't just serve a piece of wood.
I wish I could.
It was even, oh, it was ketchup.
Oh, do you want ketchup in wood?
I feel like that's the kind of shit
that we're gonna be eating
when like the apocalypse happens.
Did you eat your, son, did you eat your wood?
Just put some ketchup on it.
That's like all we have left is just ketchup.
God damn it, hold on.
I think I can do it.
I'm gonna try.
I put some wood in the grinder.
Can I make like a wood sauce?
Hold on, can I, I can't chop up the wood.
I can't shred up the wood.
Oh well.
Okay, put this in.
What is, oh, I just, extra sauce, okay.
Somebody said this looks like a crime scene.
Yeah, let's break it down.
Okay, so let's say we came from here.
We open the front door.
Let's go, let's open the front door.
Where's the front door?
Over here, okay.
So, we open up here.
Cha-ching!
Okay, so very obviously, it was a struggle, right?
It was this, and peppers on the ground.
The person was definitely had just gone downstairs
to get something from the pantry, right?
You've obviously filled the pantry with this,
but it's on the ground now.
Why is it on the ground?
Window open.
Why is the window open?
Perpetrator may have escaped through the window
in the second floor pantry and kitchen area.
Coming through here.
Perpetrator pissed on the ground, too.
Marking his territory.
Perpetrator could be a dog.
Perpetrator could be a rabid dog.
Guy was coming up from the pantry.
Dog smelled the aroma.
Rabid dog jumped through the window.
Let's see what else.
Oh, and there it is.
He must've, he could've, this is two attacks
probably at the same time.
Bludgeoned by the dough case.
Smashed his head right on here.
His brain matter flew over all the way
to the left side of the kitchen.
There's no body.
Where's the body?
We're closing for today, and we finished where you,
oh, get out of here.
I'm busy.
It's a, it's the pizza.
That's not a whole lot of blood on the counter.
Blood on the counter.
And this dough looks really, really, really weird to me.
Hold on, let me go down.
Yep, okay.
That's human flesh.
Human flesh.
Multiple piss wounds.
Multiple, multiple blood stains.
And then somebody baked somebody into,
oh, he's gonna bake him into a pizza.
What would you even think coming in here?
Another open window, escape through this window too.
Nice band name, multiple piss wounds.
I said that and everybody hated it.
You said that and they all laughed.
This looks like somebody just like chair shot
at somebody just bang right in the back of the head like.
This place is a fucking mess.
Okay, let's cook this last pizza and then I'm done.
I'm done.
Oh, things don't break anymore, right?
Turn the heat up.
Let's burn this.
Let's burn this until like it actually sets the place on fire.
Is this my pizza shovel?
God, I have no idea.
Oh, here it is.
Too hot.
Oven is too hot.
We're getting to extreme levels of heat.
Where's the gas tank?
Where is the gas tank?
Oh, right, it got, it disappeared.
Can I buy another one?
What's the point of the gas tank?
I can't put it anywhere.
It's for gas, but gas to what?
I don't think it can explode.
It's a nerve agent.
All right, let's get that pizza out of there.
Mm, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum,
Scrumptious.
Mm, I actually kind of feel like this would be
a weird appetizer at a really expensive restaurant.
It doesn't really even look that bad.
Extra sauce on there.
Holy shit, what, what?
What?
That just scared the absolute hell out of me.
I didn't know you could do that.
Oh, crime scene.
Well, this looks like a typical,
typical game of I'm going to try to,
I'm going to put a chair here
and jump into the ceiling fair with my head.
That's so, it must have been,
yeah, it must have been making a really,
really crazy YouTube video.
The guy got shredded.
His body doesn't even exist.
It's just blood.
Of all the things you can break in this game,
the ceiling fan, really?
You can't like blow up the oven.
Where's the blood pizza?
Here it is.
Oh, I got to serve this to somebody, right.
Need a blow torch?
I just don't have it unlocked.
There's an artichoke on there.
Oh, oh well.
We're closing, I have to, wait,
I still have to fulfill these orders?
Cheese.
Okay, do I, I don't think I don't have any more dough.
I actually don't have any more dough.
Oh, fuck, just make dog, just make shit dough.
Who cares?
Down the stairs?
Oh, yes, yes.
They're like slam dunk pizza.
I forgot about slam dunk pizza.
Wait, I want to see it one more time.
I want to see it.
There he goes.
He's reaching out to do a big slam dunk.
Nice.
All right, cool.
Here, you can have it.
It's a cheese pizza.
I kind of don't want to sell it, but I have to.
Didn't even have to.
All right, nope, she has to take a plate.
I get to keep the pizza.
You motherfucker, it's mine.
All right, that was it.
Billy is such a joke.
Like, why do I have to do this?
I can't just like play the game normally.
I have to like fucking make like piss stains everywhere.
All right, I'm out.
I'm done.
Let's see how much money I made.
$765.
So that's times 200, which is 70, that's not even,
that's like nothing.
In the grand scheme of the massive amount of debt,
that's only the $153,000.
I thought it was going to be like at least a million.
It was honest work.
153K is not bad.
That sense not, no, you can't take sense off of the debt.
That doesn't make any sense.
I was fucking around too much, yeah.
All right, I will see you guys.
Let me see.
It's today, Friday.
I got something I got to do tomorrow.
So there's something that I have to take care of tomorrow.
I was going to go today and tomorrow,
but something came up like it sometimes does.
So you know, here's what we'll probably do.
I'll probably go,
I'll probably do Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday this week
coming up.
Cause I know I've done like one day, one day,
one day, one day.
Let's just, I'll take the weekend
and then we'll come back and do Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday.
Tomorrow, he's got something going on.
No, I just have to take care of something.
I hope you had fun.
I did.
I saw somebody say this is the worst stream of the year.
And I was like, ban that guy.
And everyone said, ban that guy.
And then we banned him.
What about Yakuza?
Yeah, we'll probably just open on Monday with Yakuza.
Cause I feel like that's a stream
that's going to take more than a day or two in a row.
And I don't want to do what I did last time,
which I played it for like three hours.
And it said, no, I'm done.
Never coming back to that again.
So I'm going to block out the time to play Yakuza
for at least a day or two.
That's not, that's going to happen again.
Well, that would be funny if it did.
You would at least be able to say that that's what happened.
Sly Cooper is going to, don't worry.
Sly Cooper is, I got to get another PS3.
Which, okay, let's make that decision right now.
Okay.
I'm going to put a poll in chat.
Yakuza zero, Yakuza seven, or Yakuza dragon.
Let's make that choice now.
Cause I've been hearing all kinds of,
don't play that one, play this one instead.
This is, no, you, you should play zero.
It's the probably the best one.
Seven's the best one.
Just play the new one.
It's fun.
And it's like memeable or something, right?
So let's just, let's get this out of the way now.
So we can get this ready for Monday.
Okay.
I'm going to Yakuza zero, Yakuza seven.
Is Yakuza seven on PlayStation four or is it on PS3?
It's on PC.
Oh wow.
Okay.
Is Yakuza zero on PC too?
I know I was PS4 only, wasn't it?
Here comes the subs for the day.
Thanks everybody.
I really appreciate it as always.
Thanks for the insane amount of subs.
End of the stream chat decides yes they do.
Well, this seems to be very, very, very unanimous.
This is like not even a contest.
Seven is dragon.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
New poll.
Wait, wait, what?
Yakuza seven is the...
All right.
Wait, hold on, hold on.
People might've been confused.
I could do new poll.
New poll.
Wait, just forget that one.
People might've been like, I don't understand.
I'm going to just, just stop, stop it.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Is it zero or Yakuza seven?
Okay.
That's way easier.
Click this one instead.
Vote on that one.
And still that didn't really matter, did it?
By a astronomical amount.
All right.
So I streamed Yakuza zero already.
Should I just,
should we just pretend that stream didn't happen
and just start to just do it over the whole thing?
What if I make the same jokes?
What if I like make the same references?
Can we just pretend like I didn't?
I probably will.
What if I make the same terrible jokes?
Nobody will remember.
It was kind of a long time ago, wasn't it?
All right.
This is, this is pretty clear.
Yeah.
So we'll just start Yakuza zero.
And I will actually give it the time that it deserves.
Because remember that's,
even after doing this kind of pulling back
on streaming recently,
four or five years ago,
I only streamed for three hours a stream.
Sometimes four.
So I only gave that game like three hours.
All right.
I'll see you guys on Monday.
We'll go Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday,
Yakuza zero opening on Monday.
I'll see you guys later.
Thanks for watching as always.
Always a pleasure.
Happy Thanksgiving to those of you
that celebrated it yesterday.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
I said, why am I saying thank you to you?
Happy Thanksgiving.
Thank you.
Well, I guess, I mean, I am thankful for you.
I am.
All right.
Let's do, let's do a raid.
Let's do a raid.
Let's go.
We are gonna raid.
Oh, I mean, if, if Mr. Sark is live,
they get raided.
That's just how it works.
It's playing Raft right now,
which tell me if it looks good.
Mr. Sark is hilarious.
Go watch him.
He's been around for a long time.
He's playing Raft.
The Mr. Sark.
And I'll see you guys soon.
See you Monday.
Take care, guys.
See you soon.