Let me just very briefly go over this because a lot of people are going to be very unhappy.
I know I usually don't say anything for at least a minute or two, but I'm here right- I'm here immediately.
All right, have I even start saying this?
All right, ladies and gentlemen, I'm very, very
not happy to announce that there will be no BLT eating on this stream.
Uh, I know what's up.
We have lettuce and tomato chunks.
I didn't go get any bacon or anything, and we have hot dog buns.
I was thinking about like, okay, can I like fake this?
Can I go- can I take a hot dog bun, just put mayo in it,
lettuce, and some tomato chunks, and let's pretend there's bacon in it,
and take a couple bites and be like, whoa, BLT!
But then people- you guys would tell me to prove I'm eating a BLT.
So I'd have to show it to the camera and really examine it to a point where there's no way
it's a BLT, so sorry about that.
Anyways, I'll eat a BLT like at some point.
Who cares?
I was laughing about this before starting because it's just like,
oh, hey, sorry guys, I'm not eating the BLT on stream today.
It's like, I- that's a- that's a sentence that is hard to understand as a real sentence.
You know what I mean?
More broken promises, it's alright.
Hey, speaking of broken promises, those of you- excuse me,
we're playing Sorcery today.
Sorcery is today.
So, broken promises, excuse me, didn't watch the Smurfs- the Smurfs movie, no.
No.
I've been pretty busy.
I haven't had- haven't had time to watch the Smurfs movie.
I'll watch the Smurfs movie.
No BLT is worse than no Sorcery.
What?
Yeah, sorry, I'm like 15 minutes late.
Well, I mean, it's gonna happen, whatever.
Stomach is being annoying.
Don't have to get into it, but it is.
As a new job, it is great.
I'm on a couple of projects right now.
You'll probably see them- I don't want to give you a time
because as it stood, when I joined the company,
they were kind of already in the middle of a few things
and I wasn't really a part of the process on them.
But later on, a lot of the stuff you'll see in the middle of this year
and into, you know, you know, the content plan into, you know,
next quarter or two, I'm on a couple of things
and I'm really, really excited for you to see them, especially one of them.
Oh, excitement, Andy.
You owe us 110 gifted subs.
Yeah, it's a lot- I'm happy- I'm really happy so far.
And I think I'm getting a pretty good idea of the workflow.
Because a couple weeks ago when this was announced,
it was almost like how- what's the strategy to do this?
So I can, you know, I want to stream still,
I want to do this still, I want to do writing,
I want to do, you know, get into meetings,
get into meetings, you know, executive meetings,
you know, executive meetings, you know, executive meetings,
you know, executive meetings, you know, executive meetings
and all that stuff.
Are you all right?
I just sat down weird.
I sat down weird and kind of did my voice get weird,
kind of sounded a little weird for a second.
Executive Andy.
Now, I think I've got a good idea of how it's going to work.
Yeah, I like it a lot.
It's real- I think I'm contributing.
You know, my role in the company,
and contrary to some of the popular belief here,
is not to just show up at the office
and see how far I can slide down the hallway with socks on.
And that's- everyone just kind of looks out their office
and be like, oh, what's he doing?
Okay.
Chief Creative Officer.
So, you know.
All right.
Today, we're going to play Steam NextVest Games.
I was supposed to do this a long time ago,
but I'm glad it's back.
And then Sorcery.
So I downloaded a bunch of these games already.
Because last time I did this, I kind of scrolled
and then installed and had to install them live.
And I just got like 15 to 16 of them
that looked interesting to me.
And we're just going to go.
It's on the docket.
That's a good question.
First, I'm just going to pick a random one.
Because I don't want to say what I have.
And then people say, no, no, no, dude, just play that only.
So let's do- I mean, how long is the Lies of P demo?
Because I want to play it.
I just want to see.
Is it long or should I-
We've got to give it like 10 to 20 minutes to each of these.
It's like 30 minutes.
Like three hours.
No way.
Like 20 minutes.
Five hours?
What?
All right.
Well, let me just check it out.
We're going to jump around every 10, 20 minutes or so.
I just want to get a taste.
So let's do it now.
Okay.
Yeah, we'll do this for a couple of hours.
Maybe two, three hours.
And then we'll move to sorcery.
Going to be chill today.
No cam.
So okay.
Everybody that's annoyed about that.
Sorry.
Shaders are compiling, really.
Do you lick your fingers after eating Doritos?
No.
Well, hold on.
Let me tell the truth.
Anytime I eat something like Takis or Doritos or Cheetos,
doesn't matter what it is.
If it leaves a residue on your fingers is what I do.
I go with the one single lick on the thumb.
Just one single lick.
And then I wash my hands.
All right.
Let me-
You guys can't see this, but now you can.
And you hear it though is a better question.
Now you can.
All right.
I got a controller.
So it's a controller game, right?
Do up to the first boss.
Let's see.
Because I don't want to spend like three hours in one demo.
Check it out.
The next best demos.
I'm going to play Lies of P for four hours
and then not even play sorcery.
This is my word.
Is it right here?
Warning.
This icon will appear when the game is saving.
Yeah.
The functions and text in the demo version of Lies of P that you-
How's the audio?
Should I turn it up?
Or it could be a little louder.
And use a license agreement.
Oh, shit.
I got to agree to this.
Let's go.
Is it loud now?
You didn't read it?
I did.
You just couldn't see.
Now Lying.
This is a good game for me.
In honor of the great writer, Carlo Colodi.
I can't actually.
I did not hear that if anybody talked.
Was I supposed to hear that?
I can't hear this.
It's a lie?
No, it actually isn't.
I didn't hear any of that.
Why?
My audios.
Oh no, sorry.
I didn't have this plugged in.
All right, cool.
Move, rotate camera.
Now I can hear.
Good.
Liar.
Okay.
So what was this game?
What would you guys compare this to?
Does this game have like a certain comparison of a certain franchise?
Or a certain like style of games that I would potentially like?
Jiminy.
Okay.
Kind of looks like Tetris.
Jiminy, please escort him to the hotel.
This is Jiminy?
Do not be afraid.
Even if you get lost in the fog, the cricket guide will be with you.
Okay.
Okay, cool.
Vod.
Hi chat.
Hey, can we please get everybody take a quick second, please.
And say hello to the Vod Watchers.
We don't.
I think they feel a little left out.
Don't you think so?
Everybody on the count of three say.
Hey, Vod Watchers.
Enjoy the show.
Now I'm going to put on a bunch of DMCA music so they can't hear anything for the rest of
the entire fucking stream.
I'm just kidding, Vod Watchers.
Stay here.
Can I move faster than this?
But the streets are not safe.
Arm yourself with one of the weapons over there.
Somebody said, is he, somebody said this a while ago, but they said, is he sober?
And it stuck with me because I was like, why did you say that?
Combat style.
Balance.
Dexterity.
Strength.
Path of the Cricket.
The Bastard or the Sweeper.
Oh, it's going to, it's, I imagine it's going to be just like the other souls like games.
This doesn't really necessarily matter that much.
And this doesn't, it doesn't matter at all because it's a demo.
So I'm just going to go with this one.
All right.
Dodge roll.
Feels good.
Okay.
Can you two hand?
Was a lawnmower inside of my ears.
Centrist Andy.
Rat central station.
Rainy night.
Special attack.
Hold down to do a charge attack.
Yeah.
Okay.
It is a little, I'm going to turn it down.
It is a little loud.
You're going to die to the first enemy.
I play these games a lot.
I'm not going to die to the first enemy.
Uh, let's get it to like, uh, that's all right.
Is that better?
That's better.
I am so glad I just turned it down right there.
The maximum number of pulse cells.
Use a pulse cell to recover HP.
There is a maximum number of times pulse cells can be used just like all the other games
that are in this category.
Okay.
If you attack enemies while the cell is discharged,
pulse cell will be gradually charged.
Okay.
So let's go.
We're checking out steam next best.
I'm not playing sorcery and I'm not playing another single other game today.
Because there's no way I'm going to get through this in 10 minutes.
It's already been 10 minutes.
Light up your, who is that?
Okay.
That's, is that Jiminy talking?
I mean, it's not dark in here.
Lies of Jay.
Yep.
Okay.
I feel like lies of P is going to be some really major consequences of the lies of P.
Lies of Jay is like, I was going to eat a BLT today and I didn't.
Okay.
Like, whoa, what happened?
Bright bumper behind, right?
Oh, it has, there's an indicator.
Hold on.
Ah, lie.
Like you said, you're going to play the great ace attorney Chronicles.
Sad.
Well, I didn't lie.
I just didn't do it.
Fable catalyst.
Okay.
Activate upper belt slot, lower belt slot.
I think I figured this out already.
I did.
That is lying.
Isn't there, okay.
But isn't there like intent when it comes to lying?
Like if I tell you, oh man, I really, really, I really, I want to go on that.
Uh, I want to go on that water slide.
Oh, I'm going to, you know, I'm going to try to go on that water slide on Thursday.
Okay.
If I don't go on the water slide on Thursday, isn't that just me expressing the thing that
I would like to do or thing I want to do?
Doesn't a lie technically have to have some kind of intent behind it?
Like I am not telling you I'm going to go on the water slide.
So you like just to make it up.
Is that, don't you need to have like intent when it comes to lying?
It was like, oh man, I've, I love, I love water slides.
But then if I don't go to the water park, am I a liar?
Just me liking water slides no longer.
Am I not allowed to say that anymore?
False equivalency.
Okay.
To me, to me, a lie of real live would be if somebody said, Hey dude, do you want to
go to the water park today?
And I said, no, no, I, uh, I'm getting nighted today.
Sorry.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I'm getting nighted today.
Oh, weird.
All right.
We'll hit us up next week.
That's like a lie.
Is an actor a professional liar?
Interesting question.
Me, me expressing desires and things that I would like to do and want to do is not, I
mean, is that a lie?
If you don't actually do the thing that you say you like to do or want to do.
Yeah.
I said, I want to go camping the fucking three years ago and I didn't go camping.
Is that a lie?
Or is it like, I just didn't fucking want to do, I just didn't want to go camping.
All right.
This is a harder enemy.
Okay.
Just, I'm going to die to the first real enemy of the game.
Is there a parry?
All right.
This guy feels harder than everybody else.
Can I, I want to parry this guy.
He usually would be right here, but what does this do?
Left arm of steel.
What is that?
I'm dead.
I'm dead here.
Why does this guy have so much more health and shit?
Okay.
Every enemy has died in three hits.
This guy is like impossible.
Who the fuck is this guy in the tutorial that is unkillable?
Tap.
What does the left arm even do?
Oh, okay.
Thanks for telling me.
Video game.
Guard against, defend against enemy attacks by guarding.
If your guard is successful, it will reduce the,
they wait for you to die before they tell you there's a block.
It will reduce the damage, but will cause stamina
and the damage will be transferred to guard regain.
Okay.
Guard regain will be turned into HP recovery if you attack enemies.
Guard regain accumulates, but gradually reduces after a certain time has passed.
If your guard is successful.
Okay.
So it's just a block.
Is it, can, is it like a, all right, let's go.
Okay.
Well, whatever.
Just don't get hit.
Okay.
Sawtooth wheel.
We're at the 20 minute mark.
I think it's time to move to a new game.
Let me, let me beat this guy though.
This game's like two to three hours for the demo.
Yeah.
Run a poll.
Um, we want a time extension poll.
Let me get, let me get past this first enemy.
How do I, it was already on.
So it's, you have to go up and down and then scroll.
Okay. I get it.
Let me at least get to the first area.
Like, let me beat this first guy.
They just lost a customer.
Wait, you mean for the game?
What?
Are you talking about me or are you talking about you saying that?
Yeah, I'm not, this is, this is fun.
No, I'm, I didn't say that.
They just lost a customer.
Press the button.
This is, that's a shortcut.
I didn't even look over here.
God damn it.
I was worried.
Right behind me was the shortcut.
Really?
All right.
All right, let's go.
Are you even supposed to kill this guy?
Okay. I'm not, this has Sekiro like block parries?
Like this?
I don't, was that person lying?
This enemy is groggy?
All right.
There's other systems in this game that I do not know exist.
Groggy?
What does groggy mean?
Groggy Gary.
Okay. Well, that was pretty sloppy, but whatever.
That was a fun spin.
You know, it means stagger.
Did I actually even have to do that?
Okay. Well, I'm going back up here.
Wait, did I get, did it pick anything up?
What did that guy have?
Did he have anything on him?
Should we extend the time for lies of P?
Oh, not extended, but hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm, I'm not done with it yet.
Sorry, I'm lying.
He's lying.
Am I missing something or?
And okay, seems correct.
Is this a case where I killed that guy,
looked at chat and missed the item that the guy dropped?
Is that, is that what happened?
Yes. Oh, okay.
Good. Okay.
Crat.
Crat central station, rainy night.
Prepare the stargazer.
At least get to the first boss.
Yeah. I can't leave the demo without.
Don't worry. We got plenty of time.
I'm not in a time limit.
All right. So this is a bonfire clearly.
It runs really well, plays really well.
I'm into it.
The lies just keep adding up.
What did this person say?
This is kind of funny.
They said you are on a time limit, dude.
Like not, nobody lives forever or something.
Like this technically is a time limit.
Clever one.
This stargazer will make you stronger,
but the stargazer strength doesn't last forever.
It's true.
So be careful with it.
Yeah.
Hurry up and come to hotel Crat.
Okay. Level up.
So this is HP guard regain.
So it is like Sekiro with a guard system.
Just go all stamina capacity.
Motivity technique.
All right.
Which one of these is strength index?
This one looks like strength index.
I'm just play this game forever.
Hey, we, you hate this game and we all know it.
Hey, listen.
God damn it.
No, I, I'm doing health and I'm doing this.
Yeah. What's about this projection?
Okay. Perfect guard.
Right before getting hit.
So this, this is a parry, I'm assuming.
Is that good?
Did I do it?
So what's the benefit of actually doing a perfect parry?
It doesn't seem to stagger them or anything.
They don't have their own bar like Sekiro.
Do you like this game?
I bet you at least 70% of people say yes.
It builds stagger and you take no damage.
What am I fighting right now?
Is this oil?
This oil.
All right.
Well, hold on a second here.
You've got me in two different directions.
People are saying this is like, kind of like Bloodborne.
But then people say in Sekiro, they play very differently.
I'm a dodge Andy.
Bloodborne was all about dodge, dodge, dodge, dodge, dodge.
Sekiro is parry, parry, parry, parry, parry.
Which one is it?
I don't know.
It's interesting.
I frame Andy.
It's a mix of the two.
Okay. Well, now I'm, I'm a lot more interested now
because Bloodborne is one of my favorite games of all time.
And I despise Sekiro.
So, I mean, this is going to be a very interesting game for me.
I don't despise Sekiro.
I just don't like it at all.
Pratt times issue 183.
No, it would be perfect.
Is if I somehow get a mechanism to have like a fake nose.
I haven't even said it.
It makes me laugh.
Whatever.
Have a fake nose and just say a bunch of lies on stream
and just keep growing every time.
Nevermind, plus two.
Yeah, you got to give me a chance.
You can't just, some of you guys really jump to conclusions.
Jump the gun.
You got to wait for the whole thing.
Okay. Um, it's just you.
Dim ergo fragment.
Will he switch before the horse race is over?
What a horse race.
Is a horse race?
I like it.
Fable arts.
Use blade fable arts while guarding use handle fable arts.
Weapons have distinct blades and handles that each have their own fable art.
Fable arts use a fable slots and fable, different fable arts
use a different fable number of slots.
Charge fable slots by attack.
All right.
So I just used all of it and the big scary enemies running down the hallway now.
That's not perfect.
I'm surprised.
All right.
Hold for a charge attack.
So if they get groggy, I can probably kill them pretty quickly like that.
Oh, you guys.
You picked the turtle.
The turtle will never be the horses.
The horses are much faster.
They have more muscular definition than the turtle.
There's no way the turtle will win.
Now watch.
I'm going to sprint as fast as I can then run out of energy.
So what does this one do?
Oh, does that make attack power more?
That's what the rabbit said, German.
Look what happened to him when he raced the turtle grinder.
Use the what is it?
All right.
Hold on.
Wait, wait.
I don't want to die here.
This is actually just do use the grinder.
This thing.
Hold on a second.
Oh, you have to grind the weapon for durability.
Okay.
Did the turtle win?
Oh, my goodness.
You know how horrible that's going to be when you fight a boss in this game?
It's a hard boss and the boss needs like three hits and you have to grind your weapon.
That's going to be so sad.
I know it's going to happen at least a half dozen times.
Hey, anything to make it so you can't just press B to dodge everything, right?
He hates democracy.
I'm almost done.
This was one of the big ones.
I really wanted to try this.
This is very obviously like one of the big ones of the next best.
This is a okay.
Cool.
Let me just get eyes on where this is because this is a shortcut.
Let him vibe.
Damn it.
Yeah, let me vibe.
I'm just vibing.
Let me get eyes on this because I okay.
I'm just trying to figure out how to where the shortcut actually is going to.
You don't know what vibe means.
Not really.
I am going to do this though.
I'm imagining.
Yep.
These are definitely crunchies, right?
Yes, they are.
Technique.
Advance.
It's just stamina and that's good.
I think this is dexterity.
This might be strength, although it's hard to tell.
I think this is strength.
All right.
I'm absolutely good.
I'm going to run.
I kind of forget where I'm going, but it's all right.
Where was it?
It was this way up here.
This way, right?
Oh, that was so completely wrong.
Where did I even come from?
Down here?
No, no, it was up this way.
The entire.
Okay.
I should just reset it this way, right?
Yeah, let me reset it.
This is going to be a 24 hour stream at this rate, dude.
It's not.
It's going to be fine.
I need to get to the first boss of the demo.
There's going to be a boss that you beat.
And then it says, thank you so much.
Next player.
Thank you for playing the demo.
Is this guy just trying to punch me in the face?
Really?
This is the first boss.
First boss, first boss.
All right.
This really wants to teach me how to do this.
Okay.
I think I'm understanding it.
The red one is easier for me for some reason.
I don't know why.
All right.
Cool.
Hello there.
Welcome to Krot, visitor.
Hi.
I didn't think there were any stalkers left to fight the puppets.
You didn't hear?
Figures.
The whole organization fell apart.
All that's left are wannabes and amateurs who think they can fight on their own.
R1, R1, R1, R1, can you?
You can't buy something.
Okay.
Rowing cell.
Electric blitz damage at the area of impact.
Electric blitz aggressive.
I mean, this is, these are different weapons and everything.
Cool.
Looks pretty cool.
But I'm in demo mode and I'm just trying to get to the end of the demo.
Philip, let's go.
All right.
Now what happens if you have two turtles though?
Mods make it happen.
I want to, I want to race with two turtles.
Which one will win?
All right.
Here we go.
Time to prove that I know how to play video games again.
This might be loud, so be aware of that.
Jesus.
Okay.
Parade master.
Let's go.
Somebody learned how to play the game.
Everybody in chat is seething right now.
Shit, that hurt.
Groggy attack.
Do the swing.
Swing.
Do the big swing.
How do I do the swing?
What?
I thought it was Y.
It's not Y?
I pressed Y.
What is that?
Oh my God.
All right.
Your moveset just got way weirder.
What the fuck?
I didn't block it.
What does L2 do?
I'm in trouble.
I don't even know what L2 does.
Advisor sidearm.
I swear to God, if it tells me what L2 does when I revive, I'm gonna be very upset.
You die in a boss battle.
Death ergo is created at the entrance.
That's actually really awesome.
That's such an unbelievably good change for these games.
It's outside the boss door.
So if you don't feel like if you go in there and you lose a shitload of souls.
I'm going the wrong way.
Glad to see this is still a thing.
Oh my God.
What the fuck?
What did they all even come from?
All right.
Here we go.
I'm going to go beat this demo boss.
Don't worry.
I'm not just going to play one demo.
Cool.
Okay.
That's actually really cool.
I really like the sort of quality of life differences.
I don't have anything.
Whatever.
It's the demo.
I don't care.
This is going to hit an hour before we change.
That's all right.
I'll add time.
I have to beat the parade master.
Ow.
I'm already.
I already fucked the whole thing up.
I did so much better on the first try.
Oh, come on.
Really?
I already have all.
Dude, I got him.
I wish I could just hold like right bumper and just reset.
Just kill me.
I got to retry.
This took me five tries.
I don't even count that one.
Why'd you give up?
Because I had zero heals and he's not even at 10% health.
If I get him down to 10% health and I lose,
that'd be very sad.
Okay, throwing objects.
I want to know what LT does.
Like, what does this do?
It's like a super punch.
I don't know.
Go read the guide.
Where's the guide?
How do I get to the guide?
You'll get different abilities later.
It's a super punch right now.
I'm going to try this two more times.
And even if I lose, it doesn't matter.
I'm moving on to the next demo.
This was a cool, good first look at lies of P.
We're moving on after two more attempts.
Two times.
Don't lie.
Okay, let's go.
Okay, I have to dodge backwards, not to the left.
Because they hit me with that every time.
I feel like I'm not even hurting this guy.
Oh, come on.
I will say, the second that I'm allowed to change weapons,
I'm going to immediately.
All right, groggy.
Let's go.
Whoa, what the fuck is he doing?
Oh, I didn't get the groggy.
Do it.
Yes.
Oh, God, that double crow hop is annoying.
Whoa, I thought I dodged it.
Oh, my God.
He's going to kill me.
No, he's not.
I'm fine.
Damn it.
This game is fucking hard.
God damn it.
L plus Y is parry.
Huh?
All right, one more time.
That's it.
I don't think that's a parry.
I think that's like a buff.
Does it say?
I don't think it says anything about it.
Over leveled.
What am I doing?
I've had a chance to level one time.
All right, time that person up for at least 10 minutes.
All right, last attempt before I move on.
I'm not sitting here for two hours playing lies of P.
Okay.
I got so close.
All right, I'm going to use patience and I'm going to go for it.
Let's go.
Need stamina.
Oh, that wasn't a perfect.
I feel like you got to be really close to hit them.
I think it's just I don't like the weapon.
He's still not, is he groggy anymore?
Oh, that's sad.
Horrible place to be.
I didn't dodge it.
My brain is conflicted playing this game.
I'm playing secure.
But then I'm like, no dodge on.
Oh, my God.
I'm dead.
All right, we're playing next game.
Let's kill me.
All right, last one.
One more.
That's it.
So should I be going more secure or more blood born?
I feel like my brain is trying to say play secure.
And then in a different move is like play blood born instead.
You should play it more secure.
More secure, secure.
OK, so I should be trying to parry everything.
Not like you like this.
OK, this is the one right here.
Guaranteed.
Holy shit, that did a lot of damage.
He broke my sword.
What the fuck?
Oh, my God, dude.
He's got so many different moves.
What?
Let's go groggy Gary.
All right, good.
I beat the tutorial boss one of probably five.
That's fun.
I like it.
I think it's very fun.
Dodge less.
Well, what?
OK, that's what I mean.
Like I was saying, my brain is trying to play secure.
But my brain is also like you need to dodge left every attack.
Now that it's like, OK, more more secure style.
Try to go for those perfect parries.
Pretty sick.
Dodge more, not less.
Wait, what?
Wrong info.
All right, that's fun.
I just want to see what's up here.
And that's it.
Next game.
I know, I just want to see.
I just want to see what's over here.
Look, there's like a notice that I need to look at.
All right, I'm going to sprint to the next boss.
My L2 does.
All right, I don't know what I just did.
They told me to be the lie.
I said I was a human.
That's a lie.
All right, OK, all right, all right.
I'm going to get like obsessed with this game.
I'm done.
We're going to move on to House Flipper 2.
Perfect opportunity to change.
Look, I'm into it.
When does it come out?
Does it release soon?
Like September, right?
I'm into it.
Let's just see what happens in this cutscene.
I know I've spent like 45 minutes playing this game, but don't worry.
We're going to be fine.
We're going to play Sorcery.
We're going to play.
House Flipper 2.
That's prune.
I'll use my power.
You can't.
All right, goodbye.
That was a good one.
All right, the next one we're going to do House Flipper 2.
This looks really fun.
Those of you that don't know, House Flipper is one of my number one games on stream.
I have streamed House Flipper more than any other game, I think.
Besides, maybe if you combine all the From Software games.
So let's give it a try.
And you should see it in one.
So what did they add in House Flipper 2?
I wonder how long the stream is going to be.
I don't know, maybe like six hours.
Oh, shit.
Okay, my capture is messed up.
Hold on.
I need to go to the settings here.
You can probably hear the music, though.
It's very nice.
I didn't even tweet that I was streaming.
Hold on.
There we go.
Screen's black.
Yeah, I know.
I'm just getting this situated.
I didn't.
I got to tweet, man.
Okay, that's fine.
Okay, let's go.
Settings.
Here we go.
Graphics.
Okay, you should be able to see it now.
Please yell at me if you can't.
Yeah, why does it look like that?
Okay, does that work?
Hey, there we go.
All right.
I'm ready.
New game.
I hope there's cleaning.
I hope there's mopping.
I hope there's clean the windows.
I have a wish list for House Flipper 2.
You're about to play the House Flipper 2 demo.
Follow the quest list to transform a rundown shack into a beautiful house.
When you're done, you can keep playing and add some personal touches to it.
Look up for books placed around the house.
They'll tell you how to use your tools.
Okay.
Is there a problem with the reception on the island?
I just tried to.
I have to leave a message then.
Oh, my dearest friend.
I buttoned them.
You may be wondering where you got here.
Don't worry.
I'm here to explain.
You said you want to try your handed house flipping, right?
I found a perfect house for you to work on.
You can throw now.
And not to waste any time.
I took the liberty of organizing your transport and everything else.
You're welcome.
So there's nothing more to do but to get to work.
Do your best.
I hope to turn a large profit selling this house.
Who wouldn't like to live in such a wonderful neighborhood?
Take care and happy flipping.
Thanks.
Get to work.
Flipper tool collecting trash.
What do I do with the trash?
Flipper sense.
Okay.
Tasks.
Stains.
Trash.
Okay.
What do I do with it?
Open?
Wait, I can open the trash?
All right.
So in the first game, it just disappears.
Do I actually have to clean it up and move it?
Let's see.
What does it say?
Paint sticks to a wall on its own, but you can't say the same for panels, wallpaper, or tiles.
Lay down some surface glue first.
Okay.
Left mouse to apply glue anywhere you want.
Don't want to go over the line.
Set the area for your glue first.
Actually, let's go back.
There's a couple of books I didn't look at.
This feels like it's not.
I got to make the FOV bigger.
I don't think I can do it.
It'll be in the...
It'll be in the full game, I imagine.
Okay.
Collect all the trash in your range with the most durable trash bags known to man.
Choose the collecting trash tool.
Find some garbage and press left click.
It's gone from the ground, but your job is far from over.
When the bag fills up, throw it in the bin.
So they went more like viscera clean-up detail style,
where I actually have to carry this around and put trash in it.
But where's the bin?
Is this a bin?
Okay, I'm collecting trash right now.
Okay.
How much can I carry?
Okay, that's way more involved than it used to be.
Clean.
So are the leaves and stuff considered trash?
I can't pick this up anymore, right?
Yep.
Okay, close the bag.
Toss it.
Ooh, is there a map?
Before I do anything, do you know what I'm saying?
Like I remember this from the first game and I'm not fucking around.
How do I swing it?
Okay, I don't think I can swing.
Okay, we're good.
Q?
I think Q just changes how hard you're going to swing at it.
Isn't there usually a map too?
So how come this is not considered trash right here?
This is not trash?
This thing is fucking gross.
What do I do with it?
Is the bag full?
Can I wash this in the sink?
Bag's not full.
Now the bag is full.
I really actually like the...
Because you can have multiple trash bags.
All this has to go.
What is this one?
Okay, hold on.
Okay, this still stains.
Sell everything.
Um, hold on.
Broken glass?
I can't pick it up.
Maybe there's a vacuum?
All the trash is going out here for now.
All right, I'm pressing R.
I don't...
It doesn't seem to do anything.
Can I take this down with this?
How do I get in here?
Seeing that just fly out of somebody's house.
How do I move?
I want to get rid of the board.
Okay, yeah.
Sell all this.
So they've...
Okay, you no longer can just throw things like this in the trash.
You have to sell it.
Maybe they thought it was too easy to just go around and go like...
Just pick up everything.
There's a lot of stains.
I wonder, how does the cleaning work?
I wonder.
Um, maybe read a book on it.
Love open spaces so does your hammer.
The longer you hold the stronger will be released to see the damage.
Okay, so you actually have to be aiming at a wall.
What about just cleaning?
Building?
All right.
Yeah, that's just like the first one.
What about cleaning though?
Because I have like a spray bottle.
How does this work?
It's Q.
Is there anything in the bottle?
Ooh, just spray everything and then wipe it.
It's getting better.
Okay.
Now, how do I mop this up?
Is there a vacuum or something?
I've never seen anybody so excited to clean.
And this game is my game.
Painting, surface finish, smart home, building, demolish.
So they're different now.
Yeah, so they've split up the tools.
This is actually particles you have to vacuum up.
Huge.
Huge addition.
Why is it giving me Xbox?
Wait.
Painting.
Paint a wall, you must buy some paint.
Open the store by pressing tab to get to the paint.
Paint roller.
Aim the bucket in.
Okay.
Now pick your painting style and then hold it just like in the first one.
All right.
So I need to go to the store.
And I wonder how much they've actually added here.
So I need paint.
I guess I can just type it, right?
They've added bread.
Nice.
They have, yeah.
Look at this.
This looks good.
Have a loads of bread.
Hey, carve me off a slice of that crusty bread.
Let me just take a look.
Oh, you can actually keep things.
I like that.
You can do plants now.
Building outside.
You can tag things.
Okay.
I need paint.
What should I do the walls?
How about orange and red vibrant paint?
So change size.
Huge addition.
Massive addition.
Okay.
So you actually have to do this now.
I feel like there's a lot more paint.
A big complaint for the last game was how much paint you actually had to put on the brush.
The noise is gross.
The noise is the best part.
What are you talking about?
I don't like this paint though.
How about this one?
That's better.
It's a really, really awesome gray.
Boring, boring, boring.
No, you don't understand.
It's a neutral color and then you have accent pieces.
Shut up.
Oops.
The music is really nice too.
They really stepped it up with the soundtrack.
That's fine.
Turn the volume down because we need to actually make sure this is not.
This is usually loud.
Very, very, very loud.
I'm going to do it here too because I'm not.
Usually it's really bad.
Let's see.
It's actually not bad.
Is this structural?
Watch the whole house collapses.
I'm opening this up a little.
I want to be able to open up this kitchen area.
It's a load-bearing wall.
It's all right.
It's a video game.
We'll be all right.
See?
Look, that's much nicer.
All right.
Now get rid of all this.
Any more trash in here?
This is too much work.
Paint the whole house one color and including all the furniture too.
Have everything be the same color?
That would give me.
I feel like that would give me anxiety being in that room
because I would have a lot of questions.
First of all, be like, why?
Why did you do this?
The second question would not even be like, why did you do this?
Interesting question.
Where did you get all this?
It must have taken you years to collect all this furniture.
That was the exact same color.
I don't need these.
Damn it.
All right.
How about still two pieces of trash that I did not get?
And where exactly are those?
Is it upstairs?
What the fuck?
Is it a doorbell?
There's way more than two pieces of trash left.
Jesus.
All right.
Why can I not activate those things?
Stains, vacuum, dirt.
There's tons of stuff to vacuum up here.
You definitely can level this up too.
Why is there a fish in the closet?
I don't know.
It's very strange.
I can reach really far.
Sell everything.
Need to make room so you can see where you need to clean.
Collecting trash.
Yep.
How to do that at this point?
I have an idea.
Get out the fucking window.
All right.
You can't do that.
I was trying to save some time.
And what am I doing?
You can do it right here.
Damn it.
Oh, that's too bad.
I'm keeping that.
Okay.
Buy 28.
Oh, we need these.
All right.
Well, hold on.
Let me sell.
Well, I need to sell more stuff.
You're very precise with this.
I tend to be.
This is a mess.
Okay.
I think that's all the trash.
Sell it.
I need to mop the walls too.
Can I clean this?
I'll try to clean it first.
I'm not going to sell everything.
Some of the junkier stuff like that and like that.
So we can...
Oh, you can duplicate.
That's cool.
Sold the plunger.
Yeah.
Do not ever sell your plunger.
I saw actually a comment.
Somebody said, what a rookie mistake.
You sold your plunger.
I mean, I didn't sell my plunger,
but I got rid of my plunger
before making sure I had another one.
That's a very big deal.
I will never make that mistake ever again.
You buy the new plunger
before you get rid of the old one.
You sold your used plunger.
We're talking about in the context of this game.
This makes or breaks my rating for the demo so far.
There's an A.
That was an A.
That's an A.
Because this one you really...
It's a whole lot more control here.
I would say it's a B minus.
You missed a bit.
I got it.
Okay.
I'm going to start in this room.
I wonder if we're going to get anybody upset
that I'm in this for more than 30 minutes.
I doubt it.
Put all the books outside.
Can stack objects?
Could you do that before?
I'm not sure you could even do that before.
Okay.
I need to buy all this new shit.
Is that what it's telling me to do?
Not yet.
Whoa.
Cool.
I like that sound too.
You couldn't do that before.
I could make a Super Mario level.
Oh my God.
I can make a Super Mario level.
No way.
Okay.
That's when the game comes up.
You can take out individual cubes now.
Didn't I say?
A couple of years ago.
Man, I wish I could place and delete individual cubes.
I said that.
Didn't I say that?
True.
Yeah, I did.
You famously said that.
All right.
Let's paint.
Are we going with just the gray?
I like that color.
You can call me a normie all you want.
That's fine.
I like the like blue gray wall.
Go ahead.
Blues and grays are nice.
I know.
What color?
All right.
Let me ask you guys this question.
What color wall would you say is the, you know, what's your wall?
What is your ideal living room wall color?
Beige?
If it isn't beige, just like kind of the same type of neutral that gray, light gray, light blue is.
Egg shell white, white, white.
How is white is also neutral?
How is that different than gray?
It's light blue, light green.
I can see light green.
Light green would be pretty nice.
They're all nice.
I can change the color if I want in a minute.
We have to get a base here first.
He's painting without paint liners.
Yeah.
Sorry.
I bowl without the bumpers on the sides.
Somebody says landlord special.
All right.
I'm coming in.
That's right.
We're getting, I'm going to be in there.
We're going to do all new painting.
That's right.
Just make sure you're out of the apartment for a little while.
Hope you like gray and I hope you're like a really shit job.
That's exactly where you're getting a dome depot.
And I just want as much of the cheapest gray paint as I could.
I don't need wall liners or whatever.
I ain't living here.
The landlord special.
Stop painting over outlets and light switches.
That's funny.
Painting over the tile.
Wait, I can make the ground too.
You can paint the ground.
Yep.
Just coming in with the landlord special real quick.
All right.
Not a problem.
Just trying to drop my property value by as much as I possibly can.
Whatever.
If I came in and somebody was doing this to the ground,
I'd be like, all right.
What kind of special paint is that?
Because you obviously you're doing that because you're trying to block
like radiation or something, right?
Like why?
What are you painting the ground for?
Well, you know, I heard that there was a radiation could come through the floor.
So I want to make sure I have the code of this anti radiation paint.
All right.
I was just my grandmother's favorite color was, you know, dark gray.
I figured I had to see my entire fucking house around it.
What is that?
Get rid of that.
Oops.
Wait, did I throw trash into the ocean?
Wait a minute.
No, you can't.
No, that's fucked up.
That's not all right.
Did it work?
Uh, I mean, it is a perfectly good bin outside, but you know,
I'll just throw it in the ocean.
Wait, hold on.
Wait, wait, is there plastic in here and glass?
Yeah, whatever.
I don't want to separate that.
It's too much work for me.
See, I will reform the evil landlord villain.
Recycling now.
See, okay.
You can't paint the sand.
Okay, cool.
Well, it definitely feels like there's a lot more control.
I think you can build houses in this too.
Maybe not the demo, but I'm pretty sure that's what they're going to do.
I need something out.
This actually is making me annoyed to look at.
Um, let's go over the ground.
I don't know, like wood tile.
Wood panels.
Carpet.
What about tile?
What do they have tile?
Ooh, look at that.
I like this.
Oh, there's a picture of a tile.
Oh, I have to surface.
I, right.
Oh, let's do a test.
Cool.
That's way better than it used to be.
Wow.
Look at how cool that looks.
How do I put this down though?
And go back to the tools.
Hold right mouse button.
It was weird.
Oops.
It's like the ocean next to the ocean.
That's what I was going for.
That's what I want to be.
I want to go to like a beach and just lie there and just breathe in the air.
How come the grid is here still?
Okay.
Oh, there we go.
Nice.
I'm telling you right now, I'm going to give you a little bit of creative input here.
This has like a streamer room back wall that slowly has the lights kind of move and pulsate
through here.
Wow.
If this was just kind of like, and this kind of was a was a glowing soft green.
Whoa.
I'll give you a little bit of creative input.
Are you the streamer?
No.
Oh, God.
No, I wouldn't have that.
No, that would be fucking tacky.
You don't catch me fucking doing that.
Having like a back wall that's like water next to and you're in like your beach house
and pulses.
And this kind of goes, no, would never catch me doing that.
I want to do it so bad.
Let's go with like a, what should I do here?
Smart home options.
Okay.
Wait, can I have this connected to the stove?
All right.
Can the light switch turn the stove on?
That's a very important question.
We're going to find out.
Magic beans.
Oh, I can see it already.
All right.
Let's get rid of this.
You missed a spot.
I need to clear everything out.
I don't like.
TV goes right here.
Where's the kitchen?
I don't know.
Now you like it all of a sudden.
Okay.
Yeah.
So how does, how do I clean this?
Do I have to mop it or vacuum it?
Okay.
Yeah.
No, I'm throwing this upside down.
Every kitchen usually is that kind of like beige, sand, brown, yellows.
That's a lot of kitchens, especially that I'm going different.
I'm doing like a green kitchen.
Okay.
I need floor, floor.
I need something for the floor, floor board.
Is there a way to quickly get to just like, there we go.
Okay.
Um, just, I want like floor stuff.
Construction, surface finishes, particle board, cool green paint.
Let's try it.
I feel like this is going to look all right.
How do I use the paint tape?
The paint tape.
Paint tape.
When does this come out?
When does the house number two come out?
I like it.
It's not bad.
I need to go outside and sell all these.
Nice infected armpit green.
Why do you know what that is?
That's what?
Infected armpit.
This looks nice.
Let's get to clean the windows up and we're good.
I hope your stomach is doing better.
Yeah, I'll be all right.
I'm good.
I just had to take care of that before the stream started.
I'm good though.
Make it bluer.
Uh, I mean, we've got cyan and gray.
We all know how much I like that one.
Blue paint.
Maybe, should I try the blue?
Cyan and gray.
Cyan and gray vibrant.
Faded.
Let's try this one.
This apparently is vibrant.
I wouldn't call that vibrant.
This is almost too blue.
No, no, no, no.
That's way too blue.
Way too much.
The green is better.
Green is better.
Landlord special.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm just putting all these buckets of paint under one giant bucket.
Oh, what are you going to do with it?
I plan on throwing it as hard as I can against the wall.
Right in the middle.
Combining four or five buckets of paint.
Hey, while you're here, can you look at the sink?
No, no.
No, I don't think so.
Rents do, by the way.
I like it.
All right.
Now, this is going to stay...
Where did all this come from?
It's trash.
Did I break a window?
Why?
I thought I cleaned this already.
What's up with this?
What is that?
This one thing that didn't get painted right?
Get a girl out.
What about the ground?
I'll try this.
I just want to see what it looks like.
That's it.
We're going to do a small test to see how it is.
I need to pick it up.
Hold to start finishing.
I want to...
Wait, is it...
What's happening?
Well, I want to pick these up.
Can I not press E?
Oh, this is weird.
How high are you right now?
No, it's just I'm not used to it.
Because you have to do this part first
and then you put this away
and then pick up the tiles
and then press E here.
Okay.
I'm not a...
I'm a big fan of it, actually.
It reflects everything.
I'm going to do it.
Yeah, I'm going to do it.
That's cool.
That's how you do it.
Okay.
Now, I can't technically go out of here.
I like it.
You did good.
Hey, thanks.
Cool.
You're making a Hilton hotel.
This place is pretty nice.
I like it.
I just need a stove and a fridge.
I'm going to see if I can make this stove
turn on with this switch right here.
We'll get...
Hold on.
We're getting to about an hour in this game.
We're like 40 minutes into this game.
There's other demos to play.
I'm going to give this another 10 to 15 minutes
and we'll move on to the next one.
I saved the first two to do first
because I knew it was going to take
the most amount of time.
Lies of P and House Lipper 2.
Don't worry.
If you don't think I'm going to play this
until I puke when it comes out,
you're dreaming.
All right.
What do I want to do?
Fridge.
Let's go.
It's like a...
It's a beach house.
I can't open it.
Oops.
No, I want a real fridge.
I mean, it is a real fridge, but this one matches.
That matches what I'm going for.
Are you going for ugly?
I'm going for swanky.
I can't paint it.
Okay.
Nice.
I like how the Twitch has the warning
that this says the stream is content
for mature audiences,
but you're playing House Flipper.
I'm assuming that's what you said after that.
I mean, that's on every stream.
I've never turned that off.
I think they changed it
to now it's more elaborate system,
but that's been on forever because he swears.
I mean, I would consider this stream
to be a mature audience stream.
He's M-rated.
I think so.
Guys, a running joke on the channel
was about me shoving a baseball up my ass.
Yeah, I'm going to keep the mature audience filter on.
I think it should stay.
I'm getting really comfy right now
and I'll stay here all day.
Okay, we're moving on.
I got to move on.
I'll stay here all day.
I love these games so much.
I'm ready to play this when it releases.
I like the new features.
I think there's a lot more control now.
It seems like it's going to be fun.
Think of how much content there'll be
when this releases.
When does this come up?
Test the stove.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't think you can do it.
Should do another House Flipper thing with Ludwig.
I think that when this game comes out,
I have a very fun idea
and it's kind of like the thing
that we did on the stream I did with Ludwig.
Imagine a stream.
Don't steal this.
It's mine.
I'm the House Flipper guy.
You know what?
Never mind.
You'll steal it.
Somebody will steal it.
No, you're going to steal it.
Bro, no, you're going to steal it.
And then you'll get 100 billion views and I won't.
All right, this is cool.
I like it a lot.
I'm looking forward when it comes out.
Wishlist.
Dude, HGTV did this 19 years ago.
I'm kidding around.
I want to get streamers to make houses in this game and judge them.
So at the same time, everybody makes a house.
You know, you got like six, seven, eight potential streamers.
They all make a house.
They all have the same amount of time.
And I go through and have to grade them.
I think that's fun.
You literally did that.
Yeah, but I'm talking about much more elaborate.
Stolen.
Here it comes.
That's fine.
I walk around with a clipboard and it's me judging it.
You have terrible taste.
I think that's why I want to do it.
Community house building.
No one could steal this.
I know that elaborate idea of play house flipper and I grade your house.
Whoa, we're talking fucking gold.
All right, let's keep going.
That was fun.
I really like it.
What am I going to play next?
How about I could do we do a bunch in a row now
because those are the ones I knew I wanted to at least hang out in for like a few minutes.
What?
Where did my steam go?
I think my steam crashed.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
That was my steam.
Well, let's try this again.
Well, my steam is messed up.
I can't even open steam anymore.
This is weird.
Hold on.
Take a break anyways.
I'll be right back.
I'll take a quick break.
Get this fixed and use the bathroom.
See you in a minute.
Okay, I'm back.
I fixed it.
I had to restart steam.
The next demo we're going to check out is called pull stay.
Pull stay.
Beat him up.
Tower defense mechanics?
I don't know.
Looked interesting.
Let's try it.
Controller.
Let me try it.
That's a weird resolution.
Pull stay.
Here it is.
I don't know if it's too loud.
Play.
Move, run.
Okay.
Attack, jump.
There we go.
All right.
Attack, jump.
Plus one ore.
Grab an enemy to throw.
How do you grab an enemy?
You can run over enemies.
Oh, you run.
You walk into them.
I see.
Run over enemies on the ground.
Interact objects.
Okay.
They are coming.
How do I use the chair?
Please help me, Robo.
I'm here on the second floor.
Make sure nobody comes into my room.
Oh, shit.
I got to go to the second floor like right now.
Can I run faster?
Choose an item.
Lower damage.
Increase attack power.
Where is this dude's room?
I'm up on the second floor, right?
Oh, here we go.
All right.
I'm here to protect you.
Help me.
Soon.
Someone came upstairs.
I can hear footsteps almost here.
Hey, Robo.
Don't forget that.
You can teleport toward me when I am cornered.
Press attack and jump at the same time.
It will unleash rising tackle.
You would lose your health accordingly, though.
All right.
Watch out.
I got to get out there.
Don't worry.
They won't get in.
Good.
You learned Goran Nappa while running.
How do you run?
I feel like they will be back soon.
Okay.
Let's prepare for that while open homework menu.
Uh, attack bar.
You can sit.
Hold on.
What does it say?
Dang.
They're coming back with their friend.
I felt this would happen.
Oh, no.
So I should go downstairs.
Can I go back downstairs?
Tap when the stairs room or second floor.
Almost done.
Oh, he's making my upgrade.
I want to use that sword more.
All right.
Get him.
We're good.
Only one more enemy.
Thank you, Robo.
Now we have a time to prepare for the next wave.
All right.
Give it to me.
Change weapon.
What should I use?
The flute?
What is that?
I'm using the triangle.
Yeah.
What is going on?
Why?
Why am I doing this?
How do I do this?
How do I hit the ball?
Oh, okay.
I did it.
Motivated.
What is going on?
Is somebody breaking into our neighbor's house?
It's time for some free time.
Oh, all right.
I got my upgrade.
Make another one.
I love this.
It's got a charm to it.
I'm interested in what you do with the actual stuff on the top.
You've ore and crystals.
I have no idea what's going on, but I'm curious.
Press B.
He's not done making it.
All right.
Here they come.
Where do they actually come in from?
Is this the dollhouse?
It kind of is.
Am I dead?
No.
All right.
I'm going to die.
How do I get away from that?
You learned knee kick.
They tricked us.
They're breaking into our backyard.
Buddy, go cover the west side.
Do I have any heals?
Fuck out of here.
I'm dead if I get hit once.
Holy shit.
What just happened?
All right.
Beat the first level.
They are coming.
Are you almost done with that upgrade?
Come on.
Hurry up.
Make sure nobody comes in my room.
All right.
I got you.
You learned karate kick.
What is this guy eating?
Attack power up.
We're good.
I don't know where that guy came from.
Who's running?
Whose shadow is that?
Wait.
Are they almost in the room?
They're almost in the room.
Oh, my God.
Help me.
I'm coming.
I'm here.
How do I?
Okay.
There we go.
I can get them on the ground.
Free time.
Nice.
Next wave.
Should I do health or defense?
Let's do defense.
Don't get hit.
Awesome.
Defense equals health.
Five head.
Task completed.
All right.
Where is it out here?
Say hello to delinquent.
Lovely day, isn't it?
I...
Yeah.
All right.
What do I do?
God.
Can I do this?
I can't.
I'm getting so many materials.
Holy shit.
Give me all of it.
How do you sprint?
They're in his room.
I gotta go.
I got it.
I'm fine.
Stop.
Okay.
Can you make any more?
Don't do that.
Dude.
What is this guy doing?
You learned pile driver.
Grab an enemy jump and then press X.
All right.
Free time.
I need you to make health.
I want to go explore the world though.
Interact with the clock.
Oh, you can have the next wave come immediately.
Hold on.
What is this?
What do I do that for?
Does that mean it's all the way over here?
Where's this health?
That's a huge...
Uh-oh.
Oh, no.
I might...
No, I'm good.
Where's the health?
That was...
All right.
This game is fucking great.
I don't care what anybody says.
Why did it...
Where is my health?
You learned stamp, stamp.
In front of a lying enemy, it's down, down.
Give me that.
Down, down.
What's that sound?
All right.
Make a defense coding.
Something else I can do back here.
Did I actually just ruin everything?
But wait, what can I do about this?
Oh, all right.
Make a...
Make another one of those.
Build an extra room.
Kitchen, bathroom, living room, living room.
And then a bathroom.
All right.
We're good.
Does the damage increase depending on how high you go?
They're in the room.
How do I do the move?
I got to get over there.
Go!
Get over there!
This dude's embedded into the wall.
Jump, dive kick, back downstairs.
Can you make some more items, please?
What's that?
What's in your head?
Yeah, what is that?
Short of resources?
Oh, I need crystals.
Where do I get resources?
I did it.
Sundown.
They are coming.
I think I have to break stuff on either side, right?
That scared the shit out of me.
Get up.
All right.
This move was good, but not really because it takes too much time.
The animation takes too long.
It's not DPS efficient.
I need health.
Really bad.
I'm all right.
I have two lives, I think.
Okay.
Actually, let me take the health and then I want to go break this stuff over here to
get materials, right?
That makes sense, doesn't it?
There's nothing else over here, right?
I didn't finish the one on the other side.
That was a mistake.
These guys are the worst.
There's so many people on this other side.
It's ridiculous.
What is this?
A booby pie?
What did I just do?
Oh, it automatically attacks.
Does it heal?
Help me soon.
Did they actually get in?
Damage.
Yes.
Okay.
It's not ready yet.
All right.
I need to make some defense here.
How do I do it?
Body pillow?
Toothpaste tube.
What is body pillow?
What the fuck is this for?
Ultra glove.
Wait, can I put it on?
Oh my God.
Okay.
Hold on a second.
Where are they coming from?
I see them.
I see you pieces of shit.
Handle this.
I have to look down.
What the fuck just happened?
I'm dead.
How do I get back there?
Okay.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Are they killing them?
They're going to get in.
I got to pile drive this guy out of the sky box.
One more.
What's going on?
Is there a train coming?
Why is there a train coming?
Citroen grill?
I need resources.
Okay.
This is hurting my eyes.
Get out.
I need a pile driver.
Can we do demos all night in sorcery tomorrow?
I, you know, I would say yes,
but the council of sorcery
would be very, very upset with me if I said yes.
Time field collapse detected.
High energy phenomenon is approaching to us.
If we are waiting here, our neighbors might be harmed badly.
Let's counter him on the way.
Jesus.
All right.
It's too red.
This is loud.
Get in there.
Give me that.
Where is it?
What?
Pick it up.
Give me that.
All right.
I got it.
That just killed me.
Let's get a virtual boy on.
Yeah.
All right.
Just, just bully.
Don't, do not let him even do anything.
Just chain grab.
Be obnoxious.
All right.
Got him.
I got him.
Hey, thank you for playing.
So that was, that was called pole stay.
The name of that one.
That was a wild ride.
Pole stay.
All right.
Next one.
That one was quick.
That was snappy.
I don't know when that one comes on.
How about pizza possum?
That was pretty pog to me.
Let's try pizza possum.
And it's, it's going to be bright when I press this button.
Just to give you a warning.
Very bright.
You ready?
Pizza possum.
Let's go.
Okay.
You eat food.
Oh, I have to eat food and then I get a key.
Do I have to not get spotted?
That was pizza possum.
That was fun.
Okay.
You have to eat and not get spotted.
I get it.
Oh, shit.
Can you jump?
Shit.
All right.
This is fun.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
So if I press, I can eat the food if I press a button.
No, I can't.
All right.
I guess let's slow down.
Got it.
How long can I do this for?
Oh, you can hide.
Now I want a pizza.
Wait a minute.
I'm too fat.
I think if you eat too much, you get big.
How come I'm eating so many of them?
Wait, nobody's hostile here.
Drop all your tomatoes.
I think things respawn too.
All right.
I can't.
Wait.
Okay.
Checkpoint.
This is the...
Wait a minute.
It might be a problem here.
Excuse me.
This is the sorcery enjoyers high council.
We would allow you to play the game tomorrow if you promise to play at least for four or more hours.
If this is not met, know that flanker is already on standby.
There is a curse placed upon you that will go into effect as well.
Hmm.
No, we'll do it today.
Energy drink for a quick boost.
So if there's no jump, how would I...
I'm just kind of a nuisance.
Okay.
So the dogs are security guards.
Holy shit.
There's a lot of ice cream.
No.
All right.
Dogs love chasing bones.
This game is very cute.
I like it.
Try one more time.
Just outrun the dog and you're good.
Can you turn around?
What game is this?
This game is called pizza possum.
Get that bone.
Give me all the ice cream.
All right.
I almost have enough.
Zeppola?
He's going to start sorcery and then he's going to end the stream.
No, that's not going to happen.
All right.
So it's about getting the best route because everything respawns.
So you're really going to just kind of go fast and eat, eat, eat, eat, and then open the door.
No, we're going to play sorcery.
Don't worry.
We're going to play sorcery for at least two to three hours.
At least.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I got you.
Council is displeased.
We'll just wait till the council here is flanker talk again for the first time in like a year.
Hmm.
I think it's going to go.
Go.
All right.
If you do too much too quick, you that's what slows you down.
I get it.
I like the soundtrack plays kind of while you're doing things.
Turn around.
Ah, I got a key.
I got a key.
Wait, that was illegal.
All right.
One more time.
And I'm done.
I'm going to throw a bone.
How long does the bone last?
Not that long.
Okay.
And I'm not going to screw up.
All right.
We're almost there.
Give me.
All right.
I can open this door.
Looks so real.
Dogs won't be able to tell the difference.
It's a dog mask.
Oh, I'm going to put it on and run right through.
That's silly.
This is silly.
Okay.
I'm going down.
So you slowly unlock the level.
This is silly.
Look at that over there.
Look at that huge feast over there.
This is going to be insane.
All right.
Hide.
I need the whole thing.
I think I got it all.
It's awesome.
Thank you.
Hungry wish list.
Oh, okay.
It was timed.
I liked it.
That was cute.
You know, this is a game that I could see myself
just kind of relaxing in bed and playing it.
I liked it.
Nice job.
All right.
We're going to do.
This is another kind of more chilled out relaxing one.
This is called Station to Station.
Looks like you build a train station.
I know.
I think this is not a controller game.
You guys ready to chill out?
Level one.
You can play Poly Bridge.
I've heard of it.
I've seen it.
Okay.
Complete all 12 buildings.
W A S D.
Click.
Zoom.
Hover over the building.
See what it does.
Wheat farm.
Buildings need to be connected to a station.
Press space bar or the station button to play stations.
Rotate the station with the scroll wheel.
Okay.
So what I want kind of put it like right here.
Start moving.
All right.
What does it want it?
The mill requires wheat.
Click on the station connector to build a railroad.
Oh.
Ooh.
And it makes the world look pretty.
All right.
You got money.
Receiving money also unlocks new buildings.
Hover over the building again to see what it has completed.
Each wheat farm can supply only one mill.
So the new wheat farm needs to be connected to a different mill than the one you already used.
Okay.
All right.
Let's go.
Check this.
Check it out.
Wait did it mean oh I needed to connect these two.
Uh it's fine.
I'm just seeing what you could do.
Waste of government funds.
I did it for fun.
What are you talking about?
Start building from this station.
Okay.
Tricky terrain ahead.
Click the highlighted area.
Yep.
Not that tricky.
Please somebody saying please develop this for the switch.
Yeah this has huge potential to be just fun to make railroads.
All right.
The building.
Check the supply and demand of the new building.
Needs produces.
It produces milk.
What does it need though?
Nothing.
This needs milk.
The cheesery.
Okay.
So this produces milk.
This needs milk.
So let's go for this.
Ready?
Is this gonna work?
So this needs milk.
Got it.
Oh shit it just got way harder.
Buildings can be indirectly connected instead of directly connecting this cheeseery to the
dairy farm on the other side of the map.
Or I connected them both to a nearby station on the network.
Does this count?
Like can I go like this?
Does that count?
Like can I stop here and then go?
Yeah it works.
I mean you can do it.
You can do it.
Stop.
I don't even know how the game works.
I'm just it's literally tutorial.
Mobile game ad.
It's the tutorial.
It is gonna be a mobile game ad when you're in the tutorial for the game.
Look at that.
Cool.
All right.
Let's do the next level.
I like this one a lot.
Look at that.
Next level.
Let's go.
All right.
I get it now and it's gonna be fun.
That's the goal.
Cheap rails.
The rails cost half the regular price.
Bridge price is unchanged.
I don't think I want to do this right now.
All right.
What's the goal?
I need milk.
So I got milk milk.
All right.
We got two cheeseries.
Is that what they're called?
So we got double cheese.
I'm gonna put this one here in case I need to go bridge up this way.
So let's go like this.
Aim it like that.
Like that.
Okay.
So then we need a connection from here to here.
And then a connection from here to here.
Let's make it smooth and not like shit.
I might have to come down here with the other track.
Here we go.
Done.
Give us some new stuff.
New cards.
I click to draw cards.
You get a hand.
When are you gonna play Fortnite creative mode?
The only time I've ever played Fortnite for real was during the tournament that Ludwig did.
And then I said I'll never play it ever again after that.
Ever.
Yeah.
I saw the clip.
I saw the clip of Myth and Ludwig just laughing their asses off at my game flight.
They got like 60 million views, by the way.
I can never return to that game.
All right.
What is this?
Flour.
This makes bread.
So I need flour.
Where's the flour production facility?
This makes flour.
So starting here.
I'm gonna go up bridge mode this way.
Because this needs wheat.
So we need to go this way.
Bridge.
Expensive.
But, you know, I think it's worth it.
And then that could connect to here.
Because then the flour can come back through here and make the bread.
What are you?
Dumb?
All right.
Now we need to go from producers wheat to flour.
Looks good.
And then we come back this way.
Right?
Through here.
Bingo.
And then press tab or hover over the complete level button to highlight.
Wait, what is it?
Highlight.
Oh, incomplete buildings.
Wait, what's wrong here?
Oh, this is making cheese.
This is probably like a cheese steak factory or something, right?
All right.
They want cheese.
They want everything.
Okay.
So the city needs bread, milk, and cheese.
The bread is here.
So this is making bread.
I'm going to have it come back this way.
Let's just double it up.
This is going to connect.
Double it up.
No, this is getting bread.
So this is making.
We need to make milk.
Double it up.
Does anybody need more milk?
I mean, they do.
I don't think anybody else needs it.
No other like cheese building.
This one's pretty easy.
Wait, how do I get the cheese over here?
Oh, like this.
I didn't even spend any of these yet.
What about city skylines too?
Oh, you better believe it.
He is not going to play sorcery.
Yes, I am.
What time is it?
Oh, shit.
Okay.
This needs everything.
Milk can come up here.
All right.
We're going to do cheap bridges.
How do I activate it?
Do I even wait?
Milk coming up here.
Cheap bridges.
Yeah, I want a cheap bridge.
Look at that.
Cheese is going up here.
Milk heading this way.
Cheese.
And now I need to make bread connection.
Bakery is making bread.
Cheap bridges.
Oh, shit.
Wait.
Well, it looks nicer.
It's fine.
I mean, lies of J.
Lies of J.
What do you mean?
I'm going to play sorcery.
I'm still having fun in the demos.
I've been live for three hours.
It's not.
I've been having my life for like eight hours.
This still needs bread.
Wait.
Oh, I have to go here.
Okay.
I don't need money.
I did it.
Yeah.
I almost had it.
All right.
Let's do another one.
This was called station to say station.
Station to station.
I liked it.
Let's do another one.
How about legendary hoplite?
And then we'll move to sorcery after this.
Play viewfinder.
I actually have that one up here too.
That was a good one.
All right.
Viewfinder or legendary hoplite?
Which one?
Viewfinder.
Try viewfinder.
Graphics.
Okay.
A little bit.
Start demo.
Great.
We're in.
Time to explore.
Okay.
Wait.
Way too high.
Time to explore.
What we got?
Coffee can.
It's a very pretty game.
Coding.
There's no time to talk like the present.
You can build anything.
Yet you start to build a lab.
I'm afraid the butter flavor is a work in progress.
We're coding pillows to watch the footage popcorn next.
To think all the wonders of the world can be doubled with
as long as you build the right space.
Whether Hiraya wants to admit it or not,
Mirren is truly brilliant.
Now how do I get out of here?
Hmm.
What is this place?
Ooh.
I've never seen this much overgrowth before.
It's...
Sky!
Whoa, you okay?
Uh, your vials look good.
I guess we know now that falling doesn't hurt.
That's some good news at least.
There must be a way to get back up there.
What?
I took way too long.
Did I run out of time?
You're what? That's sick!
I didn't want to do the whole demo again.
To think all the wonders of the world can be doubled with
as long as you build the right space.
Okay.
Whether Hiraya wants to admit it or not,
Mirren is truly brilliant.
I'm fine.
What's an old photograph doing here?
Do not double tap R.
I'm telling you, it takes you to the very beginning.
What the fuck just happened?
Whoa, okay, that's kind of cool.
Did, hang on, did you just shift reality?
A teleporter!
Glad you made it in one piece.
Hmm, interesting.
Gonna power it!
How do I power this?
Is this technically traditional?
It's two batteries.
Have you charged one?
Enough questions.
Stop moving.
Smile.
That was pretty cool.
I thought outside the box big time.
It's almost working.
Looks like we need one more.
Yeah, just hold the thing upside down.
Just let all the shit fall out.
I wasn't smart, it was just lazy.
I feel like it's...
Oh shit, maybe that was not a good idea.
What direction am I falling?
This is really, really neat.
Uh, looks fine like that.
Just one?
I should just put it upside down.
How do they even do this?
There is a, there's a coder who probably has spent a very long time
tediously making this possible.
They just made that up.
Made it up.
Wait, it wants me to make a bridge.
I was just curious what happened.
Made it up.
Close enough.
Uh, there's some programmer right now that's sitting there saying
you chat motherfuckers have no idea how difficult this was to do.
Actually, cool.
Okay.
Chill, bro.
Well, I'm...
That's what I would be saying.
Maybe there's a surface you can use to climb up there.
I need, I need to understand.
Climb the surface?
Beautiful as it is.
Whoa.
Carries so much weight.
There is promise here.
Promise of a future we can surely achieve.
Even now, I'm striving to reach heights I never thought possible.
All that I hope is that, that everything we do here continues...
Ah, it shows you where the other ones are too.
...up there as well.
For our sake.
For Miren's sake.
Climb this?
Wait, I'm confused.
There we go.
Is this game out?
When does this one come out?
Because this one's really fun.
July?
Three weeks?
Okay, remind me to play this.
What's happening?
All right, I need to go back.
How do I get back to where I was?
Oh, shit.
I'm back.
I'm fine.
But your nose...
I'm bleeding nose.
News bleeding.
I'm fine.
Oh, hold on.
Let me put my middle finger up and put it under my nose.
My god.
This is a way better way to reveal that.
Have the blood come out of their eyes.
Nobody does that though.
Plus two, that changed my mind.
Good.
This one's a little different.
Can I actually go into this one?
Sorry, the edible hit right when I saw this one.
That's pretty magical though, I'll say.
What?
Cool.
I like how each one has a backdrop.
It's a nice touch.
Can I go in?
Like a dungeon?
My mouth is open.
I just want to make sure you know that.
Cool.
Did I miss a picture?
Wait.
Ah.
All right, let's fuck this whole thing up.
That wasn't gonna...
Okay.
Shit.
Hey, good one.
It was all right.
Wait, the demo's over?
Take a photo?
I gotta get this lined up.
That's how you take a photo right there.
That's how you take a pristine photo.
All right.
This is fucked.
Oh.
I'm all right.
All right, I gotta go all the way back.
I really like this one.
All right, this is a cool game.
I'm playing it on launch day.
You get five charges on the camera.
All right, so this is what they want me to do.
They want you to take a picture like this.
And then flip it around.
Like that.
Very nice.
Ah.
I get it.
And then I gotta go over here.
Some of these are gonna get way too big brained for me.
But it's cool nonetheless.
All right, so let's go.
Upside down strat works pretty well here.
How many do I need?
Probably three?
Let's see.
I might need a screwdriver.
Hey dude, we need...
Oh, it's only two.
Okay.
Oh, wait a minute.
Go back and spin it.
Wait, can I flip it around?
Wait, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What if I go like this?
Does this fucking do anything?
It does.
All right, it does, it does, it does.
We're good now.
Is that an account?
Oh, wait.
Oh, it's over.
Yeah, I'm playing this day one.
This is great.
That might be the highlight of the whole day so far.
And they've all been good.
I've enjoyed each one of them.
All right, I think it's time to take a break.
Come back, play some Sorcery.
Those of you that don't know what Sorcery is,
we have a lot of catching up to do.
I'm going to do my best to spend 10 seconds telling you what it is.
I'll do some more NexFest.
Well, wait, when is it done?
When's it done, done?
A couple of days, right?
Oh, because I want to play Final Fantasy 16 and just kind of hang out.
Maybe we'll shoot for Monday?
Is it over Monday or is it Monday all day and over technically on the 27th?
Yeah, we'll do Sorcery now.
Excited for House Flipper 2.
I'm going to lower the volume so it's not horrible.