An ally has been... Oh my god. Oh my dog just farted. Oh, this sucks. It's horrible, dude. I can't...
You're shitting me right now. I can't even, like, play the game. Be careful, they're right here. I can't even... I can't get...
Smite's one of those games where you can't leave. I can't leave right now. I have to, like, accept this for what happened.
It's not like I can just get up and, like, walk away right now.
Seriously? Man, this is horrendous. Oh god, hold on. No, I'm serious right now. Hold on a second. I'm wicked sorry.
Oh my god. I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming. Here I come. Oh, you guys don't even need my help, do you?
My ult didn't even go off. I got him. Oh, I'm sorry. Seriously? Alright.
Alright, go on. Shoo. Dude, can you imagine if, like, I just, like, if you guys both died right there?
Oh, dragon, dragon. What? Yeah, that was weird. I saw that. No, that was miles away, but I, like, got hit instantly.
What? He's going down. He's gonna die. I don't believe it. Oh, he's gonna die, don't worry. Don't you worry nothing.
Don't you worry nothing. This dragon is toast. No, you're toast. No, I just saw him. You're dead. You are dead.
Fucking dog. Oh, god damn it. If this dog didn't, like, fart in my face, like, that would not have happened.
He didn't, like, poop. No, he didn't. He's right here. Have you, like, checked the floor?
No, there's no, like, ugh. That, like, completely threw my game off. We were doing, like, oh, actually, we killed him, but I was doing, like, well, and then the dog farted in my face, and it was just over.