Hi guys. Let's talk about this. No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait. I'm flustered already.
And I haven't even started anything. A little ill. I've been feeling ill. I've been watching TV.
But listen, I just found the dumbest fucking thing I've ever seen on a computer. And it's on
my computer. I own a computer and I found the worst thing ever. All the shit that I talk about. Oh,
I can't believe this. This person has this. Can't believe this company. I have the worst
computer case. I just found out why. Just in a moment, you'll find out. I'm gonna tweet that.
One second. All right. So I, as you guys know, I'm just your average Joe. I'm not a computer
scientist. I dabble in it sometimes. I think it's fun to build them. But here's the issue. I got a
USB cable. I have the USB front panel right on the top of my computer on the case is USBs. Four of
them. And then next to that is this thing called the power button, where you press it and your
computer turns on. Or if you hold it, you can force shut off. Everybody has power button. Okay.
If for some reason, directly next to the left of the power button is a reset button,
and it is touch sensitive. I didn't, I just found this out. I'm trying to plug in my USB from my
fucking Xbox controller. And I like slightly grazed this other little button right to the
right of that slot. And my computer reset. What is the, what does that, what function is that?
Why would you have a fucking Nintendo reset button on a PC? Is this a fucking Super Nintendo? Why is
that here? To reset the computer. No, it's a restart, not like a reset. That fucking thing.
No bullshit. Here's what that thing should be. Okay. Shouldn't be a button that you can just
like slightly graze and then it's a meme audio. You're trying to turn on the fucking Nintendo.
No, no, no. Have that be a hole where you can stick a fucking pin in like a actual reset button.
I can't fucking believe it. I turned my computer off. I was about to turn the stream on.
My computer restarted and I had to set everything back up again. Oh, I was fucking flustered.
Just don't press the button. What, but what, but why is it there? Fucking computer cases, man.
The things that just goddamn plastic and steel. That's what people want. Don't, you don't have to
add any frills. Just give me the good face plate and things made it a goddamn plastic and glass.
It's all right. You don't have to do that. Some fun buttons. How about this one is like the help
button. My keyboard. You got a keyboard. Look down right now at your keyboard. Does it have a help
button? Pry it off with pliers. Tonight we're going to play Celeste. As you can see on the
screen right now. There it is. Jeremy, are you okay right now? Yeah, I just, I couldn't believe it. I
couldn't believe that I accidentally restarted my computer because I tried to plug a USB in.
I hope you guys had a good few days. I haven't seen you guys in a little while.
Was not supposed to be off yesterday, but I was feeling fucking shitty physically.
And I really didn't think I was going to be able to sit here for, you know, three, four, five plus
hours. So, but I thought I should be okay today. I should be okay today. I mean, okay right now.
Yeah. You can always tell my level of health by the old person rant that I do at the beginning of
the stream and how many swear words were in it. So I don't know. I have no idea what this game is
about. I know that it's a game about climbing up a mountain and I know it's a platformer.
I don't know. It's kind of like in the realm of Super Meat Boy. Am I wrong? Is this completely,
is this not even the right way to describe this game? Is this like Super Meat Boy? Kind of. Well,
let's find out. What do you say? I have been told, Jeremy, you have to turn the music up.
Otherwise I'm leaving. So we're going to turn it down a couple of notches and let's get the
sound in a good spot. Sounds about right. Ah, all right. Fine. We'll get it to five,
six and a five for the general average rating. This stream is probably going to get by the end
of the stream from the audience itself. Now let's climb. Did I choose, choose character?
Assist mode. Should I, what should I do about that? Should I keep the assist mode off? Rename.
Uh, keep it off. How about a series of numbers? Jax. Should it be Jax? I don't know. I've been
feeling kind of ill the last couple of days. I'm not sure Jax is going to make an appearance.
Jax is down in my like lower intestine right now, hiding. Is there like a, okay, is there a
mid-level Jax that we can try to figure out here? Cause Jax is like Super God. Jonks? Does that work?
How about just Jon? All right. Jonks. Jon. Just J-O-N. Jonks. Now I think it has to be Jon.
This Jerma, this Jax, and then his Jon. You guys don't want Jon. Let me just tell you.
If today's going to be a Jon day, this is it. Jon. Oh man. I can already tell I'm going to have
problems. Just breathe. Okay. I'll listen. Should I breathe out? Okay. What's wrong with my computer?
What is wrong? What's my computer doing? What's wrong with my computer? Whoa. What the fuck?
I got a virus. There must be a virus. All right. So press A to jump. Press B to jump. Press A to
jump. Press C to jump. Press B to jump. Oh, okay. This is not, how do I read? Is there a fast run?
If I hold down Super Meat Boy Y, hold LT to climb and then press up. Okay. That's not,
that's not bad. I will say I'm okay. Does right trigger do the same thing? It does. I would rather
do right trigger. He's asking a question in the tutorial. What? Just, just relax. Okay. Did you
breathe? Excuse me, ma'am. Do you want me to do, do you want me to do voice acting here?
The sign is busted. This, is this mountain, is this the mountain trail?
You're almost there. It's across the bridge.
Tell us about your driveway. The bridge collapsed and I nearly died.
My driveway almost did you in. The mountain might be a bit much for you.
Is Jerma doing the beeps? I don't know what, I have no idea what you're talking about.
My computer's making weird noises though.
Well, if I'm an old bat, like you can survive out here. Like I think you'll be, there's no likes.
Like if I'm an old bat and like, why am I doing that? But you should know Celeste mountain is a
strange place. You might see things, things you ain't ready to see. Uh, you should seek help lady.
That lady just did the Super Mario fucking theme song. She's still laughing at me.
Is the bridge going to collapse? Of course it should. Dash. Ah, there's a dash. Okay.
So X is dash. You can do this. I know. I mean, I know I can. You're talking to her.
You're talking to John. So there's a level select. Chapter one forsaken city. Climate.
Click save and quit from the pause menu at any time to take a break.
You resume from the same screen and you won't lose any progress. You know
when a video game gives you the we-mote take a break sun warning that you're probably going to
have to at some point cause it's going to be hard. Okay. Oh, I got to change that one because I'm
used to holding down that X or square button for a fast run. It's just the platform of blood that
runs through my veins. All of you know what I'm talking about. Holding down X, holding down Y
to just the run. Oh man. I'm good. I can go up or down. Jump. So what is that? A thousand points.
I don't know. Wait, I'm not done. Okay. I only got one. I'm like, ah, I only got one dash.
And when you're okay, when your hair is blue, you've used your dash. That's a really good
fucking high quality indicator to know that you did it. Can it go down? No, that's not down. All
right. Here we go. All right. I, I figured it out. You, there are Yakwas in this one.
There are Yakwas. Hmm. So I can go, uh, so is it just each stage is a different
Mega Man screen? Is that what I'm understanding? Straight up. Yes. Basically. Okay. That's cool.
What about down there? Is there a secret? Are there secrets in this game that I need to know about?
I already figured out the Yakwas. Okay. But I needed to know if there's other secrets.
Whoa, whoa, what happened? What's going on? You can only hold on for so long. Okay. I get it.
How long can you hold on long here? All right. I see nothing up in that little crevice.
Well, I guess we're just going to go. I just got baited. So these things, I can get those.
This is no jumping and this is no dashing. Not allowed. Oh, or it goes away. I get it.
Okay. You're going to give me a challenge here. Don't speak so soon. Don't speak so soon streamer.
He doesn't even know. Just wait till he gets to the world too. Okay. Let's get the fruit. Oh,
carefully crafted. All right. So no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I got, I have a dash still.
Just don't use it until right now. So what do you, what do I get for the, uh,
the stroke, the snowberries? Is there like an upgrade feature? It's an ending. Don't tell me
the ending. I don't want to know the ending. Oh, here's the ending by the way. Oh my God.
What have you done? Uh, anonymous gifter anonymous just gave 20 community subs. Well, whoever you
are. Uh, thank you. Really appreciate it. That's a lot. That's fucking so much money. Thank you.
And congratulations to all the people that got a community sub. You can now put
emotes in the chat and not affected by slow mode and you don't get any ads and I don't play ads
on the stream anyways, but you know, all right, let's see. Can I look or should I just look around,
just explore? That's a death, right? Oh, there's a strawberry over there. Pay to win chat. Uh oh.
I'll figure it out. My brain is bigger than anyone's on earth. I can figure this out.
Uh, I think I need to go the other way. Oh shit. Okay. So you can actually, there's, there's physical
fitness movement in this. Okay. I get it. So you can actually use that stuff. Cool.
So that's a different little globe. Hmm. There's two of them as big as this gets. He's in one of
his moods, isn't he? The hell does that mean? Oh my God. Don't die again. No, don't. Oh my God.
I died again. I'm getting so angry at this game. Oh, does it count? No, I've got to complete the
level. Okay. He's happy now, but he won't be in a couple hours. Well then we're just going to have
to play GeoGuessr. Uh, the way I can get this. I have to go down and around. Look, this is a,
this is a Metroidvania. I'm going to unlock another ability. Maybe not. Hold on. I got it.
Another 10 community subs. 10 community subs from FergBernandes. Thank you. What?
Did I not get it? Huh? That's a speed run feature, isn't it? I got to get them both
in like five seconds. Whatever. This guy will tell me what to do.
No, you've heard it already. I'm not going to do it again.
What a killer night for a hike. I guess so.
Read chat. Read chat. Read chat. No. All right. Fine. This place is so crazy. I kind of can't,
really is the same noise though. I mean, you got to give me credit for even fucking,
give me some credit here. I didn't fucking know that this was going to happen.
I had no fucking idea. I just, you can ask anybody in this house. I just said,
I'm going to use this on stream today. And, but I mean, it's my computer making that noise. So
I mean, I'm going to use my computer on stream. Not the easiest climb, is it? But I guess that's
what I was looking for. Well, that sounds pretty serious. I'm just happy to see another human in
such a lonely place. It's the same fucking sound. I can't get over it. I'm not going to be able to
the whole time. Theo, by the way, an adventure from a far off land. It's not much of a talker,
are you? Serious lone wolf type. I get it. I just imagined some dark backstory for you.
This is where I bring my souls and I'm thinking, I'm thinking like a Dex build,
maybe a little bit of endurance, some vitality, and then stack resistance.
Dex, look, there's a fire here and there's an NPC in this little camp over there. Give me a break.
Well, John, I'd say you've come to the right place. I'm freezing my toes off,
but I can't imagine a better place for some quiet reflection.
Maybe you're right. Wait, what far off land do you hail from? Well, my inquisitive compatriot,
I don't hail from the mystical. It's going to be like Ohio or something. The mystical exotic kingdom
of Seattle. Got you. I wrote this. No, I did. No, I did. I did. No, I did. No, I did. Sounds like a
special place. Hey, okay. Anything else? Why would an entire city be abandoned?
I read that some mega corporations started building it, but then no one wanted to live here.
I wonder why. My money's on a government cover-up. What a waste to build all this for no reason.
At least we get to enjoy the leftovers. All right, thanks for the war.
Oh, my meat boy instincts are making me just jump off walls, and it's annoying me. This is blocked.
Keep talking. Are you here to explore this city? Yeah, I have a thing for abandoned places,
and I like to think of myself as a budding photographer. Oh, really? Cool. Do you have a
vlog or something? A vlog? John, everyone uses Instapix now. I'm Theo Understars. Look me up.
Instapix. This terrain's pretty tricky. Are you turning back soon?
Nope, I'm heading for the summit. I can really see the determination in your eyes.
It's inspiring. You say so. I bet you can make it to the summit too.
Maybe. I don't really care about reaching the top TBH. Oh, but I heard there are some legit old
ruins up beyond the city. Like 1800s legit. I know it's risky, but I have to see them for myself.
I'm gonna do this one more time. What's that thing you say right before you do something
irresponsible? You're okay. Let's whatever. I don't know. It's YOLO. I know it's YOLO.
Throw caution to the wind. Ah, no, that's not it. I'm thinking of.
This game loses a foe letter grade. Wait, but I gotta collect the gems.
I gotta figure out how this works. Wait, hold on. Oh, that's all that does? Well, what's the other
side do? All right, so now let's go get it. Let's go to the right. This is open. There's a lot of
ways to go. I missed a secret. Oh, I'm gonna miss them all. Don't worry. I did it. I did it,
but I didn't do it. Secret. I don't see a secret over here. How is he supposed to know that it is
a secret? I don't know. How would I know that? I can see this. I could go that way. No, we're
looking for just game completion. I can load this up later and YOLO into the secret. It's all I want.
It's not just a watch. It's a symbol. Stop saying that.
Are you beach ready? Oh, no. Super Meat Boy. Stop making me do things. No idea where I am.
I hope I'm going the right way. Secret over there, right? I found it. See? Ah, I think I got them.
No, I need that. Oh, shit. I didn't need to do the dash. Maybe I did. Yes, I did. I've got seven.
I'm not gonna do it. Okay, so I get to go. I guess I gotta do it faster. I gotta do it faster.
Meat Boy, stop fucking up my video game. Oh, Super Meat Boy. You made my muscle memory into Meat Boy.
Fuck. I gotta go faster. I gotta let go. Switch to commander video. I'm trying to do a double jump.
Oh, boy. I had it too. I got it. That counts, right? No, it doesn't. They give you these Pac-Man
fruits and I'm expected to get them all. You can't be expected to get them all. Maybe one. So what
does this do? Okay, here we go. I figured it out already. What first try? Guaranteed. No, no,
I'm just kidding. What have been? Oops. Damn it. All right, got it. So I'm gonna say at nine
bandages that I'm not gonna get anymore because I don't need them. Oh, I can't. Oh, shit. Did I get
it? Does it count? It counts. Fuck. Oops. I just was out of here. No, hold on. Okay, so we can go
up. There's a paid in-game currency right here. I was wrong. Did it wrong. Did it wrong again.
Okay, I'm gonna say up, over, left. Meat Boy. Don't, Meat Boy. Side, lift up, boing, boing.
Clown car joke incoming. I'm sorry to severely disappoint you, but I do not have a clown car
ready to go. Not right now. Yet. All right, where are we at? Can I go down? I might want to fix that then.
What, the clown? Clown car? It's probably in the closet already. Oh, shit. I get it. No, I don't. I
could just go around this way. Wait for a charge up and then I want to see down. Oh, come on. I landed
on the fucking shark teeth already. I was gonna say just do this. Oh, fuck. That was it. I had to
just wait for the charge. Derma, don't touch the spikes. Are you sure? Give me a, come on. It's
not gonna work, is it? Oh, fuck. Uh-oh. Yeah, I can't. It's wrong. It's wrong. You have to land for
the recharge to even happen. All right, so then I gotta go dash and what do I have to grab here then?
Oh, hmm. Oops. Can I knock this down? Ah, I can knock this down. Ah, I can knock that down.
But there's spikes on it. Grab the side? Apparently. What? I have to, all right, I gotta grab the side
of that and fall down with it and then jump off of it. You know I'm a fucking meat boy. I gotta get back over
there first. Holy shit, I'm just spamming. What are you spamming? Ow, my head. Just hold on. Hold on,
it'll do it again. First boss. I have to jump on his head three times. This memorial is dedicated
to those who perished on the climb. Okay, so I've made it. Here's the top of the mountain. I plant a
seed in there when a tree grows. I'm exhausted. But see, it's an orange tree. I'm not going to
use the automaton. This might have been a mistake. Ow, damn it. God, I thought that just said game
over. I was looking over here to my left and I turn and I'm just like game over. Oh, okay.
Ten. Ten out of twenty. What? There's so many more places. I have to go. Only ten berries. Yeah,
because there's a million places to go. There's so many places to go. This is chapter two old site.
Nice automaton, dude. Thanks. I really appreciate that. All right, give me a song. I'll do it right
off the bat. I will first try it. First song I see in the chat. All-star. And all that glitters is
gold. Oh, I have to press A. It's so annoying. Shut up. How dare you. I'm kidding. Don't shut up.
Some things are all weird now. Is there a secret message here?
This mirror dedicated to those... it's just backwards. That's not how you do it.
This is a really pretty land. I can get up there. Look, it's probably a berry up there. Move on,
John. I like this place. I knew it. I knew it. I knew that eventually they condition your brain
into thinking that falling down is bad. Falling down is good sometimes. I'm gonna get this. That's
the one I can see, so I'm gonna get this one. I thought I was supposed to be climbing a mountain.
What the fuck did I just do? What? I obviously have to go like this. Oh, all right. I figured
it out. I got it. There's even more of this. I went completely opposite direction of where I
may have supposed to be going. Oh, fuck. Okay. There's a secret down there. How do I get back
down there? How do I get... look. I think there's a secret right there. No. How do I restart? The
reset button. I need to go down here, land on this, and then... secret berry. Nice. That was cool.
Ooh. This is... a door. All right. Can I open the door? There's no way to open that door. How do I
get out of here? Like that. Is it a mirror? Whoa. Can I talk to the mirror?
All right. Well, I'm not going to react to that, apparently.
Whoa. Hold on. But I wasn't even ready. I needed to see what this was. I needed to...
I'm so overwhelmed. That was... okay. What is going on? I can hold on to this thing and look down.
Let's see. The game... I already knew there was a secret down here, and the game gave me binoculars
to see. But the thing is, though, guys, what the heck is in that cube? Epic just dropped it one day,
and we're all trying to figure it out. Does it give items? Does it hurt you? Can I go up through
this? Ah. You go up. So you go all the way through. That's really cool. So no matter what trajectory
you go, you can always pass all the way through it. It's good to know. It's right there. I have to
do it again. Cool. Is this fall? Secret? Hey, thanks, Fortnite Street. There's so many directions to go.
Oh, it turned... it turned him into jelly. I get it. It Christmas caked everything that was
impassable before. Cool. Where am I going? There's a secret... extra secret tape over there. I don't
know what that does. Fuck. I just pancaked myself, okay? So wait, I gotta go through now, then.
So we gotta go like this now. I can't see. I can't see. Oh, shit. Oh, don't...
What... what... what the heck is even inside that cube? I don't know. Maybe I should make
10 videos about it. B-side unlocked. Music track? All right, I'm gonna give... let's give the... I'm
gonna give this game a couple of extra points for one reason. You ready for the extra point reason?
Like, right now, you are... we're playing American football, and I'm going for the extra point, and
like, the knowledge I'm about to give you right now is the ball, and you're leaning down right
in front of it, like as on the opposing team. And I'm gonna... I'm gonna kick this ball, like you're
like a foot away from the ball, and I'm kicking it right into your face. That's the knowledge.
There's a lot of ways to go. How do I get that one? John... John... I get to go around and then drop
down to get that one, don't I? Damn it. Go up and then down. But where? But where? Wait, this one right
here. Wait a minute. How do I do this? And they said it couldn't be done. But I want to get that
other one too. How far? Oh, this is too much. Did everything do this? Uh, no. I feel like that's the
progression route. Hold on. What is this way? Nothing. Is there anything? Can I go out? I'm just
curious. I just need to know. Up there. Wait a second here. Hold on. One gosh darn second. Can I
get through? Can I get up there like this? Wow. Oh, I can. You gotta go up. Okay, I get it. And then
you have to go down. Straight up. Straight up again. No, and then down this way. And then across.
John, darling, slow down. Who said that? This is, this is progression. Ah, fuck it is.
Boom. I'm simply a concerned observer. You can tell the reason because I have red eyes. Are you
me? I'm a part of you. Why would part of me look so creepy? It's just what I look like, okay?
Deal with it. Sorry, I didn't. Forget about it. I can't tell you what a relief it is to finally get
out of here. But look, I'm worried about it. We need a hobby, but this. I know it sounds crazy,
but I need to climb this mountain. You are many things, darling, but you're not a mountain climber.
Not in a fucking million years. Who says I can't be? I know it's not your strong suit,
but be reasonable for once, you fucking idiot. You have no idea what you're getting into.
You can't even handle it. This is exactly why I need to do this. Okay, I'm done doing this.
Are you the weak part of me or the lazy part? I'm the pragmatic body. And I'm trying to be
diplomatic here. Let's go home together. Well, not anymore. Do I have to run away? Can I attack?
Dashing doesn't do anything. I can't. Okay, I just tried to goomba. Goomba doesn't work. What about
skeleton? Oh shit, I'm running out of energy. Wait, I need that. Shit. I can get it. I got it
already. Good. How do I get it? How do you get this? Can I break the wall? Oh, fuck. How do I get
over there? I can't get that. That's some secret. I'll have to figure it out like on a third playthrough.
Go in the door? I can't go in a door? Door. That's not gonna work. Can't open that?
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. What the heck? I thought I had to touch it again.
I don't. Okay, hold on. I can do twice. I can do two dashings. I didn't know I could go for
the spikes. All right. All right. All right. I thought I was gonna die hitting the spikes there.
Dummy. I had it the first time. Oh my god. Do you know what I wish I could see
with this game? Definitely a speed run. Okay. I fucking shut up and play. I'm doing so bad.
No, fuck. I gotta get that one first. Oh, fuck. Oh my god. All right. Hold on. I need a sip of
coffee. You have to bait and then dash. You don't get it all in one go. I gotta dash this fucking
thing. I'm literally just outplaying myself. I really am. You idiot! What do I do? Holy shit,
I'm so stupid. What's happening? Slow down. What's wrong with me? What's wrong with me?
What's wrong with me? Why is it three? You gotta go real fast to get this one.
You know what I would love to see with this game? No, I have to get it. I have to.
Wait a minute. Hold on. Oh, so they're not chasing me. Now I am unbeatable.
You stay here for a second and then... I already got it. What the fuck am I doing? I already have
it. All right. Everyone just stand still. I just stared into the microphone. Yeah. Please, God.
What? Go, go! Come on. I don't know what to do. Fall? Holy shit. Oh, I had it. Oh, fuck. All right.
Get ready. Get up. I'm trying to do a double jump. Fall. Fall. Fall. Fall. Go. Oh, you stupid.
Idiot. You deserve to be punched. Oh, you don't. You missed it. You missed it. But it's okay. You
can miss it. Oh, my God. Again, I'm shaking. I'm not shaking. I'm fine. Up. Go around. There's four
of them. What? I thought there was only three. Three. What's inside that cube? I don't think
we're ever going to find out. We gotta wait for them all to go by. You idiot. Let's do it. Oh,
fuck me. All right. This time, wait till they all go underneath. Holy shit. What have I done? No,
no. You gotta just... How did I do that? What do I grab? Go back. Is there anything over here?
Wait. Should I go up? No other secrets or anything? No, no. No more ways to go. There is
another way to go. There's a secret over here. There's so many ways to go. Uh oh. Now I'm in
trouble. There's so much to do. I'm so dumb. You gotta go diagonal. Should have went through.
Like that. All right. Give me the berry. No other secrets? Not that I can see. So much to do. So
much to see. What's wrong with taking the back seat, you know? Sometimes you have to.
Nothing. What about over here? This looks breakable. All right. We have a coin center.
Answer the phone. Why am I doing this to you? What are you talking about? I'm just checking for
secrets. What? I'm not allowed to check for secrets? John, are you calling from a payphone?
Yep. No, wait. You called me. What are you talking about? It doesn't matter. I'm in trouble.
I'm being chased by someone. I don't really understand what's going on, but I know I'm in
danger. I can feel it. John, you only call me when you're panicking in the middle of the night.
You don't have to make up some ridiculous story just to get my attention.
Not making it up. You always do this. It's all right. Calm down. I'm sorry, sweetheart. Talk to me.
I'm climbing Celeste Mountain. I found this old mirror and it shattered, but part of me escaped.
And I'm dreaming, aren't I? John, of course you're dreaming. I haven't spoken to you in months.
Why would I start now? Why am I even climbing this stupid mountain?
I'm wondering the same thing. It's time to give up and go home.
First boss. Thanks for playing. Wait, I didn't even do it? Wait, I have to do this?
Now I do the real level? I have to do it again? Is it fall damage? No. Interesting though. Look,
can I go over here? I can. Okay. I don't even remember his name. If you paid me a thousand
dollars right now and told me to save this guy's name and you get a thousand dollars in cash,
I wouldn't be able to do it. Thane? Is it Thane? Hey John, you made it. Climbing up here was tough,
but totally worth it. Just look at those ruins. I took so many great picks. Want to see?
Thane. Is that why I'm thinking that? Because somebody said Thane last night? Last night? It's
been like four days. I don't- my brain sometimes has problems remembering things. Oh sure. Last
night. I was sick, okay? I'm sick right now. Theo. There it was. Thane. I have two letters.
And no, three letters actually. The T, the H, and the E. Maybe I'll finally hit a thousand
followers with these. But we need to formally commemorate this occasion. Take a selfie with me.
I don't take selfies. I hate them. I hate pictures. I don't like pictures. I don't like selfies.
Guys, a selfie is just a permanent looking in the mirror. You might- I don't want that. Every
selfie is just the way that you look at yourself in the mirror. You want like four hundred thousand
of those on your phone? I don't know if that's such a good idea.
Come on, it's easy. Like this. See? What's a regular picture of you then? A photo?
No, everybody does the same thing when they take a selfie. I'll show you.
So anyways, forget about how fucking bad this hair is today. And yes, I've got a Death Star
t-shirt on. The Death Star. People have made jokes before about how my whole wardrobe is Star Wars
related. I've just- over the years, I've just- I have probably 12 to 15 Star Wars shirts.
It's bad. They're just so easy. Look, Disney bought Star Wars. So at this point,
it's everywhere. You can't get away from Star Wars. So there's like a 10% chance that 10%
of your clothing has to be Star Wars related. Is it? Is 10% of your guys clothes Star Wars related?
Are you sure? Go into your t-shirts. Are we certain about this? Anyways, what's your
guys name? Thane? What was I just doing? Why did I turn the camera on? Oh, right, right, right.
Selfie. Okay. So when you take a photo, you are locking away a memory, right? Because you want to
take a photo and you want to make sure you preserve it and remember it. So, you know,
you're like, oh, it's me and some friends. Like, okay, like, cool. Okay, nice. You got it? Nice.
Hey, remember that time we went to, uh, Las Vegas? Yeah, here's a photo.
A selfie is just the way you look at yourself in the mirror. You go like this.
Ready? You tell me how this is any different than any selfie you've ever fucking seen in your life.
It's fucking stupid. Don't take him anymore. You need to smile. No, nobody does that. Look.
Yes, they do. No, they don't. Okay. If somebody links me one photo of a selfie of somebody smiling,
I will eat a thousand dollars. All right. Let's fucking go. Sorry about that. Don't worry. I
won't post that one. No, it's all right. You can post it. It was a joke. It was a fucking bit.
No, no, stop. That was, I'm kidding. No one links. No, I, I banned, I'm, links are banned.
Also, one other thing before we move on. I know people are probably like, oh, go back to fucking
Celeste. But listen, why is it? Every picture I ever take when I'm trying to smile, it's like pain.
I can't do it. I can't fucking smile in a photo because it takes too long. I'm right now like,
I'm like, we're like having some fun. We're like smiling and laughing and stuff. This is like fun.
We're having a good time, right? Well, I'm smiling. If I take a photo of me smiling, it always looks
like this every single fucking time, no matter what I do. I don't fucking understand. Why does
this happen? And even when I think it looks good in my mind, I'm like, oh, all right. Like,
hey, this is fun. We're having a good time. And I look at the photo and I zoom. Everybody does this.
You zoom in. Hey, can I see that for a second? Let me see. Like you took a photo. You took like
a group photo. Let me see. Let me see how it looks. Let me see my fucking face. God damn it.
Don't be so hard on yourself. Okay. Fine. I won't. No one looks good without a filter.
It's true. Show the automaton. Me on the right. Yeah.
Casual yet refined. Any more things this guy needs to tell me? What made you want to try
photography? My grandpa was really into it. Apparently. Do it again. I wasn't looking.
You lost your opportunity. Rewind 15 seconds. Apparently he was semi-famous in the photography
world. I don't know if I'll ever be that good. But it's nice to feel close to him. So you're
determined to climb the entire mountain. Yeah, I told myself I would. I'm done breaking promises
to myself. And the stream. I've told you Dreamcast is coming for like six months.
And I keep telling you, oh, we're going to do that like next weekend. I keep breaking it.
I gotta stop doing that. Life goals. I dig it. I doubt I'll make it to the top like you,
but I'm not ready to turn back just yet. Are you getting any data up here?
I don't have a smartphone.
John, I don't even know how to respond to that. All right. Bye. How do I like jump and like karate
kick the support of this 10 and heavenly? Nevermind. That's mean. Well, let's go. I'm
going to go to the left. I'm going to go underneath. I'm going to go up through and drill under.
All right. That didn't do anything. It was just there for fun. So let's just go.
This is not a secret unless no, you know, sometimes I have complaints about controls.
Like, I don't know if I got to tell you when I press B and I don't move it, I pressed it very
tight. I've not had one real complaint about the controls of the game, but I am going to
continue to accidentally meet boy. It's going to happen for the rest of the entire stream.
Secret. Oh yeah. Where's the joystick? Got you. Not allowed to dash, but you sure can. If you
grab it, are we ever going to find out what's in the cube? Oh, are you, you want to know what's
in the cube? Oh, okay. All right. So what I'm thinking is I think Epic is now, do I actually
make a phone call? It says mom. Hi mom. John, what a nice surprise. How does your trip? It's okay.
I'm just kind of overwhelmed. Oh no. Are you having another panic attack? Focus on your breathing,
honey. I'm here. What's going on? I picked up the phone. But what if inside the cube is another
cube? Well, then Peter Molyneux is going to have a lot of explaining to do. Six out of 18. I did.
Oh wait, hold on. I want to go look at that. What is this? B side. Old site, black moonrise mix, music.
So it's you. So it's just a different, oh boy, hold on. This is different.
Ow. This is just a secondary fun mode. Figured it out in 10 seconds. That's all I needed.
That's all I needed. I'll get it. I'll get it. I just might control it.
Control. Something about the control. Jump. Yeah. What do you mean jump? Why is it going to jump?
Jump. That's what I'm doing, isn't it? Just jump.
Hmm. Oh, shit. Well, okay. Come on. Do it. Oh, shit. I gotta go faster than that.
Ooh. All right. All right. All right. Okay. I had it. Had it. I'm gonna go straight up to this one.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Oh, that's it. No, no. You blew it again. I can't. I got it. I just regular jump.
Fuck. I'm gonna do it straight up. There's the question though is how in the heck you gotta
just grab a B. I get it. You gotta grab and don't dash. You need to jump around. How the fuck am I
gonna do that? Because you gotta go like this. I'm so annoyed at that. Not the game myself.
I mean, I'm pressing A. Pretty clear. Shut up and play. Okay. Who am I talking to?
All right. I'm losing it here. I'm hitting the ceiling. I'm not doing it fast enough in there.
I'm so dumb. I can get it. It's fine. Come on. Recharge. Recharge. Whoa. Whoa. Wait. Okay. Hold
on. Oh, fuck. What do we got? Oh, no. Not one of these. Not one of these. I don't want to do this.
So, we gotta go through up. Oh, man. I gotta block this out. Maybe jump up here first
and then hold on. Oh, maybe. Cookie CRM with 10 community subs. Thank you, Cookie.
How do I get up there? The real question actually. Oh, come on. Really?
You do have to get that one first. It's the yeah. Do I have the extension turned on or is this part
of the game? Shit. I gotta go at an angle down that way. I actually should probably get this one
first and then go to the middle. No, go from left to right. This one straight up and then into the
corner. Into the corner. Get out. Come on. Come on. Let's go. Now what? Oh, fuck. Straight up.
Looks like it. Whoa. Yep. Oh, this is gonna be tough. You gotta hit that while you're going in.
I don't know where to go from there, though. What? Hold on. How does this end?
And then back up. I am so confused. Hold on. Through the whole thing? Okay. All right. All right.
Oh, it did. I angled it wrong. I didn't mean to angle it. Sometimes it just angles.
That's it. There's a lot to this. All right. At least the clone is gone.
Left. Left jump up. You idiot. I had it. Again, I didn't mean to do that.
I didn't mean to do that either. Fucking Meat Boy. I should have never played Meat Boy.
More. Up. Up and then up and down to the bottom right and then walk. I don't know. We're gonna
have to just do it. Go down maybe. Oh, fuck me. Whoa. Okay. Hold on. So I gotta get that one last.
All right. Go up. What are you doing? I really think you have to get this one last. For some
reason, I'm a moron and I'm getting it. Shit. I'm doing this in the wrong order.
Like that. That much is absolutely certain. I fucked it up again. Why? You have to go. I have
to go from the top left to the bottom right. So get the top left one last. I mean, I guess it
doesn't really matter, does it? Shit. That's not the right one. I gotta get up there. Trying to
bait them. No. Sometimes the controller really does make me go the direction I don't want to go.
What are you doing? Shit. That was it. I had it. I just didn't do it fucking far enough.
Oh my god. Give me a break. Why? I had it again. At least I have a pattern down that I can reliably
do. Got it. So somebody just said, if this is end game content, what am I doing this for?
I just have to hold it. Because you're a troll. Is this like bonus end game kind of shit?
Fuck. So what you're saying is I'm going to get like this stuff out of the way. Come on,
you can do it. And effectively I'm doing some of the harder mission. Okay, that's cool.
It's really fun. Down and now what? If I go, I guess I did it like that. But
what's the up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up. I had it. What am I doing?
I forgot about the spikes. Stupid. I don't know why I'm trying to go left there.
No, there's more. How much more is there? I just like, what's going on here? Down,
diagonal, diagonal. Hold on. I got caught there. Hold on. I'm literally pressing up.
All right. Okay. So I can dash right at the last second before I hit these spikes.
Holy shit. Okay. I got to grab the wall. Shit. Oh man. All right. So it's hold the wall,
go, dash, upright, bottom right, up, left, and then grab the wall. Damn. Shit. I don't have any more.
Oh no. So I, I got to jump out of this one, right? Really? What's that? You saw me dash? I
dashed off into it. Meat boy, quit fucking me. That came out. Meat boy. No. I wonder.
Can you straight up? Yep. Straight up. And then what? That's the real question.
Holy shit. I didn't even get to see that part. So hold on. Up, up, up,
top left, top right. Just play the main game. Yeah. I kind of just accidentally clicked on this,
didn't I? He's going to finish this and he's going to breeze through the campaign.
I am. Maybe I shouldn't be like muscle memory learning how to do all this.
There are no checkpoints on B-side. Really? Jesus. Wait a minute. My goodness. Um,
at least I can see that now. I already passed the checkpoint. I did.
Now I'm trying to rush it. I'm trying to rush it. I'm not even trying to rush it. If you
quit a chapter, you lose all. How close am I to finishing this? How many more are after this?
How is that not working? I probably should start using the D-pad. That's going to happen
over and over again. Now I'm using the D-pad and it's still working. It's still happening.
Okay. Both very close. No, I would agree with you, but I am using an Xbox one controller,
which as you know, the D-pad is one giant button. It's the worst D-pad of any controller.
If you press up on an Xbox one control, you're pressing like all of the top of the whole
control. You might as well be pressing every face button, dude. All right. Come on. I can do this.
Arrow keys. Yeah, but you can. So irritating. Uh, arrow keys. Sure. But then you actually,
you have to play with the keyboard, which is, uh, I can't. It's un-variable for me.
Dammit. What the hell do I do when I get there? Do I have to go grab on to the, okay,
through top left, grab the ledge and then drew top right. Let's try it. I can get there.
Oh, I got to go through there. Oh, I had it. Oh, that sucks. No.
Shit. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it.
I'm not going to fall through that damn thing. What the hell am I going to do about that?
I tried to jump out of it. Just didn't do it. Why is it not jumping out?
Is there a reason why that's not happening? I keep trying to jump out of there.
Holy shit. All right. Come on. That's it, right? This is it. This has to be it.
I'm on level one. I'm on level two of the actual campaign. All right. What do I need to do?
Why did I open this? I guess we're going to go straight up.
Get that one. The left. I got to just do it. I can't just peek. Holy shit. What the hell
did I just do to myself? I didn't jump. Um, well, hold on. I got it. I got it. I got it.
So then we're going to jump over, fall through. Hold on. Hold on now.
Through. Hold it. Hold on now. What do I do now? What happened? No, I had to, what does it,
where does it go? What the fuck was that? It makes a wall. So I gotta, I gotta go from there
and diagonal up to the right. Shit. All right. I had it. Got it. Now let's just make sure I get
this correct. Let's do it. Let's finish this damn thing. That's high. Um, uh, so I'm going to get
a start on the right screen. Left. I think we just have to go back and forward. Grab that one. You
get a dash again. I got to get that jump down. I wonder, can you just queue it up inside? No,
it has to be right on the left, doesn't it? Damn. I guess I'm going to do it that way.
Maybe not. Can I just go, I can just go up. I mean, maybe that's going to be tough.
No, no way. I mean, maybe, maybe. Hold on. If I just jump up the normal way. Okay. No, I can do
that. I have to jump out of that, which is the biggest pain in the ass for me is trying to get
the jump. Okay. Where does that go? Oh, come on. What, where does it go? Give me the stupid
fucking skull thing. What does it drop? It drops down there. What's the point of this?
I don't know. What's the point of this? Why don't I just leave? Can I just leave?
What does that do for me? Can jump. So unreliable for me. And so that makes spikes all the way down.
Come on. I don't get what, what's the point of putting it down? Jesus.
I guess maybe I'll just grab onto it. Why is the jump so unreliable?
I'm doing it at the same time, every time. Oh my God. What am I doing? What the fuck?
I'm so confused. So straight through and then up, up. Yeah. And then I got to go back down
and around the whole damn thing. I guess maybe not curious of how the hell this plays out.
I can only look at it again because it seems like that's not the right thing to do. So I grab onto
the, it comes down and I grab onto it. I have to go to the top left or maybe I could just go back.
Why would I go back to the, yeah. So I got to go top left.
Okay. All right. All right. Straight right. I feel you. Now I'm just rushing because my brain
is scrambled eggs. All right. Here we go. Oh, fuck. Um, um, oh, I dodged. No, fuck. Oh, hi.
That was it. I got it. I'm sorry. I had, I didn't, I thought I hit the wall. That's why I freaked out
because I didn't, I didn't have control. I like, I took my, I'm brushing again. I got it. It's over.
I beat it. I mean, it's a fucking pain in the ass, but I did. All right. Would you slow down?
You did it. You know what to do. Just finish it. Bingo. Anything else? I guess we just gotta
go straight up. Just get, just pick it up. Black moon ride. What does that mean? What do I get
for doing that? Side complete. So what does that do? Times. I get 199. I hate that. I wish I died
one more time. Go back and die again. Okay. Well that was cool. I like that because that was,
okay. So that was challenging, but it wasn't impossible. It was just challenging and fun.
He's so early in the game. I know. I, I don't know why I did it. It was fun.
Celestial resort. Chapter three. It wasn't dog shit impossible. Yeah. Sometimes games like this
just make it dog shit impossible for you. Be proud of your death count. The more you die,
the more you're learning. Keep going. Yeah, that's true. Hey, welcome back to the regular game.
It all feels so easy now. Look, I just have to walk. That's great. Look at how easy it is to avoid
mold. Wait, can I get on the roof? You're going to die more times here than the last level.
Just saying. Really? Got a berry. Don't I die. It's okay. Let's just start here. I'm going to,
yeah, I'm probably going to go up here. Why not? I guess I do have to get up there somehow.
Hmm. Oh, fuck. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Okay. Wait, wait, wait. Oh, look at that. I cheated.
I'm still cheating by the way. The dash just resets upon exiting. And yeah, that's cool.
Picking up berries. Any more? 17. Ooh, a key. Oh, that's not that exciting. It opens this door.
I was going to say, cool secret. What else is up here? Berry. Well, I probably have to go
inside and then left for this one. I got the secret fucking key. That's right. And I said the F word.
I'm sorry. This is kind of like the last level in DuckTales. The last boss room when you fight
Dracula. Oddly specific, I know. I'm sorry. That's just the way it is. Please ring for service.
I'm wasting the battery on my automaton. Welcome. May I help you? Are you a ghost?
Ghost? Don't be silly. I am the concierge of this fine establishment.
Welcome to the world-renowned Celestial Resort Hotel. Mr. Oshiro at your service.
Two guests in one day. This is finally picking up. How long will you be staying with us?
Oh, I'm just passing through. I'm climbing the mountain. Do you have a back exit?
A back exit. Just passing through. This will not do. You know, I can still hear you. Right.
In any case, our rear service door is reserved for hotel staff only. However, our top floor
presidential suite features a wide class view of the peak. Yes, you'll be quite comfortable up there.
Why am I hearing phone signal sounds? I don't know. I'm not hearing those.
Maybe I could get on the roof from there and climb down the back.
Presidential suite. Marvelous idea, Oshiro. What is your name for our records?
I'm John. But again, I'm really not interested in staying.
Right this way. Ms. John. I can ring it again. What's this? Very old dusty guest book. Many of
the pages are damaged or missing. The comments, however, are glowing. We'll never forget our time
here. I've never felt more at peace. Thank you. Okay. Does it come back? Nope. All right. Get it
easy for me. Yeah. Yep. This ball. I don't think it does. So Barry, I'm going to, I can jump down.
Bradbury dash left. Okay. That would hurt. I need like take a break.
That hurt. It really did. Some weight is involved in this one.
Okay. This was curious how it worked. I can put extra weight on it. They could go faster.
Didn't even need the other dash. Did I get too good at the game to not need that dash?
Is there such a thing? Secret. Oh, wait, what's down here? This is going to go all the way to the left,
right and out the door. Did I just skip everything? No. Don't, don't get a big head about this.
So that's just the way back. Okay. I didn't even know that was there.
Too lazy. More community subs. Why did I end up here? It's just a great Canadian thing.
A great Canadian fuck club. Thanks for the 10 community subs. There's been a shit load
tonight. There's been like 50 or 60 community subs tonight, hasn't there? Thanks a lot guys.
Seriously. Did I miss a secret? So much mold. Oh, okay. Well, let's check a, let's check a look
over here. Another tape. I ain't doing that one. I'll do that one. I'll do that one like next week.
How do I even attempt to do this? Do it now. I can't, I can't even go that way.
I'm going to pee my pants. All right. Just all right. Let me pee my pants and then we'll get
going. It's always after two hours. It's two hours on the mark every time. Right before I leave,
DEDO, DEDO, thanks for the 10 community subs. Thank you for your like 75 community subs in the
first hour and a half of the stream. Two hours. You guys are too generous. I'll be right back. I'm
just going to pee. Hi there. How you doing? Grab some water too, because you need to hydrate when
you're playing video games. How's the audio too? Am I too soft, too loud? I feel like I might need
to drop the audio a little bit in the game. Maybe like, maybe like by 2%. How's that? Better?
That's probably a little better. Yeah. I'm, I'm never loud enough for some crazy reason. I don't
know why. All right. We're good. Okay. There's a little spot to fall down there. Ah, it's going
to take me all, all the way to the left. It's going to be the thing that I need to get guaranteed.
Oh, I didn't see that meatball there. There it is. BRB, my McAfee antivirus needs to update.
Why do you have McAfee? Is it, is that, is that like an all the way to the left best buy computer?
Cause they all have McAfee on them. Oh, he's getting political. So that takes us to the key.
Then we got to go down. Oh, I stepped on it. Cool. Got the two berries in there.
I tried to rush it and that's what happened. The music is changing. Oh, what about,
can I hold these? Oh, no, I got it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I see. Did they ever go back down?
I don't think they do, but it's okay. I don't even need them.
Well, I might, I actually might need them. Oh, what am I doing? Same deal. Got to go across.
All right. Oh, I wait, I can go up there. I want to go up there. I think I want to go up there.
So I need the dash. So how am I going to do that to not dash? I just waited a little too long.
Oof. Ah, that was it too. Shit. Grab on the edge and just climb and jump. Got it. All right.
What's up here? Berry. I didn't even see the thing at the top. Didn't even look. Well, I have to have
a dash. So you have to fall in dash. Got it. No shit. You got to grab the edge. Jeremy, Jeremy.
Okay. Go. Any more dialogue for me? Please follow me closely, Miss John. The elevator is just down
the hall. The hotel's pretty rough shape. Is it really open for business? Of course we're open.
The Celestial Resort Hotel would never close during prime tourism season.
This water is a little, I think it might be time for a filter change on that water.
Uh, my bag? No, thanks. I'll keep it.
Very well. What a peculiar guest. Don't do that. I'm sorry. I forgot. That was a mouth noise.
What are you thinking? What are you thinking? I'm thinking this.
I didn't get that. Do I even need to jump? Probably, yeah. I gotta wait. Oh my god.
How can I not do this? Oh my god. What's wrong with me?
This is the moment you have to wait. I don't like waiting. Just wait. The diamond. There has to be
some reason why I did not see that. I don't know why. It was just right in front of me the whole
time. I don't know. I didn't even see it. Locked door. I don't even need the diamonds. Can you
get me my reader setting? I got an idea.
So I obviously have to push that all the way to the bottom and then dash back onto it.
If I were a gamer, that's what I would be doing right now, but I'm not doing it right now.
I'm just, shouldn't have played the B sites. Shouldn't have played the B sites. I'm not to
go slow. And I was so used to just like, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
That might be enough. Stupid idiot. What's wrong with you? Got it. Get it. Collect it. Collect it.
Thank you. Well, guys, look at this gamer. I played one before. I played a game before. One.
Well, that was really stupid because that's exactly what I had to do. But I used my dash.
Did it again. Fuck. You gotta grab onto the side and jump. I'm so dumb.
Oh shit. Shit. Well, now I get it. You got to skip that one. What the hell am I doing?
Look top left. Look top left. What are you guys doing? What about it? You want to go up there?
Boomer vision. I don't have boomer vision. I just, so this is where you get the super secret one.
All right. Hold on. It's one of your powers. There is, all right. There actually is a lot,
there are a lot of ways to go. You gotta go diagonal. Maybe fall this way and then,
okay. Ooh. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Just fall in and dash up. It's that easy. Collect it.
I don't want to do this again. Collect it. You're going to make me do this whole thing
to prove that I, I mean, ah, I'm not capable. My fucking dirty hair just got in the way.
Why don't I just go this way? Well, oh, okay. I'm fine. Fun game. So I did it.
Let's just go. Secret down here. Yes, there is. Okay. Wait, I gotta get that key.
Will you get up there? Why is this harder than me doing the thing? Not even hard. I mean,
it was a little hard. I mean, that's where the meat boy powers come in and all. Okay. For a second,
I thought I could stand on the piano and then my brain immediately corrected itself.
I don't know what the hell I'm doing. I can slow down. There's no reason to go that fast.
See, just slow down. There's no reason to go that crazy. Key. Got it. I could go left though.
No, this is the key to the door, right? Oops. It's all right. I can get it again. No, fall.
No. All right. I saw the meatball on the left. I thought I was going to do something for me.
I gotta go from the other side. Up top. Wait, but what about down there? That looks really,
it looks like I'm supposed to go through that. Doesn't it? There's a lot of secrets in this game.
Ms. Joan, I'm really the most employee to keep up. I'm running a world-class establishment here.
I don't have time to wait around for meandering guests. You really don't have to wait for me.
I'm just looking for a way through this place. Oshiro, you idiot. The customer's always right.
Business is finally picking up and you lose your temper.
Of course, Ms. Joan. My sincere apologies. I was out of line. Please feel free to explore
at your leisure. And I will. Right through. I don't like the Tetris room. This is just
failed Tetris. This is what it looks like when I play. I don't like it. I obviously need a key.
Where do I go? Ah, I gotta go down? Down? Down again? Down more?
Uh, can't break it. This must turn into something. This must, this is probably a dream level up here,
I would assume. Goddamn maze. Yeah, this is gonna open up. Hello, sir. This clutter is out of control.
When did this happen? I don't even know where to begin. Do you run this place by yourself?
You're right, Ms. Joan. I'll never sort this mess out alone. It's hopeless. It's not what I meant.
Just breathe. Mr. Ushiro, breathe. It's just a little spring cleaning. Well, more than a little,
but I can now. No. It's a lost cause. I gotta fix this. I gotta fix the Tetris room.
How long you been running the hotel? Quite some time now. Business has been slow. You must really
love your work. Oh yes. In the hotel business, our passion is perfecting the delicate art of hospitality.
A truly great hotel lives eternally in the cherished memories of its satisfied guests.
That's the spirit. Now let's get started on this mess. I'm going this way, so we're gonna go this
way. Oh, Thane! What's up, man? YOLO! Remember YOLO! Are you a guest here, too? John, I'm so happy to
see you right now. I'm all about spooky mysteries, but this is getting too real.
Have you talked to Mr. Ushiro? I think he could really use some help.
You think? He's a creepy old weirdo. I bet he's cleaning out a nook to hide our bodies as we speak.
I'm gonna crawl through this vent. It's blowing cold air in from outside.
Come on! I was gonna just scream of Captain Falcon, but then I thought I don't think I
can do a Captain Falcon, so I stopped myself halfway through, and that's how it turned out.
Mr. Ushiro's troubled, but I don't think he wants to hurt us. He just needs to clean up this mess.
I want to help him. John, that's very sweet, but this is dangerous. We need to get out of here and
call an expert on creepy old dudes. We aren't prepared for this. I think I can get through to
him. Well, I mean, you gotta deal with the caramel that's in the dryer right now. Somebody's fucking
doing something weird in there. That's not how you make candy. Actually, I guess you could.
I'll catch up with you later. Man, you're more stubborn than my sister. I thought that was
impossible. Take care of it. You can make candy in a dryer in a controlled environment, and don't
try this at home. Thanks, Thane. I'll see you outside. Wait, there's a spot right here? Yes,
there is, but what? I need to get rid of the purple candy. Oh, I get it. I figured out what's
going on here. That all the red, that's all soap. That's like all dirty soap and shit from the dryer
the washing machine that flaps. This is like laundry. I get it. It's like a laundry soap level.
Okay, I understand now. Remember that's there because I won't. Am I going the right way? I
think so. How do I get that? I can't jump. I can't dash. How am I supposed to go through that?
Oh shit. Okay, hold on. I fell off. I didn't even press the button. I just tripped,
but I gotta grab onto the edge. No, no, no. I gotta grab the other edge. That's how you do it,
but come on, man. Stop doing that. You're getting me in trouble. Why just jump over?
What am I doing? Meat Boy has ruined my brain. I'm going to assume there's probably a few buttons
that I have to press and eventually it's going to take away all the purple, all the green,
all the right. It's going to be like that. I know it is. If anybody says I'm wrong,
dip band. And I'm talking forever. Not like five minutes and no until Twitch TV turns its servers
off. There it is. Yep. Folded all the laundry, sorted the laundry. Everybody thought that I
saw a shitload of question marks and a bunch of like a boomer brain and shit like that,
but that actually was laundry. This is water. It got folded and put away. So
I thought, really? My goodness. Cuter. I mean, this is a secret, but is this a secret just showing
me that there's another secret? What are you doing? I don't know. Purple. All right. See,
look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look.
Ooh, scattered and lost. Okay. Cool. What is it? Do I, is that a track of a music track?
Holy shit. There's another secret. No, that's just an easy way to get back. Okay.
No, wait, wait, wait. Oh boy. Okay. Well, I lost the opportunity to get the berry that was over there.
A secret level is unlocked after four hearts. So I have two of them, right?
Can you die in the water? You can always just replay levels. Yeah, that's true.
Ah, right, right, right. Here's the other secret it was showing me. Computer. All right. The Pico
8. Celeste. Oh no, it's a commander video machine from meat boy. It's, it's a meat boy
commander video machine. Hey, I got a strawberry. Does that count? Or is this a joke? Everything is
meat boy. Can I go to the bottom right? All right. Okay. I can't, I get a, I can't dash.
Come here. I can't climb in this one. I can't climb up. 5,000. What? Got it. Oh,
no, I'm not going to do it. Here's the question. I guess I go like this.
I had it. You did it, but you just didn't do it. I had it again, but you just didn't do it again.
Is there a reason why you're doing that? Is this, there's gotta be a reason why he's doing that,
right? So I don't know. Maybe if you look up why he keeps doing that balloons. Okay. That's balloons
are the dash thing. Jump on the frog or the clouds. Yep. What the hell? Just dash and get it. Dash
and get it. All right. Now how much is left in this little mini game here? This is probably it,
right? A thousand. I got to hold onto that. This is the rest of the game. I get it. I get it. I get
it. I get it. I get it. And up here, diagonal thing, though I did it. No, I don't, do I get
something for doing this? Is this like a thing that I'm going to get? I got to get the, you don't get
anything. You don't get anything. It's just a side thing. It's just fun. Oh, okay. It's just the
original game that they made in a game jam. Oh, all right. That's cool. That's why it's all in
one of these little computers. Old side. All right. I beat the game. This is it. I win. I beat it.
Yeah, I win. Not playable from the main menu. All right. That's cool. Interesting stuff. Finish
this or you get your gamer license revoked. No, that's not the real game. I mean, it's the
original. An old paper sticks out from a clutter. Attention, hotel staff. It is my sad duty to
inform you that the Celestial Resort Hotel will close indefinitely following this season due to
circumstances beyond our control. It was an honor to have served alongside you all as we work
tirelessly to ensure that our guests enjoy the most hospitable and memorable experience possible.
I write this with a heavy heart. This hotel has become my home. It's staff and patrons,
my family. I miss you all dearly. He's a ghost. He's a ghost. All right. Well, that's all we can do
here. No shit. What do you mean no shit? He could have been like a ghoul. He might have been a ghost.
He could have, I guess he is very clearly a ghost. I gotta get rid of the green. But he might have
just been a guy. No, he wasn't a guy. Is there another way up here? Blocked, blocked, blocked,
blocked, blocked, blocked. We have new dialogue. I'm begun cleaning and already I feel a renewed
lightness of spirit. That's the power of positive thinking. Actually, I cleared out some of the
clutter for you. Oh yes, thank you. Please relax and let the hotel staff handle it. You fool. You're
losing her. Guests don't want to spend their time cleaning. Are you okay? Yeah. This is the finest
hotel you're ever going to visit. How could I let my problems pile up like this? And there's how we
go. One, two, I'll go down. Goodbye. We're looking for green. If I can remove the green, then we
should be fine. That's a chest. I'll try to get it. Wait, are you sure this is a ghost? Maybe he can
just float. Okay. I have to squish myself. I'm just going to grab a hold of this. It's very lucky.
And I got a hole. Ah, you got to go slow. Sometimes the levels are slow. What's that?
Oh, when you slow me down, that's when I have a problem. When you take it, when you take me down
a notch and I have to go very slowly. Look at how much of a problem this causes. And I tried to dash
off the screen. I guess, should I have gone down? Nope, it's a secret. Well, gotta get back. So, um,
fuck. I think I have to go all the way around. I don't, why am I doing that? What are you guys doing?
Why? Why? What are you doing? What are you doing? That doesn't make any sense. That doesn't make any
sense. Who came up with that? You guys are throwing me off. God damn it. I can't jump on those.
Stop jumping on them. You threw me off. So hardcore. Don't blame us. Well, when I look over
in my chat and all I see is people talking about how they're fucking farting and shit. Like,
it's going to throw me off a little. It's going to fuck me up a little bit. Just don't touch
anything on the ground and then grab this dash, get over here. What the fuck just happened? What?
You guys are fucking kidding me. Pat's fault. Chat's fault. I mean, come on. I mean, look,
it's not chat's fault. It just is. I definitely did not do that correctly at all. I'll take it
though. What are you doing? Oh my God. You guys really going to do this shit? I made it. Left.
Buried. Well, I think I have to. Come on, move. I didn't even press X. I didn't, I swear.
Whatever. Let's just see if I can time this right. Nope. This is like one of the easiest rooms and
for some reason I just, I can't do it. I'm so desperately trying to go as fast as I can and
I got meat boy syndrome, which remember, if you don't know what meat boy syndrome is,
it's instead of climbing up, you just launch off the wall. So I have this meat boy syndrome
that I can't get rid of. Dick. No. Fuck. That's it. I had it. Damn. There it is. The Cheshire
Trest. So that gets rid of all those. The Graham one to go. Wasn't there a blockage over here
somewhere? I know there was. All right. For the new viewers that are coming in, you guys really
want this to be the chat experience? Do you want the chat experience? Oh, this is this channel
I've never heard of. Oh, Jerma985. Let me click on his channel and see what he's doing. Celeste.
Okay. Cool. So how's he doing in Celeste? Nope. I almost missed that one. You try to get that one
again. He's farting. I'm farting. I love to fart. Okay. Well, bye. They're going to think you guys
are bots. Do you guys really want to be bots? Like, I barely enjoyed the luxuries that our
hotel has to offer. I don't know, man. Viewers are going up. No, they're not. No, they're not.
They've been the same. You've lost 600. No, I haven't. Have what? Seriously. Seriously. I don't
know what to say. I missed dialogue. One person wrote that and then everybody decided to jump on
and just start grabbing it. She hates you. I don't. I'm sorry. Wait, I thought I couldn't hear that.
Well, I guess because he's a ghost, you can see right through his brain so I can see his words.
I understand. Well, let me take a look. There is this place that just got open.
Didn't I already do this one? No. Stop me for it. Hmm. Ferry. Can I get it without dying?
No. That's dash across. Very clear. Very clear. Gonna fall, grab, dash across. Watch. I ran a dash.
See? Fall, dash across, grab. I watched you since Scary Face Cam Fridays. Oh yeah, I remember those.
I do. Shit. Too bad. Scary Face Cam Fridays. I need to pay attention.
Now what? Bring him back. Guys, there's no such thing as Scary Face Cam Fridays.
You know why? Because I'm just... shit. What am I doing? I did it on Saturday. Yeah,
that person's not a true viewer. All right, I'm doing this wrong. No, I fucked it up. Maybe not.
Holy fuck me. I did it. Holy shit. I hate you. I'm so in love. I'm so in love. You know what I mean?
I've rented a fucking juice. I missed the thing that I needed and I rented a juice again.
Fucking ceiling again. Stop hitting the ceiling before I call your parents. I'm calling your
fucking parents. I'm calling both of your parents at the same time on different cell phones. Oh my
god. And then I'm going to get them both on the phone and I'm going to put them both on speaker
and they're going to talk to each other. I'm going to hold one end to the other. I got the game kit.
Whatever. Cleaned up the house. Good for me. What's going on here? Oh, this is just a clean room.
They're at work. I'm going to call them. There you are. You certainly have a knack for wandering off.
It was tough, but I sorted everything out for you. The Celestial Resort Hotel extends its
gratitude for your assistance. Of course, the staff had the mess under control, Ms. John.
Oh, sure. Yeah. How humiliating.
Your pants are unzipped. Actually, thanks for telling me that. Thank you. I'll zip them up.
It's just up the elevator down the hall. Sure. What the heck. Show me the presidential suite.
Sounds lovely. Don't lose her now. I hate it. I hate it. I hate this. This is worse than anything
else. I hate this thing you guys are doing. Man, it's amazing here. How's it going with El Creepo?
I helped him clean up that huge mess, but he was kind of a jerk. He still thinks he can convince
me to stay. It's gone seriously. My bad idea radar is off the charts on this one. You should get out
of here. Emote only mode has been activated. If I disappear now, Mr. Oshiro could have a meltdown
and maybe I can actually do something good for once. Forget your karma, dude. I think that guy
is going to melt down no matter what. You have to think about your safety. Theo, I'll be okay.
Yeah. Yeah. I didn't expect you to listen. See you on the outside. Jail bird.
Up, down, up, down, up, down, up, down. First try guaranteed. No. Holy fuck. First try guaranteed.
Nope, not first try. I gotta get. I hate it. I hate the thing you guys are doing right now.
I've lost entirely. I had it too. I just forgot. My brain didn't turn it on. I'm doing this so
incorrect. No, I wanted to go up, not diagonal. You piece of shit Xbox controller. Why are you
the worst controller? And why are you the only one that works on fucking Steam? The PS4 controller
doesn't like to work and you have to unplug it and get like this fucking software. Okay, I know
what I gotta do. I know what I gotta do. I know what I gotta do. Wait, wait, wait. Don't grab onto
this. Grab onto the edge here and you can't, you gotta go back down. Why is everybody putting the
cheese? Should I even ask that question? No, that's it. That's what it is. You gotta dash,
win right on the edge. This, right on the edge. Got it. Bingo. Oh shit. Oh my God. I didn't even
see what was at the end of this level. Stupid Xbox controller. Hey, are you sure you don't want to
go? Hey, when you press and press left on d-pad and sometimes just press, press all 180 degrees
left down up and every, the whole side, do the whole thing. Did you not want to do that? Did you
want, you didn't want to do that. Sorry. That'll be $80 per controller please. I didn't do that.
I didn't do that. Why do you, didn't, I pressed left. Doesn't even, yes, no.
Give me that strawberry. By the way, listen to these. You know how annoying it is to play a game
that requires you to press R1 or L1 more than once every few seconds? Fucking Xbox. Cool Xbox. See,
like 2030 when crackdown comes up. I'm being, I'm being mean to Xbox right now.
Why are you being so mean to Xbox? Big bits. We got big bits. Big bits. Pugatron. Give $30.
Thank you so much for the 30 bucks. Hey, love you, German. Thanks for being such a great
entertainer. Thank you. Thanks for hanging out. We're just having fun. That's all we do.
This is your last chance, Oshiro, but thank you so much for the $30. You already ruined it,
making a guest clean up your mess. I don't hate the Xbox. I don't hate the Xbox. I just hate the
console. I hate the controller. I hate the games and I hate the internet connection and I hate the
UI. Something I don't hate the Xbox. I'm just kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. You're already
making a guest clean up your mess. She'll never stay. She's still here. There's still a chance.
Did I just get banned for making a fart joke? That's a banned word now.
Presidential Suite is the key. It will surely impress her. Get it together, Oshiro. Wait,
but he's doing this. There you are. Follow me quickly. We're almost there. I have a confession
to make. I actually like the layout of the Xbox controller. I prefer the layout to the PS4.
It's true. That actually is true. This guy keeps smashing me. I literally got banned for saying
fart peepee. Well, maybe you shouldn't be saying fart peepee. Well, you guys just let me enjoy my
pizza. Shit. That's what you have to do though. And I fucking blew it. I blew it so bad. I gotta
leave the last couple of pixels. I gotta get. I am going to get angry. No, I'm not. Why? This
game's fun. I'm not actually getting angry at anything in this game. Come on. Come on.
Stand still. Got it. Wait, sub only? Sometimes we have to go to sub only because people write fart.
Farts are like I'm farting. It's the only thing that I get to see in chat and we're gonna. We're
gonna sour. I don't. You gotta stop bringing it up. When people are asking why am I getting like
timed out and they write the thing. I have to answer it. I have to tell them why. Berry up there.
Two berries, really? Have and then climb. Very fast. No, no. Have it right the first time.
To climb over and then dash and then jump around dash again and land over here. There's two berries
right now. I can't just not get them. Just land. Just land and you'll get it. Co-op juke. Nice.
Baby gate. What's the baby gate? Open the baby gate. I just itched the back of my head really fast.
That's how you know that things are starting to heat up. Big time. I just ruined everything. I have
to dash across. I can't use this dash. You slow stupid idiot. Like you fucking. Look at how slow
that guy is in comparison to the other one. I think that's all I can do down here. I gotta go back up.
Yes. This way and I came from this way. I gotta get a key. Let's go over here and get the key.
Madder than Hotline Miami. That is that is so far from the truth. I'm having a visit rate.
Well I have to dash through. It's my own fault. Key that there's a secret and there's something
over here. Do I keep this key forever? God I hope so. I do. I gotta time that to jump when it comes up.
Oh shit. I get it. I get it. Oh my god. I had it right there. That was done.
I get it. I get it. I get it. And I just pressed A for no reason. For no reason. There wasn't any
reason to press A. You just slide down. I itched my fucking nose. I have like birds up there. I
don't know what's in there. Why is my nose so itchy right now? Why is my nose so itchy? Yeah.
I okay does anybody else get like this? When you play a game that requires your
complete immediate 100% focus do you go into a spell of where a place on your body starts to itch
and you can't it doesn't stop. I don't know why. What's it for? Why does that mean? Does that mean
like somebody's talking about you? You know you sneeze and people say oh that means somebody just
talked shit about you. Gotta b-side. 3000 people are talking about you. Well stop because my nose
is itchy. Mr. Oshiro's diary. The final entry appears to be decades old. As of today the hotel
is officially closed. Charlotte organized the staff for a farewell hike up the mountain. Most
of us have never seen the summit. It seemed like a fitting goodbye but when the time came I couldn't
bear to leave without looking around one last time. I told them to go on without me. I will
catch up with them soon after I double check that everything is in order. I can't believe my time
here is over. What am I gonna do now? Perhaps I'll stay one last night so that the hotel and I can
have a proper goodbye. All right what what is going on in this chat today? What's going on here?
Somebody like sawed open chat's head and like threw up into their brain and then closed it.
What is going on today? We had too much sugar. Where am I going right now? Interesting. So I
gotta this is gonna be okay and up it's gonna climb and then across holy shit up no what oh
god i just had to slide climb it climb it all right we've got a drop up it's gonna be kind of hard
we're good that's it right nothing up here that i can what the fuck would i do that for
i don't know what i did that for who why would i do that i'm looking for a secret why what are you
doing oh no am i gonna get chased by the image again here we are our award-winning presidential
suite truly it is the very definition of rustic luxury i'll stand back and allow you to soak in
the majesty i understand it can be a lot to handle uh-oh don't look in the mirror don't look in the
mirror after midnight you're like a gremlin the gremlins gonna come out and start chasing you so
what do you think it's uh it's beautiful the furniture looks expensive it's very spacious
colors are elegant i can tell you put a lot of work into it i can tell you put a lot of work
into it i knew it would impress you yeah so can i get on the roof from here you imbecile you're
losing her oh i forgot to mention valued guests such as yourself stay in our finest accommodations
at half price i don't want to stay please miss john please stay you're sure i've already been
sidetracked too long no you know i have to do the thing where i run away no sweetie forget this loser
loser you're in denial old man this resort is a dump no one would ever want to stay here
someone had to say it she doesn't mean that i i'm very busy
you heard the man where would you be without me sad because bad sad because bad sad because bad
mad because sad sad because bad mad because sad sad because bad bad because mad mad because sad
sad because bad bad because sad i figured out the whole algorithm why would she say my beautiful
tell is it done you got more how dare she insult you like that you done no you got more what if
she's right of course she's right you couldn't even clean up without her help john only wanted
to help but why was she so cruel how dare she insult you like that i got them all no i didn't
what if she's no i did get them all okay fine let's go i thought we'd never get rid of them
you owe me one and add it to the list leave me alone i thought you were so determined to
keep climbing now all of a sudden you're some weirdos therapist why won't you go away
uh miss john before you go i need to ask a question why would you be so nice to me
only to run away what did i do wrong i'll give it a break you still don't get it
she only helps people to feed her twisted ego she never cared about you
i just wanted to help you're both pathetic oh pathetic you only came here to humiliate me
i won't ruffle your feet any longer boss fight okay secret over there all right let's go he's
gonna be where he dashes i get it it's super easy once you know what happens
oh almost got me that time didn't you not today uh-oh i missed a strawberry who cares
what are you thinking i tried fucking xbox xbox unbelievable xbox tilted the wrong way
xbox tilt controller hey xbox tilt controller sideways instead of up he's tilted he's tilted
i'm gonna name this uh this stream celeste legend of the tilted streamer right that'd be like funny
what an awesome title that would be what did i just do my god i just figured out a brand new
mechanic to the game you can actually step on his head oh thank you no don't do it that fast just
wait for him oh that kind of threw me off so how do i end this i didn't even see the goo on the
ground i think i can get up on top of the building oh wait a minute hold on i think i can probably
climb the building okay stupid idiot just go i'm gonna miss a secret but fuck it whatever
that's it i gotta jump right through that no at least i got the raspberry now i can just go
wait i'm just trying to go so fast because i don't want to do this part again
slow it down this really it's not like timed or anything why even go that fast the berries
the berry no i'm not getting all the berries mr rishiro stop i just wanted to help
you okay so you can open this thing's mouth here people want to see what this looks like
might as well show you
stop you're hurting him what no it's water fucking god damn why don't hold on
hope i didn't get liquid in the keyboard no it went forward into the like splashed on the monitor and
on the desk and everything thank god this is just water if this was coffee or something i would be
fucking so mad i would have i would have turned the stream off in rage would be the second time i
would have done that no it's all right it's just water just kind of everywhere hold on i gotta like
tip this hold on i'm this is gonna be really loud so i need to mute all right what the fuck is going
on now my screen just went all green and it just said i had the wrong cable connected i just got
you you have the wrong cable connected to your monitor get a dvi cable that's what's in there
the water didn't even get there no that's that's completely unrelated somehow
but i fucked this all up because now the screen is in the wrong spot and it's gonna throw me off
all right we're good let's go hey uh want some water
wish i had more of that unbelievable let's go i've decided to close the hotel for repairs we dry
kind of it's all right he'll try second floor is leaking the libraries and complete this array
and not to mention the hole in the ceiling of the presidential suite please just leave me alone
is the flute thing okay let me check you all right it means yes chapter complete you're hurting
this thing is so cute you know i like this thing so much because it looks like pac-man doesn't it
and yes i know cut your nails cut your nails it's been a rough fucking few weeks
chapter complete 21 i almost got them all name the automaton um let me see it's got a
face it's got it's got an interesting face um she she shito shito little shito shito s h e e t
awful name why this little shito all right whatever let's go we're almost at the top of
the mountain look golden ridge chapter four low on energy in a pinch jumping away from walls
doesn't consume stamina oh that's pretty good idea fluffy clouds looks like it's a jumping
mechanic new mechanic introduced into shito i mean celeste what about down there's an orb
oh bubble mechanic oops so you can aim it so you have to aim it in a direction so if i jump in
i come out with a dash can i jump out of this i wonder if i can jump out doesn't look like it
but i still have a dash when i'm outside okay good to know that's pretty cool come on i'm
making a reference to mario 3 any other boomers in this chat get it you probably do you probably
went oh all right yeah i remember that little tune oh yeah it's me oh well well i didn't expect to
see you up here i'm glad you're still in one piece so you made it to the hotel did you meet
mr ashura i did oh well i met him all right he chased me out of there after i cleaned up a bunch
of junk that sounds like a fun morning he's a lost soul dear that place is much more than just a hotel
to him don't make him your project you know what i think i think this mountain drove both of you
crazy you know you're not the first person to say that maybe you're right how would i
know if i were crazy the way i see it the mountain can't bring out anything that isn't already in you
but you gotta be a few crows short of a murder to live up here in the first place right
what are you even talking about oh i'm just rambling like the old bad i am ready to give
up i know shortcut back to your car back off lady i'm heading for the summit sometimes it's
hard to tell the difference between stubbornness and determination isn't it you remind me of myself
when i was young good luck and mind the wind you don't get many visitors up here do you
no i can't say that i do i don't mind the solitude though sometimes i think i should
live in solitude too i really tried to get through to mr ashura i wanted to help him
sure needs to move on from that hotel but it's not going to happen on your schedule
and doesn't help that you've got something to prove i'm talking very strangely i don't know why
i'm doing this i don't know you know what am i doing this why am i saying it like this why am i
doing this why am i doing that arrow pointing up you've got an arrow that's pointing look at
that arrow right there pointing up for what it's very clearly an arrow right there look see
where my head is hitting don't you get lonely in that little cabin i have friends dear i may be
crazy but i'm not a hermit sorry i didn't mean to assume when i was younger i couldn't imagine
staying in one place for this long but then i found this mountain i knew right away that it
would be my home what's so special about it the mountain shows you who you really are
whether you're ready for it or not it keeps me honest isn't that interesting that just
interesting too much wind no i don't like this those are spikes i thought they were just frozen
cactuses but i'm wrong there are no cactuses in canada wait can i go okay these can be broken
donkey kong barrels nice nothing else i can do about this little secrets
oh that's does it come back oops a daisy
more wind more wind you know this game uh it's like dark souls in a way with uh
i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm just being annoying oh actually i don't have a dash stop right now
yeah i don't know about the way that the uh you know you die
and it's you're supposed to lose a bunch of times it's kind of it makes sense oh man you gotta go
faster than that to get this really really really i didn't even point and grab the ledge
easiest barrier the whole game right there official death counter five out of 75 575 deaths
that's not bad for a playthrough one is it not bad that's not bad something down here we got we
got a raid raid coming up from joel we got a joel raid oh well welcome everybody welcome to the
channel thanks a lot joel if you're here playing celeste trying so fucking hard i don't need to
turn you away i probably shouldn't have done that you don't know what's here here's if you don't
know what celeste is so this is a puzzle platformer rpg well i get skill points that
i put in at the end of every level i have a 32 strength 21 faith and five into
magic finding so that's how i'm finding these little droplets here
it's kind of like dark souls in a way no but honestly i hope you had a good stream joel
welcome everybody and if you have if you're not following joel i suggest you do got a great
great goddamn channel over there please link it one of the mods link that channel
by the way i need to figure out what the hell i'm doing here do i have a time limit on when i can
order it up to a certain order i don't think i'm getting this maybe it does have to be in a
certain order or if they go fast enough or they can't but they don't touch me
joel got timed out how what yeah i have to go fast they can't touch me he posted the link and
got banned no he didn't oh god let's start at the top left here where's the sounds he did because
he's not a sub i'm sorry i didn't mean to time i didn't mean for the automatic bot to time you up
wait still here you were supposed to learn this in chapter two but you skipped it like a dumb ass
what do you mean like what do you hold on what do you mean like a dumb ass
because i went a different way what uh so i can't touch the ground exactly that does not count as
the floor so i probably start up here then the thing is you got yeah the grip thing is really
gonna fuck me over here because i can't have to touch the ground so i gotta wait till the wind
that's how you do this i bet does this count as the ground this doesn't count as the ground it
does it well i wasn't not collecting this wind is killing me here so how the hell am i gonna get
this one dash through well i think that's what i have to do i was on the right track here maybe
this is this one's uh i feel like i have to dash to get this one dashing with the wind or get it
absolutely last let's try it again okay yeah i gotta get this one and then this one last i
shouldn't be dashing at all except for to get this one fuck i'm gonna get it it's possible ah
if i had a dash it was impossible all right let me take a look so
maybe if i drop down i shouldn't be dashing ran in the dash again this is celeste if you're
wondering if you're curious what the game is what if i get this one first that may have just done it
because i can reset it every time over here all right that should be it right
as long as i can get over here got it i thought i was gonna run out of grips all right that was
fun interesting so you gotta get them all before touching the ground cool it just took me a little
while step two oh god welcome to hell this is gonna take a long no it's not i'll get it first try
guaranteed where i'll delete my twitch channel right now it's still the first track thank god
i don't have to delete my twitch channel another b-side tape very cool can i go anywhere else
looks like i can go up but can i really though jeal nine thanks for the 10 community subs jeal
nine you guys have given so many community subs tonight jeal thank you nothing up here anyways
jeal all right fight the wind i got my berry i got the tape i just have to guess where it is
just guess correctly this time oh my god what are you thinking why can i not do this
what the fuck am i doing almost soiled it there but i got it all right berry right there don't do it
like that there's no reason to do it like that all right climb probably have to time this to when it's
not snowing i mean windy you know what i mean if i go the other way no that was it i had it
oh i think i have to hold on and not do the dash maybe not i gotta wait for the
wind has to blow me back that way okay i get it so we how much let's count it ready one
two three one two three one two three one one two three oh my god you gotta go when the wind is
blowing right when it starts get it come on blow it's close never really i really had it there too
i'll get it i know it's right i have it just fucking xbox controller
do it i didn't even need the wind didn't even need it bite controller no no biting spikes
very two berries okay i would assume that's probably correct it is correct if i could just
do it there's one and that's not how you get that one how do you get that let me see hold on
is there a way to go up from here well this is blocked off now let's try this way it's different
oh shit
um okay well you this can be controlled with my mind to break that
maybe not i have to go all the way up and then all the way down
apparently i guess maybe i do have to break it no i don't oh i have to control this too shit
come with me i forgot to press the button this is it this right holy shit okay just let go man
just let go i didn't even hold i didn't hold right trigger i'm so angry just do it man i really am
just trying to jeremy i'm not gonna ask you to do this again it's really that wasn't that hard you
just had to do it all right got all the berries that's it you're grounded jeremy you're grounded
any other ways to go there is what we're looking at there's a way to go to the top right this is
gonna be a pain in the ass i can already tell oh my god holy shit there's a spike so nothing
not it's a that's a level is done good good for you got it what there is how do i get up there
there's gonna be a way right jump on here and then fall maybe no because i don't think i can
reach no i can't reach oh fuck how do i can i get that to move nice all right so this is the water
why do i always play a game a year after release i mean do i do that i just i play games and i don't
have to play a game at all here's this is a i guarantee it as a reference here what the
fuck did i tell you i knew it so what do i do with this yep everybody talked shit when i made
the flute noise and there's the reference right there and i got it first try your boomer brain
helped uh this is gonna be interesting okay i gotta go and then jump on this before it crashes in
maybe i have to do that first can is that even possible holy shit man got it so that's another
cool i didn't go up though interesting ow i never played super mario 3 so it took me 20 minutes to
figure that out if you have that's just a white block why would you ever know what to do if you
never even heard of it oh this is on track i can't move it oh shit i just have to go the other way i
had it whoops that's gonna screw the whole thing up isn't it jex it what is jex it
don't act like i don't know shit no the wind really is tough why did i scream in your ears i'm
sorry because i'm an awful streamer and i forget the how loud noises hurt all right this is an
interesting scenario here i jump fall down dash up that i knew i figured the wind would have carried
me there that's what you gotta do it's close i'll get it patience myself patience i'm giving it some
pretty decent patience here all right so then it's just fall grab hi we love you no matter how loud
you scream maybe i should just get the bubble no are you calmly mad or just mad i'm just calm
i'm just enjoying the video game got it yikes okay that was got it nothing else just fall
hold on oh no oh no go up to the top quick up this game is surprisingly calm and cozy
despite how tough it is yeah it is up maybe anything no ice cactus again i did it again
okay shit now i got it wind is going the other direction now yeah typically i would play a game
like this for only a few hours at a time because they can really just get inside your brain
gotta go up but i'm still this is still i like it oops from here uh ride the platform with a
bubble and then bubble up i just freaked out because oh shit what i thought i was gonna need
to jump it's gonna put me right here perfect that's what you gotta do you gotta just that's
what you gotta do oh what all right i'm gonna pantomime something and i want you to know i want
you to guess what it is okay no i'm not it was the xbox controller surprise i don't have that's not
what pantomime means yeah well i was gonna do it but i decided against it did i ruin it
no i'd rather i would rather die than have to do that an xbox uh looks like i'm going this way
because i have to let's think this through let me see what happens when i touch this
right okay right right okay we gotta catch it on the way back
okay
no right right right right right right what you gotta do and i'm just not getting i that's what
you gotta do you gotta do it quick bingo one you gotta that's not what you gotta do you have to
grab the edge i gotta grab the edge you fucking got it idiot come in oh it's not possible without
thing yes it is don't ever tell me that's not possible it's not possible oh go down this
okay go ahead i gotta go ahead right i would have had it bring it up good very good very good very
good so pretty this is a very pretty game isn't it i agree probably should hold on secret no wait
can i go up gotta check for secrets it's possible this one's up here i don't know
you gotta check down down right in video game controllers man i swear
there's a huge it's a it's a big conspiracy i think what the fuck are you what's happening
to the controller i swear to god oh man i did it and no fruit there's a hole right here though
just take a look this looks like hell sure let's do it have you tried turning on the controller
it's one thing i actually haven't tried is turning it on i'm using my teeth like all right very
clearly i have to jump off and you also have to pull it and i jumped over it running out of gas
here running out of gas i'm gonna be on the other side just covered in fucking water just sweating
my ass off my hands are sweating i'm like a dog you know a dog doesn't sweat the only sweats
take through his mouth i don't i didn't even know i didn't even know and i would have known if i
known i would have known i i i'm sweating through my hands right now it's the only part that's
sweating can i get it oh i'm so happy drink from your hands i'm not sure that's a good idea
very you probably have to just dash only because jumping is not gonna help i don't think
shit you gotta get to the very edge try hitting jump and that i didn't know you could do this
you just you can ask this actual dash jumping new mechanic and i didn't even learn it somebody told
me about it just do it oh just do it hold on sorry guys i have to get the the layer of oil off my
hands how's that for a gamer challenge my hands are covered in like oil hold on no no i turned
on the camera and it stopped that's gonna haunt me for three days now i'm not gonna be able to
sneeze for three days fuck why did i do that wind wind no it's not enough why is it not letting me
jump up is this because the wind i don't think i can do this from right now i can holy shit you
got it oh boy you gotta go fast my hands are falling off the controller god face the snowball
this sucks i hate this wind i hate the wind i don't like the wind i'm playing tug of war with the
video game right now oh fuck itchy face stop it just go what am i doing that's all right i got
the berry oh i didn't have a jump didn't have a jump i thought i had one still all right something
i gotta remember that uses a dash maybe that it's not just like a fancy jump it's actually dashing
i almost died i think it didn't this is the guy that beat dark souls on stream yep one of the only
ones i have to jump on them this is such extreme when oh no oh i had it was so close
this is the hardest level in the whole game they fall to oh i've overshot it that would have been
it too i had it thank god i don't have a face cam on right now you can see what i'm doing
this is the longest i've spent on leveling it's probably this is probably one of the easiest
slides in the whole game and i'm still here my fucking god
all right did it i just beat the easiest slide in the game don't do diagonal uh blame phil spencer
it's his fault because he owns these controllers and they're his all of them he sells them out of
his fucking truck in his house he makes them in his spare time oh did the truck no no no no
oh my god oh it's too much i feel like i'm getting the wind blowing on me in real life
do it i was doing now i'm going real fast i jumped over how did i jump over i can't believe i had
oh i just to go underneath it what the fuck not i think i'm just doing it wrong let me sit here
okay got it i win john wait up what i nailed it this is the most comical character
theo you all right yeah just give me a second a gondola i've always wanted to ride one of these
it looks pretty old but maybe it still works i don't see any other way to cross this
chasm let's do it
this lever looks important easy every time i was probably going to go to the operator in a past
life do you think this is safe i'm sure it's fine how to check out with oshiro
i shouldn't have tried to help him because i told you so but
i should have listened they didn't get hurt and that's what matters
local boomer can't beat children's platformer i can barely breathe that's bullshit that you know
that it's not even like that what okay if we don't get a selfie on this thing we're going to regret it
i can't even see the ground through the mist this is not a children's platformer i know and
you're gonna have to explain that to i don't even know who said it i just read it how high up are we
less panicking more posing looks like we stalled out this guy's always taking selfies
maybe if i you broke it
dark world oh this really isn't good you cool oh no i'm not cool i can't breathe
you're having a panic attack why would you think it's a good idea to ride this stupid thing
don't take it out on me stay with me my grandpa taught me a trick for this close your eyes
picture a feather floating in front of you see it okay your breathing keeps that feather floating
just breathe slow and steady in and out am i supposed to do this oh it's x a i have to match
this i don't know i i don't know how to calm down okay i'm trying i know i have to keep it
in the box but there we go nice and easy did i win i mean i'm not really breathing very well here
look at i'm going like i should be going see easy feeling any better i think so thanks for helping
me calm down how did you know we were gonna start moving again
oh i totally thought we were done for but there is no there's a raid up here
uh there's a rare charizard and i gotta get the gym up here i'm sorry what were you saying
lol lol whoa that's a crazy selfie technically so who took this picture is what i want to know
scary right we don't ever find out who that is shit almost looks like we're almost at the
summit right we got maybe a couple more worlds mirror temple chapter five not close
not even close to it said there are seven total chapters plus one bonus okay i wonder if i should
break this into two streams what do you think tomorrow two go for like another all right so
if i go for like another hour right so would that be like two like five to six two like six
hour streams two five hour streams back to back that makes sense right the end worlds are really
long okay so after this chapter call it and finish it tomorrow and do the tapes too bonus
worlds and b-sides okay we'll see where we're at in like another hour so we'll just take a look
oh man look at this place feeling adventurous i don't know you're not going to do the tapes in
one stream well i mean i don't plan i plan on trying to do some of them looks pretty dark in
there more like a nightmare than an adventure i'll just take a quick i thought he was gonna say
selfie oh he that is what he said he is gonna take some pictures this place must be ancient
the oh wait my insta pics followers are gonna eat this up you won't do the tapes in one stream
i mean i don't really have an intention to i would try to do a one or two of them or three
of them or all of them in like 45 minutes it takes about two minutes per level two minutes per level
five levels per side two four six eight ten twelve yeah i'll beat it in probably like 14 minutes
secrets no this place is interesting looking i like the foot sounds that kind of glass sound sounds
good uh i don't have a there okay so there's a mechanic i can just squish that that like
whoa so they activate when i activate boy interesting stuff mirror oh this is tio's
phone don't panic john maybe it just fell out of his pocket i'll give it back to him when i find him
that's a cool mechanic i like it secret right here new bubble is red is that okay it does
mean something let's say up oh boy left
shit nope that ain't gonna work shit i can get it i gotta just jump from left right i got this
now what do i go how do i get out of here shit can't get out of here i have to have a dash
so what's the progress route here what are those crystals doing that blue crystal just lit up when
i touched it i have to light them all up because look see i definitely have to light these all up
there's no way i don't that one i think that's all of them no not on this side i got them right
is that just for show those just actually don't do anything you don't have to light them up okay
whoa
shit all right i figure i got it i got it i got it i don't know what to do sit up i'm it's this
it's the dash it's screwing my face up oh my god jeremy you're gonna drive me crazy
oh
jeremy is what he named his xbox controller
it is trust me it is i know what it's watching
this one's so easy just watch
now for this one there's enough spring on it all right so what are you doing
shit i had it
oh i didn't even need to do that real talk strawberries are the best berries
you know i might actually i might agree with that but i don't think so
well that's how you think okay it's that easy apparently this is my first time watching this
stream i won't be coming back oh well i'm sorry sorry i told you guys to behave we didn't do
anything it must have been the smell same deal this way can i make it over here
oh geez okay
i get it
no i don't
both sides are open more berries i get it i get a jump though i know you can do it
i'm certain i know you can do this you know you can do it
i know i just figured it out i give them just slowing down
i'm just slowing down remember this is the gamer fatigue
gamer fatigue sets in and you start to kind of just make the fucking dumb mistake
why am i going anywhere that didn't go because i went left i went right can't go down
up go the other side down here i already did this one down i think i got everything here didn't i
dude gamer fatigue sets in and then you start to make dumb mistakes and you need to go eat like a
snack i'm just gonna leave so how do i leave that's a great question because this is the
point straight up isn't that just called regular fatigue no no no it's different
come on i can grab the edge
come on i didn't jump slowing down gamer fatigue sets in oh fuck sorry i got
that one nothing else over there right uh-huh i'm gonna have to get in a bubble to go through
that one i think bubble from the other side there's gonna be a bubble on the all the way
to the edge i'm gonna bubble my way over there oops i see uh can i get through that is it a
secret it's not oops you know you could just duck jerry bane that is a possibility all right so
i'm gonna take that out so that one goes straight out let me get the cherry here first though
back
i was trying to donkey kong it probably still can i i i know i can do it trust me
all the way through go go go go go up so introducing blades there's the key
and a secret but not really because i didn't get the thing that was necessary
i didn't hit another button somehow shit i got a great question for all you guys watching
where in the name of god is the door that this key goes to i forget can i get that
oh i see i see that okay i don't think i can i get reliably back in there that's gonna be
paying the ass to get back in there i see exactly where it is though see right there i see it
okay bingo that's the other door so now let's finish this and there's a way to go through here
oh shit i need a bubble don't i so i got to take bubble from here all the way through
damn all right
oops oops
no stop it just
i got the super secret berry nice now we can get the hell out of here for god's
sakes the strawberries i just i mean i said berry didn't i i said berry i said berry right
berry a berry is a strawberry is a berry i'll be honest with you no idea no idea what that door is
how did i even get in here
oh this is new oh found the door excellent yes they know
they oh where are you hey uh why are you inside a mirror i'm pretty sure you're the one in the
mirror what happened well i was taking a nonchalant mirror selfie you know it's your boy
in this ancient temple no big deal hashtag i refuse to say it next thing i know i wake
up lying on the ground what does it look like over there how can i find you it's uh it's really
dark and weird there's wait something's coming i'm feeling a strong inclination to run away
be careful okay it's very dark in here here let's see if we can get in there yes we can
yeah secrets i think i see what looks like a secret entrance it is oh it's one of those
ah there are lanterns now that makes sense so i gotta go over here anything else
i get i did it okay yeah need more of those lanterns lit up i just stay hiding things from me
you know what i mean need to check every single wall that's it you either beat it or you die
let's light this room up though forget about progression light it up oops uh
can you pause yeah sure i'll pause you need to pee you have five seconds one okay that should
give you enough time can i get on the other side probably not just drag me over no no you
no don't drag me over i just went up it was too dark for me to realize that out there this place
is huge oh my goodness this place is gigantic all right what do you want me to do with this
oh yeah it's so big wrong balloon secrets no what see what's on the other side another one
that looks pretty to me it's not so we gotta go right then jump off the wall
or die either one oh that little space i saw it right the last second come on really oh give me
a break oh my fucking god i'm gonna i'm gonna return this controller i bought it four years ago
so definitely above the eye yeah oh yeah oh yeah i mean of course there is there's a key up there
nice a warranty so somehow there's a there's a bubble that goes all the way up if the controller
has a nice d-pad yeah the xbox d-pad i think is really bad though i mean let's be real it's okay
it's got a four-year warranty
here swish pro controller has a god tier d-pad yeah it does it really does
it's got separate buttons right for each d-pad how hurry let's try
oh i got a button shit i touched the candy crystals and i died oh
is there a secret that's probably a secret right there
that's it down here i can go back to this huge open area do have a key though is there a door over
here from the door but i'm not done though not i don't want to go there yet hold on
yeah that's okay that's where the door is there's so much more it's all the way to the right
giant eyeball monster all the way to the right but there's so much more to see look at this
look at all this bullshit and i don't i don't mean bullshit isn't bad i mean just stuff
no i thought i did this last time i jumped up fast
i'm dead trying just to jump out it won't jump out
can i not jump out i guess i don't need to but yeah i don't i guess i don't
okay that's that one chat calm down a little yeah i mean we're just having fun they were
there was some there was some memeing going on earlier how hard can i how far can i just climb
just climb how i just did that
come on give me a break i think i need this yeah i do it's that one
so i went down i got everything down yeah well i gotta go up there really seeing a reliable way
to get over here probably from the other side all right let's go back up this way
shit i don't remember oh this is back with the
some of you guys are going to bed well good night have a great night see you tomorrow
we're gonna do some more celeste tomorrow and finish it get to the end do some of the bonus
stuff how did i get here i i went so quickly through a ton of rooms i don't remember where
the hell i go i want to say down not this one right was it this way all right chat help me out
here i actually am lost bottom of the temple the bubble that go you can go right
oh this one
thank you all right i gotta get on this side oh shit just gonna make it over oh shit
just get across
fuck no diagonal again oh i really i think i'm gonna use a different control tomorrow
i'm gonna just plug my ps4 in that's really starting to get very very very irritating
use the keyboard i can't do a platform with a keyboard i don't know how anyone humanly
possibly does that platform with keyboard is off it's no way how did i not do that come on
some of you guys like i said are fucking super humans why not because something about like
putting your my hand down on keys like this and having to use my index finger my ring finger
to move around or my um it just doesn't doesn't translate to me it's not like wasd
anything else i missed up here i don't think so now i'm of the opinion that a controller is
is better in at least a very specific few scenarios all right don't touch the ground
i have the i'll get this one first i think a lot of third-person games just feel better
platform must feel better with the controller for me another cassette currently unlocking
content for tomorrow let's see i i mean you're just gonna have to go at some point
right can i get the whole thing in one go i might be able to
oh my god i gotta get through that it's gotta be right when it switches
so it's gotta be one two uh here we go no i had it i don't know why i just freaked out
oh shit okay now what about this one looks like i could uh bounce off the sides here
okay roo and then hold on because i can't make that jump so i have to hold on to that
like this okay well you fucking xboxed me thanks a lot just got xboxed
ready
shitty secrets that i missed maybe not that i can see that takes us that's the cassette
and now it's here down and then uh i get everything that i wanted to get i think so
i think it's time to leave i'm gonna go open the door now that's the gamer fatigue i got the
cassette the door wait what is this here to go back i'm just curious is there any reason to
go up or left or down or i don't think so here we go no reason to use the dash until now
i don't want to start this whole thing over again i'm gonna say down why no reason to go now
oh my god a couple different directions here well that's i just stretched i felt so far
i've got to take the i'm not gonna do that yet i'm gonna go right i guess that's the only way to go
no it's not
me to kick yes it is this is the game with the flying strawberries it is this is the game with
the flying strawberries you got it you nailed it completely i think we're just gonna go up
hold on a minute here though wait a second there's gonna be something on the side i know it
that you you wouldn't shoot that fast through the whole thing unless there's something to do here
i mean too late now this is gonna be a giant mirror i'm gonna assume that what a huge mirror
final boss i think we have at least four or five hours to go
it's gonna chase me the whole level isn't it i'm gonna have to fucking flappy bird through this
whole thing and oh it is me what am i supposed to do okay i can break and smash my head into stuff
and break stuff strawberries does the monster really even give a shit about strawberries i
would assume probably not there's no harm in checking what do these do can't go through them
why did chat slow down so much um i think it's starting to get a little later and people may
have left yeah there's probably people took off people had fun for a little while and then kind
of dwindled down a little just chilling out nothing else i feel like i'm gonna miss secrets
and i don't like making well did i just lose no now i am the monster i thought i could maybe
get up there the game forces you to go to the middle wait now it looks breakable let me go hey
where are we what did you do to theo you think i'm doing this that's cute sweetheart this is exactly
what i warned you about jump on your head easy as a don't try to make this my fault
you still don't get it the mountain gave me this body but i'm not the only creepy thing living in
that messed up head of yours don't like what you see what a surprise shut up i tried to stop you
look in the mirror all this is yours this temple only magnifies the mountain's power you're in
control here not me dialogue again let's see it i don't believe you if you're part of me why do
you want to hurt me poor john always the victim all i do is babysit you and you hate me for it
you're unraveling and you know it i care so much about protecting me why didn't you just
explain what was going on listen john you never gave me a chance john please just help me get out
now you want me to save you why are you doing this just be on my side here please stop trying
to make me feel like a monster you really want to know why i won't help because you deserve this
still think you can climb this mountain shut up i don't need your help i'll do it alone and yes i
was gamer fatigue reading that i'm sorry i had i had some energy earlier but after the gamer
fatigue set in
wait i gotta hit the button gamer fatigue you know what gamer fatigue sets in you just gotta be real
careful i have to hold on no hold on i gotta actually around idiot he's reading garfield bits
oh garfield's fatigue no stop jumping you don't need to
shit fucking garfield's fatigue holy shit i went right into the wall why am i launching so far
all right you have to let go it forces you to let go and you grab onto this
oh okay i had to do it like a half second earlier oh great don't chase me around you can't do me
like this he's gonna he can crash into these i get it i played the tutorial of this guy's body
oh my god i made it i got a fairy too out of the way out of the way come on hands are greasy
that's what i call a save you'll see that in the fucking yearly book of saves
how about that one for a save a lot ow ah i'll get that one last
whoa the way get out of my fucking way is this all in my head why is it so hostile those things
are hunting me i'm a trespasser in my own world he was trapped somewhere in here because of me
if i give him fully maybe the temple will let him go i'll have to do the feather thing
get the feather i don't have to do it well i'm dead
i don't even need to get out well
wait how do i get out no there was a thing to do over there go back down
oh shit i missed it damn it that's too bad that's too bad
right key another key this is another huge place all right he can break that
what did that even do for me what's going on what did that do for me what happened released him
fuck back to dragging through the whole thing
jumping his head he can hit those too okay let's trap him i did oh i saw it coming from a mile away
too there's one key okay strawberry up there there's a lot of things to see a lot of ways to go
um i um it's gonna unlock this one oh shit okay let's get him to break that door
it's progression it might be i think this is progression probably shouldn't do this
keep going i got no more oh no this is the worst speed run i've ever seen
i wonder if i can let me think about this for a second maybe i don't have to do that
is it possible that i okay i don't second key i didn't get that though unfortunately
so this is another lock somewhere that i have to unlock now where that is i have no idea i might
have to go back up i mean there's this way grab on uh um get it get uh i had to do hdq but i play
every game i feel like a lot of people would probably not want to watch that i got the berry
i already went in here back down looking for the other door i'm gonna get lost again i just know it
i'm certain of it this way down up okay i found another berry
i have the right idea i go back am i skipping this shit
wait a minute that gives me ah my hands
didn't even need to do that ah secrets
button to press needs us back here he's gonna break this where is he
i get him i get him to break it does that help me though
oh there's more thank god i found you he's in a crystal happy to see you
are you okay yeah i'm gonna be fine i've been stuck in this crystal for ages
do you get the feeling that this place knows you better than you know yourself
yeah i'm so embarrassed that you have to see the side of me i tried to stop you i hope that
selfie was worth it needed the you just did it here you heard it
it's the minute it's the middle one selfies are always not worth it i shouldn't be mad this isn't
your fault i'm glad you're safe but you're trapped because of me and now this temple is showing you
what i'm really like i'm horrible hey we're in this together don't act like this is all on you
what do you mean you didn't trap me in the crystal sure those monsters are coming from you but the
temple is shaping itself around me too i can feel it these eyes are staring at me and the
crystal is coming from me i know it i hate to ask but i really need your help right now
okay i've got your back i'll bust you out of that thing and then we'll escape together
just as soon as i find my way around to you my only hope right now i believe in you for real
i hope that's not a mistake you shouldn't have believed in me oh
you can skip cutscenes all right bye i'll get you out of there eventually soon baby
it's possible i gotta go up from there more shit that we haven't seen yet
um got another key there's three keys does that come back it doesn't is it oh shit
i'm kind of amazed out here um where was this door where's my map i need my map in the top right
corner this is where i was locked this what the hell was that for what was that for why did i
unlock that oh shit am i losing connection it'll be all right don't pass oh i can use
the bubble here okay no stay alive what time what time is it yeah sometimes you get a bump
we should be fine okay i need another key for that door did i miss anything up here
jeez well yeah that'll probably happen a couple more times
shit i just gotta move out of the way don't even touch it
ah that guy's freaking me out losing internet again
well now that's what i'm paying attention to so in fact let me just pause it for a second to make
sure there's nothing actually going on no it's just being annoying no ah he's right there
oh my god he's gonna fuck this whole thing up
still has comcast i i do not have comcast i have a different company but i got some
news for everybody here they're all bad all the question is let me see hold on
although i don't really have any reason to be over here this is locked hit it oh it'll be like
something hidden there's a berry in here or something i'm killing me there's a thing to jump
on right the other one it's gonna be the button god damn it i gotta go around no did i get it is
it open is it just open tell me it's open i'm just getting stuck don't you dare i'm at it smash it
with a hammer theo i finally found you i knew you'd make it it wasn't easy all those monsters
really coming from inside me that's a valid question i'll be happy to discuss how the
monsters relate to your inner self but right now my inner self is real sick of being stuck in the
crystal oh right this crystal is like an expression of my negative psychic energy or whatever
yeah but how do we break it if i knew why i trapped myself in this thing maybe i could bust out
but i don't and i don't think i can get at the bottom of it while we're stuck in this nightmare
dimension you might have to carry me oh what no i would have been like carry me i don't wait that
much i'm not leaving you behind hell no you better not leave me in this place i was gonna say you
might see i can do that i told you dang girl you're gonna lift oh this is gonna be horrible
all right you got this now we have to play the puzzle game with this guy's body
hope you know how to deal with these things i do i was gonna use use a weapon let's go wow
what the fuck was that he did the same thing i did he's in twitch chat right now
is there no button here either that wasn't where was that what was that it wasn't on the head
diarrhea that is from there too don't touch that
i felt it in my bones all right you guys talking are you guys doing politics in this chat
no politics no political discussion end of discussion don't you understand unless what
you are doing unless you're doing an impersonation of somebody's voice you can't say anything to do
with politics oh go go what the hell happened don't throw them in the spikes oh fuck just get
throw this idiot over here throw him the whole way i have to throw him up there or the god damn
it oh my god i'm glad how they added i'm glad they added a fucking resident evil 4 companion
in this game no no no just he has you have to hit it i have to i have to hit him i have to throw
him into it after jumping on this guy come on get over here out out i just screamed so
long that was really loud i'm really sorry vio saved the day i did actually well that was the
right idea but wrong execution oh my fuck killed him i crushed him fuck get away from me please
help help uh now what that's not good okay he's gonna be right help help help me someone help
i'm not gonna do this fuck i just leave him all right what if i could
okay i get it it has to be ready ah that's what you gotta do no
no stop killing him that was it i had it got it game over come here we have to be close i can
feel it and you know stay there for a minute while i figure out the hell's going on it's
literally right here uh hold on no just go leave leave forget about the fucking berries i can get
them later some other day playing the electric guitar someone's just got the amp up way too loud
throw him into the eye i got to the center of my brain that's good how many deaths that's gonna
be like probably 500 deaths 300 deaths 400 deaths not even 200 get a b-side awesome okay
i think i think i'm gonna call it here we'll pick it up tomorrow that's probably where we
should stop it's about six hours and then just pick it up tomorrow i'm gonna actually start
on time tomorrow and then we'll just play it tomorrow starting at the normal time until
i finish it because one two three four five six said there was like another two worlds three worlds
another few hours and then the bonus content why did he stream hit and run for 12 hours
and not this um it's called i was never going to open hit and run ever again and i knew it
see with this i know that i'll open this again i'm certain i'll play it i'll play through it i can
come back to it another day i there was not a chance in hell i was going to open hit and run
ever again so i had to beat it so we'll start regular time tomorrow somewhere around three p.m
pacific not like 4 30 this time i feel fine i felt like kind of shitty the last
day before yesterday and yesterday but we'll be all right i'll be ready to go uh first impressions
after six hours i think it's great i think it's got just enough of a challenge factor
and a replayability factor where it's not super rage inducing but it's challenging and fun i
think it's great but i'll see you guys tomorrow around 3 p.m pacific and let's get to the bits
which is okay the game saves itself right let me just make sure like my game we're good right
climb yeah okay now there's the total deaths 893 total deaths so far still missing a few hearts
still missing a couple of bonus tapes wow how much did you guys have that's very off from 922
where are you guys getting the other 30 deaths from 922 i literally accumulated each individual
level oh the little computer one right that would make sense all right i'll see you guys tomorrow
let's see the bits take care those of you that came over from joel's channel if you stuck around
thanks for sticking around i'm germa nice to see you and let's get to the bits and pick it up
tomorrow the outro screen i'm gonna go back about six hours ago here with a lot of community subs
so there's a lot to scroll a shitload actually of community subs back here we had uh i free for
one dollar hey germa sad to say that i won't be able to join many live streams from now on
uh due to looking for work and doing small jobs but i sincerely appreciate watching your streams
are working into the night please do not slap yourself my fellow scaly friend well congratulations
on getting some small jobs and hope you find something hope you find some work
it can be a tough environment i wish you the best and i i hate to break it to you but i'm not a
scaly i don't even know what that word means but thank you ivory don't worry about making it to
every stream appreciate appreciate you nonetheless double d thanks for the one dollar all right so
welcome everyone to the 68th meeting of the bias as you know we do this meeting every single month
to make sure that we agree on things so let's get started okay opening a can of beef opening a can
of beef 18 wheelers wheelies going the respected speed limit in a school zone meeting of the
bias is commenced i'll see you all next month thank you jess for the one dollar thanks for
showing me what picross is i've lost so much time already countless hours sleepless nights i can't
stop i'm ruined picross is some of the most fun ever and what do you mean ruined you're training
your brain you're doing puzzles you're doing you're getting knowledge mathematics there are
plenty of good ones siroc thanks for the dollar for rats rats he lives with rats eating out of
the garbage and trash germa he lives in the sewers now watch out for floods until the coast is clear
who does me fgw thanks for the one dollar the germa old emo looks like larry david or george
castanza it's a 10 out of 10 evil well it should look like me because it's my face thank you divas
for the three dollars three dollars every stream from divas thank you really appreciate it just
consistently every single time thank you bake me home thanks for the one dollar
golden foxy thanks for the one dollar i just want to say did you know that you can make your
own sega 1000 sega genesis sega saturn meaning you are the check and make your own games
for example mr sneak man jex ultimate the rats invasion hope you get better sega 1000
you can make your own sega games oh i don't really know how to code so that's interesting
that's available aren't there still people making nes games and they actually make the
cartridge and stuff i swear to god this is am i making this up hold on 10 minutes 10 minutes
slow mode oh no no no that that's you have to be here for 10 minutes okay i see for a second i
thought it was just 10 minutes slow mode i was like what the fuck is happening that's interesting
stuff though i've seen nes kind of games made before on their own cartridges which is interesting
thank you smelly boy for the one dollar power steering on my van gave out at college today
so i had to drive all the way home hoping not to die find found out i'm not just out of fluid but
there's a massive leak i have to borrow a friend's car praying the repairs in over a thousand dollars
then i open up the stream and my name is jeremy i
get me with the story and then you try to pull me in with a little fucked up comment
sorry to hear about your car hopefully it fixes itself what no hopefully gets prepared hey sticks
renegade thanks for the one dollar stream idea get this book called wreck this journal almost each
page has a suggestion of how to damage the book that's so why uh thank you tippy tim tan for the
one dollar you and your new toy sound like my brother when he bought a nine pack of kazoos
off amazon what's his name what's the toy's name shiito right no no shiito all right is your name
shiito that's yes what's your name is your name shiito he said what's it what's your name shiito
shiito yes okay i feel you and it looks like pac-man so i love it thank you to
e-word twerky word word thanks for the three dollars and 75 cents germa are there any plans
for a best of 2018 video well we did a end of the year 2018 stream some of the best of was
in that stream and if you mean game wise uh i have no plans on doing it i think we went over
him already but number one i don't know i don't remember we did do it do an entire stream narrated
by shiito shiito will make more than one appearance don't worry but no plans for like a video or
anything did a couple of streams based around the last year that's probably where i'm gonna
leave it but thank you thank you benny jets for the five dollars i'm playing through hotline miami
and germa made it look five times harder than it actually is that's not true that game is
incredibly difficult that's one of the hardest games i've ever played um so i mean if you want
to put yourself in like the zero point zero zero zero one percent that's fine that game is fucking
insanely difficult and that's great i'm really happy that you're in the zero point zero zero
zero two percent of all people on earth zero point four percent actually i am yeah we already
went over during that stream like the steam achievement for the second level being completed
all right you can't deny the facts they're there and they're right in front of you somebody
mentioned hotline miami and he's already salty no i'm fine i'm doing just fine but thank you
benny jets congratulations on being in the zero point zero zero four percent of all video game
players i'm very happy that you're there i'm not that's just the way it is we had a ton of
anonymous gifted subs earlier like 20 whoever you were thank you a ton from fert bernandes
dr fudge thanks for the five dollars finally in time to catch a stream and it's one of my
favorite games yay i could see why it's i don't really i currently don't have any real complaints
about the game well i have one but it's not a complaint it's a preference and that is no you're
not gonna hold off when i finish celeste we'll talk about it but currently i don't have any
actual complaints about the game i think it's fantastic it's just a couple of preference
things and none of them really have anything to do with the game like the gameplay but thank you
dr fudge thank you kerplunkers for the ten dollars no message thank you kerplunkers
no message but thank you thank you door cube 700 000 games for the one dollar this entire
game is sour please that's got a great soundtrack thank you creel for the five dollars whoever said
press b to fuck when we met uh okay i'm gonna skip this one uh thank you for the five dollars
superintendent chalmers thanks for the one dollar hey germa really enjoying your videos
your last video about the spy cycle really helped me improve as a spy main you should do
another tips and tricks video on the huntsman though the first one wasn't very clear also really
enjoying the grandpa videos but the germa craft series is very lackluster i suggest you combine
the two and call it grandpa invades germa craft would make it a bit more bearable best of love
and congrats on 8 000 8 000 subs thank you for the one doll thank you demonic cucumber for the
one dollar the amount of times you just screamed idiot at yourself when you died earlier is only
reaffirming my belief that you are actually dennis from always sunny in philadelphia
so many girls who i don't know what that is i've never i've never seen that show
except i on stream i think three or four times talked about how it was like one of the better
comedies that was on tv i already told you guys my top like five favorite shows
is curb your enthusiasm always sunny philadelphia curb your enthusiasm again deserves to be on there
twice game of thrones seasons one through four or season maybe maybe five if i if i really gave a
fuck uh and then i don't know that's it and then one punch man he's laughing so fucking hard
no that's a great show it probably would be on there the books are better thank you to uh
one black sperm for the one dollar hi germa are you gonna play resident evil 2 when it comes out
uh yes i am absolutely play the demo no i'm not gonna i no i no demo the demo just the problem
with the demo is you do it and then you're already into the game and you want to keep playing it and
you just can't so then you have to wait for the actual game to come out i'm not gonna vermin tied
to myself again not gonna happen you know the story with the vermin tied to i played the demo
for six hours straight and played the same three levels and then didn't want to play the actual
release when it came out i ain't gonna vermin tied to myself again but thank you thank you too
uh for the two dollars by the way thank you tomorrow cucumber for one dollar i had a similar
problem with my smile a way to fix it is to try to keep your mouth closed when you smile
you look less like a psycho no i just look like a psycho in every photo doesn't matter
i have a gift of looking awful in almost every picture i've ever taken
freudian weapon thanks for the one dollar thanks for showing me another awesome challenging game
to play also you shouldn't be so hard on yourself about selfies they're the modern self-portrait
yeah i was just messing around i was just kidding around thank you for all the community subs to
cookie crm thank you dead oh thank you dead dead oh dead oh dead oh i know i say your name
correct no i don't but thank you for the community subs mostly lost thanks for the one dollar this
picture is very important when you guys think the gnome thing is going to transition over to
something else because right now it's we're current we're like in the gnome we're in the gnome zone
how long does it take for a new thing to replace the old thing five years but thank you to
trust harry for the one dollar germa i'm not kidding please help they're right i'm sorry
matthew martin thanks for the one dollar hey germy hey germa oh sorry i don't know why i do
that sometimes uh thank you for the one dollar uh matthew hey germa it's me golden foxy i've been
banned on my other account you've just been well i how do you keep getting banned anyways
uh want to let you know that you make me happy i have depression and i want you to know you're
the best live streamer and youtuber ever watched uh i want to talk about school and my bullies to
you since i do that with all my friends i can't because this account is on the risk of being banned
i also want to let the mods know i'm sorry um all right well first of all uh and then you say i'm
gonna miss you because you're getting banned well let's go over a couple things here if you if you
get banned more than a couple times you kind of need to take a look and see what's what's happening
there and maybe you're saying something or doing something that you might need to think about
potentially changing so maybe just take a look and see maybe the things you're saying take a step
back and breathe a little bit and see second of all um hope you have a great day too you want
to let the mods know that you're sorry if you get banned and create a new account why even mention
the other account um i i'm not sure but uh all everybody is welcome to hang out here and have
fun but there are certain things that you kind of have to you got to play by some rules and if the
line is crossed a couple times and you're you know warned or told or there's warning systems and
there's it's not just if you said something you're gone forever right all the mods here are very very
happy to hear out a grievance and try to work it out but maybe if you're getting banned a bunch
of times just maybe step back and try to figure out maybe what the things you're saying
or what what you're doing you know but thanks for sticking around hopefully uh hopefully you
don't get banned again i really hope that doesn't happen but thank you for the donations you've
given thank you so much uh thank you mandum requiem for the two dollars no message thank you for the
two bucks d jack thanks for one dollar very refreshing to watch you be good at video games
after re-watching the simpsons hit and run vaude today that game is fucking hell look if you put
your hand on a stove okay if we're standing there together you and me we're both standing in my
kitchen and the stove is on and there's a pan on the stove and i tell you hey uh this pan is burning
hot i'm gonna burn my hand if i touch that and you say no you're not you're not gonna burn your
hand that pan is not even hot and i'm like dude the pan is the pan is burning fucking hot right
now if i touch i'm gonna burn myself and you're like no you're wrong you're gonna get burnt
and i put my hand in there and i burn my fucking hand okay fuck oh my god it's all red and shit
and then you stare at me and you go to you stick your fucking hand in there
and you're staring in my eyes and your fucking hand is melting and you're like dude it's not even
that hot i yes it is just because we have a different tolerance for pain doesn't mean the
pan isn't hot you burnt you look look look look at your hand you literally your hand is melting
off your fucking wrist the pan is hot i i don't want to get my hand burnt you can hold your hand
in there all you want that doesn't mean the pan ain't hot what does this have to do with anything
he said it's refreshing to watch you be good at a video game after rewatching the simpsons hit and
run the simpsons hit and run is the hot pan wow you're really sucking simpsons hit and run you
know i beat simpsons hit and run first try keep you keep your hand in that pan all you want it's
still hot you get triggered so easily well stop triggering me i was gonna try to put this i was
gonna try to scream with this but i i didn't end up doing don't say that what i said people saying
i'm getting triggered all right she knows time to read the bits thank you d jack for the one dollar
shitload of community subs on great canadian fuck club thank you
dead oh so many community subs it's unbelievable unbelievable you guys are seriously you guys are
too much thank you peaceful hailey thanks for the one dollar i hate when i donate i don't exactly
know what to say but anyways hope all is well with you thanks for being my inspiration have a good
night germa and chat you as well thank you peaceful hailey i make triggered jokes in 2019 no that was
responding to somebody that said that to me and chat so i responded with the reference back at
them because that's what they understand right that that person that's what that person understood
when i said that back master of comedy wouldn't stoop that low because i said don't trigger me
screaming it as a joke responding to the guy that said the word triggered in the first place i was
doing a back and forth with that guy because that's what they understood you understand
thanks for the one dollar matthew now let's have shido do one thank you to please go out with my
grandpa for five dollars and four cents and they say thank you not peeing in your closet bathroom
combo like a god tier streamer no but thank you please go out with my grandpa for the five dollars
dead oh thanks for 15 dollars please get pc medic i remember pc medic it's like a total scam right
lower the pitch on the peeper machine but thank you dedo for the huge amount of money and the
huge amount of community subs thank you so much c4g thanks for the one dollar please give us the
first clue in the germa arg i'll have shido do that did you get all that you have to open up
first of all you have to open up portal 2 and then there's a wall you need to look at and i'm
not even going to give you the hints why would i do that hey bream bin thanks for the five dollars
showing off your true gamer skills thank you thanks a lot thanks for the five dollars and
thanks for the message thank you matthew for the one dollar the whole level is you jumping on
laundry that's kind of cool but then he does the sideways kind of i don't know about that face
dork cube thanks for the one dollar that computer mini game you played is actually an extended
version of the game's demo that's really cool cool that they would hide that somewhere in the
game that's fun uh unamused panda thanks for the one dollar it's just fun germa just smooth
ass clenching fun yeah it is uh spatins spatin sfm thanks for the eight dollars and 15 cents
hey germa been watching for years and just wanted to say that i appreciate everything that you do
i love putting you in the background as i draw you're somehow the most relaxing and hysterical
streamer on twitch and i really and i hope to enjoy and support your content for years to come
take care thank you for the eight dollars and 15 cents spatin uh i will have to tell you relaxing
relaxing i think i screamed a dozen times tonight you're like sitting there drawing i imagine you're
just like you hear a loud scream and your hand moves because i startled you and you fuck up
the drawing hopefully that's not happening yeah i'm gonna finish it tomorrow we'll finish uh
celeste tomorrow i mean usually you're still pretty calm even when you yell compared to some
i don't i still like to scream because i know how upgrading and annoying that can be sometimes for
people the loud sound you just kept to pull your headphones out like jesus i try not to do it that
often but thanks a lot i'm happy to be the thing that you can relax to for sure thank you crusty
earwax thanks for the two bucks oh my gosh germa i thanks for the two dollars uncommon thanks for
the four dollars pj salt pj salt pj salt i think that was when i was talking about the diagonal
xbox controller super seal thanks for the one dollar after playing this game for a stream or
two you should replay meat boy and see how you match how much your new climbing reflex fucks you
up i love this game so much thank you drosophilia for the one dollar all you have to do to get the
ps4 controller to work flawlessly on steam is to plug it into your computer then in steam go to
settings controller general settings enable playstation configuration support and use steam
big picture mod mode i've actually i used to use the ps4 controller and i don't know what game it
was but there was a couple of games in a row that even having the big picture mode and playstation
configuration just didn't work it didn't matter what i did wouldn't accept it for some reason i
don't know which one it was but thank you for the tips done playing thanks for the one dollar
for five dollars actually i am done playing for tonight i'll pick it up tomorrow
pogatron thanks for the 30 dollars we got you earlier but thank you so much for the 30 bucks
much love to you thank you uh trying on a fee thanks for the one dollar gabe and andrew are big
noobs um all those friends here a future gamer thanks for the two bucks since chat was talking
about scare saturdays could we watch this i'm surprised that you kept this on the channel
no is this the is this the demon lord fucking video again if this is the demon video i swear
to god no it's it's eerie scariest game i've ever played why does this have 266 000 views why didn't
this just get buried so many these so many of these old old videos had like 30 000 views why
does this have 300 000 and it was uploaded fucking almost five years ago this is such a bad video
is it i haven't seen it show it on stream no i'm not going to i don't feel like getting embarrassed
i'm not going to get third hand embarrassment yes that's right that was me embarrassed when i
first made it embarrassed at the comments people wrote now embarrassed going back and watching
the embarrassment that i felt with everybody else here getting embarrassed that's third or
fourth hand embarrassment there it's i'm just kidding i'm it's probably fine but it is 12
minutes and i i don't really i don't really want to watch a 12 minute video right now
put it on the list we're gonna watch 700 000 games too i swear to god the first thing we're
gonna do is we're gonna watch 700 000 games and then we're gonna do whatever right remember that
one but thank you future gamer i appreciate it tod fluoride thanks for the of tod flowered thanks
for the one dollar let my hold on this just went down oh somebody just gave another dollar
oh it was a dollar how much was that oh rip came too late rip hopes and dreamcasts no it's in the
closet behind me it has to be done eventually it can't just not happen you understand it's
gonna sit there and taunt me i already own it tomorrow no we're gonna finish celeste tomorrow
and then i'll see the dreamcast probably next week the dreamcast got lost in the mail
uh thank you ever scarf ever scalf for the one dollar double d for the one dollar there's an
image here let's take a look all right that's pretty that's pretty good you said dreamcast today i know
i did i know but then i saw celeste and i kind of had to play it uh thank you kai lu anderson
thank you kaiu anderson for the one dollar double d thanks for the one dollar also please watch this
i saw it on the subreddit thank god all right i will watch this one we'll watch this one just
because i don't i don't have i have i seen this just exit out of celeste preparing to launch
celeste what let's get it on the screen feels to chew five gum stimulate your senses
oh
you're here to did this one i got a bucket of chicken what the fuck is this
is that it no that wasn't it i fucking accidentally clicked out of the window
that was funny good work excellent work hey damona cucumber thanks for the one dollar it's another
youtube link just check it first make sure it's not a gnome it's one of my videos a long time ago
come on now come on use those legs
i've been around for a long time okay look let me explain
i've made a thousand videos okay i've made a thousand videos i've streamed like three
thousand times sometimes shit like this flies on on the radar and it just happens i got got a
thousand videos where did they even come from is it because of the it's because of the fart
shit and i kept on talking about how not cool it was and how bad content it was you are so quick
how do you even remember that i don't remember even doing that do you understand i don't remember
that video i don't remember that portion how did you find that unbelievable and then damona cucumber
says someone in chat really wanted you to see that oh i love it that's that's fucking great
thank you for that kayu anderson thanks for the one dollar frody and weapon thanks for two dollars
swiggity swanky thanks for the one dollar play the spill clip at the lowest speed setting
the pain you show is real the lowest speed setting hold on oh the pain i show is real all i i i i'm
just me i'm just who i am that's it stop you're hurting him what no it's water fucking god damn
stop you're hurting him what did you say at times 0.5 speed i love this thing stop you're hurting him
what no that shit looks like a different person but that doesn't look like me my eyes are coming
out of my head what jesus all right well thank you thank you swiggity swanky for the one dollar
and the clip uh gil thanks for the community subs you came in with the shit load thank you so much
why is your chin so thin and go so far down i don't know i have a fucked up face hey damona
cucumber thanks for the one dollar hey jeremy i'm back again with my weekly bits and such i'm staying
with family till the home situation can be sorted out so life's okay i have a lot of disposable cash
i want to spend it on a passion of mine custom lego figures but god are they expensive i was
wondering where you stand on how much you should spend on your hobbies if you have the money
anybody love the stream keep it up i would say let me turn a sheet let's let put chido to bed
for a second here as long as you're taking care of stuff that needs to be taken care of in your
life so if you have rent if you have bills and you're taking care of them and you're paying them
right once you have that extra income that you know that you can spend
then go for it there's no i don't think there's a reason to stop well and savings as well make
sure you're saving some money too whether you have other accounts or if you have an investment
portfolio if you have one of those but once all your necessities are taken care of and you have
something else left over then why not but just make sure you cover all your bases first don't
forget about savings it's very important buy gold hey if you have disposable income and you have
some in money you maybe want to try some investment opportunities you want to try something else
buy a little bit of gold do it that's for you to decide that's for you to do what you please
not a bubble by the way bald coin by the way i am not a financial advisor i just play one on tv
just to let you know but i wish you luck custom lego figures sounds cool if you're into it and
you got the money and you've taken care of yourself go for it make sure you take care
of yourself first though it's very important dork cube 700 000 games thanks for the one dollar all
the berries you missed inspired me to make this germa is blind what the fuck i spent all my money
on gold well at least you'll be able to dig down into the dirt faster there's a little minecraft
gag for you hey garfield monday killer thanks for the one dollar garf is about to eat his tuesday
dinner germa so as our guest of honor in the arbuckle household why don't you come over here
and cut the roast beef i've actually never had roast beef before is it good i'm not a fan i mean
i'm a fan but not a big fan oh look odi's about to give a toast to germa bark bark he says i knew
odi wouldn't stop himself from crying he gets emotional at these types of events anyway germ
what's that you got on your plate wow you didn't think you were into that sort of thing all right
chat let's dig in what roast beef what are you talking about dork cube 700 000 games thanks to
the one dollar have you ever thought about ending the stream before 3 a.m so i can hear you read my
bits before bedtime i thought about it before but remember it's three it's not 3 a.m for me
it is 10 47 p.m pacific time but that's why i know i'm on pacific so when we go you know we're about
five six hours into a stream and we're at that place where i know it's early for me but it's
not for everybody else maybe dial it back a little and do it again tomorrow that's totally fine
i want to make sure that you don't stand up too late looking out for you hey boy 314 thanks for
the six dollars have my ad bits junks i'm getting my wisdom tooth out tomorrow morning but your
shitty stream with no webcam really keeps me relaxed i don't do webcam i don't do look i don't
do webcam there's a guy in the corner of your screen sitting there i don't want to do that
he does webcam i don't he almost got me there he does webcam all the time i do webcam all the time
but i don't leave it on webcam facecam to me all the time just feels like there's a security camera
that's pointing at me you know that feeling you get when you know you're on camera you're standing
somewhere you're out somewhere you're in a place where you know you are on fucking the security
camera and you just are like oh okay i'm just on that camera right now i guess it's like staring
at me i don't want to be i don't want to be done twitch chat security cam but we can tell you when
someone's behind you i i know that too i have mirrors you guys don't see them i got i got my
monitors here and above them is three huge mirrors to make sure i can always see behind me
haven't you done webcam for outlast i do i do webcam all the time but for me webcam and facecam
has to make sense as to why it's on in the first place if it's a scary game or i'm talking or
chatting or hanging out then yeah but i don't like the twitch chat security cam
you haven't noticed me behind you though how do you know that i haven't but i'm not i don't i'm
not against using a webcam i just don't i don't i don't why do you want to look at my my ugly mug
i think it just tracks from a lot of stuff that happens on the screen now
sometimes it doesn't maybe sometimes it is fun to have it on and i've done it before
it's just my personal preference hey thank you jen thorough for the two dollars after you beat
the game don't forget to check out uh instagram check out theo's instagram that's actually real
okay well i'm gonna do that after i beat the game because i don't know if there might be some
spoiler stuff in there that i don't want to see i don't want to see those photos yet but thanks
to the link thank you mr methanie for the five dollars no message thank you honey chain thanks
to the one dollar or a boros thanks for the six dollars and 66 cents 666 or a boros panda appreciate
it clue the sniper thanks for the one dollar fibly biblies thanks for the one dollar i made
some goodies from the last stream oh boy did you you combined that's william defoe's mouth
i know what william defoe's mouth looks like when i see it this second one oh my god this is
terrifying oh that almost looks like it's in the game thank you fibbly biblies for those two great
pictures max pain ariel thanks for the one dollar ariel uh tay thank you tay for the two dollars
hey germa the stream was an absolute joy to watch you named your character john but you had plenty
of jex moments now that you have more experience with climbing mountains maybe you can try getting
over it again i'm not sure i could do that i don't think i have it in ariel thanks for
the two dollars no message thanks again tingy thanks for one dollar thank you mostly lost for
the one dollar mostly lost thanks for the one dollar you're welcome coordinating coordination
ever scaffold thanks for the one dollar hey germa it's me golden foxy i want to let you know that i
told you so if i get banned i won't care i wait hold on a second i'm so confused i'm very confused
wait wait let me read this i got a d in my class also i found out how you can unban my account
just go to the settings channels and videos scroll down and the band chatters is right there it shows
you the username on january 30th the we shop shuts off forever that's the we shop does the we shop
actually turn off why would they do that i can't believe they're i cannot believe they're shutting
the we shop off forever wait wait hold on does that include we you just the week so they're
they're when they're windows sevening the week they're making it they're taking it they're no
more updates no more anything more like xp wasn't windows 7 the support for windows 7 stops in 2020
that's going to be a huge deal you want to talk about like the day of reckoning
when windows 7 is no longer officially supported by microsoft in 2020 what the hell is going to
happen there wait really oh yeah windows 7 is no longer going to be officially supported by patches
next year it's true oh yeah that is hopefully windows 10 will be better by then buy a whole
bunch of games and do a shitty we stream i think i already did that didn't i didn't i i had you know
i did a lot of wee stuff a year or two ago but do i have any advice again for bullies um
i mean the thing the thing about getting picked on and bullies and shit honestly you kind of have to
like there there's a thing no don't bully him back no no no no i'm not sure what your friend
situation is but if you can make a few friends and you can kind of be around them and hang out
with them and it kind of makes it a lot harder for someone to kind of come up to you and be like
oh hey fuck you it's like well i got two buddies here like you fuck you actually
there's like strength in numbers and what a lot of times a bully will kind of pick out and so
single out somebody and it's really really unfortunate shit you have to learn to laugh
it off and invalidate them yeah but it's it's really hard to do that really it sits on hopefully
in the school system wherever you are you know people are looking out for that watching out
for that i feel like in the current year that we're in now the current generation
i feel like people are starting to really pay attention to it now or try to
just ignore them advice doesn't work no i don't know why people are just so fucking mean sometimes
it really i don't get it i wish i had a perfect answer i really do you know what even tries
everyone just tries to look like they care yeah in my experience confronting a bully always kind
of scares them off one way or another not saying physically but bullies bully people because they
think they are weak yeah there's a whole lot of complex things going on when it comes to
bullies trying to make their friends laugh trying to you know impress somebody trying to look
strong tough there's so much going on there it's just laughing it off can help if it's just
trash talking yeah but if it gets to a point where there's actual real you know physical
consequences then somebody somebody has to be told about it you know somebody you can't live
your life just getting fucking picked on and shit that's just not fun it's not cool wish
people just wouldn't be assholes but i guess that's too much to ask yeah there's a whole
like i just said there's a whole lot of complex shit going on as to how it even starts
so i wish i had the perfect answer but i don't i'm not necessarily qualified to have like a
perfect answer but i wish you luck hopefully you can find a way to make you know alleviate it or
you know get the school involved at that point let somebody know that that shit's going on but
thank you best of luck to you thank you door cube for the one dollar by the way if you ever get to
be get to a part of the game you just can't be especially in the b sides there's invincibility
and infinite dash cheats in the options menu they help less than expert players see all the game
has to offer they help less than expert players well i haven't done them yet i did the first b
sides without a problem we'll see hold on to that thought there because i haven't done it yet
but thank you ever scar for the three dollars here since you have a we and the other systems
what else to what a couple consoles do i own i don't have any of the consoles at the moment
because i moved besides what's in the closet right here playstation 1 playstation 2 sega dreamcast
and obviously playstation 4 i don't have the xbox one anymore although i
cannibalize the controller here i should get an original xbox i didn't have an xbox before
i never had an original xbox but what's on the original xbox that's not on a ps3
besides halo this halo what else was an exclusive for the original xbox
jet set radio future gears of war that's true gears of war is on there but i didn't really play
gears of war even when it transitioned to 360 because i had a 360 but thank you thank you
fgw for the one dollar twitch try to get me with the purchase failed shenanigans again
but i didn't fall for it this time my boyfriend and i are going to broadway next month to see
a musical called be more chill not sure if it'd be your cup of tea but if you want to check it out
it's great you're the best as always well thank you be more chill it's the first time i've ever
heard of it mostly lost thanks for the one dollar your analogies never make any sense but we love
them anyways i think that one makes sense ever scarf uh asks you to get a sega dreamcast probably
not because i mean all that's mean meh they're actually that's a hard question to answer
because there really are a ton of games that you can't play anywhere else besides on a dreamcast
depends how much you value uh oddities that you've never seen before what if germa doesn't
actually have a dreamcast and he's delaying it because he doesn't want to tell him how's
that for a delay huh how's that for a delay that's a fake box that i painted no it's not
this is real i got it out of the closet now it's out that means it has to happen soon i'm going
to leave it right here hey dub ski do we're almost done with bits uh just a little bit more let's
rapid fire these what do you say dub ski do thanks for the one dollar glad you streamed today was
only able to catch the last hour because i spent the whole day at the hospital holy shit that's
horrible my best friend had a huge accident at work and i got a lot of second degree burns
and nearly died of heatstroke holy shit it's been a rough day for everybody glad you're
around to help me get my mind off things take care everyone please be careful when operating
walk in ovens sorry uh i think i think you got me yeah is that this fake is it fake it's fake
right it's fake is it i don't know i can't say that it is because what if it isn't i don't know
i know the end uh no all right thank you for the one dollar thank you elizabeth for the one dollar
i watched the vaude of 700 000 games and every time you came back from a brb there was a dick
on the screen it was just like you were a teacher being like haha very funny kids much love musty
face cloth thanks for the one dollar my favorite song enhanced it was very loud i'm really sorry
thank you door cube for the one dollar i want to know what your thought process was when you're
about to sneeze earlier and your first thought was i better turn the webcam on so my audience
and joel's audience can see it because the first 700 000 game stream i don't know what i was doing
didn't i do that before i don't know anyone have a clip on hand i tried we tried to sneeze before
and it never happened what was it no no i ended up i did sneeze like the day after thank you to
evisca for the three dollars here uh they said uh okay now i can recall from movie night there
were two shows that had edited you in which there was a best crossover ever but anyways that show
was ed ed and eddie really hope i know what yeah i know what ed ed and eddie is it's a great show
have i named my sega dreamcast um i'm gonna call it sega wait this is what what is in here
compatible with microsoft windows ce what is windows ce thank you ike turtle for the one dollar
here's what your face reminded me of not to scream no it's c it's not emmy it's ce
it's very clear a ce windows combat evolved and then ever scav gave another five dollars here
talking about star wars republic commando instead of doing dreamcast do the we uh i already did
i did the week a lot i did an entire we stream three of them in a row i think right like a year
ago compact windows and have i checked out the germa lore i i have seen the germa lore wiki
you have 200 star wars shirts so star wars games would be fitting yeah i did uh what games did i
do for the we did that shootout game i did i did a lot of the we shop exclusives didn't i i did
like the eating game the yeah that i there's at least three or four streams of kind of shovelware
we games i did a lot of them but that is going to take us to the end let's take a look at the
credits that's not the credits button that's the camera button yes yes let us click on let us click
on this the credits button look at this fucking gremlin thank you everybody they were a absolute
shitload of community subs tonight so and tons of bits and tons of money you guys are fucking so
you guys are so amazing thank you when is the germa gremlin gonna be
have shito sing over the credits what song star wars doesn't mean you need me everyone
keeps talking about it it's hard to go up and down this little tube look i have to like go
like this it's not just like a simple like
make them wait that's actually better wiggle your finger how about this one sometimes stone cold
steve austin super mario brothers no don't listen to them it's perfect you've got the glass smash
how about one more one more one more how about what give me uh give me something
something dancing queen i broke him no i didn't okay he's fine
you are you you are you are you are you are dancing dancing queen 17 only 17
oh you can dance you can love having the time of your life see you tomorrow