I am Beck. I don't know if Ster is Beck. Can you change this? What should I make this?
Like a cooking class. Cooking class with Ster. Hey, what's your what's your title?
Because I want it to be different than yours. My title is, do you still talk to Jerma?
I get that question a lot so I just put in my title.
How about uh, how about should I just make mine Ster and I are talking?
Yeah, I think that'd be good. That'd be a good co-op title.
That's fair, right? Not bad, pretty good. Okay. And then this is played up, right?
Yeah, all one word apparently. One word. Yeah.
This has been on the whole time. I'm sorry everybody.
I am so ready to make a 2018 YouTube video. Are you? Wait up, let's go!
So invite, how do we, how do we, are you using a controller or a keyboard mouse?
I'd have to find a controller. I just did invite only. We don't know how to even play. Oh, hold on.
How do I like add, hold on, multiplayer. Oh, invite friends.
There's a Twitch integration and options where the customers are chatters, I think.
Uh, options, advanced, Twitch integration. Open Chef application which handles
Twitch integration, Twitch settings can be configured within Chef.
I don't know if you want to deal with that. Uh, this is asking a lot right now.
It is, it is asking a lot more than I thought it was.
Yeah, it's like, I got to like, okay, this is like, I have like a new window.
It's like a whole nother application. Oh, no, no, no. Oh, no, no. I'm sorry.
I haven't, guys, I haven't even played the game.
I don't know what my Twitch password is.
There's a lot of stuff, I don't know.
Well, maybe, maybe at some point later. We have to like figure out how to play,
join each other's games. Can you join off me?
Um. Let me see if I can just invite you.
I mean, are you hosting a game?
I am right now, but it says like, oh, invite only.
And it says invite friends. When I click it, nothing happens.
Are you even online on Steam?
Yeah.
Uh, your name is probably like Pancake Recipe or some shit.
It's, it's.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
It's German.
What?
It is.
But wasn't your name like Ice Cream Sandwich in the last game?
I mean, it was, maybe.
Wait, were you, were you paying someone to play that game with me?
And you were just reacting on camera?
It's just, it's the new meta.
All right, can you join the game or not?
I, I don't think I can. I don't see a like join.
How do we do this?
Because I can't, when I click invite, maybe I should do this.
Okay. Wait, no, I'm in the tutorial.
Oh goodness. Do the tutorial.
Okay.
That's a problem. God, what have I done?
Oh my God, I just exited this tutorial.
Shit. Um, okay, hold on.
Why can I not invite you?
Is my, okay, you make the game because my Steam overlay like is disabled.
Do I have to do the tutorial?
Because it has like a.
Try, try making an invite only.
Go to multiplayer, go to invite only and invite friends.
Because I don't, I think I do my, my Steam is off.
What?
Like my Steam integration is like fucked up.
I can't, when I click invite friends and nothing happens.
Okay. This is also going to need a controller because the interact key is P.
I am using a controller.
Oh, hold on. I'm going to find a controller real quick.
Oh, no.
We could have just, I was enjoying Ember.
I'm sorry that you played it for like four hours with me and didn't enjoy it for a moment.
I did.
We invite only was broken for me.
Try something else.
Really? For real?
Okay. Can you join off me now?
I can look, I was looking for a controller.
So this is broken. Somebody said in chat.
Oh, you can just leave the tutorial.
Yeah. That's what I did.
But that means we're not going to know how to play the game.
Yeah, we will.
Okay. I have it set to private.
So I wonder if you can just join me.
I'm trying.
There's a built-in invite.
Yeah. I'm trying to do it.
I did what you did.
I couldn't get out of that.
I did quit game.
Calm down.
There was nothing else to do.
Okay. Just relax.
I'm relaxed.
Maybe do that.
Go into your menu, but go and just like see if you can join off of me from your Steam.
It's okay.
Multiplayer.
And just see if you can just join my game.
No, there's only like, hold on.
Well, you broke it.
I broke it.
I can't even right click your name on Steam right now.
Something's wrong.
What's today?
Maintenance?
It's Monday.
My whole Steam friends list.
I can't click any of it.
Restart your computer.
I'm not doing that.
You need to invite through the plate up options.
The Steam overlay does not work.
Yeah, I'm in the plate up options.
Multiplayer and invite friends doesn't work.
I can't click it.
When I click it, it just goes, yeah, I'll show you.
I'll show you my black screen.
I don't know, just in case it's like a lobby code or something.
I don't know.
Yeah, I sent an invite to you.
You did.
I believe I did.
Did you?
You did.
Okay, play game.
All right.
Do you have it on private?
I think so.
Okay.
Am I in your game?
Joining.
Yeah, you've joined.
All right.
Now, everybody.
Hold on.
I have to capture the video feed.
Okay, so should we do the tutorial?
Yeah, the buttons for this game.
I couldn't find a controller and the buttons seem insane.
Oh, do you want to play the tutorial?
Yes.
Let's grab while looking at the fish to take the fish.
Place the fish.
Stop touching things.
Well, place the fish on the hob to start cooking.
Oh, combine the fish with the plate.
Once a customer has arrived and chosen their meal,
interact to take their order.
Okay, so there's no customer.
You can now see their order above their head.
Place it on their table.
They want a blank plate.
Oh, why wasn't it looking?
Yeah, I looked at it that way too.
I just want a plate.
Yeah, like I'm not hungry.
Customers won't sit at the table with something on it.
Once they leave, grab the dirty plate.
Put it in the sink.
I had a question before we continue any further.
So when you're streaming and you go to the bathroom,
are you not trying to finish the bathroom as quickly as possible
or like are you in your sanctuary
and you're like on your phone watching a stream
while your stream is live waiting for you to come back?
Well, here's the thing.
I have never taken a shit in the middle of a stream ever.
Not one time the entire time I've ever been on Twitch.
So you would just end the stream before you would do that?
Yes, I would either go to the bathroom before or after.
I would never do it during a stream
because it would take way too long.
And plus, I don't know.
Look, when you're sitting there and you're taking a shit,
isn't it in your mind you're just thinking
about all the people that are leaving your stream?
It's like, dude, it's been like 10 minutes.
Where is this guy?
I'm out of here.
And I'm just sitting there.
I'd be kind of panicking.
Yeah, but it's got to happen sometimes.
It's never happened.
People always ask why I'm late
or why streams start so late or, oh, dude, you said two,
but then you said three because I need to make sure
that all liquids and solids are out of my body completely
before I turn the stream on.
Empty, zero, empty, empty, empty.
That's a rough life.
Wow, why?
Because I don't want to have to do that
in the middle of the stream?
Like everybody else in their jobs,
they get to go to the bathroom.
It's not like you're allowed to go to the bathroom.
But I know how my bathroom habits are.
And even if I hurry, it will be 15 to 20 minutes.
How do I cut?
Oh, fries.
Do you chug coffee like beforehand?
Yes, I drink coffee all the time.
Get him his fries.
He wants fish and fries.
I got a heart.
Place a plate in a sink.
Oh, I can't.
Why not?
Oh, we have to wash the dish and then get it out.
These sound effects are kind of loud and annoying for me.
Are they for you?
A little bit.
You can, there's always like a,
you know, you can lower the volume or.
Yeah, let me do that.
Groups expect all their meals to arrive together.
When they're ready, take their order.
You got it.
Oh, you got it.
Oh, I wonder what they're going to want.
A fish or a French fry?
Oh, you baste.
Oh, wait, you didn't want fries.
Why, these are on the house.
Survive as many days as possible.
Okay, that's pretty, that's pretty hardcore.
If a patient's bar runs up.
Okay, we know what to do.
Why are you minus twoing me?
We can't get one bad review on Yelp.
And you should be striving for that as a business.
What would you guys rate my stream?
Oh, let's get a poll up between one and five.
You made a bad joke.
I didn't make a joke.
I just said a word.
I said one word.
All right, take this order.
And that's somebody's to sit there with a cooked fish.
It's like, so what are you going to order tonight?
Like, I don't know.
I was thinking about the soup.
Oh, the soup, huh?
What about this thing?
You think this looks good?
Okay, so we need to take a portion of mashed potatoes.
Oh, we can buy stuff too.
How many days do we make it?
I think we make it to day two.
Five.
Okay, cool.
What's the name of a restaurant?
Oil and Char.
Oil and that sounds disgusting.
How do we start?
Complete the plan to begin.
Okay, so we need to go to the city.
Oh.
Put the floor plan there.
Okay.
And then the menu is steak.
We have steak.
Okay, add oil and char.
Oil and char.
I think you have to get over here.
Yeah, I don't know if we're getting day two.
I think we get to day three.
Cook steak once for rare, twice for medium, and three times for well done.
What is happening?
Why are we losing progress?
All right, here we go.
Okay, we need rolls, rolls.
Behind the counter, start cooking a steak.
I'll take the orders.
You take the orders.
I will take the orders.
You start the food.
Don't move the fridge.
I just start day.
We press K.
Okay, are we ready?
It's why?
I thought you had a controller.
No, I don't.
That's tough times, dude.
Okay.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
But the name of the restaurant is High Steaks.
The first level.
It's going to be like three people are going to come in.
All right, so why am I taking orders?
They're going to want a steak.
That's it.
Okay, what would you like?
I would like a steak.
Oh, I wonder.
Okay.
What do you want to done this?
Okay, that's what they want.
They want it like that.
Take it off.
Get it.
Go, go, go, go.
You are.
Hey, you can't stand the heat
and you better stay out of the kitchen.
Clean that up.
I told you this is going to be so easy.
Clean that up, you little baby busboy.
Yeah, you got to earn a position.
How much water did you just knock on the floor?
I didn't.
All right, what do you want?
Let me guess.
Oh, they want a...
I think that's well done.
You already have one halfway there.
Wait, what is this?
Oh, that's just a bonus one.
Here, I got them.
How do you clean?
Oh, okay.
You have to hold X to clean.
I don't see you doing anything.
I was...
You're going to take his order?
We don't even need to.
We know what it is.
Is it going to be steak?
It's a medium and a well done steak.
This one needs to go back around.
You can't because it's already on the plate.
What?
Wait, wait, wait.
Take it off.
Go.
Here you are.
Ah, bon appetit.
Steak.
All right, Scott wants the steak.
Take that one off.
This one's burnt.
I'm cleaning.
The plates go back in the rack.
You're an idiot sandwich.
Oh, no.
What have you done?
What are you doing?
Well, we did it.
We won.
What do you mean, what am I doing?
Stop it.
Stop.
Oh, disgusting.
What are you doing?
No, stop.
It's fucking raw, mate.
It's bloody fucking raw.
Have you ever seen Gordon Ramsay's TikTok food reviews?
Uh, no.
Wait, what are these?
What's happening?
We rerolled.
Upgrade a blueprint?
What the?
We don't have enough money.
We only got 28 money, so it doesn't even matter.
They just give you one?
Wait, what are these little, these bouncing?
I think these are upgrades.
Okay, I understand.
Then you like interact, hold up.
That one's like hidden.
Oh, we can rearrange our kitchen even.
What is it?
Oh, okay, I see.
So what do we do?
Do we just pick them up and they just get stored somewhere?
Why don't we just put this in?
Why don't we just put all this shit out here?
You can't do that.
Why not?
I don't understand why not.
We're doing hibachi grill?
What's the?
Hibachi steak.
Yeah, sure.
Okay, let's rearrange.
I don't understand why we would not want to be
like two or three steps closer to the seats.
Uh, sure, you know, you bring up a really valid point.
You want to make this, um, sufficient, then that's what we can do.
And the storage will just be in here.
Research, yes.
I feel like we had, we had good flow on.
What is this heat sign that is next to these tables?
I think it's just decreased patience.
I think today they don't have a lot of patience.
That's like prepare for this because people have really
want their food quick today.
And you just took a seat away from that.
Okay, you ready?
I wait, hold on, hold on.
We can buy one of these.
What's the work boots?
We can buy an extra sink.
Okay, we don't want none of this.
Unless you want an extra dining table for more people.
We can buy that.
Well, we're in level two.
It's not gonna happen.
Okay.
Yeah, okay, let's start.
Start day.
Yep.
I remember if we lose one day, we die.
They actually pull us out back and execute us.
Just get some food going.
Okay, we got one, that one and then one well.
Why did you take that one off?
Because that wait for that one to be well and then we're good.
Okay.
On the plate.
Let it up.
There it is.
10 bucks.
Okay, clean this ship all the way in the other room.
That's fine.
All right, I will take care of this.
You, you, I will do this.
Just go and leave.
This is like nothing's happening yet and it's already stressful.
Behind.
Get that, get that off, get that off.
Wait, two more on the grill.
Two more on the grill.
I'm cleaning.
Okay, wait, no, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's like farm these guys.
What do you mean?
They don't need like we have plenty of time before we can take their order.
We don't know what they want for steaks.
Take them off.
We don't know what they want.
We don't know what they want for steaks.
This is two mediums.
You fucking donkey.
Get it off.
Let's go.
Oh my god.
You fucking.
You put it on.
Just dance in front of them.
Dance quick.
Just distract them.
Oops.
Oh my god.
I can't believe you got that.
What?
Yeah, we fucked up, dude.
Actually, it looked like I don't know.
It was milliseconds.
Okay, so we're good.
Wait, we didn't?
No, it's restarting that day.
All right.
Well, that just didn't work.
I was hoping it would kick us back to the beginning.
I did not like the kitchen set up at all, by the way.
Someone was outside, you donkey.
What do we do about that?
Like, who cares?
So do we have a seed?
I believe so.
There's a seed.
That's interesting.
Get me to clear the table.
Oh, we needed to clear the table.
Okay.
This is a rogue light.
What?
Okay, that's kind of cool.
All right, let's go.
That's why I was interested in this game because it's like,
it's not like the other games like Overcooked are all like individual puzzles.
This one was like, they murder you.
But didn't we just lose?
How come we were able to do it again?
I don't know.
Okay, well, let's go.
It's just stakes.
Just don't screw it up.
We just have to not be idiots.
Oh, it's after three days.
Okay, the first three days.
Oh, the first three days are free.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right, let's go.
So you're ready?
Okay.
All right, we need to have actual roles.
I will be the cleaner and I'll get the plates.
I'll do the cleaning.
I'll clean up the ground.
You handle the meat because same thing will happen like last time.
I'll put one on when you scream it at me.
Okay, take the rotor.
Okay, with that, we need one well, one medium.
Exactly.
Perfect.
Get out of the doorway.
Let me deliver it.
All right.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
You're right.
See, now you can do this.
This is how you do it too.
Yes.
Isn't that like not fair?
We only have one sink.
Okay, we need two mediums.
Very good.
Two mediums.
Got plenty of time.
Okay, incoming.
We need one medium.
One, I don't know what that is.
One medium, one well.
Okay, I'll wash this.
I'll wash.
It's going to be a second.
Can you entertain them?
Enter.
I'll wash.
Okay, one well, one medium.
Put it down.
Now we need one well, one medium again.
I will do the dishes here.
You just pick it.
You clean.
I mean, you cook.
What?
I'm doing everything.
You cook, you clean.
You do everything.
Hey, just do everything.
And I'm going to like just stand around.
What kind of mom's dust?
Why are you standing still?
What's a well done?
When you were just standing still.
The day's over, dude.
It's like four minutes before closing
and you're like, you could be cleaning.
You know that we have the auto clean
end of the day imaginary auto clean restaurant.
I actually didn't know that.
Can you fill up our loading bar faster?
Okay, we got a lot of money now.
So what we got?
How much do we have?
We got eight extra plates.
We don't have a lot of plates.
I like that.
That sounds great.
That feels like too many plates.
I need that many plates.
No, that's going to be too many.
They're going to be on the ground and scattered.
Watch what happens.
Can't place it in this corner.
How can we sound like you have a joint hit in your lungs?
I can't place it anywhere.
It's because I'm 40.
Oh, I'm pressing the wrong button.
That's our plate room.
A plate room?
You don't have a plate room?
Actually, that's not a bad place for it.
That's a huge stack.
I told you this is too much
because now we have 12 plates.
A research grant?
What is a research grant?
Let's take this and figure out what it is.
Upgrade a blueprint.
What does it do?
That's our potions, if you need any potions over here.
What does it actually do?
I don't know.
I think it's a research so we get better stuff later.
So presumably we can cook more than just freaking steaks
and we make more money.
We got no more money.
Hold to carry two items at once.
My ears just rang when I did that.
I'm not doing that again.
My like ears are ringing.
You ready?
I'm ready.
We've got more plates than we have chairs.
What idiot bought all these plates?
Okay, they're going to want steaks.
We got a medium and a raw.
Medium and raw.
That's not correct.
What are you doing?
You actually just ruined it.
It's still day three.
That's good.
With the tutorial.
You don't have to put them on the table till they're all ready though.
Maybe that was actually your fault.
You didn't cook it right.
Wait, we didn't buy everything again.
You want me to do the cooking and you can do the kind of placement stuff?
Okay, do you think you can handle it?
What was the...
It's the easiest job in the restaurant.
Do you think you deserve to be the chef?
Yeah, let's see.
Go, go, go.
You didn't buy your plates yet.
You were so into that.
You don't need the plate.
You're the chef.
I'll be fine.
All right, let's go.
Let's show you how it's done.
I want you to call out L, M, H.
L is raw, M is medium, H is high.
I honestly don't understand what the shades are.
Low, medium, high.
M, H.
See?
So you guys are celebrating anything?
Is any of your birthdays today?
Anyone celebrating anything today?
You're going to come get the food?
Can you fucking let me do my job?
Call it out, please.
L, M.
See?
Look at that.
Let me do my job.
Oh my god, we can't open that door if someone sits there.
Hey, hey, hey, I need some orders.
Uh, L.
Is there already one there for you?
Oh no, I didn't mean to...
Sorry.
The plates are piling up, friend.
What do they want?
Any orders?
I haven't ordered...
I don't have to ask them yet.
You put them on to...
I can't drop this plate.
I cannot drop this plate.
We need more counter space.
Does anybody want this?
I can't put this down anywhere.
I cannot put this down anywhere.
Okay, just...
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
He wants the lightweight.
You had an opportunity...
You are starting...
You have the calmest job, dude.
Just clean...
We need another counter.
I distinctly remember...
scenario you don't pick up the food don't start the meals until I take the
order yeah and you were I don't know what you were doing you were like
walking around in this room we have circling in circles I was trying to put
plates down did you see run back to stream run the stream back you were
going like this you did this like 15 seconds down I was panicking I was trying
to think of what to do do you want more plates after that shit we want a
counter I want another counter I don't think we have another counter we would
have to reroll there's a reroll blueprints out here it's all right we'll
be all right let's go for it you just spent ten bucks doing that yeah we
fucking needed it don't wait F they F you see K come on come on what's the
specials menu the fuck is a portioner hey we can get double space let's get
these breadsticks yeah that sounds pretty good all right I'm gonna yeah
right there yeah yeah wait wait wait wait wait wait how do you pick them on
up there's two buttons on the game try one I want to put the breadsticks out
here cuz they fit they fit snugly in that corner what I take your own bread
sticks no I am the breadstick man okay it's my responsibility if you want me
out of the kitchen and the breadsticks are on me because already made okay
ready are you ready I'm ready let's go are you feeling comfortable yeah here
wait wait wait wait let me move uh because that was blocking the door up
here we got to at least get a day five okay this is easy just make sure you make
sure you're not cooking things before people even fucking show up and I
haven't taken their order yet yeah oh LM oh interesting very interesting and what
were you yelling at me when I was the chef I was pre I was pre firing I'm
saying shouldn't shouldn't I be the one to take the plates out if you're the one
cooking and we need to clean those plates and you didn't even give bread
sticks to our customers all right there we're good six I breadstick them we are
good to go we're saying I've ever seen a lead LH LH LH LH yep L I'll put it down
when you have the H one more one more step one more step on that what what
what happened oh no oh my god I'm so sorry it's a good thing that I respect
it that you're an idiot and I didn't put the L down before you made it go
that person up there's nothing they said no they want to come in in here but we
have no tables okay oh my god I can't fix on the table why did they not eat
them they just staring at them has to go on the other side okay what does that
person want a big fat L how do we lose I think cuz the guy couldn't come into the
store I don't understand what the breadsticks did they didn't eat them they
didn't touch them and I still had to take them off I don't know that's my
fault I timed it wrong I pulled it too early you are so bad L yeah this will
make this easier you know what is messing me up here I'm doing some
movement I don't like it didn't I don't like the corner here I want it in a row
like this here look how clean this is now we've never had a table of four this
is so much better for my brain rather than this little corner bullshit get it
out of here this is so much better for me I hate this door because if I'm
coming in to pick up plates it like fights me why can't we just delete it
all right you ready let's just we this we don't even need to do any upgrades
just bank the money yeah ready yep well I got an extra table so people won't get
stuck outside anymore well nice day chef looks like you're ready to cook a steak
waiting for you to take the order I'm taking your criticism I can't two else
chef yes chef I got the door for you three two one here you go perfect
perfect well execute it here let's clean up these plates before we take the next
order yes chef all right now you know you get out of here I'm getting the
order two M's okay two M's incoming here two M's done let's go taking this order
one L got it I will give this to this customer you just get the plates
handling plates yes chef good handling plates it's good plates are ready I'm
gonna go take this order mm-hmm yes chef one L1 M cleaning up the floor for you
did Alan M LM oh how's it going guys you guys been in town long what's up oh wow
okay here we go happy birthday happy birthday it's your birthday it's your
birthday what do you guys want one L1 M need a plate I got one order easy all
right delicious cook serve delicious don't I think that's it right should be
why are you cleaning because like I like to keep my hands busy if I stop for a
second then I think like my engine just stops and it's kind of like a shark
that's not swimming I fucking die you know yeah you're making a joke but that
actually feel that a lot of time yeah I'm a shark that's right I'm the alpha
what do we look at a steak sauce mushrooms adds mushroom sauce as a
topping what does that minus 15% people I don't know what does that mean guys
that means less customers per day let's do that that sounds great yeah but if we
need to make a mushroom sauce you think we're ready yeah I'm ready I mean you're
the chef are you ready for that chef yeah all right let's get it chef press
X whatever the button is on your computer if you have to select one of
these and hit like X it's not showing me a button to press okay we got a lot of
money a lot of money rolling in very successful business add onion and water
oh my god oil and make and then put chopped mushrooms over it okay that's
like that's like two ingredients water onion and then oh my god we have no
space I think before the day starts we can enter practice mode so you can make
one first we because now now we're in like yeah we're in like the lose the
game territory yes now we got pots we have mushrooms this onions this is where
do we want these I'm gonna put the pots down by the plates I feel like that
makes sense we can move we can run faster all right let's do practice as
the I don't I'm not confident wait was there a run faster one it's 60 bucks but
you we can move faster a hundred percent doing that oh wow you do run faster all
right let's we need to try this okay okay so we need a pot by the cats coming
in it doesn't like cats okay so boil the pot of water put it in onion well they
don't want it but just yeah just figure out how to make it but there's onions
that goes in the pot this water is not boiling how do we put the onions in how
we put like the ingredients in don't chop them but you don't chop no chop oh
okay so one onion onion and water makes the broth and then we take the mushroom
does the mushroom need to be cut up I don't think you can't even chop the
mushrooms but you already can that one's already cut okay so that this is done
and then you said this one's cut already so do we add this so we now that a
chopped mushroom goes in and then that makes that and now we have this and we
can put it on a plate okay so if somebody wants a steak with that
mushroom sauce we just have to go up to it and press like the action button here
try that there's no steak I think you got to put that on top of the steak okay
so then go and get the sauce on it okay okay here's what we do then here's the
play right as soon as the day starts or even if it lets you do it before it we
prep the soup we prep we should just leave that on the side we should prep
two of them have just a bunch of it I don't think we have enough counters to
prep to otherwise like we're gonna be we're gonna be able to put plates
anywhere I agree okay yeah so let's make let's make a broth in the morning and
then after the broth is made then we open the store okay yeah that sounds
good I agree with that do you need help making the broth I think I I think I got
it okay ready hold on well let me let me start making it like I'm not sure of
starting the day oh we have to start the day first yeah so you got everything in
your brain ready what you need to do yes chef yep mushroom how long until they
get annoyed was the mushroom supposed to be chopped yeah then this goes in we
need to the burner okay that's going in and then this is gonna be done oh I see
okay I'm gonna take the order make the order what they want an L and an H with
sauce okay L and then H with sauce all right I take the take the L when it's
here you take the fucking L okay don't get don't do not what because then it's
the timer before you can place the fucking we're good oh we're good we're
fine I just that was a delicious scrumptious meal and they just enjoyed
it taking the order H with sauce do these fuckers they want all this sauce
on an eight it takes so long to fucking cook and they just want it now don't
take the other order and with sauce okay okay M with sauce yep okay taking the
order good L with sauce and then L L with sauce L well done two M's medium
right I think that's I think that's well done I know that's well down to H to
a cheese can you grab that um grab that a G is a sauce good for more than one
day I think that was pretty clean it was good and we said what the fuck why
aren't they fighting anymore uh cuz we found that it's better to cooperate we
found you know our flow what works for us if my server did that I wouldn't
return let's spin around it be like whoa I think that I think that I added
something to the atmosphere worth coming back for but you don't think it'd be
funny if like the server walked out with a big plate of food nice and hot and did
a I'm gonna pass it underneath the leg kind of like a basketball and grab it
with the other hand and pick it up you don't think that'd be funny chef look at
this look at this one down here this one you might want to consider here chef we
can afford the gas override so what does this do cooks faster burns faster I
feel like that's terrifying is that a little too scary do we even have a
garbage by the way I that's the kind of thing you do if there's four people in
here I don't know this is a two-person upgrade what is this filing cabinet oh
do you want another dining table I'm stuffed in the corner I don't think we
need we're actually maybe to make it so people won't sit outside okay and then
we'll start and remember this is like a do or die all right well let me get my
right okay so let me get my sauce ready I'm gonna belch like a weirdo okay wait
it actually might be nice to have another counter yeah get it get it I
didn't see that there was a counter yeah we are starved for counter space oh
okay oh man oh geez it's really coming together is that a good place for it I
think we need to can we expand the restaurant no I think the layout we
chose at the beginning when we chose the city layout all right oh that's right
that's right okay I'm ready okay you ready you understand the soup needs to
be made immediately I'm going chef I'm going for it immediately okay starting
day welcome welcome off the street Wow you're naked and handles junk sauce okay
you already took the order ooh why'd you do that chef we're gonna need an L with
sauce why'd you take the order the soups not even ready I think he's I think
we're making time it's only one guy it's not like a full table oh we need the
breadsticks wait I need first okay soup is good this is going over here L with
sauce L with sauce you got it come in right up just an L plane an L coming
right up hey sir your food is gonna be a little bit late just kidding what would
you like today sir and with sauce is an L or an H looking like an H here sir
sir sir that's an M sir please sir please oh big lunch rush hey good evening hey
there you want an L with sauce and an L with sauce wow you guys really are quite
the same there you know if we don't cook it enough you can get sick these both
have sauce yes you sauce I got it it's awesome one H and one an L with sauce
gonna want to put that H on you know what I'm saying it's an H an L with sauce
L with sauce that's gonna turn into an H in a minute here hey can you get that
one thank you yes chef those of you that thought we weren't gonna make it to day
five look at this formal or exclusive high standards high standards focus on
making customers happy people will wait a long time for a destination increased
queue patients extra money why wouldn't we do exclusive formal seems harder yeah
like what one of the left seems hard well oh the one on the left is it
creates no mess oh what is the zero out of three decreased mess yeah what's that
mean well I'm cleaning all the shit up you're like a total fucking slobs you
haven't noticed how much shit is on the floor let's say it's upgrade levels you
need decorations to increase that number okay um look like a snow cone today good
I'll just be your call sounds like you want the one on the right um the one on
the right seems easier I feel like people will wait longer all right use
your shoes wait we don't have our shoes on wait do you have to like go in here
and turn like shoe up oh they're on the right front opens there's a lot of stuff
on the ground oh yeah now they're starting to give us decorations statue
painting some decorations I mean this stuff is kind of just in the way plants
Christmas tree there's a Christmas tree what is this what are these fucking
litter boxes this is like a wrapping paper on the ground what is this for
it's throwing so much stuff at us fairy lights of rug oh banner litter boxes are
floor tiles did you see the floor changing right now or is that yeah I do
what do you want in here chef you want floor I don't want to die I need to
differentiate the contrast so I think that one whoo did you pay for that yeah I
did I did pay for that with my own money I feel like this is a joint business and
I can make a couple of decisions without you jumping down my throat swipe the
company card 30 times look look how much fancier this place looks now I didn't
buy it for me are you ready for another day you know how to make this fucking
soup I know how to make the soup you talk all right that's my I'm the soup
guy all right five-star chef in here can make two items Wow Wow you're so big and
important why don't you do it do you really you really want to take that
chance not on day day six all right let's go chef we've got six customers
out here working on it onion yeah so our chef he doesn't really
he doesn't make two things so I don't know what you're gonna order and they
all come here cuz they want to eat the same thing some restaurants have like
two things on the menu hopefully everybody goes there for that one thing
you've been to a steak and cheese place he wants a steak he wants an H with
sauce if you want to get these shoes on I guess there's only one pair it's
coming what is all over the ground I'm cleaning it H with sauce I'll take the
order for the small guy H with sauce do it again I have to clean this this is a
that's gonna slow me down H with sauce coming up but I gotta clean this this is
what is why is it such a mess on the ground you have you know shoes on
you're the one that didn't think the mess was a big deal I didn't say looking
for that H with sauce it's here looking for that L with sauce in an L get these
guys out of here fucking quick ready to open up these tables bro L with sauce
yep this is do or die motherfuckers pick that up pick that up pick that up pick
that up I got it here you go sir have a pleasant evening let's spend some time
cleaning before I take his order you can put you can put a shrimp on the fucking
Barbie or something I thought you told me not to do that because you don't we
don't know what it is and then sure oh yeah true you would have overcooked that
you would have cooked the shit out of that guy just wants a simple little
fucking L one L and with sauce and with sauce okay I'm behind chef okay you need
to put sauce on one of those do I like what do you need me to for chef I'm
cleaning I'm doing my I'm doing my I need you to grab that one because it's
about to be ready here we go 1m 1m I think that's it it's a rainy day yeah
behind the scenes of the Cracker Barrel do you ever have Cracker Barrel of mac
and cheese I don't crack a barrel I don't even know the Cracker Barrel mac
and cheese is the best off of the shelf just grocery store mac and cheese you
possibly order like nothing else compares you know what I'll have one on
you okay by on you I mean I'll like I don't know if I see what I'll get one
yeah Cracker Barrel if you go to the mac and cheese aisle if you have Cracker
Barrel mac and cheese get it please okay he's out of things to talk about are you
out of you uh what was it what's the Kraft mac and cheese you're not you're
not in that's Cracker Barrel goodness all day no no no no no no no no no I mean
Kraft isn't Cracker Barrel is unmatched it's s-plus all right what do you want
to do left left we don't we can only handle two ingredients let's be real I
mean we already have the potatoes stocked actually we have right no we
don't we have onions onions and mushrooms are mine let's go left okay I
got the speed boots like it's not a problem
NP mate NP yeah Kraft is Kraft you know exactly what it is yeah I mean Kraft is
is very very solid and it's also you know it's consistent I've been holding
that burp in for like an hour and a half I'm sorry I didn't even hear Kraft is
consistent you know exactly what it's gonna be every time even though it's
like a that's like a good seat plus there's an extra grill up here for 20 do
you want to fit that down in the corner probably because yeah it's cheap and we
were cooking a lot of steaks we are getting more customers change the sign
can you change and you and you yeah see whoa oh you can go for it what what it
was uh boiled and charred it was like boiled and onions and yeah okay what
did I say boiled and onions that's just the thing I'm making every day boiled
and anything else chef ready to start I don't know you got me making the same
food every single day I that's all I know boiled and onions okay let's go
just steaks hey you're the executive manager of this restaurant you need to
give the chef something else to do since when are you doing that I thought I
would help I'm sorry you mess with my flow I'm out I'm out I'll entertain the
guests I got oh my god I put the shoes on I'm zooming around look at this wait I
need those shoes cuz I'm flooring your people and you took the fucking shoes
I'm breaking these things in okay I'm taking the order then two M's why would
you do that cuz now we're gonna say you don't need the sauce you don't need the
sauce you don't need the sauce oh my god I we are so slow coming out of this door
out here this is I hate this and you took the fucking shoes you said M you
said two M's what the heck happened here it'll be fine just cook it faster okay we
need to clean here dude you need to clean oh my god I gotta go take the
order you get that order on the bottom left get that order on the bottom left
an L and an H I'm gonna clean you just you just you gotta okay we gotta go we
gotta put more steaks on L and an H L and an H L and an H stop screaming everything's gonna be
fine that's not an H put it back on put it back on put it back on put it back on oh my
god he's collapsing he's collapsing you're the cook you're the cook you're
the cook I got it oh we're dead we're dead get that L get that L we got it
just throw it in the trash dude just put it just no no no no no I already have
the H oh if it L God oh okay what do they want easy very easy okay there's a
oh my god dude you took the fucking shoes dude I'm throwing I'm out there
with the customers with the slow speed and he takes the fucking shoes and like
look how fast I can run look out well I have to say it I heard two it two M's I
and it was two H's fuck that up but my mind like my fucking wife just left me
dude we go again I think we're supposed to lose we did pretty good you're
supposed to lose oh it's like vampire survivors you're like just supposed you're
not supposed to win so we actually did great I mean if you're comparing it to
one of the games of the year last year then I would I mean that makes sense to
me all right we got a new menu item let's do salads a new layout mix it up a
little bit wait I think we can change clothes I did uh you know I like that I
like the the speed the high-paced environment all right I like hot dog
we're gonna do like a maid cafe if I'm gonna be the one out there oh I can do a
pumpkin meow look what do you what do you want to eat here meow you ready I
want I want orange are you sure you can make sounds well figure it out let us
optionally add up tomatoes this means can be good okay yeah I'm feeling all
right oh I like this layout you you I really can just be up out here you know
what I'm saying let's practice salad okay okay so let it name of the
restaurant is let us eat I just I just chopped that into tomato soup so what is
it it's chopped lettuce lettuce lettuce on a plate and that's it
optionally add yeah what lettuce one tomato okay so you can do a tomato
twice so that's it oh this is gonna be easy all right cool I like this layout a
lot this is way better than the other layout you don't got to cook anything
do you want vegan and I was chef last time and I did a phenomenal job you want
me to be the chef want to be chef this time I mean I think our roles were
working why don't you try it it's fun but okay I mean if you okay well then
maybe I should have been the one learning how to make it I mean dude it's
literally just chop a tomato and chop lettuce put it on a plate it's not that
hard I mean it's hard when you keep covering up every fucking surface now if
you do that if you chop the tomato twice it makes tomato soup be aware of that
oh and I gotta cut I gotta chop that it's just it's just chopped okay I'm
ready that is it okay let's really okay we don't have any money so we can't do
any wait booking desk interact to accelerate time to next customer it's
like a hard mode how confident are you you want to do that um yeah let's do
that like you handle you handle the exterior I'll be in the interior I'm
gonna be ready we're gonna be feeding each other through here sounds good all
right I'm ready thank us fucking order I'm just why I thought you want a little
bit of time perfect you gotta memorize that layout I saw you move around a
little oh you're really gonna backseat that backseat me just look over the
counter because you have nothing to do and just tell oh you're a little bit
slow there buddy take their fucking order all right this person just was a
lettuce lettuce and all right we got to think of some how to describe this some
people are gonna just want lettuce okay just say lettuce an actual real salad
that's too long to say that like this person wants lettuce I think okay well
today come up with what you want all right it just by default fucking order
hold on I did it's going to nighttime we won't get the money if we don't serve
them okay so when I say to mate that means the whole thing to me if I say two
orders and I say one to mate that means the tomato goes on one you understand
to mate the whole thing or what was the other one okay so we got two teammates
that means the whole works everything tomato and lettuce just say salad no
salad okay I was focused on the task you say to mate if it's the whole with
tomatoes right and what do you say when it's not with tomatoes nothing if I say
there are two orders one to mate is this too much for you I feel like when they
order something and you say nothing if no sounds like I'm going to tell you the
number so three customers come in and sit down right now and they order three
different salads I am gonna say but later later on three customers two
teammates later on when we're handling more than you know one type of food like
if we had steaks in the mix yeah you omitting the type of sat when you can't
just say fucking salad what's your point it's gonna cause it's what I'm saying
well we're not good but we're not okay do you see how many levels in a row we
had steaks it's gonna be like this for the least the next 40 minutes but once
it changes you're gonna change everything okay so how about this if
they're if it's salad I'm gonna say salad with tomato that sucks though no
it's we gotta do it like a diner okay I'm ready you you just say what you're
gonna say and I'll try and react I'm telling you you're gonna get it and
you'll be like and when it's gone you're gonna miss it too one to mate yeah I
want to mate with you two salads one to mate how's that is that better on two
that works for me good plane salad yeah plane plane plane plane this only works
if more than one person is sitting at a table I'm realizing that right now
there's a lot of issues like we there was there's nothing on the menu called
plane based on what we just discussed for like 10 minutes to make salad
apology with tears now just say salad yeah but what if the salad salad with
me yeah we can take that order just cleaning two salads one to mate two
salads two to mate I fuck I made the soup oh you turned it into soup it's
easy to do by accident I'm just so strong don't you dare put that down I
have you noticed I have not you imagine your waiter hovering over your table
with a plate of food ready for you to eat it and just staring like waiting and
then waiting for you to be done yeah very cool I put on these cat ears so
that I could be the like the one interacting with the guests by the way I
just want to point that out and I'm stuck in the kitchen I don't think we
need more seats I need another counter we always need a counter more buffer
increase the movement speed and prevent spills that's all pensive can't counter
here we go right here got a counter for you what do you want it in the corner
this corner up here yeah okay we're good to go that's a good setup actually I'm
curious if you can grab diagonally if you can like grab that plate do you try
yeah oh good yeah this is awesome okay here we go two salad two to mate well I
can also like if we're in a hurry I can put stuff down you could start chopping
it oh I can chop it from here you're right one salad to mate man this is too
easy this is like taking money from babies they're paying for food one to
mate salad themselves clean that plate okay come on come on come on come on one
salad nothing on it I don't know if I could do that here I enjoy your fucking
grass one salad one to mate ah wash the dishes because I have to walk I would
have to walk across the whole thing I got customers out here they complaining
one salad one to mate still waiting for it it's hard to make these there's like
so many steps mates out we need an extra sink we actually put a sink out
here you actually should put that sink out here that makes so much sense that
makes so much sense yeah you mean let me have that sink over oh 25% love oh you
get it wait why would we do that yeah why show me a potato salad but why would
we do the one on the left I don't case you're scared of making potato salad
you're the one making it make the customers do their own dishes chop a
potato add to water in a pot and boil we don't even have a stove oh they
probably gave us the stove wait wait wait wait wait wait a second I need to
like screenshot this no just go into practice I'm telling you it looks that
was intimidating when I looked at it too but it's literally easy you just have to
go and put it I'm putting that description on my other monitor in case
I have a dumb moment I've got a little cheat sheet okay so let's go into
practice real quick oh we need to open all our parcels well we just got an
oven for free yeah cuz we needed to make the salad was that eggs because I have
to crack an egg oh dude and I'm in the kitchen all fucking alone dude oh man
home hey how do you think I felt they need to make the sauce every day how
about this you want me to add the olive oil how about we put the sink down in
that room I can wash the dishes if that's what you want me to do do you
want the sink up in the corner so we can just put them right on the put yep yeah
put the sink right there that's so perfect because then I can put it right
here I can put the clean plates right here this you don't really have a whole
lot of room in there olive oils over there I'm gonna need the sink to add
water to a pot for the salad I get okay I don't I don't know if it's like the
thing you were making we only have to make it once I don't know let's do
practice because if you pass it to me I can fill the pot and just put it back
over here yeah I just want to figure out this layout on this is the olive
Jesus Christ told you we could add this one thing to the menu okay let's do
practice instead of you want another counter we're down here in the lower
right yeah absolutely always counter I think you can even have a counter out
there for an extra dirty plate so I somebody saying you should do the olive
oil I mean I should yeah like you as in me like I should do the finishing on it
maybe well let's just practice it say here let me wait don't do it yet let me
I can hit B it's easy I'm stressed okay let's go ready practice okay this plate
up chop potato add water water this up germa germa drink germa germa my drink
right there they want okay we want whoever that is then you boil that
what's your next step this is crack egg and add olive oil so I think you need to
put olive oil in that egg okay I think I just did okay then yeah then the
potatoes are ready to go combine all three out of plate oh my god I got to
boil the potatoes every fucking Jesus every time rice interesting okay and then
yes let me to make salad if I put the pot there it needs water I thought you're
gonna put I thought you're gonna do tomato I'm just because it's practice I
don't think that's done by the way that doesn't look like the thing the cat
wants is it missing something it looks like a different picture doesn't it
yeah okay let me let me go through this one by one chop a potato oh you're
missing the onion add to water in a pot crack an egg olive oil with the egg chop
onions I didn't skip the onions and then you just you just throw that on the you
plate then I need an empty plate and I gotta like I'm not I I don't know about
this man we got it we're gonna leave practice how about you do make it a
couple times make it like two three times okay let's okay so in this pot
means I need water hot say it to go pot and when you need oil just say like
like grease oil egg oil egg oil egg that's too many syllables grease is one
and then water what I'm missing the onion okay onion comes at the end I think
I'm good I think I'm good are you good just a lot of steps try it one more time
just say oil oil is two syllables no grease oil oil is two syllables this
oil oil grease oil oil I don't want our customers to think we're greasing up
their food no just say grease just say grease grease yes thank you right wait
up you're that extra quarter of a second could be time you're chopping the onion
oil grease oh my god and don't say give me water give me water it's hot oh can we
use like English it was like it's cool we just like those are both English words
that I just said did I not chop what am I doing I just cook a whole potato what
did you even make what is that I'm ready trust me trust me trust me I know you're
not I want you to do it right leave practice mode trust me with your fucking
life right now this is gonna go so smoothly okay good afternoon welcome to
let us see water my name is nevermind I'll talk to you in a minute not just
take the order we're good I just want to like get started on at least one yeah
cuz of course he's gonna fucking want it guy coming to my restaurant in my
restaurant look how long this takes just make it and shut up grace see how quick
that was what that is you do you buy it put the whole potato in there you told
me you already I don't have a trash over here you do wait after this outside
water I can we restart why you mean what we do water twice yeah get out of the
goddamn kitchen I got I'll do it I I see what I did no trust me I got it
I forgot we had another girl that actually would help a lot why does
every single person want only this we're a sad let us eat we're a salad place
and they all came in and they want this crazy fucking dish anybody want to lick
the bottom of the pan it's okay I think we get a redo on this one because it was
day three no it's day four I don't know please please I need this fucking job I
need this job please God you were saying you told me you were you were so
confident we do I'm chef again wait we have you just unlock pizza let's pizza
pizzeria pizzeria I get to make like fun food and not food for like people that
like want like a bowl of fucking dogshit potatoes onions a nice creamed a nice
oil and an egg that sounds delicious what do you mean that you should have
handled it then okay you choose that you choose the kitchen style we're doing
pizzas are you cooking the pizza then you should I am style no you styles on
you why you should be what 50-50 partnership but it should be what you're
comfortable with because you're the one in the kitchen the whole time um well
this a floor plan not just for the kitchen but also for you okay so if we're
doing a pizza oven then we need a big space see that top right corner that's a
big space okay let's go for that let's go for that honey it sounds okay let's
go yeah I'm a bit of a kitsune by the way I identify as a kitsune Fox okay
okay let's go I need okay let me take this picture you don't just don't skip
it and just read it right now I'm gonna trust me dude I'm gonna need it but why
are you taking a screen just read it right now I have it forever now you're
ready to practice get out of my way there's no trash oh let's uh start the
day cuz you can't fail the first day I'm gonna I'm gonna bang out this pizza
first try easy remember you're questioning stir too much we need to
show he just assured me that he was gonna do everything and he didn't even
get one plate out the door oil chopped tomato hey we got two pizzas we want two
pizzas just put it into the oven without any cheese on it do they ask for cheese
you didn't say cheese who a sauce pizza what do you have you ever had a pizza in
you before can you need that doll I asked as well I don't this is why I
didn't I don't know what the ingredients I don't know what's happening you put a
sauce pizza in the oven and you mad at me trust me I got this just like wait to
take the order I know you're like standing still out there you're having a
fucking great time you've already a pizza in the other guy it's seriously
one piece that you didn't even cook it yet I thought I had to make two whole
pizzas here give them you have to chop it that's what I mean yeah I got it we
got to chop the slice it ah and then plate it and then plate it okay sounds
good well they're gonna leave I mean are they maybe not okay get they get the
order someone's gonna get the order get the order get in the order quick you
need to move this plate so I can do anything yeah you got to move the plate
okay I'm supposed to watch the dishes too I need we need plates I need to play
do you have the plates I need I need pizza over here please go help if I walk
in there he's going to he's going to berate me if I spy well there I will if
you even come a foot in this kitchen I see okay it's not as bad as I thought
because they all want slices so it gives us a lot of time to like prepare one and
we can handle a few people yeah no we're good we got it okay I just think that
there may be like one step of this that like you could help with and what do you
want that to be all you said was are you put dough here and you screamed at me and
you said why are you not kneading the dough which I didn't even know that that
that needed um you took the screenshot remember you remember you it was on the
screen and you just pressed a yeah I remember here um let's see what we got
I think just wasn't with another counter that'll be a lot easier I think that's
all I really need and we've got like the three like the Omega counter set up your
plates and sink I could do plates I could do plates and sink yeah you you
give me the option to do something in here and I will leave your kitchen alone
yeah cuz uh yeah you were spending a lot of time watching me and judging me so
yeah you put those where you want we're all just pointing and laughing at you
over here you're gonna wash the dishes wash dishes and then I need a spot
because I think about this right if I wash a dish here I need to walk in here
yeah give me something that you can come and grab really quick I guess you could
you could do it there would you eat a raw pizza for a trillion dollars yes but
I could literally change the entire earth if I had a trillion dollars like
would even just eat a raw pizza and like shit my pants and puke for a day like a
trillion dollars but what is this I could solve every problem probably on
earth I could do so much with that I would do I just do but I just shit my
pants once like a couple days I'll do it right now free yes but it's yucky and
gross oh yeah right yuck all right are you good yeah so I'm gonna wash the
dishes I'm gonna put them on that counter on the left or if there's an
open space you could even just place them on the front counters then I could
put pizzas on them yes like just play it by ear we'll figure it out during the
day sounds good I wonder what this person's gonna order you can take it
it's a cheese pizza and this person wants a cheese pizza you have the
plates I think you can handle up this person wants a cheese you need to cut
it what are you putting what is this weird banana you put on your face that's
cheese what I don't know how to take it off how do you how do you get it off
you just throw it away just throw it away you put like banana pudding over
here it's a oh fuck we're good I think I think this is it feels like a lot but
we're we're serving you know four people we are serving we need her pizza slice
like this is practically already ready to go take that order before the night
ends nice all right that's a pretty good system let them serve yeah we're doing
all right fine yeah that was very calm relaxed there's also an extra sink for
cheap get it and put it in your room if there's an I need this counter we I
absolutely need another counter yeah cheese you're you like five guys right
I do what's your five guys what's your go-to five guys order my in general my
burgers I've grown to like pickles quite a bit okay but if I'm if I'm not going
for like a basic burger with pickles I like to get you know barbecue sauce onion
rings grilled onion rings onion rings okay or like grilled onions or onion
rings either one depends you know how hard you want to go like a like a
Western burger you want to give you an order to try you want me to cook you a
burger right now no I'm saying give you an order to try it five guys sure I
haven't been in a while but sure you know what burger I can get so I can get
some crackle crackle barrel and go down to the five guy and get the burger put
it all together is that what you want so here's what you're gonna do you're gonna
order five guys burger grilled onions jalapenos and a one sauce cheeseburger I
don't like jalapenos not at all they're okay I mean it depends if they're like
when does a jalapeno become like super hot they're all pretty much the same
you might get one with a lot of seeds but it's really not that hot jalapenos
are pretty low on the scale okay I'm a pretty baby boy to be honest I'm I'm kind
of like a little toddler they are fresh-cut jalapenos that's why they're
the best they're not really that hot now you get that kind of run-of-the-mouth
tangle but they're not they're not that bad they're not yeah I remember I would
also get them with a green pepper yeah a little bit of green pepper that's not
bad barbecue sauce on a burger is nice barbecue sauce on a lot of stuff is kind
of overpowering to me you can take that order we need two cheese peaches yeah
the kitchens open for the day looks like you could take that order yeah no
problem yeah we got you guys don't worry about it I'm gonna have the chef I'm
gonna put plates up here for you so you can just put it on there and just cut it
and just cut it up all right we need it we're looking for just pizza pizza
pizza hey looks like it eats up like these guys want some pizza it's a piece
though looking like a little well-oiled machine we serve too many people too
quickly hold on kitty cat in the background will you stop it hey they
come here for the atmosphere yeah you're in the back of the kitchen they're not
pizza anywhere but they come here because they're like they can't hear
you what you're saying it's up it's up oh dear oh we're out of plates put it
down we do need more counter space oh I need help left the oven on who left the
oven on this motherfucker it didn't even order we knew what he wanted and he
didn't even take it yeah slices up you fuckers can walk up here and get at
your fucking selves this isn't fine dining it's a fucking pizza joint some
pizza places are amazing walk up to the counter it's oh my god thank you for
coming to pizza German stirs like a chimpanzee yeah I only eat pizzas if
I don't know I was in the moment too pumpkin pie pizza and pumpkin pie it
sounds like a recipe to have a stomachache um that sounds stupid just
walk slower you can handle walking slower right yeah yeah where pizza place
we don't do pumpkin pie I want to come in for a little bit of pie and some pie
I'm eating possibly already rotten pie from Christmas dude I'm I don't you
probably shouldn't be doing that right now when Christmas is the 25th what day
is it is it was today the 9th I don't know if you should eat that Christmas how
long what kind of pie is that eat that pie yeah I don't think you should eat
that pie this thing cleans floor messes faster rip chat member we got another
table let's get that yeah that's a big deal I'm gonna put this in the corner
yeah we want to keep them away from the kitchen too because you'll walk slower
if you're near him so we want them like on this on this side yeah I think that's
not maybe this corner and then don't put them by that door trust me even we
have never sat more than three people okay you might have trouble getting to
the people in the corner only one person at least two there you go two two two
okay wait what is that sign I thought did you write that that's the name of
the restaurant I just saw that I just saw pussy I'm like wait why did you do
that I'm like why did you write that why did you make the name of the
restaurant because I'm a cat I was like what does this say is that are we gonna
have a problem I thought you came down here wrote like that I thought you just
started writing shit okay like you're um do we want more plates the plate rack
also holds eight instead of those so they're easier to stack and that's the
last decision if you want an extra set of plates I think we need more counters
before we have more plates well then we would have to reroll the blueprints
there buddy why did you read it because that's the name of the sign dumb waiter
what do we got going on here teleports items to other dumb waiters finally he
said it for the auto sentence generator what are you doing what does that mean
what are you ready what does that mean why they say that what does that mean
what were you hello are you good ready I think I'm good
it's up welcome to the restaurant covers $10 cover to get in what's the name what is this place called
atmosphere I thought you just lose your job sink two slices you walk so slow
this is actually horrible I told you that's why you want away from the door
black black black black black black black black black black black black I need
another slice plates are becoming an issue why is that one so hard that is
not a plate that's the that's the un-sauced pizza two pizzas is what we
need pushy cat pie I'm so slow clean I'm not gonna take that order just quite
yet we need thank you I will do it now and I'm gonna clean up this all right
get to work there buddy I think we got enough the rest of the night thanks I
can come out and come out and greet the customers pussy cat who can I get you
take his mic from him yeah other employees a bit of an idiot let me take
your order he said oh you want to beat oh it's crazy smashed yeah we need to
I'm not doing this do we have a clean can I can you give me a plate pass
through twice you can you can combine but it's finicky to touch it from over
there finicky that place is a your fucking side of the restaurant is a
pigsty pie restaurant are you changing the name oh let's see what like cool
restaurant name you've got the pizzeria welcome to the pizzeria
somebody said blame no fine I'll keep it I don't understand what these research
desks are upgrade a blueprint in an adjacent cabinet I said lame lol lol I
don't understand why do you look like that why does he sound like this why does
he look like this why does he smell like this what's wrong with his face he looks
like he doesn't give a fuck today no I do okay I'm ready I will wait I got you
extra plates you can stack so many plates in there I like this is only two
we need a table that could sit more than two people okay I mean set it up the way
you want you know you can handle that side of the you didn't change the name
holy shit now I left it I want to hear you do that joke another hundred times
do you actually cuz I can keep it going no no no no what is he doing was he
okay would you eat at a place called this no I want to be clear let me be
clear don't know why did you why did you press it then you pressed it I pressed
it like ten minutes ago when people sit on the vertical of that you're not gonna
be able to walk past them dude that's the kind of reaction for somebody cutting
the red wire when you said yellow yeah nice job you made a soup yeah I know you
don't like touching that one cuz it's too finicky well I'll do it all can you
please welcome them to the restaurant what do you think he wants can you
welcome them to the restaurant you're gonna lose your job man
stop what stop what annoying why do they hate each other minus two RP well we
supposed to be RPing right now I didn't know that's what we were doing
instant service instant service right there we eventually add toppings like
pepperoni my favorite I'm surprised they haven't thrown that curveball in here
yet I feel like that'd be the easiest thing and instead they wanted us to make
pumpkin pies like can't we just add pumpkin to the top of a pizza no we need
pumpkin pies but that be kind of gross I I've you know you get what you came for
rancid stanky pie shut up stop making so much fucking weird noise I thought I
just almost lost it for us okay affordable or formal a formal pizza
place decrease mess the mess as they amped up the mess on us last time you
remember we were walking in quicksand and you're already slow out there that's
true I agree formal pizza place what's wrong with them today so then we gotta
change we gotta change the name again if we're a formal place now
Oh calm painting double patience yeah what do we what should we rename it I
don't know you like I've come up with a few I feel like you didn't like any of
mine so you can just you can do you know how's that that's great man how is
that lame that's 2012 humor I don't know Merry Christmas
Merry Christmas are you do you actually put that down
ooh that's snazzy Merry Christmas yes we're spending all of our money all
right I'm ready I'm trying to get that fat no mess but we should move that
down okay you ever walk into a pizzeria by yourself sit down and order one slice
and then eat the whole slice in the pizzeria like that's pretty normal
thing to do huh I don't know loser looks like he's alone people are on their
lunch break they just walk in grab slice you're talking about like half of New
York City does that looking like he has no friends right now like I've done that
before oh my god oh my god I made the pizzas man can you move that out of the
way black that was not just burnt that was in the oven for a day you left that
there and fell asleep oh it's over I think it's over oh it's over it's over
it's over you burnt it is over you burnt it you burnt it and it's over and it's
okay yeah you're really adding to the mood look at all these dirty dishes
it's cool you're just standing around wait wait wait it's okay it's okay it's
okay it's okay okay I need another slice you got another slice bring it out here
bring it out here quick we no no no no no no no no no we don't we don't just
pick that up pick that up pick up those dirty plates pick up the dirt one dirty
plate no one is washing the plates dude you burnt an entire pizza are we
supposed to have three people can you imagine going to a pizza place you sit
down there's like a ton of people in this place and the chef you just hear
him screaming ah and he's he's walking by the kitchen you look over and he has
a black pizza in his hands and it's smoking and he's running around oh my
god I have done that a few times where I like forgot I had a piece in the oven
and it's just turned into like it's been like 10 plus years but I definitely
murdered a few pizzas yeah though that was just not just a little overdone or a
little burnt that was that was just charcoal it was just gray oh that was so
funny do you want to pizza again you going fine I I need the redemption arc
wait wait wait what is this we got new items in the garage upgrade kit holding
in your hands what are these somebody said put the
washing station at the counter yeah why I think those are like our unlocks I
don't know that was almost the Voldemort scream all right man let's go let's go
all right you know what you're doing you like this setup you like this setup
this way no you know I don't like it well then we should probably lay out
that you want to be in you I like do you want to wash the dishes this time that I
was but we don't understand is you burnt the pizza and people got angry at you
all right well let's start the day and then you can wash the dishes on our this
is our third venture together there's a door right here by the way there's a
lot of doors okay you ready to go yeah I'm ready to go this one is gonna be our
multi-million dollar franchise well guess what they want pizza yeah original
ingredients Papa John's ingredients one it fast one it fresh up a genos is way
better Papa genos in my genos do you know how to plate that I was sorry I was
thinking about Papa Gino's and I just do you know how to play I'm sorry I'm
thinking about the delicious flavor of Papa Gino's pizza and I got confused
think you can handle the plating dear get out of fucking way person was in the
way I'm hovering I'm hovering don't get out get out of here it seems like you
need all the help you can get there little boy okay people said that I'm
being weird tonight are you sure it's not him I feel like I am I think you're
being kind of weird tonight no earlier with no like you know hated ember and
didn't want to say it and then played it anyway to play it off like you like the
game and we're in that was like the weirdest shit you've ever done no nope
no you are the weird one today and I we have evidence I feel like you shouldn't
have agreed to play it no I enjoyed that experience fun that was like a good time
so I was the problem like it was with me you are better you were just sitting
around like man I would like this game's fun but I wish like Ludwig would
ask me to play is that how it is now I mean he's fucking funny guy super funny
super talented you get a problem with that yeah he definitely would have
wouldn't have been a pussycat pie shop can you help what do you mean can I help
can you handle the plating yes or no do you want me making pies or do you want
me out there you're running around running around and you're running
around and it's causing stress that's a door what do we want this counter I
mean an extra plate counter hmm you would like Ludwig I fucking met him like
what do you mean I would like Ludwig we did the thing together you got me so
fucked up tonight what have I done the thing is I was gonna try to fuck with
you back but then I realized what I was saying it was just so wrong oh my god
are you drunk no no oh my god that's so fucking funny I wish we had one more
dollar to buy that thing introduce me sometime oh that's so funny that's so
funny don't tell me right now that that's not funny tell me I'd love to
hear it you need to read a clock are you ready yeah he's zonked I was trying to
be cheeky and I and I couldn't I couldn't do it you handle that you handle
the plating like that I can handle it start on batch number two up here oh
hold on one sec we're not out of counter space oh my god I forgot they needed
piece over here I'm gonna go chop this in the kitchen in the washroom in the
bathroom in the sink dude this layout actually sucks it does we need so we
need to like figure something out this is not great no this is a terrible pizza
I have a pizza ready to cook like I'm ready for them just it's it's the plates
man everything's very far away like Ludwig that I love that so much my
attempt at being cheeky with you backfired immensely in my brain I was
got him I'm right here literally I got it okay we can eat these two yeah we
know yeah I had another pizza ready in the oven I am so ahead maybe I should be
helping you with plates more because they are the issue did you forget they
were sitting there no I was trying to do this thing where it's like I was trying
to do a thing where it's like oh yeah you'd like him if you met him knowing
that you did but it wasn't even funny and I just look like a fucking imbecile
that's a lie honestly I'm trying to plan the layout over here you're like you're
still embarrassed because you're a fool you're a jabroni yo I yeah I would like
them yeah I would all right let's get it I'm in the zone just move your tables
actually yeah I know you can put counters here but I kind of a good idea I feel
like I'd be using that door oh it just deletes the door too you're forgetting
that stir was even there I mean that's like one of my favorite streams I've
ever done do you think I forgot it someone have been telling me about the
baseball thing for like a year if I wanted to come down and and then what do
you know suddenly it's just happening do we need another like burner or anything
we do not cook anything on burners but like oh you don't it's only the oven
right okay mm-hmm I like this setup because I can go right here bang bang
okay we buy that other sink because there's always like you you go to clean
a plate and there's already a dirty plate okay let's go look remember you
look like a word would elf you guys are fucking me up today okay pizza pizza
focus focus focus focus focus are you for real what do you mean I'm working on
it there coach okay we need to splice is it's up got another pie in the oven
ready to cook not gonna cook it yet perfect looking pretty slick looking
pretty sly okay I absolutely I aced this mission you've done a pretty good job
okay that pizza is ready to cook and we have another pizza ready to cook after
that pizza if you need a hand I'm good I'm good okay pie up wash the dishes for
you know thank you oh yes slay Queen yes oh we're if we just beat it bonus pie
why are they sitting at the dirty table that was pretty weird are you able to
like delete counters at a certain point like if we wanted to delete this plate
tray so we can get the bigger plates yeah yes yeah one star yeah yeah dude
nice my heart messed up now racing why are you pretending isn't that this
chopped onion is a pizza topping let's get oh finally chopped onion and add to
pizza before read it was wait was it before cooking I don't know what do you
think it sounded like you said before or before you don't even like
pizza you poser who doesn't like pizza oh yeah okay so I think we can buy the
bigger stack of plates and if we put the this stack of plates outside it deletes
it is what I think oh yeah there's a trash out here
some of you guys not like pizza oh and you sell it I don't know if you get
money for it I feel like humans have developed these taste buds that pizza
just hits everything that you like and I feel like it's impossible to not enjoy
the taste of pizza tomato sauce has that savory on the your savory taste buds
cheese hits you you know I mean it's I feel like it's impossible I've never
been hit by these humans were built to enjoy pizza it's like our mouths were
created to like to enjoy that flavor yeah I think that's in the Bible yeah
when when when when Jesus makes the pizza and serves it at the last day
hey good gonna get a plate ready for you up here back I'm gonna get two plates
ready don't be mad at me I'm mad okay so here's the issue they want onion and
not onion do I gotta cook two pizza do I got fucking two pizzas right now yeah I
think so I can't just put half on a pie like a fucking competent human being we
can't I'm gonna move this out of the way temporarily what does this person want
onion all right we've got an onion we've got an onion we're good okay what if he
didn't want an onion what if he wanted that was a gamble I was really what if
he wanted to see me dance in my cat outfit then I did I don't know but yeah
he wanted onion and I the second you get me that other one we're good to go okay
just gonna make this happen really quickly I know they're getting a little
upset but you're different you're the weird one like you are the weird one
I'm role-playing okay hold on we need they just want cheese yeah we should
have enough there is yeah I'm gonna claim this plate you got another pie
ready if it's onion or not onion double cheese oh look at us two bros washing
dishes together what do these guys want they want one onion one cheese one cheese
one cheese okay we got it all good I want these people leaving happy satiate
it not hungry okay we need it can you cut that for me please I want some happy
tummies leaving here okay I don't need this right now but I'll plate it we need
two cheese well now I know I mean plates you will in one second finish mine off
a little bit oil making the final emergency pie we should have we have
everything unless they want to onion unless these assholes actually want two
onions no we're good thank God imagine hearing that like well I guess I guess
we're gonna order the cheese then I uh every once in a while I really enjoy
watching some of like the trashiest possible reality TV and it was
recommended by my sister-in-law was saying that um what's the name of the
show the rich people on yachts fucking below deck they like follow the crew of
a yacht that need to like serve like rich pampered people and I fucking loved
the chef because like every time someone would order something he didn't like he
just like stop he's fucking idiots so I'm channeling that a bit what would
what network is this on uh on Bravo whoo into the counter I know you like those
I think we have enough counters unless we want to throw another like there's
actually no room for it could why I put it up in this corner hey rolling pin
three times faster and rolling the dough uh it rolls really fast I don't think we
need that that's like the fastest part of the process okay so let me I'm gonna
get the extra counter we're gonna put it I let me do my thing here darling I'm
gonna put these here as honestly like I feel like I'm running in here way too
much is that a good spot though can I switch it yeah I can get it we need the
research desk I have no idea what it does what does it do what do we put it
like what is it for it says it upgrades the thing on a cabinet next to it which
we put it next to I don't know I don't know I haven't noticed to do anything I
tried to use it last game when I put it next to the cheese but I guess that's
not a cabinet put it next to the filing cabinet saying filing cabinet filing
cabinet well then we'll move the cheese oh it is doing something what is it
doing though it researches it has to be next to a filing cabinet oh okay thanks
okay I'm gonna try this new plate set up okay we're good
whoo you know that's you know that's uh that's looking pretty nasty let's go one
pizza coming up my little pizzeria in my pepperoni welcome welcome welcome to
our store alright slice cheese never wanted two slices how many slices do you
Easter oh I'd like the whole fucking pie I honestly true I will look at how much
I've eaten from a box of pizza and go oh oops I'd say I'd say I on average eat
like 75% of the pizza that's a lot but I mean it yeah like I could see that all
right let's see this one we just cheese right now no onion um no onions yet no
onions just regular cheese still I'm working on it just need one more all you
best believe this pizza is coming up this is my best pizza yet this might be
my magnum opus of pizzas okay thank you no onion at the moment let's see we do
have an onion now one cheese one onion one onion required here's an onion for
you sir yeah very good just one slice of cheese over there get that in a second
pretty smooth we need a one cheese one onion you know what we should open our
own pizzeria for real isn't that that seems like not a great idea you know
anything do you know anything about like making pizza I know you know a lot about
eating pizza but you know about making pizza I make pizzas now and again I
enjoy making a nice pizza it's pretty simple you have a big paddle that you
use they're like I think that would make it more fun the big like spatula paddle
yeah doesn't that just seem awesome like how powerful you'd feel using that
yeah you get it nice all right but hold on but we have to we have to figure this
out because I have a kind of a way that I like pizza you probably have a way that
you like pizza but it's about the customers are we like we're basing this
around our personal taste and they come in for like the authentic germ area well
because you need to you need to you know how much you like certain pizza you know
how you want it to taste what's your pizza toppings what do you what do you
put on your pizza well I wouldn't make a deep dish pizza place I don't really
like it and I don't really know about it right I my pizza thin New York style
crust super crispy not a whole lot of grease super super crunchy that's the
kind of my favorite pizza super thin what's going on it I mean honestly be
the not just cheese or pepperoni and I'm talking like you get this shit so thin
that those places where they throw it into the oven and it's in there for 60
seconds like so thin and so crispy you could cut someone's throat with it I
don't know why that's where you're going with this but I mean no so a little bit
a little bit of give but right okay you're not not them okay let me do let
me show you like you know I'm talking about when you do that like you bite
and then you bite bite you know I mean yeah yeah yeah you first bite you bite
bite bite that's my favorite kind of pizza have you never had deep dish or
like I've had it's just a lasagna you don't like it it's a it's a lasagna it's
a lasagna a deep dish pizza is a lasagna to me I don't think that there's like
bread in a lasagna but it's just like a bunch of sauce it's a lasagna there's a
bunch of cheese tons of cheese tons of sauce it's like thick it's like I could
eat it with a fork and knives little Zion okay I did I I don't dislike it a
deep dish pizza tastes really great I just don't it's more growing up in the
90s my family really wanted to believe that they were Italian because the
Sopranos was very popular so they would get Sicilian pies pretty often that's
it is but that is like a that's basically deep dish mmm that's not like
deep dish Chicago style that Sicilian kind of you talk about like the square
slices right yeah that's not deep dish that literally is like deep dish how is
it not it's just it's just like a better it's just better but it's deep dish well
deep yeah Sicilian is that's not it's not no it's not see I don't know cuz I
only like we weren't actually Italian there's a lot of different kinds of
pizza that you think oh that's that's pizzas all the same there's like a
dozen at least versions of different pizza there's like Chicago style Detroit
style there's our own style we go like drama style and like we franchise it and
everyone would know like I don't like Chicago I like the German rumble pizza
whatever you would call it so you want us to be like a kid's restaurant no like
we could come up with like a whole new and there's whipped cream and there's
there's anchovies and there's the bake style there's got to be like an
undiscovered bake style I don't I don't think so I think it's I mean maybe this
is like a new twist but I don't know anything about baking food well that's
why we got the research desk going on up here all right but to answer the
question so I what is is your is like that Sicilian like or Detroit style is
that what you like I mean I think I only would like it if I was near like an
authentic place that was like we make Sicilian pies we do it good so what if
otherwise like I'm out here in Texas like everything is a chain restaurant
there's no real food it was all made like a year ago so I'll make the thin
crust kind of Connecticut or New York kind of style pizza and you do the like
Detroit style we have two different ovens we'll just have two we'll just
compete with each other yeah the competing ovens and you come in you
got to like put a ballot in we'll just be the Twix brothers but we're in the
same restaurant so okay so imagine this you walk into the restaurant and it's
kind of like I'll describe it as a hallway on the left is your pizzeria on
the right is my pizzeria and like we're shouting at each other across like but
you can come up to order from me or him and like if you if someone comes up to
order you know and I try and like haggle them like I'll give you five dollars one
piece I don't know prices no what I went out fighting over who gets more I'm just
saying we could have no I think it would be a really cool environment to like sit
in the middle of like two arguing people trying to make better pizzas and serve
you better yeah but what if somebody comes in and they want from one side one
pie from the other side and like we're getting all upset about it but I'm
never gonna argue to somebody that comes in wanting a Detroit style pizza to eat
a New York or Connecticut style pizza that they've already come in and they
already know what they want so they're gonna go to you okay but you could try
and convince them that they're wrong why would you oh hey I love Detroit style
pizza oh this place does Detroit style pizza I'm going in there that sounds
great new place what's it good on Yelp oh like 4.3 I'll try it and then they
walk in and I go Connecticut style peaches better eat mine you don't want
his pieces he's got the cockroaches in his pieces you want my pizzas they're
just not gonna this is gonna be this thing like a dickhead they're gonna be
like that guy's an asshole 4.3 on Yelp omega low that's good of the
environment that's just the environment people are omega low in 4.3 on Yelp bro
that's a high high score on Yelp okay the woman it sounds like you're not in
on this I mean what you you want to like do a stream where we make pizzas and
compete and rent out space in like New York City is this what you want to do
didn't we actually like 20 years ago say it would be like funny to take like
cooking classes yeah that was this was like a thing it was that was immediately
dropped it was like totally not ever gonna happen I mean it sounds kind of
fun yeah maybe we have a lot of the hallway
pizzeria I would call it the pizza gauntlet you have to sign a waiver
before you come in because we can get rough let's just save our money man but
like I'm fucking frisbee-ing the pan the pizza goes on at each other what are
you talking about I don't know like there could be I don't know like
anything could happen it's just like you frisbee it at me and it's just perfect
spiral that big pizza pan just hits me right in the forehead and if it's
crispy enough again you could really break the skin as is in your
grandmother's pizza shop so essentially you just want to you just want to make
a mess for a few hours is what you want to do I think I don't think it has to be
a mess I just think the end I like you know how you okay imagine this you're
growing out to eat you're going to a nice restaurant you're with your family
and like the waiter comes over like everything's nice and proper where can
you go to just like eat but also get totally fucked up and just to be like
scared and like a little bit on edge and like looking around but it's like a
it's like fun it's like you're not actually gonna get jumped like it's the
other people that are like people are saying Ross Waffle House how many how
many people watch like people arguing on tik-tok or like these like YouTube like
all this guy was like freaking out and the Kentucky Fried Chicken that's crazy
like you would be like that every day but it would just be us doing it so it's
like but you want like like medieval time like a medieval times restaurant
like with actors or do you what do you mean I mean in a sense I guess we are
acting through the competition of our pies so you're talking about like hey
when you come in here and sit down we're actively trying to hurt each other
we you and I are actively trying to hurt each other and people are like in here
it's like wrestling like WWF competition pies and like we're putting on like a
show like some people like is this real I was cool you know and like we're gonna
be making their food but also it's like fighting each other we don't have to
like physically fight but we're definitely gonna be in verbal arguments
there could be things being thrown so I send out like this guy like you know
like Louie comes out to like to like go fight you or something he's got like a
yeah and then I send out my goon and he's like fucking Louie or something and
then they just like brawl PVP pizza restaurant yeah kinda it's like a
theater it's like food and a show like every day at 630 we do the same bit
we're like we've practiced this for years where we like toss pies across the
room and like you catch it and throw it back and it's spinning and I catch and I
twirl and I put it down on the you know and I start cooking you know what I'm
saying but you if you're doing Detroit style pizza if I throw my dough over
there it's gonna ruin your entire thing eventually it comes back to you and then
like pizza it's the combo pizza we do one combo pizza a day 630 it's a whole
bit and like it's the best pie you got to get you got to be there at 6 and I
gotta come out I gotta come out with my fully done pie to the customer and be
like okay here you go guys I know you and you come up from behind me and you
do the thing you like grab my head and smash my head into the pizza yeah and
like it like like a cake and to be clear I'm not doing Detroit style I'm not like
Connecticut whatever you're I'm doing cat style I'm doing the fucking whole
cat like made-outfit cafe type style of pizza yeah it's gonna be like you know
my own little twist all right I'm just imagining doing that to me and I'm like
look like pizza sauce all of my face and like it does like five to ten cuts in
like at that moment and you show like a close-up of somebody's face that's
looking around like oh my god and that's really really intense music is being
played like that it like reality TV music mm-hmm and then that look like it
cuts to Louie in the back he's like taking off his fucking gloves he's
throwing him down he's like I can't believe he fucking did that that fucking
piece of shit and he walks out there with that and he's in it's like now it's
time for a brawl everyone likes watching Gordon Ramsay where they do like the
Hell's Kitchen and they cook in front everyone like you know it's like oh man
this seems kind of an intense environment it's like that just every
day but like staged like is that that crazy can we get some fucking orders to
know if I'm putting onions on these motherfuckers I mean it'd be funny for
probably like ten minutes all right well then like you'll come back when you want
some more dude we would go through an elaborate thing and then it'd be like oh
shit we still have like four hours of stream you focus we will die the second
I take a steel pizza pan across the head I'm probably gonna need a few
minutes it's that's it okay okay okay we need a two cheese and one will help me
with this up for a second or two what we have to deal with with pizzas and then
and cleaning I'm we got people waiting at the door I need your help like forget
about anything else I know that guy needs plate immediately immediately
where where where is it what does he want
what is the sky wasn't food does that guy want okay no it's over it's over it's
over it might not leave you get now then you no they're not no no no no no no no
no no no no we're okay oh my god I need one cheese one cheese one cheese one
cheese one cheese one jeez the place is black one onion if the one onion I need
We were too busy fucking talking about fighting in a restaurant, and that's what happens. It's okay. I feel like that was all I made the pies the pies were ready
No, but you guys are ready, but you got me on a topic, and I can't I just say it's that nothing else is important
See I was up here. I wouldn't even sit in the chair anymore. I was just up here sitting in like a sofa
Let's take this one shark tank
I was just up here sitting in like a sofa
Stop pretending
All right, we're doing sad. This is my turn to cook your turn to cook. Okay. We're doing well like things are actually gonna get played it
I hope you can handle, but I hope you can handle the incredibly difficult put lettuce on a plate dish
You're gonna be serving up you pick the hard one. Why do you I that's not my fault
The pizzas were coming out the pizzas were out, but then you were talking about a funny scenario
I'm sorry. I'll be less entertaining this one the name of the restaurant. Let us entertain you that's gonna have to change
Are we ready?
Ready for
Ready for service. I'm ready. I know what to do. I know what I'm doing. Okay, can you make a salad?
All right, so how do you want to communicate this?
I'll say one salad and I'll say tomato when it needs tomato
You really are the voices guy today. It's not me tomato tomato
Tomato tomato tomato tomato. I need a tomato. Oh, it looks like a long walk to get those tomatoes
Yeah, you hold on. I think you
Enjoy your tomato, sir. The most disgusting vegetable. I'm telling you
Wait, you don't like tomato. Neither do I
If you put tomatoes on a fucking sandwich
Why?
Can we get some grass grass? Thank you. You and I finally completely agree on something
I mean like a hundred percent agree completely
Finally after all these years we've agreed on one thing
Today I'm not a big fan of tomatoes on very much
It has no taste and it's just mushy water
Tomatoes are amazing on some things, but not honest. I don't really like it. Why you what do you why did you do that?
We need one tomato
sabotaging
And is this my fault or yours? You're gonna blame me for this?
Gonna need one tomato one salad
It would have been done already
Excuse me. Sorry. Our chef's a fucking imbecile. You'd have your food. It's not hard
Let me tell you if I touched you or pizza
You would have screamed
You would have been like
You would have screamed at me and I would have been like, oh shit. He's mad
Two tomatoes
Get out of here. I'm trying to help
Get out of the way
You just so used to being up here in the kitchen that you're like, okay
Now I'm gonna get up there and do everything. Oh
It's cuz it's slow service. You're trying to um, we need to we need to rearrange. This is a disaster. It's terrible
I will handle. I don't know good. Let's just like speed run
the starting
Yeah, I mean, honestly, there's one counter the first two three days are absolutely on it's impossible to lose
Here give me I'm gonna take the sink outside
Can you give me the plates I feel like I'm
Way too far away. Well, when my when I have clean plates, I'll just play some here for you. Okay, that makes sense
Yeah, let's try this. Let's try. Let's try a surface like this
I know people like to go out to a restaurant where like instead of watching the food being made they get to watch the like
The dish guy just clean the dishes right next to their table
I think it's like a new like thing. They're doing an ally. I have a plate. Hey one tomato
Hey one tomato
One tomato
Man, if we could just get customers in the door, I get the best salad in New York. How's this flowing for you?
That's not quite that's not an accolade
Oh, you know, I got I got the best salad in New York. I mean when you have a like a really good farm close by
You know, it's like oh since since like 19 oh since 1903 best salad
When I was really young I had my own very special methods of
cooking like
Eggo waffles, okay
All right, like, you know, like oh first you like butter it then you like put in the microwave
Then you toast it then you put in the microwaves like it's like softer and I was like man I should like when I'm older
I'll be able to open my own restaurant
I've never seen a restaurant where someone like makes you eggo waffles and eggo waffles are fucking awesome
Like you get like pop darts and other stuff like that. Do you like like real waffles the bait in a waffle maker?
Yeah, because those are you like eggo waffles. You could you know, just take the next step up
Well, I'm saying this was like I was really really young
Better than like a legitimately made Belgian waffle. I'm like making fun of your child palate
Man, you could have you could have like, you know, step it up a little kid
We were looking for a sink a counter is everything going well, we saved the money buy some big stuff later
I think reemptively get a counter because in case we don't see one later, you know, what do you like?
Yeah, I think you get another I think you get another counter in there. I like what?
So eggo waffles, what are the ones over there? It's four smaller little waffles. They're individual big waffles that oh, yeah
Yeah, what are those called? I can't remember just like minis this something though. Those are better than the regular waffles
There's those are better than regular eggo waffles
I like the the cinnamon toast eggo waffles where it's like two and they look like breads
Haven't had those in a long while here. Do you want this?
Want this want this? Oh, you need a I need plates up here. I could just yeah, I don't have plates fucking disaster
I don't have plates up here
We need to grass
There it is
There's a door in the front, you know, but I feel like that would have taken longer
Not so easy, isn't it? That's pretty easy. I want to clean this. How come I can't clean this up?
Though I don't know. It's weird. I really do feel like the difficulty hits a point for us
We're like, I think we're supposed to have a third person
Oh my god, I can't get around them. I cannot get around these people. There you go. You got it
Mm-hmm
Yeah, it's funny there's there's already a plate there for you a little funny
You think you're better than me you think cuz you're in the kitchen now, you're better than me
Oh nice tomato on a plate. We need a regular. I have it right there
Um, what's last me called out a single order by the way, I feel like
You're putting either leaves on a plate or leaves and a tomato on a plate
Do I really need to call them out when like they're sitting right there in front of you and you can see
What's that emote of mine like fucking gourmet dinner? Oh, right. That's a new sub emote. Uh
As olives and onions as a salad topping. Yeah, give it me. All right
Do you want to practice it?
In case there's like some weird thing add chopped onion or olives onto a prepared salad. I think that's all I need to know
Okay
onions or olives
Okay, so that's that okay. That's olives
I gotta get this in a let me put this in the right order though
Cuz I know I freak out if I don't lettuce
tomato
Onion olive and everything needs to be chopped. Okay, I'm good unless you want to add something we do research desk
Another actually I need I need plates or a sink up here
I would like to do the research desk successfully one time to start that and see what happens
Yeah, though you need another counter you said and fuck you not a counter
I need a I need I just need access to plates because you have to give you have to give me a plate every time
That's kind of an issue. Anything. Um
Is it yeah, give me the plates or put you maybe put them maybe put them like put them in
If you're gonna do that then might as well do you do you have enough counter space with these four and this one down here
Trust me on the plates man. Just trust me. All right plates. Okay, I trust you research desk research desk
No, we got one sink in cabinet. All right, avoid that. Wait a minute. There's a sink here
I can put us but how would you you wouldn't be able to get in here if I were to sink go over here
Corner you could block the door. Yeah, but if you block the door it turns into a counter that we can pass stuff over
It does. Yeah. Oh, that's actually better. Let's do that. That's a hundred times better
So also if I'm really in a bad situation, I can put some dirty plates here for you. Yeah, okay
All right. I am ready to start off a
Fantastic service here in slow service. Welcome. Welcome. Welcome everyone. Would you like to watch me wash some dirty dishes for you?
Oh coming right up. We need a salad with onions on it a salad with onions and
Olives I need plates trust me with the plates trust me with the plates bro
Onions and that's it and then onions and olives said yes. Okay, you don't need to chop those. Okay works
Hold oh my god, those guys eight salads and how much how dirty is that? It needs uh, it works onions olives and tomatoes
Works it works. I need plate
One grass one with everything. I got it. It's a plate one grass. Yep
Two with everything got it one plate for you. Nice moves, dude. I saw that I fucking saw that dude
I respect it. Don't take them both. I'm ready for the next one. We're gonna be ready. Yeah. Yep to grass
That's it to grass like coming up one with everything one grass one grass survey said hey, look at that
Solid service looking good. I think I can put more dirty plates up there for you
yeah, the the issue that I'm having with this setup is
The fact that there's so many ingredients that I'm gonna run out of counter space eventually
I mean, I you know, I need counters on the right
I think also I can probably just put dirty plates straight into your sink. I should do that
Yeah more often drop a dirty plate in there. I'll wash it
When does our research pay off like what what is happening? I think I'm gonna move over here, too
I want this like over here easy to get to and grab it. We got another counter, you know
Yeah, I'll take another counter right here right to the right blueprint in the filing cabinet blueprint in the filing cabinet
Blueprint in the filing cabinet. Do we put a blueprint from the ground into the filing cabinet?
Like if I put a sink in it, yeah put a blueprint into the filing cabinet. It will upgrade it
Oh my god, that would have been useful information 30 hours ago. Yeah
We can get an Omega sink out here that would be huge actually
I think this is a good counter space for me. We got sinks. We are gonna run out of plates there
We're at the extra place
I'm gonna put these in here just in case that's the just in case emergency plates
Everybody use the desk like use the desk
So I have to go over here and it's a thing that we have to actually use it to do it
We have to research it you have to interact with the research desk
Okay. All right. So that's how it's a challenge
So when if you got nothing going on stir, we have to fill this thing up during the day. Okay, he's reading
Let's go for it. Yeah, while you're preparing the first meal, I'll be on this you got it
Oh, that's all it takes. Where can I go again? Okay, that's it. Oh, I like this line you got going. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I'm ready. I won't say everything one grass
Is that actually everything or I don't see tomato. I don't know tomato one with no tomato
In all of my bad a little bit one miscommunication and you fucking die good thing I got these fucking eagle eyes
Hawk man. Why do you even need me?
Tomato olive I need some plates. I
Got you. I got you just say plates
Said you said just tomato and all
Yeah
To grass easy one grass one tomato
Look at this. Look at this. Look at us here. We're insane one with everything one with onions
Steve plate
One grass one tomato boom bingo
That worked out pretty well, yeah, that was uh, it was our best service yet. I think we're gonna get a raise
So what do we do to here? I would love
Standards aren't as important or people will wait a long time
What do you think? Um, I think exclusive I think a lot of the ones we've lost have been because someone's waiting outside
Yeah, it's true. Oof. All right, we got a lot of stuff highly flammable rug. Ooh
Painting you know a little bit of danger. We only have 70 coins though. Uh
Yeah, I think we should like think check the sink and we have to go in the filing cabinet. Oh, yeah
Yeah, a wash basin. Ooh
Oh
Washes up to four plates at once. Oh
We're on we're incredible. We just unlocked the next level. We just throw the sink away
There are that sink in here with the other the emergency plates
I don't know if you actually sell things for money or what?
Okay, I'm gonna get it. Yeah, and we pop that one out in front. Oh, hell
Yeah, four plates can go in here. Are you kidding me? You can upgrade it again. Oh, that's cool. Let's upgrade something else
What what do you use the most? Um
What can be upgraded or what are those other envelopes you got in there? I mean there is
chandelier and
Whatever this is banner. Oh, well, that was free. It says if it can be upgraded. Okay
I don't think we have anything else. I think we're good upgrade the counter. Wait
Yeah, I think we need the blueprint to put in there not the actual
So I think we could reroll blueprints then start upgrading something might be
But I don't know when you get to the stage just gives you all these random Christmas
Oh, wait, people are saying the wash basin needs water. We need to put a sink next to it. Really?
That's not a sink. We need to sink next to the sink. No, it doesn't they are just keep that sink there
There's no reason not to have that in the corner. Now put that thing back. We're back. Yeah, it's an empty space
They're like I can I can side put a plate in there. Okay. I'm good. Let's do it
Oh, good evening, sir
Oh
Salad and one with tomatoes and onions. Okay
Okay
one with onions one with everything wash wash wash wash wash wash wash grass and
tomatoes and olives grass and tomatoes and olives
And then one with everything once you're done with that and you said everything. Oh, look at that insane and they all stay there
Insane one with onions we got somebody outside you see you see yeah, you're good
One with just olives still good to grass easy easy. Very easy. Very easy to play it's coming up
Won't everything one with tomatoes and onions
How come that guy let this whole plate of food?
That was the one you made
Holding it there just saving space so I don't have to run so it's actually hard to get from this counter all the way to
The bottom right table like
It's a race against time
Slow service, but this is the best unironically that you guys have done because we're taking it slow
I think we also figured out that you can upgrade stuff that that helped a lot. I feel like that was a
very important thing to know
Allows customers to change their order. That is a death sentence
Going straight to the gulag with that one. Oh, yeah, that's terrible, but you know pumpkin pie though
I think they can change
It's just salads
It is but I want to learn a whole pie
They're gonna change it up and except for the salads all look very similar though. That's the problem. They do portioner
automatically performs
Enter on things placed in front of it. Oh
Upgrade counter and dining table. Should we make a bigger dining table or do come I would upgrade the counter and I think we could
Upgrade the counter. Yeah, I don't think we need anything else. We could even like what would we want at this point?
What are the work boots? They are pushed through things easier, which I assume is like doors. I don't really need it 60
It's too much money. You think so. Yeah, I think we're fine. It's not movement speed. It's just pushed through things easier
I think it's better if the emergency plates are here next to me. So I don't have to go all the way down
All right, cool. All right, we good. Yeah. All right. What do they want? They want dog food one with everything
I made it in that soap shop. It's all right. Slow down slow service. We're good
We're everything's fine grab those remember they can change their orders. Mm-hmm
One with olives one with onions one with olives one with onions. Yes, sir
Done with olives. I gotta take that plate out. Yeah, he changes the grass. Oh, he did change the grass that
Bastard
Let me figure out what these guys want both everything with tomatoes one with olives one with tomatoes and onions
I got the dishes one with olives and one with tomatoes and onions. Yes, sir. Yes, sir
Tomatoes and onions, right tomatoes and onions and one with olives just one with onions or olives olives olives
Go go go go go go what two onions and tomato
Do you change what I got one right here? I got one right here
What I don't even know what I did wrong
What happened you get the wrong plate? What did it happen? What happened? I I put I think I put the wrong plate or something
Down what happened? He gave them the blank plate. Oh, it all fell apart so quickly. No
We're doing so good. Oh
Fuck we unlocked medium-sized though. You forgot you left the salad on the counter
Grab an empty plate and take it to him and think I think you miss clicked. Yeah, I want I need to go again
We're like we're like right there man. I mean we have a medium place now. You want a bigger one?
Look at look at this one. This one's pretty good. Let's go back to the classic classic steak. You want to cook? Uh
Sure. Okay now that we know we can upgrade
Turns out changing the order actually kind of sucks because you have to constantly look for it
Yeah
It was really hard for me to like look and catch any of that
Especially the salad because it's like the olive sometimes blend in the onions. Yeah, that's different. That's that's hard
Okay, I don't know if you want the booking desk. Um, that's kind of hard mode. Maybe we just shouldn't do it
What's your title right now stir and I are having a breakdown. I'm having a break up truly. That's all so bad
Never mind. No, not true. Not true. You know set the tables where you want them
They're pretty spread out. Did you get them right in front here?
Dude, they could sit up here. Okay. I messed this up. They it's like they can do like bar seating
Yeah, there was like options on it too of like what it modified. Can you put it back? Oh, yeah
What was that decreased patients increased mess? So could you just awful? Could you do that's awful?
But hold on. Can you just go like right from you could probably just serve them immediately if they sit there, right?
Is that work or didn't know I don't think so, right?
It sounded like all negatives other than like how long it would take me to get to them
Then you put it on the other side. Wait, hold on swap it done. No, it does work
You have to remove the counter really so they can just come sit in the kitchen
That kind of sucks. Yeah, I don't I don't want them in my
In your space
Okay, so I'm gonna put one here and then one like we just go bang
Outdoor seating can you that's a lot of way to go though. I'm so ready
You were just like back and forth back and forth. I know cuz I'm I don't I wanted to be three and three
Okay, I believe you. Okay. I'm good. You're ready to go steak Andy
Yeah, I'm gonna have that there so you can put dishes straight in it's it's the strap. Yeah, I'm gonna go
Why are you putting stakes on immediately? They?
Okay. All right. Okay. We want a two wells all the way
I think I can handle a couple of steaks
this person wants a
rare
You made a bunch of mediums, I want you to take that on over that customer right there
Oh, yeah, why wouldn't you go back there? Do you start to talk like this? Oh
Just having a nice all-time good in my food. Just keeping calm. I had this person wants a
medium which is right there I
Think I can I grab it from here kind of you can yeah, I wish you could like take down parts of the wall for this
counter
Put this in the sink
I think we're done
One more fucking yokel
People are saying it's the wolf man voice it is
rare
Golden rare why is there steak in the sink give it a little bit extra juices. All right, we just go I think we just go
Just go just I mean, I don't we I think we just go we don't have we don't have money for anything
Get his order immediately son. That's a dangerous game. You're playing right now
Medium you see that's exactly that's not me. That's a well done. I planned it. I played it
I don't like this
Yeah, you don't like a lot of things. I see these kick up a whole bunch of grease on the floor
Are you just trying to make one of each kind of thing to have is ready?
I'm trying to make the ones that take longer first so that I can make a rare quicker
like if they come and they want like a
You know a well done and a rare
All right, so if I have a medium one, then it's you know, it's easy to go plus one
Media man rare enjoy. Sorry I peed on the ground
Rare I think that's it
Fucked up us to mine. We should not have we should not have immediately gone
We needed to put a blueprint in the research. We need to look for a research
Bumper to bump up the research
Shucks, we're gonna get their research going ASAP on one of those that that kitchen sink
revolutionary gradable plates
sharp cutlery
Place on table to have customers eat faster. Ooh, that's actually pretty good
Oh, I'm upgrading the sink. We're going for it. You need a research table
Don't you think you need the research table to actually research it?
But it looks like it's like holding that in is oh we got by the desk
Huh research desk, yeah, we're not one we don't have enough. Oh, yeah, we do. It's 40 out of 60
Okay, when we open you start researching you ready? Yeah, you got it. Let's go
Is that the room code that is the seed for this game? I guess I don't know why this seeds
rare
Rare about to make some pumpkin. Ah
They really want us to make that pumpkin pie. Hopefully these guys want mediums
rare and well, sorry
Rare too easy
dominated
one shot one kill
You do by playing overwatch. I have been a bit lately
You like it?
Yeah, is it fun? Like should I play it? Should you play it? Probably not. Okay, I
Think you should try it one probably when the PvE stuff comes out. That's a play together. That's what I'm waiting for
Is that coming at any point?
Um
Apparently like piecemealing it it might be like another like six months sometime in my life. Yeah, my goodness
It's basically like a year away. I thought that might be generous. Wasn't that like the whole selling point of
Yeah was but they realized that was taking so long that they
Said okay, we'll do multiplayer stuff and not like hold that off because that's actually kind of sort of a little done interesting
Yeah, we 20% slower sounds awful
Okay, so we should have an upgraded thing over there
What kind of psycho wants chopped tomato on their steak like you go to a nice steak restaurant, which is what we are
We're incredible. Mm-hmm to like just tomato slices
Yeah, that's kind of weird or is it like a tomato sauce tomato sauce would be kind of weird, too
Oh, we don't have the money for this so we can upgrade it again do it again. Okay. I'll start here. Um
Hold on I did the breaking bad thing where I haven't let my eyes hurt. I haven't blinked in like three hours. Okay, okay
Order up this person wants
Probably the new thing I would imagine
Nope, just a well done. Oh, yeah, I gotta keep that in mind that I might have to chop some tomatoes
Yeah, that's some dangerous cooking
these two want I love that rain sound they want a
medium with tomato and well done
You already have a medium here stir
Fuck
Doing too many things these two would like I need I need more counter space they need
medium and rare
I'm waiting you're burning. It's burning. You're burning it. I don't care what
No, give it to me. Oh
It's bad news
Wait, wait
Too much you cooked it too much
This is ugly. It's getting ugly over here
Everything's fine. It's savable. We just need one rare
I'm sure I'm like over complicating. I'm trying to like be maximum efficiency
You're okay. We're good. Everything's fine. I don't have to take that order yet
Yeah, this this grease ground we need like a mop as soon as we can get it
It is so hard to walk around and click on the right thing. Okay, you good to take an order
Yeah, rare rare one of them tomato. Yeah, I can't even get in the door
Why does my steak taste like soap I
Need a mop. Yeah, and if you're ever like
Really waiting for me. Let's come do that. I need a I need a clean boy
All right, I think I need to get on it earlier because you can clean the small ones quicker get him up
Off is better. I mean if we get offered one
gas
Eight more plates another counter you wanted that right and a sink you want the counter. Oh
But what's wrong? Hold on. This is a dishwasher. It's like a full dishwasher
I don't know if that's a problem. Is it it's probably better. It does it automatically. No, that's phenomenal
That means it'll do it without us even touching it automatically
I was just thinking in the case of a kitchen where I actually need sink water
But I guess you know, we saw the sink. Do you want the um, oh we only have 15
Yelling at us. They're saying I'm great more. Yeah, I'm upgrading something. Are you are you doing you confident? Yeah, I'm upgrading a grill
All right, I'll do the upgrade when we start is that where you want the dishwasher? Yeah, that's good. Cuz I got actually yes
Okay
Maybe it's on the left side next day because it's kind of far. We're good
Okay, taking it nice and slow cooking to order. All right. Here you are
well with tomato medium tomato, I
Desperately need another counter now we need
Rare tomato well tomato
So when you do that, I can't place the tomato now. Yeah, all right now any well tomato and then this guy
What do you want?
medium tomato
Wait with these people might want well, yeah
No, they were too medium. So we need two mediums one tomato and one rare tomato two mediums one tomato
Okay. Now I need a medium and a rare tomato
You need a plate. All right, so I need a rare tomato. Yes, darling. Oh
All right, this person wants a medium tomato and a well
This thing is amazing by the way
This thing is absolutely just cracked out. I just need a well. I think that's it for the day
All right. That was a little that got a little heavy, but we're okay. I got a little rough
I've written just one counter dude. Just one counter the plate rack next to the sink. It is it is though
Charming sure we have never actually successfully set up decorations for one of these
No, imagine going to a nice restaurant and the dishwasher is in the dining room
Oh
Dark board. We don't have enough money to do this though. Yeah, aha a danger hob
Double speed but catches fire after burning food. I can keep that we can we can get the final upgrade on that
Walllight, how do I move this? I don't want to this isn't a really stupid place
Do these blueprints get re-rolled into useful stuff cuz like really it's counter space
I don't know but the banner over the dishwasher. I gotta pick the banner up. I don't think I can I think it's just here forever
You know, yeah, that's that's annoying me. I'm actually very upset
It's pissing me off how the way this is and I can't pick it up. I hate it
I don't think I can move it. Oh, thank God. Okay
Christmas. All right. Um, I'm nervous. I'm nervous. You nervous. Hold on. I need to do it some adjustments here
Okay, I think I'm okay. Hold on. I want this not quite against that
Okay, I am
Plate rack plate. I didn't press it plate somebody saying plate rack plate rack plate rack plate rack. What about it?
What are they what? I don't know we're being yelled at what happened plate rack plate rack move the plate rack move the plate rack
Why I don't know they're just yelling it plate rack swap with the sink swap the sink with the plate rack
Oh, yeah, you know, it's because I the dishwasher is over here and I can just put the clean plates onto the dish
Okay, I get it. Yeah, you guys are right. That's true
You're calling me how to telling me how to run my kitchen like telling me how to raise my kids
Hey, how do you feel? You all right? This is the big one is we have to get past this hump. Sure
I remember a research in the beginning. Oh, yep
There's nothing to research. Oh, I guess it's maxed out. All right. This person is coming in
They want a nice delicious steak and they want it to be
Medium just medium nothing else. Nice work
Hey open, what does it think?
Shit, there's nothing in there. This person wants a
Yeah, well with an onion with a tomato. Okay, I'll give an onion well with a tomato. No tomato. There we go
This person wants oh my god get out this bad well with tomato this person wants well with tomato
Wow, how original?
Good
Medium only got them service up clean it. What are you doing? You're fucking idiot. What's happening to my guy?
You won't clean it that
My life rare medium both tomato. I fucking stopped that move that plate
You cannot do that you need more counters put the plates with the plates
There's a plate stack you need more counters. That does not fix the idea that you need more counters. I do need more counters
We agree oops
Two wells one with a tomato, where's my plate? Where'd you take my plate? They're all stacked up
You told me not to do that anymore. Yeah, but I set the plate there at that time on purpose. Hey, but you
We talked about okay didn't okay. I you don't think I know what I'm doing over here
That's the 300th Boston accent this stream. Oh dude this guy from the East Coast or something. I don't know
Um bone in steak serve with the bone which must be thrown away after yeah
I just gotta move bone and steak which I need to figure out like if I need to do something special for that
Yeah, remove. I think I have to do that. I think I have to take the bone out remove bone before cleaning
So give me the trash because I have to do that here
Oh, no, I have to like it's a whole separate cut of meat. We we need a counter gas limiter
No counter. All right, dude. Okay. Well, I'm gonna buy the extra hub
And I can use that as a pretend counter take out the upgrade is the one in there. Yeah, I got it
Oh, you got it already. Okay. Let's upgrade the plate stack or maybe the gas limiter because this is super dependent
What does the gas limiter do 70 burn 75% slower?
Burn slower but cook slower. Oh
Burning has not been a problem at all. I think the entire time we've been playing how much money do we have?
25 we can get these breadsticks, but I don't know how they work
It kind of I tried to use them it kind of like a detriment
I think we do you put the plates or plates in the research. Yeah, okay
I'm ready. You ready to go for bone in I'm ready to bone
Oh see you need to throw the bone away then I need to throw them. Oh the garbage we did
That's GG fuck that's GG. What does he want?
Also got a weight for them now in case they want bone in her steak
This is a rare tomato. Look at that. Look at that cook speed. Boom tomato. Just testing you
medium tomato
That is so convenient. We don't even need all these burners now. It's just way faster. Yeah, I need to move those plates
I like to have the the middle open
they want
They went well and then rare tomato
Look at that. That's so much better. Well, you have to be on top of that though
You get that convert I can like fuck it up so quickly the bone in not very popular. Hey
Rare tomato well done the plate down, please
Put the plate down, please sir. Ah
Fucking I fucked it up. I fucked it up. I fucked it up. Yeah. No, we're good. We're good. We're good
Great tomato thought it was the other way around. We're good. This person wants a bone in tomato and that I that looks like medium
Medium bone in with tomato. There we go. Sir. I'll take this order
Good good. Oh
Trash you gotta throw that away. I can't go in here until it's thrown away. Yeah, that's I
Need that over here. So hopefully we make it through this good that they didn't order
That would have been so awful. And then how do we take the trash out because the trash fills up?
We need a well tomato. I
This trash outside I can do that
Alright, we're good. We made it
Yeah, I can't even dump a second one. Yeah, we just have to move that next time. We're good
They bone into mate. Yeah, I like the way that it rings
Okay, cool. Alright, so priority number one. I need the trash in here
auto plater
conveyor oh
Finally a counter didn't you want another one? I don't understand this one
It says automatically plates anything placed in front of it. I don't know we pick up the tonight pick the trash up
Okay, that solves literally every problem
What we did upgrade the plates? Uh, they need to upgrade again again. I was looking at let them let them cook a little longer. Um
I mean, I think we're good if you got the trash out there. Oh wait, that's another counter
We're taking with countertop countertop countertop. I think I'm gonna put this up. Yeah, like right there. Okay
Do I need I need to upgrade this right? Yep. Let's go
No, and I'll be up wait what it cannot
Okay, then I don't really understand what it does. I think some things can only be operated once
I mean, I don't understand what the auto plater does in general. Oh
All right rare, you know
upgrade this I
Think this this grill also doesn't make grease all over the ground
medium
Things got infinitely easier. I could see where that would be hard to use though because it just happens so quickly
All right, we got
Bone rare bone in rare with a rare bone in tomato rare
No, it needs the tomato. No rare bone in tomato rare. Oh
boy
We're good. My old age is kicking in just that's a well done bone in
Well done. Is that no? Well, well done sure. Yeah one more
okay, and
I was gonna wait but yeah good
Now we need rest. Well, well tomatoes made. Oh well tomato. Well tomato
A plate I gotta put this shit down
Okay, got two plates for you. Oh
We were born for this. Okay, let me get this other order
We are looking for
bone in rare bone in well
That's got you got to cook that more that that's what one of them is rare. Yeah one sir bone in rare bone in well, I
Fucking add the trash this all the way out here. I'm doomed. I need help just pass the bad
I just do I gotta go right here. The trash is full. The trash is full as well. Shoot. It's okay. It's okay
It's okay. I got I gotta go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go good good
rare
We're good. We're good. That was uh
That was scary. Okay
incoming
blink
Incoming this shits full again. The trash is fucking full. Yeah, it fills after one
I think it's two. I don't know about that there buck. Oh, all right. These guys. All right, we need a
bone in bone in bone in
Bone in rare with tomato bone in well
Man, if my guy could just learn how to take this thing off of a plate
That's too much
That's not rare that this is well. Oh, no. No, you're good. Yes. All right. I thought I was looking at one stop
All right. Well rare needs a trail. Yeah, the color of those is uh
Weird we're good. We did it
Okay, can you can you upgrade the trash? I don't think there's a trash blueprint. This is the furthest we've ever been
I think you should put the trash near the door so you can take it out easier. Yeah, it's gonna do
It's like right next to the door. What if I just told me at all?
Why would you want to tomato things? I don't know. Maybe you can upgrade it. Yeah, looks like you can
He knows if you can actually Oh meat more meat. Yeah. Oh
Oh, they don't like that, okay, they don't want to sit next to like the smelly trash, okay
All right, we're good
Yeah, this I what I need an explanation what this auto plater does because you like auto plates
What if I put something on it's already going on the plate? Um, let's see if anybody in chat tells us what on twitch integration
It it's not happening right now. Not tonight. It's this you're gonna like open up a page log in like link do a link
Activate it. Oh, I get it
It's for like if you have the conveyor belts
Then it would like you'd conveyor belt a plate down in front of the auto plater, but we don't have conveyor belt
We have a hundred dollars. There's nothing else here. We need not really we could upgrade something. Is that a counter?
That is a counter here darling. We could reroll. I'm gonna upgrade this counter
We don't want to reroll the tomatoes. Uh, no, I just want to like ten bucks. Wait, hold on. Let me make the counter. Sure
That's my shirt. That's an Andy mark shirt do it. We need a Andy mark a mop would be nice still
That's what I'm saying. We should just reroll reroll. You're out there. Let's reroll scrubbing brush
Wipe the floor scrub the dishes don't think too much
So hold this to do floor two times faster on floor messes and scrub is three times faster on something wellies
I think this makes a huge mess, but you don't care about the mess anymore and then another dish rack
I think we're ready. What about the dish right? Yes
Yeah
No, let's go. We are wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, maybe the dish rack
We're we're like we're limited we can clean plates quickly, but we have a stack of four for this whole fucking place
All right, let's get it here. I'll pass it to you the wall. No, I won't. Well, what was that?
Why does it look so different? Wait, there's no dishes. It's a dish rack
Oh, so you can put dishes in the dish rack, but who cares right now?
Wait you go away. Wait, what is it? Yeah, who cares? It's for dirty plates, but I don't get it
All right. Well like that here. We'll just put that in the we have so much money. We're so wealthy
We're so well off but what I mean even matter it's for dirty plates
Yeah, but what does that do that doesn't we don't have whatever. Yeah
I guess if the dishwasher is currently running and I could put some in there better you want the wellies
What do they do you make a huge mess but your character does not care you you never oh, yes
You should put those on up there. Yeah
Put them in here just the same space and I'll put them on will you play putting them over there?
No, what you're doing my wellies stop. Okay, let's go can't upgrade you better plus to that. What's up? Okay, here we go
Oh, they're still hungry. They're conjoined into one person. I thought I was one person. I'm gonna hate you both
No, you don't. All right. We need two double well bone ins. We have four plates. I think this is it
Four plates. Yeah, I don't like it's not done
My god, oh my oh my
I'm like I'm like colorblind to them. I know that's it
The bone ins are a little there look a little finicky
No, like like like phase one is the same color as phase three fucking
Fucking hell man. Hey, we got a new stuff. There's a colorblind mode
It puts a letter next to the meat. Really?
I would I would not have made like any mistakes at all ever ever in my life
Does it letters inside looking? Where is it? Oh accessibility? Oh
That's that's big that's actually a huge deal. Let me cook these pizzas. Let's let's get a let's get a pizza run
You want to do pizza run?
Maybe a medium floor plan with a pizza would be huge. I don't really care about the floor plan
I'm just the pizza god. We need to get to day 15
First of all, I don't think we need to first beat this place the garage items in the loading bay
Oh, we did get garage items. Where are they? Are those the garage? I was wondering about that. Like nothing is really explained. Oh
We get to start with a wash basin. We get to start with this stuff. Whatever we put whatever two things we bring in here
Fucking hard mode butts candles for patients
Yeah, we restart from the beginning. It's a cooking cooking a rogue like extra life. You're going the whole way
Oh, that's actually pretty big deal. That's great. That's actually really helpful. I'm good to go. What you doing a small one
What's I can't tell which one's big? I think the long one here is in wait
Do we even have a medium and you only do pizza on small or is it wrong?
These are the three we were offered. There's like a whole bunch of them
It's probably random. I'll just pick the one you like if it says plus upgradeable on the blueprint
See if it says it it does not on this one. But yeah, well we have um, we also have upgrade kits
Should we replace the extra life? I think that would make us start with a dishwasher upgrade at up
Wait, hold on. Once you level up you can do any seed but for now, it's mid ones. Okay upgrade the sink. Wait, so
Mean like wait a minute. I didn't even realize you could walk through there. How is this? Oh, okay
Wait, what did that do just wash? Oh, we start dude. It starts with the dishwasher. Okay, what happened to the other thing?
Uh, it used it consumed it we can do it again with an upgrade yet. You want it again? Yeah. Yeah
What is better than a dishwasher? I don't know. What is it dude? It's an assault rifle soaking
Washes dishes but cannot provide water for recipes. So it's just like a soap a super sink. All right
I am I am about to make every pizza. I actually could I could what time is that?
I want to order a pizza. Somebody said that thing sucks. Uh-huh. Okay good. You're gonna get a pizza. No, it's too late
Wait, this is throwing it away. Okay, that extra life has to be inside. So so
Soaking sink is this thing this thing suck. How is this better than dishwasher? I don't know. We'll find out do this IRL
All right, you did it. That's kind of fun
This turns back up
I'll keep it where it was should you have this sink over there or should I have it over here?
I feel like it's gonna be a mess. It's not a dishwasher. It's just soaking sink
Let's do what we did in the other one and put it like in the middle there so that we can all just dump dishes
Into that. Yeah, can you put the
No, that'd be hard. Okay. No, if you put the dish rack like over here so I can um, but clean dishes
Oh, no, actually, you can just take them out. Can you the booking desk is free? Yeah, but isn't it make it harder
I think it would help early on because then you can make more money if you can just like serve more people in a day
Yeah, let's just put it up here. Okay. It's a what is happening. I don't know. Oh my hand was oh
That's in a bad spot. She's pizza. She really forgot how to make it. That's day one. They don't fucking care
He's never coming back. Oh, yeah more than one person our kitchen needs a little work. It does
Are you dizzy? No, I'm good. Oh, hold on
You can just stand there with that food and you can wait how many plates can go in the sink?
It ain't just one right? It should be at least four. It's
Ottawa I'd like this one. It's one
It's oh, I see
This is awful. It's one that okay the dishwasher can have up to four
Why can this only have one that was underwater by the way the tier two one can have?
Four in it when you wash them all at once, but you have to do it manually
It's just faster. Yeah, but I would rather have the convenience of putting more than one in
Because otherwise you just it just piles up. This thing kind of sucks
We need another sink. Let's upgrade the sink of our sink sucks are fully upgraded super sink. Okay, we need a desk then
Oh, we're missing one dollar for the research desk and the research desk itself is upgradeable weird
Interesting put the research desk in the drawer instead
I wonder what the but how would this we need a research desk to research the research desk upgrade sure do
Yeah, but you save it. We already have I mean, I don't know I think we're kind of think let's put the sink in there to save it
Ah, there's a something in there already. Are you take it out?
X. Hey, okay. All right. Let's try it. I can't believe we're going all 30 days. Good luck
I
Bet you they want a cheese pizza better not add they do put in the sink
I feel like you should move one of those counters to over here. Yeah, I agree. What do you guys want pizza? Yes, you do
Welcome to the restaurant. We can only make cheese pizzas
Pizza's good, you know what you're doing if you have a recipe and it's really great. You don't need to do anything else
Please be sure this guy wanted cheese pizza
He's just gonna pre serve every table. You don't have pepperoni. We have nothing
We only have cheese and pizza. Do you like pepperoni? I don't think I even asked you that I love
Are you a big?
Circle pepperoni soft kind of guy. Are you a small little tiny circle crispy crispy on the edges better
Okay, I'm noticing you're like crispy things I do but here's the one problem with that though
I do like it
but sometimes the pepperoni all the edges curl up and you get these pools of kind of oil in the
Middle of all the little ones it can it can
Not a huge fan of that, but it's okay if I'm in the mood for that
There's this place right here. They have really small pepperonis
I've only ordered from here like once small pepperonis and they curl up into like pods like craters on the moon for all of
The gross pizza juice to just like like miniature lakes. That's exactly what I just said. Yeah, I didn't like it
You don't like that I did not like that I felt like I was like IV dripping like pizza grease into my vein
Yeah, that's what I mean the small ones to have a tendency to do that. That's that's okay
Well, I guess I'm in like a medium like normal pepperoni cuz I know there's like the New York pizzas have those gigantic like super peps
I like just a standard a standard pepperoni. That's what that's where we're at. Yeah
Hey
Yo, that's what I'm talking about. You want to get that extra dining table or up? Let's upgrade wait
I feel like that's what was our sink situation. Oh, we know we don't actually have the research
No, we need a table. Let's get that table by that table. Didn't we have one what happened to it? We couldn't afford it
Shit, we didn't why why do we keep the sink in here?
Because we get to keep the upgrade across like you still have to buy the sink
We want a better sink, but this is the best sink and we have to live with it is not the best sink
Okay, you're right. Just reroll. We
Only have $30. All right. I forgot I named the restaurant that and I was if I got like got taken aback for a second
I have I just I I didn't even notice that
What are you gonna order? Let him do it. Let him order a little more. Oh, he wants one single water
No, I could just have a water. Okay, and yeah, you're good. I cannot cut pizza. I cannot reach it from here
I know I'm thinking wouldn't it be funny if like we had his pizza ready and we could give it to him right now
But we like made him wait and you're like sitting there at your table and you're wondering like where's my food? I
Can see that there's a pizza back there. I'm telling you right now. I I do not like this whole setup
I hate it. This is absolutely hate it. This is ending at
day like six
Space is so important and we just don't have any
Especially with all the plates, but we will make it. What are we gonna do about it complain over and over again until
We decide to stop playing. I was looking for like a practical. How do we arrange this?
If the sink is the problem
Mm-hmm chips messes are created in a well, that's awful
Let's go to make but because you have to make these I'm the chef
Pizza and chips chopped potatoes and oh you have to actually cook them you can just empty like a bag of
Lays or something into like a like a bowl. What am I cooking them in? Hey, here we go research oven research desk
Alright, the sink is in here right now. Yeah, is it like chips like oh chips or is it right?
Like potato chips potato chips, so it's potato chips not chips like fries not not chocolate chips
It's crisps is it crisps or chips it is for I don't know man. I think this is an English game
Yes, I'm I putting it in the oven. I'm just taking potatoes and putting them in the oven
I'm chopping potatoes and ovening them. I guess okay, then I am
ready
Research we want the sink in there, right? I like I like that word crisps crisps. He wants pizza and crisps Betty does
Don't hope you don't want chips. Oh he does it's a baked potato
Sorry, we forgot to cut your fries and we baked the whole potato. Here you go
We want one cheese one cheese and crying fries
I'm not what I've stopped saying it one cheese. And are you fucking me? I
Know why can't you just pick it up and put it on the other plate? No
We want just two cheese nothing else. They're gonna make a whole other pizza. So this is uh, I think you got time
This is looking a little dicey. No, you're good. Hey waitin we picked didn't we pick like comfy they don't care
That's just scared this fucking shit. I mean scared me too. What happened to I don't understand what I don't what I don't get
I'll put the fully prepared pizza in the oven and put it into the trash
What I didn't see
So now we're fucked now we are fucked
Instantly just like boom gone
You throw a whole piece into the trash, oh my god
Pete's my mic, which is hard to do. I
It's not okay. Okay that really I'm moving that garbage this whole kitchen. I like it
Bat flu in your room swoop down and try to bite you on the neck
Oh
Compromise from the chef here. Can we like next guy who comes in we give them the trash bag
There I saw this meme video like this tick-tock video one time this lady
He was she was at a restaurant back in the kitchen. She was balancing for somebody
she was trying to hold five different old dinners and she was
balancing them on a trash can and
She moved a little too much in five full plates of dinner
Just went to right into the trash
It's awful. It's such a sad video every single one goes in the trash and she just goes
It I feel it
We're gonna upgrade that sink again power. What does it wait power sink?
I don't know speed but cannot provide water power jet. We put it in there again
Yeah, well that thing cook will it turn into a dishwasher eventually and can we I think the next one is the dishwasher
Did you get the work boots? I didn't I might want to buy the plates and buying the plates
I'm gonna say this clip pizza eviscerated it. I didn't even see you do it
It was such a clean like I want that to step through the step five ready to put it boom
Let's see. I think you got time. Just look at a little dicey. No, you're good. Hey waiting
We picked didn't we pick like comfy they don't care
I was gonna say yeah, definitely move the trash. Yeah, I put the trash out with you
So you guys can relate? I am ready ready. Come on
They want pizza. I
Don't know why it's funny, but I like the way you said it. It sounded like disappointed
Oh, they're pizza and they just order something else. This can't what anything else burger or something
Pizza pizza only pizza ever another day another pizza pizza. I can't reach that one. It's common
Can you please tell them our company slogan I said
Can you think you could use your influence to get Costco to bring back the pizza combo?
Can you talk? Can you take the order? Oh, you don't even have to you don't even have to wash
We need one cheese one cheese and fry
Influence order up the influence that I would have on a company like Costco is your equivalent of me
Like showing up with like three people and we're all in like clown outfits, it's I don't not very much
You're just ignoring customers. I'm doing a funny little bit man. You're like on your phone
There's a customer right next to you and he like knows you can serve him and he's just like side-eyeing you and you're like
Watching like a tick-tock. I mean we would get the attention, right?
Like if three people in clown costumes had a meeting with the Costco representatives, it would be like oh we would get there
It would be like attention-grabbing, but they'd be like, okay and I'll get the fuck out of here you you clown
Take their order already take their order guys. They're ordering pizza. He knows what to make
What am I doing? There's too many plates in that rack
Looks like we got three left over if you want to share a bite go my pie
Again, you're back there and you're just being a weird guy. I'm the I'll be a weird guy no matter where I am
All right affordable or charming
Again, we have never done one of these
So what okay affordable focus to serve as quickly as possible
So eventually they have decreased eating time
Haves the time but no, what'd you pick? You picked the right one? You were already on the right? Oh, I was reading
Oh sure you were water basin a water
Basin you want the water base when you want to wait again for the washer
I like the water basin the water basin. I think is immediate, but what do we do with the super sink?
Um, it's like in here in case like something no the trash is causing customers to be upset
I think yeah, it can't be up here. Is it? Yep. See they look at the stinky fish thing
Oh, we lose a money dog. Okay, so it's gotta have to be somewhere up here. Yeah, put in
I'm ready. You ready? Um
So this is a so this is the one we want. What about a plant? Oh, that's expensive expensive plant. I'm gonna sneeze fine
I hate that more than anything. I thought about it too much. Oh that angry. I
Hate that more than anything. You can use a barrel as a counter when we need money. He spent it all. Can you I think so?
That's awesome. Then cuz it counts as a decoration. Okay, let's go. We got no money. We're poor. We're good art making the dough
Come on. It's 8 a.m. Okay. I am doing it. I am doing it. I am doing it. I'm sorry boss
Hey, can you guys wrap it up? It's my bedtime soon. Um, okay
I'm just gonna throw this pizza in the trash. I can't you can't put wait. We can't put them in there. Oh, oh
This is bad. We need to pivot here. Okay. Where are you? Just this book? No, they can't have that take that's not yours
Hey, can we have someone handle that customer the way on the left someone handle that guy? You see I am working
Okay, I just hate to see a customer neglect it at the fuck you customer leave pizzeria
Fuck you customer leave put a nice place need a slice. I can't reach it need a slice on here. No
I need a fry. I blew it. It's over. I fucked everything up. I it's over. It might not be put it on there
Thanks for coming and make sure to give us a nice review on Google. Yeah, this saw this center this sucks
We're still fine, man
It's a good thing I have cat like reflexes
When he said guys move everything to the left, please
On us to maximum group size. Let's do that. That's kind of interesting 200
It's it's better reward to and I think that's actually easier. So not that I know what experience well when you make a big pizza
It's because we're doing pizza. So that's actually here and no we're making the same amount of pizzas
And let's like four dudes want fries then I'm like then we're fucked. Yeah, but I mean you make one whole pizza
That's a whole table. How many slices it or five or four or it's been four provides oil oil
You could oil me up. I left the call. Okay. I
Wonder what the oil does and that makes sense that it's one for a plate and one for washing
Yes, I think everything you just said for the last few minutes. I completely agree with great
That's all that I asked. It's all that I asked. Are we good? Wait, what about an upgrade upgrade?
Everyone okay increases movement and prevents spills. We can upgrade this upgrade that I wonder what that does. Okay, let's go
I gotta be top of my game here. Yeah, you have this three people. Okay, what do they want? We're looking at
pizza pizza pizza fry
Pizza pizza pizza pizza pizza pizza pizza pizza pizza pizza pizza pizza pizza fry you can do it
It's this fucking plating nightmare. It is a nightmare. I actually like how do we get three pizzas out at once right with this?
You know, I mean
Hold on then you just hand it to me through the
Resets the timer every ding we need a fry. We need a fry on there. We need a French fry on there French fry
Hey
We're good
Pizza pizza pizza pizza pizza pizza fry again. How are we doing this? How are we? How am I getting this out?
I don't know. You only hand me the pizza when it's done cook it give it to me through the window
I'm gonna put on a table. No
The way
God okay, just pizza pizza pizza pizza. It's a pizza pizza pizza pizza
We get we can fix this can't we just put the whole pizza on there fucking I just need two slices
Yeah, I know but I can't make them two at a time darling
Okay, I'm ready to start going one second. Okay
I actually can't move
pizza pizza that's it just pizza pizza okay we got that this I can't put any
more play we need to put the bigger plate stack over here I think I need
them over here okay we're good man that was some quick thinking we made it we
have a lot of money we might be able to fix this whole thing right now increased
patience also helps if we can get that two more decorations yeah all right what
you got what was the thing we upgraded what is in here robot floor cleaner
250 that's way too much I'm gonna put a dining table someone help me with my
homework yeah okay we're gonna go through one through one through 20 ABC a
BBC a DDA BCDB AB got it thanks dude I got a zero I think we should re-roll try
and get decorations mixer thanks dude I failed no do your homework
do your homework what this this item place on a table to reset their order
like you just distract them with the specials menu oh so they we can actually
use buys time that's actually kind of good what about the work boots you don't
care if it's a mess up here not real I mean I really just want to get the the
patience increase you under the menu I mean you're the one out there if you
want to use it it's okay what we need to do right now is solve this plating
situation yes we do okay so the problem is there's not enough space here or I
mean now that there's eight plates it actually might be okay you can also
roll again take that you can put a plate on there so you can take one from the
table and then move it over you see what I mean okay yep I have access to three
spots I think that helps a lot the mixer is goaded I don't we don't have
anything to mix in oh yeah well you can chop and use your hand what I don't know
whatever I don't know what I meant I'm ready to start I guess I guess we're
ready we roll again it's 20 bucks get ready to upgrade the table in the
research oh yeah yeah what is in this cabinet what cabinet what do we what a
dining table okay yeah it's pizza I really like when you talk that way to
me I have never liked you more than when you say to me pizza pizza pizza pizza
that's just what you just did an AI response that's how an AI response to
something like that here like prep prep the barrel with the pizza you see I'm
saying yep hey guys welcome over to pizza barrel hey left waiting for you
on the top yeah that bad you're ordering pizza and seeing that when you come in
and the waiter or waitress just picks this up just places it'd be like excuse
me at least put it into the oven for a second at least reheat it ma'am I do like
this barrel scenario pizza pizza pizza fry what I'm gonna fry see to fry the
barrel pizza is really like if you go to a restaurant the most disgusting thing I
can think of is like there's food already prepared on random decor and
they just it's already played it like oh you ordered that good we had one ready
yeah do you eat it isn't that kind of what fast food restaurants do though
they make it and they put it under the warming lights I said just sit in there
for some difference in like these are warming lights we designed it for the
situation and it's on the barrel when he double pizza double fry yeah it's not
under a warming light it's just on it'd be like if it was just on the counter
it's true fucking I hate this thing what is that I'm in a situation what did you
just like the chart I'm in a situation how can I help how can I help how can I
garbage that I'm gonna help okay good good good good just need fries okay just
need and I just need another fry the pizza all right the button to open the
door and then take out the thing it's like and I fucked up and I burned it
what if the barrel is heated it's not it has like a cobweb on it that would be
dangerous somebody said this game has two buttons yeah but this it could be
either one you never know yeah you know what else what other game has two
buttons like Dark Souls dodge and swing got you there wrong oh look at that shit
what is it extortion customers pay 50% more to use our fancy table we're gonna
be millionaires how much does it cost fancy 60 I mean let's get it we need
another table we I can't we just put it on one of our taste we have already I
think it's like a whole extra table oh let's just let's get it yeah get it do
it do it do it do it do it do it you you kind of did one of the only one
person should be over here doing this you're doing it you're doing great this
is gonna be interesting I think we have to get rid of one of these no I can
swing this you can swing that I guess can I swing this you think what if you
put one of the tables in the extra room oh wait a minute I can do that wait wait
wait wait wait wait I can just put them right next with zero people can sit
here I'm saying like what if we do a secret if I can only zero people sit
here okay you come to both where the barrel is yeah I think they go to barrel
I think so I think this is okay by the larger table need it we need we need
bigger tables because expect the group sizes are for people are saying big
portion are people people are also saying the fancy table should have four
yeah because it's the fancy table and they pay more money but what would the
portion are due for us hey I think this is okay the barrel back here that sounds
like a to me it slices the pizza for you it slices the pizza for you
autocuts the pizza read chat I'm trying it's a fast chat room right now I just
look so do I make this the portioner and then you can grab the pizza off of it I
don't know how it worked should we practice it yes we're pretty high we're
high I don't want to mess this up on yeah it's a portioner okay give it a try
we just make my 400th pizza today just leave pizza on the table from when they
come in unfortunately not how the game works unfortunately I do agree with you
though so well how does this work how is this any different than what it was
before isn't this just the same thing make it face a counter oh oh we gotta
restart the plates on the arrow side I think I understand I think I understand
oh okay like that I put the pizza here or the other way the way it was no no
you're the gamer I don't know I'm not a gamer I think it's like that let's try
it well don't start the day let's practice it I feel like I feel like I
can really just run my own business after this the other way it's upset why
is it upside down wait don't oh it's slicing it and then putting it there
that kind of doesn't even seem that helpful it's only cuts one at a time I
mean if we if we put it in the back I don't want to have it in the front of
the restaurant taking up the counter space so wait I'm confused what's
happening here basically exit exit wait I like wrapping my head around keyboard
looker Andy yeah I stir do you do the home row typing or do you look down at
your hands like I've never learned it was horrible to learn that it made me
like physically ill look wait wait I'm I'm like I've been playing too long I've
been up too long I'm getting mind-fucked by this really simple interaction yeah
so yeah and when you when you put your hands on the home row do you do you type
looking down at your hands or have you memorized where all the keys are you
know if you look down I don't have to look down at my hands we had type in
class in school and I was very fast typer and I enjoyed learning how to type
and being becoming a faster typer because I would play Starcraft and then
if someone typed to me in Starcraft like I can't stop for like a full minute to
type I would have to learn how to type quick that was all one sentence yeah
okay so but do you do ASDF JKL semi and do the home row or do you just know
where how do you what's your placement for your hands where are the the
freaking the knobs are on the the J and the F you put your index fingers on
those yeah like that's called see you don't call me role placement okay yeah
you don't have to look down you just know there that where that is how else
would you place your hand on a keyboard but you have a you have a mechanical
keyboard right yeah whenever I do that I feel like I get stuck moving my fingers
around I feel like I get kind of trapped in between the little divots you know
I mean like it then I press the wrong things well I don't understand your
problem because if you play Diablo 2 and you need to use your potions on one two
three four then you can also just easily go from WASD and all the buttons that
you need up to one fours and you learn how to do the numbers as well I can do
hands are always in the right spot I can do WASD without looking one two three
four space control I can do pretty much it's just needing to go to like type
words right so W1234 WASD Q ERT is everything over here right is fine I
don't need to look but the issue is going from pressing J to E to like B to
other sides of the board that's the problem that's what I mean like is it
like a brain issue or a keyboard issue it's a brain issue because I have what
I'm talking about is trying this same problem if you try and write on paper
but no I could write on I could write on paper without looking but I could you
just write my name without looking that's so you know where all the numbers
and letters are on the keyboard but when you try and form a word my fingers can't
find them because I have never locked into complete muscle memory the exact
spacing for all the letters on the keyboard can you can you boot up like
type racer comm right now I mean I would I wouldn't be able to do it I would love
to see that I would love to see you look straight ahead into the camera and not
look down at your hands and play type racer can I rain check this I'm tired I
feel like it's not that big of a deal I'm tired though I if it's gonna be
awful well isn't that what everyone wants to see let me drink like a coffee
let me eat a piece of salmon and drink a coffee like an espresso and get a full
eight hours of sleep okay okay rain check on the type racer yes don't worry
I'll tell you I will follow up on we're gonna play Elden Ring co-op anyways so I
mean you we could start with that okay I'm gonna eat a piece of salmon I want
to eat spinach and shit I want to have like an espresso and I want to have
simple eight hours sleep do you really need to rest up for this like triathlon
you're gonna run you're a coward I know you can say that they can and they are
I'm just honestly I'm just like too lazy to just minimize this winter I think
that's what's going on here but like you just it's just minimizing a game that
you're barely paying attention to at this point we're gonna lose the next
mission cuz I like started talking to you and you've had a conversation the
last one and this is the problem right what look at we're doing pretty good if
we disappear out to do it like type racer we're gonna come back we're gonna
be rusty and it's gonna be all I think it's already beyond the point where like
that's gonna happen there was just like me I'm really concerned for this next
day we're gonna be fine stop I don't know how the fuck this thing works well
why I'm using why did we buy it let's start okay it's just like me just pay
attention but we have to at least get further than we ever have I think of
us already is not yet think we have one more all right pizza pizza pizza that's
all it is your customers don't respect you I put the pizza I put the plate and
I put the plate here I guess I do I do I do it into one of these plate trays like
to make it actually helpful in any way he's dumb sad I don't know if you're
talking about me or him you're probably talking about collectively all right we
need a pizza pizza pizza all pizzas one fry pizza one fry just just make up that
chop that chop that all just make a huge pizza I see okay I understand we ready
ready yeah yeah it's fry on that one okay now we need pizza pizza pizza just
three pizzas okay I am about to start okay now we need this is a big fry two
fries pizza pizza pizza three pizza fry we just need one pizza pizza fry fry
fry pizza fry pizza pizza fry two fries the amount of focus now just need one
more pizza oh you fuck it's okay I can burn the time I can burn the time pizza
don't burn the pizza I can burn the time we're good it's still time and just need
one slice got it okay uh a full pizza one fry pizza pizza pizza fry just all
you need to worry about is make fucking pizza and put a french fry on one of
them and we did it two fries I meant to say two fries we need two french fries
two fries and then two slices bring along time my god I can't get in the
fucking room okay here we go just need two slices we've got doing doing doing
doing doing doing doing all right I'm going good hey this is the furthest we
ever been three star streamer my streamer less money uh-huh yeah we've
got enough money I don't know about this pumpkin soup so what did this do freezer
items inside are not removed overnight oh blink oh wait you could freeze pizzas
could you make a bunch of frozen pizzas yeah that's kind of awesome oops for
those emergencies were like four dudes are like hey pizza pizza pizza pizza
yeah just pull one out of the freezer that's right yeah we cook this fresh
Gordon won't even know should we operate something at the table they have a
double tablecloth table uh sure okay I mean I think we're pretty much ready to
go okay let me mentally refresh I'm making pizzas yes you are I am making
pizzas and french fries you're making french fries too there's something I
forgot that life wait what am I making making pizza and french fries you're
just making pizza at the moment don't screw it up right you're good but I want
to be the best bro I don't care how bad the review is I just care that we beat
the game it's valid oh I cannot put these plates down all right the we don't
we oh you're right we need a fry just need one french fry is that good yeah I
get a grip we have too many plates here I'll move some plates we need a french
right we need a slice in front of slice slice french fry very good hey look at
this we it's like easier than the last level I think the knife that I finally
remembered to put on helped a lot that like the whole tomato process of the
pizza like I'm jamming these pizzas straight out are you doing pretty good
all right we need just pizza and I got it right here look at that done wait wait
wait wait what's wrong oh you want to put you want to freeze one you want
I'm freezing this one yeah freeze it oh tomorrow it's gonna be good still have
too many plates over here just regular pizza dude I think this is the last
customers make like three more pizzas how many can fit in the freezer okay I
will come I'm gonna help you make one let's make like five I don't I'm you're
making me nervous oh sure just put that with that all right I just need two
slices oh it's only one I just spit everywhere it's only oh fuck never mind
we're good but okay good thing we didn't do that I need two slices okay I need
french fry one french fry we're good to go game over all right I'm ready to go
need a plate bingo look at that we go bingo and we have a frozen pizza ready
for whenever we need it we can only put one in there so we're good to go can
these fucks please put the portioner next to the sink before I blow a
gasket that what he said I think that I might be it's that was close enough it
was something like that okay we have a lot of things going on here rug we have
a lot of money we should put some decorations we haven't done any
upgrades what case plant put a rug down all right I'm buying a rug yeah we have
patience if we get a decorations down Christmas tree you all you want a
Christmas tree I'll buy another rug here's a highly flammable rug okay so
now we have patience increased cabinet can the rugs not go under the tables
metal table 50% less food and I think they order less but they have less
patience hmm sides are optional oh you don't have to put fries on their plate
so you could actually just not put french fries in front of them that's
actually kind of good I don't know what do you think you want to be faster you
put the sink next to the oil you can skip the rolling dough step I'm still
confused the oil in the sink yeah we don't have a normal sink anymore bro
move the portioner there's a lot of negative comments coming in to you it
was I saw someone to do like the face nice my child are saying that that's
like a glitch that's like an exploit we're getting that oh wait why what did
I say you know that email where it goes oh yeah but what's what's the problem
with me they're saying that that's too far away from the sink what's too far
away from the sink the portioner apparently that should be next to the
sink why I don't understand portioner above the barrel so it puts the puts
the pieces over so I can grab them what just happened
oh that hurt what happened to me what just happened to me it goes closer to
the barrel so then it puts the portioned food in front of me so I can
take it that they want that so I put the pizza here and it goes over and then
you get the pizza and you put the put on the plate I think that's how it works I
like bumped my headphone here and it went in my ear yes yes yes finally yes
yes that works yes but also some people said no stop sending psychic waves to
next to the sink oh my god these instructions let me read this upside
down t-shape next to sink with counter but pizza so it goes down just practice
it so we can see what this does we're way too far to have this be messed up
what does that mean what are these words what's the upside down t-shape I'm
getting a Christmas tree I feel like we were doing fine you're doing fine Chad
is just trying very hard drum up mm-hmm every pizza I make yeah it's going in
the trash why we're doing don't do that all right I'm ready I'm super happy with
what we have you it's getting over complicated by like too many cooks in
the kitchen right now there's also too many chairs in the kitchen
can we do an outside seating sure we can handle it we've handled it before all
right just go for it pizza that's all you didn't need to do your master of it
you know it you know the sauce you know the ingredients of the cheese mozzarella
I do I'm glad that I'm getting some of the fucking respect that I deserve you
got that you can plate those yeah but now I see what people mean okay well
then you're gonna have to set it up next time cuz I am dense fucking granite all
right we have another group coming in uh the soccer game just got out and here
are all those kids we need something here what do we need we need pizza we
need this is cringing is there not enough I'm just waiting for there to be
enough isn't there enough this isn't a fucked up spot yeah I don't I was happy
I was happy before I was happy before all this we're so fine we need pizza we
need french fries and hey kids how about an extra large fry all right we need I
don't have anywhere to put the fucking tomatoes every time I want to cut them
we need one fry don't don't repeat what I said and then say minus two that's not
fair yeah yes chef are we okay you ready are we just need one more slice good we
don't need to tap into the freezer yet we're good okay we need a French fry I'm
not gonna press that yet right down I can't reach remember coming out with the
fry and this group wants you shouldn't have done that this one just pizza pizza
got that right here this is not what the bug doctor prescribed whatever happened
just good old-fashioned home cooking or like you don't have to worry about these
like conveyor belts and auto plating Alexa make me a pizza please I can't
reach that uh that is a huge knife that's actually scary I think we're
actually gonna beat this I think so too I think I hate it that whole layout I
was really happy with what it was before I was really content to just move my
pizzas around myself you get a little hands-on with the dough you can really
feel it you know it's like a rustic kind of like connection to the food now
actually put the portion of the sink make sure it's facing the right way
because now I can just go like much easier okay and then and then what if it
goes too fast and it shoots straight into the sink and that will be a funny
LOL moment because we're at the end of the game okay and what it okay here's
the legitimate serious I'm not messing around what if okay I put a pizza here
it shoots over a slice here it's shooting and it's gonna shoot a slice
that I can grab and put it on the plate immediately you you need a French fry
let's where do I where do I put where do I put the French fry that's what the
practice is for mmm you can put plates on top of the portioner ah so then would
you load it with a bunch no no okay wait wait here I just want to explain what
I'm talking about so I only grab this don't go crazy put pizza down pizza goes
onto the plate boink next piece is ready okay so now that's when when when we
need a French fry okay are you then waiting for me to put a plate down I
would need you to put the I put a plate down can you that works no that's okay
then am I making french fries to order then like if what if two french fries
are coming up and I could plate down over here you'd have to put one down
over there but sink in corner never and not on a plate just don't put it on
anything just put it just on the ground okay I'm I'm good I'm good I'm good are
you good I yeah yeah yeah go go go go go go but this is it this is a change this
is a change but you changed it I did change it what and why is this changing
again because it is you understand that it's harder for me to like go diagonal
and put stuff in the sink though why because it's like it's it's a kind of a
finicky little spot it's a tiny it's like two or three Frank it's like two
you already had to do that before to grab the plates yeah but it's so much
easier for me to scope a boom but like does this thing automatically plate
things if the plates are there I don't like it I don't like it see do you see
what's going on right now it's cuz there's a little area I'm playing on
this member I have control on an issue for me I'm playing controller so I have
like a tiny little window here let's go for it we're good rotate the potion so
it takes the pizza from above and not the right oh dude yeah what that's
exactly what should be happening cuz then no okay so you want to put the
portion or it's a yeah I get it so you can put that you can put pizzas there so
it sucks it that way okay and then I put the fries here yes no when he cooks in
the kitchen this sir please be smarter I checked out an hour ago I'm ready for
that 20,000 chefs in too many cooks in the kitchen we're going for it this is
it this is work this is it I mean we have when we're with this bar let's just
change the layout of our kitchen every service we'll get real used to that and
get real efficient hey your chats the one saying all that stuff I look over
here and I just see people talking but I look like a fucking like elf I wish my
child would call me a fucking elf right pizza pizza pizza yeah I look over here
and there's people to say like dude yes but boogers in his nose and stuff like
it yeah I need a french fry this is a pretty good start we have a lot of food
you're freaking french fry dude okay so I need you to put that french fry onto
that plate you okay bro thanks bro anything you need okay let me just get
this loaded up this is gonna mess me up okay so the we need a french fry toss a
french fry on that well we got a big party hey the soccer game okay I'm not
gonna do it everybody relax okay everyone was so ready to press the
button you're doing it anyways stop I didn't even do it a bunch of jokers what
we got we got two french fries oh yeah and now we need a french fry oh we have
enough pizza the party at Ford's gave it that was close
pizza that's a fucking pizza right there okay we need to put you two fries two
fries two fries it's good actually this is getting a little hairy two fries last
two parties here we need a pizza what you fry why would you say to me this is
getting hairy we have like a full duration you look at the left your
food's all done yeah but it's scary I need to fry fry right God some people
some people I feel like I'm underappreciated here at my job and I'm
looking for a new employment all right we need one fry that's all we need is
one fry that's what he says one fry and we got a frozen pizza in there if we
needed you good anyone looking to hire a totally incompetent doesn't know how to
place the portioner cook you've actually been doing a great job we just need one
fry so I'll give you a plate thank you there is the upgrade that allows you to
carry two plates as well that might make this if we can get it a lot easier for
you no that was okay you know the issue is we need there were three parties of
four at one point and they were sitting outside we need to have three tables of
waiting can we actually place tables outside I feel like I'm scared to add
any food no and it even says they take a lot of work yeah you cannot just remove
I'm gonna remove one of the tables and just make another four you don't have
room for three parties of four what do we do we could use that's yeah we could
use the small room you've heard the small room it has a lot of penalties I
don't think it matters anymore we have so much money it's really just like can
we finish yeah we still mean we have three levels to do so we need to make
sure we did this right we have this service thing we don't need we haven't
used this one time honestly we could get rid of the research I don't think we
know this whole room out yeah make it I'll move the freezer and everything in
the kitchen this is this is the expensive private dining area right this
is a way you just use this extra money for this table yeah that's where you go
to like really be in a kitchen room that gives me more room here too so that's
good the trash do we even use the trash really seats to oh this is a table
customers share but they eat longer because it's romantic we just use them
replace this three I think two fours like we still can have a group of two
show up I don't know if we can fit it anywhere we should put the tablecloth on
one is what people are saying we have one with a tablecloth no this is the
table table simple cloth it's like a it's like a whole two table napkins
prevent mess when you put it on a table just spend our money yeah we have so
much money okay but you have to actually I mean can eyes the very beginning just
put these everywhere I guess I mean I'm not researching anything cabinets please
just one per table okay yeah you restock them all right well whatever let's go
for it you think you got it and you I'm a pizza machine okay let's do it sir
we're gonna be some of the only people to ever complete the end as an
achievement ever point zero zero zero zero to have ever done it they also say
that uh stir in germa have never completed this before so this will be
actually a world first we need two slices of pizza ask her if they want the one
out the freezer you want a fresh one I don't want to fucking cook it another
pizza I can tell you're tired party for coming in and they're going to the fancy
room you ready oh fancy guys it's kind of late for me one French fry thank you
you got it you got it snuck snuck it in the back that's actually kind of far okay
we need just three pieces of pizza which I think we almost have it oh I gotta
clean that up no shit I think this game would be much worse if it didn't have
the when you finish things like that's keeping me going we're okay all right
it's just pizza so I'm gonna go for it let's start it okay
replay okay all right so these people want what do you guys want we need two
french fries oh pie and two french fries I don't know where my knife went I put
it back you can put a French around that one all right we need two french fries
hey you ready you got another fry yep now I need a slice thank you all right
what about these people one french fry okay can you grab a slice toss it over
there yeah maybe I got it oh you got it okay we need French fry this is it I
need another pizza yes you're gonna need another pizza going going going going
going going going going okay so I need a french fry I get a french fry on one of
these just a pizza we're good got it no fries let's go let's go oh only two more
levels we got it this is free how could it get harder how could how gonna become
harder in like two levels so we just do the same thing just you know grind it
out and do our be fucking jobbers we just gotta keep going two more levels
that's it a little coffee table anything that's
upgradable just do it I'm sure we'll wait here for a dining table this place
is like packed this is too much I don't think we do anything here yeah I think
we just finish I don't yeah we just go we're on a roll right higher with this
money I still got that pizza pre-made a month ago hey frozen pizza probably last
for months all right I'm gonna hold off for a second give you a little bit of
time to make that cheese and okay we need just pizza pizza feels like one of
the easier ones too cuz like I'm just it's all they want and I'm just banging
out pizzas it's okay I'm not gonna sit there was no reason to scream I bet I
didn't have to do that I just like I don't know I got the door there was a
lot of us we're good I didn't hear you scream this is actually a bad place for
this table you didn't hear me scream I think your mic cut it out like the
sudden noise we need one french fry yeah bet we do there you go buddy okay let's
go two french fries this time two french fries okay two french fries okay one
french fry what do they just keep wanting these french fries I might I'm
gonna have to make another pizza unless you want it I know keep the frozen one
for next that's the last level here we go I'm not gonna serve this yet until
you got that ready hey hold on oh okay we need just two slices we already got
it after this give me a hand picking up these plates because can you grab the
ones that they're about to dump on the left side next to you yeah yeah that's
another group another group I'm gonna have to make other pizza yes you are
okay so we need just we got it's already you got it right here no fries good all
right those plates out for open space only pizza perfect we're done last level
here we go well not quite two people left well they don't even count as real
people that's all good uh no fries yep thank God we're good all right so I want
is the last level gonna be hard at the last level I'm pretty sure you have to
fight Godfrey the first Elden Lord you guys have worked an eight hour shift
without any food true we just have worked a pizza shift here I'm alive nine
hours um is there decorations because if we could really use the last two if
there is this is a decoration night only candle now we can just reroll until we
get them decorations no what is this no decoration oh man that's actually
bonkers hold up you're gonna get it stores identical pieces of food yes so
you could like chop four potatoes and put them on that I think that's cool but
you've just added a variable in the last level just be careful yeah it's a space
I didn't need okay maybe you can't reroll yeah I don't think you can reroll
into look like just decorations doesn't expanded bin stir is going to throw for
views I I don't think that's happening I'm winning for views because winning
and being cool is also poggers all right so you don't have to just like cheat on
your wife to make it to live sure we have should we have some music for this
one you know what let me let me I'm gonna I'm good if you want to music you
can I've got mine already now let's go I'm ready we have to lock in here this is
a victory here coming up all right all right start off right I'm gonna hold off
we do have the frozen pizza french fry I'm in the zone no I don't do we've been
doing this like that's like five and a half hours I don't want to blow this
right now dude his pizza making efficiency I have never seen anything
like this two fries that's a big curveball and a big party three that's
fine I've got all my got all my fries already lined up already chopped okay I
need two fries thank you and can you know what can you bring a fry over here
with with yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah just just just pie we gotta start a
whole new pipe okay we're good I'm not gonna take that yet all right I need one
fry need one fry need a new pie yeah yeah yeah can I reach that slice one fry
just pizza I'm a I'm a bucket okay yes pizza clean it all right we're good one
fry and then that's it now we got one more party okay can you grab a couple
pieces here we have enough pizza we need one more slice wait wait we need one
more slice frozen put in the oven okay go nice need one fry one fry and we're
good that's game over we got it that's it we did it no you don't no you don't
no no you never make another pizza for the rest of your life five-star restaurant we did
a five-star man I'm a five-star man when you complete this run you'll be able to
convert three of your cards into a franchise and continue in a new location
they really got us capitalism really got us we just beat the ball we're off the
train chopped off her flower pots or 50% chance that blueprints can be purchased
again I mean if we I think we're done I mean we're done but let's just take the
flowers because we weren't getting decorations when we want them so what
happens now what happens now is I you probably dinner I think it's just like a
new game plus so you just go keep going oh you you go as many days over time day
I'm good I'm good well that was really fun yeah I like that was intense simple
yet intense enjoyable I could okay so with two people it's kind of manageable I
think with three or four people that's where this game becomes kind of a mess I
think it's harder the more people you have well I've never played like
overcooked either which I know a lot of people really like in this genre yeah
this is this is not this one looked on simple I like the idea this because it
was like a consistent one kitchen yeah could work in but overcooked after like
I enjoyed that a lot so maybe we could try it sometime no that's cool and we'll
um we'll figure out the Elden Ring thing that sounds fun yeah and you're gonna be
playing Jade cocoon until then I mean cool I'll try to get it cool cool yeah
it's always a pleasure dude I'll see you probably they don't know next week week
or soon I'll see you when I see you yeah have a good one take it easy
that's stir buddy yeah you know y'all know stir is what I do you all know me
come on oh I thought he just booted me he did very cool always fun to hang out
with stir we will see him again probably in the next couple weeks do some Elden
Ring Elden Ring randomizer I'm very tired and I'm very hungry so I am gonna
get out of here I think that guy would probably like Ludwig don't you think
it's like like caught in 4k right like this Jesus I'm getting fucking old
probably yeah all right I'll see you guys later the net the plan for the next
stream is just get out of here keep an eye on the sus it'll be the Thursday or
Friday probably Friday and we are going to do some old console stuff so I got
driver one I have a dozen old Xbox games we're gonna load up the Xbox I have
enter the matrix for the Xbox we're gonna do the thing we've done before kind
of back in like 2017 2018 we're doing a console fuckface night the same rules
30 minutes each game you have to move on unless I get addicted should be a
good time I have a lot of shit that's still over there so should be a wild
night that will be Friday we're gonna start with driver so the person that's
been want me to play that for a long time if I end up making a Thursday just
keep an eye on the sauce like I said I it'll be Thursday or Friday but plan on
Friday you still have the New Year's Eve poll in yeah that's true that's true
I'll take care of that right now thanks for hanging out late night I know been
long stream longer well not necessarily long long but you know I kind of had to
see that through let me let me do that right now that guy's really fun it does
remind me of overcooked but it reminds me of overcooked but you know I don't
know I almost like it a little better than overcooked because overcooked is
more individual levels you know in increasing difficulty different
environments each level was a little different that felt like you were
running your own rogue like restaurant so that's fun I like it I can't imagine
doing some of the more difficult things though overcooked is fun too though and
that that firefighter game was fun as well that I didn't was in dislike that
game don't let stir put words in my mouth thanks for hanging out appreciate
it see you guys on Friday call your mother get some sleep some of you
probably been up for a pretty long time and I'll see you soon take it easy