How's it going? I'm not late. I'm out maybe, I am 60 seconds, 30 seconds, maybe if that.
Would you ask what size toothpick do you use? I don't, I don't think I've ever used a toothpick
based on, buying it based on its size. I think I've only ever, I think I've only ever bought
toothpicks maybe three times in my entire life. And I really mean that maybe two or three times
total. Where's driver? All right, hold on. Just wait, I'll explain. I'll talk about it. Just wait a
minute. I wanted to ask how the tortoise you hit an Elden Ring but you never finished off is doing.
Will you just go drink a glass of water? Does somebody know? Does somebody say true?
No, they didn't. Did I make that up? No, nobody did. I made it up. True. Change your pinned tweet.
I can't, I can't yet. All right, let's talk. Here's the deal. I was going to play driver today.
I decided not to because I was going to play it on PC but the PC version is kind of all messed up
on any of the newer operating systems. There's a patch you can get that fixes a lot of stuff
but it still has resolution issues. So what I've decided to do is this, not today
but I don't know later on this coming week, this coming weekend, maybe something like that.
I'm just going to get it from PlayStation 1 and we're going back. We're going back to PlayStation
1 Xbox old console Insanity Night. Kicking it off with driver one. We're going to do a,
is that considered retro? I don't know. Retro in my brain and maybe it's because we're,
you know, different ages but when I think of retro I think of Pong. I think of the NES. I think of
the Super Nintendo. Is retro PS2? Is that considered retro or is that some in-between period?
How many years have to go by for something to be retro? 10, 15, 20 years? 15, 20? I don't think a
decade. I think a decade is not long enough. Please at least try King's Field 1 and 2.
Pong is vintage. PS2 would be retro. That's true. Did you start Mob Psycho? I did not.
No, I did not. PS3 would be retro if it was a decade. Yeah, that's not enough. These would
be at least 15, 20. But anyways, that is what's happening this weekend. So today, change of plans
today. Gonna just play something fun, something cozy. I've, you know, had my eye on a few games.
Landed on this one called A Little to the Left. It's a game about organizing. I think it's kind
of in the same world as that unpacking game, I think. So we'll see. I don't know. It's like
a puzzle game where you have to organize things correctly. I think. He's gonna mauled. I don't
think so. So we're gonna have a chill day today. Just gonna relax, play a little bit. And this
takes us not very long. We'll do something else. Are you gonna play Tetris? I'm never gonna play
Tetris. Jerma, don't chill. Why not? I can't play Tetris. We've talked about this a thousand
times. I cannot play Tetris. I put down the first row and then just start shaking. I just hate it.
I have to get out. I don't even get past one cycle of dun dun dun dun dun dun dun. One cycle of that
and I'm gone. I just, honestly, I played Tetris just to hear that song once. And I go, all right,
that was fun. No more. Played Beam NG? I did a few months ago, right? A couple months ago.
Let's play Checkers. Frog Detective, you liar. The longer you wait for Frog Detective when it
actually happens, you're going to freak out. You should play with chat GPT. You know, maybe I will
as soon here, but I don't have that prepared. You should play Pong. Pong to me sounds more like a
punishment stream. Like you gotta play Pong for an hour. I want you to be honest. Would you play Pong
for one straight hour? I'm seeing, I'm seeing a ton of nos. No, no, no, no, no way. No way.
Okay. What would it take for you to play Pong for one hour? Would someone have to pay you to play
Pong? Not versus the person. No, versus the computer. Pong versus the computer for one hour.
100 bucks, 50 bucks, 100 bucks, $500 dude. What? Actually, I mean, that like sucks. Playing Pong
and that's all you can do for an hour. That's true. That actually would be, that'd actually,
yeah, that'd be hard to sit there for more than like 30, 40 minutes. 50 bucks, 40 bucks. I would
do it for a Philly cheesesteak. You know, that's actually pretty good. A real one. You mean like
from Philadelphia, not the people that just say Philly cheesesteak, but we're in Cincinnati and
it's not even close. Do you mean like a real one from Philadelphia? I think it's, I would play Pong
for five hours to get one of those. Yeah. I would play, I would do a full five hour Pong stream.
If a, like one of the best Philly cheesesteaks from Philadelphia teleported hot, fresh, ready to go
in the middle of my room is worth it for me. Like, and I'm talking nice and hot,
fresh. They just made it and it's from one of the best places in Philadelphia.
That'd be worth it. No, not on the floor. I mean, I put my hands out and it goes,
I put both my hands out and it does the camera trick that was shocking back in the fifties,
where you just hold your arms out and, and then they cut and then they put the sandwich there
and they roll again and they make a sound effect and the actor kind of shifts a little and like
moves their arms up or down a little bit and it's just there in their hands. That's what I want.
What the fuck is a cheesesteak? What? Oh my God. Really? You don't know if that is. I mean,
I wouldn't eat one every day. I'm a new viewer. Hi. That's interesting considering you've been
subscribed for 29 straight months. I don't know if you're on somebody else's computer right now, but
you've been here for years. I don't know what a cheesesteak is either. A cheesesteak is
shaved or chopped steak that you cook on a flat top and you put maybe some onions in it. I don't
know. It depends on who you talk to. You put some cheese on it, slide it into a big, nice hoagie
roll, cheese whiz on it. I don't know. I would, I, I've never had a real one. I've just had
imitations. No, you don't put milk on it. What are your thoughts on schnitzel? I'm a new viewer as
well. Um, schnitzel's awesome. Anything that's breaded and, you know, smashed to a point where
it's crispy and delicious. Of course it's going to be great. What about haggis? No, I've never,
I'm not going to eat haggis. All right. Hey, is this, is this food AMA hour or are we playing a
game? Well, it's a chill stream. We can, whatever. All right. Okay. A little to the left. Let's,
let's play it. See how it is. If you can hear it. You can now. There we go. Okay. So this game is
going to be super cool. I don't know. I don't have, I'm not going to eat sir. What is it? Sir
Stroming? No. Oh, eat sir Stroming. You mean the thing where people literally take a can opener,
puncture it, start to turn. And then all of a sudden everybody in the area goes,
no, it's a, every single time I've ever seen a sir. Oh, we're going to do a sir Stroming thing.
They puncture the can. It goes something that can fill the air with that much smell in less
than one second is something I don't want to put near my face. Okay. I don't want that near my face.
Your face cam is on right now. All right. So how does this work? I'm ready to organize. Would you
ever eat haggis? No, I'm not. I'm not going to eat foods. I don't want to eat home sweet home.
All right. This is going to be cool. Are you guys ready? There he is. Okay. So how do I do this?
Where's the fucking safe? Where's the fucking safe? Is that right? Oh, I did. Okay. I actually,
I had to do, Oh wait, I have to organize this. Should I do, honestly, it's just all going in
there without any rhyme or reason because I don't do, are you going to, that's going to get messed
up anyways. That your pet goes over there, picks out whatever they want and then just knocks the
whole thing over. Is that right? Oh, this color up here. Okay. Hold on. I feel like I'm watching a
baby sensory video. All right. Hold on. This is, it's getting a little hard. How do I know
where the beginning is? It's right there, right? Yeah. I had it. Here we go. It's right there. I
had it right. I had it correct. This is, I didn't know I had to, I thought they had to be touching.
There you go. This shit drives me crazy in real life. Every time I, I, something on the wall,
like a painting or a picture or something, and you have to get it sorted, but the music just
changed. This is by size. Is it big on the bottom? Okay. It's big on the bottom like that. That kind
of felt good. Slow down. I can't keep up. You're going to be all right. Where's the ding? Is it,
does it want to buy thickness or does it want to buy height or thickness? Here it is. I got it.
It was height. Shit. I should have gone, I should have gone bottom to top. Sick. You legitimately
look like a toddler. That's very weird. Stamps. Yes. What's going on? Oh, oh, these are animals
up here. Okay. Now I sort them. No, we're good. This is, I like this. Are you seriously faking?
Okay. You don't, I'm sorry, but you don't open up like a chill game and just like relax and play it
and have somebody be annoyed with how you are chilling. Are you really mad at how I'm chilling
right now? How I'm chilling? Hey bro, dude, ah, you're not chilling the right way. You're
not doing it right. You can't, you can't tell somebody how to chill. This is not a backseat
scenario. This is a chilling out scenario. You don't walk into somebody's room. Nah, dude,
you're doing it wrong. You're not chilling out right. Hey, did you smoke yet? You smoked today?
No. Ah, fucking idiot. You fucking idiot. All right. Listen, I'm chilling again, but you're
going to walk in my room. You're going to walk in my room, holding one in. You know what I mean?
Like you just walk in. What's up, dude? Fucking cough out that smoke. And like you, you, why didn't
you just breathe that hit up before you walked in the room? What is this? What is this for kids?
Is this a kids game? Bro, I'm chilling. Don't tell me how to, how to do it. Oh, I thought it was
making a circle. I thought it was making a big circle. I'm trying to make a circle. Don't tell
me how to chill. This is not what I thought it was going to be. Did I just do that wrong, but still
got it right? What am I doing? Oh, what do these say? Are these colors? Why is two written upside?
No, is that a two upside down? What is that? What is one? This one's two, one, two, three, four, five.
All right. What does that have to do with the colors? I got it. You didn't, you did not know
that until I just did that. You actually did not know until you saw me do it. Idiot. There we go.
I like this game calendar. All right. The second this gets to be, they're going to, they're going
to pull a papers, please. Isn't it? It's going to get so hard. I think it's going to get too much
for me. We'll find out. I'm chilling. Yes, I am. Once papers, please introduced the fourth thing
you had to pay attention to. I just let everybody in. Once it was like ID, birth certificate, work
form. Once it got to be three or four different things, I just was like, you know what? Let me
look at the ID and then stamp you or whatever. All right. Speaking of this. All right. Here we go.
This is, wait, what? Whoa. That actually had, you had to pull it. Look at this. You have to rip it
off. I don't, I don't get it. Or one, two, three, four. I don't get it. One, two, the star is on day
three and day 12. 12 is divisible by three, three, six, nine, 12 by four. So therefore this has to go
on the four. I don't know. Three. Um, hold on. Three, 12. That's nine days. So one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine. I for some reason thought I had to do stuff up here. Okay. So this
is one, this doesn't show up anymore. Okay. So 10, so 10 days. So then this has to be here. Wait,
what? Oh no, it's just nine days for everything. Okay. That's be legible. I don't have any more
of these ones though. Doesn't have to be perfect. Wait, what? What's happening? That's what I meant
to do. This reminds me of math class. Please stop. You're going to just something in my eye
every one second. Why'd you do that? I cursed you to have something in your eye. All right. The
game's called, uh, a little to the left, right? We're going to do this by size. What did you stop
that? Reverse it. Shit. That's actually kind of hard. I just wanted to do a sorting algorithm.
Yeah. Like he's the same size. That not it. It's not this height. There's more things than how
tall something is. Oh God. Wait a minute. How do I know what the first one is? How do I know what
the first one is? Oh shit. Okay. I just got to get it. Let him cook. What am I doing? I, it's a
mirror. It's a mirror. I'm sorry, but at this point, if I'm setting up my bookshelf and I am
looking at this shit, I'm just spinning spine in and we're going height. We're doing spine in
by height. Is this the middle? This has to be the middle then, right? There wouldn't be a big
flourish in the middle like this. This is a big flourish. This is a big flourish. It has to be
the middle. This is, it has to be over here. Why am I taking so long doing this? This has to be in
the middle, but how do I know what the end, what, how do I know which one's the end? Why even make
this? Why can't you just make it a name? Make it like, oh, like, like Arthur or like Gregory.
Just make it so I can put it easy. I'm confused. It's so, it's, it's a mirrored image. So that
means some of this shit cannot be over here. I'm fucking the whole thing up because nothing can,
how do I, what can attach to this? This edge is too tall. See what I mean? Like this is,
this edge is too tall. Nothing can fit here. Is that it? No, it's not. That can't be it, right?
I don't, I don't, I don't understand it. This is too many symbols on the screen. See, if I was in
my bed with my iPad, I would be sitting there going like this. It's fucking stupid. This is
so fucking dumb. Fuck this, this game. This is stupid. This is a fucking dumb game. And then I
would, I would eventually figure it out and go, oh, this is cute. I like this. Mods, what do I do?
Give me some guidance. I don't understand. I don't know what, I don't know what the break point is
for the mirror because like it did, it just goes like this. I don't get it. This, then this is not
the middle then it can't be. You all said, yes, this is the middle. You are lying to me. There
ain't nothing that fits here. The only thing that fits here is this. This is it. Nothing else can
fit here. You had it before. Compare the height of the two mirrored pieces. Height and, height and
pattern. The hell? Oh, I've thought it was just, I thought it was just pattern this time. Wait,
height and pattern? This is the worst gamer moment. I just don't understand. It can't be height. No,
it can't. Oh, yeah. Yeah. It's a chill stream, but I'm just going to tell, I'm telling you.
Some of you guys would open this, but if you're on your fucking iPad and guess what you're going
to do? You're going to go, I think I'd rather just go eat something. I get a snack and you're going
to press the home button. It's going to disappear and you can just run away. You get to go, you get
to go like this. It's gone. It's just pattern. I'm going to blow through the rest of this fucking
game. I'm telling you right now. I promise you. It's just like the different squigglies. My brain
just is like, they're all the same. I said this year we're going to chill. We're going to do a
little bit more chilling. I'm going to be stuck here forever. I just don't understand what they
want me to do. Just pattern, but it's height and pattern. No shot. You're going to do it. The only,
the two curly ones are at each end and the one everyone says is the middle is the middle. All
the rest are doubles. Yeah, but that's what I have, but nothing else can connect to this. Watch this.
Yeah, that's what I had. See, but nothing else can connect to this. Bro, if it's this, I'm going to
be real mad. This one doesn't fit. This one, I'm going to be pissed if it's this one. These don't
fit. These actually don't fit. This is a fucked up weird image and this is not, it doesn't fit.
It is it, isn't it? It's it. It is it. This doesn't look like it's supposed to fit. This doesn't look
like it's supposed to fit. What even is this picture? They're all the same image in my head.
If I don't beat the next one in less than one minute, I will something. Dude, these all blend
into the same picture in my head. I can't see anything but the same line. They're all the same
line. What side is this one on? Where does this one go? Dude, where does this one go? This one
can't be here, right? Like this, because it's, there's two of each one. So there has to be one
on each side, right? This is correct. So where do these fucking random ass pieces go? Calm down,
switch them. What do you want me to do? What's wrong with this? I got it. I got it. Give me one
minute. Give me one minute. Literally one minute. Come on. That's correct right here, please. Wait,
what is it saying? That's not right. I was just, that's how is it not flat? One minute told you.
Oh shit. No, no. These little squiggly lines. I can't do the squiggly lines. Oh boy. Everybody
put it into, don't, no, don't even. You know what I just realized? I'm the guy that walks into the
room holding in the fucking blunt smoke. I just realized it right now. It's me. I'm the guy that
leans in. Who is this? Ah, now fuck that. I'm gonna go play Super Mario. So this is correct here.
It's got a line here. No, I mean, this is correct. This might be bait though. It's in the wrong spot,
but. Ah, look at that. What is this even supposed to be a picture of? What was that? What is this
thing? What was that image? It was a doodle. Yeah, but I mean, what was that? I'm trying to make
pictures. That's my problem. All right. What does this want me to do? Oh, guys, it's by sharpness.
I got it. It's by sharpness. Oh, the eraser. Guys, we're not getting any dings. It's not
eraser. It's not sharpness. I mean, there's the rainbow. How come I can't? There's no dings. Oh,
right. What is this? By thickness? Height? Thickness? It's definitely gonna be size. Small
to big. Thinness to widthness. Horizontal length. If it's horizontal length, this is it. All right,
it has to be. This is the maybe biggest horizontal length first. That's what I would think. Yeah,
horizontal length. I guess not. Maybe smallest horizontal length. But I had that already,
though. This thing. It's not going to be small to large, right? What? I'm confused. How is it?
It just wants me to spread them out? Is it? What's the pattern here then? Wait a minute. I think
it's going to exactly fit on the screen. Yeah. Okay. All right. I got it. I got it. I got it.
There it is. Great. I'm going. I'm going thinness. This is where we're just talking centimeters. We
can see all the sweat stains all over you. This is a bright. This came right out of the dryer.
Yeah, I know there's patterns on it, but I can't you do this more than somebody said you can do
this more than like a few ways. I can't do it by thickness. Yes, you can. Yeah, I can. I don't have
to do it by the pattern. It's so close. These three and these four are the problem. Every,
every book has it. Listen, listen, everybody. I'm going to tell you, you can do each of these
puzzles three or four different ways. It doesn't have to be the patterns. It can just be how it
can be. You can be length wise. It can be the the witness. It could be the length. It could be the
pattern. I'm trying to do it by the witness of the books. Book girth. All right. I'll just do it.
But is that true? Oh, it was people just lying to me. All right. I'll do it by pattern line,
line, line. This one is our glass, our glass line line. These lines should be the height of the line
top to bottom. That'd be a weird way to do this. Is that actually what it is? Oh my God. I thought
I could do it more than one way. I'd put the pencil shavings back on the pencil. I need to
get them all out here. What do these all look like? The one, the line. I think I understand it. Hold
on. Two, one, two, three, no, three, four, one, two, three, four, five. Don't overthink it. What
do the symbols mean? Overthinking, overthinking, overthinking, overthinking is the complexity of
the pattern. That's what I was thinking. This is the most complex one, but I don't think that's
correct. What's with the shavings though? Why are they here? What's the point of these? This is the
most, this is the least complex line. Just do it by height. I tried that the other time and it didn't
work. The pencil shavings are the pattern. All right, but how do, what am I supposed to, right?
Because it's like squiggle, squiggle, squiggle. Just do trial and just brute force it. Try it by
height. I think that's going to do anything. Get all this shit out of the way. How do I match these
up? Where am I supposed to place it? Like this one is without a doubt right here, but how do I,
what am I supposed to, where, wait, what do I put it? Throw them away. Clean them up. Size of the
shavings with their shape, but wouldn't, this is correct though. This is like, this is like just a
small one, right? It's just decorative. It's, wait, is it actually just decorative? Let them above or
below maybe. There ain't enough shavings. Throw them off the screen. What just happened? That's
what I was supposed to do? I don't know who this artist is.
But your music is bad. I don't know like what record this is, but it's the same two loops.
Oh wow. Okay. Okay. I got it. Okay. But hold on. I thought that was different tracks.
Call that one looking out the window over an airplane. Whoa. Hold on. What kind of soup is
this? Shit. I'm sorry. I just went like, I got mad. So this is the left side of the can. This is
the middle of the can, right? Like that. And this is the right side of the can. And what does it want
me to do? I wonder. This pattern here is this. I don't know what that's trying to tell me.
What's my IQ? More than you. Last time I took it, it was 70, 71. You're overthinking it. Am I though?
I'm overthinking it. I don't, I'm not trying to overthink it. I'm just thinking in my brain,
it wants me to show the whole can, right? It wants me to show the whole can. I would need that,
this. Is that not what it wants me to do? Oh wait, what it wants this? Um, make it 71. I don't have
a 71 IQ. It's like, it was 121 when I took it. Um, like now it's been like 10 years, 15 years.
It was 124, went down to 121, which means it's definitely like 115 now, 110. I've, there's no
way I've gotten smarter. I've only gotten slower. Um, sorted by flavor. It's only one can. How would
you arrange this in your kitchen? I would be like, um, first of all, I'd say why, why the heck is
this not Bertoli? It's not one can. What? No, that can't be correct. I thought it was with all the
other stuff. What was with all the other things? Did I get Luigi'd? All right, so we got three.
Let's go over here. A lot and a lot. One, two, three, four, five. Okay. Is it by the amount,
the level of the liquid? Because look, there's three, four, four. Three, four, four, five. One,
two, three, four, four, six. Right? Or should I do, do it by the level of the liquid? I'll try
level of liquid. All right. It's level of liquid. I, I was, I, why have this, that, whatever. There
it is. Oh, this one here. I didn't see this one. I didn't see that. Give it to me. It's right there.
Stack them. But what, I, what, I want to do it by length. Oh, nobody stacks spoons like that.
I got it. I got it. I get to do it from the top. Okay. So I'll just, here it is right there. Okay.
That's correct. This is not correct. That is not correct. That is also not correct. That might be
correct. And it is almost there. Not quite, quite, not quite, not quite. At least he's trying his
best. I don't know about you guys, but puzzle games like this, you're supposed to just kind
of hang out and do it. Nobody just goes, ding. Why didn't you do it faster? Okay. So this is
a bunch of sand into not a lot of sand. I don't think it matters. It doesn't matter what, what
side it starts. Speed run. Thank you. I figured that out really quick. It's not like this was in
the trailer on steam. There's more. I feel like the crumbs in the middle. No, I'll clean it up.
Right. Why, why is there my, what did I do? Minus two pinned by me? Why did I, what, I didn't
pin this. What do you mean pinned by me? I, when did I pin that? He found out. I did not pin this
message. I genuinely don't, I did not do that. How do I unpin this? Did one of the mods do that? I'm,
I'm being very serious. Did a mod do that? Or did I somehow accidentally do that? How did I do that?
I don't even see it. How would a mod do that? It says pinned by you. Oh my God. Okay. So that
was not supposed to be there. So let me explain what happened. I have three monitors and when I
move the chat, the chats, the chats, my chat window. Wow. You got to be kidding me. How long
is it there for? I'm not fucking around. I promise you this. When I, so I, anytime you hear the music
stop like this, it means I've clicked out of the window. So I probably clicked over cause the chat
is right up against the right side of the, of my left monitor, which is over here. This is where
you guys are. And the pin this message is right on the space that connects the monitors. So I must
have just put my mouse over, gone to the other monitor, clicked to get to the other monitor and
clicked pin a random message. And it was minus two. I, I, okay. I thought a mod did that. Whatever.
That's so funny. I can't, I don't know. Should that be that easy to do that? Hold on. I'm uh,
what's that? Oh, yeah. This is the, uh, this is the Xbox. Yeah. Let me just take that. One Xbox.
What? There's no other fruit. Where's the other fruit? All right. One of the workers was just
having fun. Excuse me, sir. What are you doing? I figured it'd be easier if I took all the price
tags off of every item and just went, I just, I just wanted to just get everything in the bag
and then scan everything. Sir. One of those is a TV. Yeah. I mean, I figured it would be easier.
Just get them all on one thing. All right. Do I throw these away? I do. Should I sort these by
my favorites? I think this is pretty accurate. This is from most favorite to least favorite.
Who cares? Just finish it. Chill. Somebody said, dude, you got to do it by the curl factor. Would
this be all the way over here then? I mean, this is technically a curl. These are the most, these
are super swirled. I don't know. Is that what they want? Or is it just by, then these would go first
then? No, they wouldn't. Is it, but is this a curl or is this a twist? You know what I mean? Yeah.
Okay. No, I had it right. I had it right. Give me one second. Give me one second. I'm not trying
to go for the world record. Line it up with the bird. I don't get this one. You have to line it
up with the background. The same image. Was that one as easy as I think it was? Stop. Get this cat
out of here. Stop. I don't want to, what do I do about the cat? Who uses a placemat? I don't. I sit
there and I eat it in my lap in front of the couch. Oh, in front of the couch? I don't know. I just
sit there like this and I eat in front of the couch. Yeah. You see, I sit on the TV. I put the
couch and I sit on this big square thing. It's called a television and I sit on top of it.
It's pretty comfortable and I watch the couch. You know, I can never do breakfast like this
for one reason. I'm kind of an all in or nothing kind of person. There would need to be two handfuls
of blueberries here in the egg. I don't like the, oh, just like three blueberries. Just give me,
give me two full handfuls of blueberries, like six strawberries in the egg. You know,
forget about the toast. Get the toast out of here. You know, maybe like one corner of the toast.
Give her the oranges and then way more of, way more of the fruits. Like another handful,
two handfuls of blueberries. By the way, there'd be two or three, there'd be three eggs here.
Probably two eggs, two eggs, handful of blueberries. Maybe not even, maybe like not even a strawberry.
I don't like heavy breakfasts either. I'm not a big, big, I like yogurt. Yogurt in the morning
is, I think it's just, just doesn't fill you up. Keeps you going. This dude eats blueberries and
eggs. All right. Where does this go? Do I have to make a shape with this or something? Why don't I
just do the funny thing? There it is. Here you go, kid. I wouldn't eat this. I feel like you were
trying to cast a spell on me. I can't move this one. It's okay. So it's got to go. Fuck out of
here. Leave now. Leave. No, actually stay. No, I mean like get out of here. You've been, you've
been in my brain. Fuck with me. Is it based on the river? It's definitely based on the water,
right? No, don't leave. Okay. So this is underwater. I'm going to imagine that's probably
like here. What does a river start? This is in the air. Is it air to up in the air to down on
the river to where the wolf is? You know what I'm saying? It has to be something like that.
How am I supposed to get it right? What's the, this is correct. But how do I, this is right.
But why, there's no dings. Like line them up in the better spot. That's correct. I mean,
it has to be, right? Yeah, this is definitely right. Or is this not right? How does the middle
connect? Uh, it does? Over here maybe? This feels like the logical place for this to go. Is this
wrong? It's not that right? Am I? Oh, I think it is. Shit. I think that is right. Isn't it?
But then how does this connect to something like that? This technically still needs to be down,
right? God damn it. Okay. I got it. This is it. Okay. I just had to move it around. Whoa. Okay.
Hold on. Is there anything else on this bottle? All right. There's something else on this bottle.
God damn it. All right. What's all the way in the back? This is not like that, right? Like this,
like that. Does it want me to connect these? No way. I don't get it. I don't understand.
Is the goal to make it one unit or just have them all connected to each other? I can
bring them to the front. Oh my goodness. Wait a minute. Okay. Hold on. This, everything changes
now. This is fucked. Mayo on the left. Here? Then where does this go? There's a worst stream.
You're not talking. Every stream I'm supposed to scream into the microphone as loud as I can.
Is that what you want me to do? Chill stream. Relax. I'm stumped. I actually don't. I actually
don't know what the hell to do. Somebody said, bro, close the fridge. You're just sitting there
like dragging the mayo, then the wine and the milk. Like, dude, you need to close the fridge
and you need to chill out. I get what it wants me to do, but I don't get what it wants me to do.
Does that make any sense? I have to do this like piece by piece. All right. Because it's like,
this is gray. This is gray, right at the bottom. This is gray, but this connects to the yellow
part here. Spread them out in a line. Okay. So this line lines up with this line, right? Yeah.
Okay. This line lines with this line, but it's the wrong color. Mayo goes on the left side.
I mean, like over here. So is this bait? This has to be like this, right? Or is this here just for
this? The milk goes behind the mayo like that. Then where does this go? Mayo. Holy shit. The
milk and the mayo. There are no overlaps. What do you mean that? How is that possible? No,
don't overlap. No overlapping. The patterns just connect. Where? You need to place them next to
one on top of each other where the patterns line up. Yeah, that's what I'm trying to do.
But like this pattern is not complete. You know what I mean? Right here, this pattern is not
complete and I don't know how to complete it like this. Wait, that doesn't make any sense though.
No, this is wrong. This is still wrong. I don't get it. I'm about to quit. I'm about to quit
and play a different game. What the fuck? No overlapping. Milk next to mayo. I don't understand.
Let's do a go play Super Mario Brothers. All right, here's what we're going to do. All you
brilliant chat players. I'm going to drag this and you tell me when to stop. No, that's not going to
help. Look at the shadows. What do you mean there's no shadows? Mayo. There are multiple
patterns that have to be lined up. You notice the milk into the wine. The mayo goes into the milk.
Yeah, but like some of these don't add up though. You know what I mean? Like is it just to be
touching? They just have to touch this? Like is it just aligning the squares and shit?
Is that that can't, that cannot be what it is. That, that actually cannot be what it is.
I, there's no way. No, this can't be. It actually can't be. I'm trying to like connect to everything
so it's a one lap. There's no way. It can't be. No, it actually can't be. Is that not it? I feel
like this is so close. This is not it. No overlapping, but it's, it is aesthetically
pleasing to me. What are you talking about? Why? You've got to be kidding me. There's no way.
It's just pattern. I thought it was like match everything and like connect all the dots and like
the colors all combined into one amalgamous image. I, no, you've got to be kidding me.
Way overthinking it. I thought it was going to turn into a different picture. Well, like connect
all the, why was all the squiggly lines there? They were just labels, bro. They were just labels.
They're not supposed to be anything. I'm connecting a big, but we, the first part of the game,
it had all the squiggly lines that you connected together. Let's see what happened here. Cat got
up on the shelf. Cat knocks over vase, breaks the vase. Person that's sitting on the couch just goes,
holy shit freaks out, knocks their wine over. Wait, that's not a vase? I feel like these pictures
aren't connected to each other. This seems the most accurate to me. Or is it like, oh, look,
the cat is kind of plotting. The cat's plotting. The cat touches stuff sometimes. And this time,
yeah, like sometimes the cat looks at stuff. Sometimes the cat touches stuff. The cat touched
this vase, smashed it. And then that happens somehow. Is it by color? All right. Without
overthinking it, what am I, what am I looking at here? Cat knocks that down. Cat knocks this
down. Cat breaks this. The cat is knocking all this stuff over. And this is just the cat looking
at an object. This is the cat starting to play with an object. So does it need to be in a weird
order? Or is this, is this it? Do I just have it? I know I had, I just did it in a weird, I think
this is where I'm going to move on to a different game. More squiggly line bullshit. I think they're
supposed to fit into each other. You know what I mean? Like fit into each other. What does this
one fit into? That? How blind are you? As every one of these puzzles has had squiggly lines, it's
had different colors, it's had different shapes. I mean, I have this, but what can connect to the,
this has to be the end, right? And nothing else can go there. What am I missing here? What am I
missing? I'm looking over at the mod chat and it's, everybody's doing this in the mod chat.
They're posting Soprano gifs. What are you guys talking about? What are you guys talking about
over here? Sorry. We're currently Soprano posting. Is somebody watching it? No, watch my stream.
Excuse me. Discussing an episode. All right, now you know it's time. I got to move on to a new game.
When the mods are discussing an episode of the Sopranos. That's actually fucking hilarious.
All right, so what's, what's going on here? This is so close yet so far. Wrong. This has to be in
between, right? What is happening? That's not correct. It has to be. What's wrong?
Wrong. Sponge has to go in the bucket. Sponge in between three and four.
Sponge what? Sponge red bottle. There's a nice rectangle there.
I would think we'd match up with the green. There's a rectangle gap. Move it up higher. I,
oh my god. I just accidentally did that. What kind of a sponge sits up like that?
Oh my god. This is going to be impossible. Get out of here. Get out. Get out. Get out.
Can I get out? I'm not going to be. This is impossible. Hold on. Hold on. Let me just get
them all in here. I actually like this one. That was, I love that one. That one was awesome. That
one was really fun too. Oh, I'm going to love this one. These, they get, they're getting better.
They're actually getting so much more fun. I can't wait to do this one. I'm not even kidding.
Yes. Now I just got to get it ready. Why is it doing that? Get in there. What do you mean?
Why can't these fit? And that is a perfect draw. This is perfect. What's wrong with this?
Does anybody else take all their clean silverware? Pick it all up in a gigantic tube in your hand.
Open up the silverware drawer and just drop it all in. No, I don't do that either.
I'm just trying to catch people that do. It's just magic's already opening up the drawer.
Just dump it. That would be such a mess. Stack them up. I can't turn them. I can't stack them.
It doesn't want, it won't let me turn it. They're just, oh wait, I get it. I thought it was supposed
to be inside. See these, these are going much smoother now. Oh dear. Oh dear. Actually,
this is not as bad as I thought it was going to be. Light bulb stream, light bulb tier list.
No, there we go. Hmm. Thank you. Oh dear. Oh, this one's going to be bad. I just got to focus.
The scissors have to go away. Getting the scissors in is a big deal. Get all the big
goofy objects in first. Like this is a big goofy object and it goes right here. Is that all right?
Any more big goofy objects? Yep. Pen has to go lengthwise. Okay. Yep. Big goofy object up here.
This also is lengthwise. It's going to go here. Big goofy pen. Hmm. What about this weird thing?
All right. Where does this go? Perfect. Glasses over here. Oh yeah. Actually, no, not quite.
This is not fit. Proprietary fondue fork, by the way. What is this shape? Something is oddly
shaped like this. What is it? What has that weird shape? Now it's a bunch of miscellaneous
bullshit. There you go. A bunch of miscellaneous shit can go in here. Okay. Wait, there's more.
Perfect. Not quite, but I'll fix it. That's fine. Whatever. It fits. It's fine. Almost done. There
it is. Shit. Give me the ding. I'll take a ding right now. What's wrong? Oh, all right. I got it.
This is fun. I like it when they just put things in boxes and not shit. What? How did I get it?
Got it. There's no orange. It was leaking from. Oh, okay. Oh, this is going to be a good one.
I don't know what to do. The big ones go in the middle, maybe? Like stack. Thank you. We got a
raid. Hey, Hazer. Thanks for the raid. Welcome. I don't know. Was that like a two hours ago?
Thanks for the raid, though. We've got a good stream. We're just chilling out today.
Let's hang out stream. One, two, three, four. I mean, this is five, but is that what they want
me to do? What do I need to stack them? Another raid song? Oh, no, I did it. I did it. It's one,
two, three. Yeah, I was thinking one, two, three, one, two, three, four. Well, that's not four.
This is one, two. This is a lot, isn't it? It's just by the holes, technically. Seven, one, two,
three, four. Yeah. So one, two, three, four, five. I wonder if I have to stack them. Oh, shit. Okay.
Hold on. One, two. It's technically three. Wait, are you sure I'm counting the wrong thing? It's
one, two, three, technically. One, two, three. Somebody said I was counting the wrong thing.
How do I get it to stand straight up? I think that this one's in the right spot, I think.
What does this one even tell me? Teeth at the end are numbers. Seven. Honestly, that would have taken
me a very long time because I'm sitting here counting how many prongs there are, not the
number it looks like. What is that, a five? So this is three, three, four, five, seven. Hold on.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. What is this? One, two, three, six.
Six. I love how you ask a question and then swivel around in your chair waiting for the answer like
Dora the Explorer. Waiting for the answer. Is it six? It's six. Come on. These get tricky.
You gotta, come on, this must be a kill day. No, I'm good. I like, these are my favorite ones.
I love these ones. These are the best. Okay. I don't, this is not right. That's okay. Also not
right, but it's all right. Over here maybe. It's a weird shape. This shit is weird. Uh, wait a minute.
I think that's correct. Golden tooth? Wrong. Got it. What goes over here? How can you not see it?
Nothing's wrong over here. What's wrong? What's wrong? Yeah. What's, what's going on?
Bottom left? What's wrong with it? The nuts? Swap the bolts. Swap the fucking bolts. Swap the
fucking bolts. Oh my God. I'm like hyperventilating. Imagine looking at a draw of tools
and it's not even, I'm just sitting here going, I need to slow down. Swap. All right. Is it weird
that I don't know what a nut and a bolt is? You gotta call this what they look like. The little
spinny things that fall off the trees. Is that what you mean? The little spinny things that
fall off the tree. That's a wing nut. Okay. This is a bolt and you want me to move the bolts over
here? Bolt is like Frankenstein, right? These are Frankenstein bolts. What is it? Is it nuts? Is it
Frankenstein nuts? What do Frankenstein's nuts look like? I know. They look like this, right?
I know. As it was coming out, I knew what was happening, but like what do they look like?
They're like this, right? What? Just tell me what you want me to do. How does that sound?
Like this? I don't, guys, what is in bolt? What do you mean? Okay. Bottom left. You mean these
alternate the bolts. There's only one bolt. I did that already. What's this? What's the problem? I
did it already. I wasn't that already like that has to be fucking with us. Oh no, this is going
to be one of these where I have to make a picture. I'm addicted to this game now. I thought I was
going to give up. I like love it. Hold on. So the labels don't mean anything. What are you guys
putting a fish in here? Oh, I gave chat a fish to help them calm down. That scene was fucking crazy.
You guys think Tony? All right. I can't move this. Can this hang somewhere? I don't think
that's right. Oh, wait a minute. Oh, please do it. Jeremy, please do it. It's 2023. No one's angry.
Are you not angry? We're just hanging out. You can just chill out. No one's angry. Who's angry?
It's great. We're fuming. No, you're not. You're not angry. You're not actually angry. You're not.
I know you're not. What are we doing with all these Q-tips? Oh, I know what to do with the Q-tips.
You were gaslighting us. No, I wasn't. Why are these not going in? Who's angry? No, I'm not angry.
It's okay. Does this fit in here? I don't get it. I can't put it in. It doesn't go in here.
I don't understand what to do with the brush. Slow down and think. I would hang this on a little hook.
And what is this thing? Is this a flosser? Wouldn't it go in here? Can anything else fit in this?
Probably not, right? This brush doesn't go anywhere. Brush goes in your pocket.
But where does the floss go, then? Right there. I can't spin it, though. Yay. Oh, wait a minute.
I know. I got it. Oh, boy. This is going to be a challenge, but I'm up for it. No, please. God,
no. I don't think you guys have not entered the chill zone yet. You guys have not entered
the chill zone. I don't think I've ever heard of somebody chilling out and screaming,
oh, God, please, God, no. I don't see you chilling out and hanging out with the hot cocoa. Oh, God,
please, God, no. Wow, I'm so comfy. Oh, God, please, God. You need to relax. This game is too
stressful. No, it's not. This is a chill game. We're just chilling. All right, let's run a poll.
Mods, get a poll in the chat. Are you chilling out or oh, God, please, God? No. What does this
say? What did you make the title? The triangle block goes into the square. What? Sipping my,
I'm chilling out or oh, God, please, God? Yeah. It's not 70% of you that are freaking out. You
guys, we just, we're, we gotta chill. God, please, God. I just dropped the hammer. Are you guys
stressing out? Oh, my. Chilling. I'm stressing out. I'm confused. You're stressing them out.
This game gives me anxiety. I want to change my answer. You can't. Big dumb stuff first. Wait,
I can knock everything off. Okay, this has to hang between some. All right, I think that's
actually a good place for it. This definitely goes here. This might go right here. I'm so
chilled out right now. I just lost connection to chat. No, is that all right? Please, God.
You say that when you go on a really scary roller coaster. There's always somebody that's
for some reason, they decided to sit in the front seat. Like, don't sit in the front seat.
And they're like, oh, gosh, please, God, make sure we get through this. You don't, don't sit in the
front car. 60, 40. Yeah, but you gotta take, you gotta take like 20 to 30% away from the memers,
right? Yeah, I gotta take, you gotta take 20% of the way because they just clicked it because
they thought it was a funny sentence. Oh, okay. Hold on. How am I supposed to fit this? I was fine
until this level. I'm making progress. Don't act like I'm not making progress. Oh, God.
Don't do this to me. You just get up and go get a bowl of Captain Crunch and be fine.
Dude, I'm like tied to a chair. You just got me. I can't get out. Shit, this is so tricky.
I'm, how could I, this is so tricky. Fucking stop doing that. I'm, I, I, I, I, I'm, you know
what I mean? I'm getting there. A 10 year old could do this. Oh, stop it. Oh, they could not.
I'm close to wherever it is. That's where that goes for sure. It's so close. It really is. Don't
tell me it's not because it is. The broom go up here. All the, all the people that are doubters,
you're about to lose big time. Shut up. That's correct. Yes, it is.
He's never going to do this one. He's never going to do it. Should have done a poll.
Why did we not do a poll? Every single one of you just lost. We should have done a poll.
There's just a couple small things missing and it's good to go. It's just a few things missing
that are a little bit incorrect. It's, oh, it's, oh, it's there though. What do you change? Stop
changing my title. Dear Jerma, there are hints in the pause menu featuring the fishies within
that little face. Why are you communicating this way? Why are you communicating through titles?
There's something that's so close. Is it right here? Did I just get it? Oh yeah. I win. Where's
wait, something's missing. Where does this go? This one stupid thing, but I don't know. Something
has to change. Where's this broom go? Over here. I got it. Done. Hey doubters. Good night. Let's go.
What's wrong? It's the angle. No, this definitely goes here. Where else would that go? There. Okay.
There it is. Done. Yeah. See you later doubters. How would this be wrong? There's no way this is,
this is correct. Where else would any of this go? Doubters are winning. The wrench, the wrench needs
to be switched with something. There's no hole. That would make sense here. The yellow pick thing.
That is. See you later. All right. We got an easy cookies one. I don't even know what I just did.
It's betting time. Will I do this in 20 minutes? Will I get the ding in 20 minutes? Is that too
long or should I do 15? Too long. 15. Mod check. Why are you checking? Oh, it's because people
are doing the fish. 15 minutes or less? No, no way. 10. 10 is this. These games are designed for
you to play them for like 40 minutes. 15 minutes. Will I solve this in 15 minutes and put it in emote
only? Oh, you've been playing this for hours. Yeah. I'm having fun. I mean, contrary to maybe
some of your beliefs, this game is not the equivalent of me dunking my head in acid.
I'm having some... Wait, timer's going? No, it's not. It has to wait to wait till people bet.
No, timer's not going until it's... There's a lot of yeses. Is that a lot of yeses or a lot of noes?
That's a lot of yeses. A lot of you believe. Can we help with emote only? You can try. 30 million
versus 16 million. Well, a lot of believers. You ready? Tell me when to go. Mods are keeping
track right now. Economic collapse incoming. Okay. Wait, not yet. I want my own music. I want my own
music for this. I'm not going yet. No, no, no, no, no, no. No, I'm not going yet. I need my own music.
I haven't looked. I want my own music. What should we do for our music? How about like... What am I
feeling? Something that's going to make me concentrate. Both headphones going in. Reset the
level. Okay. That's fair. I'm not looking. No, not Miku. The Bloodborne OST. Oh, the misery. I mean,
this is... That's going to get muted. Do you think I can do it in the time that we listen to, oh,
the misery? I'm just going to get muted. Is it worth it? What if it gets shut down? It's not
worth it. No, not doom. Something that's going to lock me in. The Flintstones? What on the karaoke
version? The karaoke version is just going to be... What? Hold on. Karaoke version. What does this
actually sound like? Put on the MIDI version? It's just... It's not... But is it just this?
This is... No, it's not. I need to sing it. If I sing this, will... Okay, will you guys be happy?
Should I just do this? Like, should I just fuck this game and I'm just going to do this for like a
minute? All right, I'll try. If I get through this, if I get through the first verse, I get another
two minutes. No, that's not fair. 15. All right, here we go. I'm going to try doing this. I don't
even know how it goes.
I even have the lyrics in front of me. The lyrics are in front of me and I still said it wrong.
You got to be fucking kidding me. I've said it wrong so many times that that's the right way.
Keep going. You just want to embarrass me even more in front of a hundred billion people? I have
to get at least the chorus and I'm done. I promise.
You, you're the great... They do that thing with their mouth.
But once you turn, they hate us. Oh, the misery.
Everybody wants to be my enemy. Spare the sympathy. Everybody wants to be my enemy.
They, they, they, they. Once you pray, oh the misery, every single laughter in the halls I stack it in
my mind and waiting for the time when I show you what it's like to be the world's Spirit of Mike.
Tell you you're the greatestest. But once you turn they hate us.
Oh the misery every single person is my
Spare the sympathy
Everybody wants to be my enemy
How does it actually go?
That is how it goes. Oh
That's it doesn't goes like ee-ee-ee-ee
Yeah, I fucked it up. What doesn't matter my version hurt. So my version hurt you. All right, let's go
Oh, wait, this must be a timer. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
I needed to actual OST. I don't know. What should I put on this?
Restart, please. All right. I need I need songs. Hold on. How about like thinking music thinking music to inspire creativity
Positive thinking music for work and for studying. I think that sounds good. All right. All right, ready ready
Tell me when to go ready one two
Go
You all just got absolutely fucking annihilated
Annihilated so many people lost points
Wait, that's not it
Wait what
That's not is it the end. Oh, that was it. All right, I went you guys so some of you guys got absolutely annihilated
I'm so sorry
That was so easy
Here's another one. Here's your chance. Well, I solve this one in 15 minutes
That probably sounded so bad
15 is too long. What are you linking here?
Oh the misery every single person is my
Spare the sympathy
Everybody that is the I just did this while you're linking this to me. All right
A lot of you guys think yes, it's my people are gonna get fucking annihilated on this one
What if this one is super easy? I don't know. It's I don't I don't know what this is asking me to do
I'm just gonna go for it put on blood-borne. All right, I'll put on I'll put on
how about the
Ludwig theme that's like my favorite song. All right, this this is literally seven minutes. So it's got time
15 minutes is way too much time. All right, well then just bet accordingly then you need to bet accordingly
I'm not gonna tell you what you shouldn't shouldn't bet on. I'm just saying a bet. All right, are we ready?
Let's go for it. Okay in three
Two one go. Oh
That actually really hurt. Oh my fucking elbow my bleeding I
Just wanted to hear the breakdown hmm, this one looks easy
Hey, pretty good at that noise heard it 500 times. Oh
Pog he did the like thing where he goes like this and makes a noise that it like he's I
Actually don't think this one will be that bad. Wait a minute. Maybe it is. No, I don't think it'll be bad
I don't think you want to bet on this one
I don't think you should bet because this is really just finding with ease fit like for instance right here
Yeah, I don't think you should bet. Well, he's off in five minutes
Under five. Okay. I mean if you get up if you want to do it then go for it
But I'm telling you it's probably better do all in. Oh, no all in you suck. Is that what you said?
No, it's not. What did you say?
Oh, let him cook. I read that his you suck. How I don't think it's just moving pretty fast. All right. Are we good?
Ready to get started. I don't think I'm gonna do music for this one. So when I pick up the first piece
That's when you can start the timer. Maybe I'll do a little bit of music. Why not?
There's less than five minutes reset it. I just did didn't I? I just did how about um
Do penis music now too many people here too many people will leave the Elden Ring theme
Okay. Yeah, this is almost this is five minutes long. Here we go. Ready. This is the right one. Yeah, it is. Okay
Here we go. Ready three two one
I'm gonna pee I'll be right back
But why did I that was weird face? I just made he is so funny. Yeah, that's the wicked funny
We just did what am I grabbing here? There's the audio. Oh, okay. I follow in the footprints
I think so turn on music. I will in just a second. All right. This one looks a little tricky
This one actually looks pretty tricky. I'm not gonna look too much at it
I'm just gonna well now I can't do that
Are you guys done losing all your points or do you want to keep going more solve it within five minutes?
That's this a lot of you are gonna either make a lot of money or lose a lot of money in relative channel point terms
This is the start of this level. So I'm gonna start here and I am gonna make sure I'm focusing
It's not gonna be music. We're gonna do thunderstorm sounds to make sure I'm locked in I put 5k
13 million more than that 16 million. Yes 6 million say no as of right now five minutes
I don't know that one looked a little weird. Are we good? I'm gonna put both headphones in I'm gonna relax
thunderstorm
Sound effects because this will help ready three two
One start it's not it's not over
Stop doing that. Stop. I don't know what to do. I don't get it
Shit, okay. That one was very easy. I thought that was the lightning. Wait, wait, wait. Are we starting? Oh, we're starting
Okay, I alright
Rain's getting kind of wild out there
If this is this much going on, I would not be live. I would just I don't know I'd be like scared
Holy shit, dude. Turn your stream off. Just we'll see you tomorrow, man
We'll see you tomorrow. You don't have to do this. All right, we good. Are you good to go? All right
Let me reset it three two one go
Turn that off god damn it. I don't understand what it wants me to do
There's gotta be some kind of pattern to this like you can't you gotta take one and then from the opposite one maybe
Jesus, I don't understand. Oh one two, three, four five one, two, three, four one one
One one one two three one two one
One this is the only this one has one one this one also has one so daisy this one has one this one has
Maybe delete these
Did you I don't I haven't I haven't figured it out yet. I did something right there, though
Maybe every other one needs to be pulled. Maybe there has to be one on each trunk. I
I don't know. I don't know. I don't get it. I'm sorry everybody. I was up. What am I doing wrong?
What did I do wrong? I don't understand. I think it's a mirror mirror symmetry make it symmetrical. What do you mean?
Oh really shit. Okay. Wait, what that's symmetrical. This is not so this is symmetrical. This doesn't belong here
Understand it's just mirrored. This is mirrored except this shouldn't be here and down here. This is wrong
This can't be mirrored. The only way this can be mirrored is if I get rid of these all of these essentially, right this one
This one then
This it right. Okay, we didn't I didn't win reset it. Well, did I already cut one off that I wasn't supposed to
Okay. All right. This one was cool. I don't think that's right though
No, it is because they want me to do here the lines probably do another pole. No, no, no, no, no
No, don't ever overlap them. Isn't it a 33% chance that I just get this right eventually
Yeah, there's a 33% chance that I eventually will get this right gems. That's wrong with that
This looks pretty great to me do it by color. I'm trying to fit them together
Got it. I can stack these should I not do that? No, what I don't know to do. Hey
That's not it. I can't do symmetry with everything because I this one's
It's no counterpart. Oh the symmetry
These face in the wrong way. I think they were these are not in the right spot. I don't know why
mirror each side
Mean like what do you mean?
The only thing cooking is his brain I kind of don't get it seems like everything seems to be in order
Is everything not in order here? So you mean put one on like this?
You mean like I'm gonna show you demonstrations mean like this. I have one object on each side just mirrored
But what about this? I can't split these
I'm gonna turn off the lightning. Will you stop doing that? Which the red and the black that looks pretty good. What's going on here?
The cat is giving you hints. I think this looks good. I don't think there's anything wrong with this
Had it in the wood. Are you streaming from your private island?
Sounds are you filming?
private island Andy the black shell ah
What do you want? It's not helping. I don't know. It's my color. This does not help at all
I did have a hint and then some kid got a hold of this fucking book and just started just
Ruining it. Yeah, I'm doing that star has to go in the middle
There are pieces overlapping did it. Oh
dear dear me I
Think I'm almost done with it with these things you have to seriously sit back and just like kind of let your eyes just
Lose focus and just look at the whole thing whole sections, right? No put it back put it back put it
Oh, this is awful. Wait, they could have grown back. They could have grown back on its own. There's only like one more. Where is it?
I
Did not expect it to be like that. I thought I've had it
I thought I had it fine the sound effects are putting me to sleep. It was nice. Just use your eyes lol
Hey one, two, three, one, two, three one, two, three, four one, two, three, four down from here one, two, three
Four five down from here one, two, three, four five
Six wait, that's on there put it down. No, I don't know where it grew back. What am I missing now?
Two three four five down this one here. We got one three four five six seven eight nine one two
You piece of shit
Close it like it's over here somewhere. I feel like it's like right here. It definitely is where is it that?
Mirrors that mirrors this mirrors this mirrors that does that does that one does this one does not
Wait, no it does this one does this one does this one does this one does
This one this one this one does
It's under the cam
That's not
Reset I'm not gonna reset. Why would I reset? It's I'm almost I need one more
Reset what are you talking about? You're not being serious. I have to reset it. I know I don't I'm doing it
One two three four five six seven one two three four five six seven
One two, I messed it up. We can't find it
We can't find it. You pulled the wrong ones off
What you removed two of the same? Are you serious?
Seven I fucking don't remember where they are two three
four five
Six seven is one more. Yeah
All right. Very good. Thank you for the help. I wonder how much there is left in the game. Oh, this is easy
That was a good sound. Okay, what's happening here? These have eyes. I think I have to put stuff in the same
I don't know. How does this work rocks go together? What's with the gold? Oh, there we go. Nice
Let's see if I like this game. It's getting fun. I wish puts in music on I'll put the regular music on put it back on
Ooh, this is nice and you beat this game. I mean I have to assume I'm getting I wonder how many chapters there are
This is gonna be some mirror shit. I think so. It is another mirror only one of these. Oh shit
It's two of them egg. Hey
Hey, okay
Okay, what's the issue? You look like you've aged 15 years from playing this what no
I do not and how much cleaner does this need to be pretty good. You see do I do by color?
This one's not a mirror pinecones. Oh, right. No, these definitely go here
I think I have the top row done top row seems pretty good. Oh
Whoops. Oh my goodness. Oh my goodness. Yeah, that was not good. That was bad. That was very bad
How does this one work actually?
demented
Demented I very clearly this one is based on they probably have to be touching the right colors
Like this. Mm-hmm. Stop doing that. I have it
I need to
That's not right you like that's pretty good
Is the neat the two colors need to this needs to be red green green
orange
Red green green orange orange black. That's not correct
Wait, then this is red green green orange orange black. There it is. I got it. I got it
If I have to fill this whole thing, this might be game over do I have to fill this whole thing actually
This might not be that terrible, but it might be one at a time
Yeah, just get the edges first and I'll be good corner get corner pieces. There we go. Okay
So there are the there's another corner down lower left Christ. I think it's top. Yeah, I think it's top, right?
Yeah, the green green goes on top right the Olympus you can fit. Yes comfy. I feel like blue has to go up here
Yeah, yeah, of course, of course. Damn. Oh, they don't okay. The colors don't matter. It's just what fits
I thought I had to be separated in different colors that changes everything. Okay, can all these even make anything in here?
They're gonna be enough. Oh
This actually doesn't help at all
Maybe someone's first chat message ever one message was this game fucking sucks first chat message first time out
That's got to be a record, right? And no it does not you are wrong
This game is actually very comfy and it's very fun and I enjoyed I've been playing it for like four hours
I quit I'm gonna play a homerun baseball game now. It was fun. I like this a lot
How many um, how many levels are here? What am I not even close? Oh
I was like, I've only done 2% of the game. Oh the misery every single person is my enemy spare the sympathy
You know how many people just like fucking click the X just like click move over here click X and
They realized they closed all their tabs and I just fucking ruin their night only
One two, three, four five six
It is enough levels to probably do another hour or two, but I want to play this baseball game
It's called I think it's called like super psycho baseball or something. It's like you have to hit a home runs and it's hard
I'll try it. That's good. Good. Good. Good. Yes. Fuck. Yeah. Yeah. All right, let's do it
That was a little to the left. I give that a
Stamp that was fun recommended cozy. There's still a lot to do and I guess maybe this time
It's timed. All right. Hold on. Did I get more than one star on any level? What? Oh, you guys can't even see
Oops, sorry about that. The answer is no. There you go