Hello everybody. Give me one second and we'll get started. Be back in a minute.
Tweeted something. Got my drink. Alright, so today we're gonna be playing some
Dreams. I'm gonna try to play Dreams. He speaks. He speaks, finally. Yeah. I had to
get this shit going here. Let me just move my character. We're gonna explain
what's gonna happen here. Okay. Let me just get it on the screen because it's
already here. Sorry, I'm listening to three things at the same time. So today
we're gonna play Dreams. I cannot guarantee that I'm going to be very good
at this. I did all the tutorials. Well, not all of them. It actually did take a
long time, so I think I only didn't do one and it was like the master
class one. So I do know a handful of things. Yeah, somebody said it took me
eight hours to do them. Yeah, it's a lot. So I am very much at the baby steps.
I've done the painting, advanced tutorials, the sculpt tutorials. I know
how to use the program now and I made something. You'll see it in just a
second. Just learn how to code. It really is. It is like a, it is
absolutely a full game engine. It is a full movie maker. It's a full game
engine. It's a full sculpting tool. It's like having every single one of these
programs and it's really, really cool. Now, what is gonna happen today? Here's
what's gonna happen today. I'll tell you. This is going to be a, I had a, I
don't know, I was trying to think of like what to do with it because I tried
searching. Remember I said, oh, I'm gonna look for like the tags or search
for Jerma in the title. There's nothing. Nobody has made anything with the, with
Jerma in the title. So there's zero. I made something, but I do want to learn
how to play this and previously years ago what I would do is I would just
spend two straight weeks in here making anything I wanted, learning
everything, making sure I knew what I was doing. It's kind of not possible
to do that unless it's kind of broadcasted out. You know what I'm saying?
Because think about it. If I stream, you know, three, four, five days a week, I
am not doing this and it used to be I would just sit here for like 50
hours and do it. Don't let your dreams be dreams. But anyways, I'm gonna go
ahead and show you when have I ever streamed five days a week last week.
That happened to literally last week. Anyways, anyways, I'm gonna show you what
I have. This is the culmination of hours of work. I tried my hardest. I'm still
learning. It's not a dunk tank. I don't even want to put it on screen. I have
to. It's so bad. Alright, ladies and gentlemen, here is my creation. It's
called scorpion boss.
He wasn't supposed to scream yet, but we're gonna dodge roll.
It's German scorpion.
I did something wrong.
Because he's supposed to go.
I beat it. I did it. That's all I got. That's the only thing I made. It's
really hard.
That's again, again, how many hours was this? I don't know. Like one, two. No,
it was like one. It didn't take that long. Again, again.
First try. I beat German scorpion. First try.
The first time I haven't played around with the sculpt tool. Come on,
give me a break. What is this music? This is Gwyn from Dark Souls. Worst
thing I ever saw. That was literally like I just had finished the tutorials
and I was like, I'm gonna try to do anything. There it is. See? Okay,
this is literally last this morning at 2 48 a.m. I spent all yesterday doing
the tutorials and it culminated here earlier this morning at 3 a.m. Go to
sleep, Jeremy. I can't. I had to make German scorpion. Anyways,
release. I don't think so. I'm going to come back and fix it. All right,
so let's go back. So let me explain again what's going to happen today.
I need to see that. Somebody said the German scorpion face is what the
official German 985 popsicle would look like.
An ice cream bar. Oh, he killed me. Oh, my God. I'm never going to fucking
be able to not. I'm only going to think about that for the next like 30
minutes. All right, let's we're going to start fresh. I'm going to make
like I'm going to make something really easy. I'm going to make like
a rock. Okay, I need to start small. I tried to go way too big here. I
was going to make like a Dark Souls boss and no, no, no, no. I know I
got to start small. I'm going to make a rock. Okay, we're going to do.
I'm just going to I'm going to make a character. Although I didn't I
didn't even do that tutorial sculpture sculpture. Okay, I'm just
going to make a sculpture here. I'm going to make a didn't do that
tutorial. No, it takes like takes like two days to do these
tutorials. Okay, I'm going to make a character here, or I'm going to
make a sculpture, something that I'm going to try to do it as best I
can. So if you don't know how this works, is I didn't I didn't show
this last time. It's really important. Look at how insane this
is. Probably should have started with a square. Oh, god damn it.
Okay. Nevermind. Here's what we're gonna do. I'm gonna show
you. I'm still learning. Alright, so anyways, the way that this
works is you have a literal smear tool that you can paint in three
dimensions. And guess what, you can also take it away too. This
is what was blowing my mind yesterday is this shit. Being
able to carve out almost like clay is really, really, really
fun. And you can do this with any shape to make a
Minecraft pig. Oh, lagging here. Oh, alright, so let's
start with I'm gonna make the fucking popsicle thing is
killing me. I need to stop using the flesh skin color.
Yeah, but it's like, that was like Doctor's Office level of
realism. I don't know what to say about that. I really
don't. That was like image and like sex ed class level of
like fucking how perfect it was. Let's start simple. Okay,
I'm just gonna make like a mountain. I'm gonna make a
mountain. Sculpt a frog. Well, let me just because look
ready to do this. Using the controller is kind of finicky,
but it's still fun. Done. I'm done. That was fun, huh? And
there's a way that you can blend this shit together too,
which is what I should be doing. That's fine. This is
fine like this, because hold on. I need to go into
here. See if you wonder this is this means it's going to
do it's going to be a gradient essentially. I'll show you
see, it just picks a random color in that gradient. It's
pretty good. Now, you're probably asking, well, what
are these might be too small. They're not. They are
not the great thing about dreams is once these are
connected together, you can make them as big or as
small as you want forever. They could be an inch tall
or they can be 30 feet high, 100 feet high. Alright,
so, but I'm just in like the sculpting menu. See,
for instance, look at this. You ready? I can make
this as big or as small as I want. You can start
small. And as you see, this is pretty good E3
demo. Well, I want to go small because then we
can we can scale it from there. Okay, let's get
back in here. And I'm going to add and I'm going
to do whatever this is like kind of rough
looking. Don't worry, I'll fix it. It's gonna be
snow. Actually, I can I can make snow here. I
need a painting tool. No, no, no, no. I'm not
making like rocks. Yeah, this is just the rock
structure. Let's go back here. Okay, this is
just the structure of the rocks. I'm going to
put some more rocks on it. Um, what do I need
to do? I need to go to Yeah, this mirror is
fine. I need the color to be. We'll just we'll
do this. We'll we'll make it just kind of a
random color, random rock type color. Oh,
shit. This is I want this in I want this part of
this. There we go. Okay, so see, we're gonna make
a little bubbles on it. Let's get in there a
little closer. I mean, you might be asking
about it looks a little rough, but it's all
right. We're gonna do all kinds of cool shit
to this. All right. It's like little puff
balls. Looks okay. Hold on. This is snow.
No, it's pustules. Is this the snow? Was
this supposed to be the snow? You tell us.
I'm just experimenting. All right. Yeah, it
was supposed to be the snow. All right, get in
there. So this is gonna be different. This is
gonna be different. Hold on. I want it to be
the circle. And then we're gonna make some
snow here. Okay. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. I need the paint tool. Paint mode. I
need. What do you think? What looks like
snow? That's kind of snowy. Because then
now this just becomes an object. Okay, get
in close. Let's see here. Dots. That could
be snow. And then just sprinkle that
around the top. Okay. What else? What are
these else? I don't know what these look
like. This is actually one of the first
times I played with the paint tool. No,
I think this is it. I do. So you can
take, you can have it snapped to
surfaces. You can paint it on
surfaces. You can have it. You can put
a grid up to have it so you can't
really get lost. You'll get like
snapped over and over. Well, you can do
the kaleidoscope tool, which
interestingly enough, see what it does
here. You can kind of make it as many
as you want spreading out. So you can
go do cool stuff like this. You can
make like flowers and shit. But we're
making snow. I think it's going to be
dots. Maybe I'll make them a little
bit, maybe I'll make them smaller.
Look, this is just to get into this
one of your things, you know what I'm
saying? Take our kaleidoscope. I
don't really know what this shit does.
Okay, tools. Let's go with the draw
flex, because this is more precise.
And by precise, I mean, if you look
ready, you can start small. And the
more you hold down right trigger, the
bigger the fleck will get. So let's
go ahead and get over here and paint
some snow. I'm just gonna Okay,
let's go with what's a good snow
color? I mean, white, like teeth
white. That's gonna be like teeth
white. Okay. And then let's zoom in
a little. And I want the dots. Now
hold on here. How to opacity
scatter. We'll do opacity scatter
is no, that looks fine. Okay, so
let's get in there and make some
snow. Tilt it a little. I think it
looks all right. Okay, there's my
place. Why is it blue now? Why is
it blue? Oh, I didn't pick the
finish. Stupid idiot. All right,
plastic, shiny, snow is pretty
shiny. Yeah, snow is pretty shiny,
isn't it? Okay, seeing now how
difficult this is to do. Trying to
work in 3d space with a dual shock
controller is almost unbearable. Get
just get down there. Get over
here. This is driving me crazy
right now. Okay, don't just bring
it over here. Learn to control
it. I mean, I know how to control
it. It's just really hard to use.
Like this. I need to turn on the
snapping for this thing. There it
is. obey auto guides. Where is it?
No, no, it's not. I have to like
go like this. Come here. I did
make that very small. Smaller. Is
that close enough? Close enough for
a picture. I still need to rough
this up a little bit. Is there a
paint to surface? There might be.
It's just I'm still trying to
figure out how the fuck to do
this. Because this is sculpt, but
then paint is, as I said, this
is a complete learning experience
for all of us. There's a snap to
surface, which is here. Okay,
yeah, there it is. Well, let's go
ahead and do that then. Let's
get rid of that. So let's go
back to the dots. Make sure the
brush fleck is fine. Color is
not fine. Go back to white with
a shiny finish. And then snap to
surface is there. Right. Okay,
here we go. Make a massive pig.
Well, I'm just trying to learn to
use the tools properly. I just want
to go in and that's all right.
But I don't I don't want this
to be one object. That's what
will happen. Okay, how's that
look? I'm just gonna copy it
anyways. All right, let's see.
All right. Three snow things.
What am I gonna do with this
when I finish? Throw it in the
trash. Throw it into the
garbage can. Looks all right. This
has to come up though. Let's
make let's don't change this.
Let's go out again. Into what's
it called? You can just style
right? Okay, I'm gonna drop this
a little bit. It's gonna be an
expressionist pain. So I'm
doing right now is I'm
loosening up the fleck, which
is kind of another word for
pixel. That one looks stupid.
But it don't matter. We're
gonna see you can make it. You
can make it a mess. Does they
make really fucked up photos of
stuff? That's okay. Let's go
into is impasto. Let's go to
tint. I want a better rock
look. It's coat mode. So you
can apply tints. You can apply
finishes. Looks okay. All right.
What do I affect? See, you
can use this. The weird
part is you can make it
move around too. So ready? The
snow can be like moving. All
right. Well, now it's wind.
It's wind now. The rocks are
moving too. It's just missed
now. Yeah, it is missed. Good
idea. Back it up. It's gonna be
much lighter. I'm gonna break it
up even more. Okay, let's get
back in. I need to paint this
again. I need to mess this
all up. Where's the tool that
I need for that? I think it's
actually where's the damn
tool? Yeah, you can like
fray it out and really fuck
it up. Let's see. Ruffle
maybe. Yeah. Ruffle. Okay. You
can change the direction. Okay.
Doesn't look terrible. And then
we're gonna paint. Let's see.
This is just by the way, this
is just part one. This is you
guys understand that this is
the background for a popsicle
scene. This is what you do.
You just have to experiment
and play around till you find
something you like. Use the
brushes. Yeah, here's the
one problem, right? This is
the problem that I had with
this stream in particular. It's
it takes like probably 50 to
100 hours playing this game.
To know where everything is,
know how to do everything and
know exactly how to use every
tool. There's logic in this
game. There's actual logic
buttons and shit to connect
stuff to. But I think I just
want to try it, you know,
add background music. Oh,
you got it. Sure thing.
Holy shit.
See, look at the speed. We can
make a song too. I'm down with
that as well. Let's go back
here. Here we go. Playback
speed.
Bratz song, I might be able
to maybe. I hate it. I hate
it. I closed that out. So for
some reason, they had one
timeline connect to this
timeline. I don't know why you
just want to make the song
in one timeline. Let's, let's
actually get a song here,
though. A decent one. I'm
gonna make a little, okay,
here's what I'm gonna make a
house like here, but not
yet. I'm painting. God
dammit. So let's do, let's
just get a song. Something
easy. Make a Minecraft
house. I might, the house
I make is going to be real
bad. What? Holly. Wait,
is this like Kingdom
Hearts? Delphino Plaza.
These things, people made
these? Face my fears. This
is awesome. Animal Crossing
New Leaf 1 a.m. I think
that's pretty good. I think
that's what we're going to
have to look for. I actually
don't think this will play
when I'm editing. Sorry,
guys. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. I
need like snow. As the
congressional debate over
gun control flares up yet
again, we regret to report
the murder of a wife and
her two children by their
husband and father purchased
the rifle used in the
crime at his local gun
store. No, that's not what
I wanted to do. That was
that PT thing. Why? Well,
Seymour, I made it.
Superintendent Tomers.
Welcome. I hope you're
prepared for an
unforgettable luncheon.
Oh, you gods. My roast is
ruined. I want let's just
I want I need snow. I
don't actually know what
here. Let's go. I'll go
tags to like they have this
all sorted out here. Motion
ambience ambience. Here we
go. Lustre winter wind.
Check this shit out. I
can't make a field.
This is just in the
background. I believe you
can make a field play
when you can disturb the
distance. Right now, this
is just going to play
completely. It's very
relaxing. It's very nice,
but we're not done. Turn
up my voice. I'm just
going to turn this shit
down. Shit. Okay, so we
and this needs to be a
little more detailed. I
don't like it. I hate it.
I'm going to delete the
whole thing. Just kidding.
Okay. Sculpt paint. No,
let's do some painting.
Let's get some more like
dirt and shit on here.
You know what I mean?
Like, let's got to be
so like, let's get some
good fleck. I want like
a 3D effect here. Let's
put the kaleidoscope on
maybe like make a
fucking single goddamn
flower right here. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
Go back to sculpting.
It's my ADHD. This is
why I can't play these
games. This needs to be
the same color though.
And I need to blend them
together. There's a way
to do that. And I did
the tutorial and you
blend shit. You can
blend it. How I forget
not looseness, not
crop. There's a way that
you can make two things
blend in together and
can move them around
and they stick together.
It looks really, really,
really cool. I think
it's like the stamp
shape. And I think
it's like you go into
the hold on. Let me
just check this out
for a second here. Is
this it here? Like
properties, effects,
no, boil. It's not
boil. Physical
properties, movable
friction. Fuck, I
forget what it was.
Damn it. I might have
to go do that tutorial
again, because I know
there's a way that you
can make it. It looks
really, really awesome.
Ha ha ha ha. This is
it. This is it. This is
it. Varying looseness.
Yeah. Okay. This is
it. All right. I'm
ready to rock and roll.
I think it has to be on
a certain. It has to be
on stamp too as well.
You can put a hole in
it. Yeah. Okay. Okay.
I got to, I have to
do stamp. This is
pretty good rock
formation though. Okay.
I'm going to keep this
rock formation. I'm
going to clean it up
a little. I'm going to
carve this up a
little. It's just gum.
Yeah. No, that's a
pretty decent rock
formation. Okay. Just
wait. I'm going to
carve it up. Don't worry.
Pretty nice rock
formation. I would say
I got to just color
it the right color.
Okay. So let's
deselect. Yeah, guys,
guys, guys, guys.
That's, that's, that's
pretty good. Just give
me a second. I'm
going to put, Oh,
no, you bet your ass.
This is how it's going
to go. There's going
to be a fucking like
a little village right
here. And then there
you go. There's your
shot. No, no, no.
It's going to be over
here. I'll fix that
later. Here's your
shot right here. Can
be like a little fucking
farm or something
right here. Can we
think we can make a
little to scale house
over there? Right.
First of all, I need to
make these the right
color. Don't you guys
know when you, when
you scale out of any
image, it don't
matter. This is what
this is the money
right here, right
there. I'm going to
show them to shave
it. Don't worry. I'll
shave it. Just wait.
Just watch. Okay. Let's
get, let's get the
shave. Let's shave it
out. I'm going to
group these two
together because this is
where we're going to
shave. I actually
group of these, you
know, just in case
group them up. Get in
here and let's get
sculpting. What do you
say? Okay. Let's
shave this up.
It needs rounded for
this one. That's way
too much. No, I need
like the filled
doughnut. There we
go. It's like
carbon clay on a
knife. Look at
link, link, link,
link. What do you
what do you mean?
What? What?
This really is
unbelievable. That's
unfucking
unbelievable. No.
Here, I'm going to
put this on the
screen. I'm going to
screen for a while
too. This is too
good. That should
be a new E mode.
Yeah. Yeah, it
will be. That's a
new E mode. I'm
going to literally
do that today. I'm
going to, that
will be the, that
that will be an E
mode you can use
tomorrow. Just like
that face. It really
does look like fucking
ice cream. Oh my
God. I'll, I'll
let that sit there
for a little while.
All right. It's too
harsh. I can, I
can change it in the
options later. With
the fleck tool, don't
worry. It's like,
well, it looks too
carved, looks too
perfect. I'll fuck it
all up. I'll make it
look better. All we
need is from this
side anyways. It's
really different. Give
me like a wedge. It's
still, I mean, it's
still going to look
kind of natural,
right? So that looks
a little, but when
that's, when I do
some more messing
around with fleck, it
will look a little
bit natural. Actually,
but no, no, no, no. I
want that to be
flat because I want to
put like a little
house here. That'll be
okay. I'll mess with it
in the fleck tool.
Okay. Let's see if I
was to be like up
here. This is a pretty
decent start. Okay. I
need to change this
though. We need to
mess with this. I
need to go into the
paint tool and I
want to make, I need
to make a, like a
cactus or something. I
don't know. We'll go
with, I got to get
the snap off, take the
snap into surfaces off
because I'm just going
to make something to
use in the scene.
All right. I'm going
to make a, um, I
don't know. What's
your, throw me some,
give me an idea. A
rock. All right. Good.
I'll do a rock. No,
I already have a bunch
of rocks. I'm going
to make a cactus, a
pine tree. All right.
I'll do a pine tree,
but why would a pine
tree be out here? All
right. Pine tree. I
don't know what a pine
tree looks like. I'll
try. Okay. Pine
tree. Let's go. We
need like a straight
line here. We need like
a draw fleck. What the
fuck does a pine tree
look like? I know it's
going to get brown.
It's like a brown
base, right? That
doesn't look brown.
Oh, I still have the
hexagon tool on.
Kaleidoscope is still
on. Okay. And they
are pretty waxy.
That's fine. We'll go
with this, this. The
lighting is weird. I'm
going to have to do it
like this. I don't like
that tool. I don't like
this one. It's
definitely not this one.
Banes. We could make
a tree out of this. It's
going to make it
smaller. Okay. Hold
on. Expressive
Impressionist. It's
scattered around
everywhere. Change the
bootleg elevator music.
What are you talking
about? I feel like
I should just do it
like this. Just like
paint it up and then
add. No, that's too
that's ugly. Go back
to the paint tool.
Close, please. I just
get, I'm so, ah, this
is so many options,
so many things to do.
Hide everything else.
Um, I know
there are other things
to do. Just lost in
the tutorials in my
brain. I know. Okay.
Let's do kaleidoscope.
We'll do three. Let's
just try this with
the color. Just go
brown and I'm going
to make it so it's the
draw. See that's as
big as it's going to get.
Okay, so let's just try
to make a trunk.
All right. Looks like
a giant Jenga tower,
but that's okay because
then it sprays out a
little. No, maybe not
all the way. That's
all right. Oh, it's
a palm tree. No, I
need to have roots
down here. They got
to be good roots. No,
okay. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. We're
going to do just kind
of random color in the
bottom there and different
black cubist. I like
it. I like it. Just
let's just see. Don't
just wait. Let's just
see what it's it's
expressionist. Oh, it's
too quiet. Sorry.
What does it express?
I don't know. It's just
like a broad paint
stroke. All right. Stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop.
Wait, wait, leave me
alone. Leave me alone.
Okay. This is done.
We're going to start
a new painting. Wait,
is it there? Okay.
Okay. Now we're
going to do the top.
This is where we get to
be really, really,
really fun. Okay.
We're going to go with
veins. Check this out.
Ready? Get rid of the
hexagon. Let's turn this
like this. Let's just see
what that looks like
painting it. Don't let
anybody tell you that
you're doing it wrong.
I think it could work.
No, they're not
fucking pubes. No.
All right. Hold on.
Let me just see what
they look like. Edit
Fleck. Like I like
the scatter. Bring
the opacity down a
little. Okay.
You can make like an
expression, just bird.
You can do whatever you want.
These need to be smaller.
And they also need to be green.
Pine tree is like
super green. Well,
I'll do the whole
spectrum here. Okay.
Here we go.
So it just needs to be.
Let's go spin it
this way. So they go
down. And we're
going to put flow on
this too. What's flow,
Jeremy? You'll see.
Just wait. This.
I want to like move
it this way, but it's
like flying three airplanes
at the same time. For
some reason. All right.
Just tilt this way.
Why is it so difficult
to have you do good?
Go over here.
Oh, I'm killing me.
Okay. That's what I wanted.
We'll do. I'll put
me new music on in a second.
So we're talking about
pine tree. So pine tree
very sticky and prickly,
right? Who gives a fuck
it's a pine tree. Spread
out a little more and
hide everything so I can
get a good view. And
this comes out.
It's looking, it doesn't look
bad longer. I think that's
good to check the sides.
It did look. Yeah.
It's a little flat.
You have to make a little
bit bigger over here.
It was a little flat,
but it's okay because
I'm just going to come
down here.
Probably should have turned
on like the mirror tool
or something. Every tree
needs another tree.
Oh yeah. I know.
The best thing about
this game is the only
to do this once you
only have to do this.
Oops. Kind of screwed
that up. Come on.
This game is going to have
VR later. That'd be awesome.
Snapping on. I don't think
snapping's on.
Doesn't need to be perfect.
Just needs to get the
idea across because it's
going to be scaled
anyways because we're
going to put some flow
on this too. So don't
worry. We'll be good.
All right. Not. I don't
know if that's really a
pine tree. It's more like
a bush, but it's all
right. Okay. So now
put this over here.
Oh, something's wrong there.
That's all fucked up.
I'll fix it.
What's like the erase tool?
Shit's all fucked up.
How do I erase it?
Is there is I don't
even know if there
is an erase tool in the
game. I really don't
think there is.
Well, I'll figure it
out in a second.
Spider-Man.
How long before you guys
get rid of that one?
Is this the whole song?
Okay. Fine. We'll do this
one. Which one of these
is animal crawl?
There it is.
Sing it. You got a friend?
All right. You got a
friend in me.
You got a friend in me.
But you got a friend
inside of yourself.
But you got a friend in me.
How do I erase this?
I know you can.
Here we go. Delete.
Delete. Ah, there is
an erase tool.
Let's connect these two
together. Kind of sad,
but it's all right.
It's, I'm not done.
No, I forgot to do like
the fucking cool shit.
Hold on. The trunk is too
long. No, it's not.
Is it? I don't even know
what a pine tree looks like.
I think I have to
shave off some of this.
This is, it's too much.
This is like a willow tree.
Yeah. All right.
Let's go shave some stuff
off here. A little too long.
Take out some of the bulk
from the back.
All right. That's a little better.
And I'm going to move.
I'm going to, I'm going to
fuck with this a little bit too.
No, Jeremy, don't fuck with it.
I'm going to fuck with it.
What's flow? I'll show you.
So here is where we get
to have a little bit of fun.
I'll connect these two
together in a second.
But let's go to style mode.
All right. And this is
what we hit. Hold on.
Bring it back a little.
What do you think?
No, no, no.
It's turning into that,
that guy's hair from the meme.
What does that mean?
That's not bad.
I don't hate this.
That looks pretty good.
And then check this shit out.
The finishing touches
we're going to put on this.
You wouldn't even believe it.
Maybe a little too much.
Look at that.
It's alive.
That's all you need.
That's it.
Don't need anything else.
And okay, back it up.
Now we're going to go to style.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're going to go to coat mode,
finish, and we're going to get
some shine, more shine
on these leaves.
Look at that glistening.
More, more, no, less paint.
We can add some,
we can add like a couple
of little things here.
Tint hue glow.
Okay, maybe this is
what I want for glow.
Where's the glow?
Okay, color.
I want it to be like
baking in the sun.
A little burnt.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not even glowing.
I'm not even doing glow.
Go back, apply glow.
There it is.
Whoa, too much, too much.
Back it up, back it up.
That looks good.
Now we're going to do the trunk.
Come on, you didn't think
I was going to make a good tree, did you?
You didn't think I was going to make
a decent tree.
And this is the roots are there
for a very specific green.
Watch, I'm not done.
This one, no.
We're going to change this a little bit.
I want to,
let's go into the tool menu here.
It's actually terrible.
All right, I'm turning on
the ice cream going on.
Hold on a second.
Hold on, hold on.
No, this was checking.
I just wanted to know.
Just was curious to see what it looked like.
We're going to make this
a little smoother.
We're going to ruffle
the black up a little bit.
So let's go ahead and do that now.
Color is fine.
The finish is fine.
Tint is fine.
Actually, I want it to be a little lighter.
Let's go to from here to here.
Let's see if we can make this a little lighter.
There we go.
That's more of like a wood look.
Don't you just want to take
these little wood chips
and just chew them up?
I do.
Okay, back it up into,
we don't need any effects on this one.
We just need to loosen it up a little.
Mmm.
Actually tighten it up.
It's already tight enough already.
I don't hate that.
Yeah, it's a little crooked,
but it's okay.
There we go.
Now it's wood.
It's square like wood.
Now let's hold on.
I'll fix it.
I'll make it straight.
Too big.
Top needs to be shaved a little.
Now this is what we're going to do here.
Oops.
That needs to be way smothered.
I just combed all the flecks like down.
Never mind.
Nope.
Now it's just turning into sheet metal.
No, tight flecks are fine.
That looks more like a trunk.
Okay, let's stick this over here
and combine them.
I think we're good one.
Tint.
We don't need any effects on here.
Unless I want to add,
all right, let me straighten it.
I don't think this ever can be straight.
Is this like an optical illusion?
How do I make this straight?
Oh, come on.
What?
This is an optical illusion.
It don't matter.
All right, we're going to just combine it.
Make sure it's in the right spot.
I almost think the bottom
should be frayed out a little more.
Don't you think?
I think so.
Maybe a little bit higher.
I think that's it.
I think we got it.
Perfect.
Done.
Why are you spending two hours making a tree?
Why not?
It's fun.
I think you're describing this whole game.
That's the whole game.
All right, that's it.
Here's the tree.
So that two hours.
I haven't even lived for two hours.
What are you talking about?
All right, so that's good.
Where's that going to go?
Here's the beauty of this.
And I can go in and change these two.
They're all identical.
Don't you worry about that?
You don't think I fucking thought about that?
You don't think I thought about that?
Don't worry.
Because these are all grouped,
I can go in
and watch ready.
Just change this one.
So let's select this one.
Let's like go into it.
And then see how I have both of these.
Now, go ahead and pull up that menu we had before.
The style menu.
Loosen it up.
Ruffle some feathers a little bit.
Can even add some to it.
And that's done.
Different.
Now I can copy this one if I really so desire.
Oops.
I can't tell the difference.
Well, look, if I really wanted to spend time,
I could do this.
You really want me to do this again?
Because this is how I do it.
Look, I make another watch.
You want me to do it again?
Because I already have an object there now
that's ready to go.
And I could make like two or three more tree leaves.
I'm going to make, no, no, no.
Look, this is just for the like, oops.
I don't even want those there.
No, okay, get rid of these two
because these two are different.
These, and they flow too.
All right.
First of all, this, we're going to change this to stone.
It's freaking me out.
Oops, that was just, that was the ambient sound.
I thought that was fucking, you got a friend in me.
You got a friend in me.
All right.
Now I'm going to RIP Fleshy Ground.
No, we can't just have the ground
be looking like that this whole time.
I need, I need to animate this.
Okay, let's get to the beginning.
Okay, let's see how that looks.
It looks good.
I'm going to make a cubert.
Oh, I want to make cubert now.
I want to make a cubert level.
No, no, no, focus first.
Focus, focus, focus, focus, focus.
So this is what it looks like alive, living scene.
And I'm going to like make this look fucking sick.
I can't wait.
All right, let's change this
because this is, I'm going to put something here.
Do cubert or RIP.
We'll make cubert at the end.
You can just hang out on top of the mountain.
I could redo that, the smoking shit up there too.
All right, so this and I'm going to make it to the level.
It's going to be a platform level
to get to the top of the mountain.
Just I'm biting off way more than I can chew.
Okay, I need, I need to go to the coat tint
and we need to make this shit not skin like flesh color.
What color do I want?
Maybe they could be like a little blue.
Like kind of like this.
It's supposed to be snowy.
It could be like cold and snowy and shit.
Let's try this one.
It's like ice.
All right, hold on.
Let's bring it back a little.
I need to, this needs to be flatter.
That's good.
You know what?
Fuck it.
Let's, now that makes more sense.
Now let me go back into style mode
and let's change this, make it look a little better.
This looks like shit.
That looks way worse.
No, it's going to be flat.
Let's flatten this out.
And I'm going to, I think I'm going to apply some fleck here.
Yeah, we're going to apply a little fleck
and it's going to be the square.
Let's see, is that doing anything?
I don't think it's doing anything.
I feel like I should just,
how did I fuck that up in the first place?
This, you know what I mean?
Why is it like that?
I think I have to, yeah, it was in here.
Right, yeah, looseness, looseness and varying looseness.
It's kind of irredeemable at the moment though.
Wait, what are you doing?
Hey, hey, I don't want to put a circle here.
What are you doing?
I want to edit this.
Wait a second.
There we go.
I'm confused.
Why is it not,
shouldn't I be able just to edit this one?
Because that's what it looks like I'm doing.
Is there a reason why I can't change that back
or am I changing it back?
Is it happening and I just don't, I'm just dumb?
No, see, it's happening to that one.
See what I'm saying?
Shouldn't that be doing the smoothness on this one too?
Oh, it's because I need to be on the stamp tool.
Right, right, right.
Okay, I will forget that a bunch of times.
Don't worry.
Stamp, there it is.
Okay, now I can go in and make this smoother.
Technically, right, should I?
Wait, why is this not working?
I don't understand why I can't change the properties here.
I have no idea why.
I have absolutely no clue
because it's making me change this one.
Put it inside the other shape and just combine them.
I guess I could do that.
I feel like there's an easier way to do it though.
Okay, now edit shape.
No, maybe it is affecting it.
No, it's not.
Well, unfortunately, I have no idea.
I have no clue.
I'm gonna have to go back and watch tutorials again
because I don't have a single fucking clue.
I changed it before and now I can't change it back
for some reason.
Mmm, oh well.
Am I scoped in?
Yo, yeah, I am now.
Like I was here, I'm scoped in again.
Is it because they grouped?
See, like, maybe just edit the object outside of sculpt mode.
Um, edit sculpture.
Will this work now?
I don't think so.
It looks like it's doing something but
maybe I just fucked it up too much that it can't do it anymore.
I guess it is doing it.
Yeah, it is.
I think I just screwed with it too much.
Oh well.
It's editing the tool that I'm using.
Yeah, but is there no way for me to revert this back to
the way that it was before?
It's all right.
Let's keep going.
All right, what's next?
L1 plus square, invisible, movable, collision labels, audio.
No, maybe, hold on.
Scope in and then L1 square.
All right, hold on a second here.
Tint amount.
Shine and, all right, hold on.
This is the actual, like, menu menu of this thing.
Waxiness, metalness.
Okay.
Roughness.
That looks kind of cool.
Hue cycle.
I feel like I don't want to screw with this.
This is the fleck properties.
I don't think this is going to work.
Looseness.
Fleck perspective.
Whoa!
Yeah, I have to have, like, big flecks that I can't really shrink.
Flex, no.
Friction.
No, I feel like I may have gone too far on it.
It's possible.
I can change the, I'll make it a little different.
Waxiness.
Yeah, it's all good.
It's all good.
That looks all right.
It looks fine.
It just looks like it's made out of puff pastry or paper mache.
But that's fine.
I'm just playing around.
All right, what's next?
This next part is, I kind of want to fix this.
And I want to change that to webcam demands.
I'm just, honestly, I'm just trying to focus.
So I haven't really been looking at chat that much because
I've been trying to focus on making trees.
And that's a pretty damn good tree.
But no, I'm not going to put on a webcam.
Why would I put a webcam on?
No, you want to see the beauty of the mountains, not me.
All right, let's go into.
Now, unfortunately, I made, I said I wanted this to be a sculpture.
So I didn't say I wanted this to be a video game.
Does anybody know if does that matter?
Or can I make this a platformer starting like over here and make it over here?
No, it doesn't matter.
Okay.
Well, let's do what I was going to do in the first place.
And let's just put these trees in different places.
And yes, they all look the same.
But you know what?
I don't got time.
I don't got time to care about that.
Because once you do this, it almost doesn't matter.
But I did.
Nope.
Nice grass.
Yeah, I should probably put grass here first.
And this isn't even big enough to have that tree here.
Now it should be fine.
Let's go like this.
That should do it.
Now, what does that look like?
That looks better.
This looks stupid.
That doesn't look like it belongs anywhere over here.
Let's just go like that.
And this needs to be changed.
I need to get in here.
Because that's just sort of sticking out.
It looks bad.
Make it bigger.
Yeah.
Oh, well, I can add a couple later anyways.
Let's get some grass here.
Back to the paint tool.
And I would say what looks the most like grass.
That's not terrible.
Do you know you don't own a single thing in the game?
What do you mean?
That's grassy.
That's good grassy.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Let's get some grass.
What do you mean?
You don't own it?
Or is it one of those scenarios where a media molecule owns the rights?
Well, I guess you have to sign that EULA, right?
Or whatever it is.
All right.
This is grass.
I'm going to do a fun thing called copy this 5,000 times.
They're going to start producing the popsicle.
I just make somebody eating a popsicle next.
God damn it.
Why?
Well, whatever.
Just going to do it like this anyways.
I'm just going to paint it on there.
Why make an object?
There's no reason to even do that.
I'm just going to paint it to the surface and call it a day.
Brush is fine.
Surface snap.
Yeah.
Fuck it.
Let's just paint it on here.
Give me the green.
And it was, which one was it?
This one, right?
Straight up, maybe?
Yeah, that's fine.
That's fine.
Once we get it painted in here, we can mess with the fleck and it'll look like grass.
Chat's bored.
Well, I did tell you what I was going to be doing today.
I did make it very clear that I was going to just be playing dreams
and sculpting random stuff and learning.
I did say that.
You promised Sam and Max.
On Friday.
Today's not Friday.
Check your calendar.
Do the whole stream like that.
You said you're playing other people's maps.
Well, here's the thing.
Nobody made any.
So that happened.
There are no maps with the title German.
Unless somebody made one and I don't know about it.
I've said for the last like week that I was going to be playing dreams today.
And that's what we're doing because I like want to learn how to play it.
Look, I can't make anything unless I learn how to play.
And I can't learn how to play unless I play.
And I can't not stream it because I stream three or four days a week.
So I have to play it.
Otherwise, I'm never going to make anything.
All right, let's see how this looks.
There's only like five new games since the first stream.
Well, it is.
Here's something I will say, right?
This game asks a lot out of the player.
It's very, very much a full video game engine.
When you have like 10 hours of tutorials,
you're expecting somebody's going to want to do it, right?
And this game has been sort of in development
for a very, it's been sitting in development for like what, five, six years?
Maybe they've been desperately trying to figure out how to make the game appealing to people
without requiring them to play for like 150 hours to do anything.
But you kind of have to do that.
It's an amazing art tool, an amazing game and crafting tool.
So it might be a hard sell for most people though,
because I mean that doesn't surprise me
because the game asks, it does ask a lot.
The game's tutorials take as long as like Resident Evil 2 did to beat the whole game.
At least one of the, you know, sides.
All right, let me see how that looks.
Wait, wait, wait.
I don't want grass all the way over here.
I'm going to do a little bit and have it fade out.
All right, let's see what that looks like.
Because now we go like this.
Okay, what's going on here?
What did I fuck up here?
I did, I screwed something up here and I don't know what.
I just want to select this and make it look like grass.
Oh god, this game would be amazing on PC.
Yeah, it's kind of baffling actually
that they would spend this much time making such a cool experience
that you have to control with like the motion controllers or the DualShock.
If I had a mouse, this stuff would be going 500 times faster.
And I think that's going to be a huge problem
for a lot of people that want to get into this game
is they'll just be like, well, why don't I just go play with Unity instead?
You know what I mean?
It's like way too much for like a casual audience to do
and way too little for somebody that has Unity.
It's weird because I'm not sure what audience they're targeting with this game.
But regardless, I need to find out why.
Why is this happening?
There we go, volume brush.
There it was.
All right, here we go.
Okay, come down.
People who want Unity but don't want or don't have a PC or something.
Maybe I'm going to make this a little tinted a little bit.
Put on music.
I will.
Just a minute.
I'm not sure what the fuck this thing is even for.
It just kind of screws everything up.
All right, let's do effects.
And we need to do wave.
That's a little too much.
That's like water.
Flow maybe.
Hmm.
But yeah, to give you like, I guess, I've put the stream for like an hour in like 50 minutes or so.
And the tutorials.
I put probably 15 hours in the game so far.
20 if we count, right?
Like 15 to 20 if you count the first stream.
Are you making a poison swamp?
What is throb?
Evaporate.
Boil.
I really think it just needs to be like wave but just a tiny bit.
That's all right.
It looks fine.
But yeah, I do foresee a very, very difficult time when this releases.
Because like I said, it's almost too complicated for anyone to play it casually,
but not complicated enough for somebody that's serious about it.
Let's change this.
Is that tight?
It is.
Okay, let's see.
Uh-huh.
Oh no, not again.
What happened?
All right, let me.
All right, now let's take this back here.
And I need this look bad.
All right, let's get it.
Wait, I can move a tree now over here.
We've got a good group of green hues.
What's the end game here?
I really don't have one.
I'm just trying to like,
I'm just trying to make sure I know how to use the tools.
And then I'm going to make like the ice cream or something.
I'm going to try to sculpt like a face, but just kind of dicking around.
Let me add some more color here.
Same thing.
We'll do more of this.
Have I tried the move controllers?
I have not used the move controllers for one reason,
because you need the camera.
And I don't have the PS move,
PS4 camera anymore,
because I gave the PS VR to a friend.
So I don't have it anymore.
So I have the move controllers, not the camera.
But I got to pee.
I'll be right back.
And then we'll make like a person.
We'll make like a character.
I'll be right back.
All right, I think I have an idea.
I've got an idea.
Once I get the scene done, I'm going to make the giant that lives here.
Play something else now.
How am I ever going to learn?
You know what I mean?
Like how am I ever going to know how to do anything?
That's been an hour.
See you later.
I'm going to play a different game.
I'll come back and do it again.
When I, yeah, impossible, by the way.
Just learn unity instead.
Imagine learning.
I know, imagine learning anything.
No, no learning.
Only results.
No preparation.
No learning.
Only results.
Imagine actually learning.
All right.
What else do we have for songs?
I should make water down there too.
Yeah, I can't tell you this is going to be the most interesting stream,
but I want to play it.
I want to learn how to do something.
So at least I look.
I was looking forward to this game for a long time, right?
And we're also going to make it rain.
They're going to make it.
Yeah, we're going to make it rain.
I'm going to take my time and I'm going to just try to make something interesting.
Look, what you see here, it's the culmination.
It's going to be in like another hour or two.
There's going to be like a whole village over here.
There's going to be like something going on over here.
I'm just going to make like a big living sculpture.
The only way you can learn is if you do it.
That's the only way.
And it's going to take a little while and that's all right.
I'm going to move this out of the way.
You can also study to learn when.
When would you like me to do that?
I'm going to take two weeks off.
I'm going to not stream for two weeks and come back with like two things
that I made in dreams.
Is that what you want me to do?
You sure?
You were supposed to do that.
I was supposed to take two weeks off of streaming to learn how to play Dreams?
What are you talking about?
What do you mean I did that?
I said I wanted to do the tutorials, which are 10 hours.
And I already did it.
We're talking about when I was with my mother.
Oh, hey, Ma.
Nah, nah, nah, sorry.
We're not what you wait.
I haven't seen you in like eight months.
Yeah, no, no, no.
Just just just just go.
I'm not going to do anything with you.
I'm playing Dreams every day for like six to 10 hours a day.
No, just go home.
I'm studying.
No tutorial is going to give you creativity.
Yeah.
Like, so what do you think I'm doing right now?
Let's get a song.
Did somebody make this?
Final Fantasy Overworld thing.
Bubble tea.
I feel like I want to mix a music.
I want to make a song too.
After I'm done with this, I want to make
I was just like, I want to play list in the background.
I thought my PlayStation just turned off.
I was like, what the fuck just happened?
Let's get the playlist.
Actually, I can't hear it because the PlayStation 4.
But on the moon theme, I feel like that'll get old in a few minutes.
Evil Morty.
Wait, is this an entire playlist?
Whoa, okay.
City folk?
Not again.
Oh, near automata.
Alien manifestation?
I feel like this is kind of soy milk.
Added vocals.
Okay.
Let's see what you got.
Added vocals.
It's just instrument.
There's no added vocals.
Let's go here.
Take the giant.
This is fucking terrifying.
Mama.
Devil in his head.
This is so scary.
It really is with this song in the background.
Oh, that's way too big of an ear.
It looks like somebody is punching through his head.
Through his brain.
That's what it is.
I don't think I can put blood everywhere, can I?
It's got to be way, way thinner.
He's doing a thumbs up.
That's not a thumb.
It's not a thumb.
I gotta get in front of him.
Look at this.
Look at that, like cooked, cut up cauliflower.
I can do it.
Hold on.
I can't.
No, I like it like that.
That's your thumb.
Your thumb bends all the way backwards.
Like a fucking deflated balloon.
It's not even pointing the right way.
All right, so that's his end of his hand.
I'll fix it.
He's sounding like a clown.
All right, that's his arm.
So that's the end of his arm moving up into here.
Into his like, bicep.
Oh my god, this is...
What the fuck have I done?
I gotta keep track of who is who.
Because this is bicep into shoulder.
Okay, so this guy didn't even see him coming.
By the way, it doesn't...
This doesn't matter because I just needed to...
I just needed to look over the edge.
It just needs to be up...
When we take the picture, it just needs to be above there.
All right, so arm and we're gonna have shoulder.
What does he...
What does it look like?
What's like a body look like?
I don't even fucking know.
The big cylinder here.
Tilt it a little bit.
Okay, so that's like chest.
I can carve it a little more.
Hold on.
Okay, let's go down here.
They don't need to see the rest of the body.
And by they, I mean you.
And by you, I mean me.
And by people, I mean anyone.
No, you don't have to see the whole thing.
Because look, I'm gonna move him over here.
He's got somebody's head as a wristband.
All right, let me just...
Let me move them over here.
Maybe I need...
Okay, I might need a little bit of legs.
That gonna be up a little bit higher this way.
That's better.
I love how this shit is moving, but he's not.
So the head doesn't matter because we don't need a head on him.
He needs a body.
I need to take like a good screenshot too.
All right, we need a body on him.
The hair too.
All right, get back in here.
It's a long ass neck.
No, no, no, no, no.
Come down and we'll go like this.
No, that's not his leg.
That's his collarbone.
What is the point of this?
To just use the program and learn how to use it.
And be comfortable using it is pretty much the point.
He's got like a ruffled shirt on.
And then this has to be a little bigger.
And arms will come out of here.
We got a paint job to do too.
He's made out of party cups.
He's made out of paper cups.
Who cares?
He just wanted to be a real boy.
All right, all right, all right.
See from here it doesn't even matter.
I was making a nice scene too.
And everyone got like mad because I wasn't doing anything.
So then I came over and made paper cup monster get punched through his head.
Are you happy now?
Are you happy that I made this now?
Now we're angrier than before.
All right, let me paint this.
I need paint.
Spray can, where is it?
What about the other guy's head?
Well, hold on, I need to get this done first.
These are like paper cups, right?
It's like fucking solo cups.
Snap to surface, let's paint.
Can that face be a new emote?
No, we can only get one new emote.
We'll get the circle that's easiest to paint with.
And spray can and red.
It's not that dark.
I guess maybe it is.
That's a great color.
Red party cups.
Proceed to party.
Careful I don't go all the way up.
Okay, now this is no longer I don't think party cups anymore.
I think this is just the guy's like spine.
I'm gonna make them plastic though.
So hold your horses.
Tighten this up just a little bit.
Okay, I also I have to make this a different group.
Uh-oh, because if I change the coat on this,
it's not going to look right for the rest of the person.
So get me out of here.
This, okay.
So this is, uh-oh, I didn't think this through.
I just kind of was making it because this needs to be a completely separate thing
from the group so I can change this without changing that.
Yeah, see, I was supposed to start a new,
I should have started a new sculpture down here.
I could just erase the neck.
But it's still part of the same sculpture though.
Yeah, I can't break it up.
Shit.
Wait, can I cut out?
Um, I'm not sure what it means by cut out.
Like cut out the, hold on.
Will it just take this whole thing?
Make sure I can see the whole thing.
Let's see what happens.
Uh, did I get it?
Makes it a separate sculpture.
I don't think I really got it.
Um, give me the shape.
Let me just get the square.
All right, how, are they all in?
I think they're all in, right?
Not quite.
Oh my god, it's so hard to control this and get it in the right spot.
I wish I could just have the camera stay put.
Like actually stay in one spot.
I don't want the camera to follow me around everywhere.
I wish I could just keep the camera just like up here.
Just keep it there.
I don't think you can.
Because every time I move, it moves the camera forward.
Did I get it?
I kind of got it.
I missed the bottom.
That's good enough.
So now, what do I do with that now?
Just, that's it?
It's just its own sculpture.
Okay, cool.
All right, so let's give it a finish.
Shiny, where's plastic?
Plastic.
It's already there.
I need something better than that.
Shiny.
I'm not really seeing a difference at all.
Shiny metal.
Hmm, shiny wax.
Shiny, plastic, rough, metal.
Back to here, shiny.
I don't really see a difference.
I mean, I guess a little.
I guess it is shiny, huh?
A little shiny wax.
No, that just makes it look weird.
Well, I mean, it's on there.
Change the lighting.
Isn't there a way to turn on like studio lighting or something?
The guides.
There it is.
Studio lighting.
That's one thing.
I don't think there was a tutorial for lighting.
Let me just paint the rest of this.
So this is going to be, we'll just go with a orange, something blue.
Big like frost demon, frost giant.
That's what it's going to be.
Shit, his head is also a part of this.
Well, that didn't really turn out exactly what I was looking for.
Well, okay.
Close the context menu.
What happens if I...
That's like all fucked up.
I need...
Here.
Here's the problem.
I know what the problem is.
Oops.
You don't know what you're looking at?
Neither do I.
All I know is I need more grass.
Okay.
I need more like snow and shit too.
Because it's got to be much more pronounced than it is.
These tops need to be changed.
That's what I'm talking about.
Should have been like this since the very beginning.
Not individual pieces.
Closer.
They look like clouds.
Yeah.
I think they're just kind of wind.
I'm going to paint snow on.
That's a finishing touch though.
We're not closing it.
We're going to do the same thing over here.
I need to like add texture to this shit too.
Because it looks like...
It looks like shit.
Those mountains look like shit.
You can say it.
You're not going to hurt my feelings.
They look like dog shit.
Say it.
Don't worry.
I can handle it.
Trees moving, right?
That's a good tree.
Hold on.
These are more color.
I'm not sure I like this.
You know what I mean?
I don't think I like it.
I don't think it adds anything.
Nah.
I don't like it.
All right.
Now we're going to do a little bit of work down here.
Because it needs to be some more rocks.
This is too plain.
Looks like a textured...
No.
This is going to be more detail.
They call me Jeremy Mr. Detail Elbertson.
No they don't.
Yes they do.
Okay.
Let's get some snow up here.
I'm going to start with the snow.
I think a splat would look good.
Splat with...
Let's see.
Make it nice and white here.
I don't need the kaleidoscope.
Unnecessary.
Don't need it.
Is it...
What is it on?
Stamp.
Brush.
Brush is fine.
Paint.
Same deal.
No, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
It's flat.
Right there.
Okay.
Why is it blue?
Shiny.
Default.
Rough.
I want it to be this color.
Why is it blue?
Am I missing something here?
Can I like...
No, it's a different sculpture now.
What the fuck?
It actually doesn't look bad.
Sprink it a little bit.
More clouds.
Hold on.
Not yet.
I need to go this.
The top should be snow covered, right?
Um.
What the fuck happened there?
No, let's get this on snap.
It's kind of hard to fucking even see what you're doing.
He's doing Yoshi's Island?
Yeah.
Yeah, you get it.
Like snow, though.
I guess it kind of does.
The clouds sort of ruin it.
This needs to be a different color.
It needs to be like blue or light blue.
It does have to be blue because the more this has to be lighter.
All right.
Back in.
Make the snow glossy.
Yeah, I could do that too.
Fuck.
Oh, I like this.
Don't you want to just lick this mountain?
I do.
I think I could make it a little bit bigger.
Maybe not.
It's getting caught on itself.
And then I also have to do some more detail to the mountains themselves.
Oh, it's the shadow.
I get it.
Okay.
I was going to say, why is it changing color?
Oh, God.
I'm going to throw up.
Oh, honey.
Now I'm going to do the tip last.
Do you think I can copy this and put it over on the other sculptures?
I mean, that's cheating.
But it's okay.
You don't think I could cheat this?
All right.
Let's get up here and get the peak.
And I got to make it snow.
Yes.
It's a little grassy looking, but it's all right.
I'm going to fluff it up a little bit.
Oops.
We need the styles.
Looseness.
All right.
Here we go.
Might be a little too loose.
That's all right.
That doesn't look terrible.
Ruffle them up.
Now I'll pull it back.
I think that looks fine.
This is a little heavy over here, though.
I think I need to move this a little or shave a little bit off
because it's a little heavy handed over here.
Just a little.
This little part kicking up right here.
Right there.
I can't get this one.
There it is.
All right.
I think that's good.
Now should I drop it?
Should I make these bigger and drop them?
I don't think I even need these ones.
I need to add a little bit over here.
A little too intense, I think.
Drop it even lower.
I think I'm getting rid of this one.
Let me see what it looks like.
Yeah.
I mean, like, yeah.
See you later.
That's gone.
Wait a minute.
I think I'm just going to shave it.
I need more, like, over here.
I need to add lore.
Not yet.
I can't do that yet.
My housemates are going to think I'm fucking insane
if they hear three seconds of that song again.
And you just keep replaying a midi version of Bohemian Rhapsody.
No, they're not going to think you're insane.
They're going to think you're learning how to play that song on the piano.
And you keep starting over, over and over again
to learn the first 10 to 20 notes.
Jeremy's going through a rough patch?
What are you talking about?
Hey, get off my case, okay?
I'm trying to learn how to play Dreams.
I might just turn this into, like, a fucking super expressionist
broad painting here.
That means I can move this out.
Make these a little bit.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Look at this.
Look how fucking huge this is.
All right.
The trees are too big.
I figured out the problem.
Now it looks different.
Looks better.
Now we got skill.
That didn't look good.
What happened here?
It's all right.
We're not taking the picture from that side anyways.
I'm taking the picture from...
I don't know.
This is a three-hour long bit.
No, there is no joke here.
Look, not everything has to be a joke, okay?
You know, and in fact, no.
We're just doing a mountain scene.
How does it...
Okay.
I know.
Your roommates are gonna fucking kill you.
Okay.
I took care of it.
These need to be changed.
They've got to look a little different.
By the way, I'm going for it.
No, don't ever tell me that.
You can't, like, change that and make that look all right.
We're taking a photo.
Look, you'll see what it's going to turn into.
It's balding.
It's not balding.
Okay, I want to rotate this.
Not bad.
It's all right.
These need to be changed.
They need to look a little better.
I'm gonna add some more patterns on them.
Some more rocks.
Try and play Dreams, goddammit.
Get up here.
No, mom, I'm studying.
I thought you were gonna show me the Vegas Strip.
No.
There needs to be more snow across it.
I'll fix it.
This is gonna be nice and tidy in a minute.
This is...
I'm just trying to get the gist of it here.
Rome wasn't built in the day.
It was built in, like, fucking over the course of 75 years.
Results, results, results.
I'll give you results.
I'm just gonna wait a little bit.
Just wait till I make my first video game on this spring.
Now, that's really fucking terrible looking.
I just don't need it.
Not bad.
Maybe even more.
Ends lower.
A little too much snow.
Facial hair mountain.
Turn.
Tilt.
Grab.
This just has more snow on it.
It's fine.
All right.
We're getting there.
Now, I need to make a...
This has to come out a little bit further.
There's not enough trees.
There's gotta be...
Maybe like a body of water.
Body of water.
Yeah.
Yup.
Check this out.
All right.
This is gonna be done right.
I'm gonna make, like, a big body of water right here.
A big ice lake.
How am I gonna do that, though?
Paint tool?
And then do, like, circle?
Now, what does that look like?
Let me just see what this looks like.
Now, it's gotta be denser than that.
Although it might not need to be.
That could be decent water.
If it's painted on thick enough, it will be all right, I think.
Maybe a little bit of a...
Let's see.
No, that's fine.
And then I can do flow on it.
But what are the other...
Let me see the other shapes.
Square.
Let's see.
Compare the two.
This one's a little more pixely.
Although I could do a different stroke here.
Let's try heavy.
That's heavy.
Although this looks like ice crystals.
You know what I'm saying?
This is more water-like, but this is ice crystals and chunks of ice.
Let me try something here.
Hold on.
Check this out.
Now, let's go with the square.
I'm gonna change this.
Can I do a custom one of these?
Okay.
I think I can.
Pure mixed.
Save color.
Clear mixer.
Let's go with this.
Add.
And then mix.
Tumble.
Save color.
And then can I...
Can I mix them up to make it so it's a gradient like the other ones?
Whoa.
That's not what I wanted.
This has to be a way to get that...
To do my own gradient.
L1 and direction.
Now, let's just change in the frame.
Mixed.
Well, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Get over here.
Pure.
Mixed.
I'll get it.
I want to make my own gradient.
Oh, well.
Fuck it.
I'm just gonna go with like a light blue.
All right.
You can get out of here now.
I actually kind of like the crystal-y ice looking one.
And I'll add the flow to it and comb it.
This is the most water-like, but I like this one.
All right.
Here we go.
So I need this to be a...
I need like a zone here.
What do I want this?
I want this to start here and come out this way.
Like that and go over here.
Let's try it.
It was this one.
And it was this color.
It was this light one.
And it was wax, shiny metal, shiny.
It is water.
Okay.
Nah, this won't be that much work.
Check this out.
Watch this.
I'm just gonna do it flat.
I'm gonna zoom out.
I'm gonna get a ballpark here.
We'll do flat like this and check it out.
One, two, three.
Why is it on Kaleidoscope?
I never picked Kaleidoscope, did I?
Wait, what the fuck is going on here?
What are you talking about?
Well, okay.
Looks like I'm just gonna have to paint a big one in front of my face.
And we're just gonna have to scale it.
Hydrate?
I will.
When I go on a break, I will.
Don't worry, I will hydrate properly.
Yeah, this looks nice and icy.
Once it starts to move around a little bit and I shape it.
How big does it need to be?
Actually pretty big.
So let's make it actually much bigger.
All right, here we go.
Let's try it.
Let's just get it in there and see if I can...
I can always fix it later.
Well, okay.
Did not know that was happening.
So we're gonna take the...
Give me a break.
Okay, for this one, let's just get it over there.
I need to just get it out here.
I can add to it in a minute.
Let's put it right here.
So I need a lot more paint on this.
A lot more and then it has to wrap around here.
Let's go.
Bring it over here.
What are you doing?
Let's do brush is fine.
I'm gonna snap to surface.
So it should be snapping to here.
All right, here we go.
Why is this a different color?
It's not.
It's just a weird shadow.
And there was a spot here that I need to fill in.
There we go.
Imagine playing MS Paint with a PS4 controller.
I mean, I think you're wrong,
but you're also not wrong at the same time.
You know what I mean?
Okay, it does look pretty icy.
Needs to come across here.
I mean, we don't care about
what it looks like underneath at the moment.
It just needs to exist.
Because all that matters is like here,
a little bit over here too.
It's messy, but it'll get the job done.
It will.
No, it don't matter.
It don't matter.
It just needs to get the job done.
Because guess what?
Now I put like a boulder over here.
Check this, right?
Now give me the, like this.
I'm just gonna see.
I'm just gonna test something.
Okay, and then it's gonna come up here.
Actually, one big one right here.
See, this is the, okay.
I just got a quest.
Okay, this is the worst part, right?
I want to like move it down,
but I can't move it down.
Because it moves my imp.
I just want to move this thing I'm holding straight down.
It's almost like I have to go
with like a strange angle
to like move this back and forth where I want to.
Like, I don't want to move the camera forward.
I want to move this forward.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, this is a tutorial.
I mean, I did the tutorials already.
Because I can go like this.
I can move in and out and all around.
I can circle.
I can go up and down, left and right.
But I want to just move this thing
that I'm holding forward and backward.
You know what I'm saying?
Is it the snap surface thing?
Is that, okay.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
That's not what I wanted to do.
Yeah, but even still though.
Okay, so snap surface is off.
And this is where it gets weird.
All right, so when I'm holding a device
and I hold back, the camera doesn't move.
It's like weird how the camera...
This controls the camera and it also controls...
You see what I'm saying?
I don't want to move forward.
I just want to move this.
Let me move this thing forward.
No, let's move the camera too.
That's awful.
Does it have to do that?
This is to lock the camera.
But when you lock the camera,
you just move in and out and all around.
There has to be a way where you can
not move the camera and just move the device.
You would think it would be maybe like an R?
Like one of the Rs?
No, let's rewind.
Well, whatever.
That's a minor complaint, but it is...
I just don't like when the camera moves.
I wish I could just stop the camera from moving.
You know, let's see how...
No, no, no, no.
No, I want the rounded one.
No, I don't.
What do I want?
There we go.
No, too fleshy.
That's not terrible.
No!
It's his hand coming up from the other side.
It's somebody else reaching up here.
There's somebody down here.
No, no.
All right.
Let's get this rock and frosty colored.
And then I got to change this
because this needs to be like a little...
This has to be...
Well, it could be just ice.
It doesn't have to be that.
It's a giant drowned in the lake.
You know, I'm sure this looks really good in his head.
It didn't look like anything in my head.
You know what?
Yeah, fuck it.
That's a metal hand.
Change the tint.
This is going to be called the War of the Giants.
What color do I want this to be?
Don't you think it should be called that?
Okay, that looks better.
And now let's shape...
Okay, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's a hand grabbing.
It's like right hand.
Face needs to be here.
Now I want some junior mints.
Hold on.
Just wait.
Wait.
I'm studying.
Let me open up the menu.
I got to do the ice first.
Hold on.
Everybody's freaking out.
I need...
We need some glow.
Needs to be bright blue.
Okay.
The finish is already a shiny metal.
Let's go ahead and apply it though.
Not that shiny.
Okay.
Let's go to effects.
Flow.
Too much flow.
It is ice, you're right.
We need a little bit though.
Just a little.
No, you're right.
No flow.
Boil.
It's boiling.
Ha, ha, ha.
Yeah, because it's going to be fire flowing down into it.
No, stop it.
Stop it.
Just like I need to finish this thing.
Wasn't I going to make like a game?
I need...
How are these looking?
These are moving a little bit.
We need some more sounds.
What is playing right now?
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's too much wind.
It's kind of just spinning around.
Where is...
Holy shit.
Whoa.
Ha, ha, ha.
I don't hate this.
I'm going to make it a little bit smaller.
Wait, hold on.
Damn.
It's like the ice.
Okay, hold on.
I need to get...
I got an idea.
Idea, idea, idea.
Back it up.
I'm going to make more of this on the ice.
Okay, close this.
Let's make this a little cleaner.
All right, so now I want to put...
Check this shit out.
You're going to see a real five trillion IQ hyper brain.
We're going to do some lines here.
Just a few.
Just like one of them to paint mode.
We're going to do a...
Don't want the surface snap.
I want a straight line and I want it to be a mist.
So I don't know.
This doesn't look bad.
The scribble is okay.
I think the scribble will do it.
Let me see what the scribble looks like.
Absolutely.
Okay, so here let's show what...
I'm going to show you what I'm talking about here.
We're going to get the scribble.
I'm going to make sure it is white or blue.
Yeah, yeah, it's going to be blue.
Oh, just wait till you see what happens.
You're going to fucking...
Everyone's going to resubscribe after you unsubscribe.
Everyone's going to just resubscribe right now.
Okay, here we go.
All right, okay, easy.
Take this.
All right.
Hold on, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Light sphere, now I need...
Wait, we've got five community subs.
Holy shit, five community subs.
Fucking shitting me.
Thank you to Torati for the five subs.
Where's the way I can make it so they...
It's a pulse or something.
Fade in, fade out.
No, no, no.
It's called something.
What the fuck is it called?
It's called like Pulse.
Where is it?
Pulse.
I know it exists.
Ooh, okay.
Okay, hold on.
Plane, inside sphere.
I think inside sphere is probably the best.
This guy hates his fan.
Salmon or breakfast?
Salmon is I think is...
I definitely didn't say anything,
but I'm going to say salmon.
There, there's like a little bit of mist.
Scale, jitter, probably like that.
And then we can do...
We can take off the fades.
Maybe do the playback.
Maybe do it faster.
Where's like playback speed?
No, no, no, no, no.
Ha ha ha.
Now what would that even be?
Now all I have to do is go like this.
Check this out.
I'm going to do like five or two or three percent.
This is going to be underneath the ice.
This is what I'm going for here.
So it's going to be like crackling ice.
Yeah, now you get it.
There we go.
Now we can just stretch it out a little.
That's what I want right there.
Come on, do the dumb thing I want.
Oh, it's so close.
No, don't touch that.
It's so close.
Oh, I like it.
I think that's all right.
I almost had it broken up a little bit more.
Let me look at it one more time.
Definitely doesn't need to be that bright.
Are you kidding me?
Like, are you kidding me?
There's a goddamn old one under there.
How does that look?
I like it like that.
And then check this.
What we're going to do is this.
I'm going to mess that up a little bit more.
Need a little bit more.
We need a...
Okay, clones.
We need less clones.
That's so much better.
Look at that.
I love it.
I don't think I want to change anything.
Except for that.
Fuck.
I got it.
And wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's not all.
Hold on.
I'm going to loosen it up a little.
So it doesn't look so...
Let's see how that looks.
Ruined?
What do you mean ruined?
Did I ruin it?
It's a little too...
Yeah, a little too much.
Okay, what about...
Okay, this is important.
No, it's not.
This is...
Here we go.
Let's try roughing it up.
Oops.
Wow, look at that ice.
And it made it perfect.
That's perfect.
Loosen it up a little bit, though.
That doesn't need to be as harsh.
Now I have to change the sky.
I will.
Don't worry.
All right.
Let's get a sun over here.
How do I cover the...
Hmm.
More trees that look bad in just one corner?
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
No, you are.
I'm going to say let's get over here maybe.
We're going to play around with some scale here, guys.
Watch this shit.
That could be like a fucking mile away.
What am I making?
Oh, it's just kind of whatever at this point.
I don't really have a plan.
I'm just kind of making random stuff.
Move this around though.
It looks too perfect.
Yeah, this has got to go on the ground.
I can put a little forest back here.
Yeah, that looks bad.
Don't worry.
I'm going to go in here and I'm going to ruffle them up.
Coming together over there.
Although this is a little too big.
Did I walk something up here?
Oh, I did.
Oops.
Are the shirts a limited time?
No, they're here forever.
I got to get the giant hair?
I will.
Let me see the whole thing.
What is this?
I feel like I want to...
All right.
Hear me out on this one.
It's just a little too perfect for me.
That's okay.
Let's do the snow too.
That's kind of cool looking.
That is really cool looking actually.
They're frozen like that.
No, that's fine.
It looks okay.
All right, let's do some work over here.
This game seems amazing if you can't draw and want to make art for fun.
All you have seen me do is just dick around.
That's it.
I haven't done anything else.
I've done nothing else but dick around.
Let's do a little bit of work here though.
Because I need...
You need hair.
What kind of hair though?
Snap it to...
Yep.
Studio lighting.
I want to change the lights.
There has to be a way I can do that.
Has to be.
Right?
All right, hair.
He has made it a metal or stone or whatever it's going to end up being.
He looks like Beaker.
Yeah, he's really not really supposed to be here.
Wait, why is it...
Oh, it's because it's shiny metal hair.
Okay, right.
Makes sense.
Why do I feel like this is going to take up all the frame rate?
This looks like the shittiest toupee you could ever wear.
Am I going to change this?
Oops.
Well, that's fine.
Who cares?
I'm going to have like a little spike.
No, it's a bird's nest.
I'm just going to put a bird in here.
He punched him so hard at his hair.
Okay, well, it's because I'm drawing in 3D.
It's because I have snapping on.
Fuck it, let's go wild with this shit.
Wild, yeah.
You know, wild I say.
He has cosmic horror hair.
You can't even tell what's going on from over here.
Dude, I've got a fucking idea.
Are you serious?
You know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to have it just...
No, never mind.
It's going to take like about three hours.
I definitely have to make his hair flowing like crazy though.
And he needs more hair up here.
Smaller, smaller flex here.
This is kind of getting out of hand.
And I'm going to turn off the snapping.
That's part of the platformer.
Look, wait, wait.
Oh, boy.
More...
Oh, it's a step.
Turning this into a level.
You have to jump through here.
You got to go around the whole goddamn robot.
The whole thing is going to be scalable.
Yeah, you got to run up his hair.
So check this out.
All right.
Hold on.
Down and like flowing down.
I need to see from a clear angle.
Flow it down and come across.
Now, let's go.
Okay, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The hair is going to...
There's going to be another thing going on right here.
We'll do that later.
We're going to make a head right here.
God damn it.
This is so in the way.
It's okay.
It's just like a tiny head.
Okay.
Is this on Steam?
No, it's not.
It's only for PlayStation 4, which is very unfortunate.
The eyes need to be bigger.
Nah, I like it better like this.
He looks like a pumpkin.
Just wait.
Um, a party hat.
It's a baseball cap.
Okay.
Now he needs to be metal.
He's a Tintin.
He's got to have one on like a purple hat.
Whoa, wheezy.
It's the Iron Giant.
It kind of is the Iron Giant in a way.
All right.
Apply the finish.
I want shiny metal, but I do not want it to be that stupid thing.
I want it to be the like spray can.
I don't know why it's on this dumb thing.
It's on like the spray can.
How did I get it off this before?
I just wanted to do it.
I don't remember.
It's over here.
Apply finish.
Let's make him nice and shiny.
I don't like the color.
No.
Let's go back to like metal.
The actual kind of chrome look.
He looks like he's made out of wood.
His head needs to be a little bigger too.
Okay.
He's Mario.
He looks like a Roblox character.
All right.
Now we're getting somewhere.
Now we need a face over here because that's his hand.
I need to see from the other side.
Here we go.
Have him peeking over with a big nose.
You mean like that cartoon character?
That weird cartoon nose thing.
All right.
Where's the hand right here?
Okay.
Now this.
This is where we set up the blending options.
Here we go.
Edit shape.
That needs to be stamped.
It needs to be stamped.
It's this mirror.
Back it up.
Stamp.
Okay.
Now I should be able to do weird shit with this nose.
Why not try to sculpt natural looking faces?
I mean because I'm trying to get used to the tools.
You want me to make like a natural looking face?
I just figured out how to pan like yesterday.
Okay.
Blend amount.
Let's see what this does because now I should be able to.
Okay.
Let me see here.
Yeah.
Look at this.
Where is it?
He's got to come out a little further.
Hold on.
This is not what I thought was going to be here.
You can't even see this guy.
It's got to be much smaller.
There you go.
That's better because it's going to get squished into here.
Okay.
What does that look like?
That's not bad.
That's not a tongue.
This has to go down.
I'm going to have to.
Yeah.
This has to be changed.
I actually think I can do it like this.
That looks fine.
Okay.
Make nostrils.
Well, no, I can't make nostrils because the nostrils are both flat down.
Like sniffing the mountain.
Yeah.
He's going like.
I'm going to look.
I'll show you.
Let me let's I got to go back and finish this.
No.
His eyes are bugging out of his head and he's staring at the mountain.
What does this need to be?
Like that.
Down here.
A little bit more to the right.
Like over here.
Like that.
Okay.
Nose is here.
I mean, I could put the nostrils here.
You know.
What mouth?
Maybe.
Maybe have it like over here.
Yeah.
I don't hate it.
Let me just see.
He's taking a bite.
No, he's just going like.
All right.
That means I don't know what the fuck's going on over here.
I'm going to have to turn these guys, I think, a little and bring them down.
Hand.
All right.
Let's do the eyes.
Those are important.
Let's get right where we need to be.
Right here.
Excuse me.
What just happened?
What's going on here?
Oh, okay.
Let's get the paint tool.
Spray paint.
And let's scare the shit out of everybody that's here.
Because if you weren't concerned right now, you will be very soon.
Just be lower like this.
Okay.
Let's get some blue.
Or, I don't know, black.
Because eyeballs fade into the stalks.
Okay.
That eye is going to be pointed down.
Like down here.
Back it up.
Um, why am I?
What is going on?
I come back here.
Where are you going?
That needs to be, like, crazed.
Much better.
Okay.
I wonder.
Okay, so I'm not going to make him not flesh-colored.
He needs to be metal.
Let's make it fucking even weirder.
I don't think I can do that.
No, that's all right.
I can leave it as is.
Can we use eyebrows?
Yeah, I'll paint them on after.
Maybe it should just be a big guy.
Maybe it's just not even a robot.
Although that would kind of break all the continuity.
Like there ever was one to begin with.
Give him more eyes.
No.
I got another three eyes pointing down.
Just not, not yet, not yet, not yet.
Hold on.
I need to figure out.
All right, so he's this kind of chrome, almost bronze.
Let's go in here.
Let's get that coat of almost like a bronze.
Like this.
I have the finish.
Now that's fucking crazy.
Maybe I might light him up a little bit.
Let's make, hold on.
Maybe like gold.
Yeah, this guy's going to be gold.
Oh no, his eyes.
I can fix them.
I'm not making you gold.
There we go.
All right, now let's do the finish again.
Okay.
I lost a little bit of the gold.
Maybe I should lighten him up to a little bit more.
Maybe that'll be better.
No.
I need like a brighter yellow.
He's not cheese.
Gold is like this.
But I don't know if I can get,
it might have to just be this kind of mustardy yellow.
I'm going to save the color.
Just doesn't look the same.
Doesn't look right with the,
I guess that's close enough.
No, that's just, I think that because of the finish.
Let me remove some of the finish.
That's a, that's better.
All right, there's gold.
Now let's go back to the eyes.
And we'll make the eyes gold too.
Maybe I should make them like physical.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
Wait, what is it?
I was wondering why it looked like that.
It's because it's metal.
I don't want, let's just do default or plastic.
That's better, okay.
Fucking ice cream face.
Oh God.
Great Lord Walden just gave,
I think I'm going to spray paint it.
It just doesn't look right.
What are you doing?
Great Lord Walden is just giving 20 community subs
over and over again.
Twice in a row.
Holy shit, dude.
Thank you for the 40 community subs.
Make it have eyelids.
And let me paint it for a sec,
but that's a lot of fucking subs, dude.
Thank you.
That's an insane amount of subs.
Get it back out.
How do you know when you get one?
Like as I look over and I see
it then blowing up in the chat.
Let's get the spray paint.
It's going to be easier to do it like this.
Circle, okay.
Reason why it's not showing up.
Any guesses?
Hmm.
I have it on paint can.
Why am I missing something here?
Maybe I need to just make it again.
Maybe I have to, let me see.
New sculpture?
No, it's just not coming up at all.
It's weird.
Maybe it's because I had the coat on already.
I'll just do it the way I had it before.
That's actually fucking horrifying.
So I'm going to keep it.
That was white, right?
Why do you look like that?
You're not metal.
Why are you doing this to me?
Well, oh, I got to move on.
I don't know what's going on.
I don't know why this is doing this.
I have no idea, but I got to move on.
God damn it.
All right, I got to pee.
This is driving me nuts.
I'll be right back.
Hey.
All right.
So what I'm going to do next,
I'm going to put a cap on this one.
Just kid this.
When I just came back, I just saw this.
I'm going to save this one
because I want to try something.
I want to try to mold my face.
I just want to see.
I want to just go make a guy
and walk around the world.
So pretty.
Mold my butt first.
I'm not going to mold my ass.
Just drop a puppet in.
Yeah, I wonder.
Let me see.
Let's go back to edit mode.
Yeah, let's drop a puppet in.
How do I do that?
Is it under guides, gadgets?
Gadgets, right?
Gameplay gear.
And it is one of these.
Blank puppet, blank puppet, puppet.
Yeah, one of these.
Don't step on the ice.
You can make like death zones too.
Here we go.
Well, the camera needs to be adjusted.
He's going way too fast.
There's no collision on those.
How do I adjust the camera?
Oh, go back to edit mode.
I want to like pull the camera in.
You have to be adjusted here.
Turn speed, movement speed.
It's way too fast.
Run speed, way too fast.
Okay, jump height.
I'm just realizing something right now.
I think this is very small.
This whole thing is only this big.
It's tiny.
It's very, very, very small.
Oops, I can scale it all up,
but I can scale everything down too.
That's the next part, right?
Okay, so now I want to...
Upper body, movement, behavior.
What is like camera?
I know that exists somewhere.
I've not done any of this yet.
Collision, labels, audio.
Yeah, you can make it first person.
It's just that I didn't do that.
I don't even know if the tutorials exist to do that.
That's something I would need to learn
kind of on my own time, I guess.
Because I don't know if there's any camera options.
But regardless, let's just stick around again.
That guy's so weird.
Oh, it's over here.
Nice trees.
Who made these trees?
These look pretty good.
I don't think I can make the jump over here through the ice.
Oops.
Oh, there you go.
This is the first actual real attempt I've really made.
Yeah, I can make the...
I can have collision under there.
But this was not supposed to be a game.
This was just me messing with the sculpting tool
and moving stuff around.
Yeah, now let's try something else.
I want to save this though.
Me, who cares?
Okay, so this has been saved.
Remix.
Save it.
It's saved.
Exit creation.
Okay, let me try this.
I want to just do this.
You can make like effects.
I could be sculptures and shit.
I don't even know how the hell you would do that.
Make a vehicle.
Make a song.
All right, music timeline.
It's got eight bars.
Let's drag it out.
Let's just go with like 16.
Okay, now I need search.
Search for music clips.
Animals.
No results.
Outer space.
What do you mean no results?
Collections.
What are you talking about?
So here's like media molecules little collection of clips.
Music tracks.
Music clips.
Start here.
Loops.
Drums.
Bass tracks.
Chords.
Rhythm section.
Okay, let's do drums.
Popsicle break beat.
Whatever this is has to be played the whole time I sculpt my face.
I'm going to try to do every detail.
Popsicle.
Okay, we'll do popsicle.
Let's add.
Let's get back in here.
Hmm, we're back.
Let's go to chords.
Yeah, this really is just GarageBand.
You can make your own stuff.
I don't know how to do that yet though.
Hey, this doesn't suck.
All right, let's change.
Let's mess with this though.
So we got pitch.
Well, I didn't, I'm not adding this part.
What is doing that?
All right, well that sounds all right.
What else we got?
Distant traffic.
Okay, let's fade that out.
I'm putting the Bohemian Rhapsody sample.
This is the beginning.
Bang!
Right here.
Lightning strike.
I need to go search by categories.
Projectiles.
Crossbow.
Pew Blaster.
We need special effects.
Wait, you got it.
And then get the other one.
Oh my god, that was fucking long.
Which one of these?
This is the first explosion.
I don't want this part.
No, actually I do.
Just get in here.
Just, I just need one.
That's just too loud.
I don't know why that's so loud.
Playback speed.
Like, does it have to be that loud?
And this is only going to happen for like a second, right?
Can I put the timeline here?
Yeah, I want to play from here.
Okay, now let's go back here.
Can you do your own voice?
Yes, you can.
I need like a heavy guitar.
Go back to the main menu here.
I need this most recent, no, tags.
Animals.
Starting point.
Phases, phrases and loops.
Track.
It just turns into Africa.
I think this is kind of broken right now.
Collections.
Because if I go to all, I want to do categories.
Category music.
Tag.
Tags A to Z.
Blues, animals, classical, like classical.
Okay.
Dance, country, it was like rock.
Heavy metal.
There we go.
Turn the game volume back up.
I like it.
Let's see.
What?
I don't know why it has to be that loud.
No, no, no, no, back, back, back, back, back, back.
What does this sound like?
Why can't I want to play it from here?
Why is there a dial tone?
I don't know.
I'm just putting stuff in just to see.
I haven't played with this yet.
The perfect theme song for Jerma Popsicle.
I don't want this to go all the way.
These really aren't supposed to be.
Unless you have a real idea where you're going to make your own song.
I don't know if more than 16 bars, 24 bars of a loop is a good idea.
You really need to come in and make your own stuff.
But I don't really know how to do that yet.
I don't know how to play around with the timeline, but nothing else.
All right, let's sculpt my face.
I'm not going to do music.
It'll take all day and I don't know how to do it.
So we're not going to do it.
So here's what we're going to do.
That sounds like 2013 Garage Band.
Yeah, it's probably very similar.
So here's what we're just going to put on something easy.
There, there you go.
So I'm going to try as hard as I can.
Let's see if I can do it.
I'm going to try to sculpt my face.
At least the front part.
I'm not going to put the explosion on loop.
I don't even know what camera this is.
Is this the right camera?
Let's find out.
It is.
So I'm going to just take a screenshot of my face
and I'm going to try to get it correct.
So there we go.
Let me change this and it should show up now.
Just want a little screenshot.
Yeah, we'll do the beard too.
Okay, ready?
I can't take it.
How am I supposed to take it?
Okay, ready?
I got an idea.
Okay, got the screenshot.
Get a profile shot too.
Hold on, hold on.
I can't do all that at once.
Is it out of sync?
Hold on.
Let me get the first screenshot.
I'm going to do this first.
Like it's going to be so much easier
if I get my other monitor back.
Oh my God, you piece of shit.
I don't ever buy a monitor
that has a fucking touch pad on the right.
It's a piece of crap.
Like it's a piece of total crap.
All right, this is a...
I don't even look like a real person.
All right, hold on.
Save that.
Oh my God.
I hate computers more than anything.
Save that.
I bet you I could probably get it pretty close
and then this side too.
I need to bring this over here.
Okay, I got it.
Wait, what?
Why is it a different image?
It's taking a screenshot of every,
of all three of my monitors.
Oh my, hurry the fuck up.
What are you doing?
I hate computers.
I can't wait till we go back to fucking newspapers.
I swear to God.
All right, I'm gone.
I'll be back.
I got to add the zits too.
There's like two zits.
All right, let's get them on screen.
When it looks like lit up better.
Okay, so that's what I'm going for.
I need these references like on my screen.
I'm going to put it down here.
That's for you.
It's your super face cam.
Make them kiss.
So now I also...
Bear with me here.
Those are three different people.
They are not.
I can assure you.
Now I get them over here.
All right, here we go.
Let's see how close I can get this.
I'll spend four hours on this.
I could care less.
All right, time to begin.
So we're going to start with...
We're going to go with the front.
Okay, so we have to go with the circle.
Or maybe like the cone.
It's probably cone.
No, no.
So let's start with the forehead.
And then it comes down here.
I just need like a base.
I don't think I can fucking do this.
I need like a base first.
To do this correctly,
it's going to take like 50 hours.
This is like an actual art project.
There you go, done.
Who is that?
No, no.
What character is this?
It's a cookie character or something.
What's the character?
There's his mouth right there.
This is eyes.
Who is this?
Oh my God.
It's like a fucking serial character.
This and then let's shave off.
Let's get in there.
What are you doing?
That was weird.
Why does it look so weird here?
All right, let me see what we got.
Does this part stays up a little?
Is that the mouth?
No, no, no.
This is like the side of the head.
This is not the nose.
I just need to get like the general shape.
Once I just get...
Let me just like get off the edges here.
I think I may have made it too big.
All these controls are killing me.
This comes in like this.
Circle's not going to work.
It's all right.
I'm doing it.
I've already started.
I don't know.
It's not going back now.
Maybe the side.
Oh my God.
This is going to take forever.
This is going to actually take forever.
I know I can do this.
Where's mirror?
Okay, there it is.
I believe I can do it on both sides.
There we go.
Okay, zoom out.
It's getting there.
I wish I could just see it all.
I don't want to like have an axis of it.
I want to like see it the whole thing
and be able to do it
and not have to move the fucking camera around.
I want to stay here.
I don't want to move in.
That's like the biggest gripe I have with the game.
I would love to just lock the camera here
and like be able to move around
and sculpt from here.
No, I have to move forward.
I can't like lock the camera.
I don't think there was anything
in the tutorials talking about
to lock the camera in place.
Well, let's just keep going like this.
Just do it in Blender.
It's free.
It probably would be easier to do this in Blender.
Look, I know I can hold R1
and rotate all over the place,
but I can't paint like this.
I can't do anything.
I have to move forward.
It's just really odd.
The fact that the camera moves with you
while you move to sculpt
is just very, very odd
that they would do that.
But it doesn't move backwards.
All right, we're getting there.
These are correct.
I just want to lock the camera.
That's all I want to do.
Okay, I must get the initial shape.
This has got to go back here though.
I'm just turning it into a bike helmet.
Okay, so let me go up.
No, no, not up.
I need to keep these here.
This has to be changed though.
Let's go square back here.
Just remember, don't do it wrong.
What do you mean don't do it wrong?
This is immensely difficult to control.
Dude, you know what?
Does it really have to be motion controlled?
I heard somebody said
that they were making a non-motion
controlled part of the game.
Like, can I just turn this off?
I don't want this.
They're adding control methods.
Thank God.
A sculpting general grievous.
It's just hard to get anything.
I'm just, ah, it's,
I'm almost ready to start doing details.
Look at the side of my face.
How am I ever going to fix this?
I'm going to look like a fucking imbecile.
I'm going to look like a, like an alien race.
That's close enough.
Let's see what's in front.
All I care about is the front and the sides.
Take this in.
No, I don't have, this is like turkey neck.
Okay.
All right.
I'm ready to start doing,
get rid of the mirror.
What does my face look like?
Let's see.
I'm going to start bottom to top.
I need the cylinder.
I have it on.
Okay.
Here we go.
I need to do surface mode and blending, right?
Oh, it's no, no, no, no.
Not blending.
So this, my nose, where's my mouth?
It starts like this.
I need to go.
All right.
So then what's supposed to measure it from here?
It's like up here.
And this is where the nose starts.
Right there, like right here, actually.
And then it's still a little bit like a bulb this way.
It's a little thicker up here.
It's like two people playing volleyball.
I need to get it right from this side.
This is a fucked up.
This is not even close.
Looks like somebody took their hand and smashed it into my face.
They just bombed me straight in, squished.
Oh, man.
No fucking way.
It gets wider here.
Look at this.
Okay.
Let me look over here.
It's kind of flat right here.
No, this is like just growths all over my nose.
Okay.
Eyes.
But hold on.
I have some like dips here.
No, that's not going to happen.
So let me see what the eyes look like.
Go.
How close are they?
This one's kind of close to my nose.
This one's a little further away like this.
Okay.
And then I have like kind of a big brow bone that sticks out.
This.
I'll get this end here.
And it kind of comes down like this, but they don't connect.
And then the forehead.
My forehead's a little longer than this.
I can't add to it though.
Let me check over here.
I want it to go like this.
Back this up.
Let's take all this out.
It doesn't need to be here.
Oh, God.
Don't cut the whole thing off.
All right.
I have to add the hair, so don't worry.
I'm just like a moon face.
Oh, well.
All right.
Getting better.
My internet design?
My internet's going fucking crazy, huh?
New emote?
Not yet.
Am I going to stream here or what's going on?
Dropped like 15,000 frames.
What the fuck is going on?
Shave this part off.
I can cover this with hair, so I'm not concerned about that.
Question is, is this correct?
Not really.
No.
Give a goddamn camera.
Let me go in here.
The mouth is wrong to try to fix this.
I have a big bottom lip.
Somebody put some indents on my face.
Let me just patch those up real quick.
The nose is way too far away from my mouth, and the eyes are not correct.
But I think we can move on.
The nostrils are there.
I need to go back here.
All right.
I need to do paint.
Go to tint.
That is kind of my skin right now.
I don't think I need to change that.
Just spray paint?
No, no, no.
It's got to be...
Well, let's go to the paint tool.
Let's grab this one.
How does that look?
No.
These would be like the veiny one.
Even worse than that.
Worse than that.
What's my beard look like?
It's really stringy and terrible.
No, not like that.
I'll probably just go with veins.
And then the color is dark brown.
Okay, and snap that.
Oh my god.
Okay.
It's like that.
No, it's not.
This is not like glued on a hair.
Wait, what happened here?
Oh, should I need to side?
No, no, no.
Not yet, not yet.
This does look like my beard.
It looks terrible.
Okay.
And you didn't think that looked like my beard?
Come on now.
Cox is trying to kill the stream.
Yeah, they do that, don't they?
Let's put the eyes in.
I can do the hair too.
Paint.
Hair, I'm going to say, would be...
I know how it looks.
Probably expressive.
Yeah, it's definitely going to be expressive.
Same color too.
Okay, so this swoops down over here.
It goes around here.
What's happening?
What do you mean?
My hairline is not higher than this?
What are you talking about?
It's already awful.
It's already so bad.
Friar tuck.
Hold on.
You look like a stooge.
Just let me get it all on there before anybody makes fun of me.
I'm going to comb it.
I have to comb it first.
Which side does it go down?
Not that one.
This one.
I'm going to try to comb this and we'll see what happens.
German looking low-key cute in this image here.
Thanks.
I appreciate that.
I don't think this is going to work.
I may have given up.
I may have given up a little.
Not completely.
100%.
Although blurry, squint your eyes a little.
I'm going to finish it.
Don't worry.
I came this far.
You think it was not going to finish?
I'm going to turn into a Final Fantasy character.
What's with the hair not being over here?
Oh my god.
And why does my internet suck?
Almost done with this part.
This needs to be fixed over here.
I just need a little more going this way.
It's very flat.
My hair is not that flat.
It does look like a wig.
All right.
I need...
No.
Back it up.
Put my eyes in there.
And then I'll do some more detail.
And I need the...
No.
I need the spray paint tool.
Paint.
I'm going to go white and spray paint.
This no joke looks like a skinny version of my dad's face.
Does it?
All right.
Okay.
I'm going to do one circle of black.
Which it's like here.
No.
I need blue.
Blue first.
What kind of blue is it?
It's like a slate blue.
It's like this.
Thank you.
I'll take it.
Yes.
I'd love to paint with this, please.
It doesn't help.
Don't worry.
We're going to do terrifying nightmare face Jeremy.
Red.
All right.
What kind of red?
It's not that red.
It's not that red either.
This is very, very, very bad.
It's okay.
It's like this.
There we go.
That's better.
This just needs to be sculpted by somebody that knows what they're doing.
Not me.
All right.
I don't know why this hair looks so strange.
No, no, no.
I don't want to paint.
This doesn't look right.
It just doesn't look right.
No.
Somehow that looks better.
No, I forgot the eyebrows.
You're right.
But this needs to be...
I just look like Tom Green.
Maybe it's...
Maybe let me paint the...
Let me get the eyebrows painted on.
And then what else to do about this?
Let's try eyebrows and see if that helps.
Kind of helps a little.
My face is too rounded over here.
See?
That could be me.
I definitely...
I'm going to do...
Yeah.
The hair is too fucking stupid looking.
Okay.
The hair is wrong a little by a little bit.
Let me try to fix that.
All right.
So here.
Get your screenshot now because I'm going to try to fix it.
Okay.
Makes you a little stranger.
What if I doesn't kill you?
I went a little too far.
Nightmarish.
You ain't seen nothing yet.
Which color is it?
This one?
No.
What's like the regular just standard?
Just default one.
How do I just get default color?
Oh, whatever.
Save this one.
There is a color...
This is like the color picker.
But I don't understand how this works.
Like pure and then mixed.
I...
I don't understand how this is...
Custom picker, right?
And then pick a shade.
Okay.
But it's not doing it.
And then it's like, whoa, this is...
Save color.
Well, then it's confusing.
It's like the eye drop tool in a way, I guess.
No, that's not going to work.
Must be bigger.
Come on now.
Come on.
What are you waiting for?
I'm trying to do like a jaw breaker.
Like I'm chewing on a big bubble gum thing.
It has to be on the other side too.
Because I'm like crunching on this side.
A little too much.
Do you have to be like this game?
Do you have to be like this?
What's going on?
What's the problem?
There's no problem.
Stop snapping.
Don't be like this.
I need like a wincing face too.
No, I should be blowing like a bubble.
Oops.
Not that deep.
Pull it forward a little.
Jesus.
Pretty good.
I'm going to turn the nose a little bit.
Like if I was...
It should be pulled up a little on this side.
You have to animate this?
The eye doesn't...
I don't even know how to do that.
Turn this down.
These eyes have to close a little.
This.
It just looks like somebody beat him up.
These brows need to change a little.
Oops.
Like that.
All right.
The nose needs to connect to the eyebrows.
Does it though?
No, he's eating the big candy.
All right.
Now I'm going to make my body.
What do I have on?
Blue shirt.
Bookers all over the nose.
Okay.
Not bad.
No, that's...
I'm an earthworm.
A little lower.
That looks all right.
Okay.
And let's do some more work over here.
Don't give it arms.
Why not?
Okay.
Let's group these together.
They already grouped?
Are they grouped already?
I got it.
They are.
Okay.
I need to do it a little differently though.
Why is everybody so horrified?
I can't make a fucking monster?
Turn the snap back on.
Yeah, that's actually a good idea.
Let's get down in here.
And now I'm not even going to just copy.
God.
I hate that so much.
Oops.
Stand back.
I'm going to vomit.
All right.
Fine.
I'll conclude it here.
But not yet.
I have to put a blue shirt on them.
And I have to put them on like a stone pedestal.
Oh, fuck.
I never grouped these together.
Oopsie daisy.
Looks all right.
Oh, didn't group those together either.
Going so slow.
No, deselect.
Am I selecting the beard too?
I hope so.
Okay.
One, two, three, four.
What?
I thought this game was going to make me puke.
Okay.
Grab.
Two, three.
Group them.
What are you doing?
No.
Now I have to ungroup this shit.
Oh, I'm about to fucking exit the game.
I'm just trying to group these together.
I did it already.
Oh my god.
Okay, that's better.
I'm not even sure this is attached.
No, it is.
All right.
Now for the final finishing touches,
I need to put a little t-shirt on them
and then turn this into stone.
Mad because bad.
It takes a lot of fucking work to figure this shit out.
Even still, I still don't know what the fuck I'm doing.
Now let's do this.
And then I want to make this stone.
I'm going to make them shiny.
Let's go with a shiny.
See what this looks like.
Perfect.
Nice and sweaty.
Oh, it looks like it's made of the glass.
Okay, now the color is fine.
Although I do need to change the color of this
because I just want this to be stone.
Yeah, just like a little place to show off.
Maybe a little bit darker.
I think that's better.
I'm going to make glowing red eyes.
I don't even know if I can do that.
Oh, I can definitely do that.
Glowing red, you got it.
I still have to put a t-shirt on them.
Okay, let's make these glow red.
I want these things to move around too.
They moving?
I don't think so.
He's wet, but I'm going to put rain in.
Thanks for telling me.
Let me glow.
Where is it under?
Is it under style?
Yeah.
No, it's not.
Where is it?
Glow right here.
Glow.
Now I want this to be red.
This glow, glow.
It works.
That's got a lot of glow.
I don't think it works.
How about blue?
Because my eyes are blue.
Why is it still red?
No, whatever.
All right, rain.
So we need paint.
I've got to go over here.
We've got to do the ruler.
We're going to put like fucking lightning and shit in the background.
I have to add a penis.
No, I don't.
I don't have to do that actually.
I'm going to do straight line, right?
Straight, make it blue.
Okay, now I should be able to...
Hey, hey, hey, what are you doing?
Hey, hey, hey, where's the other one?
Oh, just like blend in.
And now I should be able to open up this menu.
And we're going to go to animation, playback settings.
There we go.
Trail length.
Okay.
That's taking a long time to fall.
Not the best rain I've ever made.
Zoom it out.
I think I made them too big.
Animate in sequence, pulse, spread.
There we go.
Jitter.
It needs to be better looking though.
Looks weird.
Get this out of the way.
I wonder how...
I need this to go faster.
There we go.
Okay.
Not really.
I thought I had it.
Because these need to be spread out a little bit more.
The effects.
Boil.
No.
Evaporate.
Ooh, okay.
There we are.
That's how we get droplets.
And throb maybe?
They're just in weird places.
Maximum throb.
Let me go down here and like look up.
Yeah.
I'm close.
I'm really close.
It's just not quite there.
Almost there.
But not quite.
How are you talking without moving your mouth?
That's like ice.
Maybe you just shrink it.
Drop the opacity too.
Hey, look at that.
It looks a little better.
Turn it down.
Oh God.
I can't turn it down.
All right.
That's good enough.
Now we just need some scary sounds.
It's almost like a windstorm.
Ooh.
I actually like that.
That really really does look like a windstorm.
All right.
You guys.
You guys remember.
I'm gonna take these off now.
Kim just brought up this.
Look at this.
I feel like I'm having like dreams again.
Of this same.
This is like the same amazing dinner.
Is it the same day?
This is fucking awesome.
She just made it apparently.
I like it the way it is.
I like it like that.
I am going to put on some song here.
Some music.
No, I don't want sound gadgets.
I just want like rain and thunder.
And scary music.
Right here.
All right.
Rain.
This means this is the field where you hear it.
But you'll hear it the whole time anyways.
Now I need like lightning strikes.
I like that too.
All right.
Now I need scary music.
Okay.
So you guys.
I couldn't go in fast enough.
Really.
I was trying to go in really fast to his face.
All right.
I think that's going to be it for dreams for now.
Unless does it does anybody?
Did anybody make something?
I could hear that from my kitchen.
Let me check again.
I'm going to save this as a final.
My creation three.
Imagine coming across that thumbnail.
Okay.
Here's what I made today.
Those of you that didn't see this before.
I will show it to you.
It's the ice cream.
That's so fucking funny.
I can't believe that.
I forgot about that.
Germapopsicle.
Or Germapop.
I don't know what that'll be.
I love how I just made a better version of this today.
You don't talk about progress?
All right.
Look at this.
Take a look at that thing.
Tell me that I didn't make progress today.
Okay.
You don't think I made progress today?
And then what was the other one I did?
I spent like three and a half hours on that other thing.
I don't even remember this one.
Oh God.
Oh yeah.
Now I remember.
I wanted to fix this.
King of the Monsters.
Oh, well there you go.
There are those are my three dreams that I was able to come out of my head
in the last 12 hours.
And I'll tell you my final assessment of the game so far.
Well, finalism.
I think we dropped a lot of frames too.
I think this game is really, really good.
It's really awesome.
I love the idea.
I just want, I want some different control schemes.
Because I would almost much rather the camera be the gyroscope.
Like I can tilt the camera around and have it set to sensitivity
and use the sticks to move other stuff around.
I don't know how true this is,
but someone who's mentioning that a mouse and keyboard, right?
Does that work?
That sounds worse.
I really just don't know.
It's hard to make a game like this on console that has this much detail.
And the journey so far.
Depending on, I know a lot of people were saying earlier in the stream
and I kind of lashed back about how this is a boring stream or whatever.
But this is really the time that I have to do it.
You know what I'm saying?
And sure, I can turn the stream off right now and go play it again.
But, you know, there's other things that I have to do.
And speaking of other things, just trying one of those tomatoes.
I gotta get this off the screen.
Okay, there we go.
Not every stream has to be like 100 miles per hour.
Yeah, I know.
And I'm honestly just trying to learn a new game.
You can't know everything and know every single thing works
in the first 10 to 12 hours of a game that's designed to put hundreds.
But I know that people want to see more high octane kind of stuff on the stream.
But I don't really have any other option than to stream it.
Because if I don't stream this game,
that look, for instance, like tomorrow and Friday, right?
I'm not playing Dreams.
I'm not learning more things tomorrow.
But it's all good.
Surf some more?
Yeah, well, we will do this all tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Well, I'm not, no, the stream's not over yet.
Because I do want to search for to see if anybody made any German related stuff.
J-U-R-M-A.
But tomorrow is going to be, the start time is going to be different.
Let me see.
Depending on when I get up tomorrow, I might go early, like really early.
It's either going to be really early or a little bit later.
All right.
We're going to looks like we're going to be an early boy tomorrow.
And when I say early boy, I mean early.
This is an EU friendly stream tomorrow.
I'm probably going to because auto has an appointment at the vet at 5pm Pacific.
So I'm going to try to start the stream tomorrow somewhere around like 11 or 12.
Stream for about five or six hours.
So you're going to get a really early one tomorrow.
No, he's fine.
He's fine.
He's good.
He just needs to go get a shot.
He gets a shot every three to four weeks because he has Addison's disease.
11 or 12 Pacific or Eastern Pacific.
So somewhere around like three, three ish pm Eastern is when the stream is going
to start tomorrow.
He has Addison's disease.
What am I going to stream?
That's a good question.
I really don't know.
Uh, there's a couple of options, but I really I don't know more dreams.
Um, maybe maybe maybe maybe make a game next time.
Like a little platformer.
I don't know.
Jet Island.
I my VR is all packed up right now.
I don't know.
I'll figure it out.
If it's not dreams part two or part three, then it'll be something else with that.
I am going to switch back to the game.
And we're going to look to see if anybody has anything.
Browse all and I believe, um, do I have all this stuff?
No, no, no, no.
I want to just get these off.
Well, should I leave them on?
Should I leave them on?
People probably coming in this room just being like, what the fuck is this dude doing?
Germa.
Bring it back.
Oops.
J E bar may.
Oh, wait a minute.
We got a couple.
Look at that.
All right.
This is germa test.
Let's try this one.
Uh, just what's what is on my face?
I'm just in a constant permanent dab.
That's a pretty nice bog too.
All right.
Hold on.
I want to get like a close look at this.
Look at that face.
I'm skipping with one foot.
My right leg's really bothering me lately.
That's fucking hilarious.
All right.
Let's go back.
What was that one up?
And this is germa jup.
Germa jupiter.
I think it's just a painting, a little sculpture.
Yep.
Okay.
And it has an ass.
Of course it does.
Why wouldn't it have butt cheeks?
What's the other one?
We got germa old.
Germa old and germa old.
This is a game after streaming for 75 years.
F tier boomer decides to retire, choosing to leave Vegas for the sticks.
He can't help to feel something follows from his past.
This is for real.
What's in the shed?
What a nice compact cabin, says me.
Yeah.
Is that it?
What about outside maybe?
What the fuck?
Six months later, a noise outside.
How do you make grass like that?
Better go check what it was.
How do you make grass like this?
How do you make trees like this?
What's this trail?
All right.
How long did it take you to make this?
How long did it take you to know how to do this?
Oh wait, there are just assets in the search bar.
Less time than it took you to make the scorpion ice cream.
All right, what's over here?
Is it a bunker?
What the fuck is going on?
I think these are the same thing.
That was fucking awesome.
For germa!
What's this one?
What's this?
Song made for me?
I want to see the timeline.
When I simply remember my favorite things so bad.
You thought it was going to be a gnome?
No, that's pretty good.
What is this one?
This is a remix of...
Is this supposed to be me?
So, okay, I see what you did here.
You got this asset from somewhere
and then you put this fucking head on it
with the Crusty the Clown hair.
That has to be what it is.
Remix.
I love how it just kind of just feeding in here.
Mystic Manor Preview.
What is this?
Mystic Playground.
Haunted Hedge Maze.
These are all going to be levels.
This is pretty great.
I mean, this is great.
It is.
What did mine look like?
Let me do that.
That's fucking awesome.
I think that's it.
What about mine?
That's so detailed.
Is another test.
All right.
That was fucking cool.
Maybe I'll do it again tomorrow.
Let me see what I made.
What did I do?
Let's see mine.
Pretty sick.
I have to publish that one.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I need to like name it something better
than my creation 8.5 2019.
How about Worm Worm?
Sad Worm?
How about my creation dash Worm?
Worma.
Worma?
Release.
Save and release this version online as public.
Discoverable, accessible, and remixable by everyone.
Version notes tell you you're a collaborator.
It's not the dream.
It's anything you want to say about this.
I want to do like point.
I want to go.
Hold on.
I got to give release notes.
How do I go down?
There we go.
Zero point nine.
Zero point three.
Zero point seven.
Zero point nine.
He's going backwards.
No, he's...
Hold on.
Made Rain.
And then 1.0.
1.0.
Okay, there we go.
There are your patch notes.
Release.
Release it.
Here we go.
Wait.
Making something public is forever.
Once you've made something public,
you won't be able to take it back.
You will only be able to stop it from appearing in searches
by unlisting it in the creation setting.
Do you want to continue?
I can't thumbs up my own thing.
Full credits.
Audio.
Oh, wait, because the song.
All right, that's it.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
I'm going to do the bits and the subs and all that stuff.
I may play this, but remember,
we're going real early tomorrow.
Starting somewhere around 11 to 12 Pacific time.
That's wrong.
It might be dreams.
It might not.
I might jump into something else.
We're going to go back.
I missed a lot today because I was just really focused
trying to make sure I was doing things correctly.
But six and a half hours ago,
we had $15 come in from Bill Buttlicher.
Thank you, Bill.
Thank you, Mr. Buttlicher.
I appreciate it.
Long time YouTube viewer.
I don't get a chance to watch your streams very much
because I work all the time.
But thought I would show some support
for all the hours of entertainment
you give me over the years.
Thank you.
Um, I was on YouTube for a long time.
You must have been around for a while.
But always a pleasure to have anybody pop in
that's been around for a long time.
Thanks for the $15.
And thanks for the literally hundreds of hours
you've spent hanging out watching content.
It means the world to me.
Thank you.
Snooze and Coffin, thanks for the $2.50.
Jerma, thanks for the stream.
I can't watch it all today
because I work tomorrow at 10 30 a.m.
And it's 2 a.m. here now.
I was hoping for a stream like this
and I was worried you already prepared
something beforehand.
I look forward to working on dream stuff.
Apologize alongside you tomorrow.
Also, are you using the motion controls?
Heard they're superior in terms of sculpting.
I'm not using the motion controllers
but the most controllers I've heard
they're good for sculpting
but they're awful for everything else.
So I've seen people switch between them.
Actually switch between them when they sculpt
they use the move controllers.
I might just try.
You know what?
Why don't we just fucking keep playing it?
You know what I mean?
Well, my blood's just beating around the bush
like I don't know maybe like
I obviously want to put time into it.
We'll do it again tomorrow
because I can't think of anything else
that I would be doing tomorrow.
It's Friday, Sam and Max.
Unless something comes up
that I know that I would rather do.
So I do apologize
if you're one of those people
that don't really want to watch
this kind of stream.
But don't worry.
Don't worry.
There's gonna be something fucking crazy
in like a week or two anyways.
So don't worry.
I'm slowly trying to like eat
and not make a bunch of noises
but I'm ready to dunk you.
I hope you are.
Thank you snoozing copter.
Thank you daddy.
I'm just gonna say daddy.
Thank you daddy for the 15 dollars.
Thanks for the laughs through the years you goober.
Thank you daddy.
You might think it's weird me saying that
but it would be really weird
if I said the rest of the name.
So thank you for the 15 dollars.
Thank you so much for hanging out here.
We also had...
Oh I got cut off here.
Spaghetti thanks for the five dollars.
Funniest streamer on Twitch.
Jermafireman.
I should make fireman.
I should make like a fireman game.
Like a volcano of lava.
I know what I'm doing tomorrow.
Thanks for the five dollars spaghetti.
The Jack thanks for the five dollars.
I want to take a screenshot
print it out and hang this on my fridge.
I'm enjoying your child finger painting
in 3D stream.
Well thank you.
Thank you demonic cucumber for the 250.
This stream is just the writing
my sci-fi post-apocalyptic novel
silence is appreciated joke for five hours.
But I know but it's like I...
Do I have to lash out again?
You're gonna make me lash out again?
I lashed out.
I did.
I put up the shield and I defended myself.
I was like shut the fuck up!
Shut up!
What'd you say?
What'd you say to me?
For like an hour straight.
And then I just I got I got confused.
I was looking at a mirror
and then I went on to talk to um chat.
It was like oh anyways um yeah you guys
I'm really trying to work on
to be better at dreams and
don't make me lash out again.
Was it like the war brand stream?
No no no no.
There was just a certain percentage of people
that didn't want to watch me do this
and I said
okay and that was it.
But no.
I kid.
Thank you for the 250.
Thank you to Smotherum.
This is 50 dollars from Smotherum.
I missed 50 dollars.
5,000 bits from Smotherum.
Your lake seems to have many layers
Mr. Jermis Sir.
Your lake seems to have many a layer.
It did.
Did I have too many layers?
Thank you for the 50 dollars.
That's an insane amount of money.
Thank you.
Freudian weapon.
Thanks for the 250.
That's quite the masterpiece
you're making.
Nicely done.
Practicing.
Daddio.
Thanks for the 10 bucks Daddio.
10 dollars from Daddio.
Anything I can do to help you through art school.
Hey thanks.
Future gamer.
Thanks for the 250.
I had a dream that involved you.
The dream started with me on this huge cube shaped building
and I decided to enter it.
I soon found out that I was trapped inside
so I started looking for an exit.
I somehow knew that the very center of the building had horses
and horses would help me escape so I head there.
I was walking and I saw a weird gray slime start flowing out of a wall
and in my head that meant that a monster was nearby.
I grabbed an axe and killed it.
I kept going.
It was at this point of the dream that I found my actual house.
I went to my bedroom and went on Twitch to watch you stream.
You were making your way through the same cube shaped building
trying to find the horses.
People in chat were all arguing in caps about how there were no horses
and that you were going the wrong way.
I turned off the stream and tried to sleep
but I was too scared that a monster was going to enter my room.
I just sort of ended up in my bathroom and took a bath.
I was just relaxing in my bathtub trying not to freak out from possible monsters.
All of a sudden more of that gray slime burst out of the faucet
and it got all over me and into my mouth.
I was trying to claw my way out of the bath
but it was too slippery and I could not leave.
This is when the dream ended.
Interpret this please.
I don't know.
The gray slime is maybe...
Why do I need to interpret that?
The only thing that I had to do with that
was you happened to watch my stream for five seconds.
You got like gray slime going into your mouth.
I have nothing to do with that.
You just watched me on camera.
You just watched my stream.
No horses thing fucking killed me.
Well, Future Gamer, that was $7.50 worth of dream.
I don't know.
Maybe the gray slime represents something that you're holding back
or something that you're afraid of
and you don't want it to catch up with you.
Make it in dreams.
You're going the wrong way.
There are no horses.
I've seen that already.
Demoniccucumber, thanks for the 250.
Welcome back to the German 95 Conspiracy Corner.
Today we're going to explore theories of italics being the man behind the mask.
After Germa's death in January, the Phantom of the Germopera.
Here it's important to...
All right, dude, this is freaking me out.
I think it just blue-screened my computer.
I don't even know what to say about that.
That's absolutely strange.
It's important to note that italics has a history of faking appearances
and had plenty of time to prepare.
Besides, Germa's death is canon.
I checked the wiki.
Join us next time as we explore the mysterious disappearance of Shito
and its dastardly cover-up.
Oh.
The disappearance.
You mean of this guy?
Disappeared.
It's just fine.
Uh, Great Lord Walden gave 40 community subs an absolute shitload.
Thank you so much.
That is a lot of community subs.
And speaking of them, why don't we take a look at them all?
Fly by.
Thank you for your incredible generosity, everybody.
And your support of this channel.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Gunther.
Thank you, Gunther, for the three dollars.
Bits to go.
1060 bits to go till I get the hexagon.
Been a while since I've been able to donate or sub,
but I'm making money again, baby.
Glad you're making some money.
Thank you for the three dollars.
Really appreciate it.
Congratulations on making some money.
Thank you.
MultiTrip.
Ten dollars for MultiTrip.
Don't worry about dreams being tough to learn.
I know how to 3D model and draw,
and I still couldn't get past the bad controls to make something for today.
Well, it's just really...
Your brain kind of hits a wall when you sculpt.
But I do appreciate the effort.
I think it's a great game.
I just, like we were saying a few hours ago,
I don't know what the target audience is.
I don't know where they're going with it.
It's kind of too hard to have anybody care about it for like a few hours a week.
And it's not unity or unreal.
It kind of sits in this weird place
where it's so elaborate and has so much shit you can do
that it's almost too much stuff you can do
to the point where I don't know if anyone's going to use it.
The controls really aren't that bad.
They're just very different than anything that's been done with a controller.
Yeah, I mean, that's true.
I think it's supposed to be aimed for everyone,
but the learning curve is really steep, but it offers so much.
It's a lot of tools in one.
It's a lot more fun to use than a usual game engine.
Yeah, that's also true.
Because I definitely found myself getting frustrated.
And obviously, I know I'm not an artistically-inclined person.
There's some people that are wonderful and can sculpt.
But for somebody that is not artistically-inclined
in the traditional sense, I guess,
it's frustrating to use those controllers.
I'm going to try to use...
I'm going to go for it.
I'm going to get up early tomorrow.
I'm going to go get a PlayStation camera.
I have my Move controllers.
I'm going to try to use them.
And we'll see if they make a difference.
Mad because bad.
You'd be amazed how nice sculpting is with the sticks.
I'm looking forward to it because it was...
I could feel myself getting just really frustrated.
And I don't want to, you know, do that on stream.
I don't want to be like, yeah, I don't like this.
Dumb. Sucks.
I don't like being that guy.
So I'm going to make a Trainwreck Scorpion Boss ice cream.
No, I'm not.
We're going to make a platformer tomorrow.
I'm going to make a...
I'm going to just make a big space.
Cubes and platforms.
I'm just going to try it.
I told you we're going to make a fireman platform.
We're going to make fireman first.
We're going to bring in some assets, too.
I'm not going to make everything from scratch.
Nobody does that.
Except for the talented people, you know, talented people do that.
Is it going to be a story?
I don't know if I'm that well-versed to make a story.
Would you mind tweeting out about the dunk tank stream when it comes around?
Oh, you will know where very much in advance.
That's going to have a set date and a set time.
At least a week before it happens.
So don't worry.
In a few months, you're going to be making games.
Well, that's one of the reasons why I got, like,
pissy pants over the things people were saying in chat today.
Well, not really, but it's because I...
All right.
To be able to make something, I need to spend time in it.
To spend time in it, I have to put the hours in to be here.
To put the hours in, I need to do it on stream
because I can't really do it off stream.
So it's almost like the cycle of...
It's either stream me learning it or don't,
and just spend 10 hours a day learning it for, like, two weeks.
It's kind of a rock-and-a-hard place in that scenario.
And I figure, I mean, if I'm going to try,
I might as well stream it.
Otherwise, I'm just going to do it off stream.
At the same time, it's hard to please everyone.
Yeah, but I know that.
And look, I was not that angry today.
Not even close.
At least you don't sometimes want to, you know,
see, tell people where I'm coming from.
You know, that's my side of the story.
This game definitely has potential.
It does.
But I'm going to...
I wonder if I can go get the camera now.
Is anything open in...
I mean, I live in Las Vegas.
Everything's fucking open.
That ice technique was really nice.
It's fun to have your Rika moments and just do it.
I just wish I knew more and knew about where things should be
and how to do them.
It's funny because if you give me 3D movie maker right now,
I could show you every fucking little technique,
every tiny little thing.
Weird workarounds.
And I will never forget that stuff.
It's burned in my brain forever.
I feel like some people think every stream has to be
a high energy clown comedy stream.
Yeah, but that's kind of my fault, though.
You know what I mean?
Like, I do these...
A lot of my streams are like fucking high energy
fucking clown comedy streams.
So I can understand when people come here
and they're like, wait, he's...
He's just going to play Dreams?
And he's going to just sculpt?
Why?
Where's like the car crash?
A lot of that's my own doing, right?
Wouldn't blame you.
No, and I'm not...
I'm really not trying to make this some kind of
thing about, well, you know,
I really wish I could do this and not have to work.
No, it's all good.
I was not...
I'm kind of making this more of a bigger deal than it was today.
It just wasn't at all.
I mentioned it for like maybe 30 seconds.
You set the bar too high with the scorpion battle.
Should I have not pulled that out so quickly?
Because then I went...
Yeah, you know what?
I went from that to just like making a mountain.
I just...
Yeah, I went from that to snow covered mountain.
You started with the main event.
Yeah, but I wanted you to see what I did.
You gave them Hogan versus Andre first.
Yeah, but do you think...
All right, do you think anyone would have stuck around
if I started with the snow covered mountains?
No, people could see the potential with the scorpion boss battle.
They know, holy shit, this isn't just a snow covered mountain stream.
You know, content creation is hard.
You never know what to start with.
Start with a beetle battle.
You know what?
Maybe I'll just stay...
I don't know.
Maybe I'll just be a psycho.
I said this last time, but I might...
Maybe I'll just be a psycho tonight
and I'll just make a bunch of stuff tonight.
And then just...
I'm streaming early tomorrow.
Maybe.
No, but then I got to like...
I got to go.
I have to like drive, so I can't do that.
No, I don't want to like...
No, that's not a good idea.
What's tomorrow?
Tomorrow is an early stream.
And then I have to take Otto to the bed.
So we're going to go for like six hours before five.
But let's finish up the bits.
We're at the end here.
The bala koala gave $14.
Dude, stop looking for horses.
There are no horses.
Fail fish.
Shut up.
Yes, there are.
Thank you for the $14, bala koala.
Thank you Sikilos for the five bucks.
Jerma, would you mind tweeting out info about the dunk tank stream?
This is...
We caught that earlier.
Yes, yes.
My friends and I want to plan a big watch party for it.
Well, it's not going to be like next week.
I will give you at least one week notice.
I'm like trying to prod every single resource here
to get this going in the next couple weeks.
If that goes well, that stream is going to be a ton of fucking fun.
Am I still live?
Did we actually turn off?
I think we may have actually turned off.
Maybe not.
I think we're still on.
But yeah, you will know far in advance.
I'll tweet about it.
I'll talk about it.
And I'll give some actual detail, detailed details
of how it's going to work when it does happen.
Hey C2K, thanks for the 10 bucks.
Hey Jerma, are you ever going to play God of War of the 2018 one?
I mean, the PlayStation is hooked up right now.
So maybe I'll just do that after Sam and Max or something.
Sounds like a fun game.
It looks amazing.
Thank you for the $10.
And yes, I do plan on playing it.
Hey Mr. Comcast, thanks for the six bucks.
Are you going to bail me out here, Mr. Comcast?
Hey Jerma, John Comcast here sitting in my screwed McDuck bank
while the money got me thinking.
Well, what if money can't buy us true happiness?
It's a question that I ponder often
and I was wondering if you knew the answer.
Also in other news, can you move the billions
that are in your overseas Swiss bank account somewhere else?
You're clogging it up for all of us other rich boomers.
If you don't move it, I'll be forced to tell people
about the Ponzi scheme you run on your Twitch stream.
Sure, well, no, I don't think money buys happiness
and happiness comes from within.
Happiness comes from within.
Um, get your fucking money out of my way.
I got plenty of those bank accounts in mine.
I've got the paper signed over Mr. John Comcast.
You ain't going to get your hands on any of it.
Oh no, it's happiness.
It's escaping.
But money can insulate you from exterior factors
that can make you unhappy.
That's true.
That is true.
But here, you know when you put a,
you know the whole goldfish in the bowl thing?
The goldfish just gets bigger,
the bigger the bowl you put it in.
It's almost like even if you have a million dollars,
your life kind of just, that becomes normal.
And even having a million dollar life,
like a multi-million dollar life,
cannot like buy you love.
It can't.
Oh, did we get cut off?
I think I was about to say something really, really important.
What the fuck is going on?
It hasn't been this bad in like months.
Well, I did not expect it to be this bad tonight.
Um, well, okay.
You got it out of your system now?
You're going to keep doing it?
You're going to keep cutting me off or what?
Money could buy some better internet.
You think that would be true, but it's not true.
Uh, what was I saying?
I sure would love to tell you what I was saying.
Oh God, it went down to zero again.
What the fuck?
You know, I'm, I'm just going to type it.
I'm, I'm going to type it because I can't say it.
Okay, got it done.
Okay. Can I, can you hear me?
That's a new coffee.
Okay. All right.
No, I think, I think I can speak again.
So yes, money alleviates the burdens of life to have a comfortable life,
but it cannot put people in it.
And as humans, we strive and we long for true friendship,
true love and things to share with other people.
We long for it.
We want it.
You can't buy it.
You can buy, you can buy pretend, but not the real thing.
And we all want the real thing.
So, you know, you could have $5,000 in your checking account.
You could have $5 million in your checking account.
The $5,000 checking account person may have a ton of fucking great friends
and a bunch of wonderful people in their life.
Somebody that they love and they just live their life.
The person with the $5 million might have,
might pay for a bunch of shit and might own a bunch of cool stuff,
but they might not have anybody to share it with.
Or the people that they are sharing it with might,
they might not have a true connection.
I know this because I have $4 million in my bank account
and everybody fucking hates my guts.
Nobody likes me.
No, I'm just, I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
I would, I don't have that much money.
I do not have even remotely a percentage of that.
That's not water.
It's a seltzer water, relax.
But no, I'm a firm believer of the only reason why you really do anything at all
is because it's somehow some way you want to share it with someone.
You know, oh, I want to go out.
I want to go out to dinner tonight.
I want to go out to dinner.
Why?
Well, because I like this restaurant.
But why do you want to go to that restaurant?
Because they have good food?
Anything else?
Uh, well, hold on.
I went to zero.
No, we're back.
Okay.
But whenever you go deeper, deeper, deeper, deeper, deeper, and you think about it,
you want to go to that nice restaurant with somebody
so you can experience the food together so you can...
It's like this human thing.
I want to go to the restaurant because, oh, hey, how is that?
Is that, is that, is the pasta good?
It is good.
Yeah, it's good, isn't it?
I got the chicken.
Oh, it's amazing.
You want to try?
Yeah, no, it's really good.
Yeah, try it, try it.
Yeah, I really like that wine that they were serving.
It was really good wine, wasn't it?
Experiences with other people.
And they don't all have to be at like a restaurant.
There are plenty of, you know, does it cost?
I mean, of course it costs something to, you know, use the internet.
But I know a lot of people that have a bunch of friends that are online
that they've met through, you know, playing video games.
And look at half of the people that I know.
The connections that I've made with people
because we were making YouTube videos and shit.
I think, I think it's nothing to do with money.
It has to do with having experiences with other people that you like.
Unless you go to a 3D movie by yourself, which is fine.
I did it.
And you're the only person in the theater
and you get to experience the 3D movie alone.
It was fucking cool and it was great.
And experience like a cooking stream.
But that's not all about the dollar.
There are plenty of people that are not happy with lots of money.
And there are plenty of people that aren't happy that don't have money.
There are plenty of people that are really happy that don't have a lot of money.
It's just who the person is.
And I'm like, I'm not going to pretend like, no, it's money doesn't do it.
Money does a lot.
It does.
But it will not fill the human connection.
And with that, that's my talk.
And I will see you guys tomorrow afternoon, early this time.
Make sure you get up.
We've got some stuff to do.
Which WWE game is the best 2K14?
The rest are terrible.
2K, well, 2K13, 2K12.
Okay, maybe they're pretty good.
Everything after 2K14 is awful.
There it is.
Have a good night.
I will hopefully have an internet that works tomorrow.
That'd be great.
And I'll see you guys very soon, actually.
Less than what?
Less than 12 hours?
11, 12, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Yeah, I'll see you guys in less than 12 to 14 hours.
Have a great night.
See you real soon.