Hello, how's everybody doing? Hope you're having a good day. I'm having a pretty good day.
I'm a little sloppy right now. That's because I just got out of an MRI and those are always fun.
And this time I had to get contrast. They put an IV in and they pump you full of
fucking squid ink. Whatever the hell it is. And then you, uh, they get a good image.
So I'm a little sloppy right now. That's why we're late. That's why we went head to stream today.
Yesterday, uh, anything before actually, uh, Otto had a surgical procedure done to
all over the place. And then I got a lot of stuff going on the next few days too.
Uh, a lot of things going on. I'm glad I did that 13 hour Lord of the Rings fuckface stream
because yeah, that, that, that was like three streams. Thankfully, because then that the next
few days, obviously I wasn't around and then juggling streams the rest of this week.
Is Otto okay? Otto was fine completely, but he had to have surgery and then I had to have an MRI.
And then there's all kinds of IRL stuff that I don't, I'm not really going to talk about
because they don't need to be talked about. So yeah, we're going to just chill out today.
I wasn't sure if I was going to, here comes the hype train.
Oh my God, colonoscopy too. I probably sound fucked up a little bit because
stuff just messes with me. Well, I like mom. My mouth tastes weird.
I like fingers were like cold. I have an MRI fear. If you didn't know while the hype train continues
to throw hundreds and hundreds of dollars at this stream. Every time I go to an MRI machine,
I always think I've had three MRIs think of my whole life. And when I go do them,
I always have this weird panic where I go, Oh, wait, hold on a second. What did, but
there could be metal in me. They might be metal inside my body. I don't know.
Then you think of every single time I've ever had, boy, what about metal like in your eye?
I've ever had metal shavings in my eye. Have I ever been, have I ever been a welder? I don't know.
No, I don't think so. What about my teeth? Do my teeth have any metal in them? If I ever had a,
my teeth gonna rip out because I've had a filling. And then when you're in the machine that like,
you can feel your hair is kind of standing up. And I'm like, is this teeth?
Is this when the teeth come out? Cause I can feel it. The magnets just running around you. It's a,
it's a shitty experience. But yeah, I have this weird irrational fear that wait, hold on,
check my pockets again. Do I have, what about the rings where the loops, you know, you know,
your pants, the thing you tie your pants with, not a belt. If you have jogging pants on that
little belt pant loop thing, there's a little metal ring. No, no, not a belt. The thing,
when you wear jogging pants, drawstring, there it is. No, not a belt. Yeah. Drawstring. I know this
word. It at on where the drawstrings connect to go through the pants to actually go around your body.
It's like a little metal ring here. And it's like, am I going to get sucked up to the top of the
machine like a cartoon? And then obviously the answer is no. We're already on level four,
the hype train too, which is fucking ridiculous. Now, obviously I don't know these things. I don't,
I don't think these things are actually going to happen, but they're, the teeth thing does
freak me out a little. Are we just doing a relaxing screen? Yes, we are. We're just going to hang out.
We're going to chill. We're going to play this game. Sorry if my voice sounds a little strange.
Um, it's a little raspy. I don't know why. I think it's just kind of, my body might be a little
stressed. I don't know. But thank you everybody for the third hype train in a row. Third time.
You guys are fucking ridiculous. Please don't, please don't die. I don't plan on it. I don't
have a plan. I don't think that's going to happen. I don't plan on that, but I don't know. I could,
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what he plans on it. What are you doing? Don't say that.
Hype train complete. We just completed the hype train. Thanks a lot guys. Hype train.
Level four. The game we're going to play is Kingsway. It's a medieval OS. And yes,
you heard that right. It's got, somebody said it's like hypnospace outlaw, but it's an RPG.
So we're going to be something we can just relax with and play. And then tomorrow,
tomorrow is going to be an early, early stream. We're going to do an EU stream tomorrow and it's
probably going to be rhythm heaven somewhere around 11 to 12 Pacific. AM is tomorrow's stream.
I was thinking about doing rhythm heaven tonight, but I just, I'm not, I can't,
I can't, I got like this thing wrapped around my arm because of the IV and like, I'm just,
I feel like kind of shitty. So I'd rather not wave my arms around and have sing songs and shit,
but we'll do that tomorrow. That sounds like a plan tomorrow. EU stream tomorrow.
But without further ado, as hype train continues to leave the station, let's get over here. He's
feeling a little shitty. I mean a little, a little, just like tired and I don't know, annoyed. You
know what I'm talking about? Anytime you go to the doctor is the day that you're going to be annoyed.
It doesn't matter. You can feel fantastic before going in. You're just going to be annoyed
afterwards. And here we go. So again, this is a operating system, a medieval operating system.
Did I dip on Joel twice? And Joel hasn't said anything to me as me. Me and Joel don't talk
unless like a stream is currently on. That's like kind of how it works. The last like three weeks,
like if one of our streams is turned on, then like, oh, then, okay. Hey Joel, hey,
oh, day German. What's up, man? The, our last conversation on discord was like,
let's see. Yeah. Last Sunday. Yo man, you still, you want to take a day off. I heard you stream
for like 12 hours. See, he's looking out for me. He's looking out for me. Actually. Hey,
the only time that me and Joel talk is when the streams live. So I'm going to say, I'm going to,
let's reply. Let's ready. How about this one? Hey dude. And then in brackets, yo, streams on. So
like, don't, like, don't, what do you mean? It's like he's going to say something. Hey,
hey, dude, the mother streams on streams on. Don't say your credit card number out loud.
All right. I'm going to say, Hey dude, um, I'm around for this weekend. EU. If you could believe
it. And I'm going to write that EU. If you could believe it, what say you on a return to keep
talking. Why am I saying it like this? All right. I sent it message sent. Let's see if we'll get
back for an email later. My dearest Joel, I must ask you. Okay. New adventure of the slight member.
This is an operating system. Let's go to make sure everything's correct. No, no, no setting.
Do I want to curse a trail? Every time I ever had this on the old windows, it, I just,
it was like a drug simulation. I just feel like I, I feel like this is not, I've done it like this.
I'm on drugs. I don't like that. You would have, I'm on drugs or my computer sucks.
All right. This is, I'm on drugs or integrated graphics card. I don't, all of these are bad.
We're going with this. Don't, I'm not doing the drugs. No. What about background?
Did you do it? Level five hype train has been completed. How many hundreds of subs and
hundreds of thousands of hundreds of thousands of dollars have come in?
There it is. Hype train success hog jam. Thanks a lot guys. You guys never cease to fucking amaze
me with how much money you pour into the stream on a daily basis. Even when the channel is not live,
a hundred subs and 5,700 bits in just the last 10 minutes. You guys are fucking insane.
Should I do pink? No, I don't like that. No, I don't like that. No, actually pink is okay.
Did you do windows 3.1? Purple, purple, purple, purple, purple. No, I don't like that either.
I like this one. No, this one's nighttime. It's time for sleep time. No, the default is okay. Dark.
I don't like the dark theme. All right. This one's fine. Or no, that's, you know, this is more chill.
I'll take it. Notifications. Sure. Sound, main volume. I don't really know what this
means yet. Screen. An 80. Yeah, I don't have a 4k monitor. Can't fucking laugh in my face.
New adventure. Name. You can have a random name? You guys even hear this? Oh shit, I'm an idiot.
There you go. Okay. Do we do random? Open juice. Open Dion. Bruno Hill. Mushy Sherry. Jack Twain.
Dr. Milk. Jam Trey. Joan Cramp. You're Already. Paul Gifts. Ivan Yu. I like Ivan Yu.
His classes in this game? Zach Last. Dr. Milk. Third Bonnet. Apple Jr. Read a book. Pearl Twain.
Stern Twain. Eugene Much. I like Ivan Hill. Pearl Socks. Alvin 5000. Done. Okay. Adventure. Well
rounded character. Not great at anything. Not bad at anything. Makes sense. Warrior. Strong
character. Skilled with heavy weapons and armor. Wise character focused on magic and light armor.
Agile master many. So do you. This is like you play this game in the operating system. It's weird.
Or beast skin. An odd character. Strong and tough but has a bad reputation.
I like mage. I'm a mage. Portrait. Okay. Eyes. Does it look like me?
That's bigger than that. Let's see. Okay.
Bowl cut. That looks all right. I don't have like an old face, do I? Should I do the mustache?
Head shape? I'm just making that one image that was made of me with the mustache. Okay.
I actually like it. Hold on. Let me see the other hairstyles. I like this. I like that one too.
These are all good. All of these are good. No not bald. That's too easy. That's too easy though.
It really is. How can you have different hair color when you have a bald head? Okay. But better
eyebrows? Do we have the concerned eyebrows? Okay. Eyebrows and beard. What about ears?
That's fine. What is custom? Oh you could import images. What? I don't have any custom images.
48 by 48? Do I have one of those? What do we do it? Do it. Import. How do you already have this?
That's not a 48 by 48 image. Yes we do. We do. Does somebody have a 48 by 48 picture of my face?
That's a number I've never heard before. Just draw one right now. One of your emotes. Well the
emotes are 50. They're not 48 by 48. Free size and emote. I've opened Photoshop. I don't want to
open up an Adobe program. Don't you know if you double click an Adobe program you're going to be
sitting there for four minutes while it opens? I don't have that kind of time. Just do it in paint.
All right. Hold on. What should I use? Every time I open up an Adobe program I feel like I'm working
at NASA. And it's like oh booting up the supercomputer. Why do you have to tell me everything you're
loading? I don't care. Just load. Adobe products have a loading screen that cycles through a
million different text files. Like loading this. It's like I don't need that information.
Just open it. Wait you have one already? In the time it took me to talk about Adobe?
Is that 48 by 48? Okay fine. This doesn't even matter. I don't think this matters.
All right well fine. Where is it? Where to go? Right there? Okay.
I need to hold on. Wait custom import. Why does it? It doesn't think this is an image.
How is this not an image? Please no. We're not just gonna we're not just gonna give.
I can't. Okay fine. Fine. Fine. That one is pretty. Is that 48 by 48?
All right. Okay. Okay. It works. It works. It works. What's this character?
Wait I can change the hair color? I can't believe this is actually a real image.
Okay when I when somebody first showed me this the first thing that I've read the comments. You
don't think I read comments. I sit there in my bed and I like bite my fingernails and I go what the
fuck are people saying? Somebody said I look like a default goldeneye enemy.
Or like a Nintendo 64 of NPC or something. And I was like ah I guess yeah that's true.
That is pretty true. All right Alvin 5000. Mage. Everyone gets the same world. I don't want to do
leaderboard. All right I'm pretty intelligent. This is accurate. Choose a starting gift plus
six health points, two magic points, or 20 gold. What's is more important? I don't know.
20 gold? It's 21 out of 20. Double click the world navigator to travel through the land of Kingsway.
Okay. What? The yellow circles on the map are math nodes.
Click a node to travel to its location or inspect it for more information.
Training room. Distance 112. Location boat.
Okay this is. There is a battle dummy.
Some locations have events that trigger when you arrive. You must deal with the event before you
can continue traveling. Okay. Attack?
When in a battle you can choose an available skill. Each skill has a special use
and some are faster than others. Press the skill to attack your target. To load it?
Alvin 5000 attacks from one damage. There's a defense too? That's the load too I assume.
Defeated. You got plus five experience. What about loot? Oh nothing. This is cool. I like you can
actually move them too. Am I gonna get overwhelmed eventually? All right cool.
You will encounter battle. You will encounter. Oh this is fucking contrast man. I got contrast
dye in my blood. You will encounter. Why can I not say encounter? You will encounter battles
while traveling as well in events. If you encounter an enemy too powerful you can try to escape.
Okay so there's a chest right here. Training room. Distance? Okay boat.
There's a supplies chest. There's a sign next to the chest that reads one free potion per adventure.
It says it's actually like on the desktop. That's cool. Double click my bag to view your items.
Click and drag to move items between bags. Bags have a limit to how much they can hold to only take
what you need. Is there, can I see that limit? Do I have to double, do I have to open this?
Just copy paste bag. Copy paste bag. Open bag. Copy potion. Paste potion. That's so funny.
Throw away bag. Is that supposed to be me? Music. Whoa hold on there's music.
All right that's really loud but let me hold on. Let me fix that. I don't like this one.
Oh oh oh I think we found it. Oh absolutely we did. Let's get out of the boat. Turn to surface yeah.
Jesus. Take potion. What do you mean don't take the potion? Hold on what's this mean?
Pause? What's the taskbar do? Oh I have music. All right how do I turn it down?
Taddis? Where's my, where's the control panel? There it is. That's better. It's a little too
harsh for me. This is the king's land. The king's, all right get out of here.
I don't like all these windows open. Actually yeah I do. We'll keep this one open.
This is the king's land. The king's castle is to the east, right? But be careful traveling to the
east too quickly. There are powerful monsters closer to the king's castle so take your time
to get some experience on the way. What about the potion? What? You got a quest. What? Double
click the quest icon to view and manage your quests. Orientation. New message. Adventure corp.
Orientation. Welcome to king's way. We here at adventure corp are here to guide you on your
pilgrimage to the king's castle. The first thing you'll want to do is get acquainted with the
guild. The guild is an organization that employs outsiders like yourself to do various tasks around
the land. Their rewards will be essential to your journey. Bring them the letter that brought you
here and they'll take it from there. You can find guild outposts at any fort and in some small
villages. Good commercial speaking voice. Come on down to your local Honda dealer. All right uh
okay we got the king summons we're gonna go to the he's reading spam
reading spam line by line line by line this is what old people do okay welcome to king's way if
you could please wire me a million dollars and then i will wire you 10 million dollars
it's probably gonna come up all right guild we gotta go to the guild where's the guild outpost
okay this is the guild outpost outpost all right distance 50 grass let's go to all right don't go
close i'm going this way travel what's my fucking emails you come across a deserted home do you
enter yes you stand at the entrance of the deserted home there are several rooms where do you go
the dining room the library the bedroom of the store room store room you enter the store room
the ceiling is sagging there is a locked chest i got a key unlock i got a key unlock the chest
oh shit okay full potion king's icon it puts on my desktop well i i would i would put it on my
desk i put it in the bag oh cool i would just put it on my desktop you know it's learning all right
cool go back i'm gonna get like killed here all right let's go to the bedroom the floor is full
of holes go to sleep in the bed but i've done that i guess i'm good go in the dining room you
go to the dining area the floor is sticky on the library what you went to the library everything's
covered in dust it's a monster kill it what about block a block blocking attack block what what's
going on no loot i'm a close friend level two how much help full potion okay let's play the
runescape ost all right go back so that's it right i got everything what is this for
oh teleport to the nearest fort do i just use this post now don't use that please play runes
what happened somebody's somebody's messaging me block how much help do i have
get out of the way i please move out of the way i didn't get a block tutorial i'm gonna die
oh beast eye what's that someone may want this that's cool this is cool what's going on somebody's
are you strong enough guild members there have been reports of large groups of skeletons in
your area members who can help clear these unwanted undead will be rewarded make sure to
come prepared as it will be a dangerous task kill skeletons at location you get a special head
oh i got a special green button helm that's cool they come through emails
quests come through emails that's i like that that's fun that's that's nice that's cool what
is this tb tb jojia has an inn and potion shop what do i have to do with this the old stories
tell the shifting the old stories tell of the shifting land when one day the sun won't rise
but instead an eternal being will travel over the land closing the sky with its unthinkable
size its footprints distort the ground those who survive were very few of them by the way
will no longer recognize the land and history will begin anew every era the people of the land
seek a savior to end the cycle of destruction but under the eternal one which i'm called the sky
eater ancient prophecy predicts an outsider will come to the king's land only days before the
reckoning and gain the power to destroy the sky eater travel to the king's castle of the east
and prove yourself the worthy savior of the land all right don't skip lore i didn't i just did it
i just did it i just did it contrast drunk i swear to god i got like a contrast heading
poop what five g contracts it doesn't work like that i know i'm just being stupid should i heal
i'm kind of scared to go over here don't i have to would have to bring this
should i go to the king's castle i'm scared you come across a derelict house do you enter
you stand at the entrance of the derelict house there are several rooms where do you go
nursery you enter the nursery everything's covered in dust
library you enter the library it looks like it's been unused for a while there's a locked chest
is that a key you need a key check the bookcases oh book of burn
apparently learn skill burn learn skill burn oh i'm that's right i'm a magician that's why i was
getting my ass kicked i don't have any spells all right what about the hall all's bedroom oh okay
burn okay that's how you that's how you do it you leveled up how the magic and defense increased
by one plus three stat points in a skill point double click alvin 5000's icon to open the
character screen choose new stats and skills and equip items oh that's cool all right
but you could be good or bad this is a broken sword dirty shirt what should i do
increase attack speed maximum magic points maximum health damage with melee look at my
my health is terrible what do i have three i'm gonna do double health and then one indolence
that sounds good what about skills okay i got burn we can upgrade the skill poison chill
more cold damage and slows target poison inflict eight poison critical focus vigilance at the start
of every battle your first attack is 40 faster what do i give upgrading burn five fire damage
and it costs three do i just have a super burn heal oh that's pretty good i got it okay heal
nice all right what does it look like heal burn walk escape i could have just had a super burn
right there did i waste it um i i'm all right close all these windows i'll keep that open beast
i can these stack no they can't rest in the bed i like this this is kind of fun
this is exactly what i needed can i see a bigger window all right so did i go across or should i
clear this whole place up resize the window i don't think i can this is an outpost
play the whole tutorial island that's fine skeleton skeleton skeleton how many do i need
to kill you see another wanderer crossing your path they look scared wonder appears to be injured
and asks for your help hey you came to the right place heal wanderer gains strength and thanks you
reputation increased slightly wonder thanks you again it gives you a treasure
oak staff oh and he already got burned too and he already got burned too burn too wait any three
intellect i have that don't i uh let's talk walk uh rumors have you heard over the foundation
they stay in the mountains summoning demons but why demons are so dangerous they must be
planning something i had another question for you did you just run all right let's put this on
required oh requires level three shit all right well i'm almost there can i put the skull on
all right should i go here i said where i gotta go all right should i keep going this way
i'm going i'm going in why is this such a big deal just go snake i took a hit sorry world fort
kbg door okay the guild magic shop armor shop in weapon shop travel let's go to the let's go to the
let's go to the in quests okay are you strong enough kill skeletons at location didn't i do it
cool okay one king summons i got one i mean you get a supply bag plus 25 experience rewards
i got a supply bag cool all right what is it oh i love that i love that that the bag you double
click it and there it is i love that i love it party ring of flight key potion of magic potion
it's what if i keep i'm just gonna keep it back okay just bag in a bag folder in a folder
oh wait i can put another i can put the bag on the desktop all right what do i not care about here
use the key back in that house not that idea i won't put the ring on okay hold on kill skeletons
yeah i killed skeletons i got it but what an experience you do not have the requirement system
at this quest how many do i have to kill this looks too loud got you i got you i got you i got
you see i will keep that storage can i drag that storage onto the desktop no armor shop
uh how much money do i have where's my money how much money do i have where's my money 68 gold
okay that was one guy turn it back up all right fine all right 68 gold slippers all right let's
see slippers any level three plus five percent magic item is magic fine that's all right travel
robe yeah all right defense for i got i got like a dirty shirt on there's one travel distance yeah
i'll get this add to cart all right that's pretty that's pretty cool but how do i no items in cart
yes oh come on travel robe view cart yes checkout complete transaction please do that's so funny
can i sell this oh that's better it's too loud music's too how is it i what what's with the
goldie locks today i what do you mean it's too soft music's too loud music is just right
that's fine that's fine right there that's fine yeah that's fine now it's actually too loud now
it's actually too quiet hey well put it in the fridge okay if it's too cold put it in the
microwave for 10 seconds put the stream in the microwave oh this food is it's a little too cold
for me yeah it's called you don't even have to do you just have to press the fucking on button
it's 10 seconds one guy is no is it one guy am i getting one guy here i can't be right all right
anyway let's go fireman all right thanks travel safe you too but can i oh i can i mean that thing's
sucked so nobody wanted it all right what did it wait what's the ring was ring do
one vitality plus seven percent escape chance uh yeah oh i like that it reminds me of fucking
diablo chip okay good can i put the staff on yet i can't use it can you speak a little louder
i'm sorry what's the deal what's the deal with what all right you get level three uh weapon shop
i have what's this do one to two damage and burn two okay wood wand one to two more
four magic regen pretty good deft wood wand for magic regenerate one agility not bad no i'll keep
mine potion of magic how many do i have i thought we should have a couple of these don't do you think
so i do i feel like i really feel like if i'm a magician i should have like at least three of them
yeah all right the in stay eight gold no thanks wait yeah yeah i'm crazy the audio
the audio is off are you ready for this are you ready one two three four five it's because the
last time i streamed i streamed the playstation 2 fucking game for like 13 hours and i never turned
it off i just guys when that stream ended i just turned the power button off on my computer it was
just like okay good night bye okay let me there you go two three i thought the stream was supposed
to be chill it is chill i'm chilled right now skeletons in your area the church of ascending
has been raising the dead from their own graveyards to protect themselves from the
many threats of the land in these trying days unfortunately the animators of the church often
lose control of their unearth and clean up their mess bring us some skulls intact and we can give
them a proper burial i did not press a button on the go xlr this is just the way that my voice is
right now until i bring us some skulls who i have i have skulls okay travel all right what was that
house i have a key now you're gonna unlock the chest but i think it's only i think it's one and
done yeah it's one and done skeleton i could get it out i didn't get hit i didn't take any damage
bone club cool oh shit a sea serpent good block what's going on oh i'm still unblock
that thing was fucking hard another key and a short sword all right hold on i need to resize this
no magic though oh shit not enough oh i need a potion got it all right we're good look at all
this shit well there's somebody else attacking me who's attacking me what wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait what the fuck where do they come from all right i have to move
i have to get out of here all right hold on there's like i've got 50 aim windows open right now hello
alvin making your way to the king's castle oh my god i know won't be an easy task there are three
beacons that first must be lit before the king's gate will open these beacons are spread out across
the island and are protected by the king's most powerful knights help you find your way we put a
map of the island in your storage box at the guild go to any guild outpost to pick it up
oh health increase by three that's good all right i'm gonna do burn three no deal two we should
chill slow target i i feel like i should upgrade something though i'm gonna upgrade heal well was
that a mistake probably i don't know all right now do i need medieval os destruction i'm not
sure that's possible i wonder i wonder if you can do it all right let's do another vitality
uh how do i think is this defense just i'm gonna do intellect two intellect yeah yeah i need it
okay so i have a better heal what's it 16 health points that's pretty good all right i got a map
at a guild you can take a look at it but i you i can just explore should i go in the sewer
how are we doing bone club what's this the weapon is that better than i have on it has to be this
thing sucks zero to one yeah it's on put on the bone club that throws away yeah that thing sucks
wait short sword what's this two to two two to two bone oh the staff the staff you're right you're
right the staff is ready i'm on level three skill burn two let's go learned burn two all right i
have plenty of room uh what do i go post uh let's go to the forest let's go hit them do damage but
those guys are rough beast i come across a derelict house do you enter yes you stand at the entrance
of the derelict house there are several rooms attic kitchens let's go to the attic all right i
got two keys right and wrap in a sphere plus 12 damage to humans in two defense i'll definitely
take it nice all right kitchen the bones are in the corner nursery oh skeleton oh shit i can take
a potion use it club did i equip burn two wait what do you mean equip burn two i should have
learned earned is that not on there oh i'll put it on there oh okay well what else can i put down
here oh that makes more sense i think i'm taking another potion no i'm not yes i will all right
get this out here side room it's messy look at all these ways to go unbind escape if you're not a
coward i mean i am so what do you want me to tell you how much money do i have 22 is not very much
let's go up here you see a hooded figure on your path sitting on a rock they look curious
the hooded figure is holding some treasure and doesn't notice you i snatched the treasure
hooded figure says he will sell you the mysterious item oh my god uh where's my heal
die oh shit this is a bad idea he's dead dead 58 experience what do you got on you oh mighty
ring of senses nice is that what that item was party leather armor that was evil yeah don't worry
i promise we'll do something nice when we get to the town all right mighty ring of sense what does
it do three strength and seven magic find can't do it yet this looks pretty this looks magical
oh shit eight strength i'm not even close i can sell it uh i should probably go to a town
yeah wait can i it's just too risky to do this yeah i'm going to town let's place hunk core
yeah let's go to hunk core made it let me shop i'm gonna sell this for how much well it's gone
was nine gold it's gone i thought i was gonna get a confirmation apparently not i'm gonna hold
on to this what's here nine agility i just i'm not working on that right now what about the beast
eyes i feel like i'm not gonna use these for anything bone clubs i can upgrade my stats two
rings two rings yeah i i can't wear this yet i know i can't wear this till level four okay sorry
all right bone club get out bone club get out should i get rid of the beast eyes
i feel like i should get a shield beast eye beast eye for this skulls in this little bag
all right two keys and a potion what else you got rabble shirt small shield plus eight percent
block i mean i'm just just get it just get it he doesn't know did i get rid of beast i know okay
i'll get rid of all of them well i know i asked do i need beast eyes and you guys said no
wait i thought i did i say you're selling the quest item am i
hold on let me get this like thing off my arm i had an iv today let me just like get this off
all right that feels better yeah i had i had an iv today i had an mri with contrast how many
times is he gonna say that today like that's added points for some reason yeah i had an mri
today yeah it was with contrast okay who cares just well you know they make that out of horseshoe
crabs wait contrast die is made out of horseshoe crabs is that correct all right anybody else feel
like this anytime you have a needle in your arm i always feel like when i take off the bandage
that's gonna like rip my vein out of my arm and like blood's gonna go everywhere okay i'm good
i always feel like i'm gonna pull it off it's gonna i took it off too early and like
blood's just gonna shoot into the ceiling let me get one of these shields that sounds fun yeah let's
go yeah all right what always happens now i have defense i am just fucking relaxed right now
anybody else relaxed okay uh let's go to the weapon shop just a general store here we go
oh i need boots potion of attacks oh i can get another bag actually no i can't i got two keys
right yeah would wand oh all right i need these yeah yeah i should probably sleep in the inn too
eight gold let's go this game's too bright is there no dark mode there is a dark mode
i i didn't like it uh yeah i like it like this this is fine okay i'm good how do i knock it
full magic from that i'm fucking infuriated what's this monolith i don't think i want to
touch that touch the monolith no no no no no no i'm going over here shit it's all right oh my god
please get away from me come on hurry up all right how many mushroom people are here all right i
leveled up blue oh antidote living seed nothing on you on you somebody over you are approached
by an old scraggly witch-like figure hunched over wearing a hood and walking with a large
staff the witch comes right up to you uh which looks at you up and down and says
i can help with your little adventure if you're interested what was that accent um i feel like
i'm gonna get i feel like i'm gonna get uh cursed or something you can just barely see a smile
beneath the hood your first one is free the witch's staff begins to shake and there's a
flash of light the witch is gone you feel a change in yourself health regeneration
permanently increased so that was a good thing all right there's something called electric skin
uh i don't care what anything else exists in the whole game i don't care i'm going to max out
electric skin i'm gonna put every single point in electric skin that's just what's happening
i'm sorry it's just on i got burned two heels to electric skin i have to bind it it's passive
see passive all right um attack speed maybe i should do an attack speed or should i just
dump it into vitality i'm playing it safe safe i have to play it safe what did i get there what
does the living seed do all right living seed someone may want this antidotes for poison i'm
assuming what is that but i have a map somewhere what do i have what's the mission i have right
now skeletons oh shit that's a quest is it the skeletons that's the scalp all right let's go
i'm going up this way this is a long way didn't even get a chance to do a goddamn thing
dead fan and hubble i got two keys let's go in store how many skulls do i have now
i think i need four skulls right uh side room okay let's unlock the chest mighty leather armor
i wonder if it's worth putting points into strength just to wear the leather armor it
probably is one axe i don't know it is absolutely not worth it out but is it it might be in the
kitchen uh sleep in the bed not for this build yeah it's true all right do i go i'm not doing
that yet rather near okay this is called vestry oh wait this is a there's a dungeon this is a
dungeon i don't think i'm ready for this can i leave how do i leave can i leave what happens if
i exit out of the window like x the window shit i'm gonna fucking die down here there's a strange
figure on your path that is carrying a small bag overflowing with shiny objects the figure
is very focused investigating every crevice of a nearby wall with a closer look you can see that
the strange figure is some sort of demon-like creature it notices you and tries to hide behind
his bag radio talk i'll let you look at my items if you promise not to hurt me and by the way
everybody in a medieval game is irish all of us it doesn't matter if we're a demon an old lady a
man at the inn a bartender or the king every single one of us is fucking irish always okay
let's i want to let me see the demon thanks you for sparing me i'll let you look at these most
wondrous objects i have found and maybe even sell you on test one am i gonna get sucked into
the bag the man with two voices that's me okay if i look at the bag he's gonna capture me
i'm gonna get i'm gonna get grabbed right i'm gonna get grabbed he's gonna holy shit
holy shit how much money do i have 14 gold no look at all this stuff can i sell
no i can't sell to him damn it this is so sad i thought it was gonna be 50 gold
come on don't get anything no random oh look at that look at that look at that look at that look
at that we only have to go one more time yes how lucky whoa okay you have to avoid the pop-ups
oh shit church guard loot priest mask
oh shit oh i have to leave i oh time is better good loot right ring of warding
i got to the chest no key right it's fully loaded it's fully loaded that's awesome all
right hold on not gonna get attacked right crescent potion grants one stat point are you
kidding this is fucking i'm excited what does the orb do plus one day it's an offhand oh shit okay
travel robe all right let me just crank it right now can i upgrade it i might be maybe i can
upgrade all right properties this is just club let's just take it oh shit all right hold on
oh shit dude this thing is fucking crazy wear the rope i know hold on wait wait wait priest
mask i gotta i gotta open up my windows what is a priest mask four defense and plus 14 damage to
bot this boss is in this game you've already got me hooked all right four defense versus what two
oh percent all right put this on uh small shield this two defense eight percent block what's this
one or deep god damn it okay just bought this fucking thing travel robe that's what i have on
right yep the same is it random of properties or same thing all right i'm gonna don't i don't get
overwhelmed with pop-ups okay so now bright ring of warding oh hell yeah two intellect ten percent
magic power nice crank the crescent potion now oof oh yes okay i put the should i put the all
right should i put the orb on plus an extra damage or should i have the defense there was
another ring too yeah there was this one plus three strength and seven percent magic find
let me look at them all one vitality with the escape chance which who cares versus three strength
and magic find probably there's a strength ring i'm not going to sell this yet though let's see
how this works look at this axe minus 15 damage to demons plus 20 damage to bosses i could kill
warrior or something strength is useless if you're a mage yeah but i i do find myself using
the regular swing sometimes at least initially here in the early game drop shield i could sell
this i'm not gonna drop it i could sell it how much is away drop the small shield how much
i can sell this it's one gold oh all right well whatever nice okay i'm ready i can't wear this
wait maybe i can ah that's right all right let's go uh this is a bad idea so i'm gonna leave
i just need to leave i just have to get out what is what is this person no i don't i don't need to
escape i want i look at my look how close you have to a level is it a raid coming g mart came
in with a huge raid welcome hey what's up g mart see i see it this time last time i didn't see it
i swear to god welcome everybody we're playing uh king's way it is a i'm gonna die
what what what what what what what what what my health is critically low
i have to kill him right now go die oh i died i died but instantly leveled up it heals me
holy shit that was bad wow okay attack speed um well let me just hold on just a second
okay skill electric skin too burn three follower only is on uh shit uh turn off follower only for a
minute raider here wait a minute but whatever you were doing uh g mart you guys had fun we're
just chilling that was a chill stream today i was at the doctor today went to the mr i had an mri
done with contrast so fuck you know that sucked what should i do i think i'm just gonna upgrade
heal too that's 26 health for what four mana five mana why did i do that why did i just quit that i
just clicked that for no reason i don't know why i did that i do i do i don't even want this
okay okay let's go although i say that now but i wonder if electric skin is the reason why i
didn't just die that makes some sense all right i need a town here we go no fighting no fighting
no fighting no fighting now nice four damage okay general store what do i got here nail club
get rid of it axe get rid of it uh what's the horn wrap was was 12 damage to humans
i don't think i really care that much of a living seed three gold but somebody might want this
mighty leather armor seven gold orb two gold you never explained the game oh this is a game
where you play it's an rpg and pop-up windows on a fake medieval browser pretty good give blue items
to the monolith will you just cheat it for me thanks appreciate it all right potion no
mana potions though i need these i have to buy them medieval browser you mean bing sure plus
three strength do i even have any potions i don't think i do just regularly there we go i mean i
have to get them i can't just not have any potions can you play the game um sorry i'm just about my
desktop right now i've just been moving around folders and shit yeah but this game we're gonna
play in a minute i just sorry i've got my desktop being captured i'm just well it's been like an
hour and a half yeah sorry guys i said to clean up my desktop a little he was running fucking slow
he's gonna that's it i'm getting a new computer all right everyone i want to see one in the chat
if putting two points in strength is the stupidest thing you've ever seen anybody do in this game
to wear this two in the chat if just put it all into vitality you have a terrible build what
happened to my what happened if i where's my where's my world there is i have one key oh
oh these look cool i want that look at that legend of zelda sword i want it so bad how much is to
sleep here i don't even have this money all right i'm going for the quest let's go what is it
oh a potion i actually wanted that kill the skeletons you've arrived at the location of
the quest are you strong enough you see five skeletons just ahead of you they haven't noticed
you approach the skeleton can i talk to the skeleton you see the skeletons are blocking the
entrance to a small tomb let's go fuck did i just do ruined armor another skull shit oh no
oh no oh no nothing on you good another skull all right i have i have a lot of skulls
bone club it's not even worth picking up just throw it away skull okay i did it let me move
the skulls out of here i can't you bought a potion for 20 gold only to use it so you can add a
worthless skull to your bag these are not worthless from what i've been able to figure out yet the
skeletons are gone and the entrance to the tomb is clear it looks to be the source of the skeleton
troubles you enter the tomb you can hear the rattling of bones uh-oh i don't need magic no
no there's a boss here i need magic oh should i take a bright maybe i think i could do it
no don't do it mistake i can come back all right but i can just come i can go in there all right
where's the he's a wuss i need magic what's points in vitality well i also don't well i
don't want to die dying wait what's this ruined armor three and then one defense where and then
i heard of this i gotta sell so go to the monolith you said all right four skulls look at this shit
all right i'm going with from the guild services we're going to the guild death spirit mask of
health my god that's a thousand times better than what i have on let me see this thing what's this
14 damage to ball i'm gonna keep this see i can kill bosses fast versus five defense four
three stats and agility two yeah this is just much better and it's ways less too it's germany
internet guy hey it's me look at this internet addict if you guys think in a world where games
like world of warcraft exists and people play fortnight all day that's an hour and 24 minutes
is not it's not even close dude he's spending too much time in this like browser game he's
gotta get off the computer oh what's that i have 280 days played in world of warcraft get off the
computer you played lord of the rings for 12 hours now that's that's the real problem right
that's the real issue you should be very concerned about you you should not be concerned
about me moving around windows on a desktop as much as you should be concerned about me
needing to complete a crusty playstation 2 game from 20 years ago why is it always the playstation
2 games every stream that's been longer than 10 to 12 hours has been on an old console like ps2
or dreamcast you know it's because i don't want to let it beat me that's the problem i don't want
to let it win because it's old game old playstation 2 you can't beat the old playstation
2 games yes you can i can't let it beat me the middle earth needs you all right bring us some
skulls i don't need mana or ah i'll take it oh i'll take it potion shop now where's the guild
how much money do i have 16 i don't know where was this guild the church of ascending has been
okay wasn't it right here any city yeah and then what that's do i have to go back here
or should i do it in here use the king warp so many things open my bag okay they use this
transport to the nearest port i guess that here we go all right guild quests skeletons in your
area i'm gonna level up right here 350 experience four skulls submit nine health okay new skill
point clear fireball no explosive fire blow inflicting 12 damage to target and six to all
other enemies wait and other windows like another pop-up windows is that how that work electric skin
three traveler's ring it's pretty good i've ruined my character joke i think it's gonna be just fine
okay so now i have a lot i think i'm just gonna do i'm gonna do magic again and vitality
agility i already have all intelligence i feel like i need to do intelligence i gotta get
intelligence this morning does attack speed is that casting speed we know it's not it is
little skeletons at the location all right that's the inside here i'm gonna take this ring out
storage map of king's way i put on a desktop what the hell is it oh please don't do that
magic shop what do i have for um how much money do i have 16 gold not even close
what's better do a regen three move speed five travel distance i'm not sure that's better than
anything i have on which does it sell for that sells for a lot i need to save money but i need
magic up the strength free strength
move speed and travel distance put it on i gotta get rid of some of these things though
i have a lot of junk yeah where's my backpack all this so this i don't think i need the skulls
anymore get rid of this mask keep the orb brew crew analysis game sucks this game is fun i'm
gonna have to i'm gonna have to like i'm gonna have to tell all the people that get all the
drew crew that came to like the parent teacher conference to please sit down like i understand
yeah we're going over questions if we're going over things about about our community and then
everything so please sit down please you're all shouting i don't and i don't want to have to have
uh bob the security guard have to take all 30 of you out of the room you don't want to do that
but see some of you guys got that some of you guys got that i said 30 yes i did i did because
i think there is only like 35 people in the drew crew i think there actually are only like 30 of
you i'm not sure there's more than like 50 people in the drew crew they're very passionate though
they're very passionate they're incredibly passionate people and you gotta love it you gotta
love the passion all right let's go drop i can't drop all now it's gonna be gonna be wrong
oh yeah okay let me continue i'm i'm not even certain there's enough people in the drew crew
to play one game of regulation baseball let's go i need to germa walk fuck off germa walk fuck off
uh i'm losing track let me let me get back to what i was doing here what's with the shadows
yeah what is with the shadows okay lol i've ruined my character fuck that's not even
shit okay i gotta go do the quest
oh no just kill it it didn't hurt me this guy sucks by the way adam sandler snubbed for an oscar
unbelievable that's just unfair how did he not that's unfair he was gonna get everyone thought
he was gonna get nominated he was he was a lot of buzz around his performance in uncoupled gems
i was when i saw that i was so mad you know why not because i give a shit about adam sandler
because i wanted to come into this stream and be like adam sandler just got nominated for academy
award and everyone would be like no no it's not true can't be and then i'd be i'd be like yes it
is but i can't fucking do that now it's too bad that really is too bad i really thought i was
gonna be like i'm gonna be like i told you guys i told you it was gonna happen sandler squad
oh a potion all right you say saying go to the monolith did i do that first it's not true it's
impossible no no no he's supposed to be not funny and a loser no i can't take it and if he won oh
that'd be fucking hilarious that would be i would have be so funny if you want i would get a i would
get a framed photo of him in uncut gems and put it in my office here if he had won the academy
award for best actor and every time i would turn on my face cam he'd be reminded and he'd be like
like grabbing your face and pulling it down like no every time i see it it makes me fucking angry
and i'd like put my hand on it and like put my head down and like say like it just like okay
getting ready for the stream that's how i would turn on every stream i would put my hand on it put
a head down and like get the energy from adam sandler that's how i would start every single
fucking stream too bad i don't want to use that do my own oscars i can't do my own oscars i didn't
watch any oscar movies stop using that move i haven't seen any of them rotten ring of judgment
okay cool i can i make it over here yet all right we're going to the monolith what is this
that's a lot one movie nominated uncut gems they don't do very much damage the germa oscars was
the new year's stream it kind of all right i gotta kill stuff before i get overwhelmed
can anybody germa wink yet i don't think so not that i'm aware of am i getting just kill him
it's burning you have 20k i think some people are like halfway there a lot of these antidote
for what oh you can do you can do that okay your guild sir you won't believe this potion
hello alvin 5000 i hear you might be interested in a unique product we make specifically for
adventures like yourself you won't find this potion anywhere else all we ask is for you to
gather the core ingredient and we'll do the rest it's that simple like two of these there's a lot
of vhp coke a bottle of coke there's a dark model if the ground is raised as if the model
is pushed out from below the surface monolith towers above you absorbing all sound in the area
make an offering all right so saying if i throw one of these in there
i mean this is super damaged right this is this is an offering or i need ring of sense
or this is the vitality ring okay give give offering you three blue items
all right mighty leather armor and this one right give offering the model takes your offering and
glows warmly you feel more skilled shit that's much as burn two do five probably fireball
click ruin the character greater heal is good because it cures poison heals burns
all skills cost one less magic point to use oh that's actually good is that better than
i think i i need something that's high damage though yeah i need it i need something that's
a lot of damage i'm doing clear mine next can't escape anymore well if i die if i die and i didn't
escape don't i just deserve to die if i'm like spam clicking this run quick quick quick get out
go go no no no don't i deserve to die shouldn't i have not fought that in the first place
that means i wasn't ready that's i'm good i want fireball this is like a beehive i have to go up
here let me go this way let's check out do i have keys right yeah what's going on he's minimizing my
window stop doing that fuck you don't do that anything on you deserted home let's go in all
right i got a key i need something big here how many blues do i have two i need one more to get
another skill point right uh nursery nothing side room nothing bedroom chest
oh robe okay 13 magic power that's pretty great what's on right now travel distance
less defense but more damage sleep in bed again do it again does this matter
here exorcists wanted the war has been posted anyone who can clear out the hostile spirits
that occupy the mansion at the attached location please find the source of the hauntings and report
back to the guild exorcist oh guild special robe i gotta do one of these what's going on here
what is what the what's the what is the dark stuff do a little concerned is this a time limit
so i have to i have to move forward is that oh that just means it's night time
don't get stuck in there don't get stuck in it don't get stuck in it stop fucking stop stop stop
okay i gotta so i gotta move i gotta move um i gotta go right can i go up is that on the line
it's i killed it i did it defeating the shadow it's still there fireball two yeah
yeah yeah fireball two fireball two fireball two i need it i need it i have to do damage
player mind is good but next time am i gonna you see some bandits they look like they're up to no
good approach the bandits surround you there are two of them talk they don't seem interested in
talking let's go fuck off oh what's that fuck out of here bandits teeth a bandit blade you defeated
the bandits and some find some treasure they were hiding come on that's all you have i already have
one of these 15 this is a better roll that's a better roll it's a perfect roll is it probably
15 percent more percent perfect girl let me just put it on the rest of this shit i can't i don't
think i can carry it i guess i can all right this is important this is very important should i do
do more intellect or should i do agility i do all intelligence agility more intellect more
intellect one two three i have to go here does that mean i missed out on the thing that i could do
over here shit oh no i i missed out so what is this one exorcists i need potions i i can't i
don't have any i need to go back to town i can't get over here go to the inn first
am i gonna get okay shit all right all right all right all right okay what we got weapon shop
let me sell all my crap how much money do i have i got money i got money priest mask this thing out
of here oh what about this two agility six magic find yeah and his blade no i'll get rid of it
and his tooth someone may want this i wonder if i should keep it i already have a better robe than
this i have two regular potions rotten ring of judgment one gold fuck off what am i keeping
that axe for something these antidotes oh that's so good that's so good 34 percent damage to bosses
four to six regular damage magical shield two i don't know what to do i need these they're just
essential i need i this is a lot of money thank you bob bobo durango bobo durango for the five
computers i appreciate it i need them i can't hurt anything unless i have mana please god stop
buying potions i need i need them i need them what about these skulls oh here comes the hype train
hope i didn't do something bad by listening to the one guy i need how many of these do i need
okay this is fine this is fine now we sleep at the end full mana full health
oh protect yourself from bandits so many inexperienced adventurers these days we've
seen some troublesome opportunists taking advantage of the situation they operate in groups
and they prey on those carrying anything valuable it's been too much for the region's guard to deal
with on their own oh this is the way the teeth come in get those boots but just get any boots
i think i should i just buy just shoes three defense that's pretty good just i have i need
them i'm getting them that's it that's like like that's what 10 more defense 20 more do that that's
like that's like 12 15 more defense all right i'm going to do that mission i'm going to go to the
exorcism you cannot escape anymore unless you get very lucky oh for the love of god ah i panicked
and did too many no no uh did i get any money for that i have to do this i'm going in
don't have it again oh you gotta be fucking kidding me oh my god i'm gonna die i'm freaking
out i'm freaking out what do i do i'm freaking out i'm freaking out freaking out freaking out
i need full health i didn't know this was in the game i didn't know this was a thing i didn't know
this was a thing what the fuck nobody told me this is a shadow following you around that's
gonna kill you get out get out get out get out get out okay i can't do this i have to leave
i read the book yeah but i thought that was like a generic like and the coming darkness will soon
consume us all run for your life i didn't know it meant like oh by the way there's a chance if
you're in the shadow you're gonna get attacked by a fucking super monster about this okay i can i can
do this i need um i need to go to my side i need to oh i okay i need to escape uh escape is going
to take the place of what attack place of heal all right i'm gonna be able to make it through this
all right i made it just don't randomly encounter anything i haven't done any quests a wanderer i
didn't know i had like time limit oh no this is so sad okay broach the wanderer greets you the
wanderer wonders what you'd like to discuss i'd like to talk advice the engines are dangerous but
they hide great treasure nice great good advice i could get better advice from the the stick of a
popsicle thanks a lot okay uh i'm going up here i can't do this anymore all right now that's
unfortunate should i go down up i'm gonna go up i'm gonna go up to this town i need money you come
across a forgotten dwelling do you enter yes advocate let's go to the hall you enter the hall
the floor is sticky there's a paper with strange symbols on it monolith research paper is drawn
by a child okay basement don't kill me don't kill me don't kill me do i have any health
how many health left get out of the way stop stop oh thank god thank god you had a thank god you
had this on you oh the run is saved the run is saved i just need to heal can i just use it okay
it's equipped again okay okay um the first thing i need to do is heal myself immediately
bedroom okay unlock the chest x wand rotten buckler rest in the bed oh no no oh i could have
just rested over and over again but no no no no no no no no bad this terrible idea
that's the storm the common storm guys no that's not this is bad too this is all bad
no this is all bad three to five damage i lose burn too but who gives a shit three to five damage
and seven magic regen rotten buckler so red mean the pink around the edges means the thing sucks
do weld steps can't do that finally mana regen okay now this stupid storm is going to be right
behind me i knew it i knew i should have done that what do i have for missions missions bandits
the exorcist i can i delete emails because i can't do that anymore okay this is the living seed thing
king's castle pretty beacons must be lit before the king's gate will open
where's my bag did i forget uh build magic shop weapons shop oh right what the hell does this
even do for me where are the beacons that you need to light beacons where do i don't see any beacons
right there are these beacons the suit the the trash can lid things i even looked at that and
i was like oh go to the sewer what happens if you don't light a beacon do i have to go i have to go
light that beacon well we got the bad ending already wonder is being attacked and is losing
help me stye i helped out the wonder thank god i have another bag the wanderer thanks you again
it gives you treasure there's a treasure in here what do you mean gives me treasure you
you gave me an empty grocery bag that's not treasure that's the thing that holds the treasure
i got scammed all right well at least i can and i'm gonna rename this i'm gonna call this uh
uh quest items why did that not type quest items i don't know and it's teeth this beast eye shit
there's a lot of research papers put over here on the desktop bag bag best i'm gonna rename this uh
pots for armor yeah armor weapons and armor it's better the bag is gonna have the stuff that i need
let's uh talk rumors slaughter a group that worships the sky eater and live in the tombs
underground and resurrect the dead to protect themselves and their forbidden rituals what else
do i need are you strong enough i can't even do this well i might as well just go to the town
away these guys have mana potions what what do you mean what do you what what what what what what
what do you mean critically low what are you talking about where's my health holy shit it is
critically low i can't i get some fucking spotify off my stupid desk top who has spotify open on
that desktop probably a lot of you guys guild quests or bandit team exorcist i didn't do it
you won't believe this potion i don't have it he's strong enough i can't do it i have to abandon these
i'm so fucking upset right now i'm gonna store all this shit though in here what a hero well i
didn't know he doesn't know he doesn't know that's right i didn't i had no idea
pushing shop all the staff they're so all right no more are there any monoliths in the area what
do i care i need money i'm almost at level almost leveled up if i sleep here i gotta make a i gotta
make a break for it after i sleep i have one mana potion i'm mad that you didn't die well i'm sorry
i'm still alive travel i can go back here but why the hell would i go back here
i'm thinking i'm gonna get uh sleep in the end so i'm fine i just gotta keep moving
holy shit this guy the fuck is going on why is there an x why is there an x
teleport directly to a nearby area on the map that's pretty good random potion
electric skin four that sounds like a plan clear mind did i do clear mind
okay clear mind that's that's good fireball two it's because i took the staff off
burn fireball two heal two i haven't even why did i even get healed too i'm not even using it
shit what do you mean this is full what the fuck are you talking about okay get going wait what's
going on here oh right okay one vitality not strength i need i need more vitality i hear the
dog come across a deserted home let's go in yes i do have a key kitchen take the paper in the
kitchen it's a monolith research paper it's three sons in a square i don't get it sun the drop in
the that doesn't probably item study lock the chest open the chest crystal staff and chain mail
it's not i mean it's the same amount of damage almost but not really i'm not using the heal
i don't know i mean i could take it and sell it it's probably worth a lot
what about this it's so good just nine defense almost half of the defense i have on my whole
character shit okay i don't sleep store room oops what what what what's going on fireball two
oh i put it i had it in a different spot i had it in different spot i did heal twice it was in the
all right why did i change that now i have to sleep
what an idiot mage what i don't damn it damn it damn it it's okay beast eye i got a lot of
these can i turn this in for something come across a deserted home i don't have any keys
this would be a big mistake fine basement did you hear a noise in the basement no in the study
i don't have that i cannot like the damn chest kitchen no it's just sleep on the bed sleep in
the guy's bed wheel shield oh key rest in the bed oh it's not going to be over on me right
back go into the study open the chest mighty ring of agility and hollow orb of strength mighty
ring of agility oh it's good it's really good but i don't know if it's good for me
ah i feel like mage might not have been the greatest starting character i'm getting lots of
great strength and agility items hollow orb will let me put on the chainmail let me get it over
here first all right how long or a sixth strength but minus 20 magic power but i gain
nine defense you have electric skin just swap builds wait so what what you're saying is just
stack health and defense and then have electric skin eight i don't think that's going to work
just heal yourself over and over again while they fill themselves on you i'm all right i'm
gonna need a minute to think about that i'm not ready to think about that yet but um key in a skull
shit okay go oh no okay um i need no no no no no no give me mana potions i was gonna say
fucking stupid don't heal don't heal it's probably in i can sleep over
oh fuck i'm so sorry that hurt that hurt me a lot too it's a lot wait wait
fruit hold on this is important crude wizard shirt oh my god um what is it rake i have any
room for this shit i'll just take it oh look at it that weighs so much trash the trash i can't i need
how much does this weigh i know i have you suck lol stop hoarding i'm not i just need to i need
to get to a town so i can sell this shit why would i mod somebody named germa's tallest fan
that person's not gonna get mod that's never gonna happen that's never happening okay let's
open this up i get let me put the new shirt on tons more defense now i can do mod if you're a
coward i can put this on now i can't 14 strength shit but no i wait wait wait wait wait wait i have
a ring one of my rings all right i'm gonna put the strength ring on instead of this one
a bit of the traveler's ring where's the one that has four and four are the literally there in one
second i have to kill one thing what am i coming up to well i have a key right yeah oh my god oh
my god i didn't think this was gonna happen damn it okay you have nothing on you let me just stop
15 health one magic one defense three stat points one skill point the build is all fucked up now
it's okay hold on i need to get a look okay yeah i get an email all right i'm 15 and i'm pretty
sure i'm taller than germa uh you know that most people uh yes that's called you get to as tall as
you're going to be by the time you're like 14 and then you're just as tall as you are until you die
uh yes you're you're describing you're describing how people grow up as humans once you turn like
17 you're not growing anymore you don't you don't like get taller it's not like oh yeah my 29th
birthday i grew two inches that's cope no you you like stop all right oh you want me i'm gonna
pull google up on you i'm gonna pull up google up on you guys when do people stop growing
um most boys will stop growing taller by age 16 oh you said 14 he said it was 15 what that's like
what are you talking about you guys acted like it was like 25 still got one more year it's 18
it's 16 actually from medical world news headquarters that's what that website was
fake website no that's a real website sort stuff i thought you just called me short stuff you said
stop stalling short stuff and i was like okay fucking whatever but you said sort stuff so one
of these days you guys realize that like i don't matter how tall you are that shit don't even
matter oh no i can't play for the fucking basketball team
guys i haven't worried about playing for the basketball team in
fucking 17 years who cares all right what am i what am i sorting here i'm just going like this
it's like right now i'm like he he wants to say something you can tell he's like
raring up ready to be like listen listen to me it's shit you know what i mean he's he's getting
ready to go off and that's why he's just moving his windows around but he's gonna you know what
he's he's gonna take the high road this is what's gonna happen he's gonna take the high road
really easy to go down the low road all you gotta do is lie on your back with a thing with wheels on
it you know how hard it is to take the high road you have to walk that shit in the snow yeah so
what do you think about that one double middle finger we're going low road uh all right let's do
can you take the high road if you can't reach it dude you should you should fucking you should
fucking write for snl i think that you know they could use a guy that does the same a joke every
day they could use a guy like you you can use that kind of fucking humor he's unironically mad
you know yeah fuck it all right let me look over at my chat right now what do you think i should
put in let me vitality oh no jeremy you should put in a two vital tiny two vital okay that person
great contribution uh what else we have um it's a 2010 strength he can't even reach anything um so
should i use the uh the club yeah jeremy the club's in club yeah use club he's not tall enough for a
club it's like come on you got better material up there i know it you got much better material up
there you mother fuck all right uh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay all right all
right all right all right all right i'm going i'm fucking all my talent hey guys oh yeah something
really bad happened today i got i got hit by a bus today both of my arms are broken both my legs
are broken and i'm actually streaming from the hospital i don't think he's tall enough to
go to the hospital oh yeah guys i i i literally can't move my arms small i i was i'm i'm in i'm
in pain help me you guys are fucked all right what skill am i going to upgrade i think i can
i do clear mine too i don't know like six times six is too small to get out of roller coaster
okay i think i'm gonna do fireball again he's dying he's mad and he's not pretending
the one time i'm not pretending is now i could i could walk off a cliff in dark souls like five
times and i'm pretending but the once the one time i'm like all right i'm calling you out on this
holy shit he's not pretending i can't i can't upgrade anyway what's what's the name oh yeah
we can damage two only two shots and he's dead you come across a hooded figure
whoa the hooded figure sees your wheel shield they offer to buy it for 25 gold
holy that's that's that's a lot of money chokuji thanks for the five community subs
thank you it's no it's not but shouldn't i just put this on shouldn't i be wearing this 14 what
do i have a string well hold on okay all right wait wait wait wait i'm just gonna put yeah
i'm gonna tell this guy to fuck off what if he doesn't take no for an answer and they increase
their offer to 38 gold for the shield uh that's a lot of money that's a lot of money did i sell it
now they don't take no for an answer so if i leave again will the price increase okay did it i give
you some advice it's easier to escape from battle when your enemy is injured thank you
did i not have done that you see the same witch from earlier seem like appearing out of nowhere
the witch is standing on your path is it waiting for someone okay the witch is oh did you like
your gift i can give you another if you like yes the witch looks up at you revealing a crooked
smile give me your long cleaver and i'll give you another gift uh yes the witch takes your long
cleaver and with a flash of light the item in the witch disappear you feel it all stats permanently
increased by plus one holy shit that's actually amazing all stats plus one that's great nice work
i can get it off yeah gathering of cloaked figures they look like they're up to no good
uh the cloak figures surround you there are three of them do i have any mana potions talk the cloaked
figures are carrying stolen goods and offer you a bribe to not tell anyone what you've seen
what that's 40 gold the cloak figures give you 40 gold and leave i have a lot of money
okay i'm just gonna go down uh how do i get out of here we don't make sure this is equipped hold on
whiz heel escape uh put on the travel distance rings they're gone why are they gone no i have
it on uh so what is the game is the play go up down and then over this way because i'm right
now i'm right here i can't go from here to there that's kind of horrible so i have to go down
here and then down i'm gonna try that wait i can't go here what the fuck is going on um what is
going on give me that mana potion give me that mana potion give me that mana potion give me that
mana potion yes yes a double yes a double good good good oh give me more mana potions come on
oh baby a double magic get off the screen stop popping up i don't want to take the
mana potion yet until i need to i don't need to right now too short on magic get out of here
get out of here i'm actually in a lot of trouble down oh i have to have to walk into it which then
what am i doing all the way up here i need to heal in case i can't run that's really important
actually fireball i'm gonna get burn out heal to an escape gain a level and then get teleport
well i don't i don't think i'll get it by the time i do this let me see if i can do this
great sword i can't carry this shit all right i'm actually i may maybe i might get to another level
should i what are you guys doing what are you guys doing grab a key yes i do check all right
all right unlock the chest book of full arm mastery do more damage with pole arms
an iron helmet caught a defense all right i guess i'm better with pole arms book of axe mastery
do more damage with axes placement oh uh uh uh i can't go down from here why can i not go down
from here wait can i go okay i can but fuck all right i have a new i new plan i'm just gonna
kill skeletons until i get to teleport then i'm gonna teleport the hell out of here
bulls ring of strength lever rest plate eleven defense what i have on now i can sell it though
but i don't think i can carry anything how much is the way way too much actually me skull
oh shit it's being crushed i'm trying no no i'm i just think that thing's so bad
11 armor versus one i i mean i replace this and throw it away minus five agility is destroying
your travel distance um do i even need the beast eyes anymore it's it's the agility it's the
agility is that what's been doing this the whole time what if i do this let's see i gotta sell
something i desperately need to sell let it's just the thing it's just deleted throw away is that
what's doing it though i have seven agility come on i need i need one more fight one more battle
and then i can travel okay here we go oh god damn it i don't want to use this potion after though
otherwise i might not be able to kill anything all right let's go
here it is level 10 teleport press a rec next time you die you don't heal fully lose the skill
teleport directly to a nearby area on the map this is gonna this is gonna be bad isn't it i feel
like this is not gonna be good a random area will it be just can i choose i guess it's not how do i
use it passive you just do it maybe you have to be closer great sword i can't even carry this
this is so much damage but i can't even carry this fucking thing wait there's an option to
teleport come on you can only teleport to areas with the yellow lines on them okay so you don't
have to fight but who cares that's not i can't even do i have any mana i don't use it to get
through the shadow i don't i'm not gonna have any mana to do that i could teleport to here and then
teleport to here and then how am i supposed to get down here what why can't i go i'm fucked i
have to i have to sleep and then wake up and teleport across the game shit all right but first
getting rid of this shit fool's ring of strength get the fuck out of here useless
uh what do i have all bags all bags open breastplate sell it chainmail sell it
great sword sell it crystal staff sell it
all this junk yeah get this is bad rotten free vitality to get out of here
hollow orb of strength i mean this is cool but stupid yeah replace this my wand
belly iron helm okay now i am not a total joke intellect and vitality i think is the play that's
one two three four five i can get a monolith travel well i'm gonna be teleporting around anyways
agility is travel distance is there like a detailed way that i can see if that's even accurate
agility isn't traveled is not traveled this way where are you guys getting this from
i'm doing two vitality right hex wand of wrath that's really expensive for how not that much
better this is crystal wand i got a lot of money silver staff plus one all right i'm gonna get a
magic potion yes buy them both and then i'm getting the hell out of here uh in sleep
travel i can only go down here and i do not want to do that oh yeah all right so i have to go down
into the right beacons i might be like wait till the next day uh there is no next day it's all dark
forever i have to go to the first beacon with i have it's down here isn't it i just i'm just
skipping the game you see another wanderer on your path sitting on a rock they look scared approach
the wanderer is injured heal wonder gain strength and thanks you talk book of clairvoyance
permanently learn skill clairvoyance what is that see farther oh shit okay ask advice
it's dangerous to travel east too quickly the monsters and bandits are stronger near the castle
all right we go to monolith teleport approach make an offering here we go everything else
only do one three blues plus a colorless is enchanting one one one one one only one only one
one put the hex wand in there wait a minute so if i do hex wand three do not do that do not do that
do not do that do not do that do not do that keep hex wand what the fuck
jesus last time i did three i got a permanent uh stat increase give all gear i'm giving it all
i'm not doing one at a time read the monolith research paper yeah i'm reading the monolith
research paper is reading the place mat at chile's when you go with your nephew it's the same thing
it's all right i got a permanent stat increase i'm okay guys do fireball four what else is here
chant item resurrect oh by the way uh those of you watching uh if i die the game ends forgot
to mention that right i think i actually didn't mention that it's been like three hours uh i don't
think i think i think it's a roguelike yeah we played a roguelike before but there's been no
indication that that it had that happens teleport too i'm not doing teleport too why the fuck would
i do that i'm doing fireball or 48 fire damage or electroskin or resurrect where's that beacon
i i need a i need to go in here what is this what is this thing should i go in here it's a dungeon
okay i'm not going in you come across some bandits oh i need more bandit people three bandits
bandits are carrying stolen goods and offer you a bribe i need to turn that thing on here we go
i think i'm gonna get there you see a hooded figure in the distance they look curious
the hooded figure is holding some treasure and doesn't notice you talk what a figure says he
will sell you the mysterious item thanks it's better than what i have on no it's not not even
close okay there's another wanderer on your path sitting on a rock they look harmless the wanderer
greets you wonder wonders what you'd like to discuss rumors those eerie monoliths showed up
a few days ago i wonder if they were here to help i hear they react when you give them a magical
item burn on the beacon you stand before one of the three guardian beacons the ground is littered
with the corpses of other outsiders there is an inscription at the base of the beacon read the
warning the inscription reads like the three beacons to open the path of the king this beacon is
guarded by brogant oh whoa what fuck you oh i died oh i got brogant sword brogant sword health
grains floor when damage is taken oh if you only can't use it are so poisoned uh the beacon is
lit and glows brightly i thought i was gonna get an area right need escape why is it gonna be bad
okay king's icon teleport to the nearest fort okay cool uh i really wish i did this
this is worth 18 gold get the fuck out of here that's that what could have gotten closer if i
walk over there that the shadow is gonna kill me i have a money mage robe what's this do 21
then shop magic shop this is terrible take one of these gravel oh wait where the hell am i
wait i'm down here all right this sword i need it's 14 agility 17 strength poison three 40
damage to beasts this thing is so good but i just can't it's mathematically impossible for me to
use this you only bought one potion next to that i made it out now this is it this is it i did it
all right i'm out where are the beacons i got this one this one up we're gonna go up i've got to get
the hell out of here no group of thieves they look bloodthirsty the thieves surround you there are
two of them talk hey they're carrying stolen goods i'll take my money please thank you all right i
feel safe buckler karma is gonna be fucked i need one on three of these right that's it i got it
right is it three or four i think that's it for my emails all right that's 600 experience
about those emails what about them i have to go to a town now where i mean i gotta just go up
all right you come across an enchanted healing fountain uh drop one gold drop a gold and coin
the fountain make a wish uh drop a gold drop one more gold wait take the gold back uh heal
you feel refreshed okay it's not a thief i i i i dropped it i just dropped it i had to pick it
back up i didn't mean to put it in there die useless deserted home do i have any keys
i don't have any keys so i mean side room nursery i knew there was gonna be a skeleton in here but
i thought i'm gonna level up no i'm not oh come on really the hell is this limp ring of warding
uh that's i'm okay with that all right i guess leave the bed this town right that's not a guild
town though is it i don't look do i have any i have this there's no guild and does it have a guild
does all right quests here we go 600 experience and a floated potion
what does it do it smells terrible what is it for guild special boots i need bandits teeth drink
drink drink now drink drink drink drink drink drink drink drink it feel more skillful i have
two points nice uh fireball four and electric skin for or enchanted view a normal item with
random magical properties i don't know if i that's a lot of mana remove all magical properties from
an item create a random potion that's not bad i like that one fireball four fireball four all
right disenchant what does this one 33 percent magic power i mean that's that's all right it's
not terrible it's good but 10 magic power to intellect 33 percent i think i'm just gonna put
it on get destroyed in attack speed though all right i'm gonna disenchant this one
bright ring of warding invisibility potion i'll just turn this into a ring what does this even do
avoid all battles while traveling that's pretty good actually that's really good
disenchant the orb i'm gonna stay the orb potion of attack cool
temporarily increase attack speed do not drink more than three in a day
i needed things in our house but disenchant the legendary ways so much exorcists kill skeletons
for bandits tea they don't have i equipped the wheel let me see did i i can't yet i could if i do
one more strength five agility 15 block 10 block this character sucks so bad what do i need to use
this 17 strength no i need agility too i'm going intellect pump strength no but i need to pump
this 14 you're a mage i yeah that's what i'm saying uh the weapon's not that good
uh should i just do 20 vitality or 22 intellect yeah yeah yep restore this
i sell this general store blue boots move speed what do i have now these things are terrible
these things are absolutely awful three and then three not worth the gold smoke bomb small pack
get it for the travel distance i mean i already that's what these are
i'm gonna keep the ring small pack is really great but that's a lot of money
it's almost all my money it's too much let's go wait no you don't have any potions well
shit this is bad all right let's go this way where is the other beacon up right next to this to the
top left all right so just stay going this way i'm gonna teleport over here because i don't want to
fight anything no key no key i didn't get a key put a button key on you come on chest i can't
i'm gonna sleep in your bed 17 outsiders slain by this monster powerful beast has been attacking
outputs at night kidnapping people in their sleep but also stolen important shipment of supplies
on its way to the guild this beast is believed to live in a small cave nearby whoever can slay
this beast and retrieve the shipment will be rewarded greatly location has been added to the
world navigator shit there it is right there there it is all right i'm gonna do that i'm gonna go do
that i'm gonna go spam six fireballs at it here's strange laughter in the distance looking around
there doesn't seem to be a source starting forward again you are stopped by a witch immediately in
your path oh did you like your gift i can give you another yes very fair i'll give you a special
gift if you give me your hex wand i need that though that's my weapon the witch takes your
hex wand and with a flash of light the item the witch disappear you feel a change in yourself
magic power increased by 10 all right now there's any weapon that's 10 damage across the board
oh i'm right here look look at this look at this weapon shop look at this crude crystal wand of
frenzy you didn't think this was going to be good this has got nine magic resistance
he doesn't lose agility who cares there's only 76 gold that's more damage that's more crit and
plus one chill on attack plus nine magic regeneration i got the money that's only 76
gold i can do it but not yet oh shit that's good too how much money do i have 150 mana region is
the most important stat well i just made it better by plus two points mage boots i give this thing
go give the mage boots too i want to buy magic potion regular potion i have exactly zero dollars
i use my money very wisely i gotta go kill this monster i really i gotta kill this thing this
thing's gotta die i'm gonna sell some of this stuff actually because i want i want to be able
to sleep i gotta pull out my storage or bring these beast eyes do i even need them i haven't
had a quest for stop stop let's wake up wake up wake up that's damage tons of regen i'm gonna
i'm gonna try it i'm gonna go for it i have two i have some potions like a two mana potions one
healing potion he can has loot too i mean i have to fight a boss if i do this quest first
i get 2000 experience and i love this this is probably harder than this the beacon is
probably harder than this quest i would assume that the quest is probably not as hard give the
sword to the monologue i will okay is solid lovely yeah let's go arrived at the location
for the quest 17 outside is slain by the monster all right get ready come to a small cave there's
a mess of food scraps and empty potion bottles at the entrance entering the cave there is an
overwhelming stench this must be the home of the terrible beast described in the message
has teleport no that's gonna waste time no i can't i can't do that because or is that smart
preserve the mana do invisibility okay i'm gonna do invisibility potion how long does it work how
long go okay how long does it last you approach a large creature half beast half man it is sitting
with its back to you and seems distracted but am i actually invisible as you get closer you
clumsily crunch some twigs under your feet the beast man's doesn't seem to react hello the beast
man turns his head but does not get up have you come to fight me too no i'm asking about the stolen
shipment the beast man turns his head away from you and says nothing he seems to be eating something
what are you eating in front of the beast man is a half empty crate of food supplies with the
adventurer's guild logo on it ask him about the stealing and the killing he turns around quickly
i didn't kill anyone he looks glum i only stole a shipment because i was hungry and don't like
hunting take right away from him the beast man doesn't resist he only lets out a whimper leave
him some of the supplies the beast man thanks you and promises to stop stealing supplies we got it
without any violence no violence necessary what is this enemies can't see you i'm getting to the
end turn to service i got i got let's take that to free level up let's go skilled special armor
and 2 000 experience oh yeah what is it that's really good what do i want to learn glass body
this is terrible increases magic power by 20 percent decreases your defense by 15
that's got to be 80 apocalypse explode everything in the area it's like 32 fire damage to all enemies
burns you fireball guys this is 70 damage 70 that's a lot i can't pass that up
okay now it's time to fight the boss did i get any money for that what do i got
what's gonna happen here i'm gonna lose i need 10 strength to put this on i lose magic power
gain defense i can't use it because i need hold on i need 10 strength to put it on
oh and the shield i can't put the shield on too what is this the shield needs even more 14
i don't have any damn it this is broken what's going on plus nine spring where is it
it's broken no wait hold on i'm gonna take off everything i might just be stuck all right yeah
it was it was just stuck it was just a little stuck it's all right what the hell is going on
this is zero why is it doing this it's because my agility is too low i'm going into the negative
agility okay so you can't have negative agility but what am i gonna increase i don't know this
thing is awesome 17 defense versus five and plus two to everything that's really really good is it
worth pumping strength for i don't know if it is i'm supposed to be a mage armor shop how we
don't wizard shirt even i have the strength items yeah i'll store it i'll store it although i do
want to bring the sword to the monolith yeah yeah you're a buffoon jerma you buffoon what are you a
buffoon oh come on this is just a better version of the thing that i have on it's the not cursed one
all right let's go fight the boss give potions here i might have enough all right here we go
i'm going in here and i'm gonna light the beacon and i'm gonna spam 70 damaged fireballs at this
guy use the attack potion and then spam fireballs read warning light the three beacons open the path
to the king okay get fucking decimated get absolutely decimated i don't even know what
your name was i don't i'm not even gonna read it i'm not even gonna read it come on the second
major boss of the game does not have something that i could use toss boulder three 10 crit 15
crit damage 25 damage to damage five agility 47 springs my god it's a charm maybe if you weren't
such a wimpy nerd potions heal more i mean that's the beacon is lit okay first beacon number three
here it is oh i need to i don't want to risk this i'm taking a potion 37 gold so all right
if i go to the monolith and i extract the legendary power health drains slower when taking damage
that's not even what's that mean oh that means i can i can heal it if i need to i see i see
telling legendary relic omega monka lol what did you just call me small did you just call me did
you just call me small i'll go off on you again don't make me what did you say unironically mad
he's still thinking about it all right what are we doing i'm gonna sell the ball mace
anger anger anger anger anger he's so fucking angry he's so fucking angry everybody watch out
he's fucking flying off the handle another meltdown stream back to back meltdown stream
back to back let's go i don't know maybe it's just sleep yeah i'm gonna i'll have plenty of
man sleep oh demon tools more and more people these days are looking to darker powers to protect
themselves in the prophecy of the sky eater some go as far as summoning unnameable terrors from
demonic planes of existence these demons can't always be properly controlled and often protect
themselves with the use of demonic wards if you can bring us some of these wards maybe we can
better understand their power and use it against them and your reward will be one of the fucking
utilities from monopoly was it i don't think i've seen this yet that's fine all right i'm going for
i'm going for it and i gotta go up here what's max level roll anybody know approach the monolith
make an offering so let me look at this three sunshines in a square one sunshine thumb drop
and piece of paper i don't know right bottom right i know yeah i'm low on low battery my
computer's gonna turn off any second which by the way can we talk about this really quickly i'm
fucking so angry at apple apple products i know it's because it's a battery you're charging a
battery but just hear me out on this how many of you guys use your iphone or your ipad until
it's dead until it's dead like it just you the little spinny thing happens it just fucking turns
off happens to a lot of us right but why is it that when you plug in an iphone or an ipad from
it being dead some i don't know why this happens to me with both my devices this shit takes like
15 straight minutes to turn on again why can't it just run off the power why does it have to charge
the battery to then turn like why can't you just run off the wall can't i activate something that
says please run from a draw from the wall it's because of safety all right what happens if what
happens if this is an emergency phone call i have to make oh my phone's dead let me plug it in
oh hold on sorry that yeah it's just one second yeah can you sit there for like 15 straight minutes
while my iphone turns on to eight percent battery before it turns on again don't let it die i'm
sorry apple phones just die that's what they do they uh drain to zero in like six hours that's
just what they do i get so annoyed with that all the time i will sit there the phone will be plugged
in and it'll be dead and i'll keep trying to like six or seven straight minutes will go by
hold the power button battery symbol and i just hold it in front of my face i'm just like turn
turn the fuck on what are you doing and sometimes the phone will turn on and it'll be at like 14
percent battery it's like why couldn't you have turned on before you're at like 15 doesn't make
any sense i get so annoyed with that or i had to let it out you could have turned on at four or
five percent i know you could have you're stalling iphones die at 30 that's great facts thank you
mod that person mod that person for like a day all right uh make an offering should i do one
legendary or should i put them both in will it do them both only do one at a time okay only one
at a time give offering holy shit that's really good one stat point i'm gonna get four stat points
nice now what does it go into i wonder vitality and it's like agility squid agility squad oh i see
right you know that age-old saying just don't just you can't eat you can't like you can't you
gotta ignore it i i know i know but sometimes the kettle has to be opened and and you gotta make the
tea so the steam had to release i but once every three years i get to release a little bit of that
steam okay once every three years you gotta make the tea what what kind of fucking saying is that
it's a really really roundabout way of me saying i fucking all right we're gonna keep going
everything else you sound insane ban that guy for a day and then mod him for a week
i gotta go up what i fucking one shot that guy that guy's dead that guy's very very dead
it looks scared the hooded figure is being attacked and it's losing i'll help
they yeah just call me one shot don't worry uh hey you can eat this i don't want this
what would you like to discuss rumors powerful monster and marks its location on your map
really could i go one shot that guy let's go one hit kill this guy
potion want to extend your life if i said low on health you know that 80% of people suffer from
low health every day now there's a help you bring us these few ingredients and you guys telling me
to get rid of that stuff why are you hoarding why are you hoarding you're hoarding everything
oh i have the beast i i had a skull too hoarding yeah yeah yeah all right let's go one shot this guy
take out let's lay let's let out a little bit of steam what do you say
oh he was so hard scroll of burn three cast burn oh i can just do it from here what's this one
four into like five crit chance potion of attack that's good too let me get let me i need to
page rose put that ring on potion ready okay all right um do i how do i have
more all right i'm okay i'm not it's all right i'm not in a bad spot i got money right yeah i'm
gonna i'm gonna rest so sleep sleep again i'm gonna port port port two shot the third beacon
and then one hit the let the king and beat again which is invisibility potion this thing's actually
really really good i want this this thing turned out to be great oops i just closed the game
all right storage nothing in here that i need no quests wish i had it wish i had it wish i had it
pump this jam the music used to be louder and that's an interesting audible level
you come across an enchanted healing fountain drop one gold and drink where is that hooded figure on
your path sitting on a rock they look harmless sir the hooded figure greets you hooded figure
sees your limp ring of warding they offer to buy it for 40 gold no deal 60 gold that's 33 that's
33 more damage across the board i mean come on that's perfect all right so this is right up here
there it is all right let's one hit kill somebody you ready read the warning this beacon is guarded
by fall ront scope not enough map whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa that's a pokemon
choose all right i'm not gonna see what's in the bag yet the last body apocalypse or should i just
should i do electric skin electric skin for 26 percent got fireballs at max yeah i know
clear mind clear mind only has one level doesn't have more than one clear mind last body please
bro dude if i get hit once i'm dead i'm not doing that we're at like the end of the game
no i'm doing electric skin for what's in the box another axe another where's the mage equipment
this thing sucks black fireball too increased damage when health is low this stuff sucks for me
it's all been sick weapons bro germa please bro germa bro come on bro all right we gotta go for it
i gotta stick the uh stick to the plan beacon is lit that's three i'm gonna get them i mean
they're they're amazing okay let's get a bunch of junk here junk junk junk junk junk junk cell
this ring potency potions heal more i mean that's not bad i think i'm gonna put this on
and sell everything else stop how much does this weigh it's always at 11 i can't carry it in a
regular bag i have to get all right whatever five agility 20 block i'm not gonna have 28 strength
to sell the damn thing 27 gold is a lot good i'll take it where's the uh wait my shopping
card is still open oops all right there's the bad guy this is the this is it right figure it looks
scared heal thanks you talk but it tells you about a great treasure and marks the location
on your map where is it oh you gotta be fucking kidding me you come across a great treasure
you approach the chest open it no don't think so you're not gonna get me with that one iron
mask antidote and book of fireball permanently learn the skill fireball oh this was worth 15
mana i guess i could enchant this now i need to use a potion no you know i don't no i don't yes
i do no wait what i can't go over here that's not what i can't go over here oh come on i thought
when i i thought i could i thought i connected read the book the book they can't do anything
why you guys want me to read the book doesn't i already know the spell let me put on my travel
ring in here somewhere see another wanderer approaching me look curious they're holding
treasure and they don't notice you he'll sell you the mysterious item just give it to me just
fucking give it to me oh mighty's shoes whoa oh that's actually pretty good i'll take it
i took the guy's sneakers off i think we just found our scenario where i can
put on the other hold on this is important that's seven strength all right hold up hold up a second
really not have any potions considering it's acting like this i'm not gonna die to the jelly
that's not even possible i didn't lose to the jelly and i got up to mana potions and i'm gonna
sleep at this end and i'm almost level 12 whatever the hell it is gonna sleep or this i'm not gonna
use it for anything or this this shit well i need this is important let's decide let's do a decision
here do i want to put this on because with these shoes i lose magic regen but i gain seven strength
which then allows me to put on this huge defense armor and plus two to every step you're gonna
give up all the fireball damage yeah use the shoes for the strength for the armor and then use the
sword i already the sword's gone i got rid of the sword and disenchanted it i offered it to the
model all right what's gonna do we're gonna go with this we're gonna go with what i have now
i made my bed i might as well sleep in it oh this is not an inn so what is in your storage
well you don't want this sword let's just see what it looks like
you know what i mean let's just see what it looks like we need to know what it looks like
wear those shoes 21 strength leading into 14 strength 22 vitality 32 intellect leading into
15 requires level 16 i'm not i can't even put it on i need to be three levels higher all right
let's go back okay can i do this now okay yes now the wheel now the wand and now the ring
four into like five great chance that's going on all right yeah we're just gonna go with this
i'm almost over 14 but you know no i said i i i i i i like i i i i didn't say i didn't not the
other way is this isn't in here now it's a dungeon shit there's no end over here there's no end what
am i supposed to do take a mana potion and then fight because i can't go anywhere the only thing
i can do is fight i'm gonna fight almost leveled a beast died use that earlier another wanderer
wanderer greets you i'd like some advice easier to escape from battle when your enemy is injured
yes it is invisibility i'm not i'm trying to level up i don't want to avoid a random
encounter i want to be random encountered being attacked and is losing there it is black fireball
a very slow but very powerful fireball inflicts 110 fire damage to target and 28 to all enemies
that's how slow is slow you know what i mean this is 8 for 70 this is 7 for 110 but i could
get two of these off before i get probably one it's way too slow okay yeah i won't use it
what should i get in its place though great teleport i don't think you can
uh i would do enchant on him but we're way too we're way too it's like the end of the game
glass body ah that's so much defense to lose i can't i i don't i can't reliably i don't i'm scared
to do that electric skin maxed out whatever uh all right i knew i want a rumor okay two healing
potions two invisibility potions two or i i have an attack potion let's go you see the king's
castle it's oddly quiet nothing grows on the ground nearby oh you stats right right right right
uh all into intellect or all into vitality already said okay approach with the three
guardian beacons lit the gate opens before you i gotta move this shit around just too much just
look at all this crap this beast i out of here uh i want the antidotes i want to move this up here
i want them next to each other cool i just want them in the easy place to be i want them right
next to each other let's go all right where where should i go invisibility potion and just walk to
the boss invisibility potion and walk to boss let's go come on hurry up uh which way up down
i'm gonna go up this is wrong am i still invisible no you can't see the i'm not trying i'm
wait i'm i thought i was trying to find and kill the boss and not go to the exit
can't teleport to it there's multiple floors so i start i'm gonna teleport i'm gonna teleport
teleport and then uh go down look at all this treasure this treasure everywhere wait do i have
any dumb useless items i do what i why do i have all this i have all this crap i shouldn't have
brought this just disenchant it i will suggest open it how's it good stuff that i can't use
i'm looking for a good wand like an end game wand it's trash leave them for somebody else
fine what's this cold ore three three magic regen 10 magic power one damage protection
15 magic fine what's cold ore three plate armor i can't use this 24 strength leave that for somebody
else get it this is six crit hold on nine magic regen three magic regen more damage more magic
fun i get the agility goes away yeah this is better learn skill cold aura what does it do
temporary aura that chills enemies four seconds when they attack you wait what i have to activate
it how much does it cost three men if it's not bad so i just turned that on uh right before they
hit me that's pretty sick okay let's keep going they put all these they put all this stuff in here
no random no random yes deft orb of stone shit hold on give me this party ring eight vitality
five percent damage protection seven agility eight damage so this has no defense but i get
a bunch of agility which doesn't really matter i lose the block and i lose the defense but i think
that's plus eight damage on my weapon i don't think that's plus eight damage to spell is it
i'm not sure that's how the way it works i think it's only on the on a melee damage protection is
good too but is five percent damage protection better than 12 defense and 15 block that's for a
fucking scientist that's not me disenchant i will i must get the last treasure
no random encounters either this is this is beautiful i got another orb 10 damage small pack
nice and potion good all right all back oh shit what'd you just do all right i'm gonna open this
up let's put this other crap in here uh it's a huge weight too yeah they're just really dumping
this all on me at the end of the game huh i wish that was magic damage it's time to do some
disenchanting it's way chat saying it's all it's global damage global damage huh
18 to 19 plus eight to 70 isn't that much no it's not this has protection on it though
five percent protection versus having the shield i have 28 defense now that's not good
just go fast and just i don't block well all right we'll go and spam that's true we're gonna
go spam technique because i'm gonna do attack power and then just spam fireball and just try
to melt the final boss all right here we go all right get this shit ready i'm no i'm making
okay here we go so i got my potions i gotta get potions i gotta beg this is not i don't like this
get the wheel out of here okay attack potion attack potion please disenchant but that uses
mana that uses mana that uses but that uses mana just tele-frag them i can't you're gonna get
potions i'm not guaranteed to get mana potions i might get i might get invisibility potions all
right all right all right all right i'm going for it we're gonna go we're gonna disenchant the mighty
boots it was a mana potion good call a hearty ring attack potion i already got one of those
the orb of destruction okay one more all right it turned out to be a net gain because i got i got
one extra mana potion these stack don't drink more than three of these okay what happens if i drink
three don't drink don't drink okay if i drink three can i one hit kill the final boss
we know if they stack wait how many have i drank already today
wait wait wait wait wait hold on everybody relax well how many have i had today i haven't slept i
had two okay i want to be full mana this is what this one was free ready you approach the king's
throne the king sits stiff and frail and these i uh a knight next to him in full armor speaks for
him this is the pause you've proven yourself to be the strongest outsider if you believe you are
stalwart enough to fulfill the prophecy then show me your power the fuck out hey i just rip
don't i can't rip that out i just broke something i'm fucking so stupid this is connected to a
different spot he's dead loot royal disc reputation is power three intelligence three vitality three
spring three gel what is it it's a weapon what do you reputation where's my reputation like this
okay well might as well just take this take the full potion and uh take the royal disc
i mean i'm not gonna use it all right so i'm gonna do should i heal i'm gonna heal use potion
all right i'm ready take another attack push take an antidote all right i need to put this
full heal up here all right i'm ready all right but wow what if i run out of mana what if i run
out of mana i'm gonna run out of mana i'm gonna run out of mana i'm gonna run out of mana king's
guard attacked you king's guard collapses there might be hope after all a layer of dust falls
from the king as he lifts himself from his throne using a large staff to hold himself up the king
mutters an incantation and looks to his side a portal opens beside him with a flash of light
and a dark aura the king sits back down on his throne and points towards the portal he says
nothing what do you mean he says nothing uh in front of you is a blue portal as you approach
the king speaks this portal will take you inside the body of the sky eater i only have the power
to send one person through so it is up to you now find a way to destroy the sky eater from the inside
okay it's wasting mana i'm get no it's not a waste of mana no it's not now i'm gonna travel
i'll show you i wanted to get close because then i'm gonna level up come on no potions no nothing
i need to i don't want to take this i don't want to take this i don't want to take this potion
because i'm gonna level up what do i do about this this is jane this is jane all right yeah
Good good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good chat. Good chat. Good work. I'm gonna just who cares about this disc
Wow, it's still in chant. All right, I'm gonna disenchant of the travel ring
Come on charmer fortitude
Got it
karma fading
Not enough magic points. What the fuck are you talking about? Oh, I have to use magic
Damn it. All right. I scroll the burn three. I'm gonna use in the next fight. All right. All right. All right
All right, there we go. Exactly what I wanted to have happen. What should I do?
Hold or three. I don't even use it
last body
Last body. No, no, no, no, no electric skin
Electric skin is already maxed out
Vigilance, how about that one? That's not that that's a I get that I can do it instantly casts
That's trash. It's it's not no, it's not it's not trash
critical focus
Just an increased chance to crit. Yeah
No, I'm not gonna do glass body I can't this is gonna be the reason why I lose the game
I'm gonna select this I'm gonna get killed. I'm gonna take two hits and die
You've already lost. I have not already lost
I'm gonna do crits critical focus. We'll go in super super boring and
Completely boring and neutral. I did it
This is now I teleport. Thank you. I'll take it
Roach it's being guarded by a creature
Hey, it's a mimic limp rune spear of vitality book of apocalypse
16 vitality that's a lot
That's a huge amount of vitality
But okay. Hold on hear me out. Oh, I don't have an opportunity for this. Well, here's apocalypse
Beast die. Oh great
Damn it. Don't want this
Okay, I convert potions because I don't want those
Start drinking them. I can't drink if I drink more than one or two more of these. I mean, I'm dead or something
40 intelligence 41 intelligence. It's a mimic. Don't drink them. You will die. I know if can I drink one more though?
Only have one mana potion. This is really terrible. Actually, this is really really bad. I'm gonna have to run away and fight
Attack normally
This is not a good idea. This is bad idea, but it's kind of working
This is what about a bad idea. This was why did I listen to this person attack normally? Why did I listen?
What did I listen?
I'm dead. I only took 90% of my HP fuck
Doesn't take glass body and may lays on his mage. No, I'm just trying something just teleport
No, no, no, I can't I don't have any more mana. I got a level up again. I
Got a level up again
What do you not have anything on you? How do you have zero anything? Come on use the scrolls? I live one scroll
Chug attacks. I can't I'm not chugging attack
Which way I go. I am regening though. Thankfully. I'm not getting any random battles. That's good
Whatever it's a down
Wow, that's what a great move. Look at that. Look at that. Look at that. I need to kill one more person
Don't miss blocks
I'm a mage. I'm not supposed to be doing this in the first place
Apocalypse 2 no, okay. All right. All right. All right. I'm at the heritage. Okay
I can disenchant and I just chance something fuck
Attack potion and then pray that I can kill it with three healing potion potion of attack
You're not but I have
Disenchant disenchant disenchant what there's nothing else. We didn't chant the royal the royal dick
Thing I already did it's bugged
In fact get this away from me the orb. It's been no, I have disenchanted everything
Yeah, it just it's bugged
There's an enormous heart like organ it beats so heavily you can feel the area around you change shape and the air rush back and forth
Destroying this will surely destroy the sky eater with great force you managed to pierce the flesh of the heart
There is no blood but instead of rush of fresh air
It's beating slows and a lump on the side opens to reveal an eye twice the size of your head
You try to communicate with the alien, but there is no response
only attack
Killed you I win I win I
Didn't get hit heart completely stops. There is a perfect stillness for a moment before the room around you begins to shrink
And the for the room around you begins to shrink and the air sucked out from every direction
You try to escape, but the passage quickly becomes too small. The air is gone. You lose consciousness
Is that the bad end?
Did I kill him too fast?
Name alvin 5000 the martyr level 17 mage killed saving the world
Of time day two hours seven minutes 24 gems earned 136
New character unlocked
worthless
Spend your gems to unlock new one
But you can unlock hot keys
10 health starting
Oh
Master key, I get it
ring of pain
But this is how you play the game more than once
I want the pink theme
And I want the bone cursor
And I want the fancy font
And
I want
plus
10 health points plus four magic points and I want to be the master of a sword
Sword mastery
All right new adventurer
Whose class worthless a weak unintelligent poor vagabond with only one arm
I don't want that let's do adventure. Obviously. I'm just curious as to what the heck what the heck's going on here
He's a starting gift
Oh
I see
Okay, let's just i'm just curious
Think or riot. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah
It's just I feel like a download my computer has a virus
Bone cursor I got all these things. I didn't turn them on screen. Okay
Nice
All right now we're really really going for it here
So ugly, well, this is fun. What's wrong with me?
Chill oh, I can't learn that I got a nail club though. Eugene gal
How black can I not use this
I just want to get the I just want to level up
I'm curious. I just want to level up
Approach the gang fight this character sucks
Now this is triple a gaming. Yeah, you can say that you can shield. Yeah, who cares? I'm but i'm gonna level up though
Hey kid
All right equip the sword. Oh, it's because of the way, but I don't know
strength
Oh, what do I need to do this? I need to be level three. Oh my god
Where's the sword?
I'm on fire. Am I am I gonna die right now? Am I dead here?
I'm gonna die here because of that
I I didn't have a weapon equipped
Saved the world
In one try and then died at the first encounter. That is very accurate
That's what happened
Can I like you want to bury them?
Yes
Who's a memento?
The club you couldn't use
Well, I can what should I bury I bury him put alvin to rest
Um, I think it's gonna have to be the northern northern mash
that turns around
Or the limp ring
Or um, I just I just get to keep his stuff
It goes to next of kin
I'm not gonna put the most powerful weapon in the world
into a coffin
It's mine now dad
But that's what you keep that. Oh, that's a good thing. I clicked it
Kylie kisser lunch lock. All right here take the best weapon in the game
Hey lunch lock take the best sword in the game
All right. I'm done. I'm not playing another one. I can say you can play this more than a few times though
Can you not use it?
In his inventory every level six
And the weapon is gone no, it's here
Here we go again with the end of the stream voice
Rhythm heaven tomorrow. Yes
Rhythm heaven is going to be tomorrow for the week
today was a
I was a little under the weather today
Because I had to go get an MRI done
So
Wasn't feeling a thousand percent today
But I did I wanted to stream and this was a requested game
So we'll leave it at that. Yes. I said yeah with contrast
uh, but I do have some
Uh potentially very interesting news for you
Joel has responded
And it looks like we're going to do keep talking and nobody explodes this weekend
I would assume we'll be doing that on
saturday
That would be nice make sense. Keep talking to nobody explode
another worst stream
Let's go worst stream 2020 no, I okay if the worst stream 2020
I mean, it's that's funny
That's funny
But I mean I and the mods go through all the nominations to see what's what and we you know take things out
Then maybe yeah that maybe that's the wrong category
Every every single worst stream of 2020 cannot be a stream that I streamed with Joel
That can't be every nominee. That is actually kind of funny though
So so i'm sorry, but that's not gonna happen
Community content night is also slated for saturday, but what i'm going to assume
is
when we played
last time
We only played for like an hour or two
Last uh, like a week or so ago when we did it. We only played for like an hour and a half
It's tomorrow. Well, technically saturday
Or maybe um
How long is rhythm heaven? How long is that game going to take to play?
Hold on. Let me look this up
How long is rhythm heaven it's long really
I always thought it was one of those games you could kind of
Holy shit. This is yeah, it's eight hours
16 hours for the extras and main game. Oh my jesus
Okay
Let me let me talk to him. Let me let me see what his what his schedule looks like
As if not saturday, then maybe we could do it
on
Sunday or monday or something
Don't cancel no, no, no, we're playing rhythm heaven tomorrow. I just didn't know it was that long
Probably two full streams to get through it
Let me let me see what his schedule looks like and we'll slate it for like
saturday sunday monday one of those days
streaming now
Maybe it'll be better to do that on like monday
I would say
Five minutes ago. He said he was playing it this weekend. Well that I I didn't realize that rhythm heaven was like a 10 hour game
I thought it was like four or three
I was under the assumption that rhythm heaven was less than three or four hours long
It's because it's very hard
Oh, i'm gonna love it then let's go
But tomorrow is going to be a very early stream
Not only is it rhythm heaven. It's starting at like 11 o'clock in the morning
so
There is that
But that's gonna be it
We do have
Um, I do want to briefly go over the bits from a few days ago
Because I was up really late and it was like a 13 and a half hour stream
so I do want to
at least
cover those
as
Much as I can
Based and like elicit. I don't even remember saying half of that shit
Gimli stream
No outro. Yeah. Yeah there there is
but i'm saying i'm gonna start with um
The bits and subs and everything or at least the bits that we missed
from a few years ago
It was about 13 hours worth
Get it open
But i'll see you guys tomorrow morning
bright and early pacific time in which 11 a.m. Is not really bright and early
but
It is earlier
You got a stream or so I can get my wink points
Yeah, I know
I do
Get some music playing
Irma wink grew pilled. All right, let's try to go through these in a timely manner
We had five dollars from an anonymous cheer
Just five dollars
It was a huge amount of community subs also. It's every stream. There's a bunch of community subs
At the beginning now because of the hype train
Thank you so much guys
You guys every fucking day
Dump huge amounts of money on this stream and now there's this incentive for a hype train
Thanks guys
We had 250 from ipod matt. I said germa. I can't do this anymore any more hype and i'm gonna spontaneously combust
And he says thanks dude, and he smashes his keyboard and it was him exploding
Hey cad, thanks for the 250 cad
Is this the hype train for the bathtub stream?
No, I ain't ever getting in a bath on stream. You know that horror story that happened in my made-up reality
near shoe, thanks for the thousand bits
Thank you near shoe potion dweller. Thanks for 250
I'm, so sick of these hype trains. They're genius because they're making you so much money though
Even though I can tell you don't want them
well, if it's not that I don't want something like that to happen, it's just
Uh, i'm gonna keep increasing
the difficulty
For them to happen in the first place
So it doesn't happen every single time
But I mean right so he hates money. No, but listen
there's
There's all right. There's a sub train every single stream
And it's like that's very very good for me. That's a lot of money
But I never I don't want to
Have people think that that's something that they have to do every day
So I I I increased it a little bit as of the last two days. So i'm gonna
Make it i'm gonna raise the challenge a little bit to make it so it doesn't happen
As often and it might take a little bit more time and might be more difficult to do
The rain pisses him off
Stream every day for a hype train every day
Taking a vitamin
I appreciate it though. Thank you near shoe. Thanks for the 400 bits
Let's go fellas
Sticks renegade thanks for the 250 what's harder beating the first level of lord of the rings changing a tire or drawing my fursona
All those things are incredibly difficult
German do you know that germa doesn't know how to chat? Hey chat, you know, germa doesn't know how to drive a car
That's why he can't that's why he sucks at fixing them 18 percent of people change their own oil
That's just that's
Okay, germa wink wink. What do you mean? What do you mean the wink happened? Oh didn't
wink
Wait, this are a wink just happened
Tingey just redeemed a wink
How did you get 75 000 points in like two weeks? What?
This is history this is history
Yeah, that kind of is
But that's still on weird i'm gonna i'm gonna look a little blue and green and shit
Because I didn't do there's literally no
All right, here you go
It's not don't be why am I being so weird about it? I hate it. I'm okay. That's it. Of course
That's the only one that's gonna happen. I don't like it. I'm not doing it again
That wasn't worth it
Of course, it's not worth it
Of course not
Now that one was
Anyways, uh all those things are hard sticks. Hey clap them back. Thank you for the 400 bits. They say my fucking
Bean, I don't know what that is my beans
Freudian weapon. Thanks for the 260
What do you mean another one? No, there's no there's not how did you get 75 000 channel?
Uh training hype. Thanks for the 260 freudian
Mace rater. Thanks for the 250. Please. Let me just enjoy my han solo rides in innocence
See 4g. Thanks for 250. Oh fuck. It's han solo dude. I can't stop fucking fogging. I
Hey gnarly, thanks for the 250
I thought I loved the hype train ride
But on my third train I started noticing the wires coming out of the streamer and the voice modifier he had
Even the starting soon planets are actually just pre-recorded footage. Honestly sucked all of the hype out of it. Thank you feels bad, man
Another wink
I don't see one
I don't see one. I don't see one
I missed another one
Dr. Piggett, thanks for the 500 bits germa. I love you
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Hey, nope. Thanks for the thousand bitch ten dollars so much hype
There was a super pug champ here. How did he even do that?
Thanks for the thousand bits
Germa sucks. Thanks for the five dollars
Monka s they say
Fluster flamingo. Thanks for the five dollars flustered flamingo five dollars
Appreciate it. Thank you
Reaper 500. Thanks for the 250
Can't believe you lied about beating jump king thing
Wait, I can't believe that you lied about beating jump king good thing. Joel told us you were there when it happened
I remember your name in chat
You pog champed and said I can't believe he did it. I remember I did like you were in the chat
Thank you though. Appreciate it
Eleanor gave 5 000 bits 50 dollars from eleanor
I like this video game. They were talking about
Lord of the Rings the two towers
Well, I like
I was gonna say I like money, but that's kind of fucked up
Thank you. I really appreciate
You do
Oh, he does we got him. He does he likes money. We got him
He likes that thing that you could trade for other things
Wait, he likes the thing that gets him
Breadsticks from pizza hut. No, he couldn't not that thing
Without it. He doesn't get that
No, but really though, that's that's 50 dollars. It's a lot of money. Thank you
Isn't pizza hut doing real bad, by the way?
I heard they were going under that true. I mean it was like one of
the
17 000 watch mojo videos. Is that for real?
They started charging an extra one dollar for their original crust
scumbags
How could they?
It's like when subway made the five dollar footlong and then made it the six dollar footlong and then made it the seven dollar footlong
And then they said oh shit, we'll do the five dollar footlong again, but it's only like four sandwiches
Got that from a watch mojo video. It's not even watch mojo
What's it? There's another one. It's called like
There's like three of them that make the same videos and they have the same person that talks
mojo watch
looper
Yeah, they
No, not much not matching mojo
All right side. I don't there's a lot
And they all have the same person talking
It's that same lady. It's that same girl
We make videos every single day. So click on that bell. It's the same person in every video
You're acting like we've watched these you had to have seen one
We make videos every single day
Are people still telling you to click on the bell?
in every video
You know, let me I I got I have to say this
How stupid do people think that the audience is?
That they have to be told
every
single day
To click on the bell
every single day
Remember click on that bell to get notifications
Oh, okay
For 364 days i'm going to tell you to do that because I don't trust that you're going to do it
Not like once a week felt like once every like other video no, no every single video
But it's because of the new people
Uh, do you know how many of those new people don't aren't even not even logged into youtube?
What bell?
Somebody just shared this video with me. I'm gonna make an account to click a bell
That's not gonna happen
Smash the like button. Yeah, but the the bell is youtube decided that they were gonna make people's videos not show up
So you have to click another subscription button to be able to get people's videos. Is that what that's it, right?
Hey, you subscribe to this person
You want to see their videos?
Be sure
What they should probably have done
Is shouldn't they just have like a pop-up come up that says? Oh, hey, by the way
Uh notice you haven't watched the last
475 watch mojo videos
Do you still want to say subscribe to them and that person could go?
Oh, fuck. Yeah
No, I guess not
Why does it have to?
Oh, by the way, this has been it's been three days. It's been three days
Oh, so, uh dear germa985. We've noticed that uh, you haven't in the last four days have not watched
Six years worth of videos from watch mojo
Oh, uh, okay
YouTube doesn't want to encourage you to cut down on potential watch time though. It's a lot to make that many videos, man
I can't I couldn't even think about it
After I make one I don't know. There's like a team of people but after I made a video back in the day
I was just I was done
I was done. I want to make one of these for like at least two days. I'm fucking tired
I clicked the bell on your youtube channel, but it must not be working because i'm not getting any notifications
Oh shit, the sub boxes are broken
Wait, hold on you you didn't get my last
Five videos in a row that were top 10 scariest abandoned buildings
Uh, well, i'm sorry to hear that you should have am I gonna play kenshi? No, I've closed the book on that
Okay
Last three videos were doctor's appointments
Yeah. All right. Let's keep going
Uh sell thanks for the ten dollars thousand bits from sell thousand bits from yoko thousand bits from lmm, man
All of you. Thank you
They say fueling the train. That's yoko. Uh nova saying fueling the train while i'm here though
What part of massachusetts are you from you say boston, but that's what everybody says from i'm from well, um
There's a reason why people on the internet don't give uh direct echo locations of where they live
so
Uh, this question is uh, when i'm not going to answer
But you don't live there. My family does my friend. You know what I mean? Like it's
Hey, you don't live there anymore. You can just like uh, what if yeah, no one will care
No, but actually what you don't understand is
You do what you have it, right?
It was boston
city of boston inside the city
I've rode the train everywhere
I ate hot dogs
What does that I don't know what that has to do with anything
Inside city limits confirmed
But I appreciate the ten dollars though. Aren't you from rural mass?
What do you mean rural mass
This is not it's not like
It's not like mississippi
Oh, I guess no, I guess that is right. I guess that is well, not you know what I mean like this
Population per square mile all the way in western mass is one to ten
What?
Wait a minute population per square mile one to ten
one person potentially per mile
That's ridiculous
Well squared mile squared mile squared mile
Dude, are you guys excited for the xfl?
I can't wait for the xfl
Like that's gonna be
I can't wait the xfl is coming back in a week
I didn't even know this was happening
This is the moment in the xfl where like there's no fair catch and people just run into each other and like
Roche it at each other didn't they get no it's back
Two forward passes are allowed
Yeah, and they have a they have a shootout
If there's overtime
Like soccer or you know football
It's gonna be like hockey
That's gonna be ridiculous. I I can't wait
I I really I don't care that much about sports that much
but
I feel like it could be entertaining to watch just
You only need one foot in bounds to make it catch. It's a college rule
What's wrong with me?
I'm talking about the the xfl
of the new football league from vince mcmahon that was
Lasted one season back in 2002. It was a disaster. That's coming back
There was like four injuries every single game in the xfl
I don't I think I gotta like read the rules, but is is this coming back?
Why aren't you from boston? I thought you liked baseball. I do but I mean I don't watch
Every single game or anything if i'll catch it if it's on
I do like baseball. I do very much
It's like the football game you played that was half mortal combat what's the league one of the greatest
Video games ever speaking of great speaking of sports
I didn't even tell you guys this but over here. I have a very special game
I got nba street over here
I'm gonna play the absolute hell out of this
I've got quite the collection over here of video games
They're just waiting to be played
Both beautiful joes
Not a big deal. Don't worry
What's that? Oh begaman legends one and two over there hanging up
They're just sitting over there ready. They want to be played
You'll see them soon
tony hawks underground
And tony hawks underground too
I went nuts
And some other stuff, you know underground is the best
When are you gonna do the diablo 2 hardcore?
When I get a little less busy
It's gonna start to get
Really really busy for me
i'm trying to not
overthink this and overthink anything here, but
Over the next three or four weeks
I'm going to be very busy
I wanted to make sure I had a bunch of stuff ready to go lined up
No, no, no, no, no, no, there's no
There's no there's no baby
Let's just quell that one immediately
Do you have any special videos that you mentioned were in the process?
Uh, they've turned into streams
And yes, there is at least one
Very very very major project that is
Getting off the ground now
It's gonna be crazy
It is not the rumble 2
Although there are plans to try to do that
Hopefully
if not in 2020 then
very early into 2021
Then that stream
is going to be
fucking insane
But i'm the ftk actually have a meeting with the ftk people in
A couple days
I will give you a full update of what's going to happen to that server and what's going to happen for the next event
So it has not gone away. That's still it's still kind of in the process of being worked on
Firing them. No, i'm done
What's the reverse of firing somebody?
All right, let's keep going. Let's keep going
Numb legs, thanks for the 5 000 bits. Yeah, two days ago three days ago hype they say
hy p p p p p p
Thank you. I gotta start to go through these. Oh my god. We're not even halfway
I gotta stop going off on like engines
We had a lot of five dollars come in in a row
Dude, bro. Come on, bro, dude
quick stall up
The adhd compels you I know it does
It really does
All right. Here we go
We had
Three dollars from kemba dog
Did the shy remind you of your childhood?
All right. All right. All right. All right
I'm gonna fly off the handle. I'm gonna fly off the handle
potion dweller 250, uh natalie five dollars
Scruffle five dollars. Thank you so much
The stream needs to be dubbed germa one guy lord of the rings germa one guy to rule them all
Yes
Uh tingy 250
Pugles two five dollars
chumbo womski ten dollars
Quirphix whips ten dollars anonymous chira ten dollars
Thank you guys very excited for this 24-hour stream
Derma tingy asked me if dropping an ipad into the bathtub would electrocute you
It's like asking if dropping a banana in the bathtub would give you radiation poisoning. No, it's not a banana's not made it have electricity
Thank you. Hey pugles five dollars
They say short jokes by jr r tolkien himself
I know you guys got fucking better material up there
I know you guys could write books with some of the things you've come up with up there up there. Yeah
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Same thing
I died of laughter when I found out that the hobbit day was your birthday
Oh, i'm just laughing about it
Listen to me, I it's hilarious
Why couldn't it have been like aragorn day or like legolas's bow day?
Why couldn't it have been like
The shire's garden day anything?
You have to make that hobbit day
I would have taken like ogre day
That's proof that we live in a simulation. It might be
Why is he spouting this out now?
Because I did I went up by why would I ever have looked online for any reason? What day is hobbit day?
What what the fuck do I care what day hobbit day is and why would I ever look it up? Why would I ever care?
Hey, you know what? I'm thinking today
You know of all things that are just fucking worthless to me in my life
What is what day is hobbit day?
Hey, could I look what is it?
Siri
What day is hobbit day?
Hobbit day is September 22nd
2004 one of the movie come out
2002 he can't escape
No, I never I never will
No, no, it's not i'm not even gonna no clear the channel. No, it's not actually real
No, it's not
It's not actually real
Okay, let's go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. I gotta go
Me grumbo. Thanks for the thousand bits. I rented this game as a kid and it was miserable
Uh gremlin. Thanks for the four dollars germa stinky monkey. Haha
reinville 50 dollars
50 dollars from reinville 5000 fucking bits
What if the hype train is in bits anyhow just moved had your vods on while I put together new furniture. I think we caught this
Yep, I did
And reinville if you're watching now talking about putting the greedy grinner in a magic the gathering card
The greedy grinner actually being in a magic the gathering game
I would love to talk about that
I'm, not sure if you hit me up yet, but if you if you're just messing around you just meme in here then okay
But if you mean business
Call my manager
me
That number is
Two the long number
He didn't believe it
That would be so stupid
Wait, that's my number
But how can it be yours that's mine, I know i'm sorry just said your phone number
Imagine hearing your phone number over stream
Getting sidetracked. All right. Fuck. I'm sorry greedy grinner in magic the gathering reinville hit me up. We'll talk
Uh lm man. Thanks for the 400 bits. That's a reward for beating the first part of fellowship. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes sob
kai sob cryo
Thank you sob for the thousand bits as a kid me and my brother used to play this game an insane amount
But for some reason in our copy
Of the game it was impossible to save
So what we did is just play as far as we could every time without dying
Because then we'd have to start from the very beginning
This made the nazgul among other things so scary and that one time I got all the way to
Moira it was so fucking fog
That I had my brother come home from school to watch
Anyways, thanks for the insane nostalgia
The game is so hard. It's just so hard and so chunky and
But it still kind of holds up
Shanji again a ten thousand bits. I think we went over it but a fucking hundred dollars
They said I was going to ask if you realize you've invaded into playing a game
That's basically just a short joke
But then you confused candy for fruit and asked if dropping an ipad in the tub could kill you
So yeah, here's to my favorite century gun. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Thank you
Hey sneak man, thanks for 300 bits germa's gamer challenge every saturday at 4 p.m. Central only on twitch.tv
I love okay, you can tell when
I was losing my mind and having a problem and freaking out and people may have been getting concerned because you get um
You get comments like this and I actually don't even remember this
But I think i'm the meme machine gave 5 000 bits so they gave 50 dollars
Which is huge
And they said for the love of all that is holy germa. You finished the first level of the game
I'm literally paying you 25 times the wager of the bet for you to go play with joel instead of dragging this out. Holy shit
that was
just about
seven hours
Before the stream actually turned off
I think the stream went on for another eight hours after that
Flushy 400 bits play with joel. We would both enjoy that more
And well, that'll happen soon. Don't worry
Yes is online is shangyi both
5 000 5 000 bits
Placid locked by a tree next game. Oh my god. This music is bootleg firelink shrine. I remember this one
Please stop you missed a pip and skip already
Yep
Is shangyi thanks for a thousand bits died to pinewheel
Potion dweller. Thanks for the 250. They say i'm in the pro bf bugleberry camp
Please tell him he has fans and that bf stands for best friends to us
Also, as I was getting in the shower, I heard you say that your birthday was hobbit day
I laughed so hard as we realized you will never escape the compact streamer meme and fate conspires against you
Yeah, and today
Yes, and today I had a little bit of a meltdown about
Yeah, I had a little bit of an issue today. Yes. I did. I'm not gonna lie
I I saw I I went off a little bit. I've got a little irritated. That's what happens
That's what happens when people throw darts at you. He's smalting
There was a little issue it was a little issue find me a clip of it being of more than a little issue
It was just a small issue
I told one person to fuck off right? That's what happened. I pretty I said hey, fuck you or something. What happened?
There were 5000 people here today. I one person I said hey get out of here. Why what did I do? Did I do that?
I didn't ban anybody. I don't I don't
I don't ban anybody
My mods do or uh bad things that people do you banned him for a day and then modded him for a week
I did say that
Oh, but yeah, bf bugleberry does have some fans. I'm one of them. He knows that
Chowder man. Thanks for the thousand bits chowder man
Hey, I remember you mentioned you were thinking of playing outer wilds the other night
And if you're still considering it, I highly recommend it. I am and I will
For the most part the next let's see
Let's go over. Let me see. I'm just i'm curious myself. He's getting sidetracked again. Why did you do this?
Don't do this getting sidetracked just fucking do the rest dude. Oh my god. He's already got it open
Let's see. Uh, one two three four
um, I have
planned out
the next
at least
30 to 40 streams
Of the things that I know what i'm going to do
I'd say I'd say I have about 30 streams worth of stuff just ready
So I don't have to go. Oh, what should I do now? What should I do today? I planned out a lot of stuff
Bugleberry is hot
That's my opinion. That's your opinion. You can have that's fine. You can have any opinion you want
Whatever you think whatever the I mean he's handsome, right?
No one said that. Yes, I did look it up in the logs swiggity swanky. Thanks for the 250
This game takes me back
There was a game boy advanced game of both the two towers and return of the king which played as a diablo clone
Good times diablo 2 hardcore
Uh until I die
Is a stream as well
I'll be playing that should be fun
Chad is going to here's the thing about that. That's what you need to make it a little more interesting
Chad is going to pick the class
And pick every single skill point
so
Make it a little more interesting. I give it 10 minutes
Are you doing that because you do not want to win i'm doing it so I can prove
That no matter what anybody throws at me
Diablo 2 is my
Favorite video game top five ever
I can deal with anything you throw at me
I you don't think I know the synergies for every single fucking item in that game
You don't think I know every single item every single skill
Oh, let's let's make him a sorceress
And put 20 points into warmth. I can deal with that
In fact, I hope you do that reverse psychology do it
See what happens
Oh shit, he actually knows the skills
Hey cad
Chad you're here. I saw you
I hear this is the stream to watch bootleg movies. Keep up the great work homerad
Yeah, that's funny
That's funny
All the shit. All right, if you look up who's watching a movie right now
If you watch it like a load of things
That stream was funny the stream was a lot of fun
But thank you cat. Thank you orange julian for the five and a bit cheers to your gamer snack. It was delicious. Thank you
Jerma's pet ferret. I don't have a pet ferret, but thank you for the five dollars
Appreciate it. They say hey jerma. I'm samey
Or saime. I suffer from swelling and pain in both of my hands. It makes it almost impossible to use them some days
I'm a writer artist and a gamer and I work with dogs
Pretty awesome
I used to work with dogs too. I volunteered at an animal shelter. It's awesome
I highly recommend it if anybody has not done it before
I've seen countless doctors still no definite answer. I'm very proactive and sitting
Around doing nothing is hard on my mental health hate feeling useless and helpless, but your streams vods and videos
Sincerely help keep me sane and positive. You're a light in the dark times
Thank you
Thank you for the 500 bits first of all
and second of all
just know that
most people
Are going through something
There are I think a lot of people forget that I think a lot of people don't remember that and don't realize that you know
and if you can collectively
You know, that's why I like to tell people about but jerma. Why do you tell people about this?
Oh, why why'd you tell me about like all the things happening in your life that aren't very good?
It's because I I want to be a real person
You guys know I want you to know that there there there are bad things that happen in everybody's lives essentially
There are good things and there are bad things and I think that talking about the bad things
Let's us all know that we're human. So that's one of the reasons why sometimes I do share
Things that aren't really going great for medical problems like you have yourself as well
I wish you the best
I wish you the absolute best
Thanks for watching. Thanks for being here
And keep going
As best as you can moving on from that we had five dollars from mishanji
recipe for jerma jerky smoothie when
Uh, it's called open a bag of crave beef jerky
the best
Without a question without any single question at all. The only problem with crave beef jerky is it is incredibly expensive
But it is it is the best
It's the best
I have had lots of beef jerky before i've never had one that was better than crave
It's just very expensive
It's like eight bucks. Yes
It is like 750 or eight bucks for one of those bags of beef jerky. It's only like one or two and a half
It's like I can eat the whole thing in one bag
And that's the problem when you go get it
Oh
Crave beef jerky. All right. I love this stuff
You know how many i'm gonna grab like four of them. Yeah
I want to I want to make sure I have some in case i'm hungry and get one of those snacks
Then you go to the checkout and you realize that you just bought like 40 fucking dollars of your grocery bill is beef jerky
And you're like what what why why is my grocery bill so high?
40 but 50 dollars, but that
All right, because like well, I got like five or six like crazy
That's a huge amount of money for my grocery bill. Okay
fine dining
Like I said one thing if it was expensive and not the best
But it's expensive
and the best
One of my favorites is is uh chili lime
Oh
Doesn't get better than that. There's a sweet chipotle. Mm. It's okay. It's not as good as the chili lime though. Seriously
Jeremy's part of the one percent one percent jerky
Jack links original well, hold on jack links
Original
Versus crave original. Let's get it. What's the best beef jerky for you?
Like what's the highest quality? Let's see
uh
Jack links if you want a classic standard
classic standard
Try crave if you like super niche flavors
Black cherry barbecue pork jerky lemon garlic turkey jerky garlic chili pepper beef jerky. Ooh, that sounds pretty good to me
It's because it's weird. No, it's not. It's great
Hold on. What's the best and worst beef jerky ranked? What's the worst?
Three jerks jerky filet mignon beef jerky apparently is the worst
Jerky ever
And then chefs cut real steak jerky
apparently second worst
Oberto original beef jerky is like
Jack links coming in at number three
Jack links original beef jerky number three. Oh fuck off
Crave original sea salt at number two. What's number one?
Oh, whoa, wait, wait, wait, wait, whoa, wait a minute. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. This is the worst. This is the worst
This is top worst. This is number two worst
What's the worst beef jerky? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
This is the worst
What's wrong with what do they say about it?
Yes craves jerky is made with an impressive list of all-natural minimally processed ingredients
But this tiny one ounce serving has 10 grams of sugar in it a third of every gram of jerky is sugar
For comparison a fifth of each gram of glazed crispy cream donut is sugar
Who gives a shit?
Although this is now the best. All right, let's hold on
This is i'm actually getting mad right now. What's number one?
brooklyn bill tong
I
Yep, alloweding. Oh do my oh, I have to do the bits. Yeah, you're right. All right. Yeah, I got it. There's a bit
I'm pretty sure he's the best
Oh, it's a donut. It's not the donut. Yeah, and when you eat white bread your body treats it like cotton candy
Whoop the fucking doom
We really have to debate that
Anyways, we're actually almost done with this. Uh 260 260 from yoda. I made this in snapchat. Thank you for showing it
Oh the beef jerky inhalation thing. Yeah, I did do that. That's fucked up
Thank you yoda and thanks for another 250. You've actually been having a really bad day. Thank you for a spectacular stream
You always cheer me up when i'm sad. I always remember that you're epic jeremy and then they do it germa hog champ germa venus
Thank you. Dunky donut brand beef jerky
Hey, man up with icy hot. Thanks for the 500 bits. Thanks for streaming made my night better. Thank you
Thanks for watching
Rock writing. Thanks for the 500 bits. Hey there notice tonight may have caused some molding
There's something for you and just between you and me there is indeed a bosley hair club
And restoration center in clark county nevada where this money may go to good use
You got like just you guys got all these apples in front of you. You got these low hanging apples that you just
Tiny what's this one?
bald
Hmm, I could go up higher on the tree and these these ones are kind of rotten
But I could go higher up and get actually good apples
No
Oh, this is bad
Okay
Get off his lawn. He's he's actually mad
All right, that's my favorite thing when people when somebody's like going off
but like on a rant step i'm gonna go off a rant people and people write like
it's like
Come on, man
like
Not really, but yeah, but not really and like I could like
I I can't okay when I if I try to if I defend myself
If I come back and i'm like, hey, hey, listen to me for a second. Let me tell you this
It's like mocha ants. Oh, no
Gerber Gerber you smell like shit
poopoo short bald
fuck
Penis. Hey, stop doing that. Why are you saying this to me? What are you doing? Why did you say that to me?
Huh? Is he mad at me?
What happened? Why are you what's wrong? I need you to chill out. Hey, he's pointed his finger at me
He pointed at me. Oh, okay
Is he mad? Hey
I can't even like present an argument against any you know what I mean? It's like I run into like a brick wall
You're most really scary
What is this?
I want to listen to this. I don't even know what this is. This is not even the same stream
Yes, god, you guys are mean. Does he tell you guys it mean because like wait, this isn't this is not in my stream
This is tomato stream streamers. I try to avoid it
Yes, god, you guys are mean. Does he tell you guys it mean because like
It seems like everyone's in on some joke about bullying him for his height. That's pretty toxic. What the fuck
Hey
You guys bully me for my color blindness, I guess which isn't actually even color blindness. It's gaslighting. So I guess
Have you not met him in person i've met him multiple times in person every single time i've met him
He hasn't been that short. Oh
He's been moderately tall
At average not at best. He was just he was he was like
He wasn't short to me didn't seem that short. Then again, he was on like he was wearing like very high heel shoes
At the time that I met him
Tomatoes a great guy. He is he actually
Show actually bad
Talking about talking about the wind being taken out of your sails
From what's like having a direct line to hundreds of nine-year-olds every night
Stop
I need to finish the bits we gotta get out of here
No, what what set it off completely tonight was somebody came in and said
What was it? It was like
Like lol i'm 15 and taller than jeremy and it's like dude
You hide his in your dna. I I didn't like
I didn't like eat corn on the cob only and like
Lettuce you just that's just how tall you are
I didn't
I didn't like eat sand for breakfast and lunch and dinner every day. I just happened to not be
That's like our dna, man
It's like not so surprising
Oh, man boxbox coming in with a braid boxbox said you would feed us
Boxbox says you would be boxbox said you would feed us
What do you want to eat boxbox coming boxbox? We're at the end of the stream hanging out. Well, thanks for the raid. Welcome everybody
What do you guys want corn?
Got lots of sand
I got sand i've got corn i've got lettuce
Apparently the only three things that i've ever eaten in my life
To make me smaller than a 15 year old
If only he had eaten his vitamins and had broccoli maybe he would
You know what i'm not even going to get into it anymore
No, i've said my piece
Sand isn't food, but hey welcome 1700 people almost 2 000 people in a raid. Thank you boxbox
Welcome everybody
We were we were currently debating
um how tall I was
and how
people are comedians
It's interesting that there's thousands of comedians here
And they must all be part of the same comedy group because they all say the same jokes
They're all together in the I guess in the same same room, I guess
It's not much of a debate
We're all funny act. There it is. There it is. There it is. There it is. There it is. There it is
There it is. There it is. Do it everybody do it. All right almost done with a few days ago if you
By the way again boxbox. Thank you
Hope you had a good stream. Hope you guys are having a great night
if um
If tomorrow i'll be streaming rhythm heaven for the week
As we wind down for the end of tonight's stream
But yeah, uh, we're currently going over the bits
I do the
I don't read subs or bits or any donations on stream. We do it at the end of the post stream
Which is what we're doing now
and we have a very very very long stream a few days ago that I
Um almost collapsed
And I couldn't stand anymore as I had to leave and it was a 13 and a half hour stream and I was like
I gotta get out of here. So we're doing them now
I could have just said that
Much easier in about one sentence
All right, like that was much easier just to say hey i'm doing the bits from three days ago. Okay
All right, uh half monty. Thanks for the five dollars and ten cents. Great job jerma
I knew you had it in you super entertaining in a painful kind of way. Yeah
orange julian
Thousand bits shanji
Shanji a thousand bits both of you go for it. You're the man. You can do this. Wow. This game looks really hard
You are also a nice person. You did it. Thanks both of you
Bugleberry is my favorite character says man up with icy hot 250
Thank you
Cad btv. Thanks for the 250
I believe you can do this. I'm sorry. You think my support is fake grass
But I still believe you can beat this game little buddy
Pugles thanks for 250 legolas is a prince. He's only here to look good. He's good with him. He's got the good bow
He's good with bow
Saren fp. Thanks for the 500 bits yo jerma
I can't believe i've stuck around for almost 11 hours and loved every bit of it
There was still over two and a half hours after that
I'll probably be asleep by the time you read this but I just wanted to let you know not to
Not to something
a turbo driver dev gave
5,000
bits
Turbo driver dev. Thank you
I wake up in europe and you're still streaming. You're truly insane
Thank you turbo driver for the huge amount of money
Sometimes that happens. It only happens when I play playstation 2 or dreamcast games
and
That's actually kind of bad
because a shitload of things I have back here are
playstation 2
games old games, so
I don't know if it's about the old games thing
But I got a lot of them behind me
So be careful
Be careful nile aureon says for 300 bits. Hey, you fucking died mate. He he xd
Thank you
Judge mortis a thousand bits jerma, please for the love of god turn it off and go to bed your mother
And I can hear your damn tears through the wall go to sleep
I
Judge you don't know my father's a judge
Thank you judge. Thank you. Thank you dad
Nile aureon again 300 bits jerma has ascended
fox club 49 or 500 bits
Jerma, I went to bed for six or seven hours had a dream you accidentally put porn on the stream during a break
Woke up sweating for some reason and then saw you were still streaming
I don't know what's with the sex dreams people have of me putting sex on my stream
There has to be some reason why this is happening more than if okay if more than one person is having
subconscious dreams
Of me having sex on stream
Or doing porn on stream
What kind of vibe am I giving off?
That has to what kind of vibe am I giving off?
It's because people fall asleep in front of your streams and then
All right, let's get to the end here
Uh bug bear and frog. Thanks for the 500 bits. They say congrats
250 from cad. I hear vego beat helms deep his first try on expert
Nope
And then finally from a few nights ago. We had fifty dollars five thousand bits from swivel
Thanks for the 5k bits
Thanks for the longest stream jerma. Love you, man. What's the software that you edit your voice with?
software
Is it's not software at all. It's hardware. Is it go xlr?
I just got it
It's pretty fun. You can do all kinds of cool stuff with it
You can do all kind of kylo ren
What do you mean? Hold on kylo ren
kylo ren
Wait, wait
Kylo ren
Do you feel it? I know you did it's in a bb unit. It's in a bb unit. It's in a bb unit
Uh, we define those droids find where he is
And then get that
I can't say anything that might possibly be
a character's name
Or anybody that's in the story at all
Because that could be a somebody will say a spoiler in chat and then they'll get banned
So tell me ray
Fuck, I just said your name. Therefore. I just ruined everything
So tell me
where
is
that droid
It's in a bb unit
Why is the bb unit funny
I don't know is it
I'm out. I don't particularly think so
You will beatbox as kylo ren
Where is it?
Oh, I know. I know you know. See the thing is
I see it
I've always seen it. I've always
Only one beatbox
He can only do well now i've turned into bugleberry. Oh, oh
You can tell when it's bugleberry ready. Oh, oh and my hands come up. Oh, and he doesn't jim carrey. Oh, I oh
Bugleberry just is kylo ren
Minus 3 000 viewers because you said the name bugleberry
He's lost his fucking mind
Viewers dropping. Oh, no. Oh, whatever. Well, I do the fact that view hold on. It's gonna be a little bit more ridiculous
And you know the thing is
All you have to do
Is let's do an experiment. Let's do an experiment if I title the stream bugleberry reads bits
Willed a thousand people leave
Do you think so? I actually don't want to do that experiment
What the fuck were we doing?
Oh, right kylo ren. I hold on. What does this one do?
Combine voice
What is he doing? I don't I I don't know
Apparently kylo ren's in school of the school
Somebody threw food at him or something
I got lost there. I'm sure you all did too. All right, let's go to the uh current bits
I'm gonna be so truant now
Do more voices so you can do
Stalled bit reading don't worry. We're gonna go to lightning round lightning lightning lightning lightning round. Here we go. Ready? One two
three
Thanks, jamie for the five community subs. Thank you potion dweller for the 250 bits another hype train another wretched hype train
You got a lot of bits to read tonight since that
Uh, what what do you mean a lot of bits?
Oh, uh, from the two towers. Okay. I don't know right right right right
You got a lot of how would you know like if you said this six hours ago?
Like hey hype train you got a lot of bits to read tonight
Like what do you mean? This is like the second this is the first bit reading. All right shitty viewbot
Thanks for the thousand bits
Lightning round over. Nope. Here it comes shitty viewbot for the 1500 bits
Vanilla math for the 400 bits
Castellion for the 300 bits. They say please watch
Are we supposed to be short? I saw this already
It was oh, oh very funny
Hey toy
Croak, thanks for the 500 bits. I've had a long history of word surgery due to my needlessly broken bladder
Which just recently started to heal
Hope whatever it is you're going through finds an end soon and you find relief soon enough me too
it's starting to be just
something that I always constantly have to think about
and
It's it's just annoying right it nobody wants to ever have
A medical issue or a problem that you don't know. What is the actual problem?
But I have i'm going down the road of knowing what it is
And trying to obviously I have to figure out what kind of treatment or solution I want to do
Do I want to have surgery on my hernia?
Do I want to just get that out of the way and just do it?
Because I have one and it might be contributing to some of these problems. Do I want to get an injection in my rib cage?
To do a nerve
Stop some of the nerve problems right from the whatever the inflammation in my rib cage
Do I want to do those things?
And when am I going to do those things? How am I going to do those things?
Uh, what am I gonna just schedule out like now do it now?
I don't know because I was told that the hernia that I have
Is not really big enough
to need to do surgery on it yet
it's kind of at the
Wait and see because it's not that it's not huge
It's compact. Yes
it is
What do you mean yet? Um hernias at the hernias can get worse
This could be something that's been developing in my stomach and esophagus for years
And it could just get worse. You throwing up softball jokes, you know
You set it up. We knock it's please explain this in the trump voice
Oh, we are all here in this beautiful. Wait, that's not correct
Uh, let me excuse me
Let me tell you something first about first about why is it so low?
All right
Excuse me
Let me oh god
It's not listen
It's not it. It's it's not a big deal
I just have a small hernia
If the hernia is big enough to be a problem, but it's not really a problem. It's it's it's a little large
It's not really
It's it always goes back to bugleberry
So we had 200
200 hernias
All of them traded
All of them every single one. Yeah
That's right. Yeah
Yeah
Yeah, he does this sometimes he looks back. Yeah. Yeah
Meow
What's the most fucked up thing I can do with this? Let's see
Stop doing that. There's a lot of cool things you can do with this thing. That's actual worse sound
You're freaking out my cat
Can I bark? Hold on
You woke up my dog
Why did we do this? What happened? What the fuck did somebody say?
What happened? I swiped. Why am I just like flash? We're supposed to be reading what happened?
Thank you. Oh my god
Anyways, uh, yes, I have medical problems
Somebody said trump you said it once and that's all
And now we're here
lightning lightning lightning lightning lightning
But I wish you uh, good luck
with your bladder
I'm just trying to figure this shit out too, you know, that's what we do
Raffra thanks for five community subs
Vandrid, thanks for five community subs
tyfan thanks for five community subs germa sucks
250 bits show auto
Otto is incapacitated at the moment. I don't want to bring him up here. He he had surgery
I don't want to
Carry him around. I want him to be he's being taken care of downstairs with kim
so
He is not going to be on camera
Not going to be on camera today
Anyways, thank you germa sucks with the 250. Thank you. Also for the thousand bits from a wild meryl thousand bits
No message just thank you
Appreciate it tyfan again five more community subs g sauce
Hey g sauce. Thanks for the 700 bits. Appreciate it. They say hey germa long time fan since 2013
And I now just have some extra money to give you your content has helped me through so many tough times
And I would even say that the laughs I get kept me from acting
On suicidal thoughts you've been my favorite entertainer on the planet for a whole decade
And I can't thank you enough. I love your content man. And here's to more fantastic streams
Thank you so much for the 700 bits
I implore you I implore you
if you have
Any negative thoughts like that?
Or anything to do with
hurting yourself or
Self-harm or any of those kind of thoughts you don't want to be having those thoughts in the first place
I would get in touch with somebody that's a professional that can help you
Because you never want to let that linger
And even if you say that it does, you know watching these streams helps and laughing here
uh
Helps you and keeps you from acting on anything
You got to be careful there
Please please please
Go at it from a few different avenues
If I can elevate your mood a little bit
That makes me really really happy
just make sure that you're
Taking the steps necessary to try to
Get better
And sometimes it takes more than one front to do that
I wish you the best of luck. Thank you so much for the 700 bits
And thanks for hanging out. Keep on keeping on no shame and getting help
That's true
Honestly, we should we should
We should think about
mental health the same way we think about
If you got hurt, you know, if you like you're handed physical
You know what i'm saying?
Medical we should not be thinking about mental health as oh, no, no, no, no, that's that's like that's completely different
It's different. No, that's way different. It's I don't know. No, no, we don't talk about that
Because it's your it's your body everybody. It's everybody has a
It's your brain. It's your body. We got to treat it the same way
It has to be taken as seriously
Everyone has a brain. Yeah, no, that's true
It's different but it's just as important
Yeah, it is
but if you go to
uh
colon doctor
and you go to a
bone doctor
Those are completely different
They're completely they're treated completely differently
The tests that are completely different the way that you treat it is completely different, but it's still
Still medicine it's still treatment and for for some there's this
There's this stigma
That I really hope that we get over when it comes to how we see mental health and how we view mental health
It really shouldn't be there
It just should not be there
We need to treat
The issues that come up
in our bodies
And that's really the end of it all that's really what it should be
That's kind of how I feel about that
The bone doctor will heal
Almost said the rest of that
But anyways one day we will all be robots and all we have to worry about is rust
S. J. Thanks for the 250 hey germo
I've been a fan for a long time and want to share a dream that I had
Here we go
Where you were hosting a tour across the u.s with chat on your bus
Halfway in a boring state people convinced you to take a test made by chat
you sat down in some first grade classroom and answered questions like
Do you think you contribute to society?
One was what is your response to baby?
The answers you could choose were
Uh, yeah, or no, no, no you screeched for two minutes
And punched a guy
What are you guys eating when you watch these streams?
Do you all right? Do you do you guys just eat macaroni and cheese before you go to bed?
What are you eating before a stream before you go to bed?
corn and sand
Germa is just a scary mother fucker. No, but I am I though?
I completely disagree
I disagree it doesn't make any sense to me. No, they're gonna have bad dreams
Have been they're gonna be i'm gonna get a message tomorrow
Hey, dude, uh, I ate like a bowl of mac and cheese
And went to sleep and then I had a dream that you went through the computer and you were a monster and you killed me
I don't understand why they're having these dreams. This must be it must be something they're learning in school
Except you probably woke up somebody. I know i'm so fucking stupid
I just forget that I forget it's not like five people in a room. It's like thousands of people here
I forget i'm not I really do I really do forget that it's not like 10 people hanging out in my room
It's 2 a.m. Eastern. Ah shit. Well, good morning
I don't know what that was but it wasn't me
Cat attack. Thanks for the 500 bits. Hey germa. Hope everything's going well with the medical stuff
I deal with chronic illness myself
So I know every day is a new battle it seems don't push yourself too hard for our sake
We'd rather you be happy and healthy
Also half of this bit donation must specifically go to auto in the form of dog treats for being a brave boy. Absolutely
uh supper eyes
Surprise
everybody
surprise
20 community subs from supper eyes
He just at dinnertime his eyes light up and he's just
Wow, what do you got there mac and cheese a vat of it
And he had another part of the name. I don't know what it was
Uh, thank you supper eyes for the 20
Community subs. Thank you
What's with you mac and cheese tonight? I'm probably gonna eat it when I leave
click link click link quick click link that's
putting teeth
That aren't your teeth
on an image of you
Is terrifying like when you put teeth on something these are not my teeth
and it's
scary
Because this is kind of what I I mean if if I did that
You know, it would look like this
But this bottom half just is all wrong. It's just not my teeth
Oh now you are gonna have nightmares
Sorry about that
It's contrast germa
I really I want that I want that image to go like this
Can you hear it? Oh, you can't because my
You can't you couldn't even hear that
No, like I cannot get it to activate i'm i'm
Clicking my teeth i'm going click click click click click like this. Nope. You can't hear it
My gate is making it so you can't hear it here. I was going like this
I was going
Don't you want that image to do that?
Bite bite bite bite bite bite bite while doing that smile
Sure
Hey, miss lily t. Thanks for the $20 2000 bits. I won't be here when you read these
But I hope you had a good stream and I hope the chat behaved themselves. See you next stream
Um, they did no people it was fun
I just went off on somebody for a short a short joke that I didn't like and I
Went I got very angry about it. It wasn't even that bad
It wasn't that it was okay. Hey invader z. Thanks for the 250 yesterday was my birthday
So these are birthday bits for you. Just wanted to say thanks for making the past almost a year now amazing
And having a pretty rough couple months
And you always cheer me up
Thank you so much for that. Also just letting you know. My real name is an invader z
It's invaders
You don't pronounce the z separately you dingus
invaders
invader what's the
Invader
Invader zim
Oh, right. Not invader z invader zim. Yeah. No, no. No. Yeah
That's that's why I was thinking that
Like I know it's invader zim, but like invader z. I don't know. I figured it was like oh invader z
It's I like that show invaders
Thanks for the 250
Uber morph point. Thanks for the $30
3000 bits jeremy say trans rights with a question mark. Yeah, I think you guys already know my stance on that
I've said it before i'll say it again
Doesn't matter if you're straight if you're gay if you're trans, it doesn't matter do you do you do you well?
Do you very well?
Nobody else knows how to do you do you you are you you can do you it doesn't matter who you are do you
Who me you?
Do you
You you're not that person over there. You're not that person over there
That person over there. You you are your own person
Me that's a jump king inspirational speech
No, i'll just do you because you're the only one that knows how to do it
It's pretty much it
That's all I really have to say about it do the voice
I you gotta figure that's probably weird for people to hear
When they just don't they don't know what's coming. It's just like oh, okay
You just like you press the button again germa. I want to go to fucking bed
Bone jackal. Thanks for 500 bits
Hello twitch, this is jeremy's doctor. I'm excited to announce that jeremy and I will be collaborating on a world's first interactive live stream
Twitch does a colonoscopy you can catch us live january 23rd
On the official v's sauce twitch page. Hope to see you there
Don't do that 20 wait 23rd. Oh shit. That's coming up
20 the the day of death too
I gotta be careful. I actually really do what am I doing on the 23rd?
I was gonna eat mac and cheese
Thanks for the 500 bits though. Uh, that stream is not happening
Thank you
freightal schlitz
Freightal schlitz with the 400 bits germa is community content night still gonna happen on saturday
We're gonna do something else
No, what will probably end up happening is
I'm gonna do rhythm heaven tomorrow
Eu will do community content night eu
on saturday
and then
Probably I would say monday or i gotta I have to talk to joel and see what he's doing on monday or tuesday
Because that would fit into because I got a lot of stuff going on this weekend too that i'm
The reasons why i'm doing a u stream just because I got a lot going on
Uh, there's people coming in to visit
There is a couple other things I have to take care of in my in real life
So I this is I got a lot going on
We'll see i'm gonna see what his schedule is like
We're good to go for tomorrow and saturday for sure
Are you gonna have a go back to saturdays?
Uh, i'm not sure it'll be on a specific day
But it's just kind of there
Hey wolf gang. Thanks for the 500 bits do a funny voice
No, I've I thought I've done it like that was five hours ago. I just pressed the button and I unchecked it
I did it like 10 times already
Uh, but thank you guys. Thank you great canadian fk club for the five hundred
Red
Five doll no five subs five. Thank you for the five subs great canadian fk club
I got that wrong twice
Uh, thank you for the five subs. Thank you hubert roames for the 300 bits. You are a good person and you deserve to be happy
Thanks for all the streams
I try to be happy
I try to make myself happy. I try to do things that make me happy. I try to do things that make me laugh
my entire life
Has been at this point up until now
Just trying to amuse myself
So I strive for it every day
I strive for it every day
Thanks for the 300 bits
Appreciate it. Just trying or doing I don't listen to yoda
Hey noodle is bad at gaming. Thanks for the 250. Hey, what's up? Jeremy? It's your boy. Here's some money
I was wondering did you ever read the bits from the screen that got cut short when your connection did like not like this
Anyway, have a good one. I think so
I think I did come back a few days after that
I know I did
I know I did. I did. Yeah, I did
Catboy, thanks for the 250. Hi, Jeremy. This is my first time cheering. You're a cool
please say
this
um
Is this is uh
I don't want to I don't want to no, I don't want to
It's it's yeah. It's like
Yeah, i'm uh, is it
I'm gonna say it very slow
it's
Yeah, I just said it. Yeah. Yeah
What is it? I don't get it. Just say yeah
It's yeah. Yeah
He did it. He's a cat streamer
Stop doing that now
Don't do that anymore
Spell it n ya
I have to apologize for this too, but I unintentionally did this
I very much intentionally did the eye
One right, but this is unintentional. I didn't I have to apologize that I didn't mean to do
This is worse than the other one
Well, whatever
Hey, silent serenity. Thanks for the 250 furiously moves windows around. I don't know what that means
Cad btv 250 from cad. Hey man, sorry to hear you got hit by a bus
I really hope you recover quickly though. I can't help but think it is your fault for being too short for the bus driver to see you
Get them for me
Untry hard. Thanks for the hundred bits. He fucked it up hundred bits. He fucked it up
But I have to say it. Hey german just want to say ronnie to cancel your yearly 400 dollar surfer monkey membership
Yeah, I know
Hey the pc int just kidding. It's the point. I remember getting corrected last time
Thanks for the 300 bits. They say i'm listening to your stream while doing homework and the music is gorgeous
Hope you're feeling okay
I know stressful and exhausting mris can be when I heard you were doing this
I surprised you even stream today
Hope you got some well-deserved rest soon. By the way, what time were you born?
Nothing creepy laughing my ass off
Hey, when were you born? I'm just laughing my ass off
Uh, no, I just like astrology
I'm like looking into people's charts casually
See what's going on. Oh you guys yeah, you know, I don't actually I don't even know what time I was born
I think it was in the night. I think it was like nine o'clock
9 pm
It's I know it was 9 pm
9 pm or maybe like 9 45. I don't know
Trying to get the star chart
Yeah, but I don't know if I want you to have that information
you know, I don't want you to look up my star chart and it's
Oh, there's gonna be some problems this week for jereby. You're gonna know things that I don't
Someone's gonna get all this info and they're gonna do a full chart and a full
The week coming up and they're gonna give a bit message saying hey, dude, um
Don't play pool
for the next week
Something bad will happen. I'm just like what the fuck dude. I just want to tell you
Don't eat anything green for the next three days. Oh, okay
I guess I guess I
Charts the charts said it
You don't anyways. I have plenty of greens. I love fucking avocados. I love I love shredded
iceberg lettuce
I love shredded iceberg lettuce
Which is 85 percent water and then weird gross fibers and it doesn't do anything. I also like cabbage
No, I don't that's a lie
I like um
Spinach I do love spinach
Shred shredded lettuce
mayonnaise and chicken sandwich
Yeah, I think so. I think so somebody said gross
Don't make me angry
You would love me when i'm angry because the jump king string is one of the top streams i've ever done
So go ahead get angry
I had the highest retention rate per viewer on that stream
Than anything i've ever done before
Also made that one up too. Hey, mr. Dask
Thanks for the thousand bits
Is this enough to cover the guild charter?
I thought I already paid for it
But you kept asking again and again to cough it up or else I couldn't sell my strongest potions around here
Hope this isn't because of my refusal to sell them to you. My strongest potions would kill a dragon let alone a man
Well, that's i'm sorry to hear that
Uh, I did not i have nothing to do with this. Thanks for the thousand bits
Peaceful hailey. Thanks for the 250 peaceful hailey. Hey jeremy. Hope you auto and kimmer well
Hope auto surgery went well in your mri. I'm sure it did
I usually have more to say but I got nothing
Just hope you have there's no music
Just hope you have a good night
Thank you. Peaceful hailey. I know what the video is
if you have
a youtube account
That was created
over the last 10 years
You've seen the video
Does that video have?
How many views does that video have like 600 billion?
Six million. Oh
That was wrong. Okay. All right. We're almost done here. We have uh niece
Thanks for the 500 bits
I want you to use my money to take kim on a romantic date to mcdonald's and only order from the dollar menu
Yeah, do you want to go to mcdonald's?
Like actually right when this is over you want to go mcdonald's? It's five. That's five bucks
You know, you can't you can't scoff at five bucks man five. It's five bucks
I love mcdonald's
I i'd love I do
I would rather eat at mcdonald's than most places because they got the big mac and nobody else has the big mac
The big mac is the best. It's just I love that thing
I get the same order every time I go to mcdonald's
And you're gonna think i'm disgusting
but if i'm hungry
I want to just
eat, you know what i'm saying e a t
Go to mcdonald's and we gotta change the screen
Yeah, this is
Go to mcdonald's to get a number one
And I don't really drink that much. I try not to drink a whole lot of soda. I get a bottle of water
I get a bottle of water number one with a good big fry
That's one
I then
get
I'm i'm this i'm naked right now. This is me being naked. I get uh two mcchickens
For me those are mine
and then
10 piece nugget
That I share with somebody
He this is a troll that is not a troll
So I eat probably like four or five
chicken mcnuggets
I eat the full big mac. I eat the mcchicken
And I eat the second mcchicken
Now that order does not happen every time
Delete the big mac
And I typically will do two mcchickens
And the 10 piece
Yes, it does. No, it doesn't
I got I got a I got a backtrack barry this one. I think
The 10 piece is a waste of money the 20 piece is 50 cents more
He eats this every day
That would be so awful
All right, let's keep going but mcdonald's is great. I mean, I like wendy's
I mean, I don't know if this means anything but the last time I had burger king I got a cold
Does that mean anything?
I don't know. I like burger king, but the last time I ate it. I got a cold
That's just true. That's that's I don't maybe it could be not even correlated but it happened
That's what the star chart said
No, I haven't eaten burger king. All right
Burger king sucks
It like I let's be honest be honest with us and yourself burger king sucks
but
Sometimes you just want it
the long chicken
The original chicken sandwich is I crave that sometimes. I'm just like, you know, I want long chicken. That sounds good
But it's just gross. It just is
And I think they know that too
But i'm not sure they care very much
Because they're still one of the big three they still do
McDonald's is kind of like that too
Long chicken. Yeah, you'll get a long chicken
It's okay burger king has this thing called the original chicken sandwich
If you order a chicken sandwich from burger king
You are ordering
A regular. Oh, yeah, it's a patty. It's our crispy chicken sandwich. It's not the long chicken
They they don't want you to order the long chicken anymore, even though it's better
They want you to order the tender crisp
Patty with bacon and ranch sauce. No, you get the long chicken. It's the only one that's good
burger king
Long chicken
There it is. Thank you
The long chicken
It's this thing
I always feel like if I look up a fast food burger and I save the image to my desktop i'm gonna get a virus
Don't you think that's the easiest fucking way to inject like a trojan in somebody's computer?
seriously
I feel like that's so simple
Like I hope that's not happening
This thing that's the bk long chicken. It's the only thing on the menu worth ordering anymore
Speaking of viruses. Make sure you update your windows 10. Why is there something in the wild right now?
You've never seen that. Yeah, because they they don't want you to order it
But they like hide it on the menu or something. It's like oh no, we don't want you to get there. We want you to get the
tender crisp
Well, we want the chicken zinger burger. What the fuck is this? This is a real what is it? What even is this sandwich?
Chicken royale. All right, let's finish the bits up
I'll be left tomorrow morning
with some wee
Just some normal guy. Thanks for the
2,000-bit donations 20 bucks. Love you jerma. Hopefully you do a you'll do return of the king
I will also i'm sending more bits because I forgot to put a message in the other one
Yes, you will see return of the king on this stream guaranteed
Hey gnarly. Thanks for 250 a few weeks ago. You argued with chad about oil changes and why they're a waste of time to do yourself
Well yesterday, I was reading my micro economics book
And it talked about how while it is cheaper to do an oil change yourself
It is more beneficial to pay someone else to do it because of comparative advantage
Instead of charging your oil or instead of changing your oil for 15 minutes spend that time perfecting your comedy
Because it makes you happier and wealthier. You're my iq. He was right all along
I know
I know. Thanks for the reassurance. Appreciate it ab joe. Thanks for the
5,000 bits a lot of $50 drops over the last few days
Thanks guys
Hello germbo. Good to see you again. Glad your mri went. Okay
So when are you going to rename the channel points to bald coin?
I thought that one was a no-brainer
Much love from one human to another human keep it up. I will thanks for the huge amount of money
Uh buccas bald because crypto was like a thing
You know, it still is by the way, it still is
But that was the big ride up to 20k and it was kind of a thing. It was it was
Bald coins a little outdated. It is a little dated
blueberry juice
Thanks for the 250. Hey germa couldn't catch the lord of the ring stream last week
So i'm super glad I could catch this one
It's a lot of fun
but
You can bet your sweet compact gnome ass
That i'm not gonna miss the rhythm heaven fever stream tomorrow
That game is one of my favorites and I guarantee you will have a great time with it
By the way, do you know the best method of getting pog stains pog stains out of the carpet?
Sorry, the wink made me pog a little more than I was
Oh, yeah, thank you. Um
Throw it away
Hey cad. Thanks for the 250 cad b tv. Look here chump. I'm an old diablo 2 pro
You couldn't last half as long as I couldn't hardcore
Uh, i'm probably gonna lag in the first 10 minutes
And die by a stray arrow
So that's just what happens in that game
Let's get the credits on the screen. I haven't seen these in a while
And they are fast stream is still hovering over 10 000 subs still
almost a full
More than two weeks later. There's still more than 10 000 people subbed to the channel
Which is crazy
Thanks for sticking around. Thanks for subbing much love to all of you
And then let's finish up the bits. We had hill synth for the 500 bits. They say I miss travis germa pluto. We'll go back
We'll do we're gonna do all of them. I'm gonna do two. I'm gonna do travis strikes again
I'm gonna do three
So don't worry. We're gonna we'll do them. There's a lot to do. I'm just busy
Trying to do as much as I can the time that I have
Hey memey. Thanks memey for the 400 bits. Thank you to quarter dime for the 200 bits. He got it wrong again
It's 250 Jeremy, but you gotta read it now
They say the problem with mental health is that people are often mentally unwell to treat their mental illness
It's like if the solution to a broken leg was to travel to the hospital on foot
I think the
the issue is
trying to
Get there before it gets there
It's hard to do
Travis strikes again is interesting for referencing soot as other work, but it's probably the worst no more heroes game
But not terrible, but still yeah
But what I mean is okay, like you said if you have a broken leg and you want to walk to the hospital on foot
Yeah, you would never do that
But it's harder to
It's harder to to not get to that state
With mental illness because it's not something that anybody can see
Right. It's not something that anybody can true. Oh that person. Well, that person has a broken leg. Everybody knows that they can see that
so it's harder to
To do and it can stay
You mentioned broken legs
The broken leg is a broken leg and it has to be treated immediately
immediately
something like
depression or mental health problems
They can stay dormant for a long time and they can slowly build up and over time
Years get worse and worse
And it's trying to find that spot
Where you haven't like you say in quotes like have the broken leg
Over time. It's tricky though
It is very tricky
We had these those 20 community subs
from supper eyes
Thank you supper eyes
A lot of subs. Thank you
How do you guys pronounce co-op juke like that?
Hey, jillette. Thanks jillette for the 250
I've been struggling a lot with addiction and depression and watching your streams and vods helped me a lot for these times
I was having a pretty rough day until I watched today. Thank you for everything
Yeah, it's the same stuff. We were talking about before
same boat
addiction depression anxiety
And same boat but different paddles
You know what I mean? It's they're they're all in the same
realm
And how to treat them?
There's a lot of different ways that people would say is better or worse
but hopefully
You know over time
You can figure it out
the necessary help and the necessary
The support group right because everybody needs it
I'm going to be stealing that analogy. Well
It's free
It's free you can have it
Thank you, jillette
I wish you luck with
Your addiction and your depression
Not something to be taken lightly, of course
Thank you. Good luck. Just some normal guy gave 400 bits
Hey germa the whole talk about mental health made me want to say this with bits to anyone who has any mental problems or know
someone who does
I had a friend long ago
Who did commit suicide and it killed me inside that he didn't talk to me before he did it or said anything
Just know that if you are suffering with mental problems, there's always someone there. You can talk to who loves you
I'm really sorry to hear that the best thing that you really can do if you really think that you have
These kind of terrible thoughts that you do, you know, you do you think to yourself I shouldn't be having these this is
This this is not good. This is not good
You got to reach out to somebody and hopefully that person is somebody that's equipped to help you
Call the hotline of need be call the hotline therapy
And try just day to day to
I mean, it's it's really easy for me to sit here and go well
Just try to make yourself feel better, you know with small things little things
While you try to get the help that you need
Try to find things that make you happy
Not things that make you unhappy
I've talked about it a few times for me
Whenever I feel bad and I felt
I felt pretty bad
over the last
Couple decades, you know, it's everybody can get
Some type of uh, you know feeling down
And not feeling like things are going well, and I think i've made even videos on this
I got happiness and I sought happiness by making other people happy
That's I wanted to make somebody
I want to make somebody else life easier. I want to make somebody else laugh. I want I wanted to watch somebody
Be excited about something
That made me feel good showing somebody something caring about something making
making somebody
part of a conversation and you what do you think about that and see what they say and
That's how I always tried to get myself out of potential ruts that I was in was trying to make other people happy
Because in my mind it's like if I couldn't make myself happy
I could make other people happy
And in return that helped me that made me happy
in sort of a rebound way
same thing with animals, too, I
Like I said previously I worked
I volunteered at an animal shelter and it was just
It made me feel good. It just made it made me feel good
because helping other people or helping other things it actually
It doesn't it doesn't at least it doesn't for me
like what when somebody says something
like when I when i'm done streaming and I look back and look at some of the things people saying in the comments and
The reddit threads and some of the memes and shit that people say
If people say how oh this was that was fun. That was really fun stuff
I had a great fucking time. That was a great stream. I'm just like, all right, that's fucking exactly
That's exactly what i'm looking for
You have to kind of find your own ways to fight
Your own ways to battle it
Everybody's different. Do I read the 4chan threads on you?
No
No, I don't really read that
Not really. I hope I hope people I hope they I hope they like me and if they don't then that's all right
You know saying
I have nothing against anybody that if that's somebody if they do or do not like the things I do
That's all right. Well, i'm not gonna i'm not gonna be like how fucking dare you
Why don't you like me? Well, how could you like it?
People have their own shit. They have their own things. I think are interesting
I've read those threads. No, they like you
Yeah, but it's not everybody though
And like you can't I know that I can't make everybody think that these streams are fun and interesting and I know for a fact
It's getting windy. You guys hear that
that was like
That was big
Um, no, but to finish that thought up
And wherever you probably hanging out on message boards or whatever websites you're on
Thanks for even watching it all even if you don't like it
And if you do then thanks again, because obviously you're still here
We have gone over a couple times
About the whole like oh like fuck the haters
Fuck if you fucking got fuck the haters
I don't care. I don't like I if you don't if you don't like me then
That's fine
I find I find that the visa is
Sort of abrasive with that kind of mentality when you're gonna go on oprah
Can I get on oprah? Will they get me on oprah?
That sounds like a roundabout way saying fuck the haters
No, I re seriously seriously
Go on konan
I've seen some threads in reddit. I've seen some stuff on 4chan. I've seen it when um,
somebody linked me when the
German rumbles were going on the live ones at one point somebody linked me a thread and people were having fun
And that's that's that's all I care about
Go on konan so we can compare heights
All right. Let's finish this up snoozing copter 250 from snoozing copter
Hey, it's really late here. Or should I say early?
It's 8 a.m. Now and i've been up the whole night yesterday. I woke up at 8 30 p.m. Yes, I know
It's been like this for three months now after the jet lag coming back to germany. I've been there before
I have been there before
It can it can fuck with you
I'm finally working on reversing it, but it's really demotivating waking up when the day is already over
Can you say in your cheers to you voice to go to bed with applause in the back?
We want to thank you for staying up with the stream
But it's time to go to bed now
Put your head down
Listen to this music
Get ready
Because here it comes
We want to thank you for being asleep
There you go. You know, i've made comments about what the best video on youtube is
And i'm not sure that one counts
But that's the that's one of the best pieces of media
That's ever been produced. It is that's the one that's the best piece of media
It's the the hog calling. No
Now cheers to you is the single greatest achievement. I think of all of humanity
When you look sleep up in the dictionary
There's your picture
It's there
How many views does that video have? It's it's probably like 32 000 or something, right?
93 000 views. Yeah
And how many of those views are have been us?
Because part two has 14 000 views part one has 100
I know for a fact i've watched this video at least 30 times at least
All right, guys
Apple shift 250. Yo, just want to share that my mom loves when you do tier lists
She always wants to watch with me when you do one
I love tier lists. They're a lot of fun
See you tomorrow at 11 to 12
11 am to 12 pm somewhere in there. We're gonna do rhythm heaven
For the week and then i'm gonna get going after that and then community content night is set for saturday
And then i'm gonna have to talk to joel and see when he has some time probably in the middle of the week next week
See you tomorrow for rhythm heaven bright and early
the final bit of the evening came in from
None other than snoozing
Snoozing copter for 250. Hey there. This is mcdonald's. Here's the mcdonald's. Hey, here is the mcdonald's tech guy
Thank you for the sponsor message that we agreed on
You should be getting the money soon
Oh and make sure not to read this out loud. Just keep it for yourself after the stream
But you should know this yourself. Hope the mixed sunday sponsor message is still on for next week
Don't order ice cream from mcdonald's
Make it yourself
When you can't do that
Why are you even getting hamburgers from mcdonald's make the burgers yourself?
It's so much cheaper and better
Why are you going to mcdonald's idiot?
Well, it's kind of fast. Just excuse me idiot going to mcdonald's what a stupid idiot going to mcdonald's you go to mcdonald's
Uh, gross idiot
Um, I just like going to get fed. So it's just it's fast. It's cheap. It's
It's
All right, the people that say gross you went to get a fast food hamburger
I bet you a dollar
that person
loves
mcdonald's
Hey you you wait, you're going you're going to mcdonald's
Yeah, i'm going to mcdonald's. Okay. Hold on. How many people are in the room?
Is there more than five?
There is there's more than five. Hey, just you I don't even eat fast food anymore. I don't do fast food's disgusting and I don't eat it anymore
Rewind the clock rewind it how many people are in the room?
Two
Oh, yeah, I love big max. They're the best. They're so good. You know with that secret sauce on it. It's it's awesome
Yeah, we should go right now
You're describing a spongebob episode
Well good. I I hope that they make this aware that if you don't have to pretend to not like fast food
You don't have to it's okay. You can eat fast. It's all right. Just don't eat it every day
He's pretending
All right. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Have a good night. Take care of yourselves