Alright, so this game seems pretty cool. I've seen a couple other streamers play this.
Definitely want to check it out at some point. Alright, so we're... I can't... It doesn't
like this controller. No. Press start to continue. Controller disconnected. What? What do you
mean? Oh, I think I turned the Xbox on. God damn it. Yeah, it's trying to turn the...
It's turning the Xbox on again. Give me one second. Let's try this again. Anyways, how
are you all doing? What's today's date anyway? Wednesday. I feel like I haven't known what
actual day it's been for the last week. Did you play any of the Wario World games? I actually
didn't. Alright, what's going on with my controller? Stop it. So this game's about speed running,
right? This is about going really fast and getting a big high score. At least that's
what it looks like. Let's try this again. Sorry about that. Pizza tower. Hmm. I don't
know why it doesn't like this controller. Well, there's that. Start. Did the Xbox app
open? I don't think so. Shouldn't be. Oh, the title. One of the mods would make a good
title. I trust him. Don't worry. Okay. What the fuck? Why do you hate my controller? Hey,
there we go. Alright. How's the audio? Good? Alright. Power status, middle, and then right.
What's the difference? What do the three TVs do? Press right trigger. Oh, it's save files.
Alright, let's go. I'm ready. The art is just so wild. It really is so cool looking. Okay.
Why can't I move? I got art. So jump. It's a run. Okay, welcome. Alright, so where's the
up? Alright, up. Alright, so what do I, what do I do? I can't go through here. This game is cool.
Alright. Press to jump, hold down, and a direction to crawl. You can break marble and metal blocks
underneath you with a body slam. Press down while in the air. Start the body slam from
higher to destroy metal blocks. Jump blocks may be hidden. Keep an eye out for them. Press
to destroy them. Thousand bucks. The game's a little loud. Got you. I got you. That's perfect,
isn't it? Grab dash. Hold dash and jump. Hold right trigger to start a mock run. If you hold
right trigger then jump on a wall, you'll start a wall run. Oh my goodness. Alright. Do that while
wall running to jump off the wall. Keep right trigger held to stick on the other walls. You
can also use the grab dash to start a wall run while in the air. Got it. Is it too low? I got
a Goldilocks. Hold on. Okay. Jump after pressing in order to do a long jump. Run up a slope.
I like that sound. The volume is too medium. Sorry. Okay, hold that to destroy a block. Okay,
yep. Cool. I'm going to puke playing this game. I'm just telling you. Alright. In the air, hold
during a mock run. I think I'm going to puke. In order to destroy metal blocks,
gain speed by doing the mock run. You can hold to go faster. Running down a slope will make you go
faster. Turn while retaining mock run. Press the opposite direction. Okay. Try turning before
falling down a hole. You'll retain your speed. Ah, I see. Is that what my buddy Eric wants?
Your buddy Eric is very well traveled. While at high speed, hold up then release to perform
the super jump. You can also adjust your position with left and right. Ah, okay. So while running.
I get it. How do I get out of this? Oh, I know. Oops. Wait to go through gaps faster. Is that
working? Press that and then down. Oh, there it is. You can grab things with the grab dash and throw
them. Okay. Put these in order to get a better rank. Some can only be acquired during the escape.
Okay. Can't go through these. You need to save most of the dudes in the cages in order to advance
the next floor. They'll give you money to pay Mr. Stick. If you miss too many of them, you'll need
to replay some levels. Alright. Destroy John the pillar in order to open the exit gate. This will
reverse the solid pillar blocks. Pizza time. Ooh, it's smooth. Get out now. My eyes. John Gutter Hall.
Power lobby. Which one should I go in? Poppins, secrets, treasures, power achievements.
All right. I'll just start at the beginning. John gutter. So just go really fast, right? That's all
I know. You're not going fast enough. Cheese. Faster. Go faster. Faster. Am I not going fast
enough? All right. You're going to go too slow. Got it. Super taunt. What's that? I have a D.
How do I get more points quickly? Go faster. I feel like I'm going wicked fucking fast.
Back, back, back. No, no, no. This way. Come on. Do it. Go. I'm going way too slow.
Why can I get in here? Got it. Killing things give you points. Oh my goodness. I got a B.
How much health do you have in this game? Oh, hold on. It's infinite health. Okay. I was like
kind of scared. What do I do with this guy? I jumped over it. Whoa. You have found one secret
out of three. This isn't, I'm not going too slow, right? Okay. Make sure I'm not going too slow.
You're going too fast. Okay. I thought I just blew it. I got it. I got it. I got everything
I needed, right? I got it. So it actually isn't about speed. Now it is. Who's this guy?
Okay. I'm so overwhelmed. All right. I'm going, I'm going, I'm going. I got plenty of time. I'm
fine. Oh shit. Go, go, go, go, go. Hit every wall. You've hurt Pepino 10 times. Why is it saying
that? Go. No, no, no, no, no, no. I got it. Come on. Give me an A. At least an A. I'm not living
till I have an A. Bonus of the door. Just leave. Font at the door. Oh, okay. That was stressful,
but very fun. Oh, I see. I get it. So the idea is you play the same level over and over again
to get like S speed only matters in the escape. Take your time. Okay. Cool. That's fun. All right.
Well, now knowing that I can take my time in the first part, what do you know about this tower?
Who are you? I don't know anything. Can I stop the rap? All right. Cool. I get it. I'm feeling it.
Now I drop down all the screams. Lame. Why was it lame? I see where to go. All right. That's cool.
Woo woo. I don't know how to whistle. Woo woo. Whistling is so weird. No, I can't whistle. I
don't know how. No. Every time I've ever tried to whistle, it's always just never works. I just
don't get it. Something to do with the way that my mouth and my teeth are. Just I can't do it.
I will move my lips to go to do it correctly. Tongue behind bottom teeth, lips together.
Nope. Trust me. I've sat there for hours trying to do it. That's a lie. Who spends hours trying to
whistle? Every single person either can do it or you can't. Nobody sits there for hours going,
Oh, get out of the way. I did. You did. I definitely didn't. The guys with the forks are
annoying. Cheesy. Double jump, double jump and then down thrust. All right. That's pretty sick.
Uh, okay. Once you're going in direction, you can't stop. You're welcome. Oh, it's damn. You
actually do get style points. I got to get down the smash the slam thing. Let's grab then throw.
Is it great? Nope. I'm actually eating pizza right now. Pizza is so good. It really is like
just like the best thing. I can't, I can't think of anybody that's ever denied pizza.
Just something you just don't like you can't deny. It's just, yeah, of course.
Oh, wait, can I get it again? I'll get it. Nice. I go down with it or can I even go down? I don't
know. I'm already at a B. All right. Now that people are telling me you got to go hurry up.
You're going too slow. Faster, faster. I already freaked me out. Oh, I need to go get that guy.
Where is he? Can I take this with me? No, the game feels really fluid though. It's definitely
got the controls are great. Just one of those games. You have to really get down. I don't have
it down yet, but I probably will. Yeah. They're very, very good. I want to, I wanted to get all
those help. Okay. Double jump my lead. No, no, no, I didn't, I missed the points. No,
I'm, I'm doing too well. Jumping over them. I go back slow. Andy. Hey, I'm okay with a B
SpongeBob super taunt up and taunt. Okay. Hold up while taunting. What does it do?
Kill everything on screen. Wait, what about that? Do I get this? Is it all right? Holy shit. The
music. Yeah, this is really, really good. B rank Barry. Not for long. Call me a rank Arnold.
That's a good thing to know. I want that. All right. I got this guy now. Can I now go in that
door? Yes. It's okay. Do it on your way back. I want that sausage. So bad. I get it. Oh my,
right. I can do the big jump. I forgot secrets. Did I miss something? It's a game. I like it.
Oh shit. No, I didn't want to do that. It's all right. You make a mistake. I just downloaded
the game like 20 minutes ago. I swear to God. I just downloaded the game 20 minutes ago. It's
all right. I just got the game 20 minutes ago. Get out of the way. Get out of my way. Get it.
What? What? What? No, I go in. Was that a pasta? I'm so happy that they have that person to come
tell you what to do. What's going on? Stop. Wrong way. Oh my God. Go down. Wait, hold on.
I have 10 seconds. Get under there. Get go. What is he doing? What are you doing? What are you
doing? Why? I couldn't, I couldn't duck. I was, what the fuck was that? What happened? I know as I
crawl, I, I couldn't move. I was trying to do this thing where you like go like this. Oh my God.
I'm fucking pissed off. Oh my God. I'm so annoyed right now. That's, this is what I'm okay.
Let me get this down. You can, okay. You can not. It's an analog controller problem.
All right. So when I use my controller, it's a, it's a controller problem.
When I go down, this is a controller problem. Use D pad. Okay. You just saved the whole rest of the
run. Yeah. Yep. It's actually really hard to do that with the analog for some reason. Why are
you not using the D pad? I don't know because it hurts my hands. Shit. I'm so pissed. The analog
is nice. It's got like a grip on it. The buttons are like, they're like hard. They push on your
fingers. I got it. Now I'm not going to get S. Why would you ever assume you're on D pad?
Yeah, that's so much better. That is actually way easier. He's got arthritis. I mean,
maybe, maybe a little hard to tell sometimes. This dude's 70. Get an Xbox one fight pad.
It has a bigger D pad. I do really like the Xbox controller. I think it's, I like the placement
the best, I think. Out of all the controllers, the Xbox, the, since Xbox one, I want to say
the placement's been the best for me. I prefer the PlayStation analog sticks and the PlayStation
um, trigger buttons, but I like the placement of the Xbox better. He's a real Xbox controller.
Um, I feel like the deep is the D pad worse on the original Xbox,
get the old one. I feel like the 360 one wasn't that great either.
All right. Once you hear, once three gulps happen, just stop moving. Oh, stop. Oh, stop it.
Good. Stop. Okay. That'd be, what's the best way to handle the guys with the forks?
Parry them? Wait, there's a parry? No, wait, that's a parry. Spoiler. You literally asked.
I know I'm messing around. Um, did I miss this? I think I missed one of the secrets
one I got last time. Yeah, I did. That parry is so much better. The secret to the left of the first
Excalibur rat wall. Can I get it on the way back or should I just go for it now?
Now you got everything in here. You can't get it during pizza time.
Okay. I'll go back. Am I going backwards? Yeah. Okay. Um, where is it? Is it right here?
Further back. We're here. Left there. It's a slide. All right. Get over there. Maybe the night
slide from right to left. Oh, yeah. Okay. Let's go. Wait, I didn't get this before. This is new.
Ooh, new friend. Three secrets in each level. Motoring flability in this guy. You got the secret
that's in the room. One or two from this one. Oh, okay. So now I can go here. Yeah. I genuinely did
not understand this game at all because all of, okay, when you, when you watch a game like this,
you have no idea, no context for anything. It's just, I would always catch people screaming this
and they're just sprinting and smashing. And I was like, this game, I don't know if I want to play
this, but now I understand it. That's pretty secret in that room. All right. Well, I'm not going to
get every single secret. You know what I mean? That guy's right there. I'm definitely not going
to get every secret. So I'm sorry if I missed them. I would talk. Yeah. I can't stop. Turn around,
please. Okay. I'm good. Okay. Yeah. I remember this. Cool. Oh, I slowed down. Okay. So that's
two out of three. All right. Don't mess this up at the end. I'm almost at S. Um, how do I,
where's the game progress door? There we go. Pretty much where I was. One more room, right?
Go pizza time. Go, go, go, go, go. Oh, I'm so bad at video games. I don't care. Take it off. Take it
off. I got to let go of right trigger when I get near a wall. Shit. I keep forgetting about Perry.
They haven't taught it to me yet. Oh my God. Oh my God. Guys. Hey, somebody had a pretty good tip.
Let me read it. When you're, when you're sprinting max speed, don't grab enemies. Just run through
them. Even pitchfork guys. Really come to the, what was that? What does it say? So max sprint.
I can run through stuff. All right. Let's check that out. I really like this. This is cool. Okay.
Where's this up? Where's the tutorial? How do I get out of here? Hey, come see me. I didn't,
I was looking, I was reading chat and I didn't see where it said to go. Come to Mr. Stick to rent
a boss gate. Where's that? You know, you could do a flying uppercut. I did know this next floor.
E, A, ah, I think I have to get a certain amount of points, right? Classic cook, the one and only.
Different outfits. Oh, just exploring. Okay. So there's two levels left on this zone. 100 bucks.
They go in here, you know, versus pepper, man. What the fuck? Okay.
All right. This is a small window. They're grabbing the air. Yep. Oh, what? What the fuck is
happening? What do you, what do you go? Got him. Oh shit. No, I didn't. What happened? Jesus.
Got an uppercut, uppercut, uppercut, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up,
I do it quick. No, I can't lose. My hand slipped off. I almost had a first try too. I get it. No,
let's go. Well, that's day forever. Damn it. I didn't want to hit him. I panicked too much when
I, uh, all right, let's go. This game is really fucking good. Like really good. Hey, two more,
two more. There it is. You got new clothes. Yikes. There it is. Get over here. Oh my God,
please don't do not regrow. All right. That was really fun. That was really, really fun.
You get a rating for these. Yeah, I'll take it. Uh, is S no damage? I imagine so. What do I take
this big key? There's another rank after S. Should I open this? I still have two other zones down
there. You and Vinny both got a ranking screen for their level at the exact same time. That's funny.
Yeah, I'm not, uh, this is, I'm not, I'm going back down. So this is a different place. Let's go
here. Yeah. Pink. Cool. Who the hell even made this? Games like this just kind of come out of
nowhere. Sometimes it's like, whoa, this is really cool. I get it. Definitely going up there. Ow.
It's a tower guy. It's been in development for ages. Really? Oh, I'm glad it's getting
attention because this is really cool. I didn't really know that much about it at all. Hey,
combo. Okay. So how, when does it explode? His full legal name is pizza tower guy.
Okay. I just want to see how long it was. You know, there's going to be some weird
shit with that, right? Jesus. I wonder what the speed runs of this game are going to look like.
They're probably ridiculous, right? I want to get it. Um, okay. Um, how do I do this?
What about up there? More points. I want it. Oh, nevermind. What's this guy? Oh, that's how you do
it. Okay. Shit. Come on. Come on. One secret. Start over. Start over. Reach right. Reach right.
Reach right. Did you face game in the TV corner? What? Come on. That didn't, that had to have hit
it, right? The, what the hell? What the hell? Damn. You can cancel your sprint in midair by
attacking backwards. Ooh. Don't slide to this, to a stop on the ground a lot of time. That's way,
that's incredibly helpful. Thank you. Yep. Boom. Rather than see in five minutes when I forget you
told me that and I don't ever do it ever again. My face games in the corner already. Yeah. That's
me. No, go down. I don't know why this is giving me so much trouble. It's giving me a lot of trouble
for some reason. There we go. Whoa. Okay. Uh, I gotta remember where that is. Goodness. Goodness.
Oh my goodness. I love the new hat, man. Oh, thanks. Trying to have a new style. What's the
right way? Did I miss something? Oh, my brain. I'm sorry. His brain.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. I gotta, oh man. Hold on. I need to,
how do I get up there? How do I, how do I get up there? The charge jump. Yeah. It's like,
it's hard to do it from there. I don't have enough. God. Oh my goodness. I was using the
analog. I admit it. I admit it. Oh, shit. Okay. Oh, I'm not even saying anything tonight. Oh,
fuck. Come on. What? What are you doing? Here we go. All right. Let go. I'm not going in that.
Should I go in that? Isn't this guy weirdo? That is like the longest way possible. Where do I have
to go? Go down. Hurry. What am I, what do I do with this? I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
What do I do? I don't understand. I don't know what to do with that. Where, where, where is it?
Other way. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what to do. Where do I throw the bomb?
The left. Why was he pointing at the bomb? Why was he pointing at the bomb?
He's not over yet. He's pointing. I always follow when he's point, point, point, point. I'm like,
oh, I got to go in the middle. He's pointing, pointing, pointing. I'm like, all right,
he's pointing right here. I have to go right here. How do I make this work? How do I decrease it or
increase it? Less dead zone. Save that up. That feels a little better. I can't watch you anymore.
All right. Bye. Thank you. How do I break this? Have a good night or wherever you're going to
sleep or something. Good night. Have a good night. I know it's getting late. You're finding
entrances to secrets and ignoring them. This game is like 500 million miles per hour. I'm going to
miss a lot of shit. Did I miss everything up here? The locked door. I'm just, I'm looking for secrets.
There you go. Okay. So meeting salmon on my cheese pizza right now. Wasn't there something I could,
I could go up with this guy, right? You know what my, my issue with this, with what the game is?
No, not my issue with the game, but my issue playing it. I always, so you, you kind of,
all right, let me, let me try to describe this. When you run, you just run up everything in my
brain. I could like jump up, you know, like, Oh, I got to jump because there's a ledge here,
but you just walk up it. I got to burn that into my brain. Don't jump up edges. Just run.
You'll make it. You only have to jump if you're trying to go up a wall like that.
This game is specifically hard to control until you get used to it at the end on the first floor.
Go get used to it. Don't worry. Oh no, I, it's, it's fucking unbelievable. I can just see why.
Like you gotta, you're going up like a ledge. If it's a hard ledge like this jump, but if it's
a slanted edge, my brain goes, go. All right. Don't go down there yet. Anything else in here?
No extra. Nope. Good night. Have a good night. I get some sleep.
I keep looking over and it's like, Hey, I keep reading. Hey, I'm going to bed. All right. See
you later. Good night. I'm getting at her. All right. Goodbye. Have I responded to a single other
comment in the last like 30 to 40 minutes? All right. Bye. I'm leaving forever. It's like,
all right, goodbye. I'm like, I'm concentrating too much on the game to be like, Oh, let me read
whatever else to everybody's saying. Is there a good way to get up there? Can you get through
there? Like that tight, you can never go up that way unless you do the super jump, right?
Great. Break that. Here we go. All right. Peanut butter. Hell yeah. Oh, I remember this part was
wicked fun. Something about those screams. They're just so, they're just so imagine being the actor
that did that. Back up there. Get that. Hold on. Wait a second. Can I? I can. Okay. Don't blow it
this time. I was going so fast too. What the heck happened? Okay. This, this part's really tricky
because you're going, you have to go so fast and stop. Yes. Yeah. Ah, slow down. So it's all right.
Relax. Relax. Relax. Relax. Relax. You're not relaxing. You're not relaxing. Relax. No,
don't relax. Get into it. Hurry up. Get, stop relaxing. Stop relaxing. All right. Go, go.
Stop relaxing. Idiot. Don't relax. Stop relaxing. So I'm relaxed and I gotta, I gotta not relax.
Hey, what happened? Let's go. That was intense. Are you going to play another game? Um,
probably not. I'm really into this. This is cool. Just stop talking and make guttural noises.
I'll do that for the next level. I mean, come on. We, I gotta fix this first level, right?
There ain't, there's, there's no way I'm going to let walk out of here with a B.
Are you kidding me? Lap two. Chef task for this level is to do it in under two minutes. I don't
know if I'm going to do that. I just don't want to be. Ooh, nice. Easy. Oh, it only activates when
pizza time is on. Okay. Already had a B. 24 hit combo. Um, I feel like there's something over here.
No, start. No, I keep hitting Y. You know what else is doing? It's me too.
I almost hold Y instinctively because of any platform game, especially Mario.
Y is kind of hold it to go faster. My brain's like, yeah, you have to do that.
Probably something back here. It's going so fast. Oh shit. I didn't. Oh, sorry. Where's the door for
this guy? First time viewer. Don't you dare read this. I fucked it up. I'm sorry. I fucked it up.
Just, just go, just leave. You know what I mean? Like I'm, I've ruined, I've ruined it all for you.
Just like, sorry. Let's go. Just go. Oh my God. Doing that. How am I still a B?
B. Oh, no chance. I do this now. Maybe I got to concentrate. God damn it. It's so hard to fit
into those little fucking tiny corridors. See like, yeah, like jump it and you go the other way.
Fuck. God damn it. Oh, no. Oh, I fucking ruined it. Yeah. It's just like fitting and I might,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go. I got it. I got it. No, so hard.
Damn it. This game is really fucking hard, but it's so fun. I keep Super Mario myself too,
when it's just like, okay, here we go. And I, I'm going to run up the thing.
Sprint cancel. I know, but it's like my, it's, you got to lock it in to memory. It's just so hard to
burn it in. Do you want to tell you where secrets are? Um, if I very, very blatantly
miss one that I opened or something, then yeah, but it's okay. I don't need to get them all.
This game reminds me of something and I'm trying to figure out what it is.
And I had similar trouble with that other game too. And I don't remember what it is. It's like,
when you stick to the walls and like, when it, so for, when I jumped, those that have not played
this, I just go up the wall. Yup. I'm not pressing up or anything. It's like a completely different,
way to see what it did. See my brain said jump, because you have to jump over this
super meat point. No, I think you still have to hold the button. I think you played in your
road runner on SNES. Oh my God, dude, you got it right. How did you do that? How did you actually
do that? That's truly unbelievable. Cause I think that's correct. Wow. Yeah. Road runner on SNES.
I remember, and I remember biting my controller at certain parts of that game because like the,
say the control scheme and it was, it was, it was a similar control scheme and this control scheme is
tight. It's very, it's awesome. It's so fluid. Yeah. I had huge teeth marks on my controller,
but where's this guy's door? This guy usually has a room, right? I don't want to activate it
until I go there. Well, and I didn't, this is okay. See, it's because I'm not just,
Oh, see that I'm jumping too early. Come on, Gwen, get, get it together. See, that's what I
should be doing. Come on, Gwen, get it together. How's that not going to pass? Fuck you. Is that
it? Okay. I got a, that's all I care about. I'll never get ass. Didn't do lap two. Bye.
Why is everybody saying bye today? It's like a meme. I don't know about. All right. Bye. See
you later. So I have to do, I got one more area down here, right? You keep, you keep responding
to them. Did that already? That was so fun. Did that one up here, right? Whoa. Oh yes. That's
right. You know that your full name is Pepino spaghetti. That's unfortunate. That's like not
a full name. I feel like if your name is Pepino spaghetti,
I feel like that people will be like, wow, that's a pretty unique name.
Pepino spaghetti. All right. I'm ready. I'm not going to mess it up. Back up some weird shit in
here. Right? Why is this like this? I keep forgetting. Don't do that. Forgetting. There's that
and go that way. Right? Does anybody know what that scream is called? Does anybody know what that is?
That's got a very specific name, doesn't it? All right. Well, I got it. Really?
Tom, it's Mel Blanc. It's Mel Blanc. Really? That's Mel Blanc. What is it? What do you call it?
Mel Blanc scream or Tom and Jerry? Is that, I don't think that's Wilhelm. Yeah, that's not
Wilhelm. Damn it. This is going to be so hard to do this on the way back. I can get in there.
How do I get in there? You're going to get probably from down. Okay. I go like this.
Huh? What? I'm under. Uh, yeah, you're right. You're right. Thank you. Okay.
Did I get everything? I think so. You guys doing a race? What are you guys doing? Why wasn't I
invited? Jesus. I don't have that guy. Harry button. I haven't pressed at all. And I missed it.
All right. Down. Oh, come on. Peppino. Oh, come on. Peppino. Did my microphone go like, oh yeah.
No, Pino. That was a lot cleaner on back. All right. Got a hundred bucks. I can do area two now,
right? I mean, my brain does this thing where like my brain, like it does this sort of thing.
I was, I was poking fun at myself. Okay. So we got this place. What's going on with these two?
Know that you can walk and parry. Yeah. Ooh, this one looks fun. All right. I'm doing this one.
It's like a banyan. How am I doing? I'm doing pretty good. Thanks for asking. Hope you're doing
good too. I love the way this level looks. Good stream. Bye. He keeps reading them. All right. Bye.
Learn to parry at the very beginning. Hollywood edge sound effects library from the cartoon
tracks volume two. The track name is called funny man yells in medium high pitched tone.
Okay. Good to know. Can I go through that way? It's not the Pino's though. It's close,
but it's not right. Really? Hold on. I want to look this up. I'll do it edge.
Dream. I just type it. What's it called? Funny man yells. Is this it? I'm going to turn it down.
It gets really loud. Dude, this is orphan of costs. This is orphan of costs. What the fuck?
No, it's not. That's absolutely orphan of costs. There's no way it's not. Especially this first
one. That's unbelievable. Orphan costs yell. It's definitely it. I can't. All right. I'm going
back to play this game. The coolest thing about finding, thinking, hearing stuff like that,
you wouldn't believe how much, how many video game sounds are just everywhere shared just from
different libraries. Wait, orphan isolated screams. I mean, we're here. We're doing this right now,
just for another minute. Yeah, that's, there's no, it's just filters on it. There's a filter on it
and that's it. I love that. That's so funny. Do that impression. I would blow up my vocal chords.
Yeah, there's a little bit of reverb on it. Okay, let's go. Now add farting to it. No, dude. Come
on. It's one of those moments where, okay, you know, the TF2 door opening sound effect and you
hear it in another game or in a TV show or something and you just, you brain goes,
whoa, whoa, whoa, wait a minute. Somebody's open the spawn door. It was one of those moments.
You're good. I can't even play the game anymore. Now it's over. I can't even play. I can't do that.
Oh, get out of the way. Double jump. Oh, oh, wait, wait, no, this is, this is a good thing. Okay.
Oh shit. Okay. Hold on. All right. I don't want to take it off yet. Look, there's a place over
there. Oh, there's a place over there. Oh, that hurts. I'm going to get destroyed on the run back
part. I haven't strung much together in this one. Hey, I'm staying. Hello. You can stay or leave.
It's up to you. If you want to go, I'll see you later. Or maybe not. If you want to go and
get dinner or food or snack or sleep, it's up to you. Not tell you what to do with your time.
I can rage at what just happened. And hey, time is a precious thing.
So make sure you use it the way you want to. Time is a precious resource.
Who is hitting me? I'm, I've hit, you know, more than 10 times now in like 10 hundred times, dude.
Can you, I didn't know if there's something over there I could do. There's so many secrets in this
game. I'm trying to find them. Are you kidding me? All right. Let's bring something together.
This is hard to do. Shaking my head. Hurry up. Oh, no. Get it together. I'll be all right.
All right. Don't don't don't don't. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This stuff I can do here, right?
No, no. Okay. We're good. No, I don't have the janitor. Sorry. Right. Oh, second lap.
That was kind of, that was a little crap. It's okay though. I'm just topping too. That's kind of
crap. That's terrifying. Holy shit. Oh, I can buy it. Oh, interesting. Is one of these a bar
saloon? Oh, this one's gonna be cool. Make a weird noise. Yeah, sure. Of course I will.
I'm the weird noise guy. That's what I do here. Tell your friends.
I got to parry this. I missed it. You can do it backwards. All right. Cool.
Don't go. What are you doing? What's this thing? Lap two room. Oh, okay. Cool.
Hmm. I thought I went all over the water. Apparently not. Cool. Just got back to the bathroom.
I did. I missed any funny or weird noises or anything. Oh, I'm sorry. I'm under my contract.
I can only do two an hour. So I can't go like, dude. What is the, what do I do about this? Oh,
you lost the race. I didn't know there was a race even going on.
My softlock. Get up there. There we go. I don't understand what's going on here. Um,
it is a little confusing. It's very fast. It's very high, uh, off pain. Is that correct? High
skill. High fast. Very quick. Very speed runnable. Is this a secret right here? I bet I could beat
you in a hair growing competition. Um, you have long hair because you've already won pizza. Oh,
I won. Yikes. No, stop jumping. No, no. I gotta get all the cards, right? Come on.
Can't just not get them. Oh shit. Oh, I got it. All right. That's pretty clean. Pretty clean.
I don't have any complaints. Okay. I didn't screw this all up. Did I?
Hmm. I want that. There you go.
Is music too low? Um, I can turn it. I probably turn it down a little.
That's far better. How's that on the wall? On the wall. Secret in the last room. You mean
we're on the wall, right side or left side? There's like three rooms back. Um, but right here,
right there. As I can get it. Hey, yes, I can. Oh man. I got it. All right. Now I don't want to,
I gotta, I don't blow on it this time. You know what I mean? Don't blow it. I got a,
this is going pretty well. Don't blow it. Oh, I don't even need to do this anymore.
Is that an emote? Hmm. What happened to me? I got, I got a chef. No lap two. I'm not confident
enough to do lap two. On a second run through maybe. I missed one. Oh, you have to beat it
one time anyways. Okay. That's good to know. Do you use money for anything else or is it just
the portals? This is a boss. Let's see it. Vigilante. Is this guy made out of butter?
Gun. I can probably parry those, right? What is going on? Oh, it's hitting. Okay. It's splash
damage. Oh goodness. Fuck. You cannot parry them. Okay. I was under the impression that I could.
You can. Why didn't it work? Really? It looked like I did a parry it. Yeah. Okay. Um, what? Well,
I had to know. I didn't know it was going to be like countdown or something. I didn't think it was,
I didn't want to fault. I thought I was, I didn't, I guess it's a draw, but I thought it was whatever.
I'm going to do a better job anyways. Restart it. Stupid. All right. We're good. What is that?
Hold on. Why can I reload it? It's weird. Let's just do. Oh, it's like a super shot. All right.
Shit. All right. Don't get too fancy with it. No reason to even do that. I jumped over it.
You dumb mother fucker. I'm fine. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
That one doesn't count. We're going to do it a different way. I know it's just itchy. Shut up.
I forgot he could even do that stupid ass move. What? Um, it's awful. I'm going to restart. I
don't care. Change this immediately. Immediately. I can't believe he does it like five fucking six
fucking five fucking six fucking times. What's happening? What's going on? I think that was
better. You have to jump those ones. God damn it. It's no, it's going to be a last try. I'm addicted.
I'm sorry. I just am. How many hits is a so I can know it's going to make me laugh at every time,
dude. Everything spawned at the same time. That was unfortunate. You just went over your contracted
limit of funny noises. Let me read chat and get hurt. Get this shit off. I wouldn't. What a character
am I? Oh my God. It's over, dude. Oh, you, there's no way you didn't die. I shot you a hundred fucking
times again. I need to get hit one less time. So was it two, three? I got screwed there. I got,
I took, I took a hit there that I should never have taken. Oh my God. I was, I didn't have it.
Quiet. I think I lost it again. Dude, when he drops a cow, a cardboard person, that it's just,
it's just, you're going to get hit. I think I got it though. Didn't I? That's definitely a right.
Two hits, three hits. That's gotta be a, is S no damage? That's so hard. That's probably so hard
to do. Let me just, for all you gamers out there, people that are watching wherever you are,
if you're able to just kind of grab this and do it and beat it in, get S on every level and shit,
man, you are, you're just, you're, you're good. You're just, you're eyesight,
your coordination, your, your eyesight in floor three. Oh, we're not done with floor two.
Like your visual, hold on. I'm going to go ahead and talk about something that I've been telling
others who know about this place of worship that you did this. Well, we're down from your pizzeria
and we're down from this tower. There are customers and they want to see one of these things.
So I got a friend. He went down one of these floors and this guy came up next to me.
The idea was, why is that when you're in the upper part of the tower?
There's the pizza face character and then there's this man from your previous life leading the way.
There's a pizza in your tower with all this information. What is this even trying to say?
Talk about these things? What does that even mean? B, eh, it's all right. S rank is one to
two hits. P rank is no hits. It sounds like the clay fighter theme song. Pizza Mark. Why am I so
bad at this game? Bro, I have a rank in almost every level. What are you on about? A means
excellent. No, I'm not going to get P in every level. I'm not going to get S in every single level.
How do you ground pound with it being turned off and down? You don't? Oh, you have to bind it.
So it's not like a button combination. I have to have it on. I thought it would be like down and
X or something. Oh, wait, is it? No. OK. Oh, wait. I had to run and dive. Yeah. Sorry.
Didn't realize that was going to happen. Can I reset it now? Oh, you can bind to buttons. OK,
that's better. Yeah, that's way easier for me. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Um, should it be
a circle left trigger? Maybe. All right. So that's left trigger. That's circle.
I'm going to flip those because that's weird to do that jump and left trigger is better.
All right. Just getting used to it. I have to relearn everything. I have to put it back.
I have to put it back. It's fucking with me. It's been too. You know what? The big mistake
was I spent way too long with it. Not on. That was a change. I should have. I was supposed to
make two and a half hours ago. You only tried it for 10 seconds. Yeah, but I'm in like, I mean,
I'm pretty far into this first part of the game. I feel like this would be a bad place to do it.
I should do it on one of the earlier levels. Do I need to go? I have to be breathing fire,
don't I? Wait, hold on. Why does it keep spawning these? Where did I get the fire? Oh, OK. Well,
what the fuck? I did not know I was supposed to do that. Ten hit combo. Why did it stop?
I should get these down here. Thank you. No, damn it. Didn't mean to press that.
I let me try to go back over here and whatever aliens. Oh, my goodness. I feel like I'm
a human pinball in this game. You just kind of like bounce over everything. Here comes an alien
rant. And by the way, when aliens actually finally fucking land, they're going to take a bite of
pizza. Kidding. All right. I'm going to get my ass kicked on this level. Goodness, I don't know.
Which way? God, am I even going the right direction? I have no idea. I didn't want to go in here.
Not that way. You know, also with this game, too, I think, oh, you when you memorize the level,
which is good luck, I ain't ever going to do that. That's into the crazy routes. This is going to be
C rank, but whatever. Oh, OK. The speed runs for this game are nuts. I'd love to watch them,
but I'd like to beat it first. That's going to make me feel bad if I watch a speed run,
because like while I go like this, oh, that person already beat three levels. So what's left?
Did I do all the third second level? Is there one more? Howdy, welcome to floor two.
Thirty one out of ninety five, eight out of fifty seven, two out of nineteen waste yard.
All right, let's make this one clean, please. It's going to be this is going to be clean.
What the fuck? My God. Whoa. Move through. OK, that's cool. That's the best way to get in there
like that. All right, let's get this right. What does this do? Just go fast. OK. Oh, it's a timer.
I get it. I hope that was all right. What are you doing over there? Where did you come from?
Hurry. Oh, better. Those ghost pepper. Oh, what is the new hottest pepper in the world?
They keep changing it, right? They keep going into science experiments and oh, this is the
Scorpion Ultra HD, like 4K, 1080p pepper. What is it now? They change it every few years.
Carolina Reaper is still the number one. Why? Why?
Here. Get in there. This guy's fucking terrifying. Get away from me. Come on, man.
Oh, fuck. I thought it was a way to go down, but it's not. Holy shit. This game is crap.
Oh, hi. Awesome. Something called Pepper X. Pepper that is most recognized as the
spiciest pepper in the world is known as Pepper X. Pepper X was created by none other than Ed
Curry, the creator of the Carolina Reaper. He created Pepper X by cross breeding various
chili pepper types to create a heat that is hotter than the Carolina Reaper. But if this is true,
why is the Carolina Reaper more famous than Pepper X? That's because Pepper X is yet to be
confirmed as the world's hottest pepper by the Guinness Book of World Records. Of the time being,
Carolina Reaper, yeah, whatever. Pepper X. Oh, I got to tweet out my sponsor tweet for Wild Hearts.
This floor is done? Yeah. Is there anything? Do I want? Yeah, B is okay for me. I'm not really
a gamer. It's okay. It's been a little bit. No, it was supposed to be within like
two days of doing the stream. So it's okay. Vacation Resort. Oh, they're happy now. They're
friends. Holly and I have been playing Wild Hearts and I recorded something that I would like to show
at some point tonight. And I don't even know if it's that funny, but I feel like it was.
It was the hardest. I've laughed in like two or three weeks at some point. How about right now?
I'm going to do it right now. Show it now. I have, I like, I prepared it because I was like,
I probably want to show this. I'll do it in a little bit after this mini golf.
I got it. Nothing. What? These count as hits? No. What? Hey, I got it. Nice. Okay. Cool.
This level is awesome. I like this. Fuck you. Can I aim it differently or can I only just aim
it up or straight? Stop. All right. That's, I don't get that, but it's hard, but whatever.
All right. Two more shots. Shit in my pants. Got it. Go get sucked into it. 15. R15. That's
kind of high. Stop. No, this is actually kind of sucks. What's the speed run on this look like?
I wonder. Can I not get hit by this? That would be fantastic. It wasn't as bad as I thought.
You just run into the ball at top speed. Interesting. How do I go backwards with this?
I wonder if I can. No. I'm kind of scared to do this. I'm going to run into the ball. I'm
just going to do like three hits on it. Stop. I get plenty of time. Suck them up. Yes. Present.
That was nice. Soda course. You know, he made it. Don't bounce back here, please. Thank you.
Appreciate it. Nice toss. Remember Boogerman? I do remember Boogerman. I've been playing it once
and I think I got lost on the first level I think when I was younger and just quit.
I never played it ever again. Backwards. How do I open that? Let's go. 15. All right. Just walk
over there. You'll be good. I think my microwave keeps going off. Yeah, that is kind of a microwave
sound, isn't it? Wait. Oh, hold on. These things are freaking me out. Let me get the right angle
here. What the hell even is this level? I didn't even know that. I didn't know that was a ladder.
All right. Get over there. All right. Stop throwing me. And I know you fucking little shit.
Get over here. 15. Shit. 14. Oh no. He's going all the way back. Thank God. Thank goodness.
Final course. It's pizza time already. It's pizza time already. It is. Uh oh. Where's the,
um, what's, where do I go? Down? Present. I want it. I don't actually have to get this. Do I?
No way, dude. I have to actually get this in. Okay. Oh, get us in there.
Okay. No, no, no. Slow down. Slow down. Slow down. Slow down. Stop. Nope. I don't have the key.
Let's go. Let's go. That one was very, very strange. It was fun though. I got all the
toppings. Good. All right. I need to, yeah, let's do two things here. Let me just,
I need to tweak my sponsor thing. You want to watch this video? All right. Let me give you the
context of this video. Is that, is actually, I don't know. I don't think it's a scripted event.
I think it just kind of happened, but he was just doing it for me for some reason.
I thought it was the funniest thing ever. All right. Let's watch it. It's like a,
it's 10, 15 seconds long. So in the game, just like in obviously like monster hunter and stuff,
the monsters sometimes will be annoyed with each other. And these two monsters like got kind of
in each other's face and they, something very funny happened. I don't know if it happens all
the time, but I'm going to play it. So here you go. So this is me and Holly are playing.
I've been, we've been playing this game off stream. I've been playing it. I think it's fun.
I want to watch it a couple of times, but I want to break it down a little bit
because I think it's funny. So this is a lava gorilla on the right here.
That's the quest was to find the lava back. Okay. Found it. But do you remember that little dolphin
that zoomed in? Cause I want you to be able to see it better. So that little dolphin squirrel from
when me and Vinny were playing it, if this is scripted, it's hilarious. I'm playing,
I'm playing on a series S by the way, if you're wondering where it looks bad,
it doesn't look bad. It just zoomed in and it's on a series S and I'm recording.
I like pulled it from the Xbox, which I think records at who fucking knows probably like
not even 720 P, but all you need to see is this. So these two monsters, they get, here we come.
They're annoyed with each other. He's like, I'm going to spray and then they just kind of sit here
and it's like, okay, what's going to happen here? I guess it gets really, maybe they're going to fight
and then watch what happens. He fucking destroys him. He embarrasses him so much to a point where
he just gets up and leaves. He's like, I'm out of here. The funniest part of this whole clip is
the fact that, so you, you go up, you're yelling at each other's faces, right? You get up on that
little podium, you're ready for a fight and then he looks behind him. He's like, why is he looking
behind him? And then finally he realizes right here. Oh shit. He does this like, oh, it's just
perfect. Why would you turn your back? And then he just grabs him by the tail, he throws him.
It was so sad. Look up this turf war video. I just thought it was really funny. I just wanted to
show it. I don't think it's scripted. I think that the monsters can literally just like Monster Hunter
can walk into each other and attack each other. It's at the level of this. Oh, that's so funny then.
Is it scripted? Well, if it's scripted, it's fucking funny because
he just gets decimated. It's technically scripted. Yeah, but it's still funny. I like it. That's my
video. You're easily amused. I think that's a good thing. How long had the fight been going before
that? They just, there was nothing. They just walked into each other and then he ran away.
We were looking for that monster and they have these paths and that one just happened to be
there. That was the only thing that happened. They found each other and then they ran away.
Okay. I'm going to do one more of it. I said video, one more level and I'm probably going to
call it. I'm kind of hungry. That poor little squirrel. Do the forest level. Is it in here?
I walked into here accidentally. 200. How many floors are there? Five? Cool. All right. Let's
do it. Ooh. Can I make it through that? I wonder, is this going to help me later?
Is there anything else I can do? Oh, I had it. Shit. Read out the pig video. Uh, yep. Hello.
Thank you for the reminder. Gustavo and brick tutorial. I guess we got to do this move faster
and destroy metal blocks. Yeah. Kick the rat. Whoa. The air to do a double jump and cancel out of the
cancel out of it with another move. This is fun. This is cute. Is there anything else that I should
do? Or is that it? I like the kick. I'm trying to read. Leave me alone. Double jump can also
destroy metal blocks underneath while doing the double jump hold while holding in the direction
of a wall. Let's go. That's cool. I like that. So these face blocks, I imagine you probably unlock
it later. And it's like a Metroid, uh, you know, mania thing where you kept to come back and do
it all again, right? No. Oh, wait, it's no, right. They disappear for some reason. I thought maybe
eventually you could open it all. That's right. That's right. Yep. Goodness. That was cool.
Checking for secret. This guy's problem. The delivery. Oh, shit. I got it. Give me those
more toppings. Um, that bounce, right? Hurry. No, come here. You can do it. Smoking.
I said, am I too high to watch this? Um, be careful, man. All right. I feel like I'm getting
close. Right. Right. That the soundtrack might be my favorite part of the whole game. It's just so,
it's very pleasant. I don't know where the door was for this guy. I'm not sure I even saw it yet.
Oh, come on. My delivery. Got to get it. Hurry. No. No. Oh my goodness. Oh, come on. Just go.
Thank goodness. Let's just go. Final delivery too. And does anybody do like a hundred percent
get a hundred percent of the clocks like that would be unbelievably difficult.
Just that's, that's so much stress. Stop bouncing around. Back to that guy. Oh,
just go. I got an A already. Just go sneak down there. What are you doing, man? Nice. Sorry. I'm
not really talking. My brain needs like 1000% power to play this. It's really fun though. I
really like it. Oh, but I have to see what the boss is. We're not done. I need to tweet out that
thing. All right. Okay. Two attempts at the boss and that's it. Two attempts at the boss and I'm
done. You're streaming a stream. You're going to tweet sponsored content at 10 p.m. Pacific.
Uh-oh. Rival Pizzeria. Okay. I'm just, I'm playing like an idiot here. Oh, it's supposed to be the
pizza hut. All right. What was that thing's name? The Noid. Yeah. Don't do that. Did I pick them up?
Okay. You can't pick up the bombs. Just restart. Why not? That doesn't count as an attempt to have
to die. Ow. All right. Base two. Jeez. What's the opportunity? Right there. Jesus. Oh, I thought
that was a little guy. Damn it. Oh, come on, man. All right. One more. One more. That was it. I had
it. He throws the skateboard out. Do your thing. Dick. Dick. Oh, you dick. Okay. Oh, I thought he
was going to go up. Oh, that bait. So annoying. Stop. Fine. I can do that too. I'm going to get an
F. Whatever. I'm going to pass it. It's probably a C. Is the lowest grade a C? He is lower. Okay.
That's a good place to stop, I think. Saves automatically, I imagine, right? Well, I'm
definitely going to finish this game. You will see it again. 100%. This game is really fun.
We're not really talking that much, especially the last like hour or two. I was gaming hard,
but it's really fun. I really like it. All right. So the next time I will be live,
probably one more time this week, maybe on Friday, but after Friday, there's a lot. There's a lot of
work to finish up for grotto piece and then come this next week and have a lot of stuff to share.
All very exciting. I'm really, really excited for it. Hopefully it's, uh, hopefully it's been
worth the wait. I think it has. It looks fucking unbelievable. It looks so fucking cool. I'm really,
really happy with it. And frog detective too. You don't want to miss frog detective. I don't
want to over hype it because obviously that's always not a good thing to do. That's why I don't
talk that much about like events that much sometimes before they happen with maybe one or
two exceptions, but there's a lot of information to share. Keep an eye on the grotto beast Twitter
and then obviously on here too. I'll be talking a lot about it next week. Oh, I need to tweet this
out. All right. I'm tweeting up my sponsor thing. This is the pig video. Thanks for hanging out
those. Thanks for sticking around. Um, that game's awesome. I feel like civilization Sim thing was
fun too, but pizza tower is very, very good. Now, if you don't mind me, I've got a tweet about a pig.
I'll see you guys on Friday. We're going to finish up pizza tower and I imagine probably something
else. Cause I imagine there's probably not more than another two or three hours. We'll see. Uh,
would raid. Is Vinny playing right now? Vinny's probably playing this right now. Let's raid Vinny.
Why not? Thank you again. I was extra sleepy today. I'm gonna wake up. Well, I didn't get very much
sleep last night. I think I slept four hours, which is not very much. I don't recommend it.
Um, but I was ready to game late night last night. I wonder why.
All right guys, take care of yourselves. Take it easy. All right, hold on. I got to tweet this.
10 30 PM. The perfect time for a sponsor tweet. Let's see. Does it look good? All right,
it's going out and there it goes. Let's see if it, let's see if it hits your feed. Did it hit your
feed? Did it hit feeds? Not yet. What's taking it so long? Hey, there it goes. I said, I don't have
Twitter. Yeah. I mean, I only use it every so often. Very cool. Thanks a lot guys. I'll see you Friday.
Have a good night. Get some sleep. You forgot hashtag ad in the tweet. Uh, no, it says sponsored
by EA. That's fine. I think that's okay, right? No, that's good. It says sponsored by EA in it.
Yeah. Good night. See you soon. Oh shit. Yeah. That's raving. Go say hello to Vinny Vinesauce.
Take care of yourselves. Good night.