Hey, what's up? Hey, hey, what's going on guys? How you doing? Hey, hey, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap.
Can you hear me? Is this thing on? Tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, pep, pep, pep. Real voice. Wait, what
happened? I don't know why the GoXLR does this. Did I fix it? Hold on. Can you hear me? I sound
fucked up. I do? That's good. All right. Let me, hold on a second. Why are you linking a clip
of you thinking that I farted on stream once like two years ago or like a year ago or something?
Why even link that? I have never farted on stream. See, a lot of you guys probably don't
understand this, but streamers have direct access to be able to control when you can and cannot hear
them. Most streamers have a button that they can just press and it just mutes the microphone.
Now, I've never farted on stream, but I farted during the stream hundreds of times. I just
mute the microphone and just let it go. You don't even know what happened. You have no idea.
I'm just like, okay, here comes one. Mute. I could sit there for 10 seconds and just fart a burp and
shit and then come back and you did not even know that I left. Guys, I've taken entire phone calls
while muted during cut scene before. Like, oh shit, I gotta make, I gotta make a quick phone call.
Mute. Oh, we're in a cut scene. Who cares? And then right when the cut scene's over, I gotta go,
I gotta go, gotta go. Bye. Whoa, un-mute. Whoa, cool cut scene, guys. I'm sorry. He hates us.
Sorry, I wasn't live yesterday. I'm on a new medicine and the medicine is a very common medicine,
but I got some annoying side effects. It's a stomach medicine and it made me kind of feel like
shit. I started taking it like two days ago. So we're going to take it easy today.
I'll acclimate to the new medicine. This stream's going to be probably pretty short,
maybe a few hours, maybe. I'm just going to chill. And in the recommended channel,
there was a game that was highly recommended. It's a game where you make your own chocolates
and you have your own chocolate company. So that's exactly what we're going to do.
Tomorrow, we're going to play Connect and we're going to play Connect the day after that too.
I mean, how am I going to, am I not going to play Connectibles? I've had that sitting there
for like a year, more than that. I have so much Connect that I, this is like still,
there's probably like 10 plus Connect games to play. When are you going to play Boom Blocks?
I don't, I don't know. Can we go back to the Wii eventually? What about GTA RP? Yeah, I,
I just haven't had time to do it. I haven't had time to like get into it and like apply and sign
up. The, the archeology stream is taken up most of the time and another one, two other streams
actually. We're going to, we're going to go bang, bang, bang, bang with streams here
over the next few months. The archeology stream is going to be a lot of fun. I can't wait.
I can't wait. I don't, I'm not going to, I don't want to talk about it that much because it's like,
you'll see, just March 6th, you'll see, it's going to be fun. And no, there's no Catboy stream.
That's not, Catboy is not one of them. Catboy is not one of them. Why? Well, because I'm not,
I want to get that ready. I'm not just putting the ears on. I'm not putting the ears on and going
like, that's not going to happen. I mean, I probably, I probably will do that as a joke.
That what I just did. No, there's a lot going to just, just wait, just wait and see.
That stream is going to be a lot different than maybe you think it is.
You're going to be a Catboy tryhard. Yeah. Yes. What are you going to do? You're just going to
have to watch. If I, I don't want to tell you what happens on the TV show before the TV show comes
out. I'm not, by the way, I'm not going to be on a TV show. All right. This is, this is, this game
is going to be probably awesome or horrible. It depends on which one. I am hoping that this is,
from the looks of it, we get to design our own chocolates and own lattes. I can't wait. It's
going to be fucking awesome. Do you have a play? Well, that you, that, that word,
that word should be banned in this chat. No. All right. Here we go. We're going to,
this is called chocolatier decadence by design. And apparently there are like four of these.
Is the, my webcam on pointing at me? I hope not. Let's cover it to make sure we're good.
And here at the olive garden, you can get two entrees for only 2.99. It's another olive garden
game. Our soup, salad and breadsticks are talk of the town. Chocolatier decadence by design.
All right. Hell, I thought that was dog food. I was like, how is this chocolate? Is it a can
of dog food? All right. Welcome chocolatier. Welcome to the world of chocolatier. Generations
ago, confectioner Martin Pohlmeister founded the chocolate company that bears his name.
And for over a hundred years, the company has survived family squabbles, hostile competitors,
and economic ups and downs. Just like the olive garden. Today in the twin shadows of the great
depression and world war two, the company's factories have been converted for the war effort
or lie unused. And the disappearance of her husband, Sean has left Alex Tanguy Fletcher
unavailable to steer the company. Can you help them? And what, there was an intro? Okay. Oh yeah.
Flash player is uninstalled. It doesn't exist anymore. Right. Okay. We'll just imagine you
watched it. Oh shit. Can I play this game? Can I play this game? I don't think I can play this game.
This game not going to work. Oh shit. Hold on. Please enter your name. Um, what should my name be?
Oh no. I hope it's not flash. It's it's I probably can't even play this. I probably can't even play
this game. Well, okay. Well, let's find out. Don't be so upset about it yet. All right. My name.
What's a chocolatier name? I don't know. Um, Angus Angus is not to me does not scream chocolatier.
Angus to me screams hamburger. Derma the chocolate boy. That's my name.
Steve. That's a, that's my full name. The last no Angus. No, get off of that meme. For God's sakes.
You're driving us mad. All right. Wonka Angus con zilly zonka, silly wonka, silly, silly,
Willy Wonka. No, that's just Willy Wonka with a silly, silly Willy. I think I kind of like silly
Willy. Silly, silly Willy Wonderful. That sounds like an old WWF character. I feel like that's,
I feel like that's the guy that came up with doink the clown sometimes. Silly Willy Wonderful
was berserker. Silly Willy zonka. I hate that. No, I'm not doing zilly zonka. You can just add a Z
and make it funny. Keep it silly Willy zonka. I hate that. Yes, you can. It does make it funny.
Watch me. Silly Willy zonka. How about silly zonka? Yeah. Silly zonka is better than Willy
Wonka. Okay. Silly zonka. Silly zonka. Silly, silly zonka Wonka. Oh, perfect. That's like a
good like copyright free version. Silly zonka Wonka. I don't care. Oh my God. I thought it
just didn't work. That car was just driving off the road. Did anybody see that? That car was just
skidding out of control. That was like a Homer Simpson car. All right. We're supposed to chill.
Look, look. Calm down. I'm supposed to relax. For most people, World War Two is... Why is this
World War Two? For most people, World War Two is finally over. Not for me. Until my husband Sean
is accounted for. The war rages on. Wait, what? I won't mince words. Silly zonka Wonka. Bow master
confections is in shambles. And I simply can't focus on chocolate right now. I need someone else
to manage the company. Okay. You need to show me you can make chocolates and money.
Once you have made at least $10,000, I'll make you CEO candidate and start introducing you to
the board of directors. That's not very much to be CEO. To make $10,000 for a conglomerate company,
that's not to be the CEO. Oh, it's World War Two. How much is $10,000 in World War Two bucks?
Like in World War Two dollars. Like with inflation and the change of the U.S. dollar
and everything. And the yields, whatever that means. How much was $10,000 now? It's not billions
of dollars. It's probably like 300 grand, maybe 200 grand. $145,000. That's okay. That's a lot
of money. That's a lot of money. All right. So let's get started. Here are 100 sacks each of sugar
and cocoa. Go see Endrid over at Zurich Chocolate Works to turn these ingredients into chocolates.
You're just gonna hand them to me? Hey, Zilly Wonka. I've got 100 bags of sugar in the back
of the truck. Here you are. Here they are. Just dumped them on the ground. Introduce yourself to
Endrid Rost over at Zurich Chocolate Works. Holy shit, these people are fucking crazy.
These cars are freaking. Is this a one-way road? Is this a two-way road? Why are there
cars parked over here? All right, where do I go? Zurich Chocolate Works. Okay, recipes,
inventory, quest log, menu, awards. Oh, Swiss National Bank. Why? Okay, why do they? You buy
my own drugs and I click this. Main Street. Oh, Chocolate Works. I feel for what Alex is going
through. Zilly. Why couldn't I just name my name like Adam? I feel for what Alex is going through,
silly Zonka Wonka. But boy, am I excited to get these machines working again. Click make chocolates
and make at least five cases of basic chocolate bars. Basic chocolate bars. Make at least five
cases. Cases per week. You have 60 seconds to set our production rate. What? Aim and click to fire
ingredients. Match the full tray you see on the right. I'll speed the machine up as you succeed
and slow them down if you miss. Good luck. Why is this a fucking double dare exercise? What do
I have to do? What am I? What am I doing? What's happened? Shoots out the window and like hits a
fucking building next door. You hear like cat scream. Uh oh, wasted ingredient. Use the full
tray on the right as your guide. I'll keep tracking each ingredient you waste up on the right. Waste
eight and I'll be forced to halt production. Okay, there we go. Fuck, I got that wrong. What?
Okay, coming up is next is oh my god. Okay, I don't understand how this works. These are all
wrong. Okay, I have another almond. So the almond has to go over here. What the fuck is happening?
Okay, well I don't that one broke. Do I have to aim it into the slot? I have to just match this,
but I fail. The hit detection is fucking bizarre. What? I don't have any room for this. I got it.
Oh my god. Okay, I got six cases. Oh, what am I doing? As long as you have the needed ingredients
in stock, we'll keep making six cases a week. That's fucking stupid. I didn't know what the
hell I was looking at. Try again. Okay, I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
The things are in the middle. Here we go. All right, snowball, almond. Wait, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. It literally doesn't matter. You just have to aim it at it.
Doesn't matter. Literally does not matter at all. Come on, get it. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Fuck. Wait, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Got it. Got it. Oh god. Oh my god, what do I do? All right, 13 cases. That's good. That's good. That's
good. Oh wait, I thought I heard the fucking Flintstones thing. That means we went out.
I thought we were done. What the fuck is happening? I don't have any more ingredients.
Bill, slow down the production. 15 cases per week. All right. Your basic chocolate bars
look delicious. All products and ingredients appear in your inventory. You can mouse over
items for more information. Okay, 15 chocolate bar cases. 85 almonds and 85 snowballs. Okay,
15 cases in inventory. As you travel, you can track how many products we're making in the status
window below. Inventory levels for each ingredient we're using are shown with color-coded bars. Green
means we've got plenty. Yellow means we're running low, and red means production will soon be stalled.
So we always have to keep the snowballs and the almonds up. Speaking of ingredients, in order to
keep making basic chocolate bars, we'll need more sugar and cocoa soon. You're going to need some
money. Visit Near Deer Dorf Chocolates to turn your chocolates into cash. Welcome, silly Zonka
Wonka. Step inside to review my prices. Why is this a cafeteria? Once inside, click sell all.
I'll take your products and you'll get the cash. This sounds like I'm in the middle of Carr
and sorcery. This is people dumping gold coins on the counter. Here's what I'm willing to pay
for your items. So $85. That's it? 15 cases of chocolate bars? That's fucking horrible.
Oh shit, that's each. Okay, I got $1,200. Thank you for stopping by, silly Zonka Wonka. It is always
my pleasure to offer the best prices for quality chocolates. Now go back and speak with Alex. You
can find her at the Bandhof, the main rail station here in Zurich. Okay, is it hard H or soft H?
Is it Zurich or Zurich? So it's Zurich. Zurich. Okay, so we're making chocolate though.
We're making 15 chocolate bars per week. We have enough ingredients for five weeks.
It is currently July 4th. Wait, we're out in America. Never mind. I'm sorry. We're out in
America. All right, where are we going? The rail station. I was going to say, where's the fireworks?
At the Bandhof. University, Bandhof. Well done, Alex, Adam, whatever. You've made some chocolates
and you've made some money. With the factory now operational, I suspect you'll be needing
ingredients soon. It's time to restock your inventory of cocoa and sugar. I'm going to give
you $5,000. Thank you. Show me you're ready to take over by doubling my investment. Now go see
Verena Zubriggen here at Main Street Market about buying some of what you need. Cacao, for fuck's
sake. Whatever. It's the bean. The chocolate bean. Okay, so we have to go see in Main Street. All
right. Thanks with five grand. Main Street Market. Purchase sugar. Look on the sugar inside. It's all
I have these days and buy enough to make sure that you've got at least 200 sacks on hand.
Look underneath. This is drugs in a bag. You have not yet. Okay, I need this. So how many do I need?
I'm selling sacks of sugar for $7 each. Enter the number of sacks you'd like below and click buy.
Okay, so I have how many do I have? 80? What was it 85? So I need how many sacks do I want?
200 at least 200 sacks on hand. All I can just buy 200. No, how do I delete 115? Where's my sacks?
116? Wait, why? What do you mean why? 117? Look down. Literally says 200. Yeah, I know. But I
already had like 85. I already had like 85 sacks. I didn't use them all. What the you guys just got
in my head. Kakao is only available near the equator. Click map travel to Dulala Cameroon
and see my friend Tom Dongo there. She'll be able to fix you up with the Kakao you need.
Where's my inventory? I fucking told you I had already had like 100. Why is everybody yelling at
me? Well, it's fine. All right, map this menu. Click map to travel to where's map? Oh my god.
Okay. Holy shit. Okay. Travel to Cameroon. Okay, this trip will take one week and cost 420 bucks.
Oh shit. Okay. All right. All right. Right. Right. Now I have to go go to the market.
I feel like they're gonna soar over this mountain. It's like a jump. You've come to the right place
for Kakao silly zilly wonka. Buy enough so that you could got at least 200 sacks. I'm selling sacks
of Kakao for $11 each. How many do I have? I got 200. I should I should probably buy enough.
I'm gonna buy another 100. Okay. Terrific. Now get back to Zurich and see Alex that poor woman.
She truly believes she'll be able to find her husband. You have to admire her spirit though.
Okay. Okay. Look at all this inventory I got. Okay. Travel back. This is a I don't want to run
the money. 117 bucks. Let's go. I think you're starting to get the hang of things silly zilly
wonka which is good because I need to leave soon. Next make your way back over to Main Street
Market. Verena has a new ingredient you can use to make a new recipe. Something that's always
good for business. Word travels fast. I assume you're here to purchase some of my milk which
just arrived. As soon as you have milk, sugar, and Kakao in your inventory visit the factory here in
Zurich to make a new recipe. Milk chocolate bars. How much milk should I have? Should I buy like 100
milks? All right. I'm gonna buy one. Well I don't have that much money. How many milks should I
make? 25? 25 milks. All right. Let's go to the factory. Okay. Here we go. Click change recipes
select milk chocolate bars and make as many as you can. More complicated recipes mean higher
profits. Keep trying until you set production to at least 10 cases. Change recipe. Oh shit. Creations?
You do not currently have any space available in the recipe for your own creations but I can make
my own chocolate. All right. Here we go. Milk chocolate bars. Silky milk chocolate slightly
sweeter than our dark chocolate offerings. Okay. Use this one. Oh god fucking damn it. I hate this.
Hey I don't want to do the fucking revolvers going around. Okay. Whatever. Let's go. Almond. Here.
Almond. Here. Almond. Here. Here. Milk. Snowball. Milk. Milk. Almond. Milk. Milk. Almond. Good. Milk.
Almond. Almond. Snowball. Snowball. Snowball. Almond. Snowball. Milk. Almond. Milk.
Okay we're good. I need I need to stop. Okay I'm good. Fuck. Okay. It's going faster. He's
doing it faster. We need milk. Good. Okay. Milk. Almond. Okay 13 cases a week. It's too I don't
just move. Okay 15 cases a week. Take at least 10 cases of milk chocolate. All right. Cool. Nice
work silly jelly bonka. Take 10 cases of those chocolate milk bars to Liranda Gygax at St.
Peter's Church here in town. I trust you'll find her in quite generous. All right. Okay a low on
milk. I need milk. Milk. Milk. Milk. Milk. Milk. Milk. You need to have at least 10 cases of milk
chocolate bars on hand. Once you do so go see. Yeah I know. As long as I have the ingredients
it'll make it. Way too low on milk. That's not going to happen. Way too low on milk.
How much can I afford? I can't go anywhere though. All right we're good. That's fine. That's fine.
Milk. Milk. Lemonade. Whatever. Okay how many cases do I have? 15 cases in my inventory. This
game's kind of fun. How delightful. I'm going to take 10 cases of your milk chocolate bars and
give you three thousand dollars as well as 200 sacks of caramel in return. I want you to go back
and see Endric Rast. As long as you have caramel sugar and cacao in stock you'll be able to make
chocolate bars with caramel. And I hear that Endric has a new gizmo at the factory that he's
eager to show you. Okay I have enough. Okay let's go. You have on hand everything we need to make
chocolate bars with caramel. Click change recipes like chocolate caramel. Make as many as you can.
Also some good news. I've just wired up a recycler for our machines. If you don't want to use what's
in your gun simply fire the ingredient at the recycler. No more unnecessary waste. Thank you.
Chocolate bars with caramel. Fresh caramel combined with pure dark chocolate. I need sugar. Don't
need milk for this. Use this one. That looks pretty good. My goodness gracious. Say their name.
Say their name. Okay aim and click the fire ingredients. Match the full tray you see in
the right. I'll speed the machine. Yes okay let's do it. And here we go. Okay we're good. Good good
good good good. Okay okay okay okay okay. Here. Here. I'm starting to get the hang of this. Although
I'll never be as fast as you want me to be. I promise. This is as fast as I'll ever be.
I will never be faster than this. I promise. I guarantee you. So many people right now I just
sit watching here going like god his APM is so fucking bad. It doesn't matter. I have to guys
I still have to count on my fingers to get to like 15. Come on fill it up. Fill it up.
Whoops. Shit. All right he slowed it down. It's all right. All right. 17 fucking cases a week.
Yeah I it takes me I have to it takes me time to process info. If I need to like if I need to add
I still count with my fingers. I do and I know a lot of you do too. Very cool. You now know how
to make three chocolate recipes. You can travel buy ingredients and sell your products as a profit.
Once you've built your cash on hand to at least 10 grand Alex will be ready to hand you the reins
of the company. Good luck. Right. All right. Who wants to. What do I got. I have 18 cases of
chocolate bars the caramel. Who likes those. You're well on your way. Silly wonka zonka. I don't. I'm
just gonna say fucking Adam. Hey I'm gonna get it wrong. As long as you got the needed ingredients
in your inventory your factory will crank out chocolates as you travel. I heard that Alex will
be ready to make a move soon as you have 10,000. Oh boy this is over. 449 a case.
It's a grid. All right. I get the factory now. Let's sell it all. Fuck it. How many do I have.
How many do I have. Five cases and 30 cases. All right. Here. I got 30 cases of this shit. Get
look up. Look at this. I'm already at 15. I came back here with extra. All right. Let's do it.
Sell all. Oh well I wanted to check. Silly zonka wonka you've done it. You've shown your prowess
at making chocolates and making money. Now we simply must go. Ready or not the company's in
your hands as I promised you are now the official CEO candidate of Baumeister confections. There are
five other members of the Baumeister conventions board of directors. You're going to need to work
with them each of them one by one to convince them that you are capable of being our CEO.
Some you find easier to work within others but they are all good people. Why are you speaking
like in like second person for me. It's weird. I am off to launch my search for Sean. I'll be in
like why is she reading a novel through my head. I'll be in touch as I can and you should and
you should also keep an eye out on your travels for my assistant Rick Lafontaine. If necessary
the rest of the board and I will be able to get messages to you through Rick. Right now you need
to go see my uncle Felix Baumeister in Cape Town. I think he's the best board member to begin with.
Also I understand that he's been working on some secret projects that may have a significant
impact on our business. I know you can do it silly Zonka Wonka. Good luck. All right we're making
wait is it we're spending 2500 bucks a week. Is that how much I'm making. I'm confused. All right
quest log. You're ready. Talk to Felix. Here we go. 447 bucks. I can't wait. I'm gonna sell the
hell out of this. All right talk to Felix. Where are we? If you're trying to find Felix head over
to Cape Town manufacturing. They sell. Oh my god sell all. About 21 000 dollars. Welcome to South
Africa silly Wonka Zonka. I'm hopeful that you will indeed be able to steer our company through
these rough modern waters. While the war was raging I've been experimenting here with this
old chocolate factory. You see I love chocolate as much as the next guy but my latest passion is
coffee. It's my personal belief that coffee and coffee products represent a new frontier for our
company. I just need a bit more time to iron out the kinks of these coffee machines. You need to
keep expanding your repertoire of chocolate offerings and building up your business while
making coffee. In the meantime would you do something for me? Grab some peanuts from the
market here in Cape Town. Make 20 cases of chocolate bars with peanuts and deliver them
to Florian Amiel at University of Zurich. 20. Okay I can eat. I eat peanuts. I will. Look at
peanuts. Almonds. Holy shit peanuts are so expensive. What does it take to. I don't have
to. Wait haggle. Wait how do I get out? I can't leave? Okay wait there we go. Where are my recipes?
Chocolate bars with peanuts. Okay so it's sugar. There's no milk. That's good. So I just need. I
need like 100 sacks. All right I need 100. No I don't. I need like how many do you want? 10 cases?
20 cases. I need 20. I need 20 cases. 20 sacks. Let's haggle. Haggle. Did you have something to
chat about? Are you joking? These prices are insane. I'm not asking for lots but I want
you to do something about your prices. Is it me or are your prices way out of line compared to
other places? I'm gonna buy from you. I'm just hoping you might be able to help a tad with your
prices. Imagine walking into a place. Is it me or are you. What do you mean is it you? Are you talking
to a bunch of people in the market? Trying to get everybody on board? Is it just me or are these
prices out of line compared to other places? Waiting for someone to be like yeah it is a little
expensive. It is a little expensive isn't it? Got it. Since I'm in such a good mood today I'll cut
you a deal. That's a pretty good deal. Last seen in Cape Town for 86 per sack. Let's, we need,
I should buy a shitload of them then if I got a deal. Should I just buy $15,000 worth of peanuts?
They don't go bad do they? Wait can I just take these and sell them? Ow that hurt. Can I just
take these and sell them in a different like country? Could I immediately get 80 like $5?
Haggle more. Okay you're nuts if you think I'll buy anything at these prices and I like look
around and I like wink at everybody because I'm buying peanuts. He didn't like that okay.
All right all right all right fine fine fine. Okay let's do 50. No I could afford 100.
Let's just, I'll do 100. That's a lot of money. It's a big investment.
Okay bring 20 cases of chocolate bars with peanuts. So we have the ingredients. Anything else I can
do here? Now that you're CEO candidate you'll be able to haggle at shops and markets. Be careful
though. If you say the right thing haggling can result in better prices but you can also insult
merchants and cause their prices to move the wrong way too. All right all right we don't want to
spend too much money. Let's go back. Let's make the chocolate with peanuts and make 100 million
dollars. I can sell these too. Penis is expensive. What are you talking about? All right let's make
let's make a few sales huh? I get 18 cases here. Look at that. Let's do it. Oh fuck I could haggle.
Wait hey hey can I have that back? Give me that back please. I'd like a refund.
Oh you'd like to return? You'd like a refund? Yeah I'd like to. Let's cancel that transaction please.
Hey can we do it again? But I'd love to do business with you. Your prices are ridiculous.
God damn it. All right how do I make the peanuts? This is what they're making right now. Change that
recipe. I want to make peanuts. Chocolate bars with peanuts. Use this one. Good luck. All right I gotta
make this one good. Mr. Green returns. So this is just peanut. Here we go. I'm gonna try to do this
fast. Recycle. Don't. Good good good good good good good good good. He's gonna speed it up on me.
He's speeding up. Fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck. More more more more more more more more.
More more. Oh fuck I keep thinking that's the end. Imagine like a guy in a factory
sitting there screaming that. It's like we can only go so fast. More more more.
More. He's on a PA system too. He's not even he's not even down there. He's up with the glass wall
looking down. That guy's a fucking asshole. Does he know that these machines are automated?
Like which maintaining the machines we're making sure everything works you know.
We can only set it to go at a certain speed. What does he think we're doing?
18 a week. We need more. We need more gas. All right I'm gonna get 18. How many? I need 20k. Ah shit.
Whatever. Enough ingredients for four weeks. He starts like playing like the Pee Wee Herman music
for the PA. And it's like oh this guy this guy doesn't fucking get it. That's gonna come through
really like garbled and shitty. Like this guy's doing the shit like that. Like the fucking
grandfather would do that. You like this song? He leans in to do that. He's the one doing that
with his mouth. Oh doy doy doy. Why? All right I gotta wait. Can I do anything else in the meantime?
I have oh with peanuts. I have eight. That's it? What week is it? What day is it? How many do I have?
I have 18 cases. I need a day to go by. Can I sleep? Talk to the University of Zurich. Oh oh
I have 20? No. Haggle haggle haggle. No I have to give it to somebody else. University of Zurich.
My dear friend Felix Baumeister told me to expect something sweet. Do you have any idea what he might
have been talking about? I have chocolate all over my mouth. An empty container of chocolates.
And I go I don't know what I don't know. Here's a card that he sent you. It's like that's classic
classic like Looney Tunes humor. Sus. It is not it's not even fucking close okay. It's a guy
smiling. It's a guy smiling. It's not even close. I think I need to how do I make time go by? Can I?
Do I just travel somewhere and buy some more stuff? I don't really want to take I don't okay
I don't want to take an airplane to a different continent so a day can go by. Is there can I not
can I? Quest. Yeah I I only have I need my production is 20 a week 18 a week. I need 20.
You have to travel. Oh god. Well where should I go? Make the chocolates again. I guess like make
chocolate. Oh okay yeah let's go. I'm gonna get this fast. I'm gonna go go go go go more come on
more. He's gonna speed it up. Come on come on fuck. I'm so uh holy shit that was loud. I'm sorry I
just fucked it up. Why do I feel like this is a weird part of an IQ test to figure out like how
fast my brain can work or something right? Okay we get 16 cases. He's sucking for his teeth.
18 cases. There it is. I now have 36. I need more peanuts. Let's go to the university.
You've made my day simply zonkawonka. Do you know how hard it was to get a hold of peanuts during
the war? These chocolates are simply delightful. Did I know you didn't give me any money? Do
yourself a favor. Take another 30 cases of these delightful chocolate bars of peanuts
to Duduzail Nikosi in Cape Town. You can find her up on the Table Mountain. I know she'll love
the chocolates and she's usually up on the latest news. How many how many do I have? How many do I
have? Oh I need more. I don't have enough peanuts. You're just this is a front for you smuggling
drugs. Okay I can I can I'm gonna do the chocolate. I can do this again. Fuck. Wait no I don't. I can
make 18 a week. Me flying takes how many weeks? Wait it doesn't take weeks to fly? Yes it does.
Why? This trip will take you spend a week in an airplane teleportation. This is the 1940s. Oh
I yeah that would take a while. It's 1940. Yeah okay I don't know why I figured it was like today.
They had planes. Yeah they had planes but the planes had like I don't know the planes have
the same technology that has the whirly thing on the top of the comedy hat. It's like the same
technology they had. All right where is this? Cape Town. Okay so I should get more chocolate right?
34. Table Mountain. Delicious. Listen I understand that Verena Zubriggen has been stalking all kinds
of new ingredients. I imagine you may just find some new useful things on your next visit. I just
got a tip and I didn't even fucking pay attention. I just that's so much that I just that was like
ten twenty thousand dollars. What did they just say? What did they what did they just say? I just
was staring at that person with my mouth open and they told me something very important that I just
got back on the plane. I wasn't even paying attention. What was it? I wasn't paying attention
either. What did what what did the game just say? Nobody had to have been paying attention to what
the game said. I was tabbed out. What? Tab back in and help. Go to the factory. This the factory here?
Oh oh no it said buy ingredients. Hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait. You're just the person I've been looking for. I
happen to have a glut of sugar. I'm trying to offload. I'd be willing to exchange a thousand
sacks of sugar for a mere 18 cases of chocolate bars with mint. Does that make a deal? Let's make
a deal. Oh I have to buy the mint from you. Oh I see but this is so I have to like just buy mint
from you and come back and and you give me all your sugar. What you meant to say is you have a
glut of mint and you don't care about the sugar because it's so cheap. So you're going to mind
game me into buying a shitload of the expensive herb from you to then think that I'm going to
come back and get a lot of the cheap thing that you don't care about. Well uh do I look like a
fool? He wants 18 cases. Well I think we can make some money with this so I'm going to get 30 cases.
No more than that. Let's make some mint. 50 cases. No enough for two weeks and I'm usually around
18 15 to 18. Let's just say like 40 cases. Okay how much sugar do I have? While I'm here I might
as well get some milk. Last seen 32 to 42 89 to 111. That's no that's expensive. Hazelnuts 152
in Cape Town. So what's going on here? That's good for milk. I'm gonna get 100. No no no no no no no
I'm gonna get fucking 500. Is that too much? 300. Is that too much? 200 is probably 200.
And how much? All right I'm good I'm good I'm good. Let's go back and get the recipe for the mint.
Come back and get a thousand. This is running out. What the hell is this? This is a guy on the plane
sitting next to me. Agiling is tricky but buying low and selling high is the secret to success and
the confections business. Silly zonkawonga. Thank you. Why is that guy like slug-worthing me? Get
out of here. I don't care about you. You're like weird. He's gonna tempt me with something later.
He's gonna be like let me tell you something. How about you sell it to me? Sell the company to me
CEO. All right 18 cases need uh chocolate works. Change the recipe. Mint. Ooh refreshing and
delicious. Pure chocolate infused with fresh mint. I love that. I love that. I don't you want that
right now? All right here we go. How many cases was it? Good. That's a full stack. It's time to
get the hang of this. Stop talking. Come on come on come on come on come on come on. Come on you can
do better than that. You can do better than that. God damn it. Missed. All right that's that's that's
19 cases. As long as you have the needed 21 actually. Ooh okay. Bring 18 cases of chocolate
bars with mint to Gavin in Cape Town. All right I'm running out of materials. Low on mint. Do I have
enough to uh low on mint? Okay I need mint. How much mint do I have? Only 19. I gotta go. Can I get
mint from here? No you've got like oranges and shit. Lemons? Oranges? Sugar. I'm gonna get a
thousand sugar for free. 18 cases I got it. Let's go back there. I'm gonna my production's gonna
halt for a little bit but let's go. One of your factories is stalled. You need to have enough
ingredients on hand to keep the machinery running while you travel so they can continue to produce
chocolates for you to sell. Throw your mouse over the factory status window below to find out where
to buy the ingredients you need. Ooh I got a trophy. Chocolate Historical Society's up and cum
cummer cup. Presented to a budding chocolatier who has arrived with a big splash on the chocolate
making scene. Oh thanks. All right here we go. Horrific these chocolate bars are mint are perfect.
Here are a thousand sacks of sugar and mint is cheaper now. You dick. Because I bought it all.
He's dumped it all on me. Should I make some more mint? I'm going full on. Give me a better deer or
I'm gonna walk away. I am not so easily swayed. Um you simply need to do something for me now or
no no no he didn't like that. Times are tough but they are tough for everyone myself included. If
you're you're nuts. I heard good things about this place. Hey if you don't like the prices you're
welcome to take your business elsewhere. You're joking they're insane. Okay go visit Felix
Baumeister in Cape Town. He has something exciting to share. Oh thanks it's okay he went back to
normal. He needs some evidence of your creative ability. We've been building a secret test kitchen
in Iceland. Far away from the watchful eyes of our competitors. This is where you will have the
chance to invent your own recipes to bring to market. Go to Iceland now. My nephew Teddy will
welcome you. Grab one sack of whatever ingredients you're carrying and I'll explain more. Hold on so
if I keep making this guy angry will it be like five hundred thousand dollars for one sugar? Okay
What do I have? I gotta sell some chocolate bars first of all. Who can I sell to? Here we go only
232. That's it? Nobody likes mint. I need money. No do I need to haggle? Uh I don't mean to tell you
how to run your business but your price is not reasonable. Uh your prices seem very close to
good. Are they totally firm here? I am not really in the mood to haggle. Okay well here just have
just give me some money. I have to go back I gotta go but let me go to like let me go to Zerg.
Fuck I need to buy stuff. I gotta go back to yeah yeah yeah yeah I got back to Zerg.
Oh shit 350. All right let's do it. How many cases do I have? 22. Bingo. All right I need to bring
some ingredients. What do I want to make the factory make? Change recipe. This is uh hazelnut
peanuts. How much how many peanuts do I have? I have 28 sacks of peanuts. I could just do peanuts
for a week while I'm gone. Special reserve. Holy shit this thing has gold pieces in it. Chocolate
honey. Yeah I'm gonna I'm just gonna do the peanuts one because I have peanuts. I need
cocoa. Okay we're gonna do 18 a week. That's enough for one week. I need to what do we got? Market.
Okay I want to bring like an orange or a lemon or something. Your price is completely stable. I don't
mean to tell you how to do your business but is it stable? God damn it I'm so bad at that. I have
caramel. I want these lemons. Previously seen for a hundred dollars in Zerg for a hundred.
Why you why is it 181 dollars now? I'll get a few oranges at market price at market value.
I'm gonna get 10 sacks of oranges. I need more oh let's get some almonds. Yeah oh that's a steal.
That's a steal. 20 okay I'm gonna get 100 sacks. Can you I want one lemon. I know that was stupid.
I know who cares. I they told me to bring ingredients. Why? I just bought one. I just
wanted one because I want to bring one to Iceland. Let's go. Secret test kitchen.
What? This is like a sad. I don't like this. Can we say can we help him? I this is like I don't
that's like a really really making me sad. Save him. I can't. Uncle Felix speaks quite highly of
you silly zonka bonka. We have a sophisticated operation here where you will be able to create
your own recipes. We offer feedback on the marketability of your inventions and you can
name and design your products. I hope it's scrumptious. Once your recipes are entered
into the corporate recipe book you'll be free to manufacture and of course sell your own creations.
With success you'll be given the chance to create more recipes and stay on track to earn the board's
endorsement as CEO. It looks like you have some ingredients we haven't seen before. We'll grab
one sack of each so we'll be available for use in our test kitchens. I can't wait for you to make
the scrumptious chocolate. All right select the ingredients to use from the drawers.
Click taste it and we'll give you some feedback on what you got. All right what we got coffee.
This is the only thing I have oh okay all right taste this all right chocolate chocolate just
triple chocolate without something to sweeten it uh raw cacao has a bitter taste try something
sweeter no only chocolate dairy without a little variety in your recipe you may as well be selling
raw ingredients all right fruits sugar nuts flavors okay how about chocolate double chocolate
with lemon this combination works for me oh next step is design name and describe your creation
dark chocolate double double chocolate with lemon what the fuck i like it when it has the
little slots on it this would be weird it's a lemon bar lemon it's gonna be orange in the middle
oh look at that hold on look at that hold on it's gonna be bright yellow like that this is
like a piece of coal it's just a piece of charcoal oh yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy and
this is gonna be like crunchies no should there be no crunchies on it no crunchies it's just a lemon
bar i love the divots too yep the divots are perfect and that in the middle that's all it's
it's viscous in the middle dark chocolate and lemon name your recipe um lemon uh lemon head
that's already exists uh something something something good something quick something that'll
catch everybody something that people want to buy and eat lemon dark chocolate lemon the urinal bar
midnight lemon now a urinal cake would be like bright pink i will make a urinal cake all right
how about um who keeps pissing by the way somebody keeps peeing into a recipe name
oh lemon sun lemon sour sweet tart dark tart art tart heart tart of the moon description
whatever that's imagine reading that description at the chocolate store it's like holy shit they
prefer that they did that in notepad and they didn't even give a shit but i want to describe
it velvety jock chocolate incompletes a smooth sour lemon tart velvety dark chocolate with a
creamy uh sour lemon center heart of the moon what oh shit okay cool so it's two dark chocolate
cocoa with lemon somebody get this guy to nestle just wait till you see some of my fucking good
for this one wait another one you do not currently have any space available within the
in the recipe book what yeah i want to come inside anyways what do you mean
all right what if it was just milk sugar and aren't okay i just made like orange juice
this is an orange julius how about peanuts mint and cocoa what do you think about that
oh it's classic i mean yuck yeah what about chocolate start over i want more spaces chocolate
no no chocolate no chocolate i want milk sugar and orange yeah like creamsicle that would be
awesome all right well whatever i'm i have my my taste of the moon whatever it's called
all right quest so i i should make my taste of them there he goes he's still okay let's go back to
zirk and i want to make my taste of the moon chocolate bars i need a bunch of cocoa i have
tons of sugar already what we use what you buy this for hello silly zonko waka i'm rick alex's
assistant i'll keep you posted from time to time with messages from alex and the other board
members alex is doing okay she hasn't learned much about shawn but that woman just will not
give up in any event congratulations on the invention of your first recipe make sure somebody
got punched somebody's got punched in the face did you hear that somebody got fucking blasted
it was like a punch sound make sure that you see analise ross in zurek as soon as you are able to
manufacture some of those tarts of the moon she's been known to pay top dollar to the first to be
the first to offer a new recipe at her shop okay you i'm not gonna sell these to you then
i'll be back with my tart of the moon i need cocoa what we got i think i can i think i can make it i
think i can make it let's change recipe creations is my tart of the moon i need lemons oh my god
i don't have any lemons fuck well you have to make something what do i have milk chocolate bars yeah
you have to make something i have to make with caramel just buy the lemons not at
255 dollars a lemon all right we're gonna check on we're gonna see i gotta go get some more cocoa
okay how is this cheap no it's not cheap previously for 11 dollars your prices went up
can we uh whatever i'm just buying it i'm not fucking around i already have almonds oh i can
make almond stuff capital sweets holy shit yeah i'm just gonna sell it all no what about uh here
i heard a rumor that you were considering expanding your offerings to include some
new product lines is that true don't believe everything you read on the internet it's so nice
to see people passionate about sweets again don't you think you're my stop by your dispensary today
your butt tender whatever that is i think i should do all right i got my production's good i'm gonna
head out of here i've got we'll sell the penis ones i'll go from here to here back to zork and
we're gonna buy the fucking lemons it can be a smart move to haggle at market silly zonka wonka
as long as you've got a sense of whom you're haggling within a good idea about his or her
current prices what the bank we recently expanded our operations and are going to be celebrating
our success soon i'm looking for something sweet to serve during the event would you accept an
order from me if you bring 20 cases of chocolate bars with lemon oh i will pay you 15 000 to 750
dollars per case what that's and that's a worst that's like a worse window than comcast used to
have when they used to come out to do like work it will be there between our 12 and 6 okay what
which is an excellent price as i'm sure you will agree will you bring me the chocolates
15 000 but that i i don't even know what that even i don't know what i'm getting out of this
i will pay you 15 000 oh i'll take it all right let's make our secret
leaven let's make our secret leaven recipe here we go i need lemons first oh god damn it
i can't haggle i need to do this i'm doing it i don't care i'm buying at market i did i've
already done here it is tartar the moon let's go this one's easy to do fucking god damn it i got
too overzealous with it but come on it's a full stack shit full stack come on come on come on here
comes the bell the bell the bell the bell here comes the bell oh i got it i got it nice 22 cases
per week there's my 22 cases of my tartar the moon my secret recipe already our little party
is fast approaching how are my 20 cases of chocolate bars with lemon coming along there right here
wrong whatever uh well i have 22 of these now i'm am i out of sugar no no no okay okay all right
all right all right right but she will buy these oh wait a minute you've created your own products
tartar the moon absolutely delicious i sure hope that they appreciate you at that company of yours
i'm gonna give you ten thousand dollars for the first 10 cases uh yeah i'll take another i'll take
another 4300 bucks and i want to take these two another 10 fucking thousand dollars these have got
caramel in them you like caramel don't you another 3400 wipe it out sell all you didn't think i was
gonna be making money business is saved now i can afford lemons from this lady all right i'm going
for a i'm just going for it low on lemons what the fuck are you talking about here we go don't
mess it up i'm this is a good flow come on hurry up this is a good flow come on come on too much
lemons hurry oh go oh look at the speed look at the speed on this one oops it's okay it's fine it's
fine who cares all right all right sorry sorry okay 25 22 23 23 cases let's go all right 20 cases
going in i'll take the 15 000 back up to over 55k awesome we're making strides here be careful
around here is silly zonka wonka not everyone you come across is to be trusted like me oh you
mean like her you selling lemons for 165 dollars each listen silly zonka wonka i'm willing to pay
you in advance all right i'll give you 20 000 right now if you were going to make 32 cases
of chocolate bars with lemon i i would love to 32 cases what i have now all right i need another 17
18 19 17 27 27 28 29 30 31 32 i need 15 more lemons big stack fuck no i'm good i'm good
oh come on dude really god damn it it's confusing sometimes come on full stack good full stack come
on full stack yes what a day what a day at the factory 24 what do i have now 27 i need more
how many lemons do i have eight okay i need more lemons i need more lemons give me more do it again
just wait a week no that was so quick and i got a bad rng bad rng right here this sucks
bad rng horrible rng terrible oh my god come on shit okay was that 25 again he's gaming chat
yeah i was gaming all right 32 cases of chocolate bars of lemon at uh matterhorn at matterhorn where
the hell is he oh okay although these chocolate bars with lemon are all for me from florian amael
he shouldn't have but i'm certainly glad that he did 70k all right and i still have some left over
so we're gonna sell them no we're not no we're gonna go somewhere else all right 70k we have a
quest i am a man of simple tastes silly zonka wonka i have had the pleasure of sampling your
basic chocolate bars and i would like very much to place a large order if i promise to pay you
five thousand dollars i guarantee a better price than you will find anywhere else will you bring
me 40 cases i just want basic chocolate bars for five grand this is a scam i got a fake mustache
scam that's 40 cases how many cases how many that's was it like one to two hundred per case
i can do that on the market no i could get more than that on the market are you willing to take
an order from me i'm willing to pay you twelve thousand dollars for 15 cases of chocolate bars
with almonds i've been hearing rumors that almonds are available again somewhere and i've got a
craving let's go i have almonds i bought them remember yep i bought them specifically to get
ready that's an expensive craving no i just want to i i i'll give you like over ten thousand dollars
if you can give me some chocolate although people have already paid more for less not bad so far
going pretty good so far shit shit going fast too fast it's going too fast it's going too fast
oh my god to slow it down please oh more i'm out of ingredients i'm actually gonna leave that
25 cases a week that's as good as i'm gonna get there it is dang 82 000 dollars nice all right
what do i need i need 25 making tony 25 a week i've got i've enough for a couple weeks all right i've
enough to go back and forth once it's more quests nothing here and i think a strong cup of coffee
can't whatever okay market prices are still absurd they fluctuate yep all right there's
one more quest here on the mountain place in order for 11 cases of chocolate bars with orange
to be delivered to florian amila here at the university i'll give you 12 000 right now
so he sent her like 15 000 dollars worth of chocolate and now she's sending him 12 000
dollars worth of chocolate i mean a simple like thank you note would be good you don't have to do
that are they going to keep just going back and forth i without with with oranges i will 11 oh no
i won't i don't want to lose the 25 a week what if i don't do it you don't lose it i have to change
the recipe though it saves your best oh shit that's cool i with orange use this recipe how many how
much inventory do i have i had nine oranges okay do you sell oranges of course you do and i'm going
to buy them from you you it makes me angry that i have to keep purchasing shit from you but you're
the only person in town all right let's make it a full stack wonderful wonderful stuff wonderful
stuff shit it's okay all right all right come on come on come on come on full stack again nice
i love that feels so good this mini game i this mini game is stupid but i kind of like it for no
reason i hated it initially i hated it a little stupid uh throw it away how many almonds i'm
making almonds uh i guess i'm making them almonds i don't that could have been an orange it's it's
orange on the screen i wasn't paying attention okay well let's change that you you'll buy these
your prices are terrible it looked like oranges change recipe orange use this one go shit full
stack shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit full stack full stack full
stack no full stack give me a full stack i'm so close ah no i'm not gonna get it
slow it down henry i don't know what your name is give me a sorry that's enough 21 cases
on very cool so let's get over here and deliver from ursel for me this gives me hope silly zonka
wonka i'm certainly in your debt all right now what do you want me to do i got a lot of almonds
now all right we're gonna we're gonna travel i need to put something else in the we got i'm gonna
put something just default with caramel okay use this one i need cocoa a lot of it that dude was
sus not everyone's to be trusted all right i'm gonna go to i need to get cocoa we're gonna we're
gonna travel to uh duala please don't go i understand that felix baumeister has finally
got his coffee machines up and running you should make your way to capetown manufacturing
visit him as soon as you're able to it's like toby maguire your prices keep going up
it was 11 then it was 29 and now it's 33 35 okay okay i see you know what i seem to recall
slightly better prices at your competitors you a week ago she knows your business is nothing
without her she wants her cut
it's true i mean it's true she knows that your business is nothing
i'll take 200 this sugar is wow wow i'll take a thousand of them no i'll take i'll take
two thousand i'll take three thousand i'll never have to buy sugar again
baumeister confections i thought i heard that they had converted all their factories to
manufacture munitions for the war effort who now we got a buyer here orange they love oranges in
duala apparently this is 400 dollars a case i'm not selling the almonds maybe i should
previously seen for 164 to 164 now i'm gonna try capetown you do know anything about a secret
test kitchen where baumeister confections is working on developing new recipes do you
you know way too much okay go down to capetown oh i got the rowena baumeister memorial plate
of distinction conferred on those players who have made at least eight different chocolate products
and put 50 cents and a nickel into every half mile there's a machine of these at disney world
wow i think i turned the hand crank well enough i love those things by the way
congrats you piece of shit all right how much are you how much are you willing to pay
oh boy oh boy this is a lot of money we're gonna haggle here you think you could see your way to
offering me a bit more for these products i expected to hear better prices from you my friend
all right let's do it i have 36 cases of this shit oh boy that's a lot of money wow that's so
much we're tapping into the market as high as it's gonna be 208 206 into all just get i'm over
100k hell yeah simply zonkabonka are you excited as i am i've been tinkering with these coffee
machines for eons it's finally time to get them into operation are you willing to make the trip
to hawaii i have a contact there who will supply us with the ingredients we need to make marketable
coffee yeah excellent travel to hawaii and go see hakili palippo at the open air market buy a bunch
of kona coffee cream and sugar for our experiment come back and see me i'll give you some cash for
your trip for the ingredients i don't have to do it i just have money disappearing in my account
i didn't do anything my hands are up just like oh god okay pay kona coffee all right what about
the prices here i mean the these are pretty cheap almonds this guy hates me i'm not gonna haggle
22 lowest it's been is 25 you gotta buy you gotta you gotta strike peanuts no i don't think so
anything else here table mountain yeah buildings is the market anything else here before i leave
all right i'm gonna go to hawaii what i have in my inventory all right there's still plenty
of production going on i got plenty of production with caramel this is a long trip i have enough to
go there and come back 818 dollars haggle for haggle for haggle for mint mint mint what
previously for 80 caramel i mean that's that's not a bad price for it but 80 dollars mint is cheap
mint sucks man with over a hundred and seventeen thousand dollars in bank account scared to
spend eight hundred dollars i mean i'm trying to make money here that's too much that's too much
for mint i'll do 20 no that's too much i'm buying 50 and that's it no no that's four thousand fine
scammed i didn't get scanned i'm fine all right let's go to hawaii 818 bucks two full weeks
oh this is cool all right open air market is it a person you're after kona coffee cream and sugar
expanding into coffee production by any chance hawaii is the best place for you my friend
to show you what i mean i'm going to give you free of charge 75 sacks of kona coffee wow
that is a hot dog i thought it was hot dogs normally you can buy kona coffee directly from
koa ko kawa loa plantation next door everything else you need you will find here in my shop
okay it's a new item cream oh man i got hey your mint is a little high what's your
well whatever i tried oranges wait a minute this is cheap this is cheap we're gonna haggle
please please please give me a better deal please okay i just begged him and i now i'm
gonna buy everything we're gonna buy i'm gonna buy a shitload of oranges now let's buy a thousand
of these i got i haven't i got the cash for it let's go no that's is that too much 500 should
i just go all out and buy like a thousand of each one of these that's so much look at these
hazelnuts they're so cheap here 170 150 to 290 previously seen for i buy more sugar oh the cocoa
holy shit i've i'm dropping my net worth by half but i mean i need it more this is i i have another
thousand stop what do you mean stop no no no no no i you need i need chocolate for almost every
single recipe every single one if i can get it cheap here i'm gonna make that three goddamn
thousand of them in fact no okay okay all right all right all right all right you just gave me
coffee buy the ingredients for a cup of joe and then take it back to felix at cape town
you don't have any sugar oh whoa hold on yeah that's a good price i need sugar i have 29
sugar i have tons of it buy more sugar you literally just bought 3000 sugar yeah but they
were only one dollar more expensive and i got haggled down more sugar i have 5800 sugar and i
there all right i'm done holy shit that's expensive 224 i have 75 in my inventory um
i'm not gonna buy that that's too expensive i have a lot of them already why are you listening to
chat i don't know anything else in hawaii all right i'm ready let's make sure let's go to uh
inventory no we need recipes coffee don't know this recipe yet oh please all right i'm going
back i'm flying back to where we're going cape town two weeks go oh cool this game's cool i like
this game all right what can i sell only 108 oh was it not good here we go silly zonka wonka
we've already received an order for 20 cases of our first coffee product cup of joe he's willing
to share a new coffee recipe in exchange for these coffees i'm going to check out my coffee
machines click to make coffee crank them up oh shit here we go sugar cream in a hot dog bun
use this one make coffee aim and fire ingredients to form rows of at least three ingredients on the
moving conveyor belt wait hold on i gotta i have to have to comprehend this matched ingredients
will fill the coffee making machinery on the right matches of more than three ingredients in
a row will earn bonuses um all right i yeah how is this i don't i'm i need i need to see how it
works wait what's going on oh god wait it's okay so you just you just have to match them up what
come on i get it i get it i gotta give me sugar sugar sugar sugar sugar sugar sugar sugar sugar
all right i get it i get i understand it oh fuck i hate this it's oh okay hot dog hot dog hot dog hot
i need more oh fuck i need 24 cases i'm doing so terribly but i'm getting a lot 27 cases
nice okay low on coffee oh shit you can sell coffee too all right cool so now we have to go back to
zurich i'm i'm almost out of uh caramel i gotta stop making money guys i gotta make some money
silly zonka wonka i keep thinking he's talking about like the tricks rabbit like silly rabbit
tricks are for kids a silly zonka wonka alex would like a word with you she'll be waiting for
you at ayers rock in the secret port of luru please go find her there as soon as you can
wouldn't she like on us what what australia that's gonna be like a million dollars to get there
so you have taken the plunge and begin to manufacture coffee products as i promised
felix in exchange for 20 cases i'd like to give you this recipe for mocha one of my favorite hot
drinks oh this one is cocoa milk and hot dogs nice i can't wait to pick my own custom coffee
we're gonna change this how much are lemons honey it's so expensive still why do you hate me i
really want a coffee now good i'm drinking one right now all right that's worth it holy shit i've
67 cases hey you gotta make some money right bang that's a huge sell right there 36 cases
of this coffee you know what i got a new product here you mother fucker all right well i'm gonna
change this away from caramel we got hazelnut these are probably going to be very expensive
but how many do i have i have 153 almonds i could do almonds i could do oranges out of lemons
this is raspberry nice what about my creation what the hell is this infusions what is all this
all right cool yours sucks play the game with your feet what the fuck are you talking about
i'm gonna do almonds i have a lot of almonds let's use this one i need to get more coffee
take only one week to get to australia i wonder if they like coffee in australia
do they sell me i mean they might sell coffee beans in australia limes oh i want one be careful
around here silly zonka wonka not everyone can be trusted i'm glad to see you again silly zonka
wonka i've not found out much yet but i have good reason to believe that shawn is still alive
the board of directors is most pleased with the market's reaction to your tart of the moon and
we've decided to award you another space in our corporate recipe book excellent test kitchen time
let's go you need to be sure to create new recipes as you awarded spaces in the recipe book this will
be a critical part of proving to the board that you are capable of being our ceo also you will
find wonderful wild limes here at kawaki's limes is the only place in the world where
you can buy limes keep up the great work i hope you have some more news soon there's only place
in the world in the world how do you haggle with somebody that how do you haggle with somebody that
has um the only inventory on earth this is one of my favorite places to buy ingredients as your
no it's not my favorite one of my favorites it's the only favorite because none of them exist
times are tougher they're tough for everyone beg you're charging tourist prices here do something
for me beg i'm not gonna beg no 400 at least i got one what's wrong oh i need coffee fuck i
gotta fly across the whole world to get coffee no i need to go to what was i doing test kitchen
but first damn it she still hates me flat earth you're uh god damn it okay hold on
i'm got got plenty of almonds that's fine didn't somebody i need to do something with somebody
here buy the honey oh this hurts to buy that many i'm seriously this this lady is taking so
much of my money all right test kitchen i got a lot of ingredients to go to the test kitchen with
i've got cream i'm gonna do chocolate cream lime i'm gonna call it the urinal cake he almost said
okay capetown no first i have to get more beans this is the only place in the world i can get
beans i'm going for it silly zonka lonka the board wants to make sure that you keep an ear
out for any opportunities to take ownership of retail locations one benefit you might not know
about is the ability to accept special orders they are a fantastic way to bump up your margins
i had a feeling you were expanding into coffees based on those ingredients you purchased from me
a while back i'd be willing to give you 25 000 if you deliver 75 cases a cup of joe
and 75 cases of mocha here to me what do you say what that's not enough 75 cases oh that's
that's bullshit price went up do i dare haggle with this guy for his fucking hot dog buns
if i get it i'll buy a thousand of them what a marvelous day what a marvelous day well i've
heard my prices are fair don't you you don't agree yeah i'd really like to get my ingredients here
can you help me out at all with the prices yes yes yes yes fine i'm not going to make a dime at
these prices hope you're happy but i will how many can i afford 200 i would get 300 oh my god
that's so much money i can afford it i'm broke but no i'm not i've got 7500 bucks that's a lot
all right do i take the 16 grand or do i not hold them okay all right i got the beans that's what i
wanted but how do i make a mocha mocha is just milk i got tons of it cocoa tons of it all right
i can make a ton of mocha now i'm gonna head back to uh i want to go to the test kitchen
the polar bear is gone looks like yeah some ingredients we haven't seen before we'll grab
one sack of each so it'll be available for yours in our touch kitchen all right coffees so we can
do uh coffee bean right cream and honey what do you think design name and describe your creation
hmm how about lemon lemon coffee flavors mint almonds flavor how about lemon lemon coffee
and call it tart of the sun sun sunshine all right we gotta make a let's go to bars cream lime and
lemon cream lime and lemon bar sprite bar it's sprite where's the chocolate why does it have to
be a chocolate it's just bar make it sprite just the sprite bar wait hold on milk or cream seven
up seven up bar urinal cake yeah does it have to be the sprite urinal cake use cream what about
sugar um it doesn't need it okay i don't so sugar lime and lemon is gonna make just like a lemon
lime bar okay so we have to make this uh like what's the what are the sprite colors what does
the sprite even look like it's white and it's white right white and green i don't know there's
no i don't think there's a there's no design on it green yellow white yeah dude so stupid
it's like i need to be a brighter yellow than that there we go that looks like a urinal cake
yeah that's absolutely a urinal cake okay sprite urinal cake but wait hold on in line thick line
oh no no i think the bottom i think that looks good okay wait i kind of looks like a sponge
okay i like it sponge bar detergent it's a tide pod uh detergent bar like it's a dishwashing
you put it in the dishwasher sprite pod are you sure you want to add this permanently yes lemon
lime and milk what i thought it was supposed to be sugared no i thought that was sugar that's not
sugar lemon lime and milk oh this is gonna be gross no sweetener at all all right get me the
fuck away from lemons i'm i no more lemon-based confections all right well we're gonna previously
seen this is gonna be very expensive by the way okay board of directors wait wait wait wait wait
oh okay no no no all right i got six thousand bucks i need to make it back to okay i have a ton
i have an absolute shit load of these i need to sell coffee to somebody who wants coffee who wants
i can get you to morocco silly zonka wonka where i can assure you you'll find new ingredients and
new contacts to help grow your business are you willing to do something for me in exchange for
safe patches to tangeres uh sure wonderful all you need to do is bring me 10 cases of chocolate
bars with hazelnuts i'll track you down in a few weeks to collect the chocolates and once you've
handed them over i'll make sure that you got your way to get to tangiers all right i need 10 chocolate
hazelnut how we doing oh my god 565 i got 139 cases of coffee this is almost the first six figure
sale of the fucking evening i haggle i could get to like six to seven hundred 139 let's go i'll
take eighty thousand dollars please look at how many cases of this chocolate almonds all right good
good good good good good good very good very good what do you got hey thank you zurich duh
with the 10 community subs i mean we're in we're in zurich thanks to the 10 subs
also hole of one zombie gave five will of d gave five and soda cat tv gave 10 thanks guys
appreciate it okay there goes homer simpson i wonder how alex is farting i don't know why i
said that a cabbage head phd thanks for the 20 community subs all right i got i sold the coffee
i'm good now i need i need hazelnuts do i have hazelnuts i don't have any do you sell hazelnut
here you do for an insane price no sorry no we're going back to zurg i need to make mocha all right
we're gonna go to we're gonna go down here i'm gonna turn this into mocha things are starting
to finally get back to normal after the war i've been seeing new ingredients in stock in markets
all over the world oh cool haggling is tricky but buying low and selling high is a secret
you've successfully invented a new product you've launched our new line of coffees i'm glad to see
how well things are going for the company you need to earn the respect of all the board members
as soon as you've been able to learn and manufacture five coffee recipes as well
as taking over at least one retail location you have my endorsement okay oh one other thing a
florian emil was most pleased with a cup of joe and has placed an order for 75 cases of mocha he's
going to pay fifty thousand dollars um yes yes please mocha i have a lot used this recipe let's
go now i know how this works come on i gotta connect those just get them whatever uh right
here and then here and then right here come i'm trying to put it in there whatever 20 set 30
cases is fine i don't care 30 is actually really good 31 32 holy shit he wants 75 cases that's 32
a week i need more coffee beans it's the cost of travel gone up lately that's not good i can sell
this right now 208 that's pretty good that's pretty good for this chocolate with almond that's the
highest price i've ever seen i'm going for it here we go that's the most money i've ever had
what about regular coffee no i have 565 what do you got i need hazelnuts that's not a bad price
for hazelnuts your prices uh do seem pretty fair but maybe can you offer me a slight discount
no i'm not pushing it i need to make chocolate with hazelnut now we get a p break soon yes not
right this second but you will soon holy shit it's a lot of money ah oh i want to sell it to her
right now no no not not the mocha not the mocha it's a really good price though all right university
i'm pretty sure that i placed an order with phoenix for 75 cases where's my coffee
oh um we're working on it lemons have come down a lot all right lady come on no no no i'm not buying
from you hazelnut i've never made it with hazelnuts i need 10 right shit i'm gonna say i need to like
sit back in my chair to get a better view come on come on i i need come on hurry up
yet too many um too many sugars finally got a stack hey the hazelnuts look the same to me
all right that was not good i'm out of ingredients but it's fine that was bad oh i got the mocha
here we go that's fifty thousand dollars i'm gonna get get get me to a fucking million how much mocha
do i have left i got a lot of mocha left holy shit stop everything stop everything is that gonna
change what if i just sit here and make hazelnut chocolate for like two weeks will it stay there
i'm gonna try it sell now and then make more i could just i could i could do this well
i'm gonna be quiet ah fuck i missed i'm so annoyed by that yes come on i'm getting way
too excited over this by the way there it is this is very exciting to but apparently to me
all right i'm doing it again hurry come on god damn i'm making a lot of mistakes in this one
holy shit that was insane rng look at that rng that was just three in a row holy shit all right
we're good 20 that's my best so far no all right wasn't somebody gonna meet me to buy this from me
i was out of hazelnuts let's just have them produce this and i'll come back and this lady
will buy them for insane prices every time yeah no you don't sell hazelnuts shit all right enough
for two weeks i need more coffee i got a lot of mocha get rid of it now sell it now sell now sell
now sell now sell keep 10 for the quest bona bona i get no no yeah that's right she's gonna track
me down isn't she didn't she say i'm gonna track you down okay almost at a quarter million pretty
good i want to make i want to make my sprite sponges i can't i can make coffee here too
what do what can i make that's not gonna have to worry about for the next few weeks
it's hazelnut it has to be hazelnut or oranges i could do orange just let it run i'm gonna keep
that the hazelnut market is currently crazy right now so we're gonna keep it on hazelnut
all right i'm almost out of uh milk my milk or is that cream what is that i think it's milk all
right i'm gonna go we're gonna take a trip i need to get more coffee anyways i need limes first of
all let's go get a bunch here we go i couldn't be more pleased with these chocolate bars with
hazelnut you will find your way to tangers shortly and i will also give you 5 000 for your troubles
there it is listen since you'll be on your way there soon are you willing to deliver 12 cases
of chocolate bars with orange to gilali abilu there he will pay you handsomely um sure oh
what happened what happened it's the only place you can buy them what happened what
is about a thousand limes is it my imagination or is the cost of travel increased how do i take
look how do i take a location buy more that's too much limes i think all right let's see okay let's
try to haggle because if i can i already got a thousand at that good price if she goes up
it doesn't matter i already got a thousand of them i know that your prices are not set in stone
what a marvelous day i know that your prices are not set in stone i wasn't born yesterday
my prices are reasonable um please please please please get what you pay for give me a better
deal or i walk i was off i don't care i already bought a thousand of them i've just seen if you
were gonna go lower because if you were i would have bought more but i look at the price i already
got them at no returns no refunds you i'm that you can't just add the price retroactively i
already got them bye and by the way hi i never have to come back here again i bought a thousand
of them taryn i need coffee i gotta wait okay i cannot go here without orange chocolate so we're
not going there yet i have to fly to shit okay i need lemons we have to start lemon production
we're going i'm going back to zerg yeah yeah yeah there you go 83 we can now start production
of my sprite lemon lime sponges i've made all that i can make here here we go come on give me
a stack give me a stack come on give me a stack got it okay good give me another stack
uh whatever filthy mouth sound waves 20 is fine all right so this is gonna keep just be punching
my sprite sponges so now doesn't somebody really like to buy new shit who is it it's not you is it
that's all that's worth sell one it's a shitty product okay um i need chocolate bars with orange
i gotta get coffee coffee coffee coffee coffee coffee first coffee first coffee coffee coffee
you literally made a fucking sponge yeah but they don't know that until they eat it
fuck these suck cheap hazelnuts i think yeah and you come down again and you come down again
give me a break okay that's a big break i have to buy a thousand i'm gonna say 500 more than that
i can afford it it's very cheap okay all right all right all right all right all right all right
we're fine we're fine i got a ton of coffee now money's gone it'll come right back when i sell
500 cases of coffee all right now i gotta go back to oh they don't they love coffee here
don't they we're gonna go sell the mocha i have a ton of it i have a ton of it oh my god you all
thought i was not gonna make out like an absolute bandit 534 there's a look at that i'm not fucking
around i'll take the 50 grand i sell the sponges i have to they're terrible whoa cayenne pepper
wait you got it is 1200 bucks for a cayenne pepper what would i chocolate hot pepper chocolate
this is a big investment this is a huge that's a major investment okay we're doing hot hot pepper
chocolate what do you mean scammed what are you talking about this is like an insane item wait
did i was i don't suppose wait that's a lot they're a hot item right now make frank chocolate just
pepper okay what if i just made pepper pepper pepper pepper pepper milk chocolate and just
burn people's mouths wait i see you've expanded operations to include coffee in my opinion the
world's best coffee beans are found in havanah cuba i'd be willing to get you passage to cuba
and hand over a recipe for cafe con leche that uses those beans if you're willing to set aside
some of your first batch from me we've got a deal here's the recipe for cafe con leche oh my god
we've got cuban coffee when you get to havanah track down chena famosa at havanah coffee beans
you can buy the coffee beans you'll need from her okay but i need to all right i don't want
to run out of money i need to bring this person all right we gotta go we gotta we gotta get milk
and then these coffee beans milk who sells do you sell milk here i mean milk whoa whoa and please
report that i'm ready to harvest a new crop of a new crop of cocoa i will sell some of my wonderful
crops to you if you're willing to take an order from me 25 cases of special reserve 66 African
cacao do not worry you'll be well compensated let's go holy shit all right i don't i'm gonna
lose money i'm gonna run out of money i have a bunch of quests i need to get back don't buy
any yet why not all right let me i gotta i have to get this let me slow down back to zerg you got
milk here you do all right that's not a bad price i need money and just get rid of this junk all
right i need talk to felix baumeister at capetown okay orange bars i need to make orange chocolate
bars and then i need to talk to this person in cuba and then make 25 cases of a special reserve
66 we're gonna do that now of course the next week or two so let's start the production on
can i get rid of this nickelodeon gac and just throw it away like i can't how do i delete these
recipes they're horrendous they're awful this thing's this is probably really expensive all
right orange chocolate i have enough to do it let's just make one let's just make it on one more
just always one step behind always one step behind always one step behind all right whatever
he's just like me feels bad man what all right so i need to bring 12 bars how many do i have please
anka wanka alexandra and the other members of the board have noticed how well your creations are
doing in the market and so they have decided to award you another space in the recipe book all
right this one's not going to be fucking gross this one's not going to be disgusting i'm going
to make an um one that actually has flavor it isn't just milk and lemons and limes or just no
sugar or anything i'm going to make a good chocolate a good one at first and pause the game
i'm gonna say break i'm gonna go pee be right back hello so i want to uh just go over something very
quickly if you don't if you didn't wear if you weren't here yesterday i currently am on a new
medication my stomach and i'm getting some side effects very very minor but they're annoying
so i probably i'm probably gonna call it here in the next like 25 minutes or so
i don't want to go too much today just went downstairs and drank some water
i'm just like okay you shat your pants i did not i did not uh but so i um i kind of really like this
game i was gonna do connect tomorrow but i think i'm gonna play this tomorrow too like i kind of
want to get to a million dollars i can save the game yeah okay and don't worry we'll do connect
friday but yeah i just want to as i kind of get used to these this new medication i'm just going
to kind of chill uh i really only planned on going about three-ish hours today so we'll call it here
soon i didn't want to not stream today because i didn't stream yesterday and it was just like oh
okay well i'm just gonna just one week break andy every other week i know seriously uh but i didn't
want to not stream today and i feel fine don't worry this is not like a problem or anything i'm
just currently i have some minor side effects of the medication so break andy let's do this for a
little bit longer i'm very invested in my chocolate company i'm i cannot wait to play this tomorrow
i'm not going to touch it i promise i'm not going to play off stream i i'm going to get the itch
too but i'm not going to uh let's keep going i'm a kind of i'm a kind of can you not see
i mean you can't see uh oh that's why okay kind of snack all right 12 cases of chocolate bars with
orange i just got that now we got i only need to send 12 so i can sell 19 18 76 54 13 12 i can sell
seven okay that's that quest now i need to bring this one 25 cases of special reserve let's do that
right now special reserve use this one all right this one's gonna be very expensive this recipe
should be easy by the way statistically speaking i should be able to do it without having to move
kind of right it's going too fast i'm having trouble aiming more than i am actually the recipe
it's going way too fucking fast slow it down slow it down please they don't want you to get more
than like 25 they really don't more more more okay so i have 25 how much of these are worth
they're worth a lot i can sell one okay quest i've got 25 cases i just have to go to cube i'm
there's a lot of travel going on i need more of those special uh beans i need milk what do you got
a little more another hundred all right i got plenty i got how much coffee do i have all right
more milk i'm gonna go here we're gonna take a quick trip here so i can buy more of these beans
i've been waiting to taste what you have created for my cocoa delightful here's forty thousand
dollars holy shit nice all right all right all right right that was a lot that was for 25 cases
that was so that what a premium that was they were 90 before you can do better than that no
you can't that's not bad we're gonna just constantly have production of this okay we're
gonna let that just run we had a lot of mocha they mocha is pretty popular here i'm gonna sell the
mocha 96 i gotta get a new coffee on the market here i think people are getting sick of me of me
selling the mocha oh shit i can sell this right now i don't think i want to do this right here
no somewhere else these peppers are so expensive all right all right all right all right i got no
almonds this is a good price for an almond just regular cocoa that's a lot all right let's do the
next quest which was we had to drop off this here we haven't been here before okay i had word of
your arrival and your chocolates here's 15 000 oh 15 000 bucks good the new confections what we got
that's new Moroccan coffee three hundred and forty seven dollars what three hundred and forty seven
bucks ah you're killing me this is the good shit i know it is all right i'm gonna go broke if i
don't relax greetings sillies wanka wanka i'm not on the board but i'm indeed a tang guy alexandra
is my younger sister alex suggests that you and i might find it mutually beneficial to work together
to start i have a recipe here that uses your our very own Moroccan coffee i'm willing to hand you
the recipe and pay you ten thousand uh in advance for an order of 40 cases sure new recipe arabian
bold oh shit okay cool maybe i don't maybe i should just say fuck chocolate and make coffee
i look forward to delivery of the products oh this guy likes mocha you love mocha a good price
okay what else can i do at the port what if i told you i was able to offer you a new ingredient to
using your recipes are you willing to bring me just two cases of chocolates if i let you know
about a newly available agree that sounds like scam just two cases of chocolate that's it
well what if i give them just a standard default chocolate okay fine terrific if you head over to
souq market you will find that magdalene gelder is now stocking raspberries use them to make
chocolate bars with raspberry and be sure to come back with the two cases you promised oh shit why
did he have to say that for them to unlock i was already here nice that's expensive but whatever
okay hold on i just saw 80 000 you'd like to keep quite a bit of coffee around for our guests here
at the hotel tangiers willing to pay you a premium 80 000 once you deliver 65 cases of your cup of joe
mocha and arabian bold wait 65 of each cup of joe is cheap to make mocha is cheap to make but
arabian bold that's uses the new beans that's not worth it oh no no deal that's not worth it
i feel bad for this guy he just wants two cases of chocolate with raspberry i could just never
come back here could i just not come back here again all right what else do i got all right cuba
right we're gonna go to we gotta go to cuba let's go vanna all right we got havana coffee beans
you were sent by shopa mudaliar well she has impeccable taste so welcome i raised the finest
coffee beans in the country and my prices are fair now you didn't think miss mudaliar did this all
a favor you'll need to repay her with 24 of your cafe con leche as soon as you can shit i have so
much coffee i don't have enough to do any of this stuff i can do like 40 50 oh it's a casino we got
some great slot machines in here silly zonka wonka but this is an exclusive casino if you'd
be willing to bring me 35 cases of your tart of the moon i could see my way getting you on the
list you got a deal you have absolutely a deal i just have to bring 35 of my gross unsweetened
disgusting chocolates to you my specialty and i get to play in the casino holy fuck i cannot
wait to do this oh allspice black tea that's a lot for black tea what all right 10 and five
too many ingredients i've been hearing silly things about you whatever no i'm holding them
all right i need 35 cases of tart of the moon we'll go do that now i want to get into the casino
i'm not sure if you realize this silly zonka wonka but ingredients do not last forever
but if you are storing an ingredient that you are not using it will expire and disappear from
your inventory over time um how long does it last a thousand limes
the peppers okay i gotta start making stuff i'm not buying any more ingredients i have a
thousand limes we gotta get rid of these i need to make a lime cuban coffee with cayenne pepper
imagine the smell shit okay hold on i need to take care of this first we're gonna sell this this is a
good price i'm not selling the mocha here okay change recipe i need to make uh tart of the moon
okay tart of the moon is being made i have enough okay what about the market
that's a good price for milk heart of the moon okay okay okay all right so i'll have enough
to give that guy i have to fly somewhere what do i what else am i need to do what do we have to do
i need to go to the coffee uh makery and do 24 cases of cafe lon leche we have to change our
coffee first of all we'll go into the test kitchen first though okay coffee i'm going to make a
cuban a all right kona coffee cuban coffee or moroccan coffee a cuban cayenne lime coffee
i don't think customers are going to appreciate fruit in their coffee well they're going to go
bad so we have to use them about cuban cayenne honey this combination works for me
cuban cayenne coffee with a hint of honey in it hazelnut cuban coffee with a hint of honey why
okay cuban coffee cayenne pepper and cream that's okay but no about just plain old sugar no honey
i like this yeah this is this is that i think this is going to be delicious don't put coconut in it
why would i put coconut in this go oh shit okay here we go this is cuban cayenne honey at base
is going to be a dark cream a nice dark cuban coffee color like that with the richness falling
to the bottom of the glass should it be the tv static yeah i want the richness falling to the
bottom this is the beer you send back at the bar because the pour was horrible right there perfect
i want that to this is cayenne remember this is cayenne pepper like that look at that perfect
the whipped cream on this is honey on this wait this is the top yeah this is honey oh
okay there's the honey and this has to be kind of this has to be like red too
oh that looks spicy look at that that looks pretty sick to me that's cayenne pepper flakes
sprinkled on top of the cuban coffee with a drizzle of honey on top to negate some of the
harshness of the cayenne peppers i gotta give it a cool name i can't whatever it's not blood it's
cayenne pepper flakes hey grow up hey grow up how does that sound grow up okay it's called
a what how about a uh cleaner clock cleaner the clock cleaner the cuban clock cleaner
this shit cleans your clock when you take a sip wait you've never heard that term before
like you're gonna get you're gonna get your clock cleaned it means you're gonna get like
knocked over like knocked out cleaning some cleaning your clock wait am i making this up
let me look it up cleaning someone's clock what does it mean give someone a beating defeat or
surpass someone decide yeah it means you're getting like the shit kicked out of you cleaning
you're getting your clock clean the cuban clock cleaner why can i not have a longer description
i want to make like a stupid just dumb marketing thing red it's red it's red red red what it's cayenne
pepper say it 10 times that looks good to me the cuban clock cleaner okay for a second i thought
i didn't put the cuban beans in it i can't wait to make this this thing this look at how expensive
this ingredient this is a delicacy this is gonna go for like fucking five grand a pop let's go back
to capetown here we go manufacturing i'm very pleased with the way things are going i hope you
are as well i understand that lynn lyanna has a coffee recipe that may be quite valuable for us
i also know that he's a fan of special reserve 66 would you take 34 cases yeah all right get
this out of here we're making our new recipe our cuban clock cleaner go make it the question
is who is making who's buying cases of pre-made coffee shit oh my god i fucked that up oh my god
it's this is actually hard to aim by the way it's really annoying come on hurry hurry hurry there's
a big one right here oh my god it's so annoying to aim this lag on the cursor it's weird okay wait
how am i low on everything i have 34 of these all right where's my cuban coffee all right i need
more cuban coffee more peppers and more honey all the doubters i'd like you all to take one step
back and realize that i'm about this is like literally i'm gonna make more money that i've
ever made in my entire life in one second here it comes that's 134,000 that's six figure sale
right there i said 5k that's close enough and we're gonna hold on to this i gotta come load
this shit up with supplies we're gonna go to duala i need honey and cuban coffee let's go
that's look at how good that thing is i'll get i might get to a million before i turn the stream
off back to havano say cuban clock cleaner five times fast cuban clock cleaner cuban clock cleaner
cuban clock cleaner cuban clock cleaner cuban clock cleaner cuban clock cleaner cuban clock
cleaner cuban clock cleaner cuban clock cleaner cuban clock cleaner i win inflation is upon us
surely it seems like every few months it costs more to get from one port to another those beans
oh you know you heard about my secret drink didn't you yeah i need a lot of these this is
this is gonna be very expensive but you gotta spend money to make money i need cayenne peppers
here we go you've honored your end of the deal i'll be honored mine you are welcome to gamble here
feel lucky would you like to try a traditional slot machine or play hide and seek for money
come on bean what i win what i win i didn't see what i won broke even all right i'm taking
this down to 70 70 000 coin broke even again uh huh i don't where's the line here i don't know
how this works this is not a winning spin come on 25 000 25 000 25 000 again more coins all right one
more that's it last one all right get up i want to let's play hide and seek raise or lower your
bet and press start the more you wager the more i'll place in these boxes open boxes and stop at
any time to keep the money you've uncovered but uncover a whammy and i'll keep it all
there's more than a hundred thousand dollars in these boxes okay what i put in 20 oh fuck you
there's only three of them oh my god get up this is going for 4 000 it's all right i made it all
back immediately holy shit okay just keep making these just keep making these quick buy ingredients
and get the fuck over there i need peppers peppers and honey how much is this honey going for
yeah i have to pay the premium on it because i need to make i have to pay the premium
pay the premium i need peppers we're going i have to pay the premium they're worth so much
i got beans should i get more beans oh yeah yes of course not that many 50 more okay and some
more honey no yeah all right i need peppers where the peppers in duala silly zonka how do you like
to make it easy 60 000 i'm gonna be doing some work in dwell for the next couple of months i'd
be staying at the bohan joe hotel if you show up before i leave with 60 cases of mocha i'll pay
you the outrageous sum of 60 000 yeah i think i already have that holy shit i had it in my
inventory all right peppers they're very expensive but it's worth it i have to buy this i'm not gonna
be able to have enough money to travel 50 i can do 60 cases okay here we go holy shit people they
you want these these tart of the moon these things suck and the mogas gonna go for a lot too here
yeah sell it all all right now we just i'm gonna bank money we're gonna go back to all right
they're worse they're not as bad as the sprite they're not as bad as the sprite that's true
i go to markets whatever all right back to zerk i need a new chocolate here i'm not making any
chocolates oh given to you for successfully marketing three of your own creations all right
price is coming down a little but i gotta capitalize what do you got here i got plenty of
honey i got i got enough to make i got enough for the last next two weeks angle not yet i gotta
change the chocolate that's in here what do i have a lot of i need lime the chocolate bars with lime
this is mint this is reserve somebody really wants reserve don't they somebody wants reserves
okay reserves are being made okay i need 34 cases of special reserve wait okay who who wanted these
the most it was 4500 where because i'm gonna have a bunch right now is it dwella that had
that was just paying insane was it havana it's cuba okay right go oh shit oh man oh man oh man oh
man this 300 000 it was worth it absolutely worth it i have enough for next week too all right that's
it that's enough all right i'm done i'm done i'm done how much did i spend how much did i lose
you had to go in and do a casino and just taking 300 000 into the casino and put like just having
going to a table and putting a 60 000 bet going okay okay okay and then you don't lose you
you go you break like even you lose a little bit and you go okay i'm done you just fucking
run out of the casino like what are you doing i should sell this yeah i'm gonna that's chocolate
business baby okay i am going to go okay i'm gonna save it here i'm gonna call it here
this will pick it we'll pick this up tomorrow we'll pick this up tomorrow i will stream for
longer tomorrow i don't want to my stomach is kind of being weird i'm getting used to
some side effects and i'm getting very excited we will pick this up tomorrow and i'm gonna i'm
gonna make sure i have some some stuff in my stomach i'll eat something and i'll be able to
sit here for much longer i didn't want to not stream today though this i'm very excited about
this i can't i'm we're playing this tomorrow we haven't even look at we haven't scratched the
surface look at this these infusions i can make truffles this exotic stuff yeah i think i think
this is a whole nother stream where the things to play i can't wait to play this we're getting
over a million we're getting over 10 million but thank you for watching everybody sorry this is a
short one but we'll be there i'll be around tomorrow i'm very excited about this game hopefully
i can just save it right make sure you get healed up i think it is just ready yeah i think it's just
save the game save is in the menu main menu save and quit okay there it is change player right
okay save and quit is right here all right guys let's uh get the credits on here there was a
shitload of community subs thank you everybody see you tomorrow it's from 2009 yeah that's true
i'll see you guys tomorrow good night goodbye hold on okay uh my whole screen just turned off
yeah i'll see you guys tomorrow and then on friday we're gonna do connect i'm assuming that i'll be
okay by then just need to get used to this new medication on the tummy i'll invite you to tf2
tomorrow well i will i will not be playing tf2 tomorrow he's just farting he's muting and farting
he's muting and farting and muting and farting he doesn't deny it no you know what i'll tell
you the truth you want to know the truth i have never not one time farted during a stream it's
never happened well i never farted while i was sitting here streaming i'm sure i have many times
when i take a break i leave the door i close the door the mic is muted and i just i'm like
i have to i think i have to so i've never done it sitting here though where's the pokemon clip
yeah the pokemon clip is not real it's it's a weird movement that i did or something i didn't
why would i have like i would have laughed guys i would have told you if i farted i would have
told you right that's what everybody says i wouldn't even care i would have laughed and
told you if i farted i don't even i don't care all right thank you for the subs everybody seriously
it's an insane amount of people thanks a lot as always and uh i will see you guys tomorrow
have a wonderful rest of your evening good night goodbye take care of yourselves