I don't know that was fucked up. I was having problems. My internet's fine. Must be maintenance.
This is Dread X. We're just gonna play Dread X because Steam still doesn't fucking work.
An hour and 20 minutes later. So we're gonna just do Dread X. Having fun. Finally, finally.
I still can't get it to download a game. Try the Steam stuff tomorrow. Is it gonna be will it be
live tomorrow? Okay, we have till the 20th. Alright. Hey guys, welcome to the stream. Uh,
pretend the last one didn't happen. I didn't stream today. I'm very late. It's five o'clock.
I'm just starting right now. Very. I'm starting right now. Dread X. This is a bunch of horror
games. It's gonna be scary. So I'm gonna suggest you. I don't care. Let's go. I'm gonna start with
Car Thank. Oh, okay. I was like, what happened? This is the first one. This is Dread X collection
one. Here we go. How's the volume? Good. Car Thank. Press enter to continue. What the fuck is
happening? I fucking hate computers. Your mission is to investigate the ruins of the ancient
Dalvik Kate civilization. But something about things there. Explore the temple and reassemble
the mummy. Is that the map? I ain't gonna be able to do this. This map is fucking crazy.
Turn your lights off. It's it's light out right now. Doesn't matter. Actually. Yeah, I do. That's
a good idea. I can see better. And I look I look a little bit more orange. Why did that make it
worse? Okay. Explore and reassemble the mummy. This looks weird. It looks like I'm being interviewed.
And I don't want my identity to be known. This is not gonna work. Okay, so we take it. Okay,
got a picture. Can I save it or something? What the hell was that? I already did this joke.
You're like a 16 year old streaming in his dark room. Oh my fucking god. There. Now it's a little
it's creepy, right? Okay, so what am I to explore and put the mummy together? Nice ring light. Yeah,
I know. It's fucking annoying. Anything there? Turn around nerd. Let me turn around. It's kind
of okay playing a dark scary game during the daytime is impossible unless you put curtains
up across your entire house. I can't like that's like glare on my fucking screen. I can't even see
what's going on. All right, I gotta put the mummy was with the mummy was the thing I took a picture
of before. I mean, this looks like a place where a mummy goes, right? What do I do with this?
Open it. How space click block the window with a piece of cardboard. Hold on. Fucking maintenance.
Fucking goddamn maintenance. I need to recalibrate the camera.
Fucking maintenance. He's a vampire. No, that just like hurt my head. Okay, how we look now?
Hey, that's better. It's a little creepier. Streaming didn't even start yet. Just relax.
All right. I'm putting on my headphones. You know that how it's going to get real now.
Can I open doors? You're walking in circles, bro. What else do we want? What do we want me to go?
The directions I have are put the mummy back together with the mummy. Do you like Dr. Pepper?
Yeah. How many games are in this collection? Like 15. All right, this one's cool. Am I missing
something? What does this mean? Something is like getting lost in the ticket line at Disney World
and complaining that the park sucks. All right, but if you got out of the line eventually,
and an attendant was there saying, thanks for coming. And you're like, wait, was the ride?
If that was the ride, then do I can I interact? I want to see this to the end. I want to see this
to the end. This guy, I got to be able to do something, right? Like look at all these
fucking symbols. Pick up the light. All right. All right. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I
get it. I get it. I just put a light to place up and find something interesting to look at.
He doesn't get it. Neither do you. Neither do you. So that's fine. We can share. We can share it.
You don't get it either. You don't get it either. What is it? You don't get it either.
Do I have like a task menu or something? It just said put them, assemble them up,
explore and assemble the mummy. Where's the mummy? Can I go in these doors? I don't get it.
The light has a symbol on the back. Where? That thing was missing. This thing's moving,
by the way. This thing is moving. Get a picture of that. What the hell is that?
There's somebody's arm or body or something. Okay. So that's there. I got a picture of it.
I want to see what that is. Get a picture of that. What is that? I have to go use the portal?
Aim it at the mirror? Where is there a mirror? What have you decided is a mirror here?
This is the hub world. This is a fucking hub world? What the fuck is that? Stop pretending.
Guys, the only information was explore and put the mummy together. It didn't say go point your
camera into a fucking mirror. All right, relax. This is a dinner serving tray. This is not a mirror.
I can go down there. This is not a roblox game. This is a game journalist. No, I am not. That
was unclear. I swear to God. How did he die? The monster must have got him in that scary game. No,
now he broke both of his legs jumping off a fucking small platform and now he's dead.
Can I make this jump? I can. All right, where's my prize? Can I open that? How do I open this?
There's definitely a mummy piece in here, right? Okay. Is there any indicator where that is?
God damn it. Put the fucking camera down. It was at the beginning of the room.
Was it really? God damn it. It really was. I got to take a picture of it.
Okay. Yeah, we're getting to major F. I don't understand. It's just like I don't know why
this happens randomly every few months. I just can't stream to Twitch. Twitch just doesn't want
me to stream to it. My internet is perfectly fine. Hold on. Hold on. Yeah, I don't know why
this happens sometimes. Sometimes my streaming to Twitch's servers, it just fucks up for two
straight weeks. Because think about it, right? Every stream during the Elden Ring streams,
this has happened for a little while. Then it went away for two months. I don't get it.
Fucking maintenance. Should I just never stream on a Tuesday?
Why is it always Tuesday? I'm just literally never turning my stream on ever again on a Tuesday.
Let me, I'm checking something. Hold on. I'm never turning a stream on on a Tuesday
ever again. It's the goddamn maintenance day for every company on earth.
All right. Let me, I'm going to run a test here. I don't know what I get. I just, we just have to
deal with it, I guess. That's so annoying. I hate when this happens. You know why this sucks the
most? Because I'm like, I'm very busy and I'm trying to get like streams in like a few times
a week during like all the busy shit. And I'm just being like, the tap is being turned off.
I can't even stream today. Am I even still alive? I'm going to be angry now. I'm just going to be
upset about everything. All right. So I, I just did a speed test right now during when I was just
dropping frames here. I was at a thousand, a thousand. I don't know. Whatever. I don't get it.
Let's just keep playing. This, I'm sorry. We have to deal with this, but it's unfortunate.
Fuck. You know what sucks the most? And you didn't hear anything else. I went off on a,
well, good. I went off on a rant. Whatever. All right. Let's just, let's just play.
I'm really thrown. I'm really thrown off today. Really thrown off today. No, no, no, no, no, no,
I had the picture taken. I just, Oh my. I'm fucking thrown off now. Give me a break.
I have to fucking be pissed in a minute. I'm so thrown off right now. All my juices are all
fucked up. So mad. At least the scream is funny. You know, okay. It's like, okay. I'm going to
settle down because I'm fucking pissed right now. I am pissed off. One, two, three. Okay.
Let's just, just as chill. Let's take a second. I can take a sip.
The music makes it seem like I'm such much more of a unhinged person.
I'm going to mute the audio cause like the audio is making me fucking mad.
I can't shake it. I can't shake it. God, dude. I can't shake it. I can't shake it. All right.
Was it, was it? Okay. Person. I don't know. Camera. I don't know. Camera TV. I don't know.
I don't know. What is this? Okay. Let's go. Person. No, put the camera down. All right.
Somebody, Ahmad helped me. Thank you. Of course for that person. You know, you got man,
camera TV. See, they say nobody gets this. They say that's my favorite part about that whole
interview. They say, they say nobody, nobody can get this. Nobody gets this. Nobody could get that.
I think nobody, nobody can do this. All right. What is it? I can't even do it.
Huh? What's the last symbol? Hey, what's the last symbol? What's the last symbol?
There's only three symbols there in that mod chat. What's the last symbol? Oh, the box opened. Oh,
cool. Oh, I got a piece of the mummy. What's up with the internet? Nothing. The last time this
happened, I ran a speed test. Oh my God. It's the mummy. Am I still alive? What happened?
Was I not supposed to die? Jesus. That was actually kind of terrifying.
I think it's a Twitch problem. The last time I did this, I ran a speed test overnight
and I was cleanly at almost a thousand, one thousand up and down for an entire evening.
This is fucking Tuesday maintenance. Can we rename this stream Tuesday maintenance?
Fuck maintenance or something. I don't know what to say. That was crazy. I think I lost.
Should I go back? There's a lot to see. I need to settle down. I am settled down.
What are you doing? I just died. That was unfair. I wasn't fair to that one.
Last time I was dealing with Tuesday maintenance. What's this one? Don't go out? Shatter? Hand of
doom. I think I want to try this one. Let's do hand of doom. Am I orange today? Because all the
blood is flowing to my face. Hand of doom. Okay. How does this one work? What did figure?
Okay. It's a book of dread incantations. Sure looks to be useful.
It didn't work. Okay. Oh, unlock doors. I got it. Okay.
Failed? What do you mean? That's right there. Open it. A locked door. I just opened it with a spell.
What is it? Talethistort. Nice. Enter the dark dungeon. Hedge wizard.
You must be the newest resident of the dungeon. How did you escape from the dungeon?
You may have been better off staying locked up. Okay. Can I throw a fireball at him or something?
Is this the same person? Wait. That book. Could it be? It's the Lost Grimoire. The master searches
for it. They say it grants the wielder great power. Pray the master does not learn you possess it.
Okay.
I know that one. Step aside. Fucking amateur. One spell Andy coming through.
And all it is is unlock a door.
Nice. Let's go. What was that? Oath of Flame.
Ethistalort.
Okay. There's a torch. Oh shit. Can I pick that up? Ethistalort.
Which way should I go?
Stop doing that. Why is it blowing out?
Oh, that's okay. All right. I got light. Where is there no light this way? All right.
Ethistalort. Is it going to speed up my voice? Stop wasting your mana on starlight.
Holy shit. Let me tell you something about starlight, by the way.
Hold on. Dude, I tried coke starlight. Coke starlight is unbelievable. It's like the
greatest soda I've ever had in my whole life. A knife with dark sorcery. You feel compelled to
take it. Coke starlight is so good. It's just regular coke. No, it's not. Coke starlight,
it tastes kind of like cotton candy with vanilla coke in it. I don't know. It's very interesting.
Of all the dumb gimmick flavors I've ever come up with, I think it's really good.
What the fuck? Ethistalort.
This is lasting a lot less than... Oh, I have a knife. So what should I do now? Should I stab
somebody? What the fuck just happened? What did I just do that for? Why did I just do that?
Just stabbed myself in the hand. Okay, does somebody... Do I have to kill that monster
that's in here? Or should I just leave? Because this is hand. Just leave? Okay.
All right, so I got the knife. Enter the graveyard.
Blood fountain? Okay.
Okay, so that's health. I get it. So there's a demo. Wait, we got demos working. Steam works
like two fucking hours later. Streaming on a goddamn Tuesday ever again. All right, so
yeah, I don't know if I'm gonna do it though. I'd rather try to do that again tomorrow if the
server shit is better for Orts. Yeah, this is just annoying. I got an idea. I got an idea.
We are at almost 10% of all frames being dropped, which that's... Fuck, that's awful.
I'm gonna... Here's what I'm gonna do. This is the plan. I am going to try again later today.
Try to come back tonight. Because this is very obviously not fixing itself. And I really don't...
Streams where you drop 10% of all frames, they just... It's just... Especially for VODs and...
I'll try later. The whole vibe of the stream gets all fucked up. And it's just like, all right,
the internet sucks. Well, not the internet, but whatever the connection is here. I'll try. Let
me try later tonight. I'll be back. Download some demos. I'll get some... We'll try some demos
tonight. Because I have to imagine that maybe later it'll be okay. Let me try coming back in
like an hour or so. Maybe like an hour or two. So sorry, guys. This frustrates me. Trust me,
this frustrates me as much as it frustrates you. And then some. But... And I'd rather just do it
when it works. But we'll try it again. These games, I want to... Let's get back to this.
I was very frustrated during that last game. And not the game's fault is the fucking goddamn
Tuesday. Here, it's already doing it again. Not the game's fault. I was already upset. That game
has seemed pretty fun. I want to make sure that I make that clear. It frustrates me more. Yeah,
I'll be back. Let me try this again. I'll see you guys a little bit later. Sorry. We'll try again
in a couple hours. Probably like eight o'clock Pacific. If we can't get it to work then, then I
don't know what to say. I'll try again tomorrow. So I'm going to turn the stream off and I'm going
to scream into a pillow. I'm going to hold it up and just go... So yeah, it's pretty fun.
Do four orbs before you leave. All right, yeah. That doesn't do anything. Smash. Smash. All right,
I'll try again later. I'll be back. We're not even going to do an outro. I'll see you in an hour or
two. Goodbye. See you later. Good night. If you're leaving, if we see you again tonight,
then hi. How are you? Good to see you. My name is me. I'll be back. Goodbye. See you later today.
All right, now I'm going to pretend to click the off button and go like, fuck,
fuck, like I did earlier, right? All right, goodbye. I'll see you in a minute.
A lot of minutes in a row. Goodbye.