Alright. Are you ready to be introduced?
Yeah, I'm here. Do the drumroll first for me.
I want a drumroll. Hey! What is going on, buddy?
No, see, that's you introducing yourself. Only I want the drumroll.
Okay. Star! Hey, what's going on guys? Welcome to...
This is Lethal League, as you probably could tell. We're gonna do
round two on Lethal League, as both of us have had a chance to figure out how to play this
video game.
You haven't played this game. Yes, I have. Since the last video.
We played it in the hotel at PAX. You played like two games.
How do you know that I haven't been sitting around
practicing? Well, do you have the extra super skins?
What's that? Oh, he does!
Play ball. Play raw. Get destroyed.
Oh, I might have increased the ball speed, by the way. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What did you do? I increased the ball speed. Why did you do that?
Well, I'm not used to this increased ball speed.
I've never played like this. It's alright.
You think you could stop me? You can't stop anybody.
Yeah, well, you told me about the balls and how am I supposed to know?
This is going a lot better than the last time we played.
Yeah, this really... says the guy that increases ball speed.
Puts his balls in my face.
I was going to warn you, I guess.
There we go. You don't get away from this.
Shit! I tried to jump on you. I just got an achievement for that one.
Okay, well, I didn't. What are you doing? I was trying to
launch it back at you. Did you get an achievement for that one?
That thing's going to be so late.
You never know where I'm going. You've got to be shitting me.
You know what's really freaking me out? It's the fact that I'm blue.
There we go. You don't like being blue?
You're not going to catch this one. Wow, I didn't. My face, maybe.
Well, I'm still ahead. Sorry, not for long.
I guarantee you, I bet you $50 billion on this net.
No, I was talking. I bet you $50 billion you get hit by this.
Are you ready? Are you willing to make that bet?
Yes. I meant, like, right now...
50 billion! 50 billion! You can't just change the parameters.
That was a good warm-up.
Can you make that color adjustment in your brain?
I'm trying to make the adjustment in my brain.
But it's okay, because I'm playing the Candyman.
You're not going to fool me with that.
You ain't going to fool me. For some reason, just completely blanked.
What's going on? My controller just fucking broke.
Oh, yes! We're going to do that again?
We're going to try to do that again. We're going to try to do that again.
Oh, he doesn't know when I'm going to hit it.
You've got it way down there. This is where it's going to get interesting.
It's going to get really interesting here. No, you're just going to get hit.
Izzy! What the fuck happened to me?
I swear, it's going to get really interesting.
Oh, it is going to get interesting. I did, yeah.
Okay, well, now I've got to put my pants on.
You're not wearing pants right now? No.
Well, that's interesting, I guess.
You know, I will just keep hitting this, and...
You're hitting it just slightly over my head.
And it's messing everything up.
Well, why don't you try to handle this situation, you motherfucker?
You're too tall. Hey, I do have a height advantage, but it's not a big deal.
You ready for this massive comeback? You're not going to get a massive comeback.
What you are going to get is you're going to get...
You're going to... I was talking to you.
Well, you should have been playing. All right. Come here.
Come here. Come over here.
Mmm. Why would I do that?
I win! So, what is at stake right here?
What are you putting at stake? Don't hit the ball.
Don't touch that ball. I will hand cook, like personal chef make you dinner.
All right. I will come over and cook you a delicious meal.
Now, I'm going to come to your apartment.
I want you to make me dinner at your place.
Okay. And it's got to be good.
You thought you could really do that? Did you really think you were going to do that?
I think you knew that I was going to do that.
So, what happens if you win while I let you just fucking farm your special?
That sounds like a great idea.
Well, if I win, I don't know. You need to make something up.
All right. If you win... I think we're even now.
If you win, then I will write you a personal song.
Like with like instruments, it'll be like a legitimate like why Star is like so cool song.
Yeah. You okay?
Yeah, I'm down with that. All right.
Whoever wins this, this is the champion. This is the champion championship.
Let's go. I think you're getting a song out of me.
You're very sorely mistaken here.
Whoa, how did you hit that?
Tall. Totally. God. What?
It's those tall hits that are up above my head. You don't understand.
Damn it. I was trying to bounce it up, bounce it around.
No, you bounce it back down to Charlie Town.
This is the one. This is the one for me.
Why? Oh, god damn it.
Oh, I'm going to get that personal ballad by my little bar to Jeremy.
You're not getting it.
I'm getting a delicious dinner of my choosing.
I want a bib with my name on it.
All right. I didn't promise any bibs.
Time to sit up.
You see which way it's going? Do you see where it's going?
You're going to have a little. Why did I jump into it?
I don't know. What kind of decision making am I doing here?
That was a bad decision.
No, I didn't want to do that.
OK, I did want to do that, though.
OK, that was all right.
Why? Yes. What kind of again, the decision making here?
What do I want for dinner? Let's think.
Do I want am I going to want like am I going to want like onions in this meal?
Do you want some frogs?
What do you even like know how to cook, by the way?
Are you knocking like maybe like microwave, like macaroni and cheese or something?
Are you? No, I know how to cook.
I hate that stupid bullshit.
You can go back to kindergarten with that that that pansy ass candy ass.
Oh, well, this is a pretty close game.
This is getting close.
This is getting close. I'm getting scared.
I mean to come on now that don't.
I freaked out for no reason.
I was you turn your freak.
Holy shit. This is bad.
Oh, my God. What am I supposed to do about this?
Holy shit.
No, I let you get it.
No, no, get away.
I don't know.
No, no, I'm getting that song.
No, I'm shutting up.
You get a fucking song.
He shines in the sky, that twinkle in my eye.
He gives me what a perfect guy at any point in time or history.
Once it's done, when we're done, stars the man.
He's so cool. He's so nice.
Everything about him is now strife.
Who's that flying in the sky?
Star on a motorcycle made for the sky.
There he goes, flying in front of your face.
Home on a journey to outer space.