I mean, the universe is such a large place, and it's a little disheartening that we don't spend more time and more effort with the research and development into certain things like the theory of relativity, for instance.
I mean, I'm not sure exactly why we don't spend that much money. I would implore the Congress and the Senate to do that, and it truly is a beautiful thing.
Did I just kill that many-
What is this? Look at how dirty this is. Like, it's like a- this was in my pocket, by the way, of these pants. You can't see them.
I have no- I must have like blown my nose in that and like wiped it on the concrete.
Hey, what's going on, everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2. It's been a while since the last Facecam Fortress, but let's go, cow man, let's-
Okay, I'm gonna show this to you because this doesn't make any sense. I don't know if I can get this in the camera.
This is my keyboard. That's my jump button. Can you-
How do they get those pita pockets? You know the little pita pockets that they make that you get at the grocery store?
How do they put those inside the pita? Like, how do they make the bread like that? That's- they can't make it.
It's impossible. Like, you need the dough to settle. You need there to be-
Am I missing? I'm missing. You need the dough.
I can't believe I'm- you know, the dough seriously needs to settle and I don't know what kind of dough you use,
but the dough that I use is truly- it sucks. It doesn't rise correctly. It smells a little bit.
It smells kind of like cheese and farts.
Come on. Somebody come over here. Somebody just walk over here right now. Come on. I could wait all day.
Get plenty of coffee. Got plenty of time. At least I killed somebody with that. This is the face I make.
When I'm really fucking mad. Now I'm mad. You made me fucking mad. Now it's time to show you
how we do things. Get behind enemy lines and start stabbing. Get like a nine-person chain stab.
Nobody up there. No snipers. What about back here? The only person on like red team is this like poor heavy.
That's about to- you know, we're not gonna kill this guy. I'm not gonna kill this guy. Yeah. Hey, what's up, man?
Got that health? He's like, huh? What was that? Who was that? Was that a spy?
I love how he's spy checking these guys, but not me.
Come on. Come on. Walk right into that crosshair. It wasn't the same guy, but it's okay.
I don't want to get shot in the face. That's the number one thing I don't want to have happen
accidentally by one of these snipers.
There was three and we lost because I wasn't capping the point, but
come on. Get it. Come on. Kill me baby. Baby speed. Come on. Turn around. Please turn around.
Turn around, please. Shoot me. Shoot me. I'm trying to walk in front of him.
Oh my god.
No, there's another one. There's two. Oh, no, they're gonna double team me.
Hold on a second.
They both have get this is on. They both just like
Like
Head shot. Head shot. Head shot. Oh, and he landed and died. Get another head shot. Excuse me. What would you like?
No, it's a pyro and he's gonna get me.
I'm burning. It's over. I burnt.
Star Wars killed me. George Lucas presents Star Wars.
Gets the kill on Jerma or Greg. Are we really getting this badly destroyed right now?
We didn't even cap it once. How did this even happen? I don't even know. How did we do that?
What?
Yeah
Yes
Yes. Yes. Thank you so much for watching everybody. I really do appreciate it. I don't know what three health great
I'm i'm very good at that. I'm very good. I i'm very good to
redo
redo just cut that out just slight just take in the file in the video file and they cut
And then drag that piece
To to the other piece to get rid of that fucking part talking to you Jerma
Don't leave this in don't accidentally leave this in
I know you're gonna accidentally leave this in and the people are gonna say you accidentally left this part in
And then i'm gonna say what are you even talking about? I didn't I didn't leave it in
I was just now i'm seriously being an idiot. Thank you so much for watching really do appreciate it guys. Oh my god
great 57
I can't wait to open it