Hello. Yeah, sorry about that. I was, I was ready to go.
Uh, but, uh, Mr. Otto, I did the thing where he runs around in a circle,
sprints, dive bombs your knees, says, get me outside now.
I did. Being early yesterday really took it out of him.
You're a baby? I'm not the baby. I'm taking care of my baby, Otto.
Did you understand? Oh, pounded. You got it.
All right. Yeah. So it's a day. I tweeted. We're good. I'm probably
talking to you. Look at my tweet was ready. My tweet went up before the stream went up.
That's how, you know, I was ready. Every other stream, I sit there, I press live and I go,
I forgot to tweet. Hold on. Give me a second. That's my proof to you that I was ready.
But we're going to do no more heroes three finale today. I believe there's only about
two or three more hours left in the game. And then from there, we're going to move back to
WarioWare. Hopefully get to level 50 in super hard. You said Spore? Oh, you're talking about
the title. It does say, it does say like Spore save file. Okay, maybe I should change that.
It says Suda 51's Spore save file. But that's like a reference to like how
fucked up this game is and all the characters are like Spore characters and like WWE 2K characters.
That was, that was a joke. Is it misleading? All right. I'll change it. I'll change it. I'll change
it. I'll change it. That's, is that misleading? You think it's, is it too misleading? That was a
joke we made like a week ago. How about, how about I, okay, how about this? I got it. I got it. I got
it. I got the fix. How about I change the title to what I imagine Suda 51 Spore save file looks like?
That's so wordy. I actually kind of like it. Yeah, I like that. I like that. It sucks.
We just play Spore. I'm going to put what I am. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. I got it. Don't worry.
Why can't I change the title? I can't change the title of my own stream. Why? I don't understand.
Edit stream info is grayed out. What is, okay. I just hit, I just pressed the cancel button. I
don't know that I, what happened? Did something happen? It was just a cancel button that I could
press on the top of my screen and I just pressed cancel. Let's just log off. I don't have no idea.
Here we go. Okay. Here we go. How about here? What I imagine Suda 51 Spore save file
looks like there. Are you happy? I like that. I like that. All right, let's go.
Hey, can you not stream? Why is it in brackets? Because like that's me thinking that's,
that's what I imagine a Suda 51 Spore save file looks like that's internal monologue. Oh, don't,
okay. Now here we go. Now you're all going to tell me you don't have an internal monologue, right?
Chat can't rotate a cube in their head, OmegaLul, right? Is this, are we going to go down this road,
this road again? If they laugh. All right, let's go. A title's fixed. It's fine.
Suda 51 Spore save, but everyone was like, holy shit, how did you get that? What? It was a,
whatever. All right, we're going back. All right, let's play. By the way, I need to make this really
clear. This is the end of the game. If you are very excited to get your hands on No More Heroes 3
eventually, you're about to see the last third of the whole game. I just want to make that really
clear. You ready? Okay. And then after this, we are going to go to, I almost said No More Heroes,
but that's what we're doing right now. WarioWare on the same console. It'll be a very easy switch.
Okay. So, uh, first things first, I'm going to try to get to at least 20.
Because I had 20 before. This just is WarioWare. I might as well just be playing WarioWare again.
Those of you asking for a face cam? Nope. It's not going on until WarioWare.
Maybe if you're good, it'll turn on once this stream here for the next like two hours.
Dude, you forgot to start streaming.
Face cam on no balls. That doesn't matter. I don't care.
Face cam does not matter to me. It's not going on.
What if I say please? Okay. Okay. They said please. They did. You did. You said please.
That one person said please. In the sea of demanding chatters.
There you go.
We're going back to 2012, German, when I wore just muscle shirts every day. Remember that?
Remember that, Ark? It's coming back. By the way, you get this until this minigame is over.
This is boring. Oh, that was, that was not you guys saying that. That was the game saying that.
Face cam's going off. Thanks, everybody. Now we're gonna play the game.
Just have to get ready. I got 20 points in that. It doesn't matter. What was the last thing we
were just doing in No More Heroes 3? How much money do I have? Alright, I just had done the
last thing. So let's go. We're out with the beard. No, the beard actually has to get shaved tonight.
The only reason why I didn't do it last night or the night before is because I knew I was
gonna probably have the face cam on for a portion of the screen. And as you all know,
I don't like the way that I look with a clean shaved face. I don't like it. It makes me look
weird. So I have this rule where I am not, and this is, I'm not kidding. People think this is a
joke, but there's a lot of new viewers. I need to make sure that new viewers know this too.
I only go into public and I only show my face to people after two days have gone by after shaving
my face. So I have, I plan my get togethers around if two days will have gone by after shaving.
So if I, let's say I get invited to do something. Hey man, you, uh, what are you up to on Saturday
night? And it's Friday, like Friday afternoon. I'm like, oh, um, I got some, yeah, I got some stuff
going on. Oh, you sure? You don't want to? No, I got some stuff going on. Sorry. What are you doing
on Sunday night or Monday afternoon? Uh, nothing. Perfect. I'm going to be free on Monday afternoon.
Exactly two to three days after shaving conventions and meet like get togethers and meetups.
Every time a Twitch con happened or every time like a PAX would happen, I would shave. Okay. So
on day one of a PAX, right? Most people are kind of coming in and people aren't necessarily
seeing each other. It's like, oh, you come in, you travel. It's a travel day. Everyone's like,
I'm going to get in. It's going to be like eight o'clock. I'm sleeping and asleep at the hotel.
I would shave that morning because it was guaranteed. I wasn't going to see anybody,
except like whatever people on the plane, but I don't care. And then like a full day would
go by day one. Like that's day zero packs. Like day one of packs will be one full day.
I know that all the people do stuff on the Saturday nights, which would be two full days.
So therefore, like for the actual time when I know I'm going to see people, I look at my,
I look my best two full days go by. I get that slight five o'clock shadow. Go watch the dollhouse
streams. Go turn on day one of the dollhouse streams. That was exactly 48 hours to the moment
the stream started that I shaved. Just get a trimmer. No, I can't get it. I don't like
trimmers. Trimmers make me break out bad. I've tried to use an electric. And by the way, half
the time those things don't even fucking do anything. I have had nice beard trimmers and
electric razors. You just, you have your face as a hair minefield. They don't do anything. I've
never had one that actually works well. I will go by and it's like, okay, there's still all the
hair is still there. And now my face just is stinging hurts. And I'm going to have like a
breakout tomorrow. I've tried every kind of, I've tried it every time. Is this the, have I done this
one? Just get a beard. No, I can't grow beards. I have to, it has to be two days without shaving.
And then it's perfect.
It's a pretty good song for this. Oh, got it. Shave on screen. I already did.
By the way, I'm in one of those moods again today. I don't know what it is.
Um, where is it? There it is. Trash. Trash. Come on. Trash. Trash. There's still trash over here.
Oh my God. I don't like these missions. These are my least favorite.
These are my least favorite missions in the whole game. Where is it? Come on.
That's gotta be close, right? Well, I didn't get it all. I didn't get it all. Whatever. These,
I don't like these ones. You see that? I'm trying to make money.
Bronze. Whatever. It's money. That's money. If level three opens up, I just really don't want
to do it as much as I love this game. And I love like completing a lot of the stuff. Yeah.
Anuvala. Whatever. I'll do it. Fine. It's right here. I don't care. I'm going to pay attention to
this. Does that mean that there's one hidden somewhere? I don't get it. I think that's what
that means. That sucks. Oh, get out of here. Hey, get out. Get out. Get out.
No, we have to move on from that. I love that reference and it's a really funny video and it's
a really interesting community joke, but I can't just do the seal every day. I have to, I can't,
I got to move on. Maybe it's just so interesting that I'm allowed to do it more than once a week.
I don't want to go too far up because I want to just go through the middle.
What do you guys think? What's the amount of time that we're allowed to be stuck on one reference
or one joke for the streams? Now that I'm only live like once or twice a week. I think, I think
it's probably, I think it's probably two weeks, three months. I think that's too long. Where is
it? How are you ever supposed to reliably do this in this amount of time? Depends on how funny you
think it is. That's a good point. You're right. Aaron should be forever. Aaron was not,
Aaron was supposed to be like a day. Aaron way overstayed its welcome and became something that
you guys now actually want to hear all the time, which is bizarre to me. And Lala too. I, people,
people unsubscribe because of Lala. You understand that? Do you know that that happened?
Liz almost lost. Three, two, one. I don't care if it's bronze. I'm just trying to get through them.
Get the non-believers out of here. I just want the metal so I can unlock the next level.
3,500. Nice. Level four. No. All right. I don't need to do it again.
Bronze. All right. Is there anything else I can do? What, what do we got going on here?
Head to the Thunderdome. Okay. Fine. I'm just trying to make a little bit of extra cash before
we go. Thunderdome. Remember, can a kangaroo walk backwards? Probably hop backwards. Shortcut.
Maybe. Or can they? I don't know. I have no idea. All right. Back in the Thunderdome. All right.
Head to the, head to the Thunderdome. Find it. Okay. We just have to do designated matches.
I got to remember how to play the video game because it has been a while.
All right. Let's go to these ones up here. And for a match. This game sucks with two C's. Can
I ask you guys something? I think we have a fairly, there's a fairly large zoomer population here,
I think, right? What do you, as the potential zoomer population, what, what like kind of your
generational slang or your generational terms do you not like the most? What do you think?
Well, like what, what's like your like genera- not even like slang, but what's your like
generational thing that you guys have that you like the least? Lit. Fringe. Suss. Fortnite. Suss.
I'm not sure Suss will continue to, I don't know. I don't think Suss will live as long as
we think it will. Remember how to play the game Andy, right? That's not even a place where that
works. Hey, you know what my favorite is? My favorite is Andy. That's my favorite. I have
like a powerful move right now. Oh my goodness. We're about to kill everybody in the room.
Right, I have these moves. Okay, cool. Game's a little loud, I think, isn't it?
Andy. Oh my god, I got it again. Full green mode. All right, I gotta get in the middle.
Everybody can see me. And, ha! It's you. You gotta be the worst. What are you talking about?
What are you, hold on. I'm, you just threw me off big time right now. What do you mean? I just
freaked out. What are you talking about? Me? I'm the worst zoomer thing? Is that technically true?
You got me all fucked up right now. That's technically a true statement.
Ego obliterated. I'm, oh, I'm dead. I, you just really screwed my whole thing up here.
You just shattered my entire world view of everything. Let me turn the game down a little.
What the fuck? Damn, that's based. I don't think based is a zoomer thing. I think that was around
when, like, more than 10 years ago, wasn't it? All right, let me get back into this.
Sussy Baka is the worst one.
Why is it giving this shit to me? Why is it giving this to me? I must be really mad that I'm, like,
doing so poorly. Based is old. Yeah, based is really old. Based is not even, like, in the last
10 years. He's not dead? What just happened? Based based cringe cringe. That was $10,000 for that?
What the hell? Onions, onions. All right, dude, I think we need a rock out break. It's been
15 minutes. I'm, I think I'm gonna be fine. I think I'm gonna be okay. There's a bike there.
And we're off. I thought I could drive over that. You know, I want there to be studies done on
things. Like, for instance, has, is pepperoni, like, has there been a percentile lossage in
if pepperoni is everyone's favorite topping generation to generation? You know what I mean?
Like, okay, from boomers to millennial to zoomers, is pepperoni, do we lose any percentage points?
What's, like, your, what's a zoomer's, like, favorite pizza topping, right?
Like, what's a millennial's favorite pizza topping? Is it, is it, is that universally,
like, the best pizza topping that everyone agrees on? I wonder. That's, that stuff kind of intrigues
me. Black olives? Because, like, those tastes don't change. Like, pepperoni universally, like,
80% of people like on their pizza. Like, doesn't matter what generation or who you are, where you
are. That's interesting, isn't it? Three of these guys. All right, I gotta pay attention.
These guys are horrible. These guys are the worst enemy. Jesus. I can't see. I've been jumping
around. It freaks me out. I don't like the jumping. I feel like, I feel like I just played,
I'm in a game of Overwatch right there. Do we talk about particle effects in games and how,
like, they've gone way too overboard? Have we talked about that yet? I know that I've talked
about that. Like, I want less particle effects in video games, not more. I'm fucking dead.
Those guys, I was on the ground. I just got combo'd. All right, this is a good warm-up
period. I'm just warming up. I haven't played this game in like a week. Give me a break.
Wait. All right, that's better.
Come on. Come in. Come on. Wait. Wait, miss? What happened?
Get over here. Anyways, what was it? Oh, yeah. Particle effects in video games.
There was, for some reason, a trend started happening in the last 10 years
that I'm really not a fan of. And it's when particle effects take over the entire video
game. I'm going to say something here that it's going to make a lot of people probably upset.
I don't know. It might. Because I don't think I've talked about this specific instance in this.
I just remember...
Personal opinion. Personal opinion. This is not... I don't... I think it's a great series.
It's an incredible franchise. I love it. I've played hundreds, if not potentially thousands
of hours of this franchise. I'm going to die if I stop talking. I'll talk about it after.
I'm going to die. And it's going to be your... No, it's not. It's my fault.
I brought this up. It's not your fault. Okay. Anyways, listen to me. So, Super Smash Brothers,
the new iterations of the game, the last two iterations, the particle effects are so
outrageous to me in my brain. Like punching and kicking and jumping. They like these huge,
massive particle effects. I like the game. I think it's a really great game. But every time
I punch and kick somebody, it's like... You see these giant flashing clouds appear over everybody's
head. It's almost hard sometimes to see. Like, okay, I'm doing a combo. I see these two or three
giant flashes of big bright clouds of sparkles and explosions over people. I want less. And now
that I said that, I'm sorry that I just... People that are going to... If you play that game and
you're a fan of it, you're now going to see what I'm talking about. And I may have just fucked up
your entire view of that game. I'm sorry. I think that's why I like the Souls series.
You may have just come up with the reason why, even though those games are kind of hard
and somewhat frustrating and annoying to me, that it is one of my favorite franchises ever.
That's a really good point. Because there's no extra shit added on those games. If I punch
somebody or if I slash somebody with a sword in Dark Souls, the sword just hits them. A gigantic
bright particle cloud of bright colors and explosions don't come out of their body.
I don't like that training. Over-stimulation. Yeah, it's just over-stimulating. Like,
headache-inducing the way. It hates this game. No. This blood... Yeah, but there's a difference
between like blood coming out and like bright sparkly explosions and huge smoke particle effects
coming out when you touch somebody. I heard that Mass Effect 2 does not have that. So this is a
roundabout way of you saying that this should be blood and smash. Oh my god. I'm sorry.
I'll be really honest with you. And I have to be. Because if I'm not honest with you, then I can't
be honest with myself, right? If there was blood and smash besides the giant huge bright flash of
particle effects every time you hit somebody, I would probably like the game more. It's very
easy to say that. But no, I'm not... Listen to me. I'm not saying that I would prefer it. I'm just
saying that like there would be less on the screen. I just want less stuff on the screen when I hit
stuff. That's it. I'm going this way. He wants to see Mario bleed. No, I just want to see Mario
have... I want less stuff on the screen. You want Mario dead. You're a psycho. I'm not though. I
know there's people here that agree with me. That want to see less obscene particle explosions
every time they see anything. Oh, hold on. I thought the game crashed.
I know these people agree with me. I know they're in here. Why did it happen?
You're literally the only one. No, I can't see.
It can't be. That's why I couldn't really... That's why I didn't care about Overwatch.
It's the way that you phrased it. What, because I said I would rather they be blood and smash
brothers than bright particle effects? I'm not talking about mortal combat levels of blood.
Oh, shit. This is bad. This is a hard place to fight everybody.
Strawberry. Yeah, be careful here. Invincible. Oh, thank God. What? Why are they staying alive
after that? Stupid particle effects. Are these my screen? Whatever. Pretending to be bad again.
Do the mission. This is the mission. This is the game. I have to make enough money
from doing the jobs in the mission. Come on. That's so stupid. Oh, whatever. Who cares?
What else do you want blood in? I don't want blood in Smash Brothers. I just said that I prefer less
stuff on the screen. And like a blood splatter would be way less than like the smoke explosions.
Let's get this over with. You're putting words in my mouth. Stop it.
All right, let's kill. I gotta get rid of these guys first. These guys are the worst.
What about Wii Sports? I don't know what you're talking about. Why would they be blood in Wii
Sports? Come on. What about boxing in Wii Sports? But there's okay. Comedy violence is different
than like mature violence. Dude, Tom and Jerry. Tom used to get like a hammer smashed on his hand
and like shot in the face and stuff. Like Jerry used to fucking torture that guy. But there was
no blood. He may have gotten like a black eye or something, right? But when Tom hit Jerry with the
hammer, sparkly, gigantic particle smoke did not come out of Tom's hand. That's the point. He got
his teeth knocked in. No, it didn't. There was no like big flash particle like camera flash
and like sparkles and big smoke. Boom! No, he's got his hand smashed with a hammer.
Okay, all right. I'm moving on from this. We've been on this for too long.
I'm gonna try to do this one again. How will you know if it's next gen if there's not millions of
particles? You know, that's probably the reason why a lot of games slow down too. Is that what
happened? Have we plateaued in graphics that we have not plateaued in the amount of shit that they
can put on the screen in particle effects? I think you figured it out. Style is becoming more
important. Today is the particle rant stream. Not. Three, four, five, six, seven, eight. Yeah,
it takes way too long. All right. I don't want to fall in the lava, but man you got to fight
the people down there. That sucks. Is this game good? This game is very good. It's really difficult
for me to rate it and tell you, like, you shouldn't. This game is really not very good at all.
I really recommend you don't purchase it. It's probably the worst in the series, out of the three
at least, in the main series. No, it's good. It's really good. I think this is probably my favorite
one out of the three. This is my last time I'm going to try this. I've been, okay, the amount of
time I've taken trying to do this mission, I could have already made ten thousand dollars doing the
fight missions. Oh, let's not screw it up this time. Hang on, right? I don't even want to know
what level three this is, or level four. It's probably so awful. All right, nothing this way,
right? I have plenty of time. I'm not worried about the time. Move out of the fucking way.
All right, let's go this way.
Oh, he did a Lord of the Rings beatbox. He's done that, like, a thousand times. I've heard
that a million times before. He doesn't have any other material in his jukebox.
My voice is already fucked up this morning. I'm yelling at WarioWare, the 35-year-old man.
That's something I have to live with, you know.
About 36 yet. Stop saying that. It's not accurate yet.
All right, what about up? Yeah, there's one up there. Is there anything left over here?
God, I don't know. Jesus. Oh my god, it didn't register. It didn't register the click.
Holy shit. Okay, I'm good. All right, I gotta go up this way. Where is this?
Shut up. Four, okay, five, six. Don't fall in the middle. It's so easy to not fall in the middle.
I don't, there's no timer right now.
Goodness. Don't dodge into the fire.
I don't know. Where am I? Where am I? Where am I?
What the fuck? All right, I'm good.
Five, okay, there's one more. I don't know where it is, though. Wait for this to flood.
Do I still eat dairy? Um, a little. I don't drink any real milk or anything, except for like a milkshake or ice cream or cheese.
Oh, I mean, I don't, not really. Here it is. All right, get me out of here.
Yeah, I mean, I do. I still eat dairy. It's only from cheese and ice cream, though. That's really it.
You see that? If I want, like, milk in my coffee or milk with a brownie or something,
it's usually almond milk or oat milk. One of those two. Cheese tier list? I've already
did all the tier lists. New level is unlocked. All right, let's just see what it looks like
because it's here. Oat milk is filled with canola oil. Omega-Lel. Yeah, and apples have cyanide in it.
Whatever. I'll see you in 10 years when they realize. See you in 25 years when drinking
coffee actually kills you. I don't care. This is the banana radiation thing again. I don't care.
Coffee's supposed to be good for your heart. Yeah, whatever. I'll see you in 50 years when
they realize that there's like a micro organism in coffee that is giving us all like diseases.
Okay, here's the real point. Everything sucks. Everything is bad for you. Eventually.
I canceled it. I'm good. All right, well, that was cool. I need 50,000. I do a couple more missions.
Coffee's worms. It has worms in it. Yeah, I don't know. Whatever. Here's the point. Treat your body
well with whatever data and science that we have now and that's it. Just, you know, eat what you
want. Eat whatever you feel. Do whatever you want. Moderate it. Don't be crazy. Don't be out of your
mind and like, oh, I only eat fucking McDonald's number twos. Like, don't do that. That's a dumb
thing to do. Some light exercise if you need to and you look and then in like 100 years
they'll look back and they'll be like, are you kidding me? They were they were putting sugar.
They were eating sugar. What were they thinking? Just wait. There will be a what were they thinking
reference for like the generations in 100 years and like, hold on a minute guys. What are you?
What are you serious? They were eating the fruits off of trees. What? No, they were not. Why would
they do that? We'll see in like 200 years. They were eating. They were eating wait meat from a cow.
What the fuck? No, they were not. I don't believe that for a second. How could they do that?
There'll be something. Just you just wait. We'll see what it is. They were drinking water.
I don't know, man. There's there'll be something that we're doing right now
that generations in the future are going to be shocked that we even thought it was a decent
idea in the first place. I don't know what it is, but we won't know.
Oh, we've got a whole combo on them.
First down. I say I saw somebody say that oxygen was poisonous.
Um, I don't I don't want to get too into this. I don't know. I who said that? It is. I don't know.
That's that's an unconfirmed statement. I can't I can't agree or deny that one.
It's unconfirmed. We read that shit every day. That's unconfirmed to me. I mean, technically,
it could be. Yeah, but isn't it like a blend? Don't we have an air cocktail that's not just
oxygen? So I okay, maybe that might that might be accurate. I don't know. Yeah, we have an air
cocktail. I get it. Yeah, whatever. It's like, I don't know, like hydrogen, oxygen,
hydrogen, oxygen,
or ander, cadmium, whatever they are. There's all kinds of shit in our ear.
Just said, Dude, German, you are on hard drugs. No, you are right now seeing the reason why I was
always afraid of ever doing a hard drug ever. I am completely drug free. But the exception
is Tylenol, caffeine, a little bit of marijuana. I'm feeling okay. No drug free, man. I don't.
I have no way. Don't do those all together. I'm no, I'm not. I'm I'm talking about in
separate occasions. No, I look, you don't need more than that. Let's be really realistic here.
Really, really hard shit that like really fucks you up and stuff. No, no, just I'll just I'll
take a little bit of weed is fine. That's it. That's kind of I don't need alcohol, maybe a
little bit sometimes. No, that's anything more than that. No, it's not. It's not good. It's
not good for you. Fucks up. You've had screws with you. This is what like no, I need ATM.
Where's your ATM? Oh, right here. What about psychedelics? Um, I don't I don't know enough
about them. I know that there's some preliminary data right of people. There being some drug
companies or some pharmaceutical companies that are experimenting with like low dose of psychedelics
to treat some mental disorders, mental health problems, right? I don't know. I've heard that.
I don't know. We'll see in like another 20 years. What happens 15 years? I'm afraid of them and I
don't ever want to do them. They're experimenting with shrooms. I mean, I know that there is some
drug companies that are that have programs. Let's study. That's deep, man. Very, very low doses of
some psychedelics can actually help. I don't know. It's just really random shit that I have read.
I have that correct, correct, right? We used to drink this after school. Yeah, okay.
I always got muscat and you always got kyoho. The sweetness of the grape really invigorates a tired
body. It was a little treat to myself for working hard. That stuff was good. It's all coming back
to me now. So you remember things too, huh? You have like Greece and all? For most things,
I sort of have to gather the pieces together or I can't remember. I see. So you are a victim too.
In that case, can't you just give up on this planet?
Sonic? Are you being serious? Yes. I think it's worth considering.
I can't back down. You should know this. My family's destiny.
That stuff again. Is that Charles from Red Dead? It is. Same actor. That's not gonna work. I mean,
Sonic? Will not back out. I will follow your orders, but I do hope that you will back out.
Future? Can you see it? I'm not sure. I must go. What's the future like? I will tell you when I
get back. Make sure you come back, Sonic Juice. Next time, let's try some peach juice. Yeah,
I would. I can't do psychedelics. I would never do it. I like to be close to.
I don't like the idea of being able to be potentially disconnected from reality. I feel
like I would have a panic attack. I think I would have a meltdown or something. I don't know if I
could do it. No, I don't think so. And that's okay, right? That's completely fine. I don't
have to do any of those things. I know the things that I know that I can do and I can handle.
Obviously, I don't want to make sure I'm not like get hurt or hurt myself or something in the
process, right? You want to even with something like that, like marijuana or alcohol, you're
going to be careful. You don't want to just like walk up and fuck your head up and shit. And, you
know, think about I think about how many times or people, you know, have you heard of somebody
that like, you know, you drink too much, right? That's that sucks. That sucks. All these things
come with potential consequences. Just to be careful. All right. Do I have enough to do this?
I definitely do. All right. Do I care about health or damage? I feel like I'm whooping
everybody's ass. So might as well dial that up to 100. Nice. What's the best way to lose weight?
I really don't know. I've never been in that position before where I've had to.
So I'm not the one that can answer that question for you. I have enough to do this.
Oh, I don't have enough money to buy these calories in calories out. Yeah, I was. I mean,
if I were to try to do it, which I'll be honest, probably I'm probably gonna have to do that
because I like slingshot of myself. I lost a bunch of weight a year or two ago,
all the medical bullshit. And then I gained it back. And I tried to get like on a program
to get it all back. And then it kept going. And then I kept going. So I went from 129 or
I think my lowest, I was 128 pounds. And then I went from that to like 145. And I was like,
all right, this is perfect. I'm done. I did it. And then like a couple, like three or four months
later, I looked at the scale and I was like, holy shit, I'm 163 pounds. How? When did that happen?
Like I went way too far back and way too far forward. I gained like an extra 10 pounds in
like three or four months somehow. So now I have to kind of eventually here, I got to do the pull
back where I get a little bit more physically active, some more weight training, maybe very
lightly, but it's hard because kind of chest and back problem that I have. It's kind of a pain in
the ass to exercise for more than a few times because I'll exercise and I'll be like, okay,
cool. That was a nice workout. And the next two or three days, it's like, oh my God, I can't even
move. So it's actually kind of hard to do that, but I need to get to doing some light stuff.
Maybe like kind of doing an elliptical or jogging or something just to drop a little bit of the
weight. I'm back down to like 155, 150 maybe I'll be happy at like 155. I will. You used to be so
yoked. Yeah, I was, I was, I was, I was an absolute stack of shit like 10 years ago. So I get to be
that person. Now that's like, Hey, you know, 10 years ago, you should have seen me. I never
didn't know what that was going to be like to actually say that. But now here we are.
That's a weird feeling. This is versus the Sonic guy. This is number three, right?
The number three ranked assassin is Sonic juice, Sonic occupation, demon God. He is known as who's
right hand. He's like the one you to foos Liu Bei. He's even called the one you of space.
Let all your madness out, Travis. Welcome to the garden of insanity.
As long as you're healthy. Yeah, that's the point. I never want to go too far or too,
too low, right? I want to go kind of something be somewhere in the middle.
But like, look, I still, I still want to enjoy, you know, oh, I'm going to go eat out. Yeah,
I'll take her. I would love like a fucking nice big like juicy cheeseburger.
All right. Also like, you know, I would enjoy I'll take like a grilled chicken salad with some,
you know, fresh greens and stuff. I just, I don't want to have anything off limits to myself.
Right. Okay. I only have the heels. You're going to look like a boxing glove soon. I'm trying to
picture what that what you're trying to say. And I'm having trouble. Because what does that mean?
Like top heavy and like big, big, big up top and small. A boxing glove is just big all around.
Big. Remember, you have really long teeth. Can I have one of them?
The day that I like sell a tooth to a viewer is the day where I have truly it's truly over.
It's just over. And it's time to pack up shop and close the door. All right, let's do it.
Oh, it's this guy. He's actually always inside of that thing. I didn't even know he was in there.
This is taking way too long. How long is this guy going to walk? Just be patient. Oh, it's so damn
long. He's probably tired. For real. This is fucking long. He might be injured. Isn't this
just a huge waste of time? Just chill. Okay. We start getting antsy. We lose. What the fuck is
the point of this? He's just fucking with us now. Right. He's getting closer. This is actually
starting to freak me out a little. Is he smoking? These are bong rips. Who's doing that? Oh, it's the
cat purring. Oh, the slowed down music. This is like a high scene. Gene, it's time. Sorry for the
wait. I'm fine. But the younger gamers don't like waiting for shit. And that five minutes probably
caused a lot of them to scrap this game. Yeah. Good point. Hey, young gamers. I'm terribly sorry.
Young gamers. You don't have to go that far. And you've probably got in cold standing out here.
Don't worry about it. I've hated the sea since I was a kid. That's all.
Look like a warrior. So even earth has some good soldiers too. I'm no fucking soldier. I'm a goddamn
killer. Anyone getting in my way gets killed. I'm a passing assassin. I like this area. You don't
look like a bad soldier. Either way, if you're going to take us down, you must be pretty tough.
Fuck head. This ain't the pub. I didn't come here to shoot the shit with coworkers and have a few
beers after work and go home. We're going to fight to the death. Let me ask you this. Why do you want
to kill me? If you're going to fuck up my town, I don't give a shit who you are. You're my enemy.
So I got to kill you. That's all. I'll be honest with you. I don't agree with fool,
but because this planet is evil, it must be conquered and rolled over.
But for some reason, I'm unable to find the roots of evil in your people. Join me. You may be a good
species. Join me and together we can destroy the sea. I'll never join you. Even if that were indeed
the case, I cannot deny that I am unable to ascertain the point of fighting you.
What's he got to say about it? Who do you mean by he?
Ah, you mean this. I got no idea how this works. It is an avatar, a physical and a robot.
It is an avatar. Wait, he kind of looks like avatar. Okay. I think I get it. Is this an avatar joke?
Kind of don't know then. Let us negotiate this. No need for any of that. You just get the fuck out
of this town. You willing to back off? That is going to be rather difficult. Fool is terrifying.
If I were to disobey him, my entire species would be wiped out. Airbender. No, like avatar,
James Cameron avatar. A place as beautiful as this. This world was purged. It's civilizations
decimated. Left with nothing but a legacy of death. I guess that settles it then. We're
destined to fight. In that case, let's do it this way. I am no good with action type stuff. So
let's do this RPG style. Oh God. Why not fight in the genre of our liking, right?
Speak for yourself, buddy. I'm all action or GTFO. Now you're trying to push your own preferences on
me. Allow me to demonstrate my power. Encounter. Ah, yes. God. Right. This is how we fight. Hey,
what the hell? I can't move. What the hell is going on? Oh, come on. You're a gamer, aren't you?
I shouldn't need to explain this to you. My beam katana won't fucking move. It's gonna be a turn
based fight. Legendary water. We got to attack with command input. We really we take turns attacking.
It's an extremely fair way to do battle. Oh, I don't like this. So this is RPG style, huh?
Maybe break my damn controller. So what? So you don't know what you're certainly behind the times.
Nope. Even if they I'm not going anywhere near it. Are they bleeping? Why not? What reason could you
have to be so stubborn about it? This must be Final Fantasy. They bleep in Final Fantasy.
You know, you're right. They look so what? I had been totally blind to that. I never noticed.
You know, but what I think really hard about it, I think it did sort of feel that way. After all,
I mean, all the revolutionary technology paired with the sheer branding power that is
is couldn't face the reality that the characters look absolutely. Well, don't beat yourself up
over it. It can be two things. Everyone and their mom shitty. And at the same time, the characters
do look shit. Nobody's at fault here. Not even designs are at fault. Wow. This is I feel like
this is like a shot take here. Looks like you really are a crazed psycho killer. After all,
this is really suit of 50 ones Willy Wonka Castle. Like this is everything. Follow your lead
off to the world of RPGs. Okay, so here we go. Let's go. Juiced has not yet noticed. Are you
serious? Okay. Fight, fight. Two damage. That's it. Building power up. This one looks tough.
Okay, what about item herb times 10? Run. Can I just run? You can't run away. I wasted a turn.
Shit. 65 damage. All right, hold on. Magic. Fire. Blizzard. Thunder. I'm gonna try fire.
Fire. Not enough MP. What? Sonic juice special attack. Legendary water gun. I don't have enough
MP. That hurt a lot. Is it battery? Summon. No, not yet. Charge. Oh, okay. Do I have to
do anything? Building up power. Okay. Magic. Fire. What do you mean not enough MP? What are you
talking about? Where's my MP? Okay. How about summon? I'm just gonna summon somebody.
Bahamut is off on vacation. Sonic juice special attack. Legendary water gun. I think I just have
to hit him. Fight. Summon. Charge. Okay, fight. System window? Wait, I can attack? Wait, come
back. What? What the fuck is this? Are you serious? Okay, that's funny. But wait, I don't want to do
that first because I'm able to see what I'm doing. 150 damage. I have herb. All right, item item item.
Take an herb. 1000 HP restored. Okay, cool. Sonic juice special attack. Legendary water.
I'm gonna attack the thing on the left first because that's info I don't really care about.
360. Summon again? Summon. Knights of the round table. The round table meeting has gone into
overtime. I still have plenty of health. All right, fight. I want to kill this thing. All right,
that thing's dead. But I want to be able to still fight. So if I get rid of that, will I?
Wait a minute. If I get rid of this. Oh shit. If I kill this, will I be able to move?
I wonder if I just kill this, I can move around. Try a different magic. I don't have MP. Blizzard.
I don't have MP. Sonic juice special attack. Legendary water. Dry thunder for a clean machine.
Oh yeah, let's try thunder. I can do thunder. Your beam cannon is overflowing with power.
Shit, all right, hold on. Try attack him? I'm gonna kill the system window. Attack doesn't reach.
Fuck. Wait, what? Can I do thunder again? What should I hit with this? Him? Oh, that's a critical
hit. That does damage. That's 700 damage. Okay. I don't think I want to kill the thing on the
bottom. If I kill the command window, can I even attack him? I'm gonna try. We'll see what happens.
Whatever. I wonder if it lets me move around. Okay. Yeah, I'll heal.
I don't know how much health I have. Let's see. Um, probably like 1,400?
All right, what happens if I do this? That's enough of this JRPG bullshit. Oh, okay.
I'm here on out. We're having a boss fight. Now I can move around.
Yeah.
Let's go. We're gonna push it to the limit. Oh, limit. So this is the power of light.
Let's go. I hope this song is an absolute banger. You know what I mean? Oh, that hurt.
Where is it? Fuck. All right. I got to time that better.
Fuck. Dodge better. There we go. Oh, that hurts.
Can I kick him from here? Nope. Okay. That was a bad idea. That hits him.
One punch man. There it is. There's the dodge. Can I get him here? I can reach him from here.
When he leans in, I can get him like that. All right. Good. Let's go.
Can I hit him with anything else?
I don't think so. There it is again. Go. Mustang mode. Oh my God. It's unfair.
It's so unfair to get this at a boss. It's a whole phase gone. Oh my goodness. What do I do?
Whoa. It takes up the whole screen. Get up. I don't even know what movie is doing.
Oh my God. Okay. Don't die. I just got a free phase. It's gone.
Left side. Stay all the way up. Jump. What? Oh, you got to go in the middle. I get it. Okay.
Let's get in there. All right. Two and then in the middle.
I missed. I'm in a good shape though. I'm fine. That wasn't a perfect dodge. How?
It is an MMO fight. All right. I got to get perfect dodge. Come on.
Oh, fuck. I was trying to dodge through it. All right. He's slow. No, get in there quick.
Please. All right. Don't fuck this one up. That one's easy to avoid.
All right.
In the middle. He's almost dead.
Get in close. Come on. What is he saying? Homey testo. All right. Is it? He's done.
That was a cool fight. I liked that one a lot actually. That was really cool.
What? I submit. I give up. I cannot fight pointlessly any longer. Begging for quarter,
huh? So even aliens have that sort of thing. There are people waiting for me on my planet.
I cannot die yet. Fine. You're an interesting guy.
You fucking dick prince. You're getting soft assassin. You can't beat me like that.
You're too soft. Wasn't that your friend? I've forgotten about all that old stuff.
We're in different positions now. Whatever. Let's settle this here.
Yeah. Who's who? Looks like we've got the stage all set. Bring it.
What the fuck is going on with her?
She keeps being upgraded every time we see her.
What happened to three? What happened to two?
Those eyes.
I borrowed it. A certain benevolent third party said I could use it.
Here's the copyright related stuff. Thanks a lot, your son.
With that kind of technology, I could have come to this planet without full armor.
This play of Slot Air enters the final act. Round and round, Travis. Go round and round
this hell of battle. Go round and round and round again. Oh, I almost forgot. It's time
for my beach yoga appointment. Sorry. Gotta go. Silvia, I need to talk to you.
Eyes are gone. Give me an S. See? That's too bad. The thing about this game that we're realizing,
spoilers by the way, if you don't know what we're doing. This whole list was just here for a joke.
None of this even mattered. That's kind of funny to me. Like, oh, the top 10
cosmic assassins. It didn't even matter. That's not even who we fought. More than like two-thirds
of the time. That's hilarious. You fight only like half of them, yeah. So I'm really just kind of
wondering what the last arc of this game is going to be then. If this game's entire storyline here
so far has been Suda 51 just doesn't give a shit and he's going to do whatever he wants,
what happens at the end? I have no idea what they're going to do. I have no idea what happens.
I'm more interested in what the last boss fight is even going to be than anything that we've done
so far. Like the story of what happens at the end is more important to me than that entire game.
There's probably going to be like three or four people that kill each other in a row.
We're going to get the dollhouse lawyer joke except in the actual game. It's going to be
a pog ending. Oh, sorry. I bumped you. Very curious. Everyone's just a lawyer. We're going
to get overstimulated again. Don't talk through the intro. Ranking the chair at the same.
Noah makes me cave perfect. He's even good at period pieces. Here it is. The big three period
pieces. The best one has got to be 13 assassins, right? After that, it's ninja kids. Harakiri,
death of a samurai is a masterpiece too. The casting is amazing. Who's this cool ass Japanese
dude? Yeah, Takayuki is great. That sort of instability is awesome. Takayuki isn't acting.
He's swimming in the sea of imagery. Kubota is going to go places too. Kubota? From Katai
investigator seven? That's one good looking dude. Is that the medic? Yeah. He's awesome.
But Nobuaki is hella sweet. Not enough can be said about Mieke's delinquent movies.
He totally gets the fine line between delinquent and Yakuza. Let's give credit where it's deserved.
Our standings for the world of grownups. He really burns depth and fear into his imagery.
Fuck, Mieke is so awesome. For real. It's a bad chill. I haven't even started over your dead body
yet. I'm gonna go outside real quick. I will, let's go on record here. I think that any voice
actor I've ever heard, I think Robin Ackendowns is the absolute best. He's got the best exclamation
sound. No one comes close. In the entire industry. I'm not gonna be able to do it,
but that like, whoa, like whoa, like no one, literally nobody can do it but him.
He's got the best exclamations in the entire industry. You know the one I'm talking about too.
His yelling and his exclamatory way of talking is just unbeatable. He's the best in the English
VA scene. Yeah, I would say he's probably up there in the top five at least. Top 10 without a doubt.
All right, let's change the clothes here. I feel like this is gonna be one of the last,
this is gonna be one of the last t-shirts. Let's make it count.
I kind of like this one. That's the new one. Are we gonna need anything else besides that?
Hmm, put on the fuck racism one. Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think so. Yeah, this is the one.
Yeah, I think we end the game with this. I want some more color. I want like reds, teals, blues,
Robin's egg blue, bright green. All the t-shirts are like just white with black.
It's just a white t-shirt with like a black print. I want more than just white t-shirts.
I have to find them probably, right? The ones that you just get for doing the game.
All the t-shirt aliens, I need to find them. I want like a bright orange shirt,
or like bright yellow or something. The boss t-shirts are all white with black logos.
Ah, that makes sense, yeah. Well, this is different. You got a mail from someone mysterious.
Okay, what is it? Order of the Emerald Knight. Wait in the motel parking lot.
My cross sword craves your blood. Once you're ready, come out to the motel parking lot.
Uh, okay. Let's check on bad girl. Hey old man, I got a bad feeling. What is it,
you gonna tell me my fortune or something? If you were a getter, then I'd believe you,
but anything else is just bullshitting. I got no idea what that means, but this town is filled
with evil. You better watch your back. Whatever may come, I'll protect this town. You don't have
to worry. I just walked around that room like it was Resident Evil 2. Seven viewer Andy. That's
because I don't stream long enough. Do you understand? I turn my broadcast on and turn
it off in 30 seconds. You're not going to get engagement that way, Travis. Um, do I want to do
this right now? I guess. Yeah, let's do it. You should do a one minute stream. I've thought about
doing that joke before where I turn the stream on and turns off in five minutes, but I mean,
people's notifications don't even come in that it's just awful. This just fucks up everybody's
timeline. Battle is all about rhythm. If you can pick up on certain rules and signs, you could
leave your body to the rhythm and simply let yourself dance to it. But even so, you know,
having a brother like you, it's fucking embarrassing. You retweet asshole. How many times must I say this?
I saw a movie about God and it just flowed through me like electricity. I realized the
anguish of having such a good for nothing little brother and came to the conclusion
that I have to stop you. Yeah, no thanks. Quit getting in my way with your personal bullshit.
Hey, do you remember? Nope. Listen, little brother, it was a snowy day. We three siblings
made our escape from our serial killer father. In TSA, he watched the movie Thor and joined a
cult because of it. And you were crying as you ran. We spent days and days in the woods.
We built an igloo out of the snow to escape the cold. We had finally found our way to a major road.
Those huge cars moved in and surrounded us. We heard the sound of the rocks. The adults,
they took us and they tied us up. After that, I lost all my memories. I had them overwritten
with those of a child born to the cool down family. So fucking what? This is something you
got to bring up right here, right now? Right here, right now is exactly why I bring this up,
little brother. You were always crying. Keep on crying as you live, as you always have. Now,
keep on crying as you die. You really turned out fucked up, you know that? The fuck is all this
dark side bullshit? Before worrying about me, first kill that ass white. He's not my time.
This sword cuts like no other. Let's go. You fucking prevert. Hey, well again,
motel parking lot. Perfect. Fuck him up. You can't even get out of my 30 hit combo, buddy.
No, I'm on fire. All right, phase two. We're going to go into space. I hope not.
Whoa. Okay. That was bad.
Nice bit rate. I can imagine how bad it was.
It's cheating at this point. Okay. That was annoying. I couldn't touch him. Shit. Okay.
I don't have any heels left. Fuck. All right. Just play well.
Good night. I wonder how much more difficult this is on hard.
I wonder if it's going to be one of those cases where it's like way too hard on hard
and way too easy on normal. I wonder. Henry, cool down, dead. You just killed your brother.
This fight was brutal on Carolina Reaper because it's two more difficulties after you beat the
game. Right? This is horrifying. Oh, smash brothers.
That's not what I was talking about, by the way. And that's what people thought I was.
Okay. Well, so that counts as two.
That is great. Yeah. Just one left. Prince fool is waiting.
The hell is going? She lives here? Once all this fighting is over, will you listen to me?
I need to talk to you. You're right. I will think about it. They're married.
So now I have to go to a food tower. Oh, no. Okay. Are they clones? Okay. Wait,
that was the whole episode? Man, the runtime on that one. That's quite a short episode.
That's not the standard 22 minute runtime. That's the non-standard four minute runtime.
That was half of an Aquatine episode. It was filler. Non-cannon filler. That's so funny.
I hope that's accurate. Someone just said, uh-oh, budget's running low. Be careful. You know,
if I were a game company or a media company, I would make the last two episodes first. Wouldn't
you? They do that sometimes. Yeah. Like make sure you get the whole last two or three episodes
done with a ton of the money. And then you cut, you know, then cut corners when they're like
having tea in the laundry room, right? We don't need the budget for that one. I'm sure they do.
I hope they do. Most writers start at the ending. Yeah. But does this production start at the ending?
Not a lot of times, but maybe not. But you're just going to bug out here.
This shit is going to get recalled. What? Am I stuck in the bathroom?
Huh? Iwasaki? Oh, you're not there either. You got to keep the saber-related stuff in working
shape, man. Who the hell debugged this shit? Don't tell me it was their checks are way too
lax. Should have gone with. Okay. Wait, this is no bug. You assholes. Are you Henry's buddies?
You dirty fucking cosplayers. Wait, I can't fight in the bathroom? What? You screwed up.
Piece of shit. I told you as your older brother, it's my duty to kill you.
It's going to take more than this to kill my ass. That's good little brother.
We just killed him. What? Page 99. Three lives left. Okay. This is Death Man. This is the beginning
of the game. He was talking about this game that he played. This game I played. It's called Death
Man. Oh, he died in one hit. I gotta be aware of that. Good thing I had blinking so I couldn't get
hurt. Oh my god. You die by the spikes. Okay. That's good to know. I can't hurt that guy.
This is cube? I think I have to collect them or something. I thought that was a pizza. That's
cool looking. Okay. Oh, it's death. Where's death? I love the Sega Genesis sounds, though.
Death. What's that do? Death. What the hell is going on? Oh, geez. All right. I need that sword.
All right. Kill. Well, all right. I like this game. This game's fun. All right. Hit him a couple
times. What the fuck hit me? Drop it. Give me the sword. Dark Souls 2 hitboxes. No, don't get hurt.
There's too many enemies on the screen. I gotta clear. Oh, how much health does he have?
Oh, fuck you. Give it to me. Shit. Got him. All right. I think this is just, it's scripted.
You're supposed to get hurt. Okay. Who are you? A passing assassin. Well, a dead assassin now.
Welcome to the world of death, man. Let us raise a glass to death. So this is the land of death,
huh? Okay. I'm not even going to try. He's unmatched. Looks like something from an 80s
arcade game. What hardware does this run on? A death drive? No, I can't. They're not even worth
it. You can't imitate like literal gold. It's impossible. Here, take this. What's this?
Blood wine. 100 year old death emperor wine. Enjoy. You got any beer? I don't have kids drinks here.
Okay, fine then. Cheers. Congratulations, Travis. You're an uninvited guest here.
Return to the piss smelling world from whence you came. Right on. Send me back. Let's give him his
head cut off. If you die in the game, you come back to life. That's not the joke. Hey, anybody
there? Hey, I'm still alive down here. Somebody give me a hand, huh? Hello, anybody there? I'm buried?
Grave keeper! Somebody! Seriously, I'm gonna die! Let me out! Help me!
Wait, not even buried? Just sitting in a cement casket? Yeah. Thanks a lot. Wait. Seriously.
I was buried, okay. What a pinch getting buried alive. For reals? You're- My name is Miike.
You're a friend of his, right? Mr. Miike. Miike. You're reading Takashi Miike.
Are you shooting something here? Are you finally making your Hollywood debut?
Andromedia 2. No, that's not it. Ichi the Killer 2. Oh shit, I hella wanna see that. Real person
Omegalo, yeah.
I've got a request. Do you mind? What is it? I'd be happy to do whatever I can. Could you film
a live action version of No More Heroes? They're not gonna do that, are they? No, they're not.
Did they do that? Did they actually do it? Did they do at least- Please tell me they did that.
Do it. Do it! Do it! This is a bit- This game goes up full letter grade if they do it.
Battle was a success. The champ's here too. Welcome back, grandpa. You're here too.
You'll be going up against him next. Do a live action bit, please. And she's here too.
Don't worry about me. My dad took choice with you. Charlotte, the bloodlust is back in your eyes.
Don't call me that. Leave the rest to me. Oh, I don't know if they're gonna do it.
I hope they do. Please. It's about time for the climax. Oh, they don't. That's too bad.
Can you imagine if all of a sudden we saw a trailer for No More Heroes?
SSR. SSR. SSR. Wait, don't write it off yet. We're not gonna show it.
What was the point in killing him? Yeah, I don't- What was that? What even happened?
How bleak. It wasn't that long ago, but it somehow feels nostalgic. It feels like it was years ago.
Give it up for Travis. Humans aren't all bullshit after all. He's no representative of humanity.
He's just a street punk. Why do you hate him so much? Netflix. I hate punks. They're violent,
evil psychos. Kind of like you, Fu. This is my fight, but it's Travis's fight as well.
As fighters, we understand each other somewhat. But you, you don't fight. Oh, Damon. That's right.
I have nothing to do with this. I was simply dragged into it all. Think about it. Why would
Travis come here? Was it a coincidence? He's, because he's an assassin. No, you brought Travis
here. You wanted me to do it. To kill Travis. I never asked you to do that.
We're connected here. So I wanted to fulfill your wish for you. What? For me?
The final battle. Watch it up close. Watch as Travis dies.
He wants Fu to die. This is like WWE. Yeah, but Travis beats up Damon in TSA. Skipped TSA.
From a window. This game doesn't feel like it's about anything.
Master, I'm sorry for the trouble. It's cool. Let's watch some movies. Today, we're doing a
Miyake and Hideaki viewing party. So, how are your arms doing? Slowly but surely, I'm getting used
to this sensation. I can't hold my sword just yet, though. No need to rush. I want to hurry up and
help you out. What do you like, Shinobu? What do I like? I like my master. It almost feels like
Suda51 was told by his parents that you can dress yourself today. It's like what this whole
game kind of feels like. Like a little kid. It's just insane. There's a bunch of combinations that
don't make sense next to each other. You got your dad's like size 10 shoes on.
Barbados swordplay. Wearing a big styled peacock hat.
The broadsword action. And how this blouse is on. It's like going down to your knees.
Four pairs of underwear on. The right way is the way of the sword.
Times like this. Miyake and swords means blade of the immortal.
Immortal? Love the original. I'd like to watch that one. Please show me the film.
Everything just so mushed up together. There's like no rhyme or reason to anything,
but somehow there is. You can play Death Man in your room. Oh, cool. This is way too deep for you,
bro. I'm afraid to save the game. We get a pee break? Yeah, we'll do a pee break. It's been
about two hours. Do I have any money? Oh, I have enough money to do this. I'm going to spend some
of the money and then we'll take a break. I'll be right back. I might get another coffee too.
I'm only a coffee mood right now. It's so funny because this game, there's probably been a few
times where I could have told you I didn't like something in the game, but I can't tell you that.
It's weird. It may have been a handful of opportunities where I really could have been
like, yeah, this is like this. I don't like this part, but my vocal cords and my lips cannot tell
you that. They can't speak it to you for some reason. I don't know why. Oh, I think.
Hmm. Let's just dump it into the cool down. It's not in his programming. Oh, okay. The real thing
that I could tell you, which is just like, holy shit, this looks awful, is a lot of the graphics
really do feel like they're from like the Wii. It just feels like a Wii game a lot of times,
but like who cares? Like I really don't care. It's not a problem to me. Okay. It would be a
problem if the game slowed down a shit load and if it ran at a terrible frame rate or something,
and if it actually impeded the video game, I'd be like, wow, this sucks.
I don't really don't care. All right. Let's take a few break. I'll be right back.
Give me like two, three minutes. I'm going to make another coffee. Back in like a few minutes.
See you soon. Hello. Hi. Oh, I fucking fell in. What did you fall in? What did you fall in?
Oh, hey, who's in the, hello, who's in the bathroom? I'm in here.
You've been in there for a while. What'd you fall in? Let's chant. All right. Let's get back to it.
This is the final, probably last half an hour or so of this game, I would assume. I don't know.
I am ready to play. Oh, I just did that. Stop doing that. Make a convention about yourself and
call it Germacon. I got like fucking shit faced one night and I talked about rent out a whole
section of one of the casinos here and we're going to have a convention. I literally made that
reference. Uh, no, that just didn't happen. All right. Congratulations on rank two. We're
coming to inform you the entry conditions for the next battle. Uh, $60,000 is the final amount of
money you need. So designated matches are where exactly? Anywhere? Just any of the ones that I've
done already. Where is that? Um, where is who's castle or whatever it is. We're here. It's two
here. I think I can just do them anywhere then. Where am I? All right. So there's a couple here.
Well, let's do that. Let's do the one here too that I haven't done yet.
You recorded stream. Got me. What is, what is this thing you guys are writing?
Women want me. Fish want me. What, what is this? What's this a reference to? I don't get it.
It's just a case of unfunny spam. Okay. Um, streamer just told you to do something.
So I, I suggest you fucking do it. I said, stop. Streamer literally just told you to do something
and fucking stop doing it. Mods started it. Really? Monka W. Start the game. Monka W is
not a chant. It's a face. I'm sorry. Monka W is not like, it's everybody collectively in the
stadium. All going like, Oh wait, if it was Monka W it'd be imagine it was like, Oh, look
out the stadium. The stadium is doing Monka W right now. There's a bunch of people that
the whole stadium is just doing that. That's not a chant. An expression. The game is very loud now.
That person just got sniped by your own teammate. You guys can't even work together.
Verbally chanting Monka W. Why would you chant Monka W? Monka W. Monka W. Monka W. Monka W.
It'd just be like, what the fuck are these people doing? Oh, suplex machine. Isn't that
somebody's actual move in wrestling? Suplex city. This guy's almost dead. This guy's a huge pain
in the ass. All right, come on. Kill the bull. Nice. What was that move? Oh, nobody does German
suplexes. They did not do them anymore? Do they not do German suplexes in wrestling anymore?
Brock Lesnar does them all the time. It's too dangerous. Come on. Swing. Swing. You're too
slow. I don't like slow enemies. I have no health. I don't like slow enemies. They're hard to predict.
Fucking die. Stars. Yes. Invincible load activated. You can't hurt me. Funny because he showed up
yesterday in Smackdown. I didn't see what the rating was. Was it good? I was looking at chat.
You still watch wrestling? I do not. I used to like wrestling because wrestling to me was
a cartoon. It was superheroes fighting each other and just wild outrageous shit going on.
It was never supposed to be real to me. It was always like almost theater in a way.
In recent years, wrestling has tried to be a like taken as seriously as baseball.
So it's like I don't care. And yeah, I have heard that like AEW is do watch AEW watch AEW. I know,
but I think I'm probably just kind of over it too in a way. I gotta go that way. Which way am I
going here? He's a jaded old man. WWE is still hitting record profits. I mean, I didn't say
that you should not watch wrestling and it's not popular and everybody hates it. I just said the
reason why I used to watch wrestling was not because of the fact that they were wrestling.
It was like Ken Shamrock being locked in a cage and incredible hulking bending the bars like
Superman. It was Mick Foley being three different people, even though you knew he was just one guy.
Oh, there here comes Cactus Jack, a dude love. They would, they were two different people,
but it was literally just him being three or four different characters. It was like the promos,
wrestling promos. Some of them were so good. They were some of the funniest comedic actors,
like theater actors you would ever see. The magic's not there for me anymore. I think the
promos are eh. Nobody's intense anymore. Like people, it's too, I don't know, it feels like
too real life to me. The three stooges. Yeah, it was very much like slapstick comedy for me.
The last great promo machine was the rock. Yeah, it was. Got enough costumes. Yeah, I,
it was fun to have these superheroes fight each other. Just think about it. The inherent,
inherently doing like a special move to somebody doesn't do anything, right? Like, oh my god,
his finisher, the tombstone pile driver. What's the difference? It's literally you're dropping
the guy on the same mat, but they were supposed to be like superpowers. Oh no, he's doing his
finishing superpower. Now, when you take that like kind of weird costumey theater out of it,
I don't care if you have a superpower. You're just a guy with a speedo on. Like that superpower
does not hold the same weight for me. It's like, oh no, here he comes. Here comes Jeff Anderson
with his superpower taking you to the bank. I don't, you're just a guy. I don't care. Like
you don't have a superpower. The undertaker could have a superpower because he was the
undertaker. The guy literally would like raise from the dead in the middle of the ring. And there
was a fat guy on the outside who was a showman that had an urn that pretended that he was like
had power from whoever was in that urn. He was like a dead guy. And you knew it wasn't real,
but you didn't care because it was a fucking show. It was like theater. I'm going to die.
Whoa. Like if, if like Dave Anderson came out with an urn and the Paul Bearer character,
it'd be like, what? This doesn't, you, you, you can't be both at the same time.
You didn't care because it was entertaining. Yeah. It was entertainment.
I've never got Travis before. Oh yeah. Oh, that's awesome. Have you ever watched Lucha Libre? No,
I have not. I've seen some of it and like they're fucking fun. They're entertaining. I would love
to get into that because correct me if I'm wrong, but they still treat it like it's a big grand show.
Right. I kind of just don't even know where to start. All right. Hold on. I'm like not even
paying attention. I'm reading chat right now. Were you WCW or WWF fan? I was both. I liked them both
for different reasons. There was a time you can remember where like Hulk Hogan, like Macho Man,
they were in the WCW. I remember people like throwing fucking drinks into the ring.
You guys remember that? When Hulk Hogan went heel and people were literally throwing fucking
objects into the ring, like sodas and drinks and trash and shit. It was insane. Like never before,
Hulk Hogan became a bad guy and everyone was like, people were like crying in the stands.
It was crazy. Okay. This is hard. Remember the chairs? Stop throwing chairs. Yeah. People
were throwing chairs into the ring. I got to get this Mustang though. Let me pay attention.
But the point is it was really entertaining television and I know, look, I'm not going to
talk like I'm some, oh, I don't understand what happened. A lot of that shit was dangerous and
people got hurt. There was a lot of problems, you know, drugs and potential like performance
enhancing like steroids. Look, I get it, right? But it's not fun for me anymore.
And I know that you kind of have to, as we, you know, learn about how things are dangerous and
shit, like, yeah, the early to mid to late nineties. Oh, whatever. Just take a bunch of
steroids and pile driver people. Like, yeah, I get, I know that's like, you can't really do that
really anymore, right? I got to get a Mustang mode. Hold on. This level actually is probably
harder than anything in the whole game so far. I got to get a Mustang mode. All right. Here we go.
This is when you get it. No, this is where you get it. What the fuck? It's nothing because you can't
heal anymore. All right. I got to go get heals after this Japanese wrestling is still wild.
Yeah. I just, I don't know. It doesn't, it's just, it almost feels like there's no weight to it
anymore. Okay. This guy is invincible. So that's not going to happen. Apparently Jesus. This guy,
Jesus, this guy, this guy, man, Jesus, this guy, this guy, man. All right. This guy,
like this guy, really this fucking guy.
All right. Give me some, I'm getting out of here. I'm getting healed. No, I'm not. Okay. Here we go.
Last try. Don't let me down, dude. Got it. Okay. Let's go. Yeah. I have to get one slot effect and
I will win. Just need one. Come here. No, there it is. All right. Mustang mode. I'm just going to
spam X. Come on. Mustang mode again. Do it. Get away. Get away. Kill this guy. I got to kill the
other guy. This dude in the back here. All right. Now it's just me and you. I can actually do this.
Let's do it. All right. Perfecto. Let's do it. What? He was stunned. No. He got out of the way.
I had half health. You got to be kidding me. Why is this guy so, this is the hardest thing
in the whole game. This dude has an instant kill moves. The end of the PS5 game announcements.
I have not paid any attention at all. Let's go. I need to get actual heals and not just
walk to the boss fight with zero Estus flasks. I would, you would, I would never do that
ever in real life. Okay. Give me all this. Good. Thank you. Thank you. Appreciate it.
Okay. Bye bye. Spider-man 2 PS5. I still have to play the Miles Morales one. All right. Now where
the fuck is this thing? Where was it? Where was that fight? Isn't it over here? Yeah. Right here.
It's already marked. Let's go. Oh, wait a minute. I need to turn in. Yeah. Hold on. I got to turn
in the cards. I have a bunch of cards and I have scorpions. Say Lala right now or I will shit your
pants. Nice. Thank you. The best part about that guy is I don't know for some reason he thinks he
can like shit my pants. So he's going to like, he's going to freak out and be like, he didn't do it.
Now's my opportunity. He's going to shit his pants. Like thinking he like, he's going to cast a spell
beforehand maybe. And then he's going to shit his pants. It's like, mom's going to come in and be
like, what are you doing in here? Okay. Scorpion. Cool. You could have that as a superpower. Would
you want it? Um, what? To make people other, to wait, to shit in other people's pants as a superpower?
Um, no. Nope. You know why? Because, okay, if I was like, I'm going to make that person shit their
pants right now, there's a probability that I'm going to potentially be in their vicinity, right?
But do I just pick somebody that I, oh, I'm going to pick someone I don't like today and have them
do that? You would have to get, what, annoyed with somebody to a point where you want to use that
power, but you don't want to sit on the train with them. You know what I mean? Like you don't
want to be in the same spot as them. Why would you do it? That'd be like, I don't want to be around
that and don't use it. Yeah. I wouldn't want to. Did you ever do a Bloodborne stream? No, probably
not. I drank a few beers. I don't drink beer, but you know what I mean? You get the idea. And I
loaded up Bloodborne for like an hour one night. I've beaten that game like 15 times. It's just not
much I could even get out of it anymore, especially on stream. I don't, I would, no,
probably not. One of my favorite games ever made, but you know, nice. I didn't take off any health.
I have to wipe these guys out. These orbs are going to kill me. I feel like I'm not even hurting
these guys. All right, back it up. Oh, invincibility mode, just capitalize on it. I don't think it's on
anymore. Oh, crazy. Perfect. Get it again. Again. Again. That's it. No power replenish. I want to
heal. Where's this guy? Where's my heal, dude? What the fuck? Did I buy power replenish things?
Where's my heal? Oh my God. Oh, that was like a, that was like a Ricky out. Oh, no, I don't.
Where is my fucking heal? There it is. Finally. 40. I have to get a perfect dodge. I don't even
attack unless I get it. What are you doing? How's the automatic attack missing? Oh my God. I hate
this guy. Oh, he's dead. Fuck him. I watched season five of Rick and Morty. I don't, I've seen every
episode. I just had to see what I had to see. It's by far the worst out of all the seasons,
without a doubt. I think maybe to one episode I was like, I don't think it was very good at all.
All right, I'll be quiet. What the hell is your deal? Hey, no, mine. This is a sort of ritual.
Also a contract. I have something to give you. Here. I'm doing the Mr. Kennedy from
Resonable 4. What's this? Had it made for you. It's a mechanism of death. One befitting of you.
Wasn't this the guy that got ran over on the highway? Yeah. Simply turn on the switch when
the time comes. Stewie Griffin. Fine. There's no risk involved. No effort required. Most importantly,
there is no hassle. You could say that all it requires is anger and hatred. Can you do the Joker?
Awesome. It's not Trump. Trump and Stewie are in the same, okay, Trump and Stewie sit in the same
Venn diagram of voices. It does. This is Donald. You know, it could be. This is Stewie Griffin and
Donald. They're in the same section. They're in the same spot. This is awesome. This death is in
my hands. Look at that face. Yes, you hold death in your very hand. Don't forget. This is a contract.
The guy who spent $100 on the Family Guy mobile game. Yeah, I am not going to tell you that I did
not spend at least $50 to $150 on Family Guy the Quest for Stuff like six years ago. I did. It
could have been any other show or material. It didn't matter. The Family Guy didn't matter.
It was the act of the dopamine from playing the game is what did it to me. Why? I don't know. I
just did. I don't know why. I don't know. Okay. Golden. Gold scorpion. Family Guy whale. That is
not a whale. No. $100 in a mobile game is not a whale. $5,000. $10,000. No, it was like $60.
Are you a whale for buying like Gears of War 3 for $60? No. You bought the Mario Party game
last year for $50. Are you a whale? Whale Cope. No, it's not Whale Cope. A whale is like at least
$5,000 to $10,000 in a game. It's not like $60. Look, I saw $60. I'm not even looking at the game.
Ouch. It's a free dress-up game, you idiot. But a whale constitutes that I am one of the
sole reasons for the game's continued development. I am one of the sole reasons for that game's
financial... When they do their quarterly results. No. $50 is not a whale. You can't convince me
otherwise. I should do some of the actual jobs. Oh, lawn mowing. Definitely. You're a whale. I'm
not a whale. Okay, if I had spent like $1,000, first of all, I would never have even told you
guys that. If I spent like $5,000 in a free-to-play mobile game, no one is going to know that.
Besides my credit card company. Why would I ever tell you that? I'm not going to tell you that.
You guys are just... No way. What about Hearthstone? Yeah, how much money have you guys spent on
Hearthstone? Some of you that have played it. That were playing years ago too. How much money
have you spent on Hearthstone? If I'm allowed to spend $50. If I'm not allowed to spend $50
in Family Guy the Quest for Stuff, you're not allowed to spend $4,000 in Hearthstone.
Volunteer level one. Ask your viewers from 2018. Not us.
A Hearthstone. A Hearthstone. A Hearthstone Adventure. Remember that one from 2018?
You remember that one? Remember when I did that? Remember when I thought it was really, really funny?
I do. This mind is decaying. No, it's not. It's evolving. Turn. Turn. All right. This is going
to be at least silver, right? Silver. Gold. Yeah. Silver. Watch Chris Angel Mindfreak on stream.
Something funny about Chris Angel Mindfreak is somebody that lives in Vegas. When I first got
here, they're like, oh, what should I do? Should I watch a show? I wonder, is there something I
should do on the strip? Chris Angel's Mindfreak live show, I believe at the time, had like a 1.2
out of 5. It apparently was one of the worst shows in Vegas. I remember reading reviews and being
like, holy shit. People said this show was like the fucking worst thing they've ever done. It's
like, wow. A ton of the reviews were just like, this is a waste of time. This sucked. I was like,
oh my god. I'm not doing this. I have seen Penn and Teller though, and they were good. They were
cool. That was a really nice show. Penn and Teller are actually good. Penn and Teller are
fucking legendary. I kind of base my opinion on somebody based on what they think about Penn and
Teller's magic show. If you watch Penn and Teller's show and see some of Penn and Teller's
greatest routines and you yawn during that viewing, I'm never calling you again. You're
getting ghosted for the rest of the time that I know you. One of the greatest routines that you'll
see. What an absolute joy of showmanship. I don't want to ruin it for you. Maybe I will.
No, no, no. Why would I do that? No, it's cool. If you haven't seen Penn and Teller's greatest
routine in my opinion, then mute the stream for the next five minutes. It's one where I
can't even tell you. Here's spoilers for Penn and Teller's magic act from like 1986 or something.
I believe it was on SNL. It was on an old episode of SNL.
Are you ready? Here we go. If you don't want to hear about Penn and Teller's greatest act
then mute right now. Here we go. Penn and Teller did this thing where the camera was just on them
and they're just kind of standing there. They're doing all these weird things that
seem impossible. They're like letting go of shit. They're like having stuff float in front of them
and fly up or fly down. Gravity makes no sense. They start holding shit like a light bulb in the
air and it just is in the air with them. It's just floating on its own. It's like how the
fuck is that even possible? Eventually the camera pulls back and what you realize is...
This is for like five to ten straight minutes. They just play with all these toys and nothing
makes any sense. The camera pulls back and they are fucking hanging upside down with a
fake set that spun the other way to make it look like they were standing up upright the whole time.
And they were upside down for like five to ten straight fucking minutes hanging upside down
and they did it live. It was crazy. Go look it up. You're free to go leave the stream for five
minutes and go watch Penn and Teller SNL upside down bit because you could almost... It's hard
to tell because they think they put a bunch of makeup on so their faces wouldn't be bright red
from all the blood rushing to their heads and you can kind of tell a couple of times after you
watch it a second time where it's like oh my god like he's talking and he's kind of struggling
a little bit sometimes to talk but he did not miss a single beat. Penn Jillette did not miss
a single beat during that entire routine. It's absolute showmanship and absolute respect.
Okay Gramps we get it. No that's a great routine. Penn Jillette the best a man can get. Yeah okay
yeah you guys can unmute. Scream upside down. I love that show. They had a show called Bullshit
Yeah they did. I think Penn still does like he besides the magic I think he still does like a
podcast or something right? Stop hitting things. And then Teller are based called Penn's Sunday
School. Oh my god I'm gonna run out of fucking time. Back up back up back up. Okay I got it.
They are not based. No I didn't get... Did I get money for that? Okay not very much but I got it.
All right that's the long-running side of things all right. Speaking of magicians if you guys you
I remember watching this guy his name is James Randy. Amazing Randy his name. He did this like
he did this talk at some either school or convention or something where he's up like
talking at the microphone and he's coming through the speakers to the auditorium and he's like he's
talking about like you know let me tell you something. If you guys you guys want to tell
me that you don't assume things and he's like oh yeah I don't assume anything. He's like you
already have assumed something. People are like yeah I usually I base my life on facts only.
He's like oh yeah this is not even a real microphone. He's been literally talking at
a microphone the whole time like on stage and he's like you assume that this is a working
microphone and he literally just like puts it down and he's just still talking and still
coming through the speakers. He had like a lapel mic on and he was wearing frames. He had like
glasses on but he was literally just wearing frames. He's like you assume that I need glasses.
I don't have these on and he just pulls them off and everyone like gasps in the audience
and then the person that's like sitting there going like I don't assume anything is just like
oh she got me. The Amazing Randy got me. Where am I going? The dick. No it was cool.
Where is there a job that I haven't done? I don't there's no more out of those missions here. Let's
go somewhere else. Oh there's lawn mowing missions here. Adventure? What is adventure?
Okay what about over here? Yeah let's do this one. This is in where is this? Where is this?
Obidden area. What's the countdown? What's the countdown? Oh that's not a countdown. Okay Neo
Brazil. Randy is great guys. Yeah the Amazing Randy has an awesome series. Remember you guys
remember Peter Popoff? Some of the voices you hear on this stream are based on Peter on Peter
Popoff talking. Oh let me get the devil. Why don't you just want to make the devil mad?
Like that's that's a guy that was like a televangelist and the Amazing Randy set up like a
audio sniffer in the guy's auditorium when he was like healing people and they heard the guy's wife
coming through and like telling people to point people out in the audience and be like oh this
person has arthritis in their knee. Tell them that they're talking about their arthritis
and he just he walks around he's like oh god is telling me over here somebody
somebody has some arthritis and they zoom in on the person's face it's like oh Mary Mary is
your name Mary god's telling me Mary with arthritis and she like stands up it's wicked
fucked up it's wicked fucked up the lady actually says into the microphone like into his earpiece
it's really like scary she's just like hello Peter I hope you can hear me if not we're in
trouble like we can't like manipulate an entire audience of people it's so fucked up yeah that
was James Randy he exposed that yeah the audience like filled out a survey card like I think it was
supposed to be like a personal card or something like a party that like it was supposed to be
given to anybody and then it was handed to the the wife who then in turn like fed it through his ear
because they like collected personal information about people beforehand or something
oh my god um this is what happens if you don't look by the way this is also back like 20 years
ago so I don't know obviously all I remember from Peter Popoff is he came back at one point
after this he got like exposed and then came back and started doing the miracle spring water
he would send you a little tiny vial of water that you were supposed to like drink and like
you might get a call from god and it would put money in your bank account
I wish I was making this up I this was an infomercial I used to watch this infomercial
and like like laugh at it because it was so absurd it was like all you have to do is just call and
get your free miracle spring water that is still on yeah and then they would like I don't remember
like the exact nature of the shit that they were doing or pulling or whatever they had these people
on tv they were like I can't believe it I woke up one day and there was $6500 in my checking
account it's like what what are you wait what happened I'm gonna lose this one get up there
no it's over restart restart restart it just restart it no just retry holy shit I got all
this time back come here oh my god trolls too hello other people who watch the Penn and Teller bit
hey what's up atheist Andy I don't know nowhere in the bible guys does it say to like
fucking get people in an auditorium and like scam them oh but it does I don't look I
we're not gonna get into religion here today okay let me just let me just kill this guy
quickly change topic by doing a savior renegade angel impression I don't know I don't think I
can't just do that I need to have been ready to do that I did like a couple days ago whatever it was
no I'm normal before I could talk to him and say that I was normal maybe he would believe
what I was saying what you wanted all right let me pay attention I'm ahead of him got him oh there
was something I wanted you guys help with it was a reference or a sound bite or something that I
wanted to I wanted to bring up to you guys because I couldn't figure out the origin what was it I
hope it comes back to me I'm gonna lose again oh my god this mission sucks okay um
well do I even need to do this I could have already made 10 grand at the time it took me
to fail this three times no not scrumptious cake I'm gonna give this one more attempt and then I'm
done do the drift I feel like hitting the break would be bad beatbox babam battlefield oh you got
it okay you have to hold both okay I get it let's double tap them
all right now I can drift I'm gonna get bronze but I don't care I just want the money
I just want money okay oh my god stop fucking already are you a smart fella or a fart smell
time that person up for 10 seconds that's actually really good I'll do the other one
there's gonna be level three right no oh shit oh enough shit oh that's a problem we're really
done with that one I think it's one of the first viral videos on YouTube really get ready three two
one go way better theme song rather than the one way I mean like a hundred times better theme
song than the other one they have now not that I don't like the new one I just think it's got a
little too much going on in it a little too many particle like sound like notes like too many note
particles
stop how would you kick me out of midair get over here these stupid man champs I swear to god
what's your opinion on pulp and orange juice remove it immediately
because guess what I can't tell the difference between pulp and bugs and I don't want to have
a bug land in my drink one day and not know because this pulp in it nope sorry I need to
be able to have complete examination skills to see that there's no bugs in my food or my drink
disgusting get it out I hate these guys like these guys are so fucking irritating
they just jump around invisible and then dash at you really fast like that I okay nice perfect
dodge but you see what I mean like fuck that like figs I do now oh this is the part where
this is the part of the conversation where you tell me you're like figs well yeah there's bugs
in it there's bees in it there's wasps in it this is the part where I say I don't care because I
know that there's bugs in it I know that there are bugs in my food when I eat things I don't
expect there to be bugs in my food when I drink orange juice so if there are bugs in my orange
juice it's a huge problem and I'm dead because of because of you I want that person timed up
for at least 13 14 seconds oh never mind that person can stay so you'll eat a fistful of worms
because you know you're going to eat them um if my plan was to eat worms that day then I would eat
the worms because I was gonna okay look here's a handful of worms eat them if I make a like a
tuna casserole I don't want it to want to be worms in the tuna casserole because I'm not expecting
that and I don't want that if I wanted to eat bugs I would eat a bug this concept apparently
is incredibly difficult to understand you sure defeat a total oh I got a burger burger I need
another red mission fighting mission that's not one where's another red fighting mission
maybe here perfect world or oh maybe the thunder dome call of that all right I'm gonna go to call
a battle this is the ugly place but whatever what about if you didn't know that they were there
until after you ate it I would be pissed and disgusted like everyone would do you eat a
hamburger made of bug paste no but your children's children's will oh I've talked about in the on
this stream multiple times I'll like I better be aware that like we're gonna be eating bugs
unless we can make sure unless we can sustainably be able to keep this shit going
uh you looking at bug sandwiches oh my god let me just over here what the what the fuck suda
suda what the fuck I want to just go over there all right is this red it's a red mission red is
it a red mission oh suda suda it's not even red where's this one more red mission somewhere
where the hell is it I need blue I do no I need red red's the big one right hmm yeah I need red
check this way perfect world okay I'm gonna go perfect world what's my favorite color
um that guy aqua teal teal is my favorite color is this one red missionaries have red
missionary we're just a couple of missionaries somebody just said oh here we go it's time to
play name that reference that's not what I'm I told you I would be doing this if the stream was off
some of you guys have to understand that I'm not trying to like oh are they gonna get it
I'm not that's not the goal oh here we go time to play name the reference where is this where is
this mission suda it's probably over here shit oh there it is no oh my god is it red no that's
not even there where is this there it is and it's red it is a red missionary friendly minor reminder
the germa would have finished paper mario by now no I would not have give me the dodge give me the
dodge is it okay anti or anti what do you say anti or anti anti-gravity anti-gravity
for me it's anti anti-gravity anti-anti watch it
no come on andy yeah lock on andy yeah nice job like lock on andy pay for mario andy
shower super kids don't d don't call one d i'm kidding
are you gonna play destiny 2 pvp why would i do that let's be honest you're likely to see me eat
a frozen pizza uncooked on stream then me play destiny 2 pvp i'm out of heals
and
most sly cooper too hold on wait wait wait wait a minute wait i don't die
okay um you guys know the rule in the channel so far at this point i think if i talk about that
i'm gonna do something and it does not happen within two to three weeks or let's say two weeks
and me bringing it up it's never going to happen there's a fine amount of time before you're never
going to see the thing i say you're going to see and that's probably at the very maximum probably
30 days all right i got it naked gun 55 and a fifth now that series is unbelievably funny if
you haven't seen the naked gun series go watch it now female convict scorpion jailhouse 51
off below 51 baseball no here's the thing all right here i'm gonna baseball was supposed to
happen last year but cove had messed it up so that's not my fault we're ready to go and then
this year the dollhouse took a lot more time and work to actually get that to happen so that took
over the summer and then baseball season is really only playable for like the next two or three weeks
before a lot of these places shut down the year baseball is guaranteed to happen most of it is
already paid for most of it's already ready to go we just need to have the right season and right
time frame that is going to be one of my favorite streams i've ever done it just will i know it will
but it might need to wait until like early spring of 2022 and make no mistake about this we have
already started working on the next like two or three large major projects with the channel those
are not going to reduce in frequency so don't worry working on it let's see the end of this game
60 000
time for the ranking battle head to daemon tower i'm not going to do that yet i'm going to go to
santa destroy i'm going to go and uh upgrade my last upgrades and buy the things and maybe change
the chips one more time too are there going to be any more big streams for 2021 uh maybe if everything
can be said and done i'd like to have a holiday like christmas special well that's kind of what's
currently in the process right now so yes i would like to i turn this i have another scorpion right
end of the year awards yeah that's obvious that's still happening too all right i need
to go back to my house where is my house where is where is my house oh here we are behind me
i miss bugleberry when is he coming back i don't know i have no idea it's up to him oh by the way
speaking of bugleberry uh if you remember on the bugleberry stream i said that all the money from
that stream that came in i was going to pay the people that helped work on it right and then i
was going to do just kind of give match it and give the rest of charity so the idea is i don't
want to give you an exact number because i don't know i forget what the exact number was but it
was more than i think 7500 total or like more than 5000 well maybe even more than 10 000 if
what i remember uh but i'm gonna split it up and i'm gonna give it to i'm gonna give probably like
half or a little bit more to uh i don't know if you guys remember that um that science center in
nevada the people that helped us do the geology stream so we're gonna i'm gonna give it a
significant portion to them and then probably another bit to um uh one of the humane societies
out here there's a couple in nevada so that's the plan that's gonna probably happen in the next
within the next week or two probably that's the plan for that money because i wanted to make sure
i was going somewhere where i wanted it to go i didn't want to i didn't want to just pick like
a random spot for it to go because i mean i could have and that money did just come in um this
previous month's payment period from twitch so uh i wanted to really get on that oh right i'm
going downstairs you still think warrior where's gonna happen oh absolutely yeah it's probably
only like another 20 to 30 minutes of this game which would take us to somewhere around four
hours and i'll play warrior where for maybe like another hour or so hour or two i just want to
make sure i tell people that i didn't just forget about that that like oh whoops i didn't do it
oh no it's gonna happen all right so this is my probably my last upgrade what should i do what
do we got that's kind of that's really cool but i'd rather just go straight up just massive damage
i think let's just kill the last boss very easily with a maximum damage output
yeah actually can i afford it no i think that's the last thing i can afford i'll put it towards
this level 10 attack do i have enough money to buy the good sushi the dining one i do all right
well let's refill all this there's five heels and then i'm gonna buy the really supercharged dining
go check this out great what we got how do i still not have this cannot create because i
haven't discovered the other power thing oh wait a minute wrestling attack power plus 20
percent not bad okay these are new at least this one is oh shit normal attack plus 15 percent but
heavy attack is not even worth doing death kick guys wait i know i don't have enough
i can do one of these i like the heavy attack though death rain is better 20 i don't like
being that low i think i already have one of these after getting back up so when you get knocked down
that's actually insane during slow down after a perfect dodge wrestling attack power is up by
20 percent these are the defensive ones i almost feel like it's just make the normal attack power
really good these are all defensive i already have two of these on right now 50 faster charging
all right what about this one no yeah i think i'm gonna go for it i'm gonna do uh where is it
i like that too oh yeah i'm gonna do more damage death kick no there dyna chip there it is
normal attack power plus 15 yeah i want to just gotta remember that i'm doing it
i'm putting the attack power ones back on yeah all right let me see what i got because right
now i have the the slow after a perfect dodge is way longer weapon attack power plus 10 yeah let's
put this one on so this is 10 more damage now it's at 25 more damage what's this chip what's
this one do no no no no uh trigger chip all right i want the normal attack power one yeah all right
now i've got 10 20 i have 45 percent more damage with a normal attack i'm just gonna shred anybody
that i even see it looks good to me let's go check on um on shinobu she's not here why is
she not here it's 35 percent that's not weapon attack power 10 normal attack power 15 10
fuck it is 35 shit i thought it was 25 all right let's see the end of no more heroes 3 it's time
are you ready are you ready so we need to go to daemon's place uh daemon tower is here wait how
do i get there how do i get to daemon tower right on the highway oh daemon tower okay all right
cutscene incoming climax of the whole game see what happens transform or maybe not oh shit
all the henchmen strawberry right off let's move now this reminds me of the first game
it's like the line of enemies that you just do do do do
oh you're still alive bit rate bit rate bit rate
am i dead wait what did i die what happened oh i thought i got killed i'm gonna kick you in the
nut yeah i forgot about that i'm gonna kick you with a dust
it was always really funny when those clips played back to back to back to back
just a random number generator on what audio file to load i'll kick you in the nut i'll kick
you in the nuts i'm gonna kick you in the nuts okay all right dude do i have enough money to buy
one of the good uh sushis have i do have enough i can buy this one increased greatly increased
health attack power intention for the next fight yes i have a feeling on the really hard difficulty
modes these you have to probably eat these before every fight all right let's go and daemon i love
you so you actually made it all the way here more pleased than surprised to think that there was a
shining pebble in the rough of that trash planet after all you're that shining pebble
fucking diamond and that's quite a huge disparity you just can't stop talking can you prince dumb
do you really fear me that much what the fuck you say fear what the hell is fear anyway
i can't even comprehend the emotion you call fear no seriously tell me what is fear
that's sad didn't your mommy and daddy teach you it's not nice to cause trouble for others no
cause trouble and you'll get scolded but nobody's ever scolded you before have they
my daddy scolded me once i was punished and was sent to rodent space prison black hole prison it's
basically paradise that wasn't punishment you just went on a nice little vacation abroad
and that's how we get prince dumbasses like you yeah just keep talking keep fucking talking
go on get angry you fucking loser get all nice and salty for me
there we go those eyes right there the dumbass is turning into a beast
oh kill you kill you i'll kill you oh nice scary eyes that's what i want to see
oh that's the thumbnail
kill me demons don't got shit on me kill you you're getting real fucking crazy now
that's what i'm talking about
oh god we're just going oh my god okay i got so much power look at this damage
i can't hear him holy shit he has a he's a bubble up
i can't hurt him this dude had a bubble up oh looking good oh shit that's bad
no it's not i have so much more health than him hey he's got the shield back
anti-gravity don't do heavy attacks that's my mistake i shouldn't be doing it
i can't dodge i can't even move i can't do anything
god damn it oh the slow time thing doesn't work on him i get it you can't use it on
yeah you can't use it on
anti-gravity yeah you get he doesn't when time is slowed you can't hurt him
almost at phase two let's see phase two oh yeah can you even turn around
oh fuck what's this oh my goodness what do i do run away oh fuck what's that do all right
i'm hitting him with my auto attack thing it's funny why can i hit him come on say something
funny how do i get him to drop his guard you have to i think it's a perfect i think i have
to perfect dodge him this is bad i think that's what you do i gotta ask you have to get a perfect
dodge eyes yeah but how do i close his eyes like hide
disintegrate oh i got him to close his eyes the last time i perfect dodged him twice his eyes
fuck i didn't do it
yeah i don't understand i can let me get a perfect dodge if i can just at least get one perfect dog
i'll be able to wait they were close okay his eyes were closed maybe in the middle of when he
does that combo he doesn't go there it was yeah all right so you can only hit him okay
his eyes are still open can't hurt him that was a good trade okay that was a good reason
phase three incoming i have no health
what oh all right he's in phase three i gotta be careful this on hard would probably be so bad
whoa
oh i can't reach up there really close those all right that should be it probably gonna be
like another complete phase here we're definitely going into space that's definitely part one
oh god what shit i have no heels what do i even swing at
oh he's got his hands come out i don't know and i hurt his hand
oh fuck this camera
okay you can hurt the hand not drop this punch me punch me punch me oh my god punch me
you
all right this is not bad
okay where is he oh fuck he hit me right with his nails
shit oh no i gotta catch him in the slow motion ready watch this and
what come on
all right well slow and steady he's almost done i don't have to hit him in the hand i can hit him
without a forearm now that's that's good to know all right one more of those i'm out of health by
the way and now what oh here come my friends all right phase two what does he do okay just the same
thing all right same thing
nobody said what a boss well hold on a second i'm just literally phase two
i'm gonna go through all this and get one shot if i like the last phase it's gonna be so
disappointing because i have no health rechat please what no i can't like rechat right now
what's up
when you see spark dodge it'll make it go faster i just walked no now it's just more annoying
shit this is gonna be annoying
oh should i kick it oh no i'm gonna die i'm gonna die the last phase i already know it
i don't even fight just dodge there's no reason to even fight this
don't get hit just go away in a second after one more rotation all right there we go
do these lasers stay for the last phase this phase sucks where's the hand
this imagine having to do this on hard it would take so much longer i know that i could probably
oh what happened
he finally did it go champ how come no super huge end of the world end of the game villain
gets to this point and then decides to just leave you know what i mean like if you're at phase four
and you're still getting hit and you're like about to die and stuff just like okay stop talking
almost speaking
i'm good oh look out yeah that was pretty challenging that was hard imagine doing this
yeah i oh yeah i did it's definitely another one he's wide open now's your chance here we go
oh we're gonna have to go i get him oh dead by clothesline i don't buy it i don't buy it yet
end it with a brain buster
leaving
i love you damon i love you damon love you damon i loved you too fu
goodbye fu now fuck off
what the hell oh that's too bad apti's family secret treasure so he's finally dead
nice work travis so this is what it was all about looks like my hunch was right
you you're a friend of his right his friend are you kidding me that crazy alien bastard was just a
pawn i'm the real king i see so the real scumbag is you then i totally missed that it's all you
travis you you you hit me didn't you you hit me not even my dad has ever hit me
oh okay so you're the asshole who forced juvenile out i remember now now it's my turn to hit you
travis thunder break
dsa lore all right we hit him we punched him in the face and and travis strikes again and
it came back and it got super alien mutant powers now we're gonna get a go-go power rangers sequence
nobody told me about this what the fuck is happening hey that glastonbury thing call it
that's been decommissioned too much dark matter and deteriorated okay then what the hell do we
do now juvenile please do something about this i cannot do anything right away if i had around
two years i could help that's not gonna work no more heroes move it the dead cage is going off
it is transferring something over from another dimension transferring transferring what some
sort of unknown huge object starting countdown it's not a monster or something is it we get one more
monster or demon or whatever and this town is screwed yeah more like this planet three two
one here it comes any second the transfer is complete an arsenal roll-off model has arrived
what is this the mech from damon x machina from the japanese publisher marvelous an arsenal
and is the roll-out model the model with the same coloring system as the glastonbury
trevis hurry up use it i got no idea what the hell i'm doing but here is a crossover
oh god i'm in the cockpit unlock all weapons and fight here we go gene here we go was this
whole game a shitpost probably yeah it was the entire game what this thing is huge it's the credits
oh it is the credits it's the credit sequence okay quick time event credits what if i fail what
happens what i stabbed him in the chest oh i okay that was interesting where the hell are we
the edge of space maybe even the promised land nice place for a final showdown
we've come so far the train keeps going on and on forever it's over travis looks like this is the
final stop we'll settle this with sumo sumo like japanese sumo wrestling yeah real men settle
shit with sumo my god fine now for the final transformation start the game the final game
it's a smash brothers reference are you fucking kidding me are you serious he didn't get into
brother so they made their own end of oh my god
hold on do i have my all my moves still knock him off the stage let's go
oh you should be full armor mode let's go do i have it and she where is he
oh that did a shitload final smash that good ravis confirms the smash
i'm taking this game is fucked this game is just like i don't even how do i even how do you even
give this game a rating i don't want to die i don't want to die i don't want to die
i don't want to die i don't want to die i've still got somewhere to go home to but you you don't
i don't want to be sure to apologize to juvenile and have fun hanging out with prince dickhead in
hell i'll be honest they're not making another one of these i don't know how how why how would
you make another one this is the shotgun blast of all video game genres and all no more heroes
how do you even do another one of these so to said this was the last one
i mean this you can't have another one yeah that was um that was hilarious you end the game on a
smash brother's joke even the final boss fight was a joke yeah this is way different than the
other games the other games were jokes in quotes and jokey and weird but like somebody said this
entire game is a shitpost like i just like blinked and i was in my bed reading like our shitposts
like whatever the top post was and it's definitely after credit scene i'm not going anywhere
it's kind of sad in a way because i don't know i like i like this character and i like this
universe it's funny interesting it's it's i mean the gameplay might be pretty similar to a lot
of stuff that you know a third person sword fighting action game where you dodge you dodge
enemies i love this like concept it's really cool i hope this is really not the end of travis
touchdown i would i would play another one of these you know it doesn't have to be immediate
right even if it was just like an action game and you just did like another one of the i don't know
it's sad to see it go but it was it was great all right nice place for the home run king huh
working old buddy fucking dying on me like that i was never able to say this but you always looked
so cool hitting home runs you always bought me marble fudge ice cream after your games i actually
wanted coffee flavor but you always assumed that a little kid would want marble so i never said
anything tsa skipper feels nothing here i own no more hero i wonder if the game keeps going
because i got money at the end there another after after credit scene is completionist stuff
yeah i imagine that's t-shirt t-shirts and collectibles and other fights probably on muck
still gonna get to level 50 and warrior wear i'm gonna try maybe gotta warm up to it though
yeah it's been four hours i'm not done i planned on at least spending like an hour or two in
wario where let's see how it goes i don't have to go far it's just the menu and then second tile
but i am gonna go pee though we're gonna take one more break after the credits gonna see what
happens this game meet your expectations um i don't think it could met could have met any
expectations because the game was so outrageous and just unlike anything that i thought there
was ever gonna happen with the game that i don't like i said i can't get this game a rating
i would say it's definitely worth playing and it's definitely probably the most fun and interesting
in quotes of the three i think the first game is a better video game but i think this is a better
experience worth playing out of 10 yeah that means at least it sits somewhere in the seven to eight
seven to nine area it was great you said it was a 9.8 on the first stream no i said 9.4
i didn't say 9.8 this game feels more like a novelty yeah it was almost it was almost a big
toy that makes any sense it was a big watchable cartoon toy that i could watch and play which is
just a video game i just described what a video game was is okay that's stupid yeah it's this
digital uh digital toy where you see and watch what's happening on the screen and you control
stuff yeah like a big digital toy a video game it was basically the paw patrol movie give it a
number i can't i love this song though this song is like a nine out of ten um i don't know because
it it changed directions seven or eight different times each one of the boss fights was its own
encapsulated joke that was taken away from the rest of the game so i don't know it's hard to
even tell us tell you what this was all right let's see we get yeah the only thing i can tell
you is i really liked it it was very good i very much enjoyed the whole time here all right here
we go okay i have come to this world as a divine messenger who's dad huh well someone kills your
kid i guess you're gonna get mad hold up now do not jump to conclusions i have traveled
vast distances to come to this planet earthling to enter into a peace accord
representative earthlings do i fucking look like it on that case it would appear that peace
negotiations have failed what wait a second at first you gotta talk with some actual representatives
and then under baptist interplanetary law i hereby seize the planet earthling
do it uh damn who the hell are dad it's me have you forgotten what your own kids look like
what a shitty dad hunter and gene is that you who master's children the twins wow you guys have
gotten big they're from another world wait a second hunter and gene is it really you
we came from the future there's no time to explain just look at the situation mommy i took out every
single one of them good boy scott dad let me introduce you guys skippers this is jean's son
scott this is your grandson i didn't mean to hide it but getting to fight you i was so happy
you're so tough grandpa hold up this is like the actual final for reals ending what the hell is
going on somebody explain this to me this feels like one of those like quick history videos is
not over yet your next opponent is up to the north we came from the future to kill uncle henry
that cosplaying dickhead killed you and is counting down to this planet's destruction
my great uncle teamed up with some super messed up aliens and was attempting to conquer the planet
so we have to change the future come with us come with us otherwise you're gonna die
oh snap welcome travis to the garden of insanity next up family war
oh snippety snap all right suda you want to how you make no more heroes four and you make it funny
and fun you can do another one make it a party game just make it a four player like mario party
game that's that's how you do it perfect i would love a no more heroes universe no more heroes four
s just jokey party game and you can throw all this crazy lore in there you can do all kinds of
weird shit so he said if he does continue it it would be in like 10 years also like this one
every 10 years he gets he just gets the itch to be uh insane which i can respect i respect it
all right there's the higher difficulty i want to see the shirt oh every 10 years he does acid
all right let's see all right so we have some new clothes here yeah oh i like that purple
no more heroes too yep is the original what about shirts i gotta get the jacket off there he is
death man uniform of dia burger burger suplex yep that's the one i want
that's cool all right that was really cool new game plus you can make the game really hard
let me just take a look and see what happens what looks like i would wear the
baptist shirt i would love i would love a foo shirt it's just him pointing like a lightning
bolt into the camera you know what i mean that was cool i love the concept too okay you know
when a concept really just grabs you and it's really interesting i love the the alien that
lands with the rocket ship and they did that little intro he turns out he comes back 20
years later and he's just like oh i'm coming to take the fucking planet over that's cool
uh it's you know it fits in a trope somewhere but whatever i think it's cool i liked it a lot
speed run the game on carolina reaper yeah because how do you do a no more heroes three
you just make it aliens and you make it superheroes and shit that's it was great
two thumbs way up very good now hold on a minute
forbidden area does this ever did this ever open up i already beat it right i already did it i don't
know all right let's move to wario where i'm gonna pee it's dlc i didn't even think about that
maybe there will be dlc huh it was cut from the game i wonder if there'll be dlc probably not
though well if it's there i'll play it yes they had three three dlcs oh shit all right well maybe
we'll play it all right uh i am gonna go pee i'll be right back we're gonna open up wario
where for like an hour or so and i'll play a little bit more i'll be right back