Okay, I have returned. I'm ready. I do before this this sponsor segment gets started
I do want to put something on real quick because I heard
Somebody said to watch this and I don't know what it is
So but I actually have no idea what this is. I was told to watch it. It might be loud
So just turn your volume down a little bit. I'm serious turn your volume down
Oh
I'm back. We're about to begin. Make sure my title is correct. And let me maybe tweet. I
Have a tweet I'm gonna do and then actually I can probably just do this right here. Gotham Knights
Where there you are?
All right, let me tweet. We'll get this started. Oh, I completely forgot that I live tweeted the entire who be Halloween movie
And I was in my drafts. It's like it's like five paragraphs. I forgot about that. We'll talk about that probably tomorrow
All right. Let me tweet this
Okay, let's go. Thank you Warner Brothers for sponsoring this a segment of the stream
This is Gotham Knights and I am ready. I think comes out soon
Mara right that accurate. Yeah. Thanks Warner Brothers. Seriously. Hey
Warner Brothers has been like an unbelievable supporter of this stream. So
Let's give it a try see how it is. I'm gonna play this for the next couple of days
Let's go
That's fine. Oh, I think subtitles are on very easy. Very easy. All right, if the game is on very easy
Do enemies just kill each other, right?
Like what do you just kind of walk around do hard hard hard hard hard, please hard hard hard. All right fine
Geez, I don't think it'd be too hard. All right, I'll do it. Yeah, I did these settings already
Okay, here we go
The fragment video file. So is it the apparently is open world. Let's find out the fragment quiet
Shit, no, that's not the right. You're watching this. I'm dead. Fuck. I've actually fucking pissed. Hold on. What the fuck
You're done you and I was that
Your disappointment
Whoa, whoa
And you're trying to fight this war and for what
Corruption still flourishes in Gotham lurking in every shadow. You don't need that mask. I know it's you
We shall cool your love this blasphemy this sacrilege. Did you think you could keep it from me?
Get a Batman smash a microwave on his head
What is that
I'll deal with you myself
Except us the Gotham nuts wait
What is that t-rex? I just did that. You saw me do that and then the other thing we just played. Oh
Wait, he's got powers like that. Oh
Look out Batman watch out
I'm the most annoying fucking person in the movie theater. Oh
What doc doc?
All right. Well, that was quite the opening
What his arm? Oh, I thought that man's arm fell off did it. Oh
You'll be dead before they get here
Your precious family. I will slaughter them one
By one that thinks he can beat Nightwing in a fight. Are you stupid when they have drawn the last breath?
What a stupid asshole. I will burn the city to the ground
You won't get a chance
Gotham is their city now
Wait, where the hell are we?
Where is this? Oh, they did they just get here?
Like a fucking meteor hit there
Incoming transmission. Okay, if you're watching this, I'm dead. This is a code black
This message was automatically triggered when I destroyed the cave and everything it contains. Oh
Shit, this is the arm
That's this is like a will know what's coming won't be there Nightwing. I know you always liked the car
You're gonna have that
Bad girl. I know you are as a big fan of my computer setup. I'm gonna give that to you
Wait, he's not a prepared for it as best as I can. I know you have to though. He's dead. Sorry. It's come to this
Oh my god, I
Wasn't looking at the shadowing both. No, it won't take long for Gotham's criminals to realize the batman who trusted us since Jim died
You get to drive cars in this game
his base of operations
Some of the technology is outdated, but it has the gear you need and all of my files
It's just chaos. Oh
Many of you knew Bruce from Gotham's celebrity pages a handsome charming billionaire
And he was that my stocks. Oh, no
Batman stocks tanking. He wasn't my nephew. He was a friend a mentor
And a benefactor to those of us gathered here today and to those of you who didn't know him as we did I
Want to tell you this?
Bruce was Gotham. He loved this city more than he loved anything
He was a protector to this city. He worked tirelessly behind the scenes to bring justice and
equality
There's nothing he wouldn't do no project. He wouldn't champion
If he thought Gotham would benefit and I think in remembering that we remember Bruce as he truly was
He's huge. Yeah
I'm getting engrossed in the story
Are they doing the bat symbol with the umbrellas? Is that what that was?
You've always had my back at you and goodbye. Well, I don't want to be right here
All right, let's get to it. Look what I got. Bye. Look what I have on. Hold on. I'm losing my
That's my window closing. Oh, there we go had it off the screen
I was offered what you'd expect in three years to agree to a vacation and Bruce turned up dead
He asked for some time. He knows none of us were there. Am I doing that? I feel like I'm doing that
What about you you let take a cane give the eulogy?
He offered lights off
He thought it'd be easier on us if he was the one to do it
Lights off. All right. He's Bruce's uncle
All of a speech let talk about a protector who works behind the scenes
He only knew
Which would be there if she suspected I can't see the anti. Oh, no, no, no, no, no. No, I'm playing this night when you get Batman's funeral
Here's something else. She doesn't know she has the body of Batman's killer in her morgue
Rachel ghouls listed as a John Doe
Slated for cremation and what if the League of Shadows finds him?
All right, we're definitely gonna be diving to your leader in a Lazarus pit
He won't be so dead in turn the key
I know I have to fix the camera you want to break into the GCPD headquarters for a what-if beam
Let me fix my camera. I think my audio is screwed up
My audio is cutting out. I think maybe my headphones are screwed up. It's hard to tell is my camera messing up
Do you see that something weird is going on with my camera? Yeah, my face is like flashing. What is going on?
Why is my computer freaking out? I decrypted the case Batman sent with his message
We should focus on that. I looked it over but I would I'm playing his night wing. It doesn't look complete
I think race interrupted him while he was writing
He says this has implications that could shake Gotham to its core
deep fried ominous, but not exactly helpful I
Saw a few places we should poke around
Construction sites a quarry. He also mentioned a dr. Langstrom
Anyone know so we split up. He says it won't just at Gotham University. Not sure what is I don't have a spray tan
Let's divide up the work. We can meet at the Belfry when we're done
Get it up and running
Okay, are we ready to rock and roll here? It's the talk to Langstrom. All right. So now do I do I press a oh?
No, okay. All right gifted acrobat rapid combos. I don't I don't need to read anything else
I'm not reading a single other thing Gotham Knights bug. All right, let's go
That's so unnecessary
I'm at Gotham you what's the story so far with this professor?
Sick all right reach Gotham University plaza is open and ready for anything then
Okay, hold a to wait you can climb
And perch okay, I don't look like a Dorito all right, I look like a fucking Dorito give me a second
Let me just change the color there everybody can relax. All right, there we go. So kind of controls like
How does it control it's kind of like?
Think of like a word. It's kind of like um, it's kind of like
my face is
Apparently this gear
Like you actually pick up items I think I have to go to my audio settings my audio is kind of going it's cutting
Out are you guys hearing the audio cut out?
Every so often. It's like if it's like I'm losing it. I wonder why
No, I don't wonder why that's happening to me
Bad news Langstrom is dead any idea where I can find his office a tap LB when you see to grapple
I would not I'd be terrified to do that. That'd be scary
Here we go his office is no
Okay, thank you reach Gotham University Plaza. All right aim so this grapple hook points
imagine doing this
You viewers are open. That's my way in body cam recording
Do I have like a?
Okay, this is a sprint. All right, what's in here? The cops didn't spend much time here. I'm sure I must have died somewhere else
This is all this office AR
Hold to use AR targeting. Oh
Okay, scan the marks on the floor. Okay, I scan. Oh right there Gotham Knights these marks are suspicious
All the trail
We are we all here I feel like this might turn into something you'd like it and I lost the trail
Sorry back girl, I don't know where the trail when I accidentally tripped the alarm
That was you. Can you give me some more coordinates lead stay safe?
You too
This is a lot of damage
Okay
It's on the ground yet
Investigate it
No, yeah, this is coming out on the 21st. So that's tomorrow, right? You get a decent look here. How do I get up there?
Hi, can I jump? Oh, there we go
This is where Langstrom died. You'd think the GCPD would still be all over this lab
There's blood everywhere Langstrom was comes out in 12 hours
Yeah, it's on everything. He tried to get away. Yes 5 Xbox both series SNX
PC I'm on PC right now
Seems to be running at Langstrom spin his final moments rolling toward that cabinet
Seems to be running at 60 try to leave the lab. Well, I think I think my camera is having problems
I think it's hold on a second. Why is my camera fucked up? Oh, there we go hidden mechanism crap. It's a hidden door
What were you hiding? Dr. Langstrom?
As you can see through the wall, that's cool. All right investigate
Tour investing investigate the crime scene search for evidence and uncover the truth
Use L to explore the crime scene with the cursor important items will be identified. All right
Langstrom made specific note of these dates and now I will too 20th and 21st of October are circled
What are the significance of these dates? Well, I mean that's because when Gotham Knights comes up. What if that was what it was?
Is the camera still fucked up? Oh, I know what that is if this movie means Gotham Knights comes out that day
The release date could be significant. Wait that it is
They find what to open the door which input device unlocks the hidden door. The passcode is 0 4 1 1 9 2
The thermostat could definitely double as a keypad the microwave
The keypad is modified with computer parts not typically found in this sort of appliance the display has room for three digits
Okay, let's put the password in oh I can solve it right I'm ready nice fail
How did I fail? Wait, I failed the tutorial passcode is it? Okay. What about what about this beaker phone number?
It's not a Gotham area code. It'd be something. Oh wait. Okay, so I had it wrong
So the password I could figure where the password is October 21 and 22. That's not even what that says October 20th and 21st
This is the gray ghost is in theaters
How many digits is this 1 2 3 4 5 6 it has to be this right because it's six digits
I've never seen a microwave like this before which device unlocks the door. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Ah, I've got it. I've got it Batman solve it that did it. Let's find out what secrets this guy was keeping
Oh, this is something. Oh
Aliens look for evidence. All right
What is this stuff that man's dead professor was researching some real sketchy stuff
Okay
Wait, is that evidence?
Langstrom's desk. Okay, what we got?
Organic material collected from various animals samples seem to be primarily sourced from creatures in Langstrom's lab tanks
Okay fatty tissue from a dolphin
Computer. All right, let's get the password. What's this?
That's a hard drive might have some answers
All right, I got this drive to the belfry. Hey, I think I'm done here
That was so funny quick missed some weird marks in the walls and a hidden lab
With an even more hidden hard drive
Great can't wait to get my hands on it
All right. Oh grapple
How do I do this again?
How do I how do I grapple? There it is. Let's go. I love his weapons. Can I I hope I can fight something right now
Fire alarm. Did someone see me?
How many polygons is on that?
What the why what was the point what's the point what
Oh, no, just one random jobber versus nightwing. Are you out of your mind?
Yeah
It's me
All right, his friends are looking out the window right now going like now he's dead
Oh shit, it's nightwing
Why would you even fight me run run away why fight me i'm a lesson
I'm on it move the icon. Oh good idea up here seems pretty good. Maybe I'm gonna do something real quick. Hold on
This this might sound crazy, but i'm gonna do this for one second
That might sound crazy
Okay
half arc of growth
Gotta stop these freaks from burning this place to the ground. Okay
Clear out all the freaks
I don't know where are they?
Do I have to press a button?
What did I just do what did I just do
So like
You can tell they're superheroes. Okay, you can tell they're superheroes because they do they do like the most elaborate shit
To like knock somebody out
Like no, I got an idea. I'm gonna put my arms behind my back and have my baton
I'm gonna grab by the neck and spin around
You can tell they're superheroes
Everything has to be so flashy
Better to stay hidden
The fume's getting to you buddy
On me
Hey there
Who said that?
Sleep I think you I think that kills people am I undetected still
Yeah time to sleep permanently
My camera's fucking broken
You look insane
Dude, I don't know if my camera is freaking out. It's like glitching
Okay, that was interesting. Well, the takedowns are really cool. There's probably more inside
Enjoying the fire range range attack
What did I shoot lasers out of my fucking eyes?
I shoot all night when he has lasers and his eyes. I don't know he has it
The whole building is burning down
That was cool. Like that was really actually pretty cool. Oh shit hostages. I'm coming
Look at this fellow
Where are the hostages?
oops
Oh
Dude, the flip star is actually pretty cool
I'm gonna die
They keep hitting me directly in the fucking head
Whoa, what is that? She shot him with like a
Oh, no, no nightwing's dead
What I have a heel
What happened? Oh my god. I have a new suit on. All right, let's go
There's probably more I think the feed is losing connection. I'm getting an audio drop every like five to ten seconds
I think it's I don't know
I have to look into that
Am I running out of like memory? I don't know
Well, it shouldn't
Maybe i'll turn our setting down
God, all right, that's cool
Let me turn a couple things down. I feel like um, it's something is being overloaded here
Dynamic resolution. Maybe should I bring this down and be like 80?
Two I wonder what's happening. Yeah, the audio is fine for stream, but for some reason it keeps uh, but
I don't want ray tracing on. All right, let's try this. Let me see if this helps
Yeah, because it's not coming through to you guys, but it's coming through me
Which is weird. So I don't I I don't it's not my webcam
Because i'm hearing the game audio go better make this quick and even one of that when the camera's off
I don't know. You let's see. I'm looking to see how if the camera screws up when it happens. It does not
All right, let's go
All right fire fire fire
Oh, I put it that's right. It's unhard. I was wondering
I was like my god, these fucking freaks are giving me just so much trouble
Who's yelling? Is that one of them yelling at me?
I'm fighting them right now
All right. I'm here
You are unbelievable. Oh, thank you
Appreciate it
If you'll bring two 50 pounds, all right, let's go
All right, you got a shield
Gonna teach me something here
old
X-ray, okay heavy melee attacks and guard break abilities can get through enemy defenses leaving them vulnerable to other attacks. Okay
Okay
bulldozer
You missed how did you miss? That was a shotgun
Shit, don't kill me
Oh shit
I knew I shouldn't have brought the foam batons this time
I could wait what I could can I I can break the counter?
Bailey wait, what's that?
Did I do it?
Oh, all right
Oh, don't kill me. Please don't kill me. I can't lose the tutorial
Oh, wait a minute. That was that was a string. I just did a combo spring
See like they light up my god, i'm gonna die
Just a lot going on tonight i'm heading back now with langstrom's hard drive finally
cool
Called the batsicle. Oh, yeah
So this is this is okay. This is an open world game. So that means I get to drive around
on the batsicle
All right, let's go
Do I get to have a bicycle?
Do people
People like me my is my i'm like is it legal for me to kind of is it am I getting in trouble or something?
I'm sure hey guys want a picture
What?
I liked your outfit. Hey, hey, can I get a drag of that or whatever it is?
What I left oh because i'm on a mission right
Some of your cigarette
There it is
Hell, yeah, let's go
open world
Let's go
What happened what happened what happened what happened what happened
What am I in trouble?
What's happening? I'm not supposed to be doing this. I'm not supposed to be doing this. I'm not a specific criminal
How do I get off?
All right, I didn't I was I didn't mean to do that
I that was an accident
It was an accident
Why?
But do you see the come on? I'm nightwing. Oh my god. Okay, i'm gonna have fun in this game
Okay, let's get on the bike
That's eject
All right. I gotta get I can do a wheelie. Wait, can I just jump off?
Oh, wait, i'm i'm getting mario carted
What happened? I can help i'm a superhero
How do I get off how do I get off this? All right, you need someone to jack you up. I got you
You're welcome citizen
Make sure to always call the batman cadets. All right, i'm gonna go this way. Oh my god. I think like what's on my mouth
Like a piece of dirt was on my mouth
Okay, so don't just drive around like a psycho
Well, i'm a
What the fuck?
I'm a bad guy
They he took it
Get me out of here. Oh, did I screw this up so bad?
How did I screw this up so bad? Ow
I don't why am I a villain?
It's nightwing get him
Someone set our college on fire. What did I do that? I didn't
I promise I didn't set your college on fire
I'm a good guy. I'm one of the bad brick but the bad uh nights the gotham nights
Okay, let's go
That was ridiculous
I can't believe that I was getting shot at
Hey nightwing, what took you so long? Well, you mean
Can I actually stop and help?
Can I actually
This is fun. Okay, so just go through here and hopefully you don't get mad
Ripped why I feel
Why did that guy just do that?
a wheelie
I almost hit my head on the ceiling, dude
Now i'm busy doing a wheelie
Come on. I'm going for the record
Imagine seeing nightwing drive by
Nick you're on the side street. He's doing a wheelie in the fucking gotham copter or whatever. This thing is
Can I wave or anything? How do I do anything?
There has to be a way I can like interact, right?
Oh
Hey, how do I do that? How do I do it?
Why the emotes? Okay. This is I this is funny. I love this
Hey nightwing
I'm having fun
Geez. All right. So how do I get in here?
Reach the east plaza. Can I climb this?
Do I have a map?
Nightwing. Yes
I i'm gonna turn it down a little though. I feel like it's very loud
Let me know if you need if it sounds better
So you can play as any of the four characters that they get any time
I'm just choosing to stay on nightwing. Maybe i'll probably get access to it
You can play as back girl. You can play as red hood
Nightwing obviously and robin
It's sweaty right now
I'm curious about the gear apparently you can collect gear the whole thing is co-op too. So that's pretty cool
Nice work grabbing that drive from langstrom's lab
Do we have any idea?
All right, i'm going we gotta watch this pay attention
Yeah, it's online co-op
I think it's like drop in drop out. I think
Once we can get at the data we can figure out what our next move is
I'm going out. I'm not gonna sit and wait for
Whatever this shit is we're waiting for intel jason
Once we have it
Then we'll go
Uh-oh a little bit of a conflict in the team here move i'm gonna solve this case my way
Stop it. He wanted us to work this together
Whatever that's making this harder than it has to be kid
I guess since we're waiting anyway
We might as well take another look at what bruce had on mainstream
All right, everybody. Uh-oh been hacked
That must have been the secondary breaker the primary went out months ago. I thought the backup would hold I got it
No need
I've put in a small fix that should hold for a while alfred
Wasn't sure you were coming alfred
I'll always be here when you need me master richard when any of you need me. He's so cool
I'm glad you're here as am I master tim
This place does need work
Dammit we've got activity all over the city sweet
Looks like my plan wins
He's he's huge we still need the intel
And alfred can't exactly set this place up alone
Indeed miss gordon
I have a list of supplies we'll need
I could do it on my own, but it would be faster if I had help
You can count on us alfred
We'll divvy it up
Let's finish what bruce started
God give him more lines
Oh
So awesome
Open the abilities menu and spend ability points to unlock perfect evade
Uh, wait, what how do I do that? How do I do that robin? How do I do it?
Hey tim
How'd it go with the quarry?
Not well, I sweep the whole place and didn't find anything. No one's been there in ages
How are we supposed to see the full picture when most of the pieces are missing?
Bruce left us one hell of a last case
I mean what kind of person builds a secret lab
in their lab
Someone who has something to hide obviously
What what was he trying to make and who is he hiding it from?
Yeah, let's not get ahead of ourselves. I'm telling you. Let's wait and see what that hard drive has to tell us
If they sell that robin raincoat
We'll get some answers. Are you shitting me? That would sell a hundred billion things
That would that would sell a hundred billion copies of this like coat that he has on right here
A hundred billion
All right. All right. Wait, okay. This is there's this is a skill tree for each character. I think
Leveling up your character rewards ability points that can be spent to learn new abilities spending ability points also unlocks access to new abilities, right?
So everybody has a skill tree
All right, so I have to get this one
Nightwing performs a perfectly timed evade that generates momentum and allows for perfect attack follow-up
Okay, so it's a perfect dodge and then you can attack cool. Holy shit. All right, well we're getting that
As you continue your investigation each hero can unlock unique momentum abilities use the momentum abilities menu to view unlock conditions and unlocked abilities
Okay. All right. So I got beat down unlocked
cool
So now we have
Did I I think it wants me to like look around
What's this one? I think i'm gonna go down the acrobat tree
Using momentum abilities restores health
Oh, it's damn good
You can chain evades
Yeah, i'm definitely doing acrobat
I'm just gonna do that for fun in front of people
Just like citizens. They're gonna be like, holy shit. This guy's sick
All right
more momentum gain
Grants an extra momentum bar
Okay, versus all defense and resistance by 10 working with allies also grants additional bonuses
Cool is oh i'm gonna see gear
momentum abilities
You just unlocked your first momentum ability
They're unique to each character and require momentum to activate when ready the ability icon in the lower right corner will change
Hold right bumper plus the assigned button
Oh, all right. So let's expect superpowers. So it costs one momentum. I got it. Okay
Exit the belfry and patrol gotham city. Let's go
Yeah, i'll play with i'll play with the other characters over the next couple of days and start tonight's patrol
After you grab an enemy what you can grab
Opportunistic crime
Tap down to display nearby opportunistic crimes. They appear as that's in the hud
Oh, I got a map
Okay
Crimes you discover during patrol can be viewed on the map along with any additional activities you have available place of waypoint
Wherever you want to go. Okay. Cool. You just got you just got it. You just got uh, no that game you just got
That'll be that game
All right. So what is what's going on here? What is this? There's just crimes all over the city
Well, let's go get one
Ooh, i'm just going i'm going to this one right in front of me
Can you get by a train?
You can't get hit by the train, right? Please tell me you
Did you get can you get hit by the train?
Go on drive
All right. I don't think you can I don't I don't know. Maybe you can't
Maybe other people get wait, is that the bat signal?
All right. I need to find some crime
There's a crime going on right there. Oh, they're breaking into the bank. You can't see me. You can't see me. I love it
Okay, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Dude nightwing just chokes the shit out of people
That killed him instantly nightwing. Nightwing doesn't care nightwing kills people, right?
What is all this stuff clues?
Defeat criminals to gather clues
What so I just did it
So that's one crime. There's another crime. Wait, why did they just tell me to something was blinking over here. What was that?
Did I miss somebody?
Oh, this is right here. Okay. Hold on. I don't want to be here
Oh, they're inside. How do I get in? I'm probably gonna drop down. All right, let me go up. Okay. Here we go
Shit oops
Oh
He's got a gun. He has a gun. You gotta run. He has a gun. He's got a machine gun
I'm back
Don't
Nice. All right. That was a good combo
What's my special move?
All right, that's cool
Sorry, what are you saying? I'm sorry. What did you say?
You got something belfry
Key that sounds like it's in his body which is at the morgue indeed with knights in gopham as they are
It should be quiet at the station
I guess I did want to see how montoya was handling the new commissioner. I'll let you know what I find
Right. He didn't want to do it. What the hell that's just get this shit. I thought I was coming to like assassinate me
That was so oh my god, all right
Good luck out there
Crime being committed
Citizen, what are you doing? Oh my god. Okay. What do I do?
All right. I get the car. I understand the combo system now
Pretty good dodges pretty good dodges
Dead
Okay, reach g c p d rendezvous point should I get on the car in the car?
You can just fly around the city. Oh my goodness. That's so high
Is it fall damage?
Let's find out I think I pressed a button can you do anything with the cars?
I don't think so. What is that? All right, let's go
rendezvous point it is
You doing an e3 presentation
I am not. All right. So what am I gonna go over here?
For a second. I thought I just grabbed onto a helicopter. Now. Here's the rendezvous point. Let's see
I'm not eat. Stop calling me e3 andy. It's I i'm
All right, that's him
Remain undetected makes sneaking into the station a little easier at least i'm sneaking into the station here. Okay
They don't see that right?
No, they can't see shit. I'm fine
E3 ernie what they call me. All right, is anybody here? There's one person there, but that's fine. Okay remain undetected still
Oh shit. Okay
I think i'm making like distraction noise. How am I supposed to get over here?
I want to be honest fucking phone call so bad. He was facetiming somebody
You're a menace
Say the current time so this is not pre-recorded. It's 7 41 pm pacific. Sorry dude. Don't forget you promised a bane impression
That's right. Okay, go past the security station. I can't just ask the front desk where they're keeping langstrom's body
Prince put the morgue on the other side of the bullpen for not to be seen on the way
There's got to be a sneakier way in he's open the door
Uh, there is a sneaky way
Goddamn freaks. That's my daughter's school
We got a few in lockup one collar and interrogation I think i'm actually doing it
Damn works pretty packed with that scientist now
I this I don't fit up here
Find a way to the bullpen
Wait, can that guy see me through the wall?
This is when I grab the microphone here. I lean in and I do this huge burp. It's like a
And then fucking run out of the building
So immature shaking my head
All right, so this is a wee okay sneak through the cell block
I don't know why I just like I think it's just one. All right, I can get up there. All right, I swear
What is that there's like a case over here, how do I get that
Gordon no batman decommissioned bat signal for a bat signal
Uh
New commissioner catherine cain had the bat signal removed from the roof and submitted into evidence
Okay, how do I get that loot box?
There it is. All right, what's in here?
Various for this chest in here was that ammo?
1098 what are those nerf bullets? What were those? What was that?
Security cameras can alert nearby enemies to your location to be spotted. All right, don't get spotted by the cameras. I got it
Search for a nearby control panel
Deactivate the camera over there. Shit. It's not in here. Don't see me. Don't see me. Don't see me. Don't see me. Don't see me
What what who saw me figures it's locked. Oh shit, I gotta hide
Can you see me
Get away from me
Did you shoot the other person?
Watch where you're
Jesus I would not be firing this Jesus man
Don't
Oh my god, if she was standing right. Oh my god
Reckless behavior. Ow. Stop shooting me. Oh stop
He's bugging out I love I'm
I'm bugging out right now
sick
Turn off your preview and oh, I'm dropping a lot of frames. Oh shit. What happened? What happened?
Why am I why am I dropping so many frames? Oh revenge of the internet. He is bugging out. Yeah, apparently I am
I don't get it. What's going on? No, I was just getting going. I was just getting into this. Come on internet
Don't do this. All right, so I can't open this I need to I need a key card. Where's there a key card over here
Okay, I already I mean who cares about the alarm system. I mean, I've already been seen
Yeah, it'll pass. It'll pass. It'll pass. It'll pass. It always does
Think about okay, it'll pass 240p andy reach the morgue
Did someone knock on the front?
All right. Yeah, this is bad. Give me uh, give me let me let's wait for it to pass
Give me like two minutes. Yeah, let's let it pass. I don't want you to miss anything for some reason
Sometimes I don't know why it does this. I don't get it, but it's all good
Uh, actually while this is let me get looking I want to look at the menu watch your back
We don't need frames for this so you do it. There is gear so you can do different weapons
Wait, I I didn't even know I had these holy shit. I was I was I couldn't even hurt anybody
That's why I couldn't kill anybody there any points. I do not I know I do I got a point
I got a point. Where should I put it while we wait for this like tornado of internet to die down an extra momentum bar
Okay, maybe health right?
I would imagine probably health five percent defense and it goes to twenty percent at full health
Probably that i'll do a little bit defense. Oh, I thought I had one. No, I don't have any you can read emails
Uh, yikes, i've dropped 10 000 frames in the last like 10 minutes. Come on. Come on, man
Really? You're not gonna do it to me right now. Are you hold on a second?
You're not gonna do it to me right now. Are you? Yeah, this is bad. Am I still live? Did I get smashed?
Yeah, I think I just got like smashed out. My internet just got smashed. Okay. I'm still live. All right, cool. Yeah, there's a
Massive problem right now at this time. It is my internet. This is like abysmal. Um
Shit I was chewing your wires this kind of came out of nowhere. I don't have a VPN on right now
Well, hold on did it pass kind of god damn it. I was just starting to have a bunch of fun
I was just getting into it. Come on
All right, go get a snack go get a snack. I'll be right back. See if it will try to get it to pass
Let's try to write it out. I'll be back in like two minutes try to write it out. All right
I am here
This is the worst I think we've ever seen it in the last like few months. It's usually not like this
I played um, I mean like two three days ago played. Uh, we played uh scorn and it was fine for six straight out
No drop frames at all. Same time frame. I don't get it
Um, I hope this fixes still had like another 40 minutes or so that I wanted to play gotham nights playing it tomorrow, too
But I really want to do it tonight. I really want to play I it should
Fix itself
It always does
Whenever this happens at the very least i'm glad I got a little time in it. I'm actually having fun
I'm having a lot of fun with it. So let me play let me play
Yeah, it's still it's still happening whenever this happens for about 30 to 40 minutes
It will be an issue like this and then it just goes right back to normal
For the rest of the night what i'm probably going to do because these are sponsored streams and I obviously want to you know
Do them I don't want to make sure they're good
Uh, i'm probably going to start earlier tomorrow to try to avoid this time frame because it's always at
I mean we haven't had a problem like this in a long time, but when it happens, it's always at this time
So i'm going to pull the stream back tomorrow by a couple of hours to make sure that I avoid this
Uh streams not over. I'm just saying for the you know for tomorrow. Come on
Try resetting your modem. I it's I don't think that's the problem. It really isn't yeah
This is by far. So i've dropped 30 000 frames in the last like four minutes five minutes
That's the most I think it's ever been in like two or three years
So I don't I have no idea I could try to restart
The stream and restart the modem, but I don't I really don't think that's going to do anything
This is a pretty regular occurrence like well not regular but it happens
I feel like it's getting better from what i'm looking at over here
I think it's we may have wrote. I think we wrote through it. I think we're good. This seems like a skill issue
It's still happening, but not as free. It'll it'll pass. Don't worry. Let me tell you a story it once
was a
Man
I don't know man
If anybody from uh wb is watching right now, uh, i'm gonna i'm gonna stream the game for longer not that anybody if anybody is
Thanks dad
I was just getting into it. We were just it was just I was just getting into it with the car and the open world
I was having fun. What's your favorite nightwing comic? Oh god issue number one
How could issue number one not be your favorite god? I love that one. It's
It is 100 getting better
I can tell we've dropped significantly less in the last 10 minutes the last five minutes
I think i'm gonna go for it. I think we're okay. It's gonna still happen a little bit. It'll pass
You tell me what do you think?
It's probably still gonna happen a little bit, but it looks like it's passing
Is it as bad as it was before? I could be so moist because i'm sweating
32,000 frames dropped
Steam is just gonna come out of my ears. You knocked these guys out during brb
No, I did not these guys are already lying down here. All right, I think I think it's passing. It's gonna happen
Um, sorry, but i'm glad it didn't die completely and i'm glad it's probably gonna pass everybody
Just we're gonna pray together. Who's this guys? You it's working. Keep praying. It's working
Who's that?
Belfry tally uncle was here. You know, you can't beat me
My beloved has trained you well pretty sure he told you to stay out of gotham
Dead men's wishes don't concern me
besides
I'm here to clean up my father's mess
Which in this case is the demon himself
Wait, you're gonna what are you doing? Oh, you're just burning up race back if he's ash talia
Even a lazarus pit has some limits
Wait
Why was he after bruce?
Is this a fight?
Oh, it got me
I was just here watching
That was funny. It was
Gandalf
I just thought of gandalf again. It was funny, but it lagged
Something tells me race isn't coming back this time
Okay, i'm gonna find the body. What's my favorite soda? Hopefully the emmy found something
You're looking for a biodecryption key
Dude, you know what actually it's kind of good the uh
The the dream world coke. It's actually pretty good. I like it
All right, find the key which device conceals the biodecryption key blood would definitely be handy for
I think so
blood sample
Which device conceals the key the tweezers 100?
It's 100 the tweezers. Oh, never mind. I'm kidding. I won't make a joke about needing a tissue
Is this for playing a game online the mmo key? Wait, do you have an mmo key fob?
You put blood on your mmo
key fob
No, that's not how that's not how it works
Here's he died slowly and painfully if the gcpd has my prints on file
cranial bruising
And swelling multiple stab wounds on his arms and legs some wounds pierced
Through him making it possible to pin his body to the wall. There are also precise knife wounds in the chest and head
Jesus
Okay
the fingerprints
and
the calculator
phone and the fingerprints
Now imagine being allergic to something as delicious as seafood
He had a heart condition. Okay, so
it was
Medical bracelet, okay
He had a heart condition and a seafood allergy. Okay, so it's gonna be like a heart thing soft tissue blood or
urine
All right. He pees onto his authenticator in the blood
Okay fingerprints blood
Urine they didn't perform in a full autopsy. It's amazing. You can read oxygen through a finger
Okay, so this is an oxygen meter health issues, but those recover certain surgeries. Okay, so pulse
Oxybeater links from had some health issues beyond being pinned to a wall and his blood
He pissed on his ds
Okay, it's I think
If i'm thinking here, it's the bone
and the soft tissue sample
It's the sunglasses. It's the okay. What is this?
Multiple stab wounds in his arm leg and abdomen. It's definitely the mmo thing, right? It has to be old coffee
Okay, it's the mmo thing
And urine no the mmo and soft tissue
am I losing experience for getting this wrong so many times it's the mmo key and the
Fingerprints it's the
It's the pulse oximeter and the soft tissue sample. It's it's not
it's the
pulse oximeter
and the urine it's not
it's the blood and the
Monitor there it is
Got it elphrey gcpd just figured out talley has been here. I need a way out
Way ahead of you. They're coming in heavy. So be careful. I'm gonna have it. All right. I got I have my new uh batons
All right, get me out of here
I'm sneaking out of here. They're bugs in my hair. Oh, wow. That's a lot of people
Okay, you stealth to get around
That was so what was the point of that night wing I like these new batons
What's in here?
5,000
stacks of something
All right, they're all over there. I can go this way, right?
All right so far so good
Belfry all clear to exit the station
Thanks for the assist
Happy to help can't wait to see what you found
Is nightwing on on the titans?
No
No, what wait what robin is on the titans is this robin?
Yes. No, that's a different robin
Yes, and no because yes, jason todd
Uh dick grason and then
The berry is like a like a ben
Holy shit
All right. I just gotta get out of here. Did you just actually kill me? He's cheering. They're cheering. Are you kidding me?
Yo, whoa, what did you do? It just took away shit. It took away a bunch of diamonds. What was that?
What did it just delete it from my my checking account my like superhero checking account? What the fuck's happened?
I saw a diamond get deducted. What was that?
All right. What was that?
Was the medical bill?
Dude, that was bullshit. That was actually bullshit
Okay, cool fast travel
I had zero crimes stopped one citizen rescued. What did I do all day?
I haven't been very helpful
How do you get zero financial records research into hearing loss?
human experimentation and trials
That looks like cash payouts and volunteers
I recognize some of these jerks. They're all known gang members
So langston was doing medical experiments on criminals
You're crowding me miss gordon
The hollow imaging system is back online as of this morning. So we're in our regular clothes
I forgot how sweet your setup was babs
It's ancient but it'll do for now
You and master bruce are the only two people in the entire world who would consider the belfry's systems ancient
While researching langstrom. I also called up all we've got on
One
Did somebody ask where batman is our party crusher? Do we tell him talia?
Or do you should you find out on your own? She was a match for master bruce. Do you tell him more ways than one?
The presence in gulfam is concerning. So is the fact that she torched her old man's body
We sure that was racial ghoul
His dna was all over the weapon. She left behind
I wonder why she didn't take a chance and use a laser's pit to revive him
Well, he is massive would just find talia and ask her himself
Wait, you mean to tell me that was robin
Yeah, I can double check talia's kunai
Holy shit, you got huge
You should also hit the streets find out if anyone had any beef with langstrom sweet bust some skulls
He hit the gym. Yeah
I mean seriously, he's an absolutely massive person got new intel for the evidence board
Oh cool. Oh, I got I got a point. I can't get over what talia did to her father's body back there
Good riddance going in a laser's pit once is hell who knows what a thousand evidence boards
Crack information discovered during investigation lead section features the most relevant information about your next steps
Okay
All right. So I got intel ross was in the bat cave with bruce when it collapsed
We might never know why he was there to begin with talia alghul daughter of ross alghul the demon's head
And next in line is the leader of the league of shadows until ross passed her
Oh, I was like what the hell is going on over there in favor of naming bruce as his heir
Last time bruce faced talia. He told her to never return to gotham now that he's gone. She's decided to come back
great
Great learn about your about your next steps a little chat or snitches
All right, the freaks claim robinson park as their territory once in the area use your compass to find the informants
Or interrogate the mob to find out more information. Let's do snitches
All right, let's go for this one. So this is the west end so get to the west end
Okay case file
Basic training. Oh, okay. Cool
All right, let's go do that
Craft a new melee weapon is crafting
complete
Relegation training. Oh, this is all my currencies. Oh, all right. I'm ready acquire blueprints and salvage to craft better suits and weapons
Go to the melee blueprint
I can make a new suit. Okay, a new melee weapon crafting is ready. Um, I already have better ones. Don't I
This is 10 damage
The one I have is better. Isn't it? Yeah, I already own it. Why would I craft it? Can I craft gear?
And not all right, that's cool. So I got to find a blueprint wait, I actually might have to do this for the tutorial
I do
Well, I mean
I'll put them on
These aren't wait. These are level two. Oh, you can dismantle shit. All right dismantle
Yep. Ooh
Yep, that was cool. All right
uh, I
Do I have any points?
That's crafting complete and terror. I gotta do the interrogation training. I'm actually I can't wait to see what this is
Practice combat stealth moment. I don't need to do that
interrogation training
You just dismantled the heroic for an uncommon that I screwed that up
Should I not have done that? It did less damage. Why not break it down?
Sometimes I wake up in the middle of the night expecting bruce to call me for help
And then I remember I thought it might have been one of you calling just now
I was worried
old habits, I suppose
That's why I thought going to bloodhaven alone would be easier
There wasn't I won't be like him offered
Bruce left some big shoes to fill
But i'm gonna do things my way
And i'll be here to support you gotham is in good hands
So if you do this with a different character, is it a different cutscene?
Or have I not opened that ability to change characters yet?
Gotham said he needs a new guardian complete knighthood challenges to unlock powerful new abilities for each hero
Including their unique heroic travel. Oh wait, you get to actually fly
Like dr. Langstrom was into some pretty wild stuff. I wish he was still alive
I'd ask him what the heck he was thinking
All right, where's the interrogation thing?
Prepare for do I have to do this?
I think I have to do this
Oh, no, I don't where is the interrogation train? I stuck it to commissioner cain back at the police station
Oh, sorry
Ah because she was fiercely loyal to him
No, because you wasn't afraid to call people on their shit including him. Is that
Actually what I have to do the training
This isn't
Physical and mental preparation go hand in hand
Here we can train the mind to prepare the body
But it requires deep focus
Let go of your self-doubt and focus on my voice. What's the hottest pepper you've ever had?
Oh a jalapeno. Oh hot hot
Time your dodge to create an opening for a powerful counter-attack. Okay
I wait I can do that. That's cool
That not perfect that was perfect
Oh cool. How was that not perfect? Nice, but don't get complacent. I leveled up, right?
I'm proud of you dick
Hey, thanks
Cool. I leveled up though, didn't I? All right. So am I missing something or do I interrogation is probably one of those advanced combat moves
I'm going to assume
momentum
Interrogate smoke bombs guard break combo stealth grabbing an L interrogation. Here we go
Hold to scan criminals and locate the informant grab informants to interrogate them interesting
Enemies can be interrogated if they've been grabbed use stealth to approach and grab an enemy. That's not grab
That is how do I interrogate? Give me a hint just what I need to know. Okay, I think I get it
What happened to that person? Okay, i'm gonna grab what do you got answers you need appreciate the tip
Cool
You're ready to move on
I'm proud of you dick. Thanks batman. Appreciate it
Oh, okay. Let's go
I have a patrol
exit the bell ray and patrol gotham city
Check your email
Wait, we're sending emails to each other. We're in the same room. We're dropping frames again
There's honestly nothing I can do about it
I I wish there was a magic wand I could wave but it just isn't and that's just the way that's just the way it is
So that's the way it is. All right. So why is he emailing me?
I have an idea. There's a thing called the gotham historical circuit that takes you to all these cool spots around the city
We should check them out. There's an app for it, but I replaced the data with bruce's files just for us
Okay, so you can got okay. I get it. So these are little side missions. That's that's cute. These are cute missions
You guys remember when bruce hid batarangs all over the city for us to find so we could practice parkour
We never found them all. Okay. All right. All right, that's cool
case file investigation
weird science
Langstrom was murdered no matter what the cops say see if anyone on the street knows what might have happened
All right, let's do it
You emailed to yourself
I did email myself. That was a
Voice sometimes he didn't remember stuff
All right, let's go
I need to do some interrogation
What's going on down here?
All right, I got it. I gotta interrogate somebody who should I interrogate?
Open the activity view
What's up
All right, i'm definitely doing way more damage with these by the way
Close
Dude, gotham city is fucking wretched
I didn't even interrogate anybody. That was my bad
Uh, give me the bike. Is there a horn?
Oh, there's like a bank robbery over here. Do you see that?
You robbed him
Sorry, wrong person
Is it the wrong person?
Somebody was running with like a bag
Oh, okay. There they go. There they go
Robbery in progress. All right, they they're stealing money right now
Damn. All right
Damn
I needed entrance. What's up? They didn't take any money yet swing
Okay, there's a lot of people now running like grenades like a like a
Rocket launcher or something
They didn't get any money
Oh, this is the guy with the money
Give me that money back. How do I pick it up?
One guy got like a duffel bag full of fucking like fives
You know, oh wait, no, you got money who else is in here shit
All right, yes, that's it
Crime resolved. I got it. I I have to interrogate. I keep forgetting to do that here
Hope you know what you're doing. I kind of all right. I have to interrogate somebody. So what do we got?
I can go this way
Yeah, let's go this way
That was the same guy
Am I just a menace to this person?
Thanks
The walk sign was not there
Oh shit
You what'd you say? I want some more of those moves. Those moves are cool
Interrogate somebody I won't do I just keep killing everyone. Come here. What do you know about the penguin?
fucking asshole
Wait, they have stuff here
Three shields or something. All right night wing. It's it's going to be a long night
You need to it's like the sun is coming up like interrogate someone
I I all right, never mind. Are you gonna stop? Can I get on the train? Yeah, I I take the train
That'd be so weird
Honestly, I would just assume that there was like a comic con going on down the street. Like this is not night wing
This is the guy going to a convention. He didn't let anybody on
I dance is locked. Come on
What is it
Of jalapeno flavored beer you gotta get a clap or something nice outfit night wing. Thank you
The fucking absolute terror
The absolute horror that was so funny
Okay, I need to I gotta stop a crime
This is fun. All right, I need another crime. Did I solve all the crimes?
No, let's run right over here. Okay
Here are they in the building? They're on the roof. I want to throw somebody off the roof so bad
Oh, you better but i'm throwing this person off the roof into the fucking ocean
Excuse me. What happened? So that's what level they are. All right, come on put him into the fan
Why didn't he stop running
Don't kill me
He's got you know punch
Hey, thanks for the help
Okay, watch out for that ledge over there
Oh
He's throw a grenade rocket
All right, interrogate
interrogate
How do I interrogate?
Where's the penguin? You're dead. Never mind. Why can I I can't interrogate?
This guy's a fucking maniac
This guy's a maniac
By the way, thanks for wonder brothers for sponsoring the stream
Gotham night
Uh will be available tomorrow
xbox
playstation pc
Uh, I have a 3090 be curious. Um, it is running pretty well. I would say it's running 60
Been a few, uh drops here and there but forget about my internet
It's a whole nother story. I need to interrogate someone. Are you humble bragging? No, no, no
I'm just saying that if you look at this and you go, oh wow. Okay. This this is running great
I I just want to make sure you know what card that I have
right
I'm like falling. Oh my god nightwing. You can't go down the stairs
I'm here. Tell me interrogate
I don't know who burned the dock. His research was top secret. Even my boss didn't know I was doing work for him
Maybe it was just an accident. Thank you
I took him out
Wait, are you still fighting?
He was about to say don't let him grab you why because i'm going to interrogate you
Don't let him grab you
Yeah, so for tomorrow
We'll start earlier tomorrow to try to avoid the internet problem that could happen at the night time. So
We'll start at probably two o'clock tomorrow 2 p.m pacific
instead of four
I mean that was
Okay
All right. So I got a little bit of info
I need a little bit more info. I do want to place the other characters
We'll do that tomorrow. All right that way. What was that? Oh, it's a oh, it's a bat. Uh wing
It's right below. All right. One of these guys has intel I think
Can't reach from here. All right, whatever they keep talking about be bugging out
Which one of you has intel?
You just threw molotov at your friend
You guys seriously
You don't have intel. Do you have intel?
Do you know anything?
Do you know anything? Do you know harvard yet? You know where he is?
Come here. What do you know? You don't know anything
That was fucking awesome. I mean don't tell me that wasn't cool
That was cool. That was really cool
That was actually really cool
Find somebody that's a higher level
This one's red. Why is this one red?
There's a photo mode too. How do I do it? Ooh
I gotta get a cool shot, right? Ready? Okay up and down
focal length
Arley freeze clay face
Arkham cobble pot. Oh, these are all wait pretty sick hide heroes facial expression. Wait, that's I like that one
This is like an awkward selfie you take thinking that you look good for your tinder profile
And then you go fuck I need to be in a picture with other people like shit
I can't I I have to be in a photo with other people body pose. No
This is way more detailed than it has any right to be you can bring a light source
That's pretty good
It kind of looks like somebody got a picture of him that was he didn't know like that. He's like wow
I'm surprised you're taking this from up here. Hold on. Yeah, like a big telephoto lens zooming in on him
That's that's really good. It's very detailed. I want to take a picture during something crazy
And now that you can do that. All right, wait, wait, wait, i'm going the wrong way. I want to go in there
Yeah, go with it. You could probably get some really good photos
With how much there is to do with that, especially you can take the heroes out. You can just do remove everybody frame up some good
Photography. All right, let's do the one that's over here. Oh, you can do a springboard. So where are we going right here?
Jesus there's a lot of people here defeat enemies. It's like rock music. He's alive
Oh, come on. What?
Who even heard that?
There's way too many people here. I gotta get out of here. Oh those explode. That sucks
No, that's so many materials to lose
All right, don't die people
Are the cops arresting who's fighting who here?
I'm trying to okay
I love that move so much
Oh, you throw it in the air and catch it. All right interrogate. Let's go
You know
Okay
How much intel do I do I need to do a mission? Let's see
batman's last case
Weird science. Oh, okay. We gotta interrogate freaks
Where am I now?
Armor truck robbery going on right now. What is this? What is this crime scene? I'm gonna do the armor truck. Let's go
Do I have I think I have a point to put in do the bane voice. Okay, I did promise I would do it
Oh, you think darkness is your ally
but today
We will find you and we will kill you you are absolutely
Able to believe that you could defeat
the league of shadows
Uh
I think my game crashed. No, why can I walk forward? Um, I think i'm trapped in a box
What happened to me? What where am I?
Oh, I clipped into a wall. Okay, that's funny. Oh crime
I don't I what did I even just do to him? I'm just lying down
Language what's this rated blows
Call it a tie. Okay, let's call it a tie
Sure
Let's call it a tie. Let's call it a tie
I was I was
Never mind, whatever
Oh man, that was bad. That was a big head injury
You leaned into that one though. Come on
I was trying to hold
See I was gonna push them into the car. I was gonna just throw her into the car. It didn't happen
I was waiting for a car
All right armor truck I let me get a good photo too. I need a good nightwing photo
What like
That looks kind of weird
This is like a skateboard video. Look at all this shit. Oh my god, really?
Pixel 1998 gonna be snowing. Hey, you guys remember the part of the movie where uh nightwing cannonballed into the pool
Off the top of the gotham city tower. It was crazy. It was a really weird scene too. I can't do body pose
I so badly want it. Oh, that's perfect. I don't know which one's better. This one's pretty good, too
I like this one. Uh, that's pretty good thumbnail. All right. I gotta get a cool photo here too get out of the way
Why did this explode?
What happened over here? Why did this explode? I'm so confused. Hold on take the filters off. Whoa, that was cool
How have none of you died from this? That's actually oh and he still has the smile. I like that. That's a good one
I want let me change the smile
You can't even believe he's doing it make him look bored that just looks odd. Yeah, it looks just weird
All right, let's go shit. That would have been awesome. What you're live right now. Yeah, what do you want?
What do you what what I mean? I'm yeah, I know i'm live. What's wrong?
I'm taking a picture of this lady getting kicked in the face. What don't let him okay there don't let him get the money
No, I can't
Why oh because he oh i'm dead
Shit, it's all right. It's fine. It's fine losing more of my goddamn currency. I think I failed it. I can't do it again
All right, i'm gonna go back to wane
Enterprises, whatever it is and progress the story. That's what i'm doing. That's what's happening
Let's go. I failed it. It's not available anymore. They're not gonna just they're not still robbing that place. Okay, let's go
I'm really glad the internet fixed itself. Yeah, i'll check on get how am I only have one crime stopped and I stopped like five
Ooh
That one's pretty sick common power 12 health. Okay. Yeah, let's put this on
That looks cool
What is that? I didn't know I had that
Beyond suit this is just way better, right? Why did I even make the other one? Okay, and I got points to put in
Um, all right. Melee
ranged darts
Made these use okay. Definitely these offer minimum stats a good way to keep your basic kit up to date. Okay
Sounds good. All right. What do I want for points here? I was gonna do acrobat
So we'll do this
Aerial attack damage is increased. Very cool looking forward to an email. Hey there boy. Yo
Fiercely typing on my way to next class see what you're doing next weekend. I have a wee break
But we could get a cuppa
coming back to
Bloodhaven till sunday night to see some folks and thought maybe you would like to be one of them
Unless you're expecting one of your infamous Grayson emergencies
Have you seen the old super speeding bullet running around out there a friend of says he's in bloodhaven
Imagine that can't be good news when the big boys start looking our way
So be careful talk about superman the flash have you seen the old super speeding bullet round running about out there?
That's the flash. They're more heroes in the game
Okay
All right. I got the new suit
Is the evidence board?
Leads, okay
All right. So I still have to do this part
Terrogate the freaks in this area. So I gotta go up there and then that's pretty much it
Unless I didn't get any do things up here. I just I don't think I interrogated enough people
Yeah, all right. So I know where to go. Why they just called freaks. Yeah, they're just they're just called freaks
All right, new suit new gear. Let's check it out
Okay, uh after this uh mission. Ooh, what is he? Okay
So I need to go
It was up here, right?
It was up here. Wasn't it?
Case file a little chat. So it's like
over here
Like right here. This is a long ways away
Get on the car
Good luck. Thank you
Turn around on the right track. Okay, that's a jump the other way
Can I drive through here? Are you sure dude? Are you sure? Okay, what's up? I'm going on up here. It's me nightwing
Never mind. It's not gonna work
What happened criminals?
Fucking photo mode. I'm so sorry, but you
Just screaming. All right, we're good. Somebody hit me off the bike. Jesus
Uh, the game's broken
I i'm not gonna i'm done doing this
I broke the game I think in what scenario would you be able to take this photo?
All right. I'm not I it's too fun to take stupid pictures
Let's go. Oh shit
Shit
Oh, that was a double swing if I you see that I hit him with both feet
Yeah
Batman would have obliterated this guy by now say that he's we only just figured that out like a couple hours ago
Come on. No, I need to interrogate somebody down here. That man's like level 50. Yeah, you can't say that
Doesn't work like that
All right. I need to interrogate somebody here. Can you see me still? I just dodged that
All right, don't kill that guy. I need to interrogate that guy
Holy shit, that almost killed me instantly
Yeah
These guys are so tanky
die
No, no, sorry. Sorry. Sorry. I mean defeat
That's supposed to be killing people. I forgot
Can you grab the big guys?
I can't grab them
Whoa
Oh shit. All right. Here we go
Why does he have like a
face
kidnapping in progress
What where I didn't interrogate anybody? Where's this kidnapping in progress?
How did I not enter? I thought that was the um
All right, let me let me get one more thing of intel
So for tomorrow
Um, i'm gonna run a poll
Before the stream turns off so we're gonna start at like two o'clock pacific tomorrow
damn
Uh, and the idea is
I mean I could play crash bandicoot again
Or do we should we do something else?
neon white
We start with neon white tomorrow
Um vampire survivor's got its 1.0 update. There's also rotato
Which I want to play
We'll figure it out
breath of the wild
I don't know maybe
Oh, I want to play like a horror game. Maybe we'll play the public combo gaming tomorrow
Maybe deadly night
All right. Yeah, put a poll up what's going to be deadly night
Uh, which is public public combo horror game
um
continue crash bandicoot 4
or
neon white
Wait, why am I what?
They're doing like a news sec. That guy's a shotgun
Okay, get out get out don't fight here
But they're just doing like a news interview
Why did I just come over some fighting people?
Get out
Stop just okay. I gotta get out of here
I have to get the fuck out of here
I thought those were um the criminals
Give me the car give me out
Okay, I need speaking of gangs. Where are they?
down here
What's up?
All right, keep that number four alive
It wasn't your day
All right, let's go
Come here
Now give me some info
Finally, I know you had deep langstrom and i'm dead
Belfry bad news gotham's criminals know as much about langstrom's death as we do we got it
Well, we know where talia is might as well talk to her in the meantime sunday court and it's now okay
Okay
Sick
Is this a boss fight? Maybe
This could be a boss fight
Oh confirm the poll options. It was crash bandicoot 4 continued playthrough
it was
neon white and
vampire survivors slash rotato
Deadly night
That's too many
All right. We're gonna make it easy
Um, i'm gonna literally make it simple for you. We're playing the puppet combo game tomorrow, but um, no
Okay, I want to do that at night. I don't want to do that like two o'clock in the afternoon
I want to I thought I wanted to be like 2 pm in the afternoon. I want to be scary at night
All right. I've got a plan for you. Here's the plan you are to choose
Here's what's happening tomorrow tomorrow at 2 pm. We're going to start
With something then we're going to move to gotham nights and then after gotham nights
We're going to do the puppet combo game. So i'm going to start with something though
What can I play for like an hour or two? What can I play for like an hour? I've got it done
We're going to play listen. I don't even need to pull we're going to play
The vampire survivors 1.0 update gotham nights and then we're going to end with uh puppet combos
Deadly night. There you go. I'm doing who needs a pole. We already got it. Uh, i'm gonna fast traveled here
It's only a third night
All right, pre-meditated crimes revealed. What does that mean?
Uh, I want to list I want to talk because I feel like I think this is a boss fight
I'm going for it
Gentlemen, this is democracy manifest
Ooh
Uh, give me the bike and again this game is available tomorrow
It's on ps5
xbox both versions of xbox pc
Get out of the fucking way
It's time for our first boss fight. That'd be kind of cool
first boss fight
Kind of cool. Yeah, this is on pc. All right. Come on boss fight. You played as the other characters yet
No, I mean nightwing is my one of my favorite dc characters. So played with him
We'll play with the other ones tomorrow
They cast me out hard to believe leadership of the league isn't hereditary
You're saying you didn't get the job after you asked rach
My late father insisted bruce would be the next head of the league despite his refusal
Since that ill-fated welcome nightwing looks like this all the league can agree on it's like the different costume. It's a different suit
Why would race kill us next in line?
None of this makes sense
I agree. It was an irrational win. I warned him the batman would be his downfall
but
Repeated exposure to the lazarus pits breaks down a subject's mind
Eventually their true self is erased
I know utalia
Could have used your father as a puppet if you wanted to
There's something else here consider it a logical choice
A painless end for him meant closure for the league
and for me
Now they want me dead. Why do I like nightwing? I like his weapons
Leave gotham
I have other matters to attend to
lost fight
The funeral was tasteful. I'm sure bruce would have appreciated it leave him where he is
You still haven't answered my question
No, but I can ask you one
Why would an apprentice to the cowl break into the morgue? No, you weren't following me
It's an ongoing investigation. I look like a ghoul
I wish you the best of luck. You'll be needing it soon
Because once the league regains its footing
This isn't good belfry talia's got something going on
Surprising but also not is that why you didn't ask her about langstrom? No boss. That's all right
I don't want to give her any leads
All right, you guys ready to call it
Come back tomorrow afternoon. We'll come earlier. We'll start earlier tomorrow
I want to start earlier because I want to go a little longer tomorrow. Oh, I didn't even do any crimes
So harley contacted batman using my homing pigeon in a usb drive
Sorry about the internet video
It always sucks. It's always so frustrating, but it's all good
It seemed like it cleared up after like 20 minutes or so, so i'm happy about that at least
Do we think it's legit bruce never talked to me about it
When bruce worked with criminals, he didn't exactly keep us in the loop. I'm curious about red hood
But it's also not crazy to think that harley made this up and just play it
And we'll know harley
It's weird because I heard a room you were dead. Oh boy
Anyway, got you dead
Hasn't harley quinn been out of gotham ever since
You know her
ex
Killed me
Isn't that what you meant wait what?
Rumor has it she did some government thing
went straight
is
She's got something
Can we go find harley?
now
He's literally alive though. Yeah
Yeah after I got after he killed me. Yeah
It's alive, but you know it hurt
Do you think this harley thing is really worth following up on?
Maybe out of her fake fan. It's a brilliant mind
Yeah
Don't know the red hood origin
I mean, I think I know
Yeah, why would she help do I know or us?
I don't know what it is
Uh, okay. Oh, that's right. Yeah, I could work
He went to yours when you could visit his grave
Who's the original robin who's the it's red hood, right?
Red hood's the original robin like the first robin you haven't and then nightwing's the second robin and then
Right
Dick is the original robin
Jason oh no, no, Jason. Todd was the second and then who's the robin in this game?
Dick was first jason second. All right, tim right, right, right. Sometimes that is gonna be I gotta remember
All right. Very cool. Very cool
So i'll wrap it up here
I'll see you guys tomorrow afternoon at two o'clock pacific
Uh, we'll play more gotham knights again
Thanks to warner brothers. There's no telling what they'll do games available tomorrow and I think they'll behave
Obviously sponsored sponsors tomorrow as well
um
It's available for everything
I'm gonna keep i'm obviously gonna keep playing it
Um sponsored to play it so we'll keep going
But again, it's not gonna be the whole thing tomorrow. It will be for a couple of hours
And before that we'll play vampire survivors and after that we'll do puppet combos deadly night
That's what we will end the stream with tomorrow
It's probably gonna be a meaty one tomorrow. I would say
I'm gonna be playing three different games so
And uh strapping tomorrow
Yeah
Uh, that's it. Thanks again warner brothers
There is a there's a multiplayer too. I gotta investigate some of this shit. Yeah
See you tomorrow. Good night
Again, sorry about the internet so hard to not bite my controller when that happens
Oh, I I had fun. I did that would be lying to you if I said I didn't
Regardless of you know a sponsorship it was kind of fun to run around hit stuff
Some of the open world goofiness was I mean it was funny. It was a lot of fun
It looks like it's something you're into then it is if not, then it's not open world games tend to just
Bring out some of the best
In random ai shenanigans. I just one of my favorite things in any video game
It's just driving around and having people just react just the ai just decides to do stuff. It's my favorite thing
Yeah, have a good night. See you tomorrow 2 p.m. Pacific
Vampire survivors for about an hour got nights for about two and a half maybe hours
Maybe we'll see after that deadly night. We'll see thanks for the subs. Uh, there were a couple raids that came into
Uh, so thanks for the raids. Thanks for the subs obviously. We'll see you soon 2 p.m. Pacific
Good night. Goodbye. Have a wonderful rest of your day. Well, it's night for everybody
So good night